- (soft violins)
(R&B music)
- (mumbles)
- Yeah, it is, like everytime,
I mean everything I do, she just
- I understand, I
understand Glenn, I do.
You know, it's just funny
that, how life is sometimes.
You know, sometimes
relationships just
don't work out
the way we want
them to work out.
You know, but, you know, I
just hate to see you like this.
I mean, come on, Glenn.
You've got to be strong
and you've got to
get out of this.
You've got to snap out of it.
I don't want you being
depressed like this.
There are too many
women out there.
and you are a good man
and believe me, you
can get a woman,
any woman you want.
You're a successful doctor.
You have so much going on.
and if she can't
see that, fuck her.
(hip-hop music)
- [Glenn] A lot of people
don't understand how
a friendly game of dominoes can
lead into some serious shit.
Now, I was getting over
a breakup with my girl,
getting together
with a few friends.
At least I thought
they were my friends.
Who would know that a good
time would turn into this.
Normally, there are three
sides to every story,
my side, her side,
and the truth.
In this case, there were five,
four guys, plus the truth.
(laughing)
- [Man] Fuck you man.
- All this time,
we waiting on you.
- Brother, you ain't
gotta wait for nobody.
Yeah, you wait 'cuz you want to.
You start when you want to.
Nobody asked you to wait.
- We ain't drinking beer.
- Hell, man I come when
I'm ready, same as usual.
- [Glenn] Wesley, like the
dearest of people everywhere
was one who we
least appreciated.
If there's anybody you ever
wanted to have your back,
it's Wesley.
But sometimes, he's
got your back so hard,
you feel like you're
carrying a brother.
And now, this new thing he's
going through with women,
man, I don't know.
You tell me.
- That's why you give
me a while girl anytime.
- What?
- Yep, that's what I said.
- You know why?
Because they don't care
nothing what you have to say.
Now, I'm talking to this
white girl the other day
and I told her, you
know what I said?
I said, "See you later, because
I'm going to get me some
"fellatio on the patio
and what time I be back,
"you better not ask."
(laughing)
- Lying motherfucker.
- He can't even, he can't
even spell fellatio.
(laughing)
- [Voiceover] Me and this
brother had this girl one time.
Naw, that's another story.
You see, his whole
trip is respect.
He don't give it
and he ain't got it.
Now, at one time or another,
something must have cost him
'cuz now he's out to
make everybody pay.
- I'm telling you, man,
tramps, every one of 'em, man.
Women ain't shit,
from, from Carla to
Wanda to Sheila,
all the same man.
- [Samuel] Shit, you
can name all day.
- [Chris] Every one
of 'em's some tramps.
- Chris, man.
- Nah, no exceptions, man.
- Man, wait, now hold on.
- Bullshit, you
pussy-whipped motherfucker.
Every one of them
hoes is some tramps.
Now, you look around the
table and you tell us
which one of us
haven't been turned out
by some low-life,
open-your-leg-tramp hoe
to anybody that come around.
Name one of use who haven't.
- [Voiceover] Samuel,
I met through Chris.
Now, they were
friends before us.
I liked his loyalty,
which regardless of sides
went always with his friend,
he's on everybody's side.
Anybody else got a problem?
He's the man with the plan,
(chuckles) as if he can
keep his own shit straight.
I mean, he can pretend
with everybody else,
but we know what's
really going on, right?
Ol' Captain Save-A-Hoe.
- Look, I'm all over town, baby.
You just better keep up.
Everyday is something,
something everyday.
Shit, what's today?
Look, I ain't got to tell
y'all. Y'all know how it was.
Before, I couldn't have told
you the day of the week,
trembling just to watch TV,
scared of a love scene,
nevermind pop radio.
Love songs was torture,
but you know what?
To hell with Gina or the
motherfucker that she left with.
You know, I was thinking
of stalking Kenny G.
- [Chris] (chuckles)
Why? (laughing)
- Now, it's a different
girl every day.
Shit, my dick don't get hard
without my appointment book.
- This is what all
y'all need to be doing.
A bunch of drunk-ass alcoholics.
- Like you don't drink?
- No, but I ain't trying
to keep nothing from y'all.
If I had brought enough, man,
all y'all would be
welcome to some'n.
But, I didn't.
(laughing)
- [Glenn] You gave me your word.
- [Samuel] And you believed him.
- Shit, that was
a long time ago.
- [Glenn] A long time ago--
- I know when I broke up with
Karen, this what I told her.
I told her that I wasn't
gonna smoke with nobody else,
you know, because that
was supposed to be
special between us.
- [Samuel] No.
(laughing)
Well, I'm over at her
crib the other day
'cuz I'm still tapping
that ass (laughs)
and she offered me a little
bit of the herb she had
to take with me and
I told her, you know,
"No, I don't need it."
I said, "I can't smoke
with nobody except you."
Telling lies so
motherfucking good,
you would swear it was
the truth, you know.
- You turned down smoke?
- It's true, though, man.
I wasn't trying to lie.
- [Glenn] A liar ain't
gotta try to lie.
- Meant every word at the time.
(laughing)
- I am astonished at
your recovery, man.
I mean after all of the
shit she put you through.
Man, look at you, man.
- On top of that, another man?
- Then, he had to
move in with his mama.
(laughing)
- [Samuel] Damn, man.
Damn, the treachery, man.
- Your delayed
punctuality precludes you
from the knowledge that
this issue is closed.
(R&B music)
- Wait until you see
what I got for him.
- What you got for who?
- This time, the fire.
- If it's over, you
need to leave him alone.
- I have left him alone,
with a vengeance.
- For what?
- For everything.
For not loving me.
For all those years.
- I am, however, grateful.
(laughing)
for the considerate
acknowledgement
of my extraordinary recovery.
- Will somebody get me a
tourniquet before I bleed, shit.
(hip-hop music playing)
Alright, damn, nigga,
it was just a joke.
Alright, I'm sorry.
- You ain't sorry.
- Fuck you, then. (chuckles)
- Hey, hey, hey, y'all leave
the young blood alone, man.
He's just like that
because you gang up on him.
Look, now can we start
this game sometime
before I got to go?
- Where you gotta go?
- Hold up.
- Hey, shit, I'll
find somewhere.
Hell, anywhere. It
ain't for you to know.
- Alright, now.
(dominoes rattling)
- Alright, now we're
getting somewhere.
(R&B music playing)
(laughing)
- You better beware.
- Beware of what?
- [Chris] Go ahead and pass,
you know you wanna pass.
- What are you hiding and
looking to turn away from?
- What am I? What are you?
- Hey, fellas. Come on.
- Play the game if
you're gonna play.
- Months, I've been
swearing that I hated him.
Guess what I finally got
around to telling him.
(scoffs)
I said I loved him.
- (inhales and
sighs) And do you?
- [Samuel] You want
something to worry about?
You worry about you.
Hell, if I could, I'd take
all of this loving I'm getting
so you satisfied too.
See, so don't
reproach me for mine.
(laughing)
- As long as you're
happy, so am I.
- Maybe next time after a
down stroke, I'll call you up.
Say, "Glenn, how
was it for you?"
- You're doing the
right thing, Samuel.
Stand all of them hoes in a row.
- [Samuel] That's
right. That is right.
- Tell them, the first
one to step out of place,
straight to the back
of the line they go.
- Now, what you got
to say about it, huh?
At least I've got
something I can say.
What you got to say about it?
- [Glenn} I think (mumbles)
- [Samuel] 15.
- [Chris] You don't
need to smoke no weed.
- What I got to say about what?
- Oh, come on, pretend
like you don't know,
as if you're not aware
that something is wrong.
- That day when he
told me he loved me,
it was in a way
I've never heard.
There was a tear on every word.
(sighing)
His eyes had so
much hope inside.
Black horses driving a
coach for a bride and groom,
on the way to a long
awaited honeymoon.
I knew those eyes.
- Look, I have no intentions
of saying anything,
but if you insist on hearing
what it is you think I think,
if you knew what I was
thinking, then I wouldn't
have to open my mouth
to tell you to shut up.
- So, how is your daughter?
- That's right, Samuel.
Make sure you get yours.
(laughing)
- Now, you don't think
she's doing the same thing?
- Look, look, listen, man,
If they get back together, fine.
You know, he didn't ask
for none of this shit.
He might as well make the
best of the situation.
- [Wesley] So, how
is your little girl?
- She's doing fine, man. Thanks.
She lifts my spirits.
You know what she said to me?
She said, "Daddy, I told
you to marry Mommy."
- Well, you did ask her, right?
- She said I was too late.
- Wait a minute,
you waited 14 years.
How long you expect
a bitch to wait?
- Are we gonna talk about this?
Because what did I say?
- Well, when you love somebody
what's the difference?
- What's the difference?
To a woman, a lot.
Hell, a lot to a woman.
- Look, I didn't understand.
I mean, the way I felt,
we had a perfect life.
- Yeah, you might
have thought so,
but what did she?
- She never complained.
I mean, I didn't know
how important it was.
- [Wesley] Y'all can count them.
- Yeah, well, what
did she have to say?
- (chuckles) Say?
She tossed him far out the
door, is what she said.
- She does love me as
much as ever. I know it.
- Shit, that's
straight up bullshit.
- Motherfucker, damn.
- I just don't want
this boy to get hurt.
- I'm going to be fine, man.
I'm embraced by a wonder
of my love for her
and the understanding of
its importance in my life.
- Yeah, well, she
loves you, you think?
- Hey, with all of
her heart and soul.
That's what I do.
- Alright, well,
she's gonna be back.
- [Samuel] Please.
- [Wesley] Trust me.
(laughing)
- Listen to you, man.
Fools, all of y'all.
- [Wesley] Your mama's
a female impersonator.
- She ain't going nowhere.
You the only one when she
kicked your ass out good.
- [Glenn] Samuel, ease up.
- It's the same
as any woman, man.
I mean, she got game on you.
She's playing you for a sucker
'cuz she's got
all the power now.
Standing on your fucking
neck with all of her
weight pressed down.
- And if she back
up for a minute it's
just to gather speed.
(laughing)
- Even when you not
around, she is playing you,
and it's getting worse, man.
So, you remember I said that.
- She knows all your buttons
and the combination to
kick your ass besides.
- [Glenn] Y'all need to quit.
- You got you a beat
down coming, baby.
- A beat down, that's
exactly what you got.
- Thinking you're getting
ready for a reunion.
Nigga, you better
get ready to cry.
- Worse thing you could
imagine, don't be surprised.
- She took from me my family.
Doesn't matter
whatever happens else.
- You can believe that
lie if you want to.
That still don't
make that shit true.
Because, see, what
you're dealing with here,
is a rebel bitch on
the attack (laughing).
- She ain't gonna be through
with this motherfucker
until he bleeding out his eyes
and the last drop dries.
- Punishing him
gradually and by degrees.
- Anybody needs to get
realistic it's you, not me.
I'm not the one running around
chasing a thousands girls,
every single one, all that
look like the last kind
claiming some kind of
victory in disguise.
- Yeah, well, better than you.
- It's all a power trip, man.
It ain't if it's nothing else.
- [Samuel] Ain't if
it's nothing else?
- I mean, you ask anybody
that got some sense
and they will tell you.
Otherwise, everybody in
the world would know.
Man, she is playing
with your mind.
Not enough that you can see it,
just enough to blind you.
It's nothing in these words
that she's coming at you with,
it's in the intentions
that's behind it.
She's got a vice and
she's just fastening it,
tighter.
Calculated tenderness,
just for the effect of it.
Got a minefield of
revelations for him
time-released so that
the agony is more spread.
You going to die for a long
time before you really do.
- [Voiceover] Listen to this,
I'm trying to
concentrate on this game.
With relentless
fools like these,
you learn to chill
your feelings quick.
Not a day goes by
I don't think about
that wedding and all
of the pain it caused.
(R&B music)
- [Man] Everybody, everybody.
Your attention, please.
It's time for the old custom,
the throwing of the garter belt.
- Come on Chris, get our
motherfucking ass up, man.
You ain't got to catch
the damned thing.
Just get in line.
- Honey, it don't look
like they want to catch it.
- Look, can we go?
What we waiting for?
- Now, where's Glenn?
- He's probably getting
his hair weaved.
- [Glenn] Look, if I
was eligible I'd be
standing over here.
Say something else
about my hair.
- [Samuel] You better
grab that shit.
Unlucky motherfucker
like yourself.
- Ask your mama if I'm
unlucky motherfucker.
- Why you gotta go there?
- [Wesley] Why not?
They need to hurry up, 'cuz
my drink is getting limp.
- Anything you got is limp,
limp-dick motherfucker.
- I give to you, my
friends, a treasure.
- Fuck you.
- [Groom] Believe
it or not, a prize.
(glass chime together)
- Fuck you.
- Fuck both of y'all.
- May God bless some lucky man.
- Ain't y'all gonna get it?
- Fuck you.
- [Wesley] It get's
very, very intimidating.
I'm gonna get me some.
(R&B music)
- Tell us, when was the
last time you had a woman?
Just any time, tell us when
was the last time when.
Otherwise, you need to shut
the fuck up until then, nigga.
(laughing)
- Listen, let me
tell you what you do.
- [Chris] No, no,
no, I'll tell you.
- Nigga, you can't tell me
shit in the shape you in.
- Please, listen to me.
Between a man and a woman,
everything is controlled.
There is but one master
who possesses the object
of the other's desire hold.
One authority commands
the keys to the kingdom
around which is gate,
where and the other outside
is required to wait.
Make no false move, lest
you give yourself away,
betraying your feelings
puts the other on you.
Kisses connive,
embraces deceive.
Watch your back, says
your lover, if you was me,
lest you lose the floodgates
to expanding your heart
filling your soul with ecstasy
to sanctify every part.
Your love, something
that begins all acquired
and ends deafening you.
Her eyes, the pools of
coolness that you swim through.
Her voice, the music of angels
that strum at your heart.
Tender and moist and
serene to the touch,
her body, God with
the power to bless.
- With all that,
you ain't said shit.
- [Glenn] Shit,
that's knowledge.
- You must have to be dumb.
- Nigga, I ain't gotta be
dumb to whoop your bitch ass.
- No-pussy-getting motherfucker,
always fucking with somebody.
- All I asked Glenn, nigga,
is what are gonna do?
- I don't have to do anything.
- That's perfect right there.
- He turned off all the engines
and the pilot has
to come to him.
- Don't be a fool, dude.
She got your number, man.
It ain't no
protection from that.
- Man, she's just a
woman like anyone else.
- No, you just a woman.
(laughing)
- Listen to this punk.
She's guilty man,
I'm telling you.
- Give me a motherfucking
break, motherfucker.
Please, I mean, this
girl could eat glass.
She don't give a damn about you.
To do what she did,
or else how could she?
I'm telling, this
is how sisters are.
This is what they do.
She is trampling all
the fuck over you.
- Sisters will do that.
- [Wesley] That's
exactly what they do.
They cut off your Johnson,
then they serve it to you,
after they microwave it.
- Sisters, I know.
(laughing)
- Sisters don't play.
(R&B music)
- We are the same, I just
want you to know that
everything is going
to work out, okay?
- You really think so?
- Baby, I know so.
- (scoffs) Alright,
if you say so.
- (mumbles) okay.
- Can you get me
something to drink, baby?
- Sure.
- Thanks.
- [Man] Hey baby, excuse me.
Is this seat taken?
Why don't you join
me in the Jacuzzi?
Come on.
- [Voiceover] Now,
he's straight fronting.
His mind ain't on dominoes.
Since that woman left his ass,
man, he's been all jacked up.
All that shit he talking,
nothing but a front.
Underneath it all,
he all bruised up.
He talks like he's beyond it,
but let's see who brings it up.
I'm not.
- I didn't have a
muscle to stand.
I was broadsided,
you understand.
One minute I'm in
my cozy little room,
then came a tornado.
Tossed me through hellfire,
a thousand miles elsewhere
landed me somewhere,
somewhere I know not.
- [Woman] This feels so good.
She fixed her mouth
to say it's over.
How she managed to put
those words together
is beyond me today.
She was unhappy.
I had no idea.
Gravity compelled
me to my knees.
I begged without
interruption, please.
How could she do this to me?
Myself, our
daughter, the family.
It could not be done.
Oh it was out of her control.
She may as well have said
that day, "God broke with me."
If I was unworthy of
forgiveness, then so was he.
An internal flame consumed
me from outside within
and with such hatred,
so wrongly baptized.
It was a miracle I didn't die.
Everybody had died, it
was just the same as.
To say it as unbearable is
to only hint at the truth.
Clouds rose up and
blackened the sky.
The sun smoldered,
taking my vision,
that nothing existed
between it in my eye.
Neither my step or the
ground together were aware.
I was conscious only of pain,
pain encompassing
all everywhere.
All this and more
I could forgive,
but that she put another
man between her legs,
legs that brought my
child into this world.
That is the reason
that she must die.
So, tonight as the cock
crows, so she will lie.
It will be brutal
- [Chris] Talking all that
and so hurt.
- [Chris] shit (mumbling).
- Check this out,
check this out.
(hip-hop music
drowns out speech)
- You gonna play or not?
What are you throwing out?
- Connect the dots, man.
- Come on, man.
- Then she told me one day,
I'd be grateful
for what happened.
Said "You gonna
thank me one day."
- Shit man, I'd kill a bitch
do some shit like that to me.
Excuse my language.
- You would not.
- Shit, nigga, I'm a
cold-blooded motherfucker.
You may think I'm not.
You can kid yourself
all you like, baby,
but believe me I ain't playing.
- Alright all y'all.
- You ain't got to believe me.
Do something and find out.
- Whatever you say, OJ.
- OJ is right. You'll be
waiting to get out of jail.
- Y'all let them women treat
y'all like a bunch of bitches,
but to me they will not.
- That's right.
- So, Chris, do you love me?
- [Chris] Oh, get out.
- (laughing) What?
(laughing)
What, what do you
mean "get out"?
We're in the middle of nowhere.
Are you kidding?
You're serious.
You're serious,
you're not kidding?
Quit playing, Chris.
You're serious? We're in
the middle of nowhere.
How am I? Where
am I going to go?
- [Operator] Thank you, ma'am.
Your taxi will be
available in 45 minutes.
- With all due respect,
Chris, kiss my ass.
- Damn, nigga, I'm waiting
for a couple hoes right now.
What the fuck are you doing?
I'm feeling sorry for
you, you pitiful man.
- If you ever looked
in the mirror,
you'd see that you ain't
got enough pity to spare.
- [Wesley] You
know what's a trip?
How after your girl
gives you the rule,
and how beautiful she gets?
- Ain't that the truth.
- You could be
unfortunate in the face,
blind in one eye,
but you be wringing your
hands to keep from the crowd.
- Yeah, that's the truth, too.
- Baby can sound so
innocent and sweet
with a venom that
no poison can beat.
- Now, which thing
she did was this?
- Eventually, she say some
other woman is going to be
lucky to have me one day.
- Oh, that's a body slam there.
- When you find somebody,
she gonna be mad then.
- [Glenn] Man, I was
trying so hard to be cool.
I told her no more,
not to do that,
and now to this
day, swear to God,
she haven't stopped yet.
- I'd be adding them up.
That's another ass-whooping
coming you got.
(laughing)
- You think I'm lying.
It's torture and
it's intentional.
- [Wesley] Mmm-hmm, 'cuz a
scorned woman's fury is hell.
- Worse thing is, I
didn't deserve it.
- Oh, please, nigga that's a
God-damned lie right there.
You would've dogged that bitch
out anytime you could have.
First time somebody
gave you an opportunity.
- Don't try to run my business.
Sure, I was tempted
but I never did.
That's the difference
right there.
- The difference right
there is you a hypocrite.
That's what you are.
Anything wrong
with somebody else,
you the first one
to point it out.
- No, nobody can loan
even a dollar to you.
You loan him a dollar,
don't expect to see it back.
He'll make a deduction
for every favor,
counting from the
first one back.
"Don't you remember when
I did so-and-so for you?"
I mean, not that that's
what he'll tell you,
but only to himself.
Anybody claim a
debt that you owe,
you'll credit them blame.
Calling me a hypocrite.
- Hold, hold, hold the
fuck on right there.
Now, wait a minute, man.
Now, what about that
patient I sent you?
After hearing his case, you
tell me who I thought about.
Who? Who could
make all the money?
You fucking cleaned up.
Why should I expect anything?
You're the
motherfucking surgeon.
You did all the work,
even though not a damned
thing was wrong with his neck.
And why should you, huh?
Nigga, I brought you a
motherfucking goldmine.
Now, you tell me if
that had been you,
you wouldn't have made some
type of stake in that shit,
some type of claim to find.
And now, you want
to talk about this
piss-ass change I owe you.
Motherfucker, I don't owe
you a god-damned dime.
- What I tell you?
- No, no, the money ain't
even the motherfucking point.
The point is, it's that
same thing with your woman.
How high her legs are
in there, I don't care.
But you curse yourself
every time you swear.
- Wait, wait a minute.
- What?
Oh, it's alright for you to
fuck other people's wives.
You just don't want
nobody fucking yours.
- Well, as long as you're
not fucking my wife,
what business is it of yours?
- How do you know I haven't?
- [Group] Woah, woah, woah.
- Somebody just tell me
what the fuck is going on?
- Look, wait everybody,
just wait a minute.
- Look, what are
you trying to say?
- What you misunderstood
what I said?
- No, motherfucker I didn't
misunderstand a damned thing,
but if you want to clarify,
you go right ahead.
- I ain't gotta
clarify a damned thing,
like I give a fuck
what you think.
- I warned you, motherfucker.
Now, you want to test me?
- It's that motherfucker
who's you need to kick ass.
- Everybody just
calm the fuck down.
- You better grab that
motherfucker before I do.
- Nigga, you ain't
grabbing nobody, who?
- Hey, look man, the man
is fucking your wife, okay.
That's who you need to
choke. Choke him out.
- No warnings, just ass
whipping from here out.
- What are you gonna
do to me, sissy?
Same thing you did
to your woman's man?
- [Samuel] On general principle,
the motherfucker
ought to be dead.
- [Wesley] Son of a
bitch, you go to far.
- Hey look man, let him alone.
That's what he needs to hear.
Hey look man, cold-cock
that punk when he's alone.
- [Glenn] You better
close your mouth.
- Threatening is all you
can do when all it takes
is a little girl to cripple you.
- What's gotta be
wrong with you man?
You go too far for what?
- Look, anybody's a fool
to sit on his hands.
That's your woman, man.
Take back what's yours.
- No, he can't claim
what ain't his.
- Just shut up. All of
you just shut the fuck up.
- Fuck you, Wesley, fuck you.
Bitch, I'll kill all
of you motherfuckers,
'cuz that's just how I
am, nigga, I don't care.
You can call it genes.
You can call it demons.
You can call it personality.
Apologize, for what,
when it's a lie?
Only apology you're
gonna get from me
is me pulling my motherfucking
knife out your back,
God-damned hypocrite.
- No, you're gonna apologize,
if I have to make you.
- Bitch, you better move
that motherfucking finger.
- You gonna regret this
day, from every day now on.
- Just fucking shut up.
- [Voiceover] Fellas, fellas.
Can't we all just get along?
Bitch, motherfucker.
(phone ringing)
- Hello?
Oh, hey baby.
Nothing.
Nothing, just getting dressed.
Oh, I'm getting ready
to go do some dancing.
Thought I would go out and
do some dancing someplace.
No, I don't know.
Oh, is that your other line?
Oh, okay baby.
Yeah, for a while.
- [Samuel] Don't tell me.
- [Glenn] She got another call.
Said she'd call back.
- [Chris] And now
she should be calling
that motherfucker back.
Instead she's calling you.
- [Samuel] She's
got your black ass
on permanent hold.
- [Wesley] That's
patience right there.
If you can't have
patience, forget it.
Then, you're losing
control of yourself.
- [Chris] Okay, well
let's see how long
you're waiting until
your next call.
Then, we're gonna see
how patient you are.
- [Wesley] You think, for once,
that this nigga ain't patient?
He's begging so hard,
his knees are scraping
up against the ground,
just hoping, just one time,
that that little
phone will ring.
It's all about
control, can't you see.
- [Chris] (mumbles)
I'm telling you.
You think she don't
have control of him?
- [Wesley] No, no, no,
baby. Patience, please.
- [Samuel] No, no,
no, no, look bitch.
You don't see him
calling her, do you?
- [Glenn] I don't
call her for nothing.
(R&B music playing)
- [Chris] You
think she's guilty.
I mean, what happened
between you two
was because of what
both of y'all did.
You think she's sad right now?
Nigga, don't even
try and do that.
And anyway, you said that
you ain't did nothing,
according to you.
- What did you say?
- What did I say, what?
- [Glenn] Just now,
what did you say?
- What did I say about what?
- I didn't do nothing, according
to me, was what you said.
- That's what you did.
- [Chris] Yeah, well, nigga I
could have said anything. So?
- But you said according to me.
- Well, what if I did?
If I did, I was just
repeating what you said.
(laughing)
- [Glenn] Uh, uh.
I didn't do nothing,
was what I said.
But what you said
was, according to me.
What I wanna know is
where you got that?
- Does anybody know
what this motherfucker
is talking about?
- According to me, means you
got another side to compare.
- He's saying you got another
viewpoint from somewhere.
- Like from who?
- [Glenn] You know from who.
- No, no, no, nigga. Take
that look out your eye.
- You know who. I'm asking you.
- Yeah, well,
nevermind what I said.
You wanna know what I think?
I think you're losing
your God-damned mind.
That's what I think.
- You've been talking to her.
- (scoffs) I ain't been
talking to nobody, man.
And wait, what if I was?
What you gonna do to me?
What, threaten me again?
Is that all you can do?
You gonna threaten me to death?
- Don't get slapped.
- Man, who's gonna get slapped?
Anybody slap me'll be a dead
motherfucker in this place.
- It seems like you do a
whole lot of threatening, too.
- Man, nigga, just
stay out of shit when
ain't nobody talking to you.
- You know what, man, I'll
put my foot in your ass.
- Yeah, well.
Anytime you ready to
die motherfucker, do it.
- Well, fuck you, motherfucker.
- Man, get your motherfucking
shoe off of my chair.
- Fuck you, bitch. Asshole.
- [Voiceover] Every puzzle in
its piece I have together now,
and such adjoining.
Now, I'm fit to kill.
All together, with
one slice missing out.
Using to conspire secretly
what alibi is about.
My innocence is secure
as lovers at first sight.
I'll surprise you in your sleep,
that you need never to wake.
Stealing your life
as you did mine,
before you can
suspect the crime.
- [Voiceover] They
talk about violence,
like if it was
something cool to do.
Who among us can say
there hasn't been a time
when they weren't
swept up in the thing?
(cheering)
(R&B music drowns out speech)
- Take it out.
All right, let's go.
(music drowns out speech)
(yelling)
- [Man] Hold, hold,
hold, hold up.
Game over, my man.
Woody Wood in the
motherfucking house.
- [Wesley] What's up
with your shit man?
- Man, fuck you. What's
up with your shit?
(laughing)
- No, no, no. My boys
are on their way.
You motherfuckers got to bounce.
- [Samuel] Wait,
wait, wait a minute.
This is a public park, nigga.
(arguing)
- What are you
motherfucker, man.
(punching thud)
(kicking and screaming)
- What does this
have to do with OJ?
What, you think he did it?
- [Group] Hell yeah.
- [Chris] Listen, man.
Y'all are some fools, man.
All of y'all, call
yourselves black men.
- How are you gonna rationalize
so many coincidences?
- It wasn't no fucking
coincidences, man.
Y'all just some sellouts.
- OJ Simpson killed Nicole.
- Oh man, that's
a lie right there.
- The brother was framed.
- And that's
exactly what he was.
- They all, the police,
in on this conspiracy.
- Soon as a black man
gets any amount of power,
they just sneak up from
behind and take it.
- Don't let it be a white woman.
- Oh, no, no.
Then, you can kiss
your black ass goodbye.
- You let the police
get away with that once,
and pretty soon--
- Whether they guilty or not.
- You got an
authoritarian state.
They can get anybody--
- I was an illegal
search and seizure.
- Anyplace, anytime.
- Anybody that
happens too white,
the whole case gets thrown out.
- Who knows from where
the evidence, they got it.
I mean, it's not their
business to assume
whether you're guilty or not.
And for all of those
years of lynching,
Emmett Tills and everybody else.
Hell, if he didn't do
it, he might as well.
- What about the DNA?
- DNA? Hell.
Now, they using micro-biotics
to convict a black man.
- The race card was
played by the defense.
- Whether you're poor,
if you are black,
you are a target.
- And the phone calls.
All what about?
- You can't convict
a black man by that.
- She had kids with that man.
Look, I might not have before,
but now I understand.
- So, you'd kill somebody, too
- Who me? No. (laughing)
- And just because I'd do it,
don't mean that he did it.
- That's right.
- Could you do it?
- [Glenn] Could I what?
- Kill.
- [Glenn] Kill somebody?
- Why not? Why not you? Hmm.
- [Glenn] Well, fuck no.
Anybody I put my hands
on wouldn't be her.
- Now see, see how she got
your mind being played?
- Straight out.
- [Glenn] Why?
- [Chris] No, I'm gonna show
you what I would have done
if I was OJ.
Look.
(stabs table) That's
what OJ (mumbles)
- [Wesley] Fucker, what
you think you're doing.
Get the fuck off, you crazy
bastard, man. Fuck you.
- [Chris] I'm telling you
don't touch my knife, man.
Just because you happy
right now, nigga,
don't be surprised.
- [Glenn] Don't be
surprised, what?
- Shit, she's
setting you up, baby.
- Man, the way
she's got you, man.
The way you feel right now,
I bet you it's because that's
how she want him to feel.
- [Samuel] That's right.
(rock music playing)
(car doors slam)
- Darling, you know how I feel.
- Yeah, I know how you feel
but don't worry about that.
Everything's gonna be alright.
- Your friends don't like me.
- Come on, let's
have a good time.
- Wesley?
- Misty.
- I see some things
never change.
- You've not met
Wesley's friends.
- No, I heard about this.
It's going to be cool.
- Well, let me explain
something to you about the food.
It's a little different.
It's going to be a bit greasy.
There will be pig's feet.
- Pigs feet?
- Yes and I know they trot
around in mud all day,
but somehow they make it work.
And collard greens.
And at first I thought
that they were spinach,
but it's not spinach, actually.
Not really, I mean, it's
actually quite bitter.
- Greens?
- Girl, what do you know
about collard greens?
I'm a collard green fiend.
Oh, girl. Don't trip.
I grow collard greens.
- Wesley!
- [pink dress] Mmm, yum.
- Damn, look at Glenn's girl.
It looks like she got finer
since she left that nigga.
- [Friend] Damn, no, shit.
Body is ridiculous,
man. Preposterous.
- It's ludicrous.
- How long they've been
broken up now, anyway?
- Fuck how long.
They broke up, man.
Just because you
step to his girl,
don't mean you doing
something wrong.
- Nigga crying because
he got soft shoes on
and that's what
wrong with the nigga.
He's walking around with
these soft shoes on,
slippers even.
(laughing)
No I'm serious.
You know what, see if it's me,
you can't let a woman have
that kind of power over you.
- [Samuel] That's right.
- [Friend] You know
what I'm saying man?
See, you gotta have
cleats on at all times.
- That's right.
- You let a woman
get over on you,
nigga, she's gonna run
you over every time.
Man, how is Glenn, man?
Anybody see him?
- [Man] I don't want to see him.
I ain't got time to sit
around and watch no fool cry.
(laughing)
- Jeanette called me last night
after talking with Brenda.
- Mmm, girl. I
heard. How is she?
- Oh, you heard?
- Mmm-hmm.
- Wait a minute. What?
- Charlie, drunk as usual,
jumped up and popped
her last night.
- So, he hit her?
- Wait a minute,
on purpose? Why?
- Why? Who gives a damn why?
A man ain't got no business
putting his hands on you.
- He accused her
of sneaking off.
- Did she?
- Miss Thing, it doesn't matter
if she did the whole NBA.
It don't matter. He still
does not give them the right.
- You see a brother down,
you do nothing to encourage
him and to help him.
See, that's the difference
between men and women.
See, women stick together.
- [Man] That's right.
- [Man] See, I'm down
for helping somebody,
but, damn, it's been how long?
- Too long.
- It's ridiculous.
- [Man] Pitiful hostage.
- See, y'all niggas
still tearing him down.
A brother can't get
up with another nigga
tearing him down.
Women, one of them
see one of them down.
Next thing you know
they calling each other.
"Girl, help. I need some help."
There are even girls who
don't like each other,
will call each other to help.
- She's over at
Jeanette's right now
trying to hide from him.
- After that, she's gonna come
and stay with me for a while.
- Well, my old
boyfriend, Lester,
he's a supervisor up
there at the firm.
He'll get that dog fired.
All she got to do
is say the word.
Lester do anything for me.
- No, no, no. We shouldn't
do anything just yet.
We don't want to
aggravate his attitude.
- You know what, you're right.
- And his temper,
you know how they do.
- Mmm-hmm, if we
fight him too soon,
he's gonna get suspicious
and he might just think
she's responsible.
- [Woman] Yeah, you're right.
Then, we should
wait. That's right.
- Yeah, because
come a few weeks,
he'll be in such bad shape
when he gets his pink slip.
He'll think it's his fault.
Okay, he ain't gonna
know what hit him.
- He'll be so busy
looking for a job,
he won't be worried
about who Brenda is doing
or who she's seeing.
- Okay, that's what
it's all about.
- [Glenn] And now
for the good stuff.
You know what, man.
No more "I Love You's"
is my weapon for her.
You hear me?
The only kiss she
gets is in parting.
- You really think she care?
Well, what did she have to say?
- [Glenn] Every word
out of her mouth
is a question in my mind.
- Yeah, well, after my divorce,
Kelly had the nerve to
say she missed me one day.
- [Wesley] She missed you?
- She missed me.
Ain't that a bitch?
- [Wesley] Damn.
- [Chris] I'm
telling you, player,
nothing I say to you about
her can you even afford
to second guess.
- No matter if my thoughts
embrace her all day,
I can't be available anyway, yo.
- Yeah, well, just don't
get too comfortable,
whatever you do.
(R&B music playing)
- Ooh, woah.
He would never make
love in the daytime.
- Come on, never?
- Uh, uh, believe me.
That nigga made love like
he was following a road map
and if I turned the
wrong way, he was lost.
I mean, lost.
- Not to change the subject,
but you're talking
about him again.
- James, I'm sorry.
I didn't mean anything
by it, alright?
- You don't need to apologize.
I ain't fading in the least.
You better recognize.
- Recognize? Recognize what?
- Maybe there's
something still there.
(laughing)
- How would that make
you feel if it was?
- The way I feel ain't
got a damned thing to do
with what anybody
else is feeling.
- You see, that's
what I like about you.
I mean, you understand
my need to want to talk
about that.
- Always.
- I think I love him.
- Yeah, I know you do.
It's not over, is it?
- No, if it was over, I wouldn't
be about to cry right now.
Sorry, I kept you waiting.
- Oh, that's okay.
That's alright.
Well, let me ask you
something, though.
Why couldn't I just have
picked you up at home?
- No reason.
- I mean, you had to come
this way, It was on your way.
I mean, we could have
come here together.
Nobody would have had
to wait for nobody.
- It's no reason.
We're here now, okay?
- I guess, I guess you're right.
I guess that's the main thing.
So.
What's the special occasion?
I mean, usually when we get
together, it's usually on me.
- (laughing) It's
gotta be on somebody.
- I mean, what I'm saying is
usually whenever we go out,
I'm the one that makes
the arrangements.
- What difference does it make?
- When was that, excuse me?
- You know what?
This has been going on too long.
You know, there's the house
that we didn't buy together,
the trip to the
Grand Cayman Islands.
I mean, I don't get it.
The French Riviera,
we never did that.
You know, what happened
to all of those things?
- Look, Shay. Sales are
down at the office, okay?
Okay, but look.
Things are now finally
starting to turn around for me.
- And I've heard that before.
How many times do I
have to hear this, huh?
- Look, how many times
do I have to say it, huh?
- You know, I don't see
that there's a difference
this time at all.
You know, I don't expect
anything from you.
Nothing.
- Shay, look, okay.
I know you've been
taking this hard, okay.
But I promise you, Shay.
Just give it a little more time.
- (scoffs) Time?
If I had time, but
I don't have time.
You know, I'm all timed out.
- Oh, you're timed out?
- Fresh out.
- Oh, you're fresh out?
No, I'm the one that's
fresh the fuck out, okay?
How about fresh out
of my pocket, huh?
How about fresh out of
kicking my ass everyday,
so you can just kick back, huh?
How about fresh out of I'm
tired of waiting on you
to stop waiting on me?
- It ain't about your money.
- Oh, it ain't about the money
- No, it's about me.
- Look here, Shay.
Don't do this to us.
Give us a chance, Shay.
- You know, what?
I won't be at home tonight
and you can pack your things
and leave.
- Shay.
Okay?
- Shay, I love you.
The worst thing they say
you gotta take is a lie.
And the kindest gesture
you gotta do just a lie.
- [Wesley] Mmm-hmm,
because you never know.
- That's right.
- Well, all I got
to do is keep still
and I got her on the go.
- [Chris] Nigga, women
are contrary, man.
Don't you know that?
You gotta treat a woman
like she's some dirt
in order for her to flower.
- What?
- Look at how
you've been acting.
I mean, what has it gotten you?
Everything you've been doing.
I mean, if you want
to get a woman,
you've gotta kick
them in the teeth
in order for them to
know how to feel good.
Then, say some shit like,
"Pick that shit up off the floor
"before it dirty the
rest of the house."
Adding a curse for good
measure in between compliments,
just to keep them off balance
so they don't know where to go
or who to turn to.
Everytime, I guarantee you,
they'll come running
back for more.
When they in front
of they family,
you gotta find fault
with everything with them
and I bet you that
they will defend you
to you, yours or anybody
else who has anything
to say against you.
And then we're you're
ready to go take care
of your night business,
you gotta be able to
look them in the eye
and smile and lie
to them dead on.
Until you can do that, your
woman ain't ever coming back.
- You weak, pathetic little man.
Look you ain't any man.
(R&B music playing)
- [Voiceover] I don't
wanna talk about it,
but I gotta talk about it.
And who else can I talk to,
when I can't talk to her?
Every time we speak, she
drops me to my knees.
- I've been missing you.
- Everything's gonna be alright.
- How do I know you won't
all let it get to me.
- Look in my eyes.
You wanna know the truth?
- Can you forgive me?
I wanna trust you.
What about retribution?
- That's all over.
- You know where
I was last week?
- What are they saying, my eyes?
- The convention in Monterey.
I thought of you the whole time.
- Answer me.
- You love me.
- What else?
- I wasn't alone.
- Tell me. What else?
- What? I don't know, what?
- You know.
- I don't k now what
you're talking about.
- I'm yours.
- I was with him.
It wasn't just a convention.
- You must think I'm a fool.
- I wanna be honest with you.
- No, you wanna see
me suffer, is all.
- I didn't want you
to find out later.
- You wanted to see
me when you said it.
- You enjoy it. You satisfied?
- I won't be satisfied
until we're together.
- Be my wife.
- Go on and call her.
See if she's at home right now.
Let's see if you've got
the courage for that.
- I'd be weak to call.
- [Chris] Don't give me that.
- Yeah, well, I called my
girl like that one time.
She picks up the
phone and she says,
(groaning)
(laughing)
Not right now.
Call me back.
Yeah, I sure the fuck did.
(laughing)
- Look. look, look, look.
What's the difference
to phone, huh?
Anything she's doing is
regardless to all that shit.
- No, no, no.
The phone is a
reminding fact, man.
That used to be his
number that he's calling.
You know, that was
your phone number.
And somebody else is
probably calling right now.
- [Wesley] Chill on the brother.
Whatever he does, why don't
you just leave him alone.
- Hey, he can express his
views the same as you,
motherfucker.
- Why don't you just
stay out of this?
- What, now you're
threatening me?
Ain't this some shit.
Huh? What, you done mustered
up some balls somewhere?
- Look, I'm just
telling you, is all.
- You don't tell me shit.
- [Wesley] Well
then, tell everybody.
- I'll tell you.
- Well, tell everybody
what the fuck you gonna do.
- What you trying to do, man?
What you turning the
other cheek today?
- I'm not gonna do nothing.
What you gonna do?
- Don't think this martyrdom
shit is going to bring
this ass whooping to quit.
- [Wesley] Fuck you,
then do it, huh?
Do it, motherfucker.
- Nevermind your brazen
chest, or your puffed up chin,
or your courage.
All the rest. You
all die the same.
The worst that
you could imagine,
you have not imagined yet.
Defenses against rage,
that's a corpse's jest.
You look at me as easy prey.
I look at you and see
what I have yet to do.
And don't bother to look.
You will see me again.
Gradually and by degrees
you will be destroyed.
I will wrench your heart
of its last drop of blood
for harms that it
offered me in mourn.
(moaning)
(hip-hop music)
(grunting)
- Yeah. (moaning)
How long do you
expect me to wait?
(hip-hop music playing)
- [Voiceover] The phone,
nothing but a curse.
Standing there.
See how it's taunting me?
I can't move, standing here
with my insides all choked out.
How come nobody told
me it was even possible
to feel this way?
Sam could take it.
Even Wesley.
So, what the hell's
wrong with me?
I can't even look at my
friends knowing exactly
what they see,
a sorry ass fool with
spit all over me.
How could this happen?
Somebody explain
that shit to me.
She waylaid me,
while we were still together.
While we were still a couple,
she lay in waiting, storing up,
waiting for the day
when she would hit me.
I was still loving her.
That's the part that gets me.
We had stuff that was only us,
that nobody knew.
And that she could plan
this after all that.
Woo.
No wonder I'm so fucked up.
I'm scared to leave the
house in case she calls,
in case this once she'll listen,
in case my words
land just right.
"I love you." I want to say.
"How are you?" is all I can.
- Daddy, where are you?
(R&B music playing)
(screaming)
(laughing)
- [Wesley] Yeah, that's
what I thought so, too.
- You lucky I don't bust a
cap off in your bitch ass.
- [Wesley] Fuck you, niggas.
- Alright, ya'll.
Quit hogging up the
opportunity to talk.
Give somebody else one.
- [Wesley] Samuel, I tell
you what happened to me?
Hmm?
White girl from
Switzerland, I tell you?
- No.
- I ain't tell you this?
- No motherfucker.
- Well, no, no,
no what, what now?
Tell us, who now?
- Well you know Richelle
and I were planning on
getting back together for weeks.
So she finally let me know,
just because we
getting back together
don't mean she's
letting her new man go.
- Oh ain't that a
bitch. (laughing)
- She actually did that shit?
(laughing)
- That's criminal man.
- No, no, she has the
nerve to sit me down
to tell me what type
of nigga he was, damn.
- Oh, man.
- And yet, you know
I wish a woman would
do some shit like
that to me man.
Drop that bitch off a freeway.
(laughing)
- The other day, I told
baby I was going out with
somebody new even
though it wasn't true.
(laughing)
- Even though she
really is (laughing).
- Whoa! Uh oh. (laughing)
- You know what though?
Man, everything she do,
see it go through her mind.
'Cuz she got to wonder if
I'm doing the same thing too.
- Now I caught myself
getting back at this
one time girl I had
for what she did to me.
Swore on my grave that I
was gonna make her pay.
So I saved paycheck
after paycheck,
'til that final payday.
- That's the Hawaii?
- Mmm-hmm, mmm-hmm, Hawaii,
the Waikiki, Kiki Palace.
Her favorite best place
in the whole wide world.
Now we had been split for a
while then, by then, right.
So when I gave her the
ticket, she says, "Fine".
(laughs) Now, martinis,
dinner by the shore,
the whole nine yards right.
But now it's time to go
back to the room, I'm tired.
We say our good night and
you know, see you later,
you know, the whole thing.
She go to her room,
I go to my room.
She close her door,
I close my door.
But oh, a brother didn't
have to wait long.
Mmm, 'cuz I was ready.
Here she come, tap,
tap (knocking).
She comes in, and
butt naked, freestyle
on the floor with a hotel
call girl. (laughing)
The look on her face was
worth the ticket alone.
(exhales sharply)
but damn, a brother
had a high price
the next day to pay.
But from the racket
coming from her headboard
outta her room, that's
the full day's and more.
(laughing)
- Fuck that man, I'd a
been making noise even if I
had to pretend, doing some
shit like this, you know.
- Hell or got a different room.
- (chuckles) Something.
(laughing)
- Ah, when Shelia and
I was breaking up,
this motherfucker called
the house one day.
Tell me to get my punk
ass up and put that
bitch on the phone,
just like this, right.
- [Glenn} Damn.
- I say, "What?"
He said, "Nigga, you
heard what I said.
"Put that bitch on the phone."
So I say, "The fuck is this?"
'Cuz I wanted to know, you know.
The motherfucker said,
"Nigga, this is me Bobby D.
"B-O-B-B-Y D."
Huh, ain't that a bitch?
- [Glenn] Yeah you
know one of your girls
must have called her like that.
- You want to know
where it came from?
That's where it came from.
- Yeah, you do some shit like
that you better be prepared.
- Yeah, 'cuz it's coming back.
- Hell yeah.
- Coming back.
- Please believe.
- (chuckles) You see, they mark
their territory with that phone.
(R&B music)
- He don't want her back.
Look at her.
Everything he does is
the wrong thing to do.
He can't move in to embrace
her without her turning away.
And every time he goes to
hold her he just gonna let go.
Wow, okay, you can't
let your good girl
have everything she
wants all the time.
And every time he tells
you something different,
deep down, he lying.
(doorbell ringing)
- Hey come on, the door's open.
- Hey Samuel.
- Donna, hey how you doin'?
I didn't expect to see you here.
How's everything?
- Good, but you
know why I'm here?
- No, don't tell me,
let me guess, Wesley.
- Mmm.
- Come one in.
- (sighs) Samuel I
don't know what to do.
I've tried everything.
- Come on Donna, dude's a
fool for you and you know it.
- But nothing I say makes
any difference to him.
- Look, can I get you
something to drink?
Juice, soda, beer?
- Yes, thank you.
You're his friend, what can
I do to make him understand
that there's nothing
there for me?
- Oh that's funny, you
doing everything you can
to make him understand
it's over, and he's
doing everything to make you
understand that it's not.
- Yeah but you know you
have to realize something
it was never that serious.
- Just don't tell
him that, all right?
- Mmm-mmm. I want
you to tell him that.
You can tell him that I
only showed interest in him
so that I could get to know you.
And how I bided
my time with him,
waiting for this
moment to be with you.
- Hey, wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait a minute,
wait a minute, now I don't
know what you heard okay.
Shay and I got our problems,
but this ain't one of 'em.
- (scoffs) So what
are you saying? Hmm?
- What I'm saying--
- Mmm-hmm.
- What I'm, what
I'm saying is no.
- You bitch and stop
looking at my ass.
(R&B music)
- And she put him through
a whole lot of things.
That I can empathize with.
But there is one thing that
he's got to understand,
for some reason, he's not.
- I'm listening.
- It's her pussy.
(R&B music playing)
- Oh my God, I forgot.
You were kissing
me and I forgot.
- What good is that?
- [Voiceover] Yeah he finally
got his shit on there,
a hickey. Okay that's some shit.
What is that?
- [Glenn] You bad.
- [Wesley] He's bad, whoa.
- [Chris] Oh, why
can't I play that?
- [Glenn] (mumbles)
shuff up, shuff up.
- [Voiceover] What
I'm saying is nothing.
- [Donna] You bitch,
stop looking at my ass.
He was there all right.
And somebody else too.
- What?
- [Woman] Oh, that's it, mmm.
Any making up he
thought was gonna go on,
he can forget it now.
- He was with another woman?
- Yep.
- [woman] I thought
you all had plans?
- [leather jacket] Yeah,
he had plans all right.
He planned that shit
all the way there.
- [Woman] Oh wait
a minute, back up.
- That fucking puto.
- [leather jacket] Yeah right.
- [Woman] What?
- I'm so damned pissed
I don't know what to do.
- [leather jacket] You don't
do anything, that's what.
You don't call, you don't
return his phone calls.
And if you see him in
public, play it off
like you never even knew.
And if he wants to make plans,
let him make plans all day long.
But you don't have
to follow through.
- Amen.
- Si, si, I did the same
thing to Lonnie Black.
Some type of fag, had
that punk meeting me
all over town, for
dinner, for drinks.
Each time I'd say, "Oh I
don't know what happened,
"but next time, I'm there."
Mmm, puto right now
probably waiting
for me somewhere (laughing).
- Oh girl, you'll
be okay though.
- What about it.
- [Waitress] Here we
go ladies, your drinks.
- Thank you.
- [Waitress] Like
these, ready to order?
- [Glenn] I wanna see,
'cuz I'm really close here.
- [Chris] Hey man
you just watch out.
- [Wesley] Go ahead and pass,
you know you wanna pass.
- [Chris] Man shut up.
- I'm a tell you what
the last time I did.
All right? That, it was
Father's day a matter of fact.
Now she invited me
over to her place
to spend the day
because of that, right.
But I was back with
my family, it felt
so good my defenses
was down, you know.
She started complimenting so
I started complimenting back.
You know what I'm saying?
'Cuz I could she wanted
me, it wasn't hard to tell.
But I insisted no, you know?
Well I stood my
ground there too.
I'm telling you it was all
I could do to hold back.
- (grunts) You held back?
- Wait a minute, what
you mean, you held back?
- I held back. You know.
- [Chris] What you hold back?
- I didn't go as far as
I, you know, as I could.
(laughing)
- You didn't put in you mean.
- You got to understand
man, I wasn't
going back to that
feeling, you know,
being dismissed, but it was
all I could do to resist.
- So what'd you do?
- Kept his clothes
on. (laughing)
- Oh is that all?
(laughing)
You know what, I should of
expected that shit from you.
- But I did for a
while, but it was good.
But still I'm not going
back to that feeling,
for my decency's sake,
so I kept a shred.
- [Chris] So what did you do?
- Because the minute
you go all the way
the power has shifted control.
- And they know it too.
Sit back and smoke
a cigarette on you.
- Yeah that's just
what they will.
- Ah, and then by then,
she started to bed.
- This motherfucker,
you believe this shit?
- She did man but
my mind was made.
Look it's surprised
me I did what I did.
- Aw, what the hell did you do?
- [Wesley] Yeah, what the hell?
- I held back.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
You holdin' back now huh?
What else did you
hold back Glenn?
- Nigga you full of shit.
- You fuck somebody
or either you don't.
- Wait, wait, you
held back what?
- No, no, no, no, no, what
the fuck he got to hold back?
- Listen, did you put it in?
- Not all the way.
(laughing)
- That little piece
of shit you got?
The moment you put
that motherfucker in
you go straight to the back.
- I didn't put it
in, not really.
- Oh please you a
God-damned liar.
- (chuckles) How did you
do it? What'd you do?
- What? I kept my
underwear on, all right?
Now how you like that?
Didn't take it out, I refused.
And she came two
times like that.
- Fuck you man, that,
that, that, what was that?
Father's day right?
That was two months ago.
- [Voiceover] But
this dude's crazy.
Some people you can
talk to, but him,
he's never gonna change.
- [Glenn] You scared
that's all, you scared.
- I'm sorry you
want to sit down?
- [Woman] Oh no I'm fine.
- Oh, oh, you gotta
excuse my manners,
I ain't see you, you know.
- No really I wouldn't
want to trouble you.
- Baby ain't no trouble at all.
Actually, you know, you
can, you can share it.
- How?
- You can sit on my lap.
Come on baby I'm just
trying to be polite.
- No that was so disrespectful.
- Wait, wait, how is
that disrespectful?
All I asked, I just
posed the question.
- You just being
rude and indecent.
- No, hypothetically,
that's what, you know,
if I did something it'd be
different, I ain't do shit.
- Mmm-mmm, you know
what, you're just
a sorry excuse for a gentleman.
- You know what, take
the fucking seat.
Yeah, can't even make fun
of, and fucking eating too.
Shit, sit your ass down.
- [Wesley] I like that shit.
- All right gimme this,
gimme something, fuck it.
Man, fuck that, bitches
man, I'm telling you.
It's, man hell no, you
ain't never gonna catch
me being punked out by some hoe.
You know what I do to a hoe?
This what I did to this
one bitch one time.
I took this hoe for everything
she had in her crib.
Everything. I left only
two things for her.
A toothbrush and a roll of film.
Her toothbrush, you
know, you know what
she saw when she developed
that roll of film?
- Mmm?
- Her toothbrush sticking
straight out my black ass.
(laughing)
- But man, you
made that shit up.
- No it takes a
sick motherfucker to
think of some shit
like that (laughing).
- (laughing) Whoever thought
of it, I take off my hat.
- And you made that up.
- Yeah you're right,
that's some bullshit.
That's like that
Father's day shit man.
I think that's
some bullshit too.
Who gonna let you fuck
'em with your drawers on?
- Come on man, what
you trying to do?
- [Glenn] What?
- Well I'm just
saying, you know,
you need to get a
motherfucking ass grip.
- Listen, everything she's
done to me is not what I do.
When she don't know
where to find me,
now she has to imagine
all the lurid details.
- Yeah, she ain't gotta
imagine a damn thing
all she gotta do is look at
them mirrors on the ceiling.
- Mmm-hmm but look out that
she don't catch your game.
- No shit, better
cuddle up real tight.
- Keep it all outta
sight 'cuz there won't
be no getting her
back if she knew.
- She might already do.
- [Samuel] You have
to make her a sex tape
or something for her to believe.
- Man, shit, you want
everybody to believe
that you so confident
and high man,
but I know better baby.
- How do you know anything?
- Shit, just looking
at you I can see.
- Oh, what is the
problem with you?
- Oh well, well pick
you the phone man,
nevermind what I said.
- I ain't got to
pick up a damn thing.
- No, pick up the
phone, let's see.
- No, 'cuz I knew
you were scared.
- Why should he be?
- Who said he was scared?
- I said it, me.
You know you want to,
pick up the phone.
- Why don't you just
chill out on the brother?
- Talking about how bad he
is, well, let's see then.
- Scared of what?
Why should he be?
- He quaking in his
boots, scared to death.
Scared that she
might not be home.
Or that she might be home
but be a little busy.
- Yeah well what fucking
difference does it make you?
- Just scared of the
truth, that's all.
- I don't see the
big fucking deal.
- (chuckles) He can't do it.
- Yeah that's
character, something
you don't know shit about.
- No a weak character,
that's what he is.
- Yeah motherfucker,
I said chill.
I mean what is it
you trying to prove?
- What am I? What are you?
What you trying to prove
how big and bad he is?
- Come on, enough of that shit.
- No fuck you.
- No fuck you
motherfucker, for real.
- Well I beat the
living shit outta you.
- Hey, don't do something
you gonna be sorry for.
- Yeah well I ain't like you,
I ain't just talking,
I'll do it too.
- Ain't nobody gonna
do nothing to nobody.
- Yeah, ain't nobody talking
to you, you little bitch.
- You pussy motherfucker,
I'm talking to you.
- Whatever Chris
said, man shut up.
I was thinking about
something else.
- Nah, I'm just
tired of his shit.
- Look, forget it.
- No, no man, fuck that.
- You threatening? (chuckles)
- I am, all right?
I'm scared man, is that what you
motherfuckers wanted to hear?
- What I tell you?
- I'll give him
something to be scared.
That's the only reason
I want to kick his ass.
- God! God! God!
- There ain't no use
to feeling scared now.
Whether she comes back
or not ain't up to you.
Regardless to what you think.
- No it isn't.
But I just can't stop.
- Besides, she already told
you, if you was listening.
She said never right?
- Well that's what she said.
- Well man, no it's
not necessarily true.
- Never again, never.
You think she crying and sad?
Shit, she laughing at you.
- It doesn't mean
anything man, nothing.
- Except it does to me.
- She's shitting all over you.
- Every chance she get.
- So how's that for you?
- You think she
really give a shit?
- She don't give a fuck.
- (laughing) If she
was coming back man,
ask yourself, would she do that?
- Everything she does,
goes out of her
way to make me mad.
- She'll be around long
enough to get tired,
tired of finally
kicking your ass.
- Then it's gonna be
goodbye for real, you know.
Start waving bye-bye now
'cuz you might as well.
- You just might as well.
- You think she
losing sleep man?
She having the time
of her fucking life.
Man she tossing and turning
but not from crying.
- It's killing me.
- [Wesley] You just about
have died my brother.
- Feels like I have.
- Yeah she's sleeping
good right now.
And waking up justly
tired (laughing).
- See you gonna make
me do something to you.
- It's just when I felt
like was over it man,
I'm right back to where I am.
- You in hell.
- You put your ass there.
- She the devil, that girl, man.
- I am trying to tell you.
- I just wanna die.
- You need to stop trying
to tell me something.
- I been hurt bad.
- That's just how she
want you to be man.
She keeping it, ain't nothing,
nothing you can do man
going to make any
difference with her.
- I can call her, that's what.
- No, no, no, no, that's
not what you want to do man.
- Yes it is.
- No, I'm telling you.
- Yes it is too.
- [Wesley] No you don't Glenn.
- I'm sick of all this shit now.
- Come on don't man,
think about it Glenn.
Now don't man,
come on man, don't.
- Fuck that.
- Motherfucker, what,
did you hear what I said?
- Man, everybody shut
up, just shut up.
- It's good for him.
- Well what the
fuck do you know?
- Call him, you bad baby?
(knocking)
- [Wesley] Do it
man, just do it man.
Just tell her I love her,
would you do that for me?
- Wesley, come out.
Come on man, come out.
- [Wesley] I want my mama.
Wesley I got something for you.
Now come on, come out.
- [Wesley] (crying) Look,
tell her I'm sorry, all right.
Tell her I'm sorry man,
I love (mumbles) man.
- Open the door, let me
in, man come on please.
- It hurts man, (gun
clicks) it hurts! (sobbing)
- Wesley, open the door,
I'm gonna kick this
motherfucker down.
- Look Wesley, I got
somebody out here
wanna talk to you man.
- Mama? Is that my mama?
- [Samuel] No, look
it's Kim, all right?
Now she says she
wanna talk to you.
- Talk to her.
Wesley, your mama's on her way.
Now what do you want?
You want her to come over here
and see you with your
brains all over the place?
Is that what you want?
- Just leave me
alone man, go on!
(pounding)
(Wesley sobbing)
I love her man.
Why? Why she have to leave?
Come on man, I mean
we had a problem and
if she wanted out man all
she had to was talk to me.
I mean, come on man, I'm not
that unreasonable, no man.
Sam you know I wouln't
hurt nobody don't you?
You know that man.
I mean, why'd she
have to just go
fuck another motherfucker
right away man, shit.
(sobbing)
The bitch could have waited
man, shit (sniffles).
Man, I mean the bitch
could've waited man.
She could've waited man.
She could've waited
man (sobbing).
- Cuss her out for me.
- All right fool, oh
you gonna regret it.
- You don't, I will.
- Are you sure, you sure?
- No I can't help it
anymore, all right.
- Good, it's about time.
- (chuckles) Does she
got you man, she got you.
Don't you see it?
- I'm gonna find out right now.
- Come on man, don't I said.
- Look motherfucker, let
me tell you something,
it's my phone.
- All right, all right, all
right, stupid motherfucker.
- You don't want to
call somebody get
your own phone and
don't call 'em.
- From now on,
don't ask me shit.
- Ugh, to hell with your advice.
What did it any good?
Huh, your advice?
- Look I'm just
telling you, don't.
- To hell with your advice man.
- [Samuel] That's right,
show her who the man is.
- You know what?
You don't tell me man.
Go to hell, every last
fucking one of y'all,
just go to hell, all right.
That's all I got to say.
(phone beeping)
- You gonna pay.
- Yeah that's what you say.
- No no, that's
what you gonna do.
- Man we're gonna see
about that ain't we?
- Oh we ain't gonna
see about a damn thing.
It's gonna happen you know.
- Hey look, shut the
fuck up so I can hear.
- So shut the fuck up.
(R&B music playing)
- Something told me something.
That I should wait for
some kind of kind sign.
And that was what that was,
a divine presence in the
form of the worst kind.
- You feel better
now, don't you?
- A lot better.
- Well?
- Well what?
- You know damn well what.
- [Wesley] Come on
man, you're not gonna
tell us what she said?
- (sighs) It don't matter, I
got her right where I want her.
She mine anyway.
- What the hell?
- Anywhere she move,
she move into view.
- Yeah that's some bullshit too.
- Look man, what
did she say to you?
- No, no, no, no, no, no,
you can't believe this
motherfucker, the way he lies.
- Why should I lie? For who?
- Look, you gonna
tell us or not?
- It kicking your
ass, nigga, you just a
cream puff, a big fucking fake.
- You ain't shit and that's why.
- See, that was your last time.
- Forget it.
- No, no, no man,
I'm tired of him.
All he got else
to say is goodbye.
- Leave the
motherfucker alone man.
What can he do?
- Oh no, he heard me
but he had to just
keep on like he didn't.
When you gonna learn
you don't disrespect me?
- Hey kiss my ass motherfucker.
I'm really getting tired
of this motherfucker.
- It ain't gonna be no
next time, this time.
- She said for me to meet
her tomorrow for sex.
If I had the time.
(laughing)
- You expect us to
believe that shit?
- It don't matter, I
ain't going either way.
- Did she really say that man?
- It's not the first time,
she trying to play me.
(chuckles) But I
just cut the line.
I got her now to where she
can't move, check mate.
- [Wesley] Yeah you
got to check your mate.
- [Chris] That's
what you got to do.
- Every time.
- Congratulations
baby, you got all these
stupid motherfuckers fooled
but not me you don't.
- She said she was
gonna get married.
- Married?
- My wife is getting married.
- She ain't your wife.
- Married to who?
- You did ask, didn't you?
- No, I didn't.
- Shit, that's what
you should have.
- She getting married,
don't you understand that?
That's everyday fucking
on a regular basis.
- Look, who is it man?
- It is isn't it, the same man?
- Who doesn't matter.
- Don't let that
happen to you man.
Marriage? Kick that
motherfucker's ass
just for the idea.
- Fuck being caution,
now ain't the time.
- Look, nothing is all I can do.
- No, nothing hell.
- What can he but cry?
- Send that motherfucker to
hell, that's what you need to.
- Break down baby, cry,
you know you want to.
- 'Cuz I'll be damned,
everybody gonna die.
- Strong motherfucker,
just look at you know.
Simple ass pussy, you
are weak and you're fake.
- I impart this small seed
to yield a field of hate.
That with vines of contempt
will choke off her mate.
Everything I would do,
she will now herself.
At last your last grand stroke
against me, tell her from me,
you played yourself.
- Man that's a final
ass whooping you
know you can't take.
- I will marry her
never, tell her that now.
I've been pushed to
indifference that I
will go out of my
way to express.
She can do anything to
anyone anytime anywhere.
She's outta my life.
- Look, marriage is nothing,
it don't mean a thing.
- You lost motherfucker.
Nigga you lose.
- All my best, this
is my now solemn wish.
- What you should've
asked was who.
- No, no, no, no, no, he
ain't ready for that baby.
- No you wrong about that.
- Yeah, well if he
was he would've asked.
- [Wesley] He can take
anything, he just don't know it.
- [Chris] Nah he
can't take this one.
He can't take it,
I'm telling you.
- What makes you think so, huh?
You know there's
nothing I hate more
than a weak ass, punk
ass, punk like you.
- Nigga I will kick
your hypocrit ass.
- Fuck you, I still
have a wife nigga.
(grunting)
Oh, get off, get off.
- Hey, hey, grab that
motherfucker, grab him.
- Get off me (mumbles)
brother get off me.
- Fuck you motherfucker.
- Don't ever touch me.
- No man.
(thudding punch)
- Do that, let me get this.
- Be a fucking nigga..
- What the?
(thudding punch)
(punching)
- Glenn, no, Glenn,
Glenn, Glenn.
- [Chris] Get him off me.
This ain't over man.
- [Samuel] Fuck, come on.
- [Glenn] Chris, I'm sorry man.
- [Chris] Fuck off.
- [Glenn] I'm sorry.
I just snapped man, I'm
sorry man, I just snapped.
- Yeah you damn
right you snapped.
But I got something
that'll snap for your ass.
- Well you ought to be
thanking this motherfucker
that I didn't kick your ass.
- All this shit over a phone?
What all did she say to you man?
- She just said she needs me.
- That's a God-damned lie.
- Fuck you man, how do you know?
- Because I'm the
first motherfucker
she told it to, all right.
- Which is what
according to you?
- I'm marrying her.
Isn't that what she said?
- Who's marrying who?
- Whose wife?
- [Wesley] This motherfucker?
- You?
- Isn't that what she said?
Man, what you think about that?
She gonna be my wife.
- (scoffs) Did you ask
her or did she ask you?
- That ain't even important.
- I thought you didn't
even believe in marriage?
- Well shit, I might
marry one of 'em just to
keep the other ones on hold.
- Now she knows all the lies
that this motherfucker go tell.
- But the truth, she don't.
- I ain't got to tell
her nothing about you.
- Look, look, everything she
gonna know about you man.
- [Voiceover] Now I can
crack this motherfucker in
the face with this
glass right now.
- You can't man.
- [Voiceover] Twist the
broken in every God-damn cut.
- No, no he ain't
marrying nobody.
Ain't nobody marrying nobody.
- [Voiceover] But naw,
hold up, they say keep
your friends close and
your enemies closer.
- [Samuel] He ain't
marrying nobody.
- Congratulations my ass.
- [Voiceover] So
the fucker sat in
my house and drank out my cup.
- Wait, wait, wait,
look, even if you do
what kind of marriage
you think you gonna have?
- [Voiceover] I will be so
close beside this motherfucker
ain't nobody going
to be able to tell
who the fuck's coming up.
- I gotta talk to you man.
Somebody gonna
hurt for this shit.
- Fuck that man,
you can break that.
- [Voiceover] We gonna see.
- Look guys we all friends
here, right? Huh? Huh?
- All right, all
right, just calm down.
- All right, look, look,
there's plenty to drink.
- Yeah and, and, and
Chris, Chris got the weave.
- So all this, just, let's
just relax, all right.
Just a very important
night for us all
so let's all just calm down.
- Nigga I'm calm, I'm just
worried about Chris here.
Is he okay?
- Yeah, no, well I'm, look,
I'm calm, you calm you down.
- (crickets chirping)
(water trickling)
(soft R & B music)
(screaming)
(soft R&B music)
(hip hop music)