["Up on the housetop" playing]
♪ ♪
- ♪ up on the housetop
reindeer paws ♪
♪ out jumps good old
Santa Claus ♪
♪ down through the chimney
with lots of toys ♪
♪ all for the little ones
Christmas joys ♪
♪ ho, ho, ho ♪
♪ who wouldn't know? ♪
♪ Ho, ho, ho ♪
♪ who wouldn't go? ♪
♪ Up on the housetop,
click, click, click ♪
♪ down through the chimney
with old Saint Nick ♪
♪ old Saint Nick ♪
Hey, y'all,
it's santy Claus! [Laughs]
- And cut.
[Applause]
- Whew, thanks.
- That was wonderful, Georgia.
- Oh, thanks.
Yeah, it felt really good.
- Awesome. All right, everyone.
That is a wrap
on miss Georgia winter
for her Christmas special.
- Thank y'all. Thanks so much.
Thank y'all.
Thanks very much, love y'all.
[Press clamoring]
- Miss winter?
- Georgia?
- Georgia, any big plans
for the holidays?
- Well, you know, I've been
touring all year,
and I'm really excited
to get back to the ranch
and get ready for Christmas.
- Are you spending it
with anybody special this year?
[Melancholy music]
- Um...
- okay.
Thanks, everyone, but we're on
a really tight schedule.
We've got to get over to
"the tonight show" right away.
- Miss winter...
- Jimmy Fallon can wait.
Somebody in the back hasn't got
to ask a question yet.
Uh-huh? You, yeah.
- Hello, miss winter.
- Oh, please, honey,
call me Georgia.
- It's not really a question,
but I was wondering
if I could get a picture
with you for my mom.
We're both big fans.
- Oh, you are? Yeah.
Come on up. Come on.
Cute.
- Yeah.
- Hi there.
- Hey.
You want to take a selfie?
- Yes, that'd be great.
- Okay, sure. Cheese!
- Cheese!
- There you go.
- Thank you so much.
- You're welcome.
- Oh, I do have one question.
- Oh, okay.
- Are you going to record
a new album?
- Well, since I had
such a good time here today,
I'm thinking about maybe doing
a Christmas album, yeah.
- You haven't done one of those
since the Georgia and Joe days.
- Yeah.
- Any chance it'll be
a reunion album?
- Oh, you never know,
but I'm pretty sure
that Joe is happy
doing his own thing.
Thank y'all so much
for coming out.
[Chatter]
- ♪ You can wrap it in paper ♪
♪ put in under a tree ♪
♪ but the spirit of Christmas ♪
♪ you still get for free ♪
♪ ♪
[Applause]
- Don't they make
a handsome couple?
- Thanks, Joe.
I mean, that was excellent.
Nice touch with
the Christmas song.
- I thought it was appropriate,
December wedding
and all, you know.
- Always been my favorite
client.
- Maybe that's because I always
play at your weddings for free.
- They say third time's
a charm.
- Oh, let's hope so.
Who knows? Maybe this time,
you'll be lucky in love.
- How about you?
- Me? Oh, no, no, no.
No, I was very lucky
once a long, long time ago.
Go, be with your bride.
Go, go, go.
♪ ♪
- This is great.
I love it.
I like how you changed,
"you're invited,"
to, "please join us."
It's much friendlier.
You did a wonderful job
on the press release, Darnisa.
You're the best intern
I've ever had.
- I'm the only intern
you've ever had.
Thank you, belle.
I really appreciate
having this opportunity.
[Computer chimes]
- Who is it?
- Captain Garrison is wondering
if you can meet him
tomorrow morning at the venue.
- Is something wrong?
- He didn't say.
Do you want me to ask?
- No, I'm sure it's fine.
Tell him I'll be there.
This is all so crazy.
It's Troy.
I've known him forever.
I can't believe I went
to my high school reunion
and came out with the biggest
client of my career.
- Yeah, the U.S. army.
Winter compass communications
is headed
in the right direction.
- Oh, you're a keeper.
[Phone ringing]
- Hello, winter compass.
- Hello, is belle around?
- OMG, you're Georgia winter!
I thought your album
"breakthrough" was so good,
and your pivot to country-alt
was groundbreaking.
I saw you at stagecoach.
- Oh, my gosh.
I thought I recognized you.
I'm just kidding you, honey.
- Hi, mom.
- Hey, baby girl.
I was just thinking about you.
I thought maybe you might be
at your Christmas party.
- Mom, I work for myself.
If I had an office party,
which I don't, it would be me,
a Christmas movie
and some hot cocoa
with my new intern
who you just met.
Besides, I have
a lot of work to do.
[Phone ringing]
Um, hang on.
I have a video call coming in.
- Okay.
- Hey, belle!
Merry Christmas.
- Merry Christmas, dad.
- Hey, belle.
I'll call you back honey.
- Hey, wait a second.
Is that your mom?
- Yeah, you both called me
at the same time.
- No kidding. Let me see her.
♪ ♪
Merry Christmas, Georgia.
How are things?
- Oh, things are great, Joe.
- Things are great with me,
too, been writing some songs.
- Oh, amazing that you have
time for that
when you're singing
at so many weddings.
- Are you tracking me now?
- I just saw it online.
- Oh. I'll give you one guess.
- [Chuckles] Richard.
- Richard again.
- Third time, really?
- That man loves weddings.
This one's kinda small,
though.
I think he's going to splurge
on the honeymoon.
- Third honeymoon,
hm, how nice.
And you and I didn't
even get to have one.
- Seriously?
- Okay, guys.
I've got a lot of work to do.
Do you need anything?
- I wanted to call to see
what you want for Christmas.
- And I need Luke's address
so I can send
you your presents.
- Luke and I broke up.
- Oh, honey, I'm so sorry.
Weren't you going to spend
Christmas at his house?
- Who's Luke?
- The boyfriend you
didn't like.
- No because I liked
the old one better.
- Will you two please stop?
- Belle, won't you just
come out to the ranch
and spend
Christmas with me?
Don't be alone.
- No, you should come out
to the city
and spend Christmas with me.
I'll take you
to my favorite restaurant.
- Thank you both.
I've got a gig that's going
to take me through Christmas,
and I won't have time
to go anywhere.
- Okay. If you change your
mind, let me know.
And, Joe,
merry Christmas
if I don't
see you again this year.
- Right back at you, Georgia.
Merry Christmas, belle.
- Bye, dad.
- Bye, belle.
- [Sighs]
- Oh, it must have been so cool
growing up
with Georgia and Joe
as your parents.
- Oh, you have no idea.
[Both laugh]
[Indistinct chatter]
- Thank you.
- What's with the Georgia face?
- How did you know?
- I know you guys better
than you know yourselves,
a duet that should
have never gone solo.
- She's done fine without me.
- Well, you've done
pretty well for yourself.
- Oh.
- No, you've written a lot
of hit songs
for a lot of talented artists.
- Not the same thing, Richard,
not even close.
- Sound like you wish you
and Georgia
were back together again.
If that happened, I'd make a
boatload of money off you two.
- That boat sank years ago.
Georgia and I are not
getting back together.
Don't get your hopes up.
- You started without me?
- Oh, you know the party
doesn't start
till you get here, Georgia.
Congratulations on wrapping
another holiday special.
- Oh, thanks.
You know, Duke,
as long as you've been
my musical director,
I never get tired of hearing
you suck up to me.
- [Laughs]
Oh, I needed this.
- Uh-oh, you got that Joe
look on your face.
- He still gets under my skin
like a parasite.
- You should see somebody
about that.
- As long as I don't have
to see him, I'm good.
- You two did have
crazy chemistry.
- Yeah, gasoline and a match,
that'll get you a fire,
just not the good kind.
Onstage, amazing,
offstage, kaboom!
- Kaboom!
- Here is to kaboom.
- Good morning, everyone.
It's really coming together.
♪ ♪
- Do you like the way
the banner looks?
- The banner is perfect, Troy,
but it's in the wrong spot.
It needs to be farther back.
Otherwise, it's gonna
block the lights.
- Duly noted.
- You never talked like that
in high school.
- Never really talked
- I'm so happy we reconnected
at the reunion,
and I'm really glad
we're working together on this.
- Yeah, me too.
- And the show is gonna be
fantastic.
I've got the media outlets
all lined up,
and the press release
is ready to go.
- Delay that.
- Is something wrong?
- I have some new orders
from the general
about the snow ball.
So he found out
about your parents.
- Oh, no. What did they do?
- Well, it turns out
he's a big fan,
so once he was informed
of the family connection,
he decided he wants to have
them perform at the snow ball.
- Troy, you know my parents
haven't performed
together in years.
They split up over
creative differences.
- Yeah, that's what
I told the general.
Look, I'm sorry.
If you can't do it,
I totally understand.
- But if I don't do it,
it could jeopardize
my getting future
PR work with the army, right?
- I didn't say that,
but that is a possibility.
- Ugh, are you kidding me,
Troy?
You know my mom and dad.
What you're asking me to do
is almost impossible.
- So you'll do it?
[Upbeat holiday music]
♪ ♪
- Belle, oh, my gosh.
I can't believe you decided
to come for Christmas.
- Hi, mom.
- I mean, look at you!
Girl, you look great.
- Thank you.
- Pop the trunk, and I'll
help you with your luggage.
- Oh, I didn't bring any.
I can't stay long.
- Okay, I'll take
what I can get.
Hey, won't you meet me
back out at the barn?
I want you to see
the new recording studio.
- Yeah.
- Oh, and Duke is there.
- Duke's here?
- Yeah, yeah.
See you in a minute.
♪ ♪
Ta-Da!
- Mom, this is beautiful!
- Belle!
- Why, Duke,
it's so good to see you!
How are Charlene and the boys?
- Oh, they're fine, just fine.
I can't wait to get home
to see them.
Your mom has got me working
overtime on the new song.
- I do not! Well, guess I do.
[Laughter]
- You know,
I'm gonna
leave you two to catch up.
I'll be up at the house.
Both: Okay.
- Thanks, Duke. Ahh.
So what is it?
- What do you mean?
- You got your belle face on.
"I need to ask mama something,
but I don't know
how to ask her."
Why the unexpected visit?
- I have something important
to tell you.
It's pretty big,
and I'm sorry I have to ask.
- Do you need money?
Did your upstart stop?
- No, no.
My start-up is doing very well.
I just wanted to talk to you
about spending
Christmas Eve together.
- Oh, honey, I'd love to spend
Christmas Eve with you!
Where do you wanna go?
- Well, I was thinking
about staying
right here in Nashville.
- Nashville is great
at Christmastime.
What you want to do?
- How about a holiday concert
at Belmont?
- Okay, who's performing?
- You!
- Do tell.
- Well, you and dad.
- Okay, you can stop telling.
- You don't even want to hear
what it is?
- Honey, your dad and I
agreed many years ago
to pursue solo careers,
so you can tell your clients,
"no, thanks.
Not now, not forever."
- Okay, I guess I'll just tell
the United States of America
you're not interested.
- Not interested in what?
- Oh, don't worry about it.
I'll call Kasey or Miranda.
- Oh, stop it. What is it?
- It's a Christmas-y fundraiser
called the snow ball
streamed to troops
all over the world,
you and dad reunited
for one night only,
performing
for the brave men and women
protecting our country.
- Well, I do love doing things
for the troops.
- So you'll do it?
- I don't know.
- This can be
my Christmas present.
- I'd rather give you
a new car.
- But you'll be the headliner.
- I'm always the headliner.
Besides that, have you already
asked your dad about this?
- Well, if I get him
to say yes,
does that mean you'll say yes?
Mom, please.
I really need you to do this.
It's important for my career.
- Well, since the stakes are so
high, and it is for the troops,
I'm willing to get into the
trenches
if your dad says yes.
- [Squeals]
Thank you!
- You're welcome, baby.
Little rascal.
[Horn honks]
- So are you really gonna go
down memory Lane with Joe?
- Oh, memory Lane is just
a road full of pot holes,
speed bumps and detours.
There's no way in the world
Joe is going to say yes.
He's stubborn as a mule,
and you know it.
Then I don't have to disappoint
my little girl.
Let him be the bad guy.
- Uh-huh.
- Where you going?
- Well, I'm just gonna go
call my wife
and tell her that I'm booked
until Christmas Eve.
You two are going to need
a piano player for rehearsals.
- You know that's never
gonna happen.
- I seem to remember you said
that when you first met Joe.
[Laughs]
- ♪ Jingle bells,
jingle bells ♪
♪ jingle all the way ♪
♪ oh, what fun it is to ride
in a one-horse ♪
♪ one-horse open sleigh,
sleigh ♪
♪ sleigh, sleigh ♪
♪ sleigh ♪
[Cheers and applause]
- Dottie.
- Oh, my gosh. Isn't that?
- Okay.
- Go talk to him.
- I want you to give them
a Thursday night spot.
All right? And we'll see
how they do after that.
I know, I know.
They're inexperienced,
but they're young,
and they're in love,
and they deserve a break before
life crushes their dreams.
Go on, Thursday night spot.
Great job, kids.
- Nice, dad.
- Well, hey!
Would you look
what the cat dragged in.
- I love the
Christmas decorations.
- Ah, thank you.
Oh, thank you.
I did them all myself.
Actually,
dottie did it all herself.
I didn't do anything.
- I saw a young coupling
walking out.
They were on the phone
with their parents saying that
Joe winter just gave them
their first paying gig.
- Well, it is Christmas,
and I'm in a giving mood.
So what do you need?
- Have you ever heard
of the snow ball?
- Yeah, that's that big event
that they do every year
where they raise money for
the children of fallen soldiers
so they can have a great
Christmas.
Count me in for $1,000.
- No, there's something else
that I need.
- Anything you want,
anything for my little girl.
- I need you to sing.
- So done.
- With mom for just one night.
- Anything but that.
- But...
- no, belle.
You know that your...
- sorry.
- Hi.
- We ran outside to tell
our parents the good news
and forgot
to thank you, Mr. Winter.
If we have any of the success
that you and Georgia had,
we would be thrilled.
You're an angel.
- Well, I've been called
a lot of things before,
but never an angel.
You're so welcome.
Merry Christmas.
You guys are great.
- Thank you.
- Wait, what would
you guys think
about a Georgia
and Joe reunion?
- That'd be like
a Christmas miracle.
I mean, Georgia and Joe
are the reason we're together.
We grew up on their albums.
[Music playing]
- ♪ Down through the chimney
with old Saint Nick ♪
- It's good.
♪ Old Saint Nick
hey, y'all, it's santy ♪
[Phone ringing]
- Hold on. It's belle.
Give me a second
while I do a little
damage control right here.
I told you he'd let her down.
Hello. Hi, belle.
Yeah.
What'd your father say?
Uh-huh.
Yeah. Okay.
Super.
Love you. Bye. [Laughs]
- Well?
- Joe said yes.
[Music plays]
- ♪ oh, yeah ♪
- ♪ ho, ho, ho
who wouldn't know? ♪
♪ Ho, ho, ho ♪
♪ ♪
- I haven't seen you pacing
like this
since your first state fair.
- We know how that wound up.
- Don't worry.
Singing with Joe again
will be like riding a bicycle.
- Well, the bicycle
is 10 minutes late, as usual.
Does that man think
that his time
is more valuable than mine?
We're doing a reunion concert,
nothing more.
These don't need
to be that close.
There.
- Georgia,
you sang with Joe
a thousand times.
- And we disagreed
a thousand times more
over set lists, outfits,
who's going to
sing which verse.
Why on earth
did I agree to do this?
- Because we promised
our daughter we would.
- Mm. You're late.
- It is so wonderful
to see you, Duke!
Missed you so much, my friend.
Give me a big old hug.
- Yeah, you too, Joe.
- Maybe I should do
the hello part again.
- Oh, yeah.
- Hello, Georgia.
- Hello, Joe.
- Hello, mom.
Hello, dad.
Thank you both for doing this.
- Oh, belle, you're
the only reason I'm here.
Who is that
good-looking soldier?
- That's Troy Garrison.
He's our commanding officer.
We went to
high school together.
- Did y'all date?
- No.
- Why the heck not?
- Mom!
- Well...
- shh!
- Ma'am, thank you so much for
allowing us to use your studio.
- Troy, I remember you now.
You were always
so nice and polite.
- Oh, thank you, ma'am.
- See?
- Oh, may I just say,
the army is thrilled
that Joe and Georgia
are performing
for such a great cause.
- It's Georgia and Joe.
- Right. Right. Of course.
As I was saying, I'm with
the United States army.
- Yeah, the uniform
kind of gave you away.
- You know, if you're sassy
in the army,
they make you do 50 pushups.
- Well, maybe I should join
the army instead of the gym.
- Maybe.
- [Laughs]
Mrs. Winter,
if there's anything you need,
please don't hesitate
to ask me.
- Well, one thing I need
is for you to call me Georgia.
Deal?
- You got it.
- Thanks.
- Here is the schedule.
- Okay.
- Today is just a rehearsal,
but tomorrow,
I'm gonna need you
both downtown
for a photo shoot
and interviews.
- The general did say
he might stop by.
- And apparently,
it's meet the general day,
and then just a few more days
of rehearsals,
and then it's
the big Christmas show.
- Well, the schedule
looks fine.
Rehearsal is always
a good idea.
- Honey, I'm good.
I don't need to rehearse,
but I can help Joe.
- No, Joe is just fine
on his own.
- The blue piece of paper
is the set list.
I had my intern
run some analytics
on your most popular
Christmas songs
crossed against the most-liked
Christmas songs of all time.
I think it's
a pretty good list.
- This one right here.
- Bad starter, yeah.
- Okay, that one needs
to come up to here.
- Top?
- Yeah, and then put that down.
- Of course, there's
always room for improvements.
- Okay, I like that.
- It flows better.
- Good.
- Okay, great.
- Yep.
- At least they agreed
on something.
- Okay, honey.
I can work with this list.
- We'll work with the list.
- That's what I said.
- Not really.
- Okay, I don't get paid
to stand around and watch
you two get reacquainted,
so why don't we get started?
- Great. Troy and I are going
to head to the house
and get some work done.
Are you two gonna be okay?
- [Scoffs]
- Of course.
What could go wrong?
- Bye.
- [Sighs]
- There we go.
- What are you doing?
- Getting my microphone
out of the way.
I don't need it
for this, right?
- That's my microphone.
- No, no. That's my mic.
It's on the right-hand side.
I'm on the right.
You're on the left.
That's my mic.
- No, you sing...
you slept on the left side
of the bed,
and you sang on the left side
of the stage.
- I haven't done either one
of those things with you
in a very long time.
- Okay, since this is
just a rehearsal,
would you please stand
on the left side?
- Okay.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- Okay.
We're going to start off with
"rocking little Christmas."
- Is the publicity junket
for tomorrow confirmed?
- Uh-huh.
- So is it
three newspaper reporters
and four TV reporters?
- Uh-huh.
- Maybe we should work
on this later.
- Uh-huh.
I'm sorry.
I'm just wondering
how things are going
over there at the barn.
[Music playing]
♪ ♪
- Where were you?
- You're supposed to sing
the first line.
- You always sing
You made it very clear,
"Georgia always sings
the first line,"
so that would be...
- the last time we performed
this song, you started it off.
You sang the first line.
- No, there's...
no. I remember.
- Okay.
Would you please
sing the first line?
- Well, since you put it so
nicely, I would be delighted.
- Thank you.
- Duke.
- All right. Here we go.
[Music playing]
♪ ♪
- Hoo! Hoo-Hoo-Hoo!
- ♪ I wrote a letter to Santa
last night ♪
♪ that's only what I want
to make my Christmas right ♪
Both: ♪ if I don't get it,
I'm gonna be blue ♪
- Why are you singing?
- We were going to
split the verses.
- You just said,
would I sing the...
did she not just ask me
to sing the first verse?
- No, I said,
"sing the first line."
- Would you please
sing the second verse?
- Since you said it
so nicely, yes.
- Thank you.
- Duke.
[Music playing]
- Hoo!
- Beautiful.
- Excuse me?
- Your mother's home,
it's beautiful.
It's like I'm working
at the north pole.
- Mom loves all things
Christmas.
- Looks like she's bought
all things Christmas.
- Don't let all this fool you.
Mom has done well for herself,
but she's also
increasingly charitable.
- Yeah?
- Ever since she went solo,
she has been a rocket.
- And your father?
- He's always been
more of a songwriter,
even more so since they stopped
performing together.
- I always wondered
what it was like for you
to be growing up
with famous parents.
- It wasn't so bad
most of the time.
I thought living out
of a suitcase was normal.
My parents used to bring me
on all of their tours,
home and abroad.
- It sounds like
the armed services.
- When I was a kid,
one Christmas,
I asked Santa for a compass so
I could figure out where I was.
I hate feeling lost.
- Is that why you're winter
compass communications?
- You've got it.
- You know, we didn't talk
very much in high school,
but I've always wanted
to ask you about that song,
"Christmas belle."
Is it about you?
- Yes.
I was born a few days
before Christmas, the 22nd,
and my parents wrote it
right after I was born.
Not right after.
It wasn't like my dad said,
"it's a girl!
Hand me a guitar!"
But it's pretty close.
- You must have loved
having a Christmas song
named after you.
- I didn't use to,
but now I kind of like it.
How's it going?
- Oh, it's going.
- Your dad's hangry.
- Wow, nice digs, g.
- Thank you, and please
don't call me g.
- All right. What's for lunch?
You make lunch, hm?
- I've got a lot
of takeout menus here.
I've got Chinese, Mexican,
and my favorite barbecue place
is just five miles
down the road.
- We cannot do takeout, no,
not with a kitchen like this.
I'll take care of it.
I'll handle it.
Oh, well, I see somebody still
doesn't like to go shopping.
- Some of us aren't home
all the time.
- Okay, one-half
a takeout chicken.
Red pepper, that's good.
Black beans, an onion,
gotta have an onion,
some green stuff,
corn and...
Whiskey!
- I don't think the whiskey
is a good idea.
Y'all are still rehearsing.
- Oh, wait a minute.
That's the best idea
he's had all day.
- Relax, girls.
It's for the chicken.
All right. Everybody dig into
Joe's famous drunken chicken.
- Have you made this before?
- Nope, never have, not once.
- Let's check this out.
Mmm!
Joe, I don't know
if I missed you,
but I sure have missed
your cooking.
- Thanks.
- Joe, this is great.
When did you learn how to cook?
- Oh, when Georgia and I
first got together,
we had this cute little house,
little bitty kitchen.
- It was terrible.
- No, it was not terrible.
It was cute.
- The furnace kept breaking.
We had no heat.
- As I recall,
we didn't need a furnace.
We made our own heat.
I can tell you that.
- We were playing small gigs
trying to get noticed,
and if we had any money at all,
we used that to record demos.
- One-fifteen Hamilton street.
- It was Henderson street.
- No, no, it was
Hamilton street, 115.
I remember because
it was right up the road
from dirt road donuts.
- Dirt road donuts
wasn't even close to us.
That was a 7-11.
No wonder you always got lost.
- I tell you, your mom sure
loved those donuts.
- Well, as I recall,
you ate all of 'em.
- Really?
- Yes.
- Really? But that little one
that looked like a baseball...
- hey, hey, hey, guys,
are you okay with the set list?
Are we in agreement
that we're going to start
with "rocking little
Christmas?"
- Yeah, that's fine with me.
- It's fine with me, too,
but we're going to need
a lot of practice.
- Yeah, practice on the lyrics.
- Somebody needs to learn
where the Harmony goes.
- I sing the lead.
You sing the Harmony.
That's the way we always did.
- I'm sorry. I forgot.
I have a work call to make.
Excuse me.
- Sure, belle.
- I'm gonna go check
in with base.
- Hurry back.
- Uh, you know what?
I'm gonna go call my wife.
- Mm-hmm.
♪ ♪
- Were we always like this?
- Towards the end, yeah.
The last time we were
in a room alone together
was with our lawyers.
- Huh.
- Joe, we gotta make
this happen for belle.
- Yeah, I agree.
We have to set
aside our differences
and make sure we pull this off.
Otherwise,
she's gonna get fired.
- She can't get fired.
She works for herself.
- You know what I mean.
We have to do this
for the troops,
and we have to do this
for belle.
- Then that's it,
only one night.
- Agreed.
♪ ♪
- Belle, this is really great,
but remind me again.
Why am I wearing it?
- Because it's Christmas,
and you're performing
at a Christmas show.
- That's right. I forgot.
Hey, come on.
Tell me the truth, does this
whole getup make me look fat?
Come on, look.
- Looking good, dad.
- ♪ Jolly old Saint Nicholas
lean your ear this way ♪
- Wow.
- What?
- Santa's a lucky guy.
- He used to be.
- Georgia, does this little
place remind you of the cabin
we were supposed to spend
our honeymoon in?
- Supposed to, keyword.
Yeah, instead, we wound up
in a hotel room in Trenton
because you booked a concert
on our honeymoon night.
- Yeah, I did.
- We were all set
for a romantic weekend
in the mountains,
and you booked a gig.
A gig, Joe. Romance went
right out the window.
- We needed the money, Georgia.
And believe me, I felt bad ever
since I did that.
But the promoter said
that if we played Trenton,
he'd book us
in some other show.
- Is that how we got the show
in Atlantic city?
- Yes, that's how we got
that show and the show after it
and the one in the Catskills.
- I never knew that.
- Okay! Can we get started?
- Sure.
- Yeah.
- Mom, why don't you
trade places with dad?
- Okay.
- All right.
Hat on, hat off?
- Hat on.
- Great.
- Mom, can you scoot
a little closer to dad?
- Can you see the tree?
- Okay, well,
this would be all right
for a prom photo,
but you're Georgia and Joe!
You know, maybe try
looking at each other?
- Okay, don't freak out.
This is just for the photo opp.
- That's why I'm doing it.
Oh! Hello.
- Sir.
- At ease, soldier.
- General hays, hi.
It is so nice
to officially meet you.
I'm belle winter,
and these are my parents.
- Oh, I know who they are.
I'm a big fan.
Georgia and Joe, thank you
for agreeing to perform
for the soldiers
and their families.
- It is an absolute pleasure
to meet you, sir.
- It's an honor for us
to be a part of this.
- And I would be honored
if the two of you
would take a photo with me.
- Why not?
- Absolutely!
- And don't worry,
it's an encrypted phone.
- Oh, good,
I wouldn't want our picture
to fall into the wrong hands.
[Laughter]
- I'm gonna share this photo
with the troops.
I think it'll
raise their spirits.
The show is streaming overseas.
- Ah, that's great!
- You know, I don't know
anything
about military maneuvers,
but I do know
how to put on a concert.
What do you think about
getting video messages
from the soldiers overseas
and then putting those messages
up on the video screens
before the concert?
- Yeah, that's
a stellar idea, Georgia.
- Yeah?
- Captain, I want you to get
on that immediately.
- Yes, sir.
- It was really nice
to meet you all.
I wish I could stay, but I have
a meeting back at the base.
- We totally understand.
- Yes, we do.
[Laughter]
That's a pretty darn good idea
you had there, Georgia.
- Well, thank you.
- Pretty darn good?
That was a fantastic idea, mom.
- Thanks, belle.
- It was perfect, ma'am.
- Thank you,
and you can call me Georgia.
- And you can get back to work.
- Oh! Yep.
- Oh.
- Yep, here we go.
Ready?
[Camera shutter snapping]
- Your parents really turned
it on for the general.
- Yeah.
- They actually look
like a couple.
[Chatter]
Yeah, if you don't mind me
asking,
why'd they ever get divorced?
- They're not divorced.
They separated
and had the papers drawn up,
but neither of them
ever signed them.
- Why'd they even separate?
- It all started around
the time I went off to college.
My dad had always written all
the songs, but he'd hit a wall.
Everything he was writing
just wasn't working.
So the record label wanted them
to start singing
other people's songs,
which my dad refused to do.
So my mom agreed to record
a solo album without him.
- He thought that
he was demoted.
- Yeah,
and then he wrote a song
about their problems,
which made mom madder.
"Christmas without you"?
- That one is a heartbreaker.
- It was a hit for Dolly.
My dad kept writing songs,
just not for my mom.
My dad thought that my mom
didn't need him anymore,
and she felt the same way.
They were both nominated
for grammys that year,
my mom for record of the year
and dad for song of the year.
But when my dad went up
to accept his award,
he didn't mention my mom.
He later said he just forgot,
and then when mom
won her award,
she didn't mention my dad,
either.
My dad moved out that night.
It's been 15 years.
They haven't performed
together since.
- So tell me about
the snow ball.
- A lot of our soldiers
never come home,
so the snow ball raises money
for their families.
- For example, the song
"white Christmas,"
that was actually written
about soldiers
who weren't able to make it
back home for the holidays.
- Will you be singing
"white Christmas"?
- Maybe.
We're going to be singing a lot
of everyone's favorite
Christmas songs.
- Yes, we will. And who knows?
We might even be singing
a brand-new song.
- Oh, we didn't
talk about that.
- No.
That's because it's a surprise.
- It sure is.
- Yeah, I've been writing
a little something.
- Really?
- Well, that sounds promising,
especially coming from a writer
who was just inducted into
the songwriters hall of fame!
- Oh!
Yeah, hey, let's not forget
Georgia was just nominated
for her 16th Grammy.
- Well, thank you, Joe.
That's very sweet of you.
- You deserve it.
- Thank you.
- You've both had
very good solo careers.
How do you feel about
performing together again?
- Honestly,
I'm a little nervous.
- Really?
- Yeah, let's face it.
We haven't done this together
in a very, very long time.
- Oh, I think we still have it.
- Well, your fans
have wanted you
to get back together
for years.
- Well, we're very excited
to get back together
for this Christmas concert.
- Yes, because we love our
troops, and we love Christmas.
- It's gonna be
a heck of a show.
- So, hey, everybody out there,
get your tickets
for the snow ball
because it's Joe
and Georgia time.
- Georgia and Joe time.
[Both laugh]
- [Mouthing]
- Good morning.
You didn't have to bring
everyone peppermint lattes.
That's really
sweet of you, Troy.
- Well, I'm trained
to always be prepared.
So in this case, it's caffeine.
- [Laughs]
- One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight.
One, ha, ho and through.
- Oh!
- Whoa, come here, come here.
Hey, hey, hey, don't let
go of my hand, Georgia.
You're going to wind up
in the drum kit.
- Joe, no! You were supposed
to hold me like this...
- no, that's the other verse.
- Not do the twirl.
- No, no. It's first verse one
twirl, second verse two.
Every time
we've done this dance,
that's exactly
how we've done it.
- Well, I don't know
who you were dancing with,
but it certainly wasn't me.
- Seriously?
- Good morning, I think.
- Hi.
- Your father has forgotten
how to dance.
- No, your father has not
forgotten how to dance.
Your father is dancing Denver.
Your mother is dancing Dallas.
There's a difference.
- Sweetheart, I don't think
we need a big dance number.
Having Georgia and Joe on
the same stage is big enough.
- What she said.
- Let's take 5,
and then we'll come back
and work on the vocals.
- Yes!
- Yeah.
- [Scoffs]
[Sighs]
- What's wrong?
- When I was a kid,
I loved watching them dance.
I knew all of their steps.
- Oh, yeah? Show me.
- Well, I don't
remember them now.
- I do. I watched a few
of the videos last night,
a little bit of recon.
- Yeah?
- Yeah. You ready?
- [Laughs] I don't know.
- So you do remember.
- I remember a few steps.
♪ ♪
- Sorry, I forgot my phone.
It's just right over there.
- Um, Troy, why don't you bring
the coffees out to the guys,
and then we'll be out there
in a minute?
- Yeah. Good seeing you.
- It's not what you think
it is.
- Well, I was just thinking
you two
make a pretty
good-looking couple.
- Mom, we're just
working together.
- Your father and I started out
just working together.
You never know.
[Upbeat music playing]
♪ ♪
- ♪ The mistletoe ♪
♪ the blazing fire
the fallen snow ♪
♪ the magic in
the frosty... ♪
- It's not right, right?
- It's not.
- You two are overthinking it.
It sounded fine to me.
- Keep writing, Joe.
That's what you're good at.
- I don't know what it is,
but something is off,
and you guys
are live in four days.
- Come on, you two.
Look at yourselves.
You're fried.
Let's get out of here.
- What do you suggest?
- I suggest pizza and beer,
and I know the perfect place.
- Where does he get his energy?
- I have no idea.
- Me, either. Come on.
- ♪ Jingle bells
jingle bells ♪
♪ jingle all the way ♪
♪ oh what fun it is to ride ♪
- Pretty cool place
you got here, Joe.
Good music, good food.
- About time you visited.
- Well, I would have
visited sooner,
but I've heard tell
that the owner can be
a little ornery
from time to time.
- Is that a fact?
- Mm-hmm.
- Thank you, Sam.
[Applause]
- Thank you, guys.
I'm Tammy, and this is Mikey.
Merry Christmas. Good night.
- Whoo-Hoo!
- So?
What do you think of them?
- I think they've got
some chemistry.
- Yeah, yeah.
You know, the other night
was their first time
performing live.
- Remember our first time?
- Well, yeah!
It was at the state fair.
- Our families were
on the front row.
- They were so proud.
- We were filling in
for somebody who had canceled.
Who was that?
- Yeah, uh, that was...
was it George?
I don't remember.
I don't remember,
but I'll tell you
what I do remember is that
I had a ball standing
on that stage with you.
Girl, we sang our hearts out.
- Hmm. Yeah, we did. Hmm.
- When you two
were starting out,
did you guys play
venues like this?
- Oh, my gosh, yeah.
We played anywhere we could...
uh, weddings, funerals,
beer joints,
honky-Tonks, rodeos.
- Rattlesnake roundup.
- Hey, why don't you two
get up there now,
see if you still got it.
- That's a genius idea, Duke.
- What about "it must
have been the mistletoe."
- I'm not sure
that's a good idea.
- I am.
- Great. I'll see if the kids
wanna play backup.
- Come on, Joe.
♪ ♪
- Oh, wow, this is happening.
- Now hang on a minute.
- What's the matter?
You got stage fright?
- [Laughs]
- It's been a few years since
we shared a stage together.
- More than a few, Georgia.
- Well, some of those years
were actually incredible.
- Some.
Let's see if we still got it.
- Hope you're talking
about singing.
- What else would
I be talking about?
- Hey, guys, how you doing? Hi!
Thanks for doing this
with us, appreciate it.
- Okay.
- That's yours.
- Yeah, I know.
- Yeah, uh-huh.
- "Mistletoe," folks.
- [Sighs]
Fancy meeting you here, Joe.
- Fancy meeting you here, too.
What do you say we see
if we can't
pass this audition, shall we?
[Music playing]
- ♪ Oh it must have been
the mistletoe ♪
♪ the lazy fire ♪
♪ the fallen snow ♪
♪ the magic in ♪
♪ the frosty air ♪
♪ that feeling everywhere ♪
- ♪ it must have been ♪
♪ the pretty lights ♪
♪ that glistened in ♪
♪ the silent night ♪
♪ or maybe just ♪
♪ the stars so bright ♪
♪ that shined above you ♪
Both: ♪ our first Christmas ♪
♪ is than more than
we've been dreaming of ♪
- ♪ old Saint Nicolas ♪
Both: ♪ must have known
that kiss ♪
♪ would lead to all of this ♪
♪ it must have been
the mistletoe ♪
♪ the lazy fire ♪
♪ the fallen snow ♪
♪ the magic in
the frosty air ♪
♪ that made me love you ♪
♪ on Christmas Eve ♪
♪ a wish came true ♪
♪ that night I fell in love
with you ♪
♪ it only took
one kiss to know ♪
♪ it must have been ♪
♪ the mistletoe ♪
[Cheers and applause]
- Merry Christmas, Georgia.
- Merry Christmas, Joe.
- Cheese!
- Platinum!
[Laughter]
- Thank y'all so much.
Best of luck to you.
- Thanks.
- Mmm.
- That was just like old times.
- I think we're going to
be fine on Christmas Eve.
- Can't believe you kept
all these old posters.
Ah, so many memories.
- Call me sentimental.
- Oh, I think it's sweet.
[Both laugh]
Oh, my gosh.
Green bay, Duluth, Bethlehem.
I hadn't seen most of these.
- I gotta shoot
straight with you, Georgia.
I bought the posters online.
- You didn't!
- I did! Come on, you know me.
If I had designed them myself,
they'd have all said,
"Joe! And Georgia."
- Of course they would have.
- Thank you, Sam.
Here.
Try that out.
- All right.
This beer's really good, Joe.
- Thank you.
- Do you brew it here yourself?
- Yes. I call that
one Peter's Pilsner.
You know why?
- Yeah, for "Peter Pan."
- Mm-hmm.
- Belle's favorite book.
- I think we must have read
that book to her every night.
- "Never say goodbye because
goodbye means going away,
and going away
means forgetting."
- I remember that.
- Mm.
I haven't forgotten anything.
- No?
Then tell me something,
Georgia.
What's it really been like
all these years?
- You mean how's it
been without you?
- Yeah.
- Well, the Christmases
were the toughest.
But sitting here with you now
takes me back to what we had,
almost like no time
has gone by at all.
- Sam, writing stick.
- I knew it.
- Takes me back
to what we had...
- like no...almost like
no time's gone by at all.
- ♪ No time's gone by ♪
- I always loved
watching you write.
- Well, you always
inspired me to write.
So I always write.
Right?
Right!
Georgia, what else did we like
about each other?
I mean, before we didn't.
♪ ♪
[Laughter]
- Looks like belle and Troy
is getting along very well.
- No!
- A little too very well,
as a matter of fact.
- Yeah.
- Did we fall
in love that fast?
- Yes!
Amarillo Christmas show,
remember?
- Oh, yeah, yeah.
- And thank you to the
coordinators of the snow ball
for all of the support
that you've given
to the military
service members
and to the military families.
- To everyone out there,
have a great snow ball
and thank you
for your support.
- These are wonderful.
I'm so glad
that your mom had this idea.
- She's really special.
- Yeah?
Like mother, like daughter.
- Yep, all it needs now
is a bridge.
[Vocalizing]
♪ Almost like at all ♪
- Are you busy tomorrow?
- No. Why?
- You wanna go Christmas
shopping with me for the kids?
- For belle and Troy?
- No, silly,
for the kids
that's coming to the snow ball.
- Yes, I do, silly!
[Both laugh]
[Upbeat music]
♪ ♪
- Oh, oh, oh, oh! Oh.
[Growling]
- Ooh!
They'll kick us out of here.
[Both laugh]
- I gotcha.
- Oh, my gosh.
- What?
- I remember staying up
all night long trying
to put one
of these toy kitchens together.
- I think that building
a real kitchen would be easier.
I remember.
- You never were that good
with your hands.
- Oh, really?
I seem to recall you having
an entirely different opinion.
- Joe, not in front
of the children's toys!
[Both laugh]
- Sorry.
- I'm truly sorry
for hurting you.
[Light music]
- Well, I’m...I’m, uh,
I'm sorry I hurt you, Georgia.
And I was just nervous
about the whole concert thing,
but I'm glad
we got a chance to talk.
- You nervous?
I went through
four sticks of deodorant.
- Oh, hey, hey,
you remember these?
Oh, my gosh, I haven't seen
one of these in years.
- Magic eight ball.
- Yep!
- Yeah, belle used to
get her hopes and dreams
wrapped up in that silly thing,
and you encouraged her!
- There is nothing wrong with
believing in a little magic,
especially not at
Christmas time.
Here, go ahead.
Ask it a question. I dare you.
- All right, magic eight
ball. Uh...
will belle and Troy
fall in love?
[Humming]
"It is certain"?
- Hmm.
- Okay, you ask a question.
- All right. Um...
magic eight ball,
how great will our Christmas
reunion concert be?
- "Cannot predict now."
- Shake it again.
Here, let me help you shake it.
Shake it, shake it,
shake it, shake it.
All right.
- "Ask me later."
This thing can be coy,
like somebody else I know.
- Ha.
- Oh, ma'am?
- Magic eight ball, is Georgia
falling back in love with Joe?
♪ ♪
"Don't count on it."
- Cute!
- Hey. What about this one?
- No, it's too small.
You don't have to pick
the first one you find.
- I thought you like it
when I'm impulsive.
- I did.
- Hey, do you remember
our first Christmas?
- Oh, yeah.
- We were so broke, we couldn't
afford our own tree.
So we had to share one
with the McCains.
- Oh, yeah, we kept it
until we went on tour,
and then we took it over
to their house, yeah.
- You know, I’m, uh,
I'm having a fun time, really,
Christmas tree
shopping with you again.
- It's almost like we're right
back at the start.
Mm-hmm.
- Yep.
- Mm-hmm.
- Writing that down.
Oh, almost like...
♪ right back at the start ♪
Start, start, that's it.
- ♪ Right back at the start ♪
- Where that takes us to...
- ♪ I needed Christmas to ♪
♪ find my way back here
to you and me ♪
- ♪ I never thought
that it would happen ♪
- ♪ now I believe ♪
Both:
♪ in a little Christmas magic ♪
- That's a song!
- That's good.
You were always my best writer.
I've never been able
to replace you.
- Georgia...
I have missed this.
Us, hanging around, talking,
grabbing words
and putting them down in a book
and turning them into a song.
I...i...
- I know.
- I miss it.
- I not only lost
my singing partner,
but I lost my best friend.
[Gasps] I found it!
Oh!
Don't you just love it?
- Yes, I do.
- It's perfect.
- Yes, it is.
[Light music]
♪ ♪
[Knock at door]
[Knocking]
- Just a minute.
- Ah! Hey, hey!
- Happy birthday!
- Merry Christmas!
- Surprise!
[Laughter]
- I can't believe
you're all here.
- Well, baby girl,
this is Christmas,
best time for believing.
- And we figured you didn't
have time to get a tree.
- Or celebrate your birthday,
and Charlene made
your favorite...red velvet.
- And your dad brought dinner.
- I sure did, Joe's famous
Christmas chili and beer.
- Darnisa, did you
organize this?
- No, that would be
your mom and dad.
- Christmas tree in position
and ready
for ornament deployment.
- Okay, y'all, that tree is not
gonna decorate itself.
But first, we need
some Christmas music.
- Yeah!
[Music playing]
All: Hey!
- How about that?
There we go! Whoo!
["Deck the halls" playing]
♪ ♪
I swear these string lights
are shining brighter this year.
- That's great. That's great.
Wait, wait, wait,
more lyrics that...
I swear these string...
what is it?
- String lights are shining.
- Brighter this...what...hey...
- brighter this year.
- No way.
- You used to
always lift me up.
- You were five!
- May I?
♪ ♪
- Careful.
- Ahh!
- Yay!
- Oh, beautiful!
- Thank you.
- You're very welcome.
All: ♪ happy birthday to you ♪
♪ happy birthday to you ♪
[Laughter]
- Hey!
- I brought you something.
- A compass!
It's perfect, Troy. Thank you.
- So you never feel lost again.
- You remembered.
God, it's so sweet.
- I got it when I was stationed
in fort Wainwright
in Fairbanks, Alaska.
- How close were you
to the north pole?
- We were close enough
to see Santa's house.
We were doing
some training missions
that took us
past the arctic circle,
and one night I got caught
in a whiteout.
I had no idea where I was
without that compass.
- Are you sure you don't
need it anymore?
- I know where you are,
and right now
that's all that matters.
- So cute!
- She says,
"no, no more pictures,
no more pictures!"
- I don't blame her.
Oh, that's the year
she told Santa Claus
she wanted a flying pony
for Christmas.
- Flying pony for Christmas.
- I guess she knew
she'd be going places.
That was our last
Christmas together.
♪ ♪
- Hey, can you believe
she's still driving this car?
Would you look
at the smile on her face?
- Oh, I am.
- You're leaving?
- Thank you so much
for having me.
I had the best time,
but duty calls,
Christmas caroling at the
public square park in downtown.
- That wasn't on the schedule.
- I didn't want to bother
Georgia and Joe with that.
But if you want
to come with me...
- I'd love to go with you.
- Uh...
- you guys are more
than welcome to come,
as well, if you'd like.
- Are you kidding?
We love caroling!
- You bet! I'll get my scarf.
[Laughter]
All: ♪ joy to the world ♪
- So what's up
with you and Troy?
- You sound like mom.
- No, I don't sound
like your mom.
I'm your dad.
There's a difference.
Now you probably can't tell,
but he's falling
in love with you.
- And how do you know?
- Well, because he's always
looking around
to see where you are,
and he's always looking
to make sure you're okay.
That's how I know.
- Do you like him, dad?
All: ♪ and nature sing ♪
- yes.
I've always admired
people who volunteered
for the military.
They're not selfish,
and they put other people's
lives before their own.
I think Troy is the kind of guy
who will always be there
for you.
All:
♪ and makes the nations prove ♪
- Mm-hmm.
- I know, I know. Go on.
All: ♪ his righteousness
and wonders of his love ♪
- Hey, handsome.
- Hey!
- You look pretty good here.
- Well, you don't look so bad
yourself there, beautiful.
- Oh, thank you.
[Both laugh]
Oh, would you look at that?
All: ♪ his righteousness ♪
- Remind you of anything?
- Reminds me of us.
- Mm-hmm.
All:
♪ joy to the world ♪
♪ the lord is come ♪
♪ let earth receive her king ♪
♪ let every heart ♪
- Oh, where are they?
Where are they?
[Laughter]
Aw, didn't think
you were gonna make it.
Oh! Hurry, hurry!
- Come on, come on.
[Laughter]
- The roads were awful.
- Yeah, but Troy brought us
up here in his tank.
- It's not a tank, Joe.
It's an army-issued SUV.
- No, it's a tank.
It's got bulletproof glass,
a satellite phone,
and four-wheel drive,
and he wouldn't
let me drive it.
- No.
- Me!
- Where's Duke?
- Oh, I told him to stay home,
he can't drive in this stuff.
- Good idea.
Nobody needs
to be out there in this.
I wanted a white Christmas,
not an ice Christmas.
- [Laughs]
- Here, let me help you.
- No, I know, I know.
I need a haircut.
- Oh, I like it.
- Oh, yeah?
Thank you.
- So, what's the plan?
The show is tomorrow night.
- Okay, honey. Don't panic.
When your father
and I first got started,
all we had was a guitar
and a dream.
We'll take care of everything.
Come on, Joe.
- All right.
♪ ♪
- [Laughs]
Well, what are you
so happy about?
- I had a really
nice time last night.
- Yeah. Me too.
It was so much fun,
and thank you for my compass.
- You're welcome.
- Except, there's something
wrong with it.
It keeps pointing at you.
♪ ♪
- Brought you some tea.
- Thank you.
- You want to talk about
what happened last night?
- Do you?
- No, but I think we should.
- [Laughs] Okay.
You first.
- Okay.
When you took my hand...
Well, that can't be good.
- This reminds me of when
I was a kid,
and the power went out
from the big storm.
Do you remember?
- Oh, yeah. Yeah.
- This is kind of fun.
- This whole week has been fun.
Part of the reason why I agreed
to this reunion concert
is so you and I can spend
more time together.
- I was hoping
for the same thing.
- Great.
Can we talk?
I think I'm falling for him.
- For who?
- You know who.
- Oh, honey.
I think Troy's a winner.
I love the way he treats you,
and...
and he's easy on the eyes.
- Mom!
- Well?
- He is.
- Uh-huh.
- There's something about
seeing him again at Christmas
just makes it
all even more special.
- Aww, falling in love
at Christmas, so romantic.
- Just like you and dad?
- Hm. Yeah.
We were in Amarillo, it was
the last concert of the tour.
All of us were
at the wrap party,
and your dad and I
were hanging out together.
We didn't realize
that everybody had already left
to go back to the hotel,
so we had to walk.
It was so cold.
It started snowing.
I didn't even notice.
Your dad put his coat
around me.
That's the first time
he kissed me.
- So, the ice took down
most of the power lines,
and service is expected to be
restored by tomorrow morning.
We might need to wait
this one out.
- I guess we'll have
to stay here.
- Wait, wait a minute.
I thought you said
Troy's tank could go anywhere.
- No, I agree with him.
I think y'all should stay over.
- Great.
I mean, uh,
that's the best plan.
Come on, Troy.
I'll show you to your room.
- Good night.
Okay, what's
going on with those two?
- I don't know.
[Sighs]
I don't even know
what's going on with us.
- Yeah, well,
want to finish talking?
- No. Not tonight. I'm tired.
We got a busy day tomorrow, and
we should both get some rest.
- Well.
- I've got a spare bedroom
down the hall.
You want me
to fix it up for you?
- Oh, no. Don't go through
the trouble, I'll...
- you sure?
- I'll just stay here
on the couch,
keep an eye on things.
- Okay.
Good night, Joe.
- Good night, Georgia.
♪ ♪
[Playing guitar]
♪ the Carols in the air ♪
♪ I can see you, Georgia ♪
- How long you been up?
- I have no idea,
I just got this melody
in my head.
I've got to get it out.
Sorry, if I woke you.
- Don't apologize for you
being you.
"I needed Christmas."
- Yeah.
♪ Find my way back to you ♪
- And me... the song we were
writing
at the Christmas tree lot.
- Yes. There it is.
- Oh, what have...
what else you've got?
- Uh, well.
♪ The Carols in the air
have never sounded better ♪
- Uh-huh.
- And, second.
- ♪ A winter wonderland
is bringing us together ♪
- Hmm?
- I like that, Joe.
- Yeah. It's...
- Joe, this could be our
ending song for the show.
- You really think so?
- Absolutely. It's great.
- Okay. Then we would have...
that's great.
Okay.
- Yeah.
You just have to finish it.
- Yeah. Well, you know
if anyone had told me
just a month ago that you and I
were going to be performing
a song we wrote
at a benefit onstage...
- yeah, I know, I never would
have believed them either.
- No. No, no, no.
I guess we have our little girl
to blame for all that.
- She's not so little anymore.
- No, no.
And she is beautiful
just like her mama.
- Aww.
[Strums guitar]
[Laughs]
- Madam.
- ♪ She wants to ♪
both: ♪ ring in Christmas ♪
♪ bring in Christmas ♪
♪ tell the world the season's
made for love ♪
♪ she wants to
ring in Christmas ♪
♪ bring in Christmas ♪
♪ that is our Christmas belle ♪
♪ she is our Christmas belle ♪
♪ ♪
- So pretty.
- Aww.
I love that song.
- Oh, me too.
I'm having a blast.
- Me too.
- So, what's next?
- What?
- What's next?
- Joe, we talked about this.
- I know we talked about this,
but why in the world
should we have
to just do this for one night?
- Honey, we've played
this song before.
- What?
- We know how it ends.
I don't think we need
to break each other's hearts
again, do you?
I'm sorry.
♪ ♪
- Oh, it's too late
for that, Georgia.
We just did.
♪ ♪
- Hello. Merry Christmas,
happy holidays to my family,
especially my two daughters,
Nora and Olivia.
Mommy misses you both so much.
You know, it's so hard
to be away from you
during the holidays.
- Yeah.
Everything is going well.
The stage is set,
the lights are up.
It seems like we actually
pulled this off.
Where are you?
- I can't talk right now.
Everything's fine, don't worry.
- Okay. I hope to see you soon.
I miss you.
- Thanks, guys.
See you in a little bit.
- Sorry. That was Troy.
- Oh, I thought so.
Your face lights up
when you hear his voice.
- And yesterday, your face
lit up with daddy.
What happened?
- Oh, we had a power outage.
How about these?
- No.
Mom, what's going on
with you and daddy?
- Oh, honey, I don't want
to talk about your dad and me,
especially now.
- I thought things
were going so well.
- They were going too well.
Your dad and I were getting
emotionally close again.
- You say that like
it's a bad thing.
- It is.
I don't wanna get hurt again.
- I don't understand.
You seemed okay yesterday.
- Well, I wasn't.
It's just that I get so angry.
- Angry with him?
- No, no.
With me, how I feel.
- I think you still love him.
- Oh, honey,
I'll always love your dad.
But I'm fine without him.
- I don't believe you.
- All right, the band
is really tight,
and I got all the cues
for the lighting guy.
- Sounds good, Duke.
Sounds good.
Wait. What?
What did you...
you sit down.
- You are really
out of it, Joe.
Georgia must have gotten
really under your skin again.
- You could say that.
I'll tell you what,
when I accepted this job,
I never dreamed I was going to
fall back in love with Georgia.
- The rest of us did.
We saw it a mile away.
You two should be together.
You're meant for each other.
- Maybe part of me
always thought that...
We might get back together.
Maybe I took this job
so I could see
if there was still something
there, but there's not.
- There is.
- No. There is not.
You wanna know a secret?
- Sure.
- I never stopped wearing
my wedding ring.
No, no, not there.
Here.
- Oh, wow.
- I've worn this thing
for so long.
- You should tell her, Joe.
- No, I can't
and neither can you.
Okay, Georgia's made it very
clear she's not interested.
- Honey, don't worry about it.
We're gonna put on
a fantastic show,
and then maybe we can finally
sign those divorce papers.
Maybe we've both been
holding on to something
we should have
let go of a long time ago.
- So, that's it?
- We were only doing this
for you and the army.
Nothing else.
- I don't care about
the show, mom.
I just want you to be happy.
- Oh, baby girl, I've got you.
I am happy.
- Hey, I've been
looking for you.
What's wrong?
- I just wanted my parents
to get back together.
I know it's a childish fantasy.
- No, it's not.
I totally understand.
- Now I wish I wouldn't
have taken this job.
And then I wouldn't have
this false sense of hope.
- I'm glad you took this job
because if you didn't,
you and I wouldn't
have reconnected.
Sorry. It's not the best time
to talk about that.
- Troy, you have been the
absolute best part of this job.
- You know, I think
I fall in love at Christmas,
the first time, with you.
- Me too.
[Cheerful music]
♪ ♪
- Never say goodbye because
goodbye means going away,
and going away
means forgetting.
♪ ♪
[Knock at door]
- Five minutes.
- Okay.
♪ ♪
[Cheers and applause]
[Dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[Cheers and applause]
- I want to thank everyone
for coming out tonight
to support the snow ball.
Now, I know we're all excited
to see Georgia and Joe winter
perform,
so let's give them
a warm army welcome.
[Cheers and applause]
- Thank you, sir.
- Whoo-Hoo!
Whoo-Hoo-Hoo.
- General.
- Troy, great job.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome, Bella.
[Cheers and applause]
- Whoo!
- We love you, Georgia! Wow!
- It's been so long, Georgia!
- Whoo!
[Cheers and applause]
- Hello, Joe.
- Well, hello, Georgia.
- Fancy meeting you here.
- Fancy meeting you here, too.
But then, of course,
we always do meet
in the nicest of places.
- And, with the nicest people,
like the U.S. armed services
and you nice folks
for coming out
tonight to the snow ball event.
[Cheers and applause]
- And, hey,
before the show tonight,
you saw some wonderful video
up here of some soldiers
who are very proud,
who are not able to make it
home for Christmas this year.
- So, we're going to stream
the entire concert tonight
to send to our men and women
in uniform
all around the world.
So, what do you say?
Let's get this snow ball
Christmas concert rolling!
- Let's do it!
[Music playing]
- [Howls]
- ♪ I wrote a letter to Santa
last night ♪
♪ told him what I want to make
my Christmas right ♪
♪ if I don't get it
I'm going to be blue ♪
♪ I want a rocking little
Christmas with you ♪
Sing it, girl!
- ♪ I don't want
no tinker toy ♪
- That's right.
- ♪ Don't want to waste my time
on any other boy ♪
♪ there's only one thing
that I want to do ♪
- What's that?
- ♪ I want a rocking little ♪
♪ Christmas with you ♪
♪ ♪
Both: ♪ I want
a rocking little Christmas ♪
♪ rocking little Christmas
with you ♪
- [Laughs]
Both: ♪ if I get my wishes,
it's going to be delicious ♪
♪ a stocking full of love
for two ♪
- ♪ ooh ♪
♪ ♪
Come on!
Ow!
Oh, yeah!
♪ ♪
Both: ♪ I want a rocking
little Christmas ♪
♪ rocking little Christmas
with you ♪
♪ if I get my wishes,
it's going to be delicious ♪
♪ a stocking full of love
for two ♪
[Playing guitar]
- ♪ O come all ye faithful ♪
♪ joyful and triumphant ♪
♪ o come ye, o come ye ♪
♪ to Bethlehem ♪
♪ come and behold him ♪
♪ born the king of angels ♪
♪ o come, let us adore him ♪
♪ o come, let us ♪
♪ adore him ♪
♪ Christ the lord ♪
[Cheers and applause]
- Good job. Yeah.
Thank you.
Oh, thank you so much.
Oh, it's been
a wonderful evening.
So many old and new memories.
- And speaking of new memories,
Georgia and I have written
a brand new song.
- And we'd love
to play it for you.
It's called,
"I needed Christmas."
[Cheers and applause]
[Playing music]
♪ ♪
♪ the way the snow is falling ♪
♪ it's all a bit familiar ♪
♪ I feel alive again here
in the dead of winter ♪
♪ takes me back ♪
♪ to what we had ♪
♪ the Carols in the air ♪
♪ have never sounded better ♪
- ♪ a winter wonderland
is bringing us together ♪
Both: ♪ that angel
on the tree ♪
♪ must be looking
after you and me ♪
♪ I swear those string lights ♪
Both: ♪ are shining brighter
this year ♪
♪ it's like that mistletoe
is kind of low ♪
♪ whispering in my ear ♪
♪ putting thoughts in my head,
love in my heart ♪
♪ like we're right back
at the start ♪
♪ I needed Christmas ♪
♪ to find my way back here ♪
♪ to you and me ♪
♪ I never thought it'd happen ♪
♪ but now I believe ♪
♪ in a little Christmas magic ♪
[Cheers and applause]
- Stop.
[Music stops]
- The reason Joe wrote
this song is because
we haven't been together
for Christmas in a while.
- No, we haven't in quite
a while,
but like the song says,
I needed Christmas
to find my way back
to you and me.
[Crowd "awws"]
- Joe, what are you doing?
We didn't rehearse this.
- That's because you don't
rehearse apologies, Georgia.
They come from the heart,
and I am so sorry
I broke yours.
I made a huge mistake
when I said goodbye to you.
Georgia, I fell in love
with you the first moment
I heard
that gorgeous voice of yours.
Do you remember?
- Yeah.
- You make everyone better.
You make me want to be
so much better,
and I'm never going
to say goodbye again.
No.
We've been apart a long time,
but I never took off
my wedding ring.
- Oh, Joe.
[Cheers and applause]
- Georgia, would you please,
please stay married to me?
- You beat me to it.
Would you
please stay married to me?
[Cheers and applause]
- Always.
- You may now kiss the bride.
[Laughter]
- I love you, Joe winter.
- I love you, Georgia winter.
What do you say
we finish our song?
- Oh, okay. [Laughs]
[Playing music]
- ♪ I swear those ♪
both: ♪ string lights ♪
♪ are shining brighter
this year ♪
♪ it's like that mistletoe
is hanging low ♪
♪ whispering in my ear ♪
♪ putting thoughts in my head,
love in my heart ♪
♪ like we're right back
at the start ♪
♪ and I needed Christmas ♪
♪ to find my way back here
to you ♪
- ♪ back here to you ♪
- ♪ oh, I needed
Christmas to ♪
Both: ♪ find my way ♪
♪ ♪
[Cheers and applause]
[Holiday music]
♪ ♪
- Merry Christmas, Georgia.
- Merry Christmas, Joe.
- Merry Christmas, everybody.
♪ ♪