Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
["Wallflowers" playing]
♪ Quiet, dreaming ♪
♪ Grab all your things,
We're leaving ♪
♪ We won't ever belong
Let's never go home now ♪
♪ We are with this
Together in the stillness ♪
♪ We won't ever belong
Let's never go home now ♪
[song continues playing]
[violin music playing]
Please let me get in.
Finley Sinclair?
Yes!
[car honking]
[woman] Is that you?
[Finley] Yeah.
[Jennifer] How'd it go?
[sighs] So much for prayers.
Oh, honey.
You can still audition
one more time in the fall.
Come here.
I know.
You might need to
think about a plan B.
Maybe what you need
is a change of scenery.
Maybe I can try
that Semester Abroad program
that Alex did.
[pilot] I'd like to welcome you
on this flight
to Dublin, Ireland.
It will take us approximately
six hours and ten minutes
of flight time...
Hey, there's an extra seat
in first class if you want it.
It's a long flight to Ireland.
- Yes, please.
- Come on.
[dramatic music playing]
Have fun.
- Magazine.
- Yeah, thank you.
[indistinct chatter on PA]
Sir, your friend needs to
put her seat belt on.
[Beckett]
Yeah, thanks.
As much as I'd love a beautiful
girl drooling on my shoulder,
you better buckle up.
I'm... I'm so sorry.
Um...
And don't worry,
your snoring is cute. [chuckles]
I'm so sorry. I don't... I didn't
even think I would fall asleep.
It's not something I...
- Beckett Rush?
- Geez.
I've gotten this far without
being bothered, all right.
Look, if you keep quiet,
I'll give you an autograph
or something when we land.
Just, no body parts,
I stopped doing that
a while ago.
- Oh.
- Flight attendant probably
thought she was making your year
seating you next to me.
We can do a selfie or something,
just when we land. All right.
I don't want to attract
any attention right now.
I really don't want anything
from you.
Somebody's grumpy
when they wake up.
[Finley] No,
but arrogance makes me grumpy.
Some people mistake confidence
for arrogance.
I'm pretty sure
it's just arrogance.
I know your type.
So, since you know my name,
I think it's only fair
that I know yours.
Finley Sinclair.
And what brings you to Ireland,
Finley Sinclair?
A Semester Abroad program
at my college.
My brother did this a few
years ago, and he loved it.
Changed his whole life.
Maybe it'll work for me.
Hmm. So you have issues?
Life can be tough
outside of the celebrity bubble.
You know, in the real world.
- A bit of advice for you.
- Hmm?
You might wanna brush up on
your people skills
if you're gonna make it
in a small Irish town.
Oh!
And are you an expert
on small towns in Ireland?
Yeah, I am, actually.
We've shot three Dawn of the
Dragon movies there.
About to shoot number four.
Touché.
I sit corrected.
You know,
you look really beautiful
when you admit
that you're wrong.
Yeah, I didn't like
that article either.
[Irish music playing]
[man] Ba-bye!
[man] Bye!
Whoa!
You any good on that thing?
Not good enough.
But I'm going to be
practicing a lot while I'm here,
and working
on a new audition piece.
Sounds boring,
but suit yourself.
Who knows, maybe we'll run
into each other
in a pub somewhere, Spindly?
It's Finley,
and I seriously doubt that.
Well, I hope you find
what you're looking for
and maybe even a little bit
of fun, while you're at it.
Welcome to Ireland,
Felicity Sinclair.
[Finley] It's...
Peace out.
[woman] Have a nice trip.
Bye, bye.
Okay, never mind.
[dramatic music playing]
[indistinct chatter]
[woman] Oh, my gosh,
it's Beckett.
[woman] Oh, my gosh.
- Will you sign this for me?
- All right, okay, one at a time.
- [Emma] Finley!
- [Finley gasps]
Hey you.
Oh! You look exactly
like your picture.
- Emma?
- We're sisters for four months.
Okay,
it's nice to meet you, too.
I heard Beckett Rush
is at the airport.
His new movie is like
the biggest thing
that has ever happened
in Carlingford. Do you like him?
You know,
a little too cocky for me.
I love him. Fact!
Hello, Finley!
- Hi!
- It is so good to have you.
We just loved your brother.
He was one of the family.
And now you are, too.
The good news
is that we inherited
a bed and breakfast
three months ago.
Sean has retired from the army,
and we're running it together.
[Sean] We're still trying
to figure it all out.
Come on, everyone,
let's get going
before we get into
the second hour in the car park.
I'll get your luggage.
Thank you,
I can get this at least.
["Hope" playing]
Take this.
♪ Well I tasted the darkness ♪
♪ As it scorched
Through my soul ♪
♪ And I tried to escape it
But it swallowed me whole ♪
♪ And I tried to evade it
By running away ♪
♪ Or filling my mind
With spurious things ♪
[Nora] This town
might be a wee bit small
for a New York girl,
but we'll get you out
to show you
the rest of the country soon.
[Finley]
I can't wait to see it all.
The old castles,
the Cliffs of Moher.
My brother used to talk about
that place all the time.
- [Nora] We'll take you all over.
- [Finley] That would be amazing.
♪ Yeah, I find hope ♪
♪ It's saving my soul ♪
Here we are.
[Nora] Emma, go show Finley
to her room.
[Emma] I'll give you
the full tour later.
There's a trampoline
around the back.
If you jump high enough,
you can see
into the next-door
neighbor's bathroom.
Don't worry, all the guests are
at the other side of the house.
You can play your violin
up here anytime.
No one will hear ya.
This is my room.
Mom thought
that you'd like your own one.
But yours has the best views.
My nan used to live in it.
She actually died there.
I wouldn't be scared about that.
Obviously,
I'm around the corner
if you ever wanna talk,
do nails, sister things
Leave her alone, Emma.
Finley needs some rest.
She has her orientation
in the morning.
Out!
[dramatic music playing]
Good morning, Finley.
- Hey, did you sleep well?
- All right.
So, we're just busy
serving the guests.
Pour yourself some tea.
Sean'll cook you some eggs.
[Sean] Coming right up!
[Emma]
I need to get my hair to behave.
Emma, you mustn't go out there!
I don't want you
disturbing the guests.
Last time, I found her chatting
on for half an hour
with one of the guests
about her earthworm collection.
I have a passion for biology.
They don't need to hear about
earthworm droppings
at breakfast.
Go around.
Why do you always have to...
- [indistinct chatter]
- [gasps]
[Sean] Always go clockwise!
That's our new system!
Never mind.
This is getting cold.
And we can't afford
any bad reviews.
We can't go out there
wearing cranberry juice.
What would our guests think
of that?
Love, I hate to ask.
But would you mind taking this
to the gentleman in the corner?
All you have to do is set
the plate down on the table,
smile, and walk away.
Yeah, of course.
You?
Good morning to you as well.
You didn't spit in my food,
did you?
- What are you doing here?
- What does it look like?
- I'm a guest.
- In one of these rooms?
Yeah,
that's usually how it works.
Are you stalking me?
- No!
- I thought you might be.
I didn't buy that whole
"I'm not interested" bit.
I'm staying here, too.
- What, the Callahans
are your host family?
- Yeah.
- Oh. [chuckles]
Shouldn't you be at some
boujee hotel with your harem?
What are you talking about?
This is boujee.
It's posh. The cooking's great.
And the service is even better.
Usually.
I have to go to orientation,
so enjoy.
Well, I'll be staying here
for the next few months
while we film.
So, no sneaking up
- into my room, young lady.
- Ooh. Don't worry.
I'm not supposed to bother the
guests. Even if they bother me.
What do you have against me?
I am trying to stay focused...
and I just don't think
you're gonna help with that.
- And how would you know?
- I see the news.
Well, maybe things aren't always
as they seem.
I know your type.
I'll see you later, Frankey.
Hmm. It's Finley,
but good try.
Um...
Why is Beckett Rush
in the dining room?
What? No.
No, that's definitely him.
You can't tell anyone.
Beckett...
Becket Rush is in my house.
I'd never even heard of him
till yesterday.
Of course, you didn't.
You're such a dad.
He's only like, the biggest
movie star in the world.
She's got posters
of him in her room.
Ah, that's why I recognized him.
Nora, dear.
- [gasps]
- [glass shatter]
Do you have any jam
for the scones?
Yes, sure, love.
[Sean]
Just made it fresh yesterday.
Ah. Brilliant.
Cheers.
[Emma chuckling]
[gasping]
Your daughter has lost her mind.
This is exactly why
I didn't want to tell her.
Now not a word.
We have promised him
to keep it quiet.
The whole town
is gonna find out.
Well, it's not gonna be
because of us.
We are going to give him
a place away from the press.
If they find out,
the B&B could be at risk.
We can't afford a bad review
from an international celebrity
right when we're starting out.
Oh, shite!
[whistle blows]
[indistinct chatter]
I heard the Heart Slayer
is staying at your B&B?
See, the whole town knows,
and I can't say a word.
Don't worry, Irish small towns
are good at keeping secrets.
The people here
won't let it out.
Yeah, and if they do,
my parents'll lose
their entire life savings,
and I'll end up in an orphanage.
Your mom is going to be washing
his sheets. How insane is that?
Not the first thing
that came to my mind, but yes.
Hey, maybe Beckett will ask you
to the dance.
Right. The hottest guy
in the whole world
is gonna break up
with Taylor Risdale.
Look me in the eye and say,
"Hey, Emma,
will you go out with me?"
No one has ever even
asked me to it.
Bull.
What's this dance?
It's the big town festival
that happens every autumn.
It's where all of our parents
fell in love. It's disgusting.
It's amazing.
The whole town comes out for it.
Outside, under the lights.
- It's so romantic.
- Or depressing.
[Emma] Guys are already
starting to ask.
Well, maybe this is your year.
Yeah, maybe.
Any lads you fancy yet?
It's just my first day.
Maybe Beckett will ask you.
I think he prefers
his snooty celebrity soirees.
Not really my type.
Dragons!
To the bottom lines.
[indistinct yelling]
Archers, at the ready!
Oriana!
My love!
Come with me, I'll protect you.
My bow!
Stay close.
[ominous music playing]
[indistinct yelling]
Hurry up, keep going.
If you save me, my father
might finally accept our love,
my one true knight.
Duck!
[grunts]
[horse neighs]
More dragons.
We have to go, now!
[screaming]
[dragon screeching]
I am Steele Markov,
son of Talagorn.
May this arrow be true,
and find
the heart of this beast.
[man] Cut!
Okay, guys, back to one.
[indistinct chatter]
How was that?
Did you feel it?
Yeah. Sure.
[Seamus] Beck. Beck.
Beck. Beck. Beck. Beck.
How are you, man?
Okay yeah, everything good?
- Yeah.
- What the bloody hell was that?
Huh?
I just thought I'd try something
a little more subtle, you know?
Subtle? Can you amp it up, man?
- I can amp it up.
- Great. Okay, good.
Because, if not, my friend,
I am afraid,
we're going to have to kill off
your character.
I am joking.
[laughing]
I no serious.
I make a joke, used to feel.
Okay, he can do it, guys.
He's okay. Let's go.
He can do it, I think.
Back to one!
Take 17.
You okay?
- Yeah.
- All right, good.
Hey, listen, I heard
the studio is considering
a trilogy of Steele Markov
spin-off movies
for you and Taylor. So,
you'll finally be getting paid
what you're worth,
plus back end.
So, you know,
just give him what he wants.
- Yeah.
Don't screw this up.
Okay, just give me some space.
Okay.
Yes, whatever you need.
Of course.
I'm here for you. All right.
Thanks.
[Seamus] So one more like that,
please.
[man] Do it again.
[crickets chirping]
[knock on door]
- It's just me.
- Oh, come in, Nora.
Finley, I'm sorry,
but we can't take you
to the Cliffs of Moher
this weekend.
Sean has to fix a heater
and re-tile a bathroom,
so I have to do the hosting
while he's working.
[Finley] Oh, that's...
yeah, that's okay.
[Nora] But I got you a bike down
at the shops today.
So, you can use that
to get around town at least.
[Finley]
Thank you. Yeah. No.
You know, we...
I have plenty of time
- to see the rest of the country.
- [Nora] Aye, plenty.
Listen, I was, um...
cleaning up in here
a few weeks ago,
getting the place ready for you.
And I found this
under the dresser.
It's Alex's journal
from when he was here.
I didn't pry,
or look or anything,
but maybe just a little.
Enough to see it's got
all his drawings and writings.
It's old-fashioned like.
Yeah, he was like that.
[Nora] I was gonna send it
to your mum, but...
then I just thought
I'd give it to you. I...
I wouldn't want it
to get lost in the post.
Thank you, Nora.
This is... amazing.
He was always working
on those drawings.
Now you can see all the things
he loved here.
Yeah, he was so at peace,
you know, when he...
when he came back, and...
he was just an amazing brother.
He was.
I'm sorry. I didn't mean
to bring up sad memories.
It's okay.
[dramatic music playing]
[upbeat music playing]
[Emma] Are you done yet?
I don't like dead bodies
near my feet.
Yeah, are there more crosses
like this around here?
Yeah, like everywhere.
Oh.
[violin music playing]
Oh, come on, Finley.
I think something
just touched me.
Yeah. I've got
to get practicing anyway.
Good. Let's go.
Run! It's no bother.
Oh, sorry about that.
Have a good day.
Come on, Finley.
[violin music playing]
Okay.
[knocks on door]
[Finley] Nora?
You can just come in.
What are you doing here?
You're pretty good
on that thing, you know.
You heard me?
[Beckett] Yeah,
you play like your personality.
And how is that?
Beautiful, but a bit stiff.
What are you doing
up here anyway?
- I'm about to ask you a favor.
- I'm about to say no.
And I'm about to ignore that.
I need some help
running my lines,
- like somebody to work off with.
- No.
How can you say no to this face?
Huh?
Oh, well, I am up-to-date
on all of my shots
and immune to everything.
- Come on, Frankie.
- It's Finley.
No wonder you don't
remember your lines.
Look...
Things have been tough on set.
and my scenes aren't going well.
Um... I'm in my head,
and I need something new
to break me out of it.
Yeah, I...
I know all about that.
Cool drawing.
Do you do this?
[Finley] No. Hey,
I did not say you could come in.
Why? Are all your deepest,
darkest secrets in there?
No, this is my brother's
from when he spent time here.
I just... I can't get
this cross out of my mind.
I mean, why would he write
my name at the bottom of this?
Have you seen this anywhere?
Yeah, there's crosses like that
all over the place.
No.
I need to find this one.
So why don't you just text him
and ask him where it is?
He's... dead.
Oh! Wow.
I'm sorry. I didn't...
I didn't know.
What happened?
I don't really talk about it.
Especially not with
Steele Markov, the heart slayer.
Well, I'd like to think
I'm a little bit more than that.
If you ever wanna talk,
I'm here.
Seriously.
Well, not here in this room,
exactly.
'Cause I'm not allowed in.
[both chuckles]
We could talk downstairs
or wherever you want.
Okay, let's go.
Where?
Run your lines.
Really?
'Cause we don't have to.
Come on,
before I change my mind.
Oriana, we must find a way.
Don't give up on us.
My father is the king.
He won't allow anything
to interfere with his conquest.
He's going to marry me off
to the Prince of Moor.
He'll kill you
if you get in the way.
Well, I'd rather die loving you
than live without you.
My heart can't handle
living a lie.
[laughs]
Come on.
- I'm sorry.
- Okay.
- It's so bad.
- Okay! Okay, okay, okay.
Just give me a minute here.
I got to find it.
Right.
Okay...
Oriana, we must find a way.
Don't give up on us.
I'm doing it to protect you.
My father is the king.
He won't let anyone
interfere with his conquest.
I'll find a way.
They're going to marry me off
to the Prince of Moor.
If you get in the way,
they'll kill you.
I'd rather die loving you
than live without you.
My heart can't handle
living a lie.
[dramatic music playing]
How was that?
Um...
that was...
that was great.
Uh, not stiff at all that time.
I need to...
I really... I need to go to bed.
I have class tomorrow, so...
Oh, that sounds amazing.
Yeah,
you should try it sometime.
I wish I could. I mean,
I'd love to go to college.
Yeah, well...
Hey, thanks for this.
Seriously, you were great.
Yeah, any time.
Night, Francine.
[woman] As part
of your Irish studies class,
you must complete
a service project
in order to see this country
from a different perspective.
So, each one of you will be
adopting a senior citizen
from one of the nearby
nursing homes.
You will spend
at least 20 hours
with your new friend,
and you will do what you can
to serve them during this time.
At the end of the semester,
you will be expected
to turn in an essay
outlining what you have
learned from this experience.
[dramatic music playing]
[woman] So, thank you so much
for coming down to help.
You'll find her
right through here.
[Finley] Okay, thanks so much.
- Hello, Mrs. Sweeney.
- Get out.
Oh, I'm Finely Sinclair.
I don't care if you're the
Blessed Virgin Mary. Get out!
Um...
Uh, I was actually...
I'm here from the college.
I was assigned to you.
I'm just...
I don't need schoolgirls
pestering me.
I'll give you three seconds
to remove yourself.
One, two, three.
Nurse!
Um...
[Cathleen] Nurse!
- Nurse!
- No, it's okay.
- I'll...
- What's going on here?
I have an intruder.
Don't you remember
our conversation, Cathleen?
What about? Me eating
more prunes? [chuckles]
The one about you being civil
to people who come to visit you.
[Cathleen]
I don't need any visitors.
I didn't last year
or the year before,
and I don't today.
You know what?
I'm sure I can get reassigned.
It was... I'm sorry.
It was really nice to meet you.
But can't you just give me
some other old person?
Please, I mean,
she's a crazy witch.
If I reassign you, I'm then
gonna have to make allowances
for all the other students. And
I'm not gonna deal with that.
But she doesn't want me
or anyone else there. Please.
The staff wouldn't have
assigned her
a student if she didn't need it.
Isn't there just a food bank
or an orphanage
or just anything else?
This is the assignment.
If you choose not to do it,
you won't pass
your Irish studies class.
I need to get
a good grade on this.
Then you'll have to go
make broomsticks with the witch.
Cheers.
[door creaks close]
Hello again, Mrs. Sweeney.
I think we got off
to a bad start the other day.
How...
How many times
do I have to tell you
to leave this bloody room?
Oh, I can't do that,
Mrs. Sweeney.
But we're gonna be friends.
I did bring Pride and Prejudice.
I don't like Jane Austen.
It's too bad.
[Cathleen] And I don't want
to spend
all that remains of my life
with the likes of yourself.
Okay, you know what? I tried
to get out of this, but I can't.
I was really hoping
for a sweet old granny,
but I got stuck with you.
So, now I have to do this
to get a good grade,
so I can be good enough
to get into this music school.
I have one last chance
to audition in three months.
So, we're gonna be friends,
whether you like it or not!
- Have you finished?
- Uh-hmm.
If this is
what young people have come to,
then the whole world is doomed.
I'm calling the nurse.
- Nurse!
- Okay. Well, I'm not leaving.
Nurse!
"It is a truth universally
acknowledged that a single man
in possession of good fortune
must be in want of a wife."
- Nurse Where's the nurse?
- "However..."
- Nurse!
- What's all this noise?
She won't leave.
She's invading my privacy.
I want to remove her at once!
Did you enter
without her permission?
Yeah. Yes.
And did you refuse to leave when
Mrs. Sweeney asked you to do so?
Yes.
Good on you, young one.
Cathleen,
you can shout all you like,
but Finley's welcome to stay.
Bye, ladies.
[Finley]
If it's any consolation,
this went much better
in my head.
Hmm.
"It is a truth
universally acknowledged
that a single man in possession
of a good fortune must..."
She calm down?
Yeah, she fell asleep.
I have to check on a resident.
Do me a favor and pop this
into her top drawer.
Cathleen always tells me
to throw her post away,
but I know she just digs
these letters out
of the bin and saves them.
No idea what it's about.
[dramatic music playing]
Hey, how was the nursing home?
Well, that bitter old lady,
Mrs. Sweeney, really hates me.
They've assigned you
Cathleen Sweeney?
Uh-hmm.
Who is this lady?
I wanna meet her. I bet you
I could make her smile.
Not a chance.
Gather round!
Fresh scones!
Damn it!
When are you going to learn?
Try a scone, guys.
Thanks, love.
Brilliant, Mr. Callahan.
Finally, something
we can agree on.
How's the movie going?
- I know Emma wants to know.
- Dad!
Well, it wasn't going well
until I started running lines
with Finley.
Now the director
can't stop complimenting me.
He says Steele Markov
has come alive.
Oh.
Do you think we could run
my other lines, tonight, maybe?
[Finley] I really need to get
to my violin composition
at some point.
Well, I can work
around your schedule.
I mean, if you want to come
to set after class or...
Or we could work here?
Uh, there's nothing special
about what I did.
Anyone could have done it.
- Thank you, Nora.
- Hey, do you think we can go
to the Cliffs
of Moher this weekend?
I am so sorry, honey.
I feel terrible.
These scrapbookers
are here all weekend.
- We can't leave.
- It's okay.
Well, I could take you.
Uh, no, I'll just go
with them when they can.
All right. Let me know
if you change your mind.
- [girl] Tom.
- Taken.
- Francis.
- Shaun.
- Taken.
- Why?
- He has a micro scooter.
- Does he?
- Yes.
[Molly]
I can see the look in the eyes
when young ladies
are thinking about the festival.
I hear the fellas
are starting to ask.
Molly runs the pub.
- Oh, hi! Finley.
- Hey,
it's where I met me husband.
A magical night.
See, it's like everyone.
[Keeva] Hey. I've been asked
a couple of times.
- Of course you have.
- You'll be there, Emma?
I mean, I know it's been
difficult for you in the past.
I mean, it was so sad, seeing
you alone last year, but...
I mean, I can help you out,
if you want.
But, I just got cast in
the new Beckett Rush film,
I just have to run on set
and shoot some things
with Beckett and Taylor.
But I'll see you guys around.
[Aileen] Get away from my shop,
you old drunk.
- Come on.
- Relax, Aileen.
- Run.
- I was gonna buy a book.
Have you got any of those
romantic novels for sale?
- Get out of here. Go.
- All right. I'll leave.
But I won't come back here
buy me books here anymore.
[Aileen]
You're scaring my customers.
Well, good afternoon,
young ladies.
Any chance
of the price of a pint
for a local struggling musician,
who places his art
above all else?
[Emma] Look, I would, Seamus.
But I only have
1.47 and a lollipop.
Well, it's a start.
Seamus, go sleep it off
in the back of the pub.
You're right, Molly.
Thanks, but no thanks.
Ladies!
[Molly] Got to take care
of me best customer,
and tonight's
musical entertainment.
He's been napping here
in the streets for years.
He's got a little cottage
up the road,
but he rarely makes it
back there at night.
What can you do?
It's his life.
He'd rather buy fiddles
than pay the bills.
I better help him.
Good luck!
[dramatic music playing]
[car engine revving]
A convertible in Ireland?
Yeah. I want to be ready
for the three days
a year it doesn't rain.
- What are you doing?
- I was actually looking
for that cross.
Oh, you're not
gonna find it here.
- How do you know?
- 'Cause I already checked.
Oh. Okay.
But listen,
I'm a little worried about you
hanging out
in graveyards like this.
It's pretty creepy.
So, I'm gonna offer you a deal.
- Not interested.
- Just hear me out, okay.
You help me with my lines,
and I'll be
your personal tour guide.
Show you all the sights
of Ireland. Huh? Come on.
It'll help sweet Mrs. Callahan
feel less guilty
that she can't take you around.
Totally harmless.
- Trust me.
- No, I don't.
No, no, no, no.
I'm merely a humble tour guide.
And for a limited time only,
I'm gonna offer you a free tour.
Just to make sure you know
you're getting
the better end of the deal.
So, come on. Let's go.
I'm taking you
to the Cliffs of Moher.
I can't. We can't go now.
Don't you have
a photo shoot to do?
No. I told them I had to help
my boring friend learn
how to have some fun.
Come on, Finley.
Take a risk.
You never know if
you're gonna have tomorrow.
Okay.
[dramatic music playing]
[Beckett] Here we are,
at the Cliffs of Moher.
And what's that?
This is my disguise, young lady.
Pretty inconspicuous,
don't you think?
Breathtaking cliffs ahead,
and you're taking picture
of grass, come on.
Well, there's not that much
of it in Brooklyn.
Is that Beckett Rush?
[groans] I was hoping
for just one day without this.
[girl]
Can we please get a selfie?
Johnny, don't you worry about
that nasty rash you have.
I still love you.
- What is she saying?
- Oh Franny, my dear.
Don't you think
we ought to get married?
It's only right
after you gave me those twins
at the ripe young age of 16.
I'm an unwed mother?
I'm a diseased baby daddy.
What do you want from me?
Come on,
I think we should leave it.
Okay, come on. Let's go.
Okay, they're gone.
You can let go of my hand now.
You were holding on to me. Okay?
Whatever.
That was close.
Thanks a lot for protecting me.
No problem.
So, what's the big deal
with these cliffs anyway?
Just you wait.
Come on, hurry up, hurry up.
Come on. Come on, come on.
["Guardian Angel" playing]
See.
Now this...
this is Ireland. Huh?
It's wild.
It's amazing, it's...
- Beautiful.
- I know.
♪ Yeah, you see
We can dance ♪
All right, come on.
There's better views up ahead.
Come on. Come on,
come on, come on.
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
Can I ask you
a personal question?
Do you even really like
being a movie star?
I mean,
who wouldn't, right?
It's not what I asked.
What was it like
going to high school?
It's...
grueling, and fun and weird,
all at once.
That sounds amazing.
Oh, yeah.
No, I mean it.
You're lucky.
Well, didn't you go
to school on set?
Usually, it was just me.
Sometimes, a few
other child actors and a tutor.
But no prom.
No graduation.
No embarrassing gym class.
Do you regret missing out
on that?
I regret a lot of things.
I bet those birds
don't regret anything, though?
They're just... free.
I don't know, I guess sometimes
I just miss blending in,
being normal, you know.
[dramatic music playing]
There's the real Beckett.
[indistinct chatter]
[man] Rolling, quiet,
no moving around, turn over
Three, two, one. Action!
Wow!
I'll have someone tell him
you're here.
[Beckett] Oriana,
it is not yet wise
to reveal your magical powers.
Indeed.
I will keep the men
until the time is right.
Just like our love.
[man] Cut!
Oh!
Taylor, Beckett,
really great.
You are marvelous, my dear.
[Keeve] Finley!
Hey, what are you doing here?
Did you sneak onto set? I mean,
I'm not going to tell anybody.
No. Beckett invited me.
I wonder what my girl Taylor
will have to say about that.
[Beckett] Finley! Hey!
- Hey!
- You made it!
So, what do you think?
It's amazing.
- Yeah.
- Hey babe, who's this?
Finley, this is Taylor.
Uh, she's here to help me out.
Kind of like
an acting coach. So...
How kind!
Um, so, what other actors
have you worked with before?
I actually haven't worked
with any other actors before.
This is my first time on set,
but it seems pretty cool.
She's a real natural though.
Interesting.
We should probably go run
the lines for the next scene.
Come on, Finley, this way.
It's a real honor
to meet you, Taylor.
The pleasure is all mine.
Come on, this side.
Tired from working
on set all day?
[Finley] Me, no!
I am perfectly fine
'cause I did nothing.
Well, that's what
usually happens on a movie set.
Nobody does anything. Oh!
Uh, is this one
of your girlfriends?
Yeah. No, it's...
- Beckett!
- My manager.
They got me
staying here tonight.
My hotel suite won't be ready
until tomorrow.
Oh, hello, and you are?
Hey, Finley Sinclair.
I'm Beckett's father,
Montgomery.
Oh! It's so nice to meet you.
It is an absolute pleasure
to meet you.
Did you get those scripts
I over-nighted?
Yeah, the first two
Dawn of the Dragon spin-offs?
You read them?
Not yet.
I've been kind of busy.
Yeah, the studio is really,
really, in love
with what you're doing on set.
So, they made an official offer.
It's strong.
Five movies over seven years.
Oh!
I don't know though. Don't you
think it's time to maybe
branch out a little?
To what?
We're building an empire here.
To something that shows
what I can really do.
I want to do something more
than just sword fighting and...
outrunning fireballs.
Oh, but you're so good at it.
That's what the fans wanna see.
Right?
Isn't that right?
You have a very small window
to capitalize on this.
Yeah, I'll think about it,
for sure.
Right now, we gotta cash in
on these sequels.
So, hurry up and read those
scripts. All right. Let's do it.
- Yeah, I will.
- Yeah.
Do they come out
and get your bags here or...
No. Don't worry,
I've got it, Dad.
Okay, great.
So sorry to bore you
with all of that.
I want to hear all about you.
Where are you from?
- [Finley] Uh, New York.
- [Montgomery] New York?
The Big Apple.
[knocks on door]
Good morning, Mrs. Sweeney.
And how are we today?
I brought a Twilight book.
Who are you?
Belinda did warn me that
you might pretend to be senile.
[groans] I don't want the sun.
Oh, that explains it.
The vampires
have gotten to you, too.
You'll really like this book.
I'll decide what I like.
"It was 75 degrees in Phoenix.
The sky a perfect
cloudless blue.
I was wearing my favorite shirt,
sleeveless..."
It's cold.
I want to go inside.
You know, Mrs. Sweeney, um...
Who's Fiona Doyle?
What?
That's none of your business.
Oh, yeah.
I just... I thought
that maybe I could help you
find the right address.
I have the right address.
- Then why...
- I don't want to discuss it.
Okay.
You've been snooping
in my drawers.
Uh...
[Beckett] What's up, ladies?
Groovy day,
don't you think, man?
Convincing.
Do you need directions
to Woodstock?
Whoa, sister!
Give peace a chance.
Mrs. Sweeney,
this is Beckett Rush.
He's an actor in Dragon movies.
Mrs. Sweeney,
it's very lovely to meet you.
I've heard a lot about you.
Yes!
I've seen you on television.
You're in love
with the princess. [laughs]
Um, hey,
I brought you some treats
because I know they're not
giving you the good stuff here.
Although I know it's
nothing like your cooking.
You're probably a wiz
in the kitchen.
Baking is my specialty.
Sugar and spice, my kinda lady.
You really can't turn it off,
can you?
There's nothing wrong
with spreading a little cheer.
Come on, make love, not war.
Tell me,
when did you start acting?
I was seven years old.
My father got me into it.
- No!
- Do you ever do any acting?
Oh, yes.
What was your first role?
At school,
I played the white rabbit.
The white rabbit.
You look kinda like
the white rabbit.
[laughter]
You're funny.
You're a twit.
[laughter]
Thank you so much.
All right, thanks
for letting me stop by, guys.
Okay. Peace out.
Peace.
He's a fine young man.
He's a total player.
[Cathleen] Don't tell me,
I don't know
what I'm talking about.
He's a good boy.
I can spot a bad one
a mile away.
Now, carry on reading your book.
[Finley]
"In the Olympic Peninsula
of Northwest Washington
state..."
Thank God we've kept Beckett
hidden from them so far.
Hey
Do you know much
about Mrs. Sweeney?
I don't like to say things
if I've got nothing nice to say.
Well, she's not that bad.
No, she's not bad.
She's terrible.
So then, who's Fiona Doyle?
Her sister.
Oh.
Mrs. Sweeney really wants
to get in touch with her.
What happened there?
I heard Cathleen Sweeney
stole her own sister's fiancé.
I mean, who would do
such a thing?
I'm saying no more.
Then, she left him, a few years
after they get married.
He was heartbroken.
They say he drank himself
to death not long after.
That's it.
I'm saying no more.
But if Mrs. Sweeney
is the man stealer,
then why is she
the one that's so bitter?
Just getting what she deserved,
I guess.
[violin music playing]
[knocks on door]
It's your friendly Irish
tour guide.
Hey!
Let's take this out
of your hands.
Let's actually be
really careful with that.
We don't really need it
because I have got
the rest of the week off, and
it's time for your next tour.
We're about to have ourselves
some real Irish fun.
It's not a good idea
for me to be going out
to one of your
exclusive nightclubs
or whatever it is you do.
And who says
that I'm into nightclubs?
Uh, every tabloid in
the supermarket checkout line.
Well, don't believe
everything you read.
Beckett,
I really have to practice.
Hey, as your tour guide, it's my
job to make sure you don't spend
all of your time in Ireland
cooped up in this room.
It's what you find
outside of this place
that's gonna help you
write your try-out song.
It's a composition.
Whatever.
God, you are so uptight.
No I'm not.
Oh yeah, you kind of are.
Fine. Where are we going?
You will see, milady.
Come on, let's go.
I'm not even dressed!
No, you are perfect
just the way you are.
Come on, let's go.
We're gonna be late.
Wait.
[Beckett] This is my favorite
place in all of Ireland.
[Finley] This is exactly
what I was afraid of.
[Beckett] Just trust me.
[indistinct chatter]
Oh! Good golly, Mrs. Molly!
I've missed you!
If it isn't me favorite fella!
- Finley!
- Hi, Molly.
Give everybody a round on me!
Drinks are on me!
[cheering]
Cole, you stand guard
at the door.
Make sure no reporters
get in here.
Beckett Rush rules!
No pictures!
These guys are great.
Where's Seamus?
He's already had a few pints.
Looks like it's time
to wake him up then.
Come on. You could learn
a thing or two from this guy.
What am I gonna learn from him?
He's like, homeless, and...
You'll see. Don't worry.
Seamus!
Oh Molly, let me just
crash here tonight, will you?
Oh, you can crash
with me any time.
Oh, it's you, boy. [laughs]
What do you want?
Well, what do you think I want?
I want you to get
this party started!
I brought
this American girl here
to show her some real Irish fun.
We can do that.
[singing in foreign language]
[Irish pub song playing]
Whoo!
[Irish pub song continues]
[Seamus]
[singing in foreign language]
He's great.
[cheers and applause]
[Seamus] Thank you, boys.
I'm told we've got
a fine young fiddler player
here in the audience tonight.
Can you go up
and give us a tune, please.
No. I don't play fiddle.
I play the violin.
Oh, fiddle, faddle, fuddle,
whatever you call it,
it doesn't matter. Come on
up here and join us, lass.
Oh, come on, go up there.
- Come on.
- [Seamus] Come on, girl!
We won't bite ya!
Come on.
Give her a round
of applause, everybody.
[applause]
I'm going to kill you.
Yeah. That's fine.
Just after you play.
Now, repeat after me.
[violin music playing]
Now, you're in a pub in Ireland,
not in an orchestra.
Enjoy yourself.
Doesn't matter what your fingers
or the notes are.
It's how you play them, right.
Play them with your heart.
Play it like you feel it.
If you feel it, they will.
Do you love that instrument?
- Yeah.
- Then show them you love it,
and then you'll have them
wrapped around your finger.
All right. Here we go, boys.
[violin music playing]
[Seamus] That's it.
All right.
[Irish pub song playing]
[cheers and applause]
Hey! Well done!
Well done, dear!
Great stuff.
Oh, you did great.
I hope you'll come
and join us again next week.
There's a fiddler in there,
and we need to let her out.
You know the name,
show what's inside in you.
- What's your name?
- Finley Sinclair.
Finley.
Now that means "fair warrior".
No wonder you were brave enough
to come on stage with us.
Well, that's pretty interesting.
What's my name mean, Seamus?
Beckett, it means, uh,
bee cottage or bee hive.
Means you're probably descended
from a long line
of irritating pests.
[Finley laughs]
[Irish pub song music playing]
And wow!
That was absolutely amazing.
I've never heard anything
like it.
He plays
with everything he's got.
Not bad for a homeless
old drunk, huh?
I stand corrected.
Wow, you are really beautiful
when you admit that I'm right.
- Did you plan this?
- No, not at all.
Okay. Maybe a little.
Thank you.
That was sweet.
Sneaky, but still sweet.
Finley Sinclair,
you're actually not so bad
when you decide
to have some fun.
You're not so bad yourself.
- But we can't get involved.
- No, definitely not.
I couldn't possibly be
a good guy.
And I'm trying
to be a good girl.
And we don't
even like each other.
We're just too different.
It would never work.
It'd be impossible.
[Irish pub song continues]
Wow! Thank you.
That was actually a lot of fun.
But, um,
we should probably keep tonight
between you and me.
I don't want you to get
dragged into the public eye.
Of course,
probably just another
meaningless kiss
- for you anyway, so...
- No, it...
It wasn't.
Trust me.
I don't.
Goodnight, fair warrior.
Goodnight, bee cottage.
Get in here. I saw that!
What is going on with you two?
You can't say anything
to anyone.
You kissed him?
You did? You kissed him.
I can't even barely still talk
to him, and you kissed him.
- My sister kissed Beckett.
- Shh!
Definitely keep this
from my parents.
It's rather obvious.
You two have been
all googly eyed
for each other
the last few weeks.
But I'll keep it classified.
Especially from Mom.
What planet
do you think I live on?
A blind man
could see that coming.
Really, it's probably nothing.
I mean, I don't even think
he meant anything by it.
Either way, this can't get out.
If it does, there's no way
he's still staying with us.
And I don't want
any late-night shenanigans.
Your mother would have my hide.
Would you look at that?
[Nora] They look good together.
[dramatic music playing]
[chuckles]
♪ Every breath holds a moment ♪
♪ Everyone a chance to take ♪
♪ You can see
If you close your eyes ♪
♪ We already know the way ♪
♪ Oooh ♪
♪ Forever you and me ♪
Finley, I'm warning you.
I'll go to work
if you don't have the money.
♪ Running wild and free ♪
♪ Chasing down the sun ♪
♪ Oh we've just begun ♪
♪ It's a winding road
O all the places we will go ♪
You really showed him this time,
still that dragon
won't be back in any hurt.
Oh, you can say that again,
Arthur.
Well, Steele, our dragon seems
to have struck a deal with them
whereby they are...
[Beckett] What? Arthur, what?
Spit it out!
♪ Oooh ♪
[Beckett]
This place is super cool,
one of my favorite spots.
You gotta go under
for good luck. Quick.
Okay, so this is called
the 'Miracle Pride'.
[indistinct chatter]
- [Beckett] You had fun today?
- [Finley] Yes.
[Beckett]
So, what do you think about
letting your tour guide
take you on a date?
[Finley]
Seems harmless enough.
Well, it was either this or fish
and chips at the pub, so.
Wow, this is so much better.
How did you do all of this?
Well, I had a little bit of help
from some friends.
My lady.
Hello.
- Hi!
- There you go.
Thank you so much, Ciara.
You are very welcome.
- Have a good night.
- Thank you, Ciara.
See you guys.
Well, bon appétit.
You have to try this, okay.
Just come here, come here.
Trust me.
All right. Make sure
you're in there. Good?
Yeah are you sure
you know what you're doing?
Don't worry about it.
I grew up on these things, okay.
Um, yeah, I... the problem is,
I'm just...
I don't really like heights.
Heights?
[gasps]
Here I come.
It's not so bad, is it?
- [Finley] Yes, it is.
- We're flying, Finley, come on.
Oh, he's so good at this.
I wonder why.
Legs up, leg's up.
Let it spin.
There you go, you did it.
Just don't look down.
See.
[dramatic music playing]
Okay.
I got you.
See, that wasn't so bad now,
was it?
No, it was fun.
So, what do you want to do
if you ever stopped acting?
It's a waste of time
to even think about it.
It's not really
an option for me.
Well, what if it were?
Maybe go to college,
study history.
I just want to live
a normal life for once.
Wouldn't you miss
all your dragons?
[dragons growling]
My love, you're injured.
It's only a flesh wound
from a dragon's claw.
It will heal.
I cannot say the same
for your father's castle.
You have defended it valiantly.
I believe in you.
I believe in us.
I will fight for your love
until the end of time.
Cut!
Print! Moving on!
Taylor, very special.
Thank you, my darling,
you my frame.
You are so money.
Fantastic.
How did you do it?
You're 100% animal,
0% vegetable.
Gorgeous.
It's delicious.
You taste of victory.
I need a little
sparkling water, please.
I felt that, Beck.
Thanks, Tay.
You did great too.
Very strong performance, son.
Thanks, Dad.
[Montgomery]
They were crying at the monitor.
Seriously.
Does that feel good?
Yeah, it felt great.
It should.
Yeah, everyone's very
impressed with your work.
You have a lot
of leverage right now.
You should really sign
those contracts.
I guess.
Hey, you're trending.
Have you seen the article?
No, I was busy.
With your assistant?
No. Just busy.
Uh-hmm. Here it is.
"Beckett Rush
was spotted in Dublin.
The heartthrob spent
the evening with two models
at the exclusive Emerald Lounge
until Taylor Risdale showed up,
discovered the tryst,
and a cat fight broke out.
R 'n R
is officially on the rocks."
Yeah, and my name
is officially trashed again.
Your movie sales
spiked five percent.
You should be thanking me.
[indistinct chatter]
[Finley] So, you know,
things with the hippie guy
are going interesting.
Oh, and I'm still taking violin
lessons from Seamus. Of course,
he calls it the fiddle.
Oh, next time you come,
bring the fiddle.
I'd like to hear
if you're any good.
Yeah, I will.
Um...
Mrs. Sweeney,
I heard about what happened
between you and your sister.
No, stay out of my business.
Well...
I mean,
you are just the grumpiest woman
I have ever met
in my entire life.
I know something, you know,
made you that way, right!
And what they said you did is,
well, it's pretty shady but...
No, no. You know what,
none of this makes sense.
I know that you care
about Fiona,
so I'm gonna help you,
no matter what.
I don't want your help.
Leave me alone.
[Finley] What?
I'm dying.
What?
Cancer.
I've only awhile to live.
Why didn't you say anything?
[indistinct]
- [Finley] Hey!
- [Beckett] You're late.
I know. But I just,
I came from Mrs. Sweeney and...
Let's just run the lines, okay.
Please.
Okay.
[Montgomery] Well, well, well,
how is my son's lovely
assistant doing?
Um, I'm more
of an acting partner.
Oh, I used to be an actor.
I mean, things have changed
a lot since then.
[Finley] I think it's so kind
how you sacrificed so much
for Beckett's career.
He was a natural.
I mean, he needed to be in LA
to make his dream a reality.
I don't ever remember saying
I wanted to be an actor.
[Montgomery] You did.
"Dad, I want to be in movies"
is exactly what you said.
[scoffs]
I was six years old.
I also said I wanted to be
an astronaut and a giraffe.
Excuse me, Beckett,
they're ready for you on set.
I'll be right back, okay.
Actually,
I need to leave too.
I could really use your help
on this scene after we shoot.
I need to do something
for Mrs. Sweeney.
Beck, we need you on set.
Yeah.
Sorry.
[Montgomery] Finley.
Hey!
You seem like
a really nice girl.
And I just don't want you
to get your hopes up.
This kind of thing happens
all the time.
What do you mean by that?
I just suggest you keep things
very professional with Beckett.
He's with Taylor.
Is he, that...
I just... it doesn't really seem
like he is.
No, they'll be back together
again very soon.
Oh, okay.
So, you manipulate his career
and his love life?
His love life is his career.
So, if you really care
about him...
don't get in the way.
[sentimental music playing]
- Seamus! Seamus, wake up.
- Hey! No broom.
No broom. Huh?
Finley?
What are you doing here?
I need you to tell me
where Fiona Doyle lives.
What are you doing
with those bickering old ladies?
I need to help Mrs. Sweeney.
Why?
- No one else ever has.
- I know, I know.
And that's what
I don't understand.
Why does everyone
hate her so much?
[sighs]
Cathleen Sweeney.
[laughs]
Cathleen
was an absolute stunner.
She was the best-looking girl
in the town.
And it was no surprise
that she was able to lure
Charles Sweeney
away from her
sweet little sister.
When he died shortly
after Cathleen had left him,
the whole town blamed her
and she had not a friend left.
She was shunned by everybody,
even by her own family.
Now, no one wants the opinion
of an old fiddle player.
Between you and I,
I think there was more going on.
It just didn't add up,
you know what I mean.
Here, show me your map.
Oh, I hate these things.
Sorry.
Look, she lives in a little farm
just outside of town.
Now it's a hell of a bicycle
ride up the hill,
but you never know,
we might be able
to figure something out.
What time does Connor come by
to pick up the empty kegs?
He said he'd be here
half an hour ago.
He should be here any minute.
[dramatic music playing]
[cheerful music playing]
Thanks.
Have you come for the pig?
Uh, no.
Hi, I'm Finley Sinclair.
I'm a friend of your sister's.
I don't have a sister.
Please wait.
Cathleen's dying of bone cancer.
She doesn't have much time.
She got what was coming to her.
Did she make you come here?
No. She has no idea
that I'm here.
Cathleen ceased to be my sister
the moment she went
after that man.
So now, good day to you.
[birds chirping]
[indistinct chattering]
So, what? She's got only
a few weeks left to live?
I just...
I don't know what to do.
Now, Miss Sweeney won't talk,
and Fiona won't listen.
So, I'm stuck.
Our latest post just reached
a million likes.
I forgave you.
You know, it reminds me
of that picture
we took in Paris
when we were 15.
- Yeah.
Hey Beckett, Taylor,
they're ready for you on set.
Thanks.
Look, Finley,
can we just talk later?
Yeah, of course, yeah.
Hey, look at all these
articles about us.
Beckett rushes back to Risdale.
R 'n R returns.
Beckett begs for Taylor
to come back, and she does.
This is very good for us.
[sighs]
Finley!
Finley, I called you
like a hundred times.
I'm trying to talk to you.
I'm busy. Running.
What? So, you just run away
when things get hard?
Not exactly a warrior.
I thought it wasn't safe for you
to be out here
- without a disguise.
- I'll be fine.
Hey! We need to talk.
- Please.
- About what?
You and Taylor hanging all over
each other on social media?
I told you it's not
what it looks like.
Okay, just trust me.
Are you and Taylor
together or not?
[car approaching]
[women giggling]
- Hey!
- Can we please have a picture?
Yeah. Yeah, yeah.
[cameras clicking]
- [girl] Thank you.
- [Beckett] All right.
- Did everybody get one?
- Bye, thank you, bye.
Thank you, guys, see ya.
Finley!
Finley. Finely.
I'm trying to work through
all of this, okay.
But this is bigger than just me.
My life isn't always my own.
I mean, my father,
he has an entire team of people
organizing my public life.
You just don't understand, okay.
I have no control.
It doesn't answer my question.
Are you and Taylor
together or not?
[dramatic music playing]
Our first film together
didn't do so well.
The studio was about to lose
a lot of money.
And then, my dad came up
with this brilliant idea
of a stormy relationship
between Taylor and I.
It started with a lot of truth.
But then...
my dad just started
making things up.
And before I knew it,
I had this whole other persona.
The worst part of it is,
it worked.
It saved the film.
So, it is all fake.
I can't be with a guy who has
this entire made-up life.
And I told you I can't do
anything about that right now.
I've always wanted to ask a girl
to a dance.
And this weekend,
there's
the St. Finian's festival.
And I would love it
if you would come with me.
In public?
Yeah.
No disguises?
No disguises needed,
although
I am pretty good at them.
But this time,
it would just be me and you.
Okay.
[Nora]
Here, let me get a picture.
- Okay.
- [laughter]
I'm good. Okay.
And... smile.
Emma!
[festival music playing]
[Seamus] ♪ When I woke up
As I was all alone ♪
[singers]
♪ Hey-yah, hey-yah, hey ♪
[Seamus] ♪ With a broken heart
And a ticket home ♪
Look, Emma and Orla.
[man] ♪ And I ask you now ♪
♪ Oh, what would you do ♪
Are you sure?
What are we doing standing here?
Let's go dance, come on.
Come on, let's dance.
♪ I've been
All over this world ♪
♪ Boys I ain't never seen
Nothin' like a Galway girl ♪
Okay.
[instrumental music playing]
[all cheering]
[Seamus] Now folks,
we're very fortunate
here tonight
to have with us
a lovely American girl
who's a very fine violin player.
But I have seen her develop
over the last few months
into becoming
a great Irish fiddler.
Finley, come up here
and give them
something to dance to.
Come on. Get up here.
[cheering]
Let's go for it.
Two, three, four.
Orla, come on.
What a surprise to see you here
without Taylor.
Yeah, you know,
I couldn't believe my luck
when Finley said yes.
She's pretty talented,
wouldn't you agree?
Yeah. Indeed.
Yeah, you know what.
You'll have to excuse me.
I'm going to ask this young lady
for a dance.
May I have this dance?
Yes, she says yes.
[violin music playing]
Come on.
[cheering]
Thank you, Seamus.
They can hear your heart now.
You better go back
to your fella.
I can see
he's getting a bit lonely.
- You wanna dance?
- Do you wanna dance?
Ma'am, can I have this dance?
Can I have this dance?
Wow, now that was
a different girl up there.
Well, thanks to
a certain Irish tour guide.
No, no,
thanks to an old Irish busker
who was the best teacher
she could ever ask for.
So, how
is your Irish prom going?
Perfect, but there's
one thing I haven't done yet.
What's that?
Kiss a beautiful fiddler
under a starry Irish night.
Well, too bad,
I played the violin.
Close enough.
[dramatic music playing]
[camera clicks]
[bell tolling in distance]
Um...
about four years ago
after my brother got back
he was helping
at this refugee center
in the Middle East
and, uh...
I guess he was just...
at the wrong place
at the wrong time.
Oh.
I'm so sorry.
Alex had this peace
about him though.
He was so alive.
I know it's probably
a stupid idea, but, uh...
I don't know, I thought
if I could come here
and see what he saw
I could find what he had.
Sorry
I didn't mean to drop all
of this on the dragon slayer.
Hey, I'd like to think
I'm a little bit
more than that by now.
Yeah, you are.
[dramatic music playing]
[suspenseful music playing]
Hey, you guys want to know
where Beckett Rush is staying?
Yeah, sure.
[indistinct chatter]
Oh, no!
- [man] That's him.
- [man] That's him. He's coming.
[reporters chattering]
[man] Beckett, who is this girl?
Beckett?
[indistinct chatter]
Is that your new girl?
- What does Taylor think of this?
- [Beckett] Get out of here.
Are you sure
you wouldn't like some tea?
With blackberry scones.
Or biscuits.
That's very kind of you,
but I think I lost my appetite.
Taylor Risdale is in my house.
Do you think maybe we
should give them some privacy?
Never!
I've got to see this.
[Beckett] It's ridiculous.
You'd think they'd have enough
pictures of me already. Right?
[Montgomery] This is a mess!
What the hell were you thinking?
What do you mean?
We just went out for a night.
What is so wrong with that?
I'm trying to save his career
before he pisses it away!
I'm trying to have a life
before you piss that away!
All right, I think
it's time to go to bed.
Long day.
Emma, Orla.
Tea is here if you want it.
Good night.
All right. This is how
I'm going to spin it, okay?
Beckett Rush crashes
a small Irish festival
or whatever the hell it is.
You have one too many drinks.
You make girls' dreams come true
by giving them kisses.
That'll keep you wild, kind,
and still with Taylor.
The fans will eat that up.
How can you do this to him?
That's not who he is!
And how long have you known him?
You need to be quiet,
and step away
from things
you know nothing about.
Beckett, she doesn't know you
the way that I do.
- He's just try...
- Finley.
That's enough, okay?
Son, you're the envy
of the world.
Why wouldn't you want that?
He just does this to please you.
Can't you see that?
He just wants
to have a normal life.
- Maybe go to college.
- Finley, just... just stop!
You know what,
maybe Taylor's right.
Maybe you're never
gonna understand!
You're just his puppet.
You don't even have the balls
to stand up
for who you really are.
Hey, don't worry. Okay.
She just can't understand
our life.
It's for the best.
Will you guys
just leave me alone right now?
[dramatic music playing]
I'm telling you,
I'm warning yous right now,
get out of here.
The lot of ya.
- Thanks so much, Nora.
- Well played, Nora.
I really wish
I didn't have to leave you guys.
But you're never gonna have
any peace
with me staying here, so.
We'll miss you.
But you know you can come back
and be my sous-chef anytime.
Oh, Sean, I got you something.
[Sean laughs]
No more burnt hands, huh!
I love them.
Thanks, buddy.
- Nora!
- Oh, sweetheart!
I'm gonna miss you, guys.
[indistinct chatter]
Beckett, let's take a walk.
I'm sorry, I'm working.
I don't care.
Come with me. Now.
Ciara, Shenae, Logan,
everyone down there,
everyone in post
and marketing in LA.
All these people
are your friends
who work on the movie,
they're here because of you.
They depend on you.
Your movies sell,
which provides
for their families.
If you're not gonna do this
for you or for me,
at least do it for them.
And Taylor.
You've grown up together.
You've been through a lot.
She's the only person
on this planet
who truly understands
what you've been through.
It's just not like you
to betray people.
[dramatic music playing]
I'm so sorry.
It's fine, no.
It's fine.
- It doesn't matter.
It's fine. It's fine.
[dramatic music playing]
[phone ringing]
- Hello!
- Finley, it's me, Seamus.
Oh, hey, what's up?
[Seamus]
Can you come down to the pub
as soon as you can, please?
Uh... Yeah, sure.
Hey, guys.
Ah, there you are, Finley.
So what's up?
Give him a chance.
Thank you, Seamus.
Hey!
Sorry about all that.
I just didn't think
you'd come if I called.
I've been thinking about you.
Your audition's next week.
Yeah.
Look, uh...
I'm sorry about the other night.
I screwed up.
Please, just give me
a little bit more time,
and I'll figure all this out.
If you wanna live
this double life,
I can't be a part of either one.
Look, it's harder
than it looks, okay.
I'm just trying to protect you.
I don't want you to
expose yourself to the media,
have your name dragged
through the mud like that?
- Do you want that?
- Yes.
If that's what it takes
to be real.
It's not just about me, okay!
I have a lot of people
depending on me,
and I don't wanna let them down.
Yeah.
You know, Taylor was right.
No.
I don't know what I was thinking
that this could work.
But we can, okay.
Come on.
We can.
You just gotta trust me.
I tried.
[dramatic music playing]
I mean,
you're probably the first girl
to ever break up
with Beckett Rush.
So why am I crying so much?
[violin music playing]
You see, Finley,
life rarely works out
the way we plan it.
You've got to learn to play
the sorrow as well as the joy.
They are linked,
like day and night.
You can't have one
without the other.
Give it a go.
Very good. Good.
Beautiful.
Beckett's told me
you broke it off.
Are you suffering?
- You saw him?
- Uh-hmm.
Make love, not war.
Love, Beckett.
Yeah.
My little troubles seem petty
compared to yours.
I asked you.
I want to know.
He's a good boy.
Yeah.
It's hard to change.
Mrs. Sweeney...
what really happened
between you and your sister
all those years ago?
I took my sister's fella.
No, don't give me that.
There has to be more to it.
People would tell ya otherwise.
Well...
being here in Ireland
has taught me to look deeper.
Things aren't always
as they seem.
My father was a gambler.
He'd bet on anything,
horses, politics...
the weather.
Eventually,
we were about to lose our house.
It would've killed my mother.
She... it had been in her family
for generations.
So, my father made a deal
with Mr. Sweeney
which had a very high price.
Our family name
meant something then.
Charles Sweeney had money,
but he had no social standing.
My little sister
didn't have many suitors.
So how did you end up
with Charles Sweeney?
When Charles Sweeney drank,
he got angry.
He was violent.
I had an eye for these things.
He was clever.
He left bruises
where you couldn't see.
So you took her place?
You were protecting her,
and she never knew.
She thought
I took him for the money.
My sister was blinded
with young love.
How did Charles Sweeney die?
People said I killed him.
Did you?
If wishes were bullets.
Why didn't you just start over?
When no one wants to hear,
it's better to hide
hide and be angry.
Well, didn't I wear my anger
like a grand fur coat!
It all was for nothing.
Wasted years!
In the end, it's a choice,
and I made the wrong one.
[dramatic music playing]
[thrilling music playing]
[thunder rumbles]
[dramatic music playing]
[phone vibrates]
- Hey.
- [Finely] Hey.
I need a favor.
So, you called me first?
[Finely] No.
I tried everyone else.
Last resort.
Okay, what's up?
Mrs. Sweeney
told me the whole story.
I have to get to Fiona's.
Where are...
Did you try riding up there
in this rain?
[Finely] Maybe.
Perfect day for a convertible.
All right,
I'll be there.
Hey, we really need
to talk to you.
It's important.
I have nothing to say to you.
She's just trying to help, okay.
Please, hear her out.
Thank you.
We just wanted to let you know
that Cathleen isn't expected
to live much longer.
We've talked about
the past some, her regrets.
How could you steal a man
away from your own sister?
She tried to explain herself
in the letters.
Did you ever even read them?
Why would I?
Miss Doyle, your sister
married Charles to protect you.
He was physically abusive.
How am I supposed
to believe all this?
Cathleen begged your father
to drop the arrangement.
But he was in too much debt,
and Charles was
too dangerous to cross.
It was so humiliating.
I'm really sorry about that.
But your sister
has been shunned for decades
for trying to help you,
and you won't even open
- the letters that she...
- Finley.
Look, Miss Doyle...
your sister's dying wish
is that she would
have your forgiveness.
Please, just...
come and see her.
I think you two
should be on your way now.
- Hey!
- [Taylor] Hey.
Come in.
What's up?
Nothing. How are ya?
Pretty tired.
Yeah.
So...
are you seriously thinking about
not signing that contract?
I don't know yet.
Beck.
look, we...
are in this together.
You and me,
we've... we're linked.
Always have been.
What you do impacts me.
Please don't do this.
After everything
we've been through.
We need this.
Yeah.
So, what are we supposed to do?
Just sacrifice our whole lives?
I don't know. It doesn't make
any sense to me.
So few understand
this life that we made.
Does she really know you
the way I do?
Think about it.
I'll be in my room,
if you wanna talk.
Hey, Tay.
Yeah?
Would you ride your bike
in the pouring rain
just to help an old lady?
Of course.
But I wouldn't need to.
Just hire a driver.
[Finely] I leave
for New York tomorrow.
It's crazy to think
that this one audition
is gonna decide
the direction of my life.
Yeah.
If you'd got
in the first time...
you wouldn't be bugging me now.
Yeah.
I guess that's true.
I'm glad you botched it.
Mrs. Sweeney,
I'm so sorry...
that I couldn't get
your sister to come.
I really tried.
I did everything that I could,
but she just...
she wouldn't listen.
I trust you did.
With everything that you did
for your father and your sister,
you are the bravest person
I've ever met.
You obviously
haven't met many people.
Just shut up.
You wouldn't have said that
a few months ago.
Yeah, well...
I guess Ireland
is just full of surprises.
Fact.
Bye, sweetheart.
Wind in your sails.
[dramatic music playing]
Can I have a word?
I'm not signing that contract.
Here's the deal.
I'll do one more film
in the next six months.
And I don't care
how much money I make.
I'm not doing this for me
or for you.
I'm doing this
for the cast and crew
so they can prepare for life
after Steele Markov.
That's my offer.
Take it or leave it.
As your manager...
I have to warn you that this is
the most asinine thing
you've ever done.
I don't need a manager
right now.
I need a father.
[violin playing]
So you think it's good enough?
You are ready for your audition.
Thank you, Seamus,
for everything.
Now go and make them
stuck up music professors
tap their feet.
I will.
[delightful music playing]
That's okay, I'll get it.
Emma, you take that.
Here's some soda bread
to bring to your mom.
We would have made more,
but we've been so busy.
Nonstop calls from people
wanting to stay
in Beckett's room.
Imagine that.
[phone ringing]
Hello!
Oh, hey. What's up?
Did her sister ever come?
So she's all alone?
[sentimental music playing]
I have to go back.
Did you forget something?
What's wrong?
I need to be somewhere else.
Are you sure, Finley?
Yeah.
[dramatic music playing]
Am I too late?
No. You're just in time.
Cathleen, your sister's here.
Cath.
Fi.
Oh, my God, Fiona.
We're old.
Yeah.
Where's...?
Finley, come and sit with us.
Fi.
We're okay now.
[dramatic music playing]
Oh, my!
[delightful music playing]
[dramatic music playing]
So, you're back in town.
Still driving this
ridiculous convertible, I see.
Yeah, I'm all ready
for the next sunny day...
in two months.
I went to that cemetery.
I told you I'd find it.
Thank you, Beckett.
Sorry it took me so long.
I had to search everyone
within a hundred miles of here.
I guess I was wrong.
Maybe I can trust you.
Well, you still look gorgeous
when you admit
that you're wrong.
So, what did you find?
Well, four years ago,
my brother drew this picture
for this moment
when I needed it most.
I couldn't see it then, but...
I was never alone.
Well, sometimes things
aren't always as they seem.
So...
I didn't sign the contract.
What?
I'm going to do one more movie
just to help everybody out,
but then next fall,
I'm going to college.
Well, girls' hearts will be
shattered all over the world.
Well, there's only one girl's
heart that I care about.
No more double-life either.
Tomorrow, a story's going to hit
social media,
telling the world
that Taylor and I are done.
Finally!
I'm happy about it
because there's a fair warrior
I wanna try and win back.
[uplifting music playing]
[Finley]
I finished the last few weeks
of my exchange program
and went home.
[woman] Where is it?
[Finely] I told the conservatory
about Mrs. Sweeney,
and they allowed me to
audition after the deadline,
one final time.
[upbeat music playing]
[Finely]
I was accepted.
Beckett visited.
And of course, we crashed
my old high school's prom.
[upbeat music playing]
[Finely] That summer,
I went back to Ireland
And helped Beckett
with his lines
on his last Dragon film.
Beckett began college
in New York.
He's trying
to be a normal guy,
but he still needs
his disguises.
And, in autumn,
at the conservatory,
I played the violin.
Or fiddle,
as Seamus would say.
[upbeat music playing]
[dramatic music playing]
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
[acoustic music playing]
[upbeat music playing]