[ Silence ]
You're so cute.
[Laughter]
What... what are
you looking at?
Look, you have a tail.
[Laughter] Look at your sister.
We're doing some...
Putting me in some skit or...
Oh my God.
I can't believe you have this.
[Laughter]
[ Pause ]
[ Laughter ]
Look, it's like
sucking on... what is...
[Laughter] My mom always tells
us a story where he was trying
to breastfeed me and she was...
Who was?
My dad.
And she walked in on him
and he's just sitting there
with like me, you
know, and his shirt up.
And she goes, "What
are you doing?"
And he goes, "I just...
I just want to see how
it feels," you know.
That's really good.
Yeah. Well, like he
just loves kids, you know.
He's... look at him.
I wish your dad can meet my dad.
Yeah. I wish I
could meet him.
[ Pause ]
[ Music ]
[ Noise ]
Linas, Linas, have
you seen my hard drive?
[Inaudible Remark] No,
no, no, the small one.
You know, the small one,
looks like about this big.
Yeah. It should
be right over there.
You find it there?
No.
Oh, sorry.
No, no, I got it.
Okay. Sorry.
No problem
[ Pause ]
[Shouting]
Okay.
Yeah! Party!
If we don't have any,
we don't have anymore.
A party toast?
Yeah. It's just for...
Do you want me to get more
of the people getting ready
or should I go out and
set up for the ceremony?
You know, you can do
that for the ceremony.
I'm sure it will be...
Okay.
Whatever you want.
All right.
It doesn't...
Whatever you want.
[ Inaudible Discussion ]
She's like an angel.
[Inaudible Remark]
[ Inaudible Discussion ]
Hi!
Hi! Like the wedding?
Uh-hmm.
What do you like about it?
Um, I don't know.
Do you think you'll
get married someday?
No? You don't want
to fall in love
with a girl when you are older?
What do you want to
do when you're older?
I don't know.
Do you want to say goodbye now?
Uh-hmm.
Okay, man, thanks
for talking to me.
High five.
We don't know.
He's [inaudible].
[ Inaudible Discussion ]
Hey, Linas.
I hope you get this
before you come in.
Now Terry [phonetic]
and I are going
to have a little date
night tonight and...
So that's where you
could just kind
of be a little bit
quiet if you come in.
And also, you know, we look...
Just love having you there and,
you know, we love
supporting you.
And we were just hoping if
you could just, you know,
clean up the dishes
maybe once in a while
or take the trash out,
that would be great.
[ Noise ]
So, what are you wearing?
I'm not going to tell you.
Come on, what are you wearing?
[ Pause ]
I'm naked.
Whoa, really?
I wish you were here.
Yeah. I have to go to bed.
Okay. I'll talk to you soon.
Okay. Goodnight.
Bye. Georgia?
[ Pause ]
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Excuse me.
Sorry.
[ Noise ]
[ Pause ]
You may now kiss your bride.
[ Applause & Cheering ]
[ Noise ]
Dude. [Inaudible Remark]
Hey. So, Terry
and I were talking
and we thought it would
be good if you move out.
Oh. Sure, yeah.
Yeah, I'm sorry, okay.
Are you okay?
I mean, thanks for
letting me stay so long.
I'm...
Sure. Sure.
Yeah, sorry I
have brought it up.
No, no, no.
It's fine.
And we're going out
of town this weekend.
Oh, cool.
Yeah. So, she'd give you
'til like Monday or Tuesday...
Okay.
To get your stuff
together and you know.
Yeah. Yeah.
No, thanks.
That's awesome.
Yeah.
Okay, no problem.
[ Noise ]
Hey, check it out.
I'm using the cutting board.
It sounds kind of like
you're making marks in it.
Okay. Here.
Can you hear anything?
Completely silent.
You don't hear anything,
there are no marks.
You don't even need a
cutting board, okay?
You don't even need
a hard surface.
I could just do it like that.
I can do it while
I drive, right?
That is really great.
You like it?
I can do... to make a little
video and put it on YouTube.
I did. That is
so... I already have.
I've got millions of subscribers
and people are throwing
away their cutting boards
and they're finally
free, all of it.
I'm going to go.
See you later.
Okay. But what time
[inaudible] later?
Six probably or 6:30.
Okay.
Bye.
[Noise]
Yeah, baby.
Right, right.
Jesus Christ.
You're kidding me.
As it should be.
Yes. Cheers.
Cheers.
Read them and weep.
[Laughter]
Do you have any tools?
No, goldfish.
Oh, I just got to do.
Oh. I just got to do.
This is such a hard game.
I love you.
I want to be with you.
Okay.
You are with me.
Look, I know you need
some time, you know,
and I know you're going through
a really hard time, you know.
I just... can you please
just tell me when?
I don't want to pressure
you but it's
like I don't know
how long I could be...
[ Pause ]
I don't know.
Excuse me.
No!
Can I help you?
Dude!
What the... get!
Get!
Dude!
This is crazy!
What are you doing?
Get the fuck...
[ Music ]
[Background Music] Wait.
Honey!
Hey. So, good seeing you.
I just I want to say sorry.
I didn't mean to get all
heavy and stuff, okay?
Anyway, I hope to see you soon
and you have a goodnight
and, okay, take care.
Bye.
[ Noise ]
Hey.
Hello.
Check it out.
Oh. [Inaudible Remark]
Hey, would you
mind not doing that.
Okay.
I need some help with
these bags over here, okay?
Sure.
Thanks.
It's all right.
[ Noise ]
This is a daily job.
Yeah [inaudible].
You get the poop
up out of the grass.
Usually they poop
in clump areas.
So, where the grass
looks really green,
you can find poop usually.
Just put the shovel
right close to the poop.
Okay.
And click it in with the rake.
That's basically
what the job is.
Okay.
You go around the pasture
and look for the green spots
and you'll find poop there.
[ Noise ]
I hope this is okay for you.
It's all we got right now.
Yeah, yeah.
This will work, you know.
I got Matt and, yeah.
Thanks.
Okay.
Yeah.
See you later.
Okay. Hey, it's me.
It'd be really great if you
could just call me back and,
you know, I'd really
like to talk to you.
[ Pause ]
Okay, the feed is in here
and you have to make sure
when you take feed out that you
put the covers back on and...
Okay.
And shut them down tight
'cause if an animal gets
in the barn and they
get into the feed,
they'll eat 'til they die.
Yeah.
So we just make super sure
that doors are shut,
the covers are on.
They don't know that
it's... like they're full?
No, they love these things.
And they just eat until they
make themselves, you know, sick,
until they die, a kind
of a miserable experience
for all of us.
Most of all for them, I'm sure.
Okay. And so, we'll
keep this on tight then.
Yup.
All right.
[ Noise ]
Weird bus.
[Laughter]
[ Noise ]
Hi. Hi.
[ Pause ]
Yeah. Hey, careful,
careful, careful.
Come on. Okay, you had enough.
You had enough.
Go on.
[ Pause ]
No more food.
Do you still like me or do
you only like me for my food?
Tell me, you can have some,
just tell me you love me.
Come on. Tell me,
tell me you love me.
That's all and then
you can have it.
No. First, tell me
that you love me.
[ Noise ]
This one looks healthy,
this baby.
It does now.
This one, we were fearful of
for a while 'cause we noticed
that the mother and the
baby weren't really bonding.
The baby was running
around trying to figure
out who his mother was and his
mother wasn't interested in it.
And I think these animals know
if there's something wrong
with their baby, they just know,
and they don't waste
any time on them.
Because even when we fed the
baby, it wasn't being nourished.
Sometimes it helps to step
in but some of the time,
no matter how much you step
in, the female is not going
to respond 'cause
they know something
or they sense something.
You know, there's
something going on there
and I've learned
to trust them more.
[ Noise ]
[ Music ]
[Background Music] You
said this runs, right?
Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah, it ran pretty well
when we drove it in here.
[ Music ]
[ Birds Chirping & Noise ]
[ Noise & Music ]
Phillips Electric,
John speaking.
Why, hello there.
I was wondering, could
you come and fix my TV?
This is Phillips Electric,
we do electrical
housework, we don't fix TVs.
But my show is almost on.
[Inaudible Remark]
I'm sorry, I have to go.
You'll have to call somebody
else that repairs TVs.
Wait, wait don't go.
It's your son actually
Lin [phonetic].
I'll fix your fucking TV
for you, a kick in the nuts.
I'm sorry, I couldn't resist.
Are you busy?
I'm cleaning my
truck up a little bit.
Yeah. But, well, how you been?
Good. I just... do
you have a second?
Yeah.
Yeah, I just had some
news I wanted to tell you.
I'm actually, I'm
moving back, back east.
That's great.
Where are you moving back to?
In New York?
Yeah, I want to get back to
New York but I was wondering
if it's okay if I
could stay with you
and mom for a little while?
I think that would be all right.
Yeah, I know that's always
been... you're always welcome.
I would like to have you.
I'd like to see you, all right?
Cool. Also, I
have this, this...
I don't know if you
got my message
about this girl I've
been seeing.
That's all right.
Yeah. And do you
think she could stay
with us for a little bit?
Yeah. I think that
will be all right.
It's nice that you have company.
[Knocking]
[ Noise ]
Hello?
Hey! Hi.
I'm sorry, are you alone?
Yeah. Hi.
Hi, [inaudible].
I'm sorry.
Yeah. No, it's okay.
Things have been
really bad for you.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
I was worried about you.
Yeah, I'm fine.
It's good to see you.
Oh, I just... I wanted
to tell you something.
I've got to move back to Boston
with my parents for a while.
You know, just going to
sort things out, I guess.
When are you going?
Maybe tonight.
I... this guy gave me a van
and so I'm going to drive.
Cool. Good luck.
Yeah.
I hope you have a great trip.
Yeah. I wanted to ask you
though, I know this seems crazy
but I wanted to see if
you would come with me.
[Inaudible] I can't, you know.
It could be so great.
I have to go.
Okay, I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Can I call you later?
I mean, we can talk about it.
I don't know.
I really need to go.
Okay.
All right, I'm sorry.
I'll talk to you later.
Okay, bye.
Bye.
[ Noise ]
[ Music ]
Are you serious?
Just want to get a room.
Just a second.
Why did you say that?
I miss you.
Okay.
I have.
No, I haven't.
I just want to check in.
Are we off this again?
I said, I love, I said I...
[ Noise ]
And this is for how many adults?
Just me.
Yeah, for you.
Okay.
[ Noise ]
[ Music ]
Go around!
[ Noise ]
[ Pause ]
[ Music ]
Hey mom, look at that van.
[Laughs] It looks kind of goofy.
Hey, you be nice.
Sorry, sir.
[ Music ]
Okay, your room is through
the double doors, up the stairs,
and stay to your left.
[ Music ]
Hello.
[ Noise ]
Jesus Christ.
[ Music ]
[ Noise]
Hey.
Hey, how's my son doing?
Good, yeah.
Yeah, where are you... where
are you at now in your travels?
Montana, I think or wait, no
actually, I think we just coming
to Wisconsin, I mean Wyoming.
Wyoming?
That's a good stop... state.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Wait.
What's her name?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Your mother wants to know what
your girlfriend's name is.
It would be nice to call her
something other than, hey you.
Georgia.
It's, Georgia [inaudible].
Yeah.
Yeah. You know,
out in Wyoming there,
how's the countryside?
You seen any wild animals,
any Indians around?
You know does and
bucks, you know,
you learning any new positions?
[Laughs]
Okay, all right.
Well, I should get going
near though dad, okay?
All right.
Well, I wasn't trying
to get nasty.
I was just trying to make
some conversation but anyways,
look forward to seeing you
in a few days and we miss you
and we love you very much.
Okay.
Bye.
All right, bye.
[ Noise ]
Hey, it's me.
I guess I understand if you
need some space or whatever.
Just, it'll be good to
talk to you, you know.
So, yeah, just give me a call
when you get a chance, okay?
Bye.
[ Noise ]
Get a load of this.
I haven't seen anything
so sweet in my life.
Does it do good on gas mileage?
Like, itty-bitty,
lightweight car.
Yeah, all right, it's good.
All right, good.
[ Noise ]
Geez.
Oh man, I'm fucking... fuck.
[ Noise ]
[Background Music] Who
knows that we're even made,
wired that way, I don't know.
I mean I don't want to just
be like some guy who's saying,
we're not made to be with
one person, you know,
but I don't know, it's
a case to think about.
It is. It's very
interesting to think about it.
I mean, not a lot of
animals are monogamous
and we are technically mammals,
you know, animals so, it's hard.
So, I guess I'm still trying
to see if it's worth it.
Commitment is a scary thing.
I've never done it
before like this long
so I'm a little nervous.
And wait, what sign are you?
Oh, I'm a Gemini so
totally dual personality most
of the time like I'm
either a really nice person
or I'm really mean.
Oh, like what does that mean?
Oh, I would never
hit anybody or anything.
I'm not a violent person or
smack somebody now and then,
you know, a little
backhanded action.
But never like in the
face or, you know,
to leave a mark or anything.
So, you would never
hit me in the face?
I...
See, I was hoping this would
go somewhere but now I'm not
so sure 'cause I don't
want you to beat me up,
you know, just 'cause I...
Beat you up?
Look at these hands.
You know...
They couldn't beat anybody up.
I mean, if I punch
somebody with them,
I'm going to break
my own knuckles.
That's... yeah, that's
true, they are very small.
You know, I mean, look at them.
They're nice.
They're just tiny little hands.
Yeah, that was... I
guess that would be stupid.
You would just break your...
Hi there.
Hi, how's it going?
Who's the [inaudible]?
I'm Linas.
Hey.
Want to go out of here?
Sure.
Good talking to you.
Nice to meet you.
Yeah, sure.
See you.
[ Music ]
[ Noise ]
Hey pal.
Oh hey, what's up?
Pretty nice, pretty
nice van you got.
Yeah. [Inaudible
Remark] It's okay.
Where you coming in from?
Smoke doesn't bother
you, does it?
No.
So, did you have a good
time talking to Angie?
Okay, I got to get going, man.
No, hold on, hold on.
What you guys talk about?
Look, I'm sorry we were
just talking, you know.
Did she talk about me?
Yes.
What you think about that?
She was just talking
to me, you know.
You're fucking pathetic, man.
Dude, I'm just...
I was just talking.
You're wasting my fucking time.
That's what you are.
Fucking pathetic.
[ Pause ]
[Knocking]
Can I get in?
Can I come in?
What?
Can you open the door?
[ Noise ]
What?
Hi. Can I come inside?
Uhm.
Is that all right?
What?
If I come in and sit down?
I'll just stay in
the front seat.
Oh, yeah.
I just, I just woke
up though but...
Thanks man.
Oh, Goddamn, Jesus Christ.
Oh, Lord have mercy.
This is good.
[ Noise ]
I'm just going to sit
here for a second.
[ Pause ]
You okay?
Oh, yeah, man.
This is great.
[ Noise ]
Okay. I'm going to
get going here, so...
All right.
Do you want to
ride somewhere or?
Yeah.
Okay. I don't
really know the town
so you're going to
have to show me.
I'll just go wherever
you want to go.
Okay, well I'm...
How about I just...
I'll take you for a little
ride and you can get out
or whatever or, you
know, take it from there.
Yeah.
Okay.
All right.
You drink coffee?
Nope.
Well, I'm going to
get some coffee, okay?
All right.
[ Noise ]
I'm going to just
get some coffee here.
[ Noise ]
Do you want to come in?
No, that's all right.
I'll stay here.
Okay, all right.
I'll be right back.
Okay.
[ Pause ]
[ Music ]
Hey, could you pull over?
Why?
I want to see something.
Could you pull over?
Yeah, right over here is good.
Okay, I don't know if this
is a good place to stop, man.
This is fine.
Right here on the
shoulder is good.
[ Music ]
Are you coming back?
Yeah, I'll be back.
[ Music ]
Do you see that,
inside the buckle?
Barn.
No, the little one.
At the top right there?
[Inaudible Remark] Uh-huh.
Starting to lean in.
[ Music ]
[Background Music]
Yeah, let's go.
Hey, how are you doing?
Are you okay?
What's going on?
What's wrong?
Sandy, I can't,
I can't really talk
about that right now.
I'm going to be there
in 48 hours.
Yeah, I'll be there.
Why do you... why do you?
No, no, no, no, no.
Wait a second.
Don't hang up.
No, you... just, could
you stop yelling at me?
No, I... I went down
there and visited him.
It doesn't mean I'm
going to trust him
with my daughter's life.
No, he doesn't have... no,
he doesn't have a key.
Okay, look, okay.
Yeah, but you need to
stop hollering at me.
Listen, I've slept
about three hours
in the last five days, okay?
Don't hang up.
Listen. Okay.
I... okay. Just wait before
you do that, all right?
Wait before you do that.
I don't care.
That's okay, fine.
I can't... I can't talk.
Okay.
[ Pause ]
What's up?
Oh, I just saw a barn over here.
Look kind of cool.
I don't know, do you
want to check it out?
Yeah.
[ Noise ]
What's your name?
Jim. What's yours?
Linas.
What's your name?
Linas. It's Lithuanian.
Nice to meet you.
Yeah.
[ Noise ]
Are you okay?
Hey dude, he's alive?
[Inaudible Remark]
Okay, he's alive.
Can you feel that?
Careful.
He's got a... he's just
bleeding from his arm.
Listen, Linas, I'm
going to go and try
to get some help, all right?
So, you just stay here and
talk to him and hold pressure
on the arm, all right?
I don't know how to do that.
What?
You just... all you got to do
is just hold it, not too tight
and just don't let it...
Try... don't let it... just.
I've never done that.
Okay, just hold on to it
and try not to let it bleed.
You can stop it by putting
your hand on it, okay?
And talk to him, all right?
So, he doesn't like pass out.
What should I say?
I don't know, man.
Okay.
All right.
Hurry. Okay.
I'm just going to
hold here, okay?
I don't have [inaudible].
My friend is just going
to... he's getting help.
He'll be back soon.
Okay.
All right, man.
Just relax.
Here, relax, relax.
It's going to be all right.
Okay.
All right
[ Pause ]
[ Noise ]
Look.
[ Pause ]
Yeah, I've tried to change
it but I couldn't change it.
Yeah, I'll be... I'll be there
at Thursday morning at JFK.
Sorry about that.
I'm still at the farm.
He's doing okay.
I think he's going
to be all right.
Okay, so I'll see you Thursday.
Okay, bye.
Was that your girlfriend again?
Not girlfriend, wife.
Two different people.
Well, what was
she mad about before?
It was something
about our daughter,
something that happened last
week when it was my week.
So, are you coming back to
New York for good or what?
Yeah, maybe.
Is the toilet broken or?
No, I don't think so.
[Background Music]
Are you ready?
Yeah.
So, do you have a boyfriend?
No, I don't.
Do you have a girlfriend?
No. Do I look like
I have a girlfriend?
You never know.
Hey, hey, what's happening?
What is up, Linas?
Hello, my name is Jim.
Hi.
This is for you, cheers.
Thanks, you don't have
to drink it, you know.
What's your name?
Kate.
Kate, nice to meet you.
You too.
Fabulous.
She's an ex-gymnast.
Yes.
Oh, that's cool.
Yeah. Oh, yeah, you
look like a gymnast.
You look like a gymnast.
That is super fabulous girl.
I'm staying up this
motel down the street.
Actually.
Oh really?
Yeah, we got two beds
and kind of a guest house.
Yeah.
Yes.
Yeah. If you feel, you
could totally crash with us,
man, if you feel like it.
You know, it'd be totally fine.
We're good.
Just right down the street?
Yeah, right down
the south side of town.
Yeah.
Good to know.
Okay.
Jim.
What? I love gymnastics.
Do you know each other really?
I'm just going to step
outside for, I don't know.
Let's step outside.
What's up man?
Okay.
Is he okay?
I guess.
Let me see.
Linas, what's going on?
What's going on?
I don't know.
What's the problem?
You just come over and you're
like, oh you look fabulous.
I mean come on.
She did look fabulous.
What's wrong?
Yeah, but it was a little
inappropriate, you know,
I thought I was kind of
getting somewhere with her.
Oh.
I'm so...
Linas, that's fine.
She was going to come... she
wanted to come and stay with us.
She... come on.
She's not going to
come to the motel room
when you say come
with us together.
It's fine.
What are you doing?
[ Noise ]
She was stupid anyway.
She wasn't stupid.
She's so...
She's not stupid.
So, look at her.
She wasn't stupid.
[Laughter]
[ Music ]
Oh shit.
[ Music & Laughter ]
[Background Music] Look.
[ Music ]
Hey.
How are you doing?
Good, good.
I just got up.
Really?
God bless you.
You can stay here all you want.
I have to go.
Where are you,
where are you going?
I'm going to Chicago.
I got to catch a plane.
Okay. Well, I could take you.
I got to get going.
I really have to get there.
Yeah, but I'm going that way.
I don't think, I don't
think that bus could...
We have to leave right now.
Do you feel like going?
[ Laughter ]
[ Noise ]
Jesus.
Would we want to go
straight there or like...
I have a few goals.
You want to camp
out on the Shorty?
Just pull over or something.
You know, there's
room back here.
Okay, if he wants...
Sleep a little.
All right.
I'll probably go in.
I like it up here.
This is good.
How are you going
to sleep there?
I don't... I'm probably
not going to sleep.
[ Pause ]
You want some of this?
[ Coughing ]
Oh no. Do you
want some of this?
You got one.
[ Coughing ]
So you guys aren't
happily married then?
No. [Noise]
Why don't you get a divorce or?
We're already sort of separated.
We don't live together.
We have a daughter.
I have her half the time.
She has her half the time.
And I have a girlfriend
but my daughter doesn't
know about my girlfriend.
Really?
Nor does my wife.
Then why don't you just get a
divorce if you're not together?
In most cases, I think
that would be the right thing
to do but not in this case.
Do you smell that?
Minty?
Yeah. That's a
field of peppermint.
[ Pause ]
When was the last
time you slept?
I think the last time I was
asleep was for about a minute
when I first got into this car.
[Laughter] But somebody
kept talking and woke me up.
And that was the last
time I had some sleep.
Do you think your girlfriend
is thinking about you?
[ Pause ]
Maybe not thinking about
me but I think she's thinking
of a way the... she
thinks we're...
Has a lot do with
me, being with me.
And if we weren't together,
we have a different
kind of thinking.
[ Pause ]
That's pretty good.
Well, I'm probably not as
pretty as she is but so... what?
[Laughter] All right.
I'm going to get
some sleep, dude.
All right.
Just feel free.
[ Pause ]
[ Music ]
Shit.
We should be [inaudible].
Fuck.
Yeah.
It feels so good.
I guess.
[ Music ]
[Background Music]
This is good.
Yeah, this is great.
Hey, bag.
I get it.
All right.
[ Music ]
[Background Music]
See you later.
Yeah.
Thanks a lot.
Yeah, bye.
You come to New
York, I'm buying.
[ Music ]
[ Noise ]
Good afternoon,
how are you doing?
Hey.
Good, do you have a reservation?
No.
Checking in?
Yeah.
What kind of room
are you looking for?
It's just me so...
It's just you, all right.
[ Noise ]
Shit.
No [inaudible].
[ Noise ]
What a fucking [inaudible].
[Background Music] Fucking!
[ Music ]
[Background Music] Yeah here!
Here! Here!
Yeah!
[ Music ]
Hi, I just ran out of gas
down the street,
just a little bit.
Can I just get like
five bucks worth of gas
like in a gas can, you know?
And if I could... oh,
I'm sorry, are you deaf?
No English.
Okay, it's not a problem.
My car, it ran out
of gas down the road.
Oh.
I just need a little bit
of gas in a container, okay?
And like, you know, one
of those, I don't know,
you call it like a container
like a, you know, like a jug.
Jug, jug, jog?
No, like... for gas.
Hello. Hey listen,
let me call you back.
I got a customer here.
I'll call you right back.
Okay, bye.
So, what did you say
five bucks worth?
Yeah, yeah.
In a gas can.
Yeah.
Good.
That would be good.
Good, good.
So, that would be
great if I could just
like borrow the, you know.
Sure, sure.
Borrow the can.
I'm coming this way
so I'll just...
Good, good, just drop it off.
Yeah.
Hey, but do you do impressions
or can you do an
impression for me?
Like, right now?
Yeah.
Okay, like, like what?
Anything? I guess I can do...
Oh, I guess I can do
Christopher Walken, you know.
It's kind of stupid.
Everyone does him but,
you know, if he was...
I used to do this thing
if he was Lithuanian.
Okay.
[ Foreign Language ]
It's good.
That's basically it.
I don't.
No, it's good.
Good work.
Okay.
Nice job.
Thanks.
[ Noise ]
Hey.
You drive this?
Yeah. [Laughter]
[ Pause ]
[ Music ]
Hello.
Hey dad, how are you doing?
Hi son, how are you?
Yeah, okay, you
know, I'm on the road.
You know, sorry I
didn't check in.
No problem.
You know, there's been a
little bit of change of plans.
What's that mean?
Well, you know I told you
I was coming with this friend,
this girl Georgia but anyway,
that's kind of changed now.
Oh, I'm sorry.
What happened?
Well, you know, it's
kind of a little complicated
so maybe I'll just
tell you later.
Well, are you still coming?
Yeah, I'm still coming.
And if it's okay
I'd like to be able
to stay there for
a little while.
Yeah. And how long
are you going to stay?
I don't know, dad.
You have any kind of game plan?
I don't, I don't know, dad.
I don't know.
Okay.
Well, it'd be nice
to know more details.
I'm sorry.
Let me just call you back, okay?
All right, call me right back.
Okay, okay.
All right.
Bye-bye.
Oh, your girlfriend?
No.
Got a lot of girlfriends?
Not really.
Oh, that's smart, a
handsome guy like you.
What? Do you prefer
jerking off or something?
Is that it?
I'm fucking with you.
Hey, there's a
picture of you, huh?
The little one?
No, that's my son.
The little one is my boy.
How many kids do you have?
That's sort of a
personal question.
That doesn't sound
like a personal question
but it's actually...
Oh, sorry.
'Cause this picture is cool.
Oh yeah, that's Ali.
For a while I was volunteering
at this hospital for, you know,
babies with medical problems.
And there weren't
that many nurses.
The babies were, you know,
all sitting in front of the TV
so I'd come in, I'd
get their toys.
I'd play with them.
Tickle them, you know,
it's really, it was fun.
And Ali is?
Well, he was there.
There were other...
There were older kids.
He was the oldest one there
and so we became friends,
and we just hang out and talk.
How old is he now?
He died, Ali.
He...
Geez.
Yeah.
So, you volunteered there, huh?
Yeah, yeah.
Why did you... how
did that come about?
Why did you do that?
'Cause I lost my daughter, so.
I'm sorry.
That's okay, you
know, I mean I'm okay.
I mean I think about her all...
Well, I wouldn't call it
thinking, I just feel pain,
you know, about it all the time.
But, you know, you know
people say, "Are you okay?"
And I am, you know, okay.
I'm okay for the most part.
I agree with that.
There's a low level,
gnawing agony, you know,
the sort of stunted
thing, you know, you can't.
I don't know.
It's like there's a thousand
little knives just stuck
in your gut and they just
stay there, you know,
'til something distracts
you, you know, a job,
a pretty girl comes along
or a thought, you know,
something pulls you out of
it but, you know, it's...
The pain is just there, you
know, it doesn't change.
It doesn't transform.
It doesn't get less.
It just sits there.
[ Pause ]
You want a beer?
[ Applause ]
And how long did
he live after this?
That's the amazing thing
'cause literally the next day,
the nurse was feeding him.
She walked out, came
back, he was dead.
So this is like 12
hours, maybe 12,
20 hours before he
died, this footage.
Wow.
So, I was just thankful for,
well, the [inaudible] I have,
you know, think you
would kiss like that?
Well, that's it.
I just want to say thank you.
[Applause]
So do you volunteer
there anymore?
I don't.
How come?
I don't know.
Is it because of Ali?
No man, no.
Ali, I mean it's 'cause of him
that I would go back,
you know what I mean?
You know, I think more
like just lazy, you know,
maybe, something like that.
I don't know.
People you don't really know
about, some people I know...
Maybe you should.
Yeah, maybe.
[ Applause ]
Hey! Hey!
Wake up! Up!
Yo! Hey, you want
to go for a ride?
I really should get going.
Come on man.
Come on, really.
I really want to
show you something.
Come on. Let's go.
Yikes, that's the things I like.
Careful.
Help me but wait a second.
[Laughter] Hello
to the nutty guy.
Hello. He's so cool.
Look at him.
Do you know what's
wrong with him?
I don't know.
I bought him.
What's wrong with you big boy?
Come on and tell me.
Hey you.
[ Pause ]
They really need this.
Yeah, they do.
Who doesn't?
[ Pause ]
[ Music ]
[Inaudible] you know.
Please.
No, no, no, no.
No, I said no.
Come on, let's go.
Please.
Whoa, easy, easy.
Please, let's go.
No, okay.
No, I said no.
Come on.
No, no, no, no.
[Multiple Speakers]
Please.
Is he okay?
Come on!
No. [Inaudible Remark]
Don't use that tone
of voice with me, okay?
Fine!
Let's go.
I have to use the bathroom.
You guys have a bathroom?
Bathroom?
Yeah.
All right.
I'm going to wait
for you outside.
Uh-hmm.
[Inaudible Remark]
Excuse me do you
have like [inaudible],
a road that go like
east like 94.
Yeah, 94 it is.
Yeah, but that
smaller, you know,
like a smaller road,
like a frontage road.
Boy! Wait!
Wait!
Whoa.
Hey. Wait.
Hey!
Oh, hey!
No, no, no!
Hey!
Hold on a second.
Wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait.
Hey, hey, I'm sorry, I
was about to pay for that.
Yeah. Nobody pay for this.
No, no, I know but I was...
He steal from store.
No, I was about to pay for it.
You don't pay here.
You pay inside.
I know.
He just ran out.
He's stealing from store.
He thought I already
paid for it.
Yes.
So how much is it?
85 cents.
I'm sorry.
I hope you don't mind.
You don't pay here.
You pay inside, yeah?
I'm sorry.
Next time you pay inside,
okay, or I call police.
Yeah.
Yeah?
Sorry. Say, thank you.
Thank you sir.
Yeah.
The name's Alex.
Hi, Linas.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, hi.
Hi.
Linas. [Laughter]
Melinda.
Hi.
The hell.
It's just around
the corner there.
Yeah, it's just
around the corner.
Then further...
Well, I don't
want to impose ma'am.
No, not at all, hello.
Are you a vegetarian?
No.
We also have some chicken.
Yeah, Peter loves,
loves company.
[ Pause ]
Do you like the eggplant, Linas?
Yeah, it's great.
It's great.
Thank you so much.
My wife grows that eggplant.
Yeah?
Yeah.
It's great.
Yeah. Eggplant
is not really meant
to be grown in these parts.
Oh really?
So you grow, you
grow and sell this?
Incredible business
actually with the corn,
artichokes, scallions, tomatoes.
And so, basically,
able to like put food
on the table 'cause
Peter's having problems.
What do you do
for a living, Linas?
Good question.
I don't know.
I used to take care of
kids but I've been trying
to make films and stuff, so.
Do you have anything
to fall back on in case
that doesn't work out?
I've been doing weddings.
So, you're an aspiring artist?
I guess.
Very admirable.
Well, that's a tough
racket, film making,
it's a hard business to
break into, I would imagine.
So if you, you're passing
through or you want to keep if,
you know, I mean, you're
more than welcome to stay.
But if you have a schedule
to keep, I don't want to...
No, yeah, just.
Yeah, I should get going, yeah.
We recommend the couch.
Uh-hmm.
Yup.
I don't want to impose.
Alex and I made
the couch already.
Maybe he has a schedule and...
Oh, right, maybe he has a...
I have to work in the morning.
You can work in the morning?
Yeah, we really
don't want to keep you.
You know, if you don't want to
stay, you don't have to stay.
Yeah. It's getting pretty
late maybe I should get going.
No, no.
Well, don't you want to
play figures with me?
[Laughter]
It's me and the cow.
You shoot people.
Why are you killing everyone?
Because they're useless.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Am I useless too?
If you don't help my
penis out of here then yes.
Okay. Here, let me
try to pull on this.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Alex, it's time for bed.
Wait.
No, no, no, no.
Wait, after this one.
No, no, no.
Right now.
You hear me, Alex?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Alex, [inaudible].
All right
[ Pause ]
[ Music ]
[Background Music] Is
his penis still stuck?
He got out.
Where are you now?
Wait, not yet.
Oh no.
[ Music ]
[ Music & Noise ]
Oh, Linas.
Thank you very much.
You know, it's really
hard for Alex.
And you being here with
him really let him be a
child basically.
So thank you, and I
have 20 dollars for you.
[Laughter]
Come on, no, it's really okay.
Yeah, just take it.
You paid for the beef jerky.
Bye. Come on you little...
[ Noise ]
[ Music ]
[Background Music] Uh-oh.
Uh-oh.
[ Music & Noise ]
[Background Music]
Go, go around me.
I ran out of gas, man.
[ Music ]
Jim, what's up?
I just got in and Shorty
just died or something.
I don't know, man, this
it just overheated.
Anyway, what's up man?
What are you doing?
Really? Well, well, shit.
Where are you?
I'm going to come
over, all right?
[ Noise ]
Go around.
Oh baby. Yes baby.
Yes baby, go around me.
Here we go
[ Music ]
Oh, nice vehicle.
[Inaudible Remark]
What year is that?
76.
[ Music ]
[Inaudible Remark]
Oh man.
So, she hasn't come in yet?
No.
I don't even know
if she's been here.
What happened?
It was supposed to be
my day to pick her up.
I just... it wasn't clear and
so I haven't figured it out.
Excuse me.
Okay. All right.
Maria, yeah, hi, yeah.
So Shawna [phonetic] was
with you after school today?
Uh-huh.
Is this her?
And when did she leave?
Okay. Okay.
Okay, Maria, thanks a lot.
I'll see you soon I hope.
Okay.
You think she might be
in the area or something.
You want me...
I don't fucking know.
Well, what happened?
What?
She was here two hours ago.
I don't know where she is.
Linas.
Want to look for her?
Yeah, let's go.
Okay.
You got your car and we're good.
Yeah.
Hang on a second.
[ Music ]
There she is.
Really?
I got to...
Okay. We'll pull over.
[ Music ]
Where is she going?
She's probably going
to her mom's house.
Well, that's okay, right?
No, it's not okay.
She's only going to freak out.
[ Music ]
[ Music & Inaudible Discussion ]
Okay.
[ Music ]
Linas, what are you doing here?
Linas! Over here.
Linas! Come on!
Linas.
Shawna, Shawna, Shawna, Shawna.
Oh my god.
Oh, shit. Are you all right?
I'm sorry.
Everything all right?
Where were you?
Are you okay?
[ Noise ]
[ Music ]
Hello.
Hey, my son.
Did you make it?
Yeah, I made it.
Yeah.
Where are you?
Down the street?
No, I'm in New York.
New York, that's great.
[ Music ]
Linas. Please stop.
Yeah. And so what's
your plan now?
Well, I was thinking
of just staying here.
I got a friend and, you know,
I'll look for a job, you know.
Uh-huh, maybe with some
kids and doing some, you know,
work like I did before.
Yeah, you always liked kids.
Yeah.
I'll see you tomorrow.
If you need anything come
and get me, all right?
Goodnight darling.
Goodnight.
You all right?
Yes.
I love you.
[Laughter]
That's the way we
should have started today.
[Inaudible Remark]
[ Pause ]
Who is that on the train?
That was her.
Who?
That girl from Seattle.
The married girl?
Yeah.
Wow. [Laughter]
What's she doing here?
I don't know.
Maybe... I guess her
sister's her.
I don't know.
Are you going to see her?
[ Pause ]
I don't know.
I don't think so.
[ Music ]
[ Laughter ]
Ah.
[ Music ]
[ Inaudible Remark ]
[ Laughter ]
[ Music & Inaudible Discussion ]
[ Music ]
[ Silence ]