[ Groaning ]
[ Vomiting, Coughing ]
Love sucks!
Morning!
What? No coffee!
I'm having herbal tea.
Well, I need
my caffeine.
Want me to whip up
one of my special omelets?
Thank you, no.
- Upset tummy again?
- Morning sickness.
- Funny girl.
- Donald, we need
to have a talk.
It's them--
The Mexican moron brothers.
Donald? Donald!
- What?
- I said we need to talk.
We will, Barbie,
as soon as I've had it out
with our two tree killers.
It's time
for a confrontation.
Yes, it is.
[ Lawn Mower Whirring ]
All right, mister,
it's time we settled this
once and for all.
Ooh! Mr. Chandler,
you shouldn't do that.
You could've been hurt.
Don't worry about that.
Let's talk about my tree.
It's dying.
I think you might be right.
- Maybe you would like
to explain to me why?
- I don't know.
- Nothing seems to work.
This might be an act of God.
- You better pray it's not.
This tree dies, you're fired!
You comprende?
Yeah, I comprehend
very well.
Good!
♪♪ [ Humming ] Sorry, mister.
No English. Sorry.Hey!
What, the tree again?
When the last leaf falls,
you and I will be fired.
Then let's quit right now,
'cause this thing's gonna die! No way, man.
We need the money.
You know that.
Let's get to work.
[ Weed Whacker Whirring ]
I'm terribly sorry.
We are completely booked.
Come on, honey.
Let's not let this spoil
our honeymoon.
We'll find some other
nice restaurant.
Thanks.Have a nice day.
Okay,
what did I miss?The shoes.
Oh, the shoes!
I always miss that.I know.
The dynamic duo.Oh, brother.
Jackie, Barbara,
what an unexpected pleasure.Donald.
So, what brings
you two lovely ladies
here today?
We were supposed
to have a talk?
We were. I'm sorry, darling.
It completely slipped my mind.
Well, since
we're all here together,
it might be a good idea
to sit down and have
a little family chat.
Of course.
Why don't we enjoy lunch
while we're at it?
Good luck.
All right! Lunch
is now being served
in the main parking lot.
- How much do I owe you?
- Nothing! It's your birthday!
I'm buying you lunch.
Thank you, my friend. Don't worry about it.
On my birthday, you can
take me out. Except we're goin'
someplace better than this.
Miguel, what do you wish for
on your birthday?
- I don't believe in wishes.
- Come on!
If I could wish for something,
it would be for Catalina
to be with us.
Catalina! Hey, if your sister
didn't have such a bad temper,
she could be living with us now.
Threatening to castrate that
immigration guy with a spoon,
that wasn't too smart.
He was trying
to cop a feel, Tobias.
Maybe he was, maybe he wasn't.
But the bottom line is
that right now...
Catalina is still living
in Mexico...
with a spoon, brother.
We are offering
some tasty specials today.
We didn't come here
to eat, Donald.
Donald, Barbara
has just informed me that...
I'm going to be a...
grandmother.
You're--
[ Mouths Word ]
Good afternoon, ladies,
Mr. Chandler.
Can I start you
with something to drink today?
I'll have a mineral water
with a squeeze.
I'll have a white wine.
Something full-bodied
and woody.
You choose.
- I'll have a shot--
Tequila.
- Tequila?
- Yes! I've just been informed
that I'm going to be a father.
- Congratulations!
You're not the father,
Donald.
Bring the bottle.
- What are you saying?
- Apparently our Barbie doll
has been having an affair.
- With whom?
- Daniel Gabois.
- The car salesman?
- He owns the dealership.
Children, the occupation
of this man is not the question.
The question is,
how are we going to handle
the situation?
He sold us the Benz.Donald, please.
I talked to my lawyers
this morning.
And the simplest way
to fix this... mess
is to file for an annulment.
It can be quick
and painless.
Oh, and I've already found
someone who's interested
in buying the restaurant.
Jackie, I put my heart
and soul into this place.
While you
totally ignored me.
If you sell the restaurant,
we'll both end up taking
a major loss.
- Consider it a write-off.
- A write-off? For you, maybe.
It'll ruin me.
I'll be lucky
to have enough money
to open a taco stand!
Oh! And I'm sure
they'll be excellent tacos.
Jackie, please.
You can't do this to me.
Oh, Donald, don't start
playing the martyr.
It's so unbecoming.
Look at it this way.
You married into money.
And now you'll be "unmarrying"
out of money.
No, I'm not gonna
let you do this. I'll take you
to court if I have to.
[ Women Laughing ]
Oh, Donald,
don't be silly.
Silly? I'm not the one
who was unfaithful here.
But I'm the one getting screwed.
Well, that is my best
and final offer.
I believe
we're finished here.
Have a nice day, dear.
[ Miguel ]
Okay, Tobias,
give me a beat.
♪ Um, um, ah, um, ah
♪♪ [ Spanish ]
♪ We likes to freestyle
every single día ♪
♪♪ [ Spanish ]
♪ Just keep it--
♪♪ [ Spanish ]♪ Ah, ah, ah, ah ♪
That was tight!That was tight, brother.
You're the Spanish Tupac.
You think?Absolutely, man.
Let's get a beer.
Let's go!
Oh, I can't.
Uh, Juanita's cooking up
a storm for me tonight.
I know. She invited me, man.
But it's your birthday
and I wanna get you a drink.
[ Spanish ]
Okay, just one, though.That's cool.
That's all I can afford.
You should shave off
that ugly mustache
for your birthday.
This mustache is G.Q., bro.I'm just playin'
with you, man.
[ Spanish ]
What, man?
Just being friendly.
I know. Too friendly.
[ Everyone ]
Surprise!
Happy birthday.
Hey, I told you I didn't
want a birthday party.I felt different.
[ Spanish ]
Happy birthday, Dad!
More drinking!
How are you?
[ Spanish ]
One for me and one
for the [ Spanish ] here.And one for me too!
All right!
[ Spanish ]
Ahhh.Whoo!
Worm food.
When we die,
that is what we are--
worm food.
And while we are alive,
we are the food for women.
You women, you just like
to feed on our dreams,
don't you?
And when those are all
eaten up-- yeah, gone,
then you start to gnaw
on our self-respect.
Don't look at me.
I've been on a diet lately.
- Whatever happened to good
old-fashioned male bartenders?
- You're the one who hired me.
I did, didn't I?
In that case, you're fired.
Are you serious?
No. I need
another drink.
Mr. "C," why don't you let
me call one of your friends to
pick you up and take you home?
I don't have any friends.
How 'bout I call you
a taxi?
No, no. If I'm to go gentle
into that good night,
I'm gonna go in style.
Get me a limo.
This will make all
our wishes come true.
[ Spanish ]
Gracias,Ansiana.
Hey.
A lottery ticket.
You know what I think
about these things.
It's a waste of good money.
This is how you
thank someone for a gift?
Be careful, man.
You know what
a powerful brujaAnsiana is.
You make jokes
about my powers?
I'm just playin' with you,
old woman.
Speaking of which,
it's lottery time! Eduardo,
put on channel nine!
Don't you wanna see
if you won?
I've already won.
I have you,
two wonderful kids,
and plenty of friends.
- Why don't you check
the numbers for me?
- Whoo!
What else did we get?
- Come on. Come on.
- [ Muttering ]
[ Spanish ]
Missed it.
Ansiana?
[ Sighs ]
Tobias, you let Ansiana
drink tequila again?
She only had a couple of shots.
You got Miguel's ticket?
Ansiana! Ansiana,
are you all right?
[ Spanish ]
I did it!
Miguel, if you win
the lottery, can I borrow
a million dollars?
Tobias, if I win the lotto,
I'll let you borrow
two million.
Sounds great, bro,
because I think you just won it.
- Let me see that.
- What?
[ Donald ]
"Now that you're pregnant
with another man's child,
"there is only one path
left for me to walk.
"May the ending
of my life...
" be a new and happier life
for you,
blah, blah, blah.
Sincerely, Donald."
Well, that oughta keep
that bitch in therapy
for a while.
One thing I'd like to say
before I go--
This thing on?
Maybe I'm overreacting
just a little bit.
Oh, oh, ohhh!
[ Gags ]
[ Doorbell Chimes ]
Mr. Chandler?
Mrs. Chandler?
There ain't nobody home.
Just leave him a note.
I wanna tell it to his face
that we're quitting.
[ Door Slams Shut ]
Mr. Chandler.
Mr. Chandler, please pick up
the white courtesy phone.
This is a nice place, bro.It's all right.
Mr. Chandler!
Mrs. Chandler.
Whoo! Damn!
Somebody's
been partying, bro.
Come on!
Don't be drinking that!
Oh, Miguel!
What happened?
He hosed himself.
Why, man? Why would a man
who has so much
do such a thing?
He probably heard
we were quitting.This is nothing to joke about.
Check it out.
He left a note!
What's it say?
His wife got knocked up
by some other dude.
He can't live without her.
"Good-bye, cruel world."
.- [ Groaning ]
- [ Gasps ]
- Mr. Chandler?
- You--
It's me, Miguel Sanchez. I don't like you.
You killed my tree.
Get out of my dream.
You're not dreaming,
Mr. Chandler.
What am I doing out here
talking to you?
- I think you tried
to kill yourself.
- But the damn branch broke.
- Tobias, please!
- [ Groaning ]
It's all your fault.
My fault!
I don't even know your wife.
I'm a happily married man.
The tree, you idiot.
If you hadn't killed my tree,
the branch wouldn't have broke.
We wouldn't be having
this conversation, would we?
Oh, my head!
Relax. There's plenty
of branches strong enough
for you to finish the job.
Tobias!
It's not so bad, man.
[ Groaning ]
No?
My wife wants an annulment.
I lost my restaurant.
I have no money.
- You're still a young man.
- What are you doing here?
It's Thursday.
- We came to tell you
that we quit.
- Fine.
You kick a man
when he's down.I'm really sorry, Mr. Chandler.
Hey. I just had an idea.No more of your jokes, okay?
It's not a joke!
I think you're really
gonna like this idea.
[ Whispering ]
Except we gotta got talk
in private. [ Spanish ]
Can you excuse us for a second,
Mr. Chandler? Okay?
One second.
So what's your big idea?
I think we should hire el jefe.I thought you said
it was not a joke.
No, it's not a joke!
He's a desperate man.
And that's exactly
what we need right now.Why do we need a desperate man?
We can hire him
to marry your sister.Oh, no, no, no, no.
Catalina can finally
come here to live with us.
We tried it before.
It didn't work.
She scared them away before
anyone could say, "I do."
That's why we need
a desperate man.
No offense, bro,
but your sister--
she's not an easy person
to live with.
She's had a hard life.[ Tobias ]
Yeah, I know.
But now you can afford
to make it an easy life.
But it's gonna take
a desperate man
to make that happen.
[ Groaning ]
I believe
that we're looking
at such a man.
It's true.
I have been blessed
with a great deal of money.
Maybe we should offer
Mr. Chandler
our assistance.
As an act of charity.Act of charity!
All right.
[ Clears Throat ]
Mr. Chandler, my brother-in-law
has convinced me to offer you
our assistance.
- Yeah! We wanna hire you!
- [ Chuckling ]
Sorry, boys,
I don't do lawns.
[ Laughing ]
Oh, I'm afraid you
misunderstand us, Mr. Chandler.
You see, recently I came into
a great deal of money.Like 62 million in chump change!
That's right!
- You what?
- I won the lottery last night!
That's why we came to quit.
And what we wanna hire you
to do ain't got nothing
to do with mowing lawns!
I can't think
without my coffee.
You care to join me
for a cup?
There is something wrong
with this picture.
- Why do you say that?
- First of all, you two
don't like me very much.
That's true.
-Yet you're willing to loan me
the money to open a restaurant.
-If you marry my sister, yes.
- Why me?
- You ain't met his sister.
What is she?
A short, fat woman
with a noticeable mustache?
Actually, no. Catalina's
a very beautiful woman.
It's just that, um,
she's got a bit of a temper.
- Bit of a temper--
- [ Pounds Table ]
She's fine, man.
If that's all it is,
no "problemo," amigos.
I'm a professional at dealing
with women with attitudes.
Let's talk more about
the restaurant part
of this deal, shall we?
Tobias,
what's going on?
Why are all
these people here?
[ Spanish ]
[ Miguel ]
Excuse me.
Can I please get out?
Excuse me. Excuse me.
[ Spanish ]
Excuse me.
Coming through.
Excuse me, all right?
Inside. Come on!
Let's go in!
Bye!
Yea! We won the lotto!
We won the lotto!
That's my ball!No, it's not!
Yes, it is!
Give me my ball!Hey! Hey!
Can I have it quiet, please?
Little peace and quiet.[ Phone Ringing ]
Let me get it for you, man.
[ Spanish ]
Sorry.
Hello?
Yeah, it is.
I don't think so, okay?
- No! Okay?
- Who was that?
Somebody who wants to help you
spend your money.Can I have a TV?
Who wants
to go play Monopoly?I do.
We're gonna go play
"white boy" Monopoly.Real money?
You know it!
You guys got cash, yeah?Tobias, no.
I'm just playin'
with 'em.
Oh, baby.
- [ Ringing ]
- Oh, God!
Oh, God!
Did you see that?
Yesterday we're moaning 'cause
we don't have enough money.
And today we're moaning
'cause we have too much.
Life is crazy.
- I think I know where to leave
the madness behind us.
- How?
Tonight we will be moving
into a new house
in a beautiful neighborhood.
Miguel, where?
The home of my
future brother-in-law.
I think I found somebody
for Catalina to marry.
Oh, no, Miguel.
Not again!
[ Sighs ]
I will survive.
Thank you.
[ Doorbell Chimes ]
Who the hell is that?
Miguel.
- How you doin', Mr. Chandler?
- What a surprise.
I got some great news.
My sister has agreed
to marry you.
Well, that is good news!
What exactly
are you doing here?
We're moving in...
a little earlier
than we planned.
- Moving in.
- Yeah. You don't understand.
It's been crazy at our house.
I decided it would be best
for the family...
to leave the madness behind us,
and move in with you tonight.
Whoa, whoa, wait a minute.
Let's back up a little bit.
I don't recall this
moving-in thing being part
of our agreement.
Oh, but it was.
For the next two years,
and a couple of weeks,
we're gonna be
one big, happy family.No, no, no, no, no.
I never agreed
to anything like that.
Come, Miguel. I can tell
we're not welcome here.
[ Spanish ]
It was a small misunderstanding.
I'm sure I can find someone else
to marry Catalina. Come on.
Whoa! Wait a minute, folks.
I'm sure we can come
to some agreement
that we all can live with.
It's either gonna
involve all of us,
or none of us.
The question is, Donald,
do you still wanna be
part of this agreement?
I do.
Then, by the power
invested in me,
the state of California,
I now pronounce you
man and wife.
You can kiss the bride.
I think a simple handshake
will suffice.
Ay,no, Miguel!
I think the one you had me marry
is one who likes the boys!
If you're going to insult me,
use something more original.
The gay thing is old material.
Aha! So others have suspected
your true tastes.
It matters little to me,
but it is traditional
for the groom to kiss the bride.
- You want me to kiss you.
- As distasteful
as I may find it, yes.
Our guests are watching.
Fine!
[ Cheering ]
♪♪ [ Latin ]
I hope you kiss your boyfriends
better than that.
Actually I'm accustomed
to kissing warm-blooded women.
Your fish lips threw me off.
Fish lips?
Listen to me, you little worm!
Catalina! Donald! You have
plenty of time to compare each
other to all kinds of animals.
For now we have
a celebration to host.
Can we greet our guests?
You remind me of a dog
I once had fixed.
[ Miguel ]
Be nice.
♪♪ [ Singing In Spanish ]
We did it![ Laughing ]
Donald, here are the keys
to the restaurant.
Thank you, Miguel.Sure.
Hi!
[ Spanish ]
[ Spits ]
Oh, look. Aunt Methuselah
just spit on my shoes.
[ Spanish ]
[ Continues In Spanish ]
Care to translate that?Yeah, sure.
She said that you are
no longer a real man, 'cause
you sold your soul for money.
You move to the song of life,
but without a soul,
you can no longer feel
the music.
And now you're just simply
a dancing bear
in the circus.
Thatwas an insult.
It was poetic, yet cutting.
You can learn from this woman.
Thank you, Ansiana,
for you have given me
a wedding present.
You gave me the nickname
to my husband, el oso,
the dancing bear.
Come, Oso,
dance with your wife.I don't dance.
Maybe I should teach you.
Why don't we save that for our
divorce when we have something
to really celebrate. I'm gone.
Don't you dare walk out
on our wedding day!You watch me!
Let him go.
Everyone knows this is not
a real marriage.
That man has no manners.
[ Chuckling ]
[ Door Creaking ]
Oso's back.
Ansiana, you shouldn't call
Donald that. It's disrespectful.If the shoe fits!
[ Footsteps ]
Miguel, you should've
warned him. It's okay.
Donald and Catalina are
married now. Some things they've
gotta work out themselves.
Ow! That hurt!
You could've put
my eye out!
My aim was off.
Next time you'll knock.
Knock? I don't have
to knock when I come
into my bedroom.
And this is mine too!
I don't want you
touching my things.
They're expensive.
Now I want you to leave.
No! While we're married,
this will be my room!
Now let's see
what kind of a man
you really are.
Get out! Out!
Your sister just
threatened me with a fork!
I'm sure she didn't mean it.
I'll talk to her tomorrow.
No. I'd like you
to talk to her right now.
She has the impression
that my room is now hers.
Donald, you and Catalina
are married now. Okay?
- Wherever you decide to sleep
has nothing to do with me.
- But that's my room!
Here. Go and show your bride
who the man is.
Hmm?
- Hola,Uncle Donald!
- What are you two
still doing up?
We were wondering who's gonna
sleep here tonight.Now you know. Happy?
Yeah!
Will you tell us a story,
Uncle Donald?
Please don't call me
Uncle Donald.
Makes me sound like a duck. Then what should we call you?
I don't care.
Be creative.
How about Uncle Oso?
Fine.
Will you tell us a story,
Uncle Oso?
Sorry, guys, but
entertaining the two of you
isn't in my contract!
Now, if you don't mind,
it's my wedding night.
I've got a big headache,
and I'd like to be alone.
It wasn't all
a bad dream.
What are you doing here?
Just paying Miguel back
the money I borrowed from him.The whole two million?
Oh, yeah! Stock market's
been real good to me.
Here, Oso, I cook this
especially for you.
Sorry, Ansiana, but I
have never considered beans
as a breakfast food.
Besides, you probably
spit in it.
- It's because we're Mexican!
- [ Juanita ]
It was nothing, Miguel.
You may live in a very beautiful
neighborhood, but the people
here can be very ugly!
-Why? What happened?
-The girl at the market asked if
we'd be paying in food stamps!
- And?
- "And?" How would you like it
if she asked you that?
It's because we're Mexican! I don't think that's it.
Well, not entirely it.
Look, I don't know how
to put this gently.
But the main reason the people
around here treat you
the way they do, is--
It's the way
you dress.
There's nothing wrong
with the way we dress!
This is a very fashionable
neighborhood. The people here
are fashion-conscious.
Oh, my God! You're just
like the rest of 'em!Miguel.
Wasn't it you that told me
it's the man inside the clothes
that count?
And it is.
As long as you're well-dressed.
Come on, Miguel. What I'm saying
isn't exactly news. It's been
going on since the dawn of man!
Cavemen used to hunt
the meanest, most dangerous
animals in the forest.
Quite often, they'd lose
an arm and a leg in the process.
Why? For the skins.
We're no longer cavemen.
You're absolutely right.
Times change, fashions change,
animal skins are no longer in.
But the concept
remains the same.
People still go out.
They spend an arm and a leg
for clothes that say, "Hey!
Look at me. I'm very powerful.
I deserve respect."
- This is a foolish way
of thinking.
- Of course.
That's the way it is.
That's all the time we have for
today's lecture on "Lifestyles
of the Rich and Foolish."
I got things to do.
I'll get it.
Good morning!
What can I do for you?
I'm a Peacock.
Buy my cookies.
Darling, that's not the way
to sell your product.
Maybe if you said "please,"
you would sell
a lot more cookies.
I never say please
to the hired help.
I'm sorry. Alexandra's
in one of her moods today.
Is the lady of the house in?
You're speaking to her.
- Ah, you must be
the man of the house.
- What can we do for you?
- Buy my damn cookies!
- We don't buy cookies
from spoiled little girls!
- Your housekeeper seems to have
a bit of an attitude problem.
- Almost as bad as your girl.
- Well, I never!
- I'm not surprised.
I'm also not interested
in anything you're selling.
Good day.
There goes
my brief moment of peace.
Relax, Oso, I'm giving you
the night off.
- What are you making?
- Pancakes.
- Panqueques!
- No. Pancakes.
Panqueques.
- I want some too.
- Sure. Why not?
You're using this?
That is pure Vermont
maple syrup. The best.
.Syrup is for the mornings.
For the evenings--
Yes!What?
[ Spanish ]
You're in for a real treat.[ Spanish ]
Yeah, it's kind of a goat's
milk, sugar, kind of a caramel.
Why don't you sit down?
I'll show you how panqueques
should be made.
I just wanna have my--Shh!
Your wife has spoken.
Go. Sit.
Go, go, go, go, go!
Well?
Good.Of course they are.
Just don't expect me
to start cooking for you, okay?
[ Miguel ] What are you doing?Surrendering to our
late-night cravings.
"Pancaca." Panqueques con--
[ Spanish ]
No! Sí!And there are two left.
You can have 'em.
I'm gonna go to sleep.
I cooked, you clean.
Oh, man, I love these!
When your sister isn't
being possessed by Satan,
she can be pretty nice.
Catalina's not had
an easy life.
We lost our parents when we were
very young. I came to California
to live with an uncle.
Catalina stayed in Mexico
and was passed on
from family to family.
Given her temper,
I can understand why.
She wasn't like that then.
At least not at first.
It's just that every time
she got close to one family,
she would find herself
being passed on...
to another family.That must've been rough.
We kept on trying to bring her
to California,
but nothing ever worked out.
Then there was a little problem
with an immigration agent.
I'm glad you told me
about her. I'll call the parish
and cancel the exorcism.
[ Thunderclaps ]
[ Screaming ]
Uncle Oso! Uncle Oso!
Snakes!Huh?
- Snakes?
- Under my bed!
/[ Sighs ]
This used to be
such a nice neighborhood.
They got really big
blue and green eyes
and long sharp fangs.
They sound just like the ones
that are in my bed.
[ Sighs ]
Relax, Domi, I was joking.
Can I sleep with you?
You're a big boy now.
You should be sleeping
in your own bed.
- Please?
- Oh, no.
Not the tears.
Come on.
[ Thunderclaps ]
I'm sorry.Ah, that's all right.
No need to be sorry.
Everybody's afraid of something.
What are you afraid of?Me?
Let's see. I'm afraid
of big dogs without collars,
people who have
homemade tattoos
with bad spelling,
and your Aunt Cat.
But enough about me.
Let's go to sleep and dream
about nice things, huh?
You don't have any problems
with bed-wetting, do you?
Not most of the time.
How very reassuring.
Donald,
I've made a decision.
The time has come for me
to spread my new wealth
on my family.
It's time we go shopping
for new clothes suitable
for our new social position.
Good for you.
If you'd like, I'd be happy
to recommend a few good stores.
I would consider it
a personal favor
if you came along.
You seem to have a good
sense of style, right?Yeah.
I'll warn you now,
if you wanna do it right,
this won't come cheap.
Donald, what part
of 62 million
don't you understand?
Let's go shopping.Yes!
♪ Come on, come on
come on ♪
[ No Audible Dialogue ]
Donald?
Barbara!Hi!
- How have you been?
- Surviving. And you?
Fine. Great!
I thought by now
you'd be a little more--
Oh, that... turned out
to be a false alarm.
So how is your little...
car salesman?
He was another false alarm.
You look great!
Listen. Maybe we should
get together sometime.
Grab some lunch or--
What do you think
of this one, Oso?
- Oso?
- Yes. It's a pet name
for my husband.
You're married to Donald?
Yes. And just
who the hell are you?
Oh, Cat, this is my ex-wife,
Barbara. Barbara, this is
my future ex-wife, Catalina.
Well, didn't take you very long
to find someone else.
This is why you wanted
to go shopping? You were
hoping to run into this woman?
- I should've known better.
- Cat, if you're looking for
a fight, pick one with her.
I'm gonna check on Miguel.
Look at the time. I gotta run.
It was nice meeting you,
"Carolina."
Hell no!
Listen to me, sweetheart.
The Colombia-coffee-bean-pickin'
spokesperson look...
is cute in a Latino
sort of way, but that's not
what we're goin' for here.
That mustache?
It's just got to go.
Man, all I want
is a haircut, okay?
- Then you gonna have to go
to a barber.
- Donald?
Miguel,
if you don't like it,
you can grow it back.
But I like my mustache, man!
I've had it since
I was 16 years old.
It's your dime.My dime?
I'm gonna make you look fierce.
You hear me? Fierce!
- I don't wanna look fierce.
- [ Razor Whirring ]
[ Groans ]
Donald, Donald!
[ Donald ]
I believe you have arrived.
I think I'll go
to the market, buy some...
eggs.
[ Domi ]
I wanna go with you.
We had this conversation.
There aren't gonna be any
children at the grand opening.
Even your mother and father
won't be there.I still wanna go.
I'll take you with me
next week.
We'll do lunch.
So, what do you think?
The tie sucks.
You're right.
We have definite
"tie suckage" here.
Let's go with something
with a little more color.
Hey.
Something wrong, Oso?
No, you just surprised me.
I've never seen you
dressed up like this before.
Money becomes you.
- You going somewhere
special tonight?
- I'm going with you.
No way!
Don't even think about it.
But your wife should be there
on such an important event.
I've invited a lot of big fish.
There's no way I'm
bringing along a barracuda.
Relax, Oso.
I promise I'll be nice.
Tonight I'll play the role
of your loving wife.
I'm sorry. This is too important
to take the chance that you'll
explode in somebody's face.
If you don't take me,
I'm coming anyway. And I promise
you it won't be pretty.
The choice is yours.
Which do you want?
The lady... or the barracuda?
- Let's see what your brother
has to say about this.
- Fine!
[ Together ]
Miguel!
Yeah, but a mustache
is a very personal thing!
Donald, you're just
the person I needed to see.
We do need to talk.This is my friend, Hector.
I'm thinking about
lending him the money
to open up a barbershop.
I just think that he should
shave off that mustache.
He looks like a thug.
- Come on, Miguel.
- It's important for a barber
to be clean-shaven.
So lose the mustache!
I had to marry his sister
to get him to loan me money.
While we're on the subject
of business,
did you realize that Catalina
is insisting on going
tomy grand opening?
- Take her. She's already
dressed for the occasion.
- Exactly!
- What harm could she do?
- Let me count the ways.
- I promised I'd be nice.
- So what's the problem?
If Cat does anything
to ruin my grand opening,
we'll be talking
to divorce lawyers
in the morning!
You heard your husband,
Catalina.
[ Everyone Laughing ]
Lose the mustache.
Let me drive.No.
Why not?I've seen the way
you drive.
What's wrong with my driving?In this country, driving is
not considered a contact sport.
I'm warning you.
Do not mess with me,
not tonight.
All right. Tonight
we're happily married, okay?
It will be our evening
of lies. Okay?
It's show time!
- Relax, Oso. People don't trust
a man who sweats too much.
- I'm not sweating.
We have live ones!
For luck.
Norm, Ellie, thank you
so much for coming tonight.Welcome.
- Are we too early?
- No, not at all.
You're just... the first!
Why don't you come with me
and we'll put the staff to work?
BpBeautiful earrings!Thank you.
More wine, sir?
[ No Audible Dialogue ]
Thank you so much
for coming.
You've outdone yourself,
Donald.Thank you.
It was lovely.
- And I will see you at the club
this Tuesday.
- I look forward to it.
Good night.
Here comes Andrew Hurley.Big fish?
Top of the food chain.
Numero uno food critic
in the city.
[ Whispering ]
I thought it was wonderful.
I loved it.
Mr. Hurley, thank you
so much for joining us.
- I trust that everything
was to your satisfaction?
- Everything was second-rate...
compared to the wit and charm
of your beautiful wife.
As far as the food and service
was concerned,
the experience
was adequate.
Oh! It was more than adequate.
It was superb.
Come along, Andy, before you
say something to really insult
this very nice couple.
Well, we may
drop by again.Uh-huh.
We look forward to it.
Thank you. Bye.
Honey.Good night.
We are going to be
an instant success.
He really, really liked us!
No, Oso.
Mr. Moby Dick liked me.
He said your restaurant
was merely... adequate.I know.
Where I come from, adequate
is not a word of praise.
It is with Andrew Hurley.
Adequate is the highest praise
he gives any restaurant.
And then only rarely.
We are going to be
an instant success.
You care to join me
in the lounge, my dear?I believe I would, my darling.
[ Gasps ]
I see someone here
has great taste in music.
To my lovely wife
who helped make this evening
a smashing success.
To our evening of lies!
♪♪
- Mmm. We should dance.
- What? Here?
Sure. Why not? Everyone's left.
Nobody will be watching.
- Catalina--
- Don't worry, Oso.
I'll teach you.
To be honest--
This is no time to be honest.
This is our evening of lies.
Come on.
You see, I told you
I was a good driver.
- You're confusing luck
with skill.
- Be nice.
I'm sorry, your highness.
The truth slipped out
before I could stop it.
You know, Cat,
when you want to--
You too, Oso.
Let's go.
Uh-uh. Allow me.
I will get the door.
.Thanks, Cat.
You were nothing short
of prefect tonight.
And you...
were adequate.
[ Laughs ]
Aw, don't look so hurt.
Adequate is the highest
praise I ever give anyone.
Where have you two been?
Don't you want to know
how the grand opening went?
- I'm sorry, Donald.
How was your opening?
- We were a hit.
I'm very happy for you.
Now where have
you two been?
Celebrating.
Drinking champagne
and dancing.
Dancing? I thought
you didn't dance.
You should've seen him. I
couldn't teach him a thing.
You want to get critical?
Let's talk about your driving.Don't start with me on that!
Hey, hey, hey! If you guys
are gonna fight, keep it down.
- My kids are asleep.
Good night.
- Good night.
Well, I think we've shared
enough lies for one evening.
I hate it when you're right.
Sweet dreams, Cat.And to you, my friend.
- Catalina?
- Hmm?
I was thinking that maybe
after we get divorced,
we might go out on a real date.
I'll think about that.
For about a year or two.
[ Woman On Radio]
Hey,amigos,
happy Thanksgiving!
It's another beautiful day
in the City of Angels...
with a brisk 68 degrees
and mostly sunny.
So put some salsa
on your turkey...
and give a hear on K.U.N.O.,
la numero uno.
Eww.
Ansiana, don't
even think about it.
That's my gravy. Mine!
This is an American holiday.
I'm the only one here
qualified to cook it.
I swear, old woman, you add
so much as a pinch of anything,
I'm calling immigration.
Correct me if I'm wrong,
but you no have-a
the green card?
Well, I see perhaps
you are right.
This is... your holidays.
So, how shall I say this?
You are
citizenship-challenged.
Donald, there's some things
we don't joke about.
Fine. I believe Ansiana
and I have come to a new...
and closer understanding
of one another, haven't we?
Why don't we go
to the living room
and watch the parade?
- Parade?
- Yes, there's one
on television.
I see! I love parades!
You shouldn't be mean to her,
you know.Why not? She's mean to me.
You deserve it.Right.
- Just be nice, okay?
- [ Clears Throat ]
Everything smells
so wonderful.Mm-hmm!
Is this the
Chandler residence? Si,and who are you?
We're from the
Department of Immigration.
I swear to you.
I did nothing to the gravy!
I beg your pardon?
For this, I place
a curse on you, Oso.
[ Muttering ]
Ansiana, who's here?
- Catalina Chandler?
- No, she's my sister-in-law.
[ Donald ] Catalina, with all
my heart and soul, I hate you!
I really, really hate you!
[ Catalina ] If you were a man,
that might bother me, Oso.
But you're no man.
[ Donald ] What do you think
you were doing?Please, won't you come in?
We'd like to speak
to Mr. and Mrs. Chandler.
My ties!
She took my ties--
imported silk ties-- and washed
them in the washing machine!
It was an accident.
Somehow the ties got in
with the laundry.
That was no accident. It was
her way of getting back at me
because I forgot her birthday!
He cares more about the clothes
than the people who wear them!
Not even a card. A card!
Silencio!You will stop your
arguing now! These people are
from the Immigration Department.
Good. You saved me
the phone call.
I want you to take her back.
- Mr. Chandler--
- She is a witch!
Take her. She's yours!
Thanks for coming by.
I'll go pack my suitcases. [ Man ]
Mrs. Chandler.
We're not here to judge
whether or not
you're happily married.
We're here to verify that
you're actually living together
as man and wife.
Which apparently you are.
[ Donald ]
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean
what I just said.
It's just my ties!
I know.
I'm sorry too.
I'll talk to you
when I get home.I'll be here.
Mr. Chandler,
we'd like to ask you
a few questions.
I'm sorry, but I have
to get to work. I'm late,
and I need some new ties.
I'm sorry about Oso--
I mean, Donald.
You don't need to apologize.
Apparently you two share a very
passionate relationship.
I envy you.
You're up late tonight.I'm trying to put together
Domi's gift.
Mmm. This family has been
a good influence on you.
I think maybe you
are beginning to find
your soul again.
Blame it on the holidays.Would you like
an eggnog?
No. I hate eggnog.Me too.
But it's the holidays!
Oso, there is something
I must tell you.
- So tell me.
- I have wronged you.
Anything in particular
or just in general?
A few weeks ago when
the immigration people
came here,
I thought you had sent them
to take me away.
I placed a curse on you.
Given the situation,
I don't blame you.
It was a curse on you
to make you face
your greatest fear.
It's only recently
I discovered what
you fear the most.
You fear love.
It is why you have tried
to bury yourself
in all of this comfort.
You need it to keep you
from feeling the things
you cannot control.
You know something, Ansiana,
you would make
a hell of a fortune teller.
It's a gift I have.
I hate to burst your bubble,
but I don't believe in magic.
While we're at it,
I don't believe that true love
exists in the real world.
People who have lost
their souls
believe in very little.
There is something else
I have to tell you.
Something I have told
to no one else.
- What is that?
- I am not a true member
of this family.
What?
It was by chance I walk
into the church where Anthony
was being christened.
They seemed
like such a nice family.
Let me guess.
You cast a spell and you
became an instant relative?
It helped.
But they were too polite to ask
if I was related to them.
- Why are you telling me this?
- I have lived with this secret
for many years now.
Sometimes it is good
to trust another with
the secrets of your heart.
- And you trust me?
- [ Giggling ]
In many ways,
you and Catalina
are so much alike.
Good night.
Feliz Navidad.
Ah.
[ Phone Ringing ]
Hello?Merry Christmas, Donny.
Barbie!I'm throwing a little
Christmas Eve thing.
I was hoping, if
you're not doing anything,
you could come by.
Sorry, Barbara, but I'm kinda
tied up. Wrapping gifts.
That kind of thing.
Did you get me anything?Gosh, no. You're not
on my list this year.
You hate me, don't you?No, I don't hate you.
You're not on my hate list,
nor are you on
my Christmas card list.
You are "listless" with me.
I got you
a little something.You shouldn't have.
Well, I did. So why
don't you come over here
so I can give it to you?
e@Sorry, Barbie,
but I've got commitments here.
Feliz Navidad.
Feliz Navidad?
- Looking for something special?
- [ Gasps ]
You startled me.
So, Cat, are you being naughty
or nice?
I haven't decided yet.
[ Both Laughing ]
I like your hat.
So, little boy, what do
you want for Christmas?
That, my dear,
is a very dangerous question
to ask a celibate.
I know.
- [ Miguel ] Ho, ho, ho!
- Great! Here comes
Santa Claus.
Feliz Navidad, Oso.
Ho, ho, ho, my friend.
wHumbug, amigo.
[ Crowd ]
Five, four,
three, two, one--
[ Cheering, Chattering ]
Happy New Year,
my almost-husband.
my almost-wife.
Happy New Year,
Catalina.Happy New Year!
Donald.And to you.
Can I buy you a drink?Miguel, I never drink
while I'm working.
You know that.Come on. We're friends.
We're business partners.
We gotta toast in
the New Year together.Yeah.
All right. Maybe one.
Up to the bar.
I'm buying.
Happy New Year.
[ Spanish ]
To health, wealth,
and love, my friend.
Works for me.
If I ever catch you
kissing my sister again,
it won't work well for you.
It could easily
cost you a restaurant.
Take is easy, Miguel.
I didn't kiss your sister.
She kissed me.
Besides, it's New Year's Eve.
People kiss each other.
What's the harm of that?
In case you haven't noticed,
Catalina's beginning
to have feelings for you.
You know,
I'm startin' to like her
a little bit too.
It's a lot better
than fighting all the time.
No! I don't want
to see her hurt again.
She's been hurt enough.
Hey, Miguel, I've got
no argument with that. Well, good.
Then you keep your
relationship with her
strictly business.
If not, I'll be forced
to take away your restaurant.
Comprende?
Yeah.
You have a nice
restaurant, Donald.
Salud.
This offer is good for now.
But it won't be open forever.
What can I say?Just say yes.
Well, just say
you'll think about it.
I'll think about it.
Donald.If it isn't Miguel and
his faithful jungle guide.
See, Miguel.
I told you that
people would make jokes.
Miguel, you remember
my ex-wife, Barbara. And
this is her mother, Jackie.
- Miguel.
- Pleased to meet you.
Can I talk to you
for a second?
Certainly. Ladies, would
you please excuse me?
Come on.Sure.
What's this?
Another business loan?Is that the fellow?
Yeah. I'm thinking
I'll lend Cruz the money...
to start
a gardening service.
First-class.
Complete with
uniforms and everything.
I don't want to be first-class.
All I want to do is mow lawns
and pull the weeds.
Trust me on this, okay?
What are they doing here?Having lunch.
I can see that. I don't
want to see 'em here.
I'm sorry you feel
that way, Miguel.
- Why don't you
ask them to leave?
- No.
That wasn't a request, Donald. That's it, Miguel.
You finally crossed the line.
You want to take the restaurant,
you go ahead and take it.
Just say the word, it's yours.
I've got other offers.
- We'll talk about
this later.
- Fine.
Right now, I've got
to go out and get
a Valentine's gift for Cat.
- That's not necessary.
- Oh, I think it is.
- Do you remember what happened
when I forgot her birthday?
- You may have a point.
♪♪
[ No Audible Dialogue ]
Hey.Hey, Cat.
I'm goin' out for a while.It's after 10:00!
Where are you goin'
at this time of night?Out!
I'm feeling restless.
Is that all right with you?
Hey, I was
just asking, okay? God!
Yes, sir.
Tomorrow at 8:00.
[ Footsteps ]
Buy a girl a drink?
So what brings you here?
I came to give you
your Valentine's present.
[ Laughs ]
My Valentine's present?
Me.
[ Laughs ]
Barbie, we still
have dinner guests.
Well, I suppose
I'll have to settle
for a drink until they leave.
So, have you thought
about the offer?
As a matter of fact,
I have.
- Thanks but no thanks.
- What? Why?
Barbie, I've already
been burned once by you
and your mother.
- I think once is enough.
- Come on, Donald.
I admit I made a small mistake.
Are you gonna hold that
against me forever?
It wasn't a small mistake.
It was a pretty big one.
But you know something?
You kinda did me a favor.
Here you go.
One cosmo, up,
on the house.
Mmm! You do know
what a girl likes.
It's gonna be different
this time, darling.
Even Mother approves now.
You really impressed her.
I impressed your mother?
Indeed you did. You've made
a success of yourself here.
But what really
impressed her the most...
was that you actually
married that Mexican woman
to make it all happen.
It's amazing what
a desperate man will do.
Well, you don't have
to be desperate any longer.
Or lonely, Donald.
You've paid your dues.
It's time to come back
to the real world...
and say adios
to that third-world family.
DpYou're not gonna
find a better offer.
Not to mention the perks.
The perks.Me!
Whoa!
Barbie, just--Donald, give me a kiss.
Come on! Stop it. Stop it!
Oh, yes, Donald!
[ Laughs ]
Barbie!
[ Barbara ]
Come here. Gimme a kiss.
Don--
Uh, I'll come back later.
I'm not playing.I'm not listening to you.
No, no.
You can't do that.
That's a guy thing.
Then what can I do
for you?
Why don't you...
take a taxi home--And then?
You wait for me.[ Laughs ]
You better not
keep me waiting long.
[ Growls, Giggles ]
[ Sighs ]
What happened between you
and my sister last night?
What are you talking about?Catalina has
gone back to Mexico.
She what?Don't play innocent
with me, Donald!
- What'd you do to her?
- I don't know what
you're talking about.
- I-I didn't do anything.
- Oh, okay.
That explains everything.
- She left because
you didn't do nothin'.
- Exactly.
Here. She left
this letter for you.
"Oso, I'm not sure
which one of us is
the bigger fool, you or me.
"Somehow, we began to have
feelings for each other.
"We may have danced
to the same song
but we heard different lyrics.
"Now the dance is over.
It's time to go back to our own
separate worlds.
My world is in Mexico."
She came to
the restaurant last night.
Why? What happened there?
My ex-wife, Barbara.
She came by to give me a very
special Valentine's present.
You know, a "real good time."
- I think he's talking
about having sex.
- [ Spanish ]
Hey!
-I want you two to go to the
kitchen and eat your breakfast.
-Nobody's made breakfast.
If you're old enough to talk
about sex, you're old enough
to make your own breakfast.
Ay!It's all your fault.
So, you've been
messing around on my sister.
No.
And while we're on the subject,
it's none of your
damn business.
You told me to stay away
from your sister. I did.
Now you're telling me
I can't see other women.
Let me tell you something.
I never agreed to become
a priest.
The bottom line is,
nothing happened last night.
Then why did
Catalina leave, Donald?
Apparently, she didn't
stick around for the part
where I said no.
Miguel, let Oso get dressed.
I will make some coffee
and then we can sit down
and discuss this like adults.
Hmm?
[ Spanish ]
Get dressed.
There's nothin' left to discuss.
I will go to Catalina
and talk some sense into her.
No offense, Miguel.
I think it might
be better if I went.
No! You've already caused
enough problems in this family.
Donald is right. He is the
reason Catalina left. He should
be the one to bring her back.
No! I no longer trust this man.
He seduced my sister.
I never touched her,
Miguel.
Don't get technical
with me, Donald.
We had a business agreement.
Nobody was supposed
to feel anything.
But that wasn't good enough
for you, was it? You had
to make her f-feel things.
You planned this
all along.
Ay! Only fools
plan to fall in love.
Oh, it's true. Donald
can be a very foolish man.
But he did not plan this.
If anyone is to be blamed,
it is me. I placed
a curse on him.
Don't blame Broom Hilda here.
If anyone's to blame, it's you.
- My fault?
- Yes, you and your family.
For reasons that defy
all logic, I've actually come
to like having you around.
You're almost like a family
to me. And your sister,
Catalina, is a big part of that.
- We're not your family, Donald.
- We are all family.
Miguel, why would it be so bad
if Donald and Catalina
have truly fallen in love?
I'll tell you, baby.
As a businessman,
Donald's got my respect.
Fine. I don't think
he's the kind of man
I want my sister to marry.
I hate to point
this out, Miguel.
You know what I mean.
Married in the eyes of God.
As a true man and wife
by a priest.
Why would it be so bad
if they did become
a real man and wife?
Because this man's
got no honor!
He married for money.
There's nothin'
left to discuss!
I'm going to Mexico.
- No, Miguel.
I forbid you to go.
- You forbid me?
Yes, Miguel, I forbid you.
You have been playing el patrón
with all of our friends.
Dictating how they should live
their lives and run their
businesses and I said nada.
But no longer.
This is our family. Familia.
And I will not keep quiet.
I forbid you to dictate
to them who they should
and should not love.
- Juanita, y--
- [ Spanish ]
I'm sorry, Catalina,
but I have no work
I can offer you.
It's the slow time
of the year.
I understand, don Carlos.
Maybe in a month or two
when the tourists
start to come back.
You'll be
the first person I'll hire.
I promise you that.
Thank you, don Carlos.
In the meantime,
you need a little money?
Oh, no. I'm okay.
Thank you.
I'm sorry things
didn't work for you
in the United States.
But we're happy
that you're back.
It's good to be back.
Tobias, here are the keys.
Thanks for filling in
for me.
Just try not
to burn it down.That's Miguel's job.
Uncle Oso,
will you bring me
back a present?
- How about I bring back
your favorite aunt?
- Okay.
Tell you what I'll do.
I'll have your Aunt Cat pick out
both of you something special.
- Okay? Wish me luck.
- [ Together ]
Good luck.
Oh, Donald?
If you truly wish
to bring Catalina back,
you will have
to face your fear.
You must listen
to the music in your heart.
It will keep you honest
with yourself.
Do not forget
what I've said.
I won't.
We'll be back soon.
Bye.Bye.
Here you go, señor.
Keep it.Outside.
Here?
I hope you enjoy your stay
with us, Señor Chandler.
Thank you.
Have you by chance
seen this woman?
I understand she used
to work here.
Catalina.
Of course I know her.
But she moved
to the United States
to get married.
I know.
I'm the guy she married.
Oh.If you happen to see her,
would you let me know?Oh, Señor Chandler,
please. Keep your money.
Catalina has always been
like a little sister to me.
uI promise you that
I will watch out for her.
Thank you.
What? Do you really think of
Catalina as your little sister?
She's more, uh,
like a cousin.
A distant cousin.
[ Laughs ]
Por qué,boss. Why didn't
you tell Mr. Chandler
that Catalina was here?
Rule number two.Ah! Uh--
What's rule number two?
Now listen to me,
young man.
Rule number two is one
of the most important rules
in managing a hotel.
Never ever become involved
in another man's
womans problems.
It can be a pit
filled with deadly snakes.
Oh, so what's
rule number one then?
[ Sighs ]
Unless you're asked,
never ever let the wife know
that the husband stay here
in this hotel.
Oh. So then we shouldn't
call Catalina to tell her that
Mr. Chandler is looking for her.
Bingo!
Do you have
a hotel phone I can use?Please.
Be my guest.
Yeah, hi, Juanita. It's me.
Have you heard from Cat?
Yeah, okay.
Please call me
if you hear from her, okay?
Yeah. I'll do the same. Bye.
Thank you.[ Spanish ]
So, you have come here
for business or for pleasure?
I'm looking for a woman.
Ah, then it is
for pleasure.
The woman is my wife.Ah. Then it is none
of my business.
Have you by chance
seen this woman?
It would be hard to forget
such a beautiful woman.
But I am sorry,
I can tell you nothing.
♪ I don't know why
♪ You should cry
♪ 'Cause you know
that for you, I'd die ♪
♪ In my sleep
when you weep ♪
♪ 'Cause there's nothin'
that I wouldn't do ♪
♪ For you
♪ You know that there is
nothin' I won't do ♪
♪ For you
♪ You know that you
are everything to me ♪
♪♪ [ Spanish ]
Señora?Sí.
[ Spanish ]
Gracias.
Hola.Hola.
Amigo?
[ Spanish ]
Gracias.
[ Sighs ]
Hi!Hi.
Do you have
any rooms available?
For a beautiful woman
as you--
How could I say no?
I'll take the best you have. Will you be
staying alone, or--
will someone join you?
Well, that all depends.
I'm looking for my husband.
Oh?
By any chance,
have you seen this man?
Are you married to this man?
His name is Donald Chandler.
He checked in
with us yesterday.
In that case,
I won't be needing
a room after all.
Do you have
an extra key to his room?
Of course.
It's bungalow 103
and it's located
at the far side of the pool.
Thank you.
Oh!
Wake up, boss.[ Spanish ]
Why did you tell her
about her husband?
She asked.
Perhaps we should
call Catalina.
What about the rules?
When a man has two wives,
the rules no longer apply.
This is quaint.
Looking for
a good time, sailor?
- What are you doing here?
- I was hungry. I thought
I'd have dinner.
I meant, what are you
doing in Mexico?
I called your restaurant.
Talked to some guy Tobias.
He told me I could find
you here. Aren't you
gonna ask me to sit down?
No, I'm not.
I want you to go away.
Cat left me because
she saw the two of us together
the other night.
I need to explain to her
what didn't happen.
Your being here
isn't helping me.Really, Donald.
.Don't you think you've
taken this joke far enough?
Barbara, listen to me.
This is not a joke.
Catalina's become a very
important part of my life.
[ Laughs ]
You can't be serious!
You and her?
Yes. Me and her.
Believe it or not,
I even like her family.
[ Gasps ]
You poor man.
They've brainwashed you.
This is gonna
get very ugly.
So this is why
you had to come down here?
If you're trying to make
me jealous, it won't work.
Just go home!
And take her with you.Cat, this isn't
how it looks.
She followed me here.Well, good for her.
She can have you.
That's not what I want.You don't know
what you want.
I can't help you
with that.
Just go home.
Go back to where
you belong.
- See, even she knows
what's best for you.
- I'm not leaving without you.
If you're worried about losing
your precious little restaurant,
don't be.
I'll see that
Miguel lets you keep it.
I'm not here because
of the restaurant.
I'm here for you.I saw you two
the other night.
I heard what
you were saying.
Well, you should've stuck around
for the part where I said no.
Nothing happened.
I saw the two of you kissing.
She attacked me.
I-I was an innocent bystander.
.- Noting happened.
- Nothing?
- I wasn't even tempted.
- Really?
Don't be silly.
With what I was wearing,
he had to be tempted.
Yeah, but nothing happened!
It doesn't matter anyway.
The only reason you want
me back is because I left you.
I know the way you think, Oso.
- She's right.
- Would you stop
agreeing with me!
,- It's really starting
to piss me off!
- How very rude!
Rude? I don't think so.
So far, I've been very polite
in this whole thing.
- You don't
wanna see rude, gringa.
- Ladies--
- Are you threatening me?
[ Together ]
What!
Before the catfight
gets into full swing here,
can I just say something?
I've been trying really hard
to talk to both of you,
but neither of you
wants to listen
to what I have to say.
So here it is,
one last time.
Barbara, I want you
to go home.
Catalina, I want you
to come home.
I'm flying home tomorrow.
If you have any feelings
for me at all,
please talk to me
before I go.
Have a pleasant evening.
You handled it very well.
How can you say that?
No injuries.The evening's still young.
You know what
your problem is, Oso?
No, but I have a feeling
you're about to tell me.
You don't know
what you want.I think I do.
No.I know that I need you, Cat.
If you want me to, I'll beg.
I don't want
you to beg.
Well, you could
beg a little.
Please, come with me.
Please! Please! Please!
No.Can we at least
talk about it?
That depends on what
you have to say.
We're just
good together, Cat.That's not good enough.
Tell me
what it is you want.
No, Oso.
You tell me what you want.
I want you.No, you don't.
I just know that
we belong together.
No.
This is where
I belong.
It's a simple life,
but it's my home.
You should go back
to where you belong.
Your fancy cars, your expensive
clothes, your big house.
Let me get one thing clear.
The big house,
the expensive clothes,
the fancy cars, they're--
Well, they're still great.
Look.
None of that matters if
it means I'm gonna lose you.
Oso, if you really
mean that, why didn't you
do something before?
Before I left?I was afraid.
- You were afraid?
- This scares
the hell out of me.
I'm used to being
in control, and all of this
has gotten way out of control.
There's one thing
I do know.
I am in love with you.
Of course you are.
[ Giggles ]
[ Spanish ]
Señora Chandler, good news.
There was a seat available,
and I took the liberty
of reserving it for you.
Thank you.Señora Chandler--
It's a shame
that a beautiful woman as you...
cannot spend
more time here with us.
Oh. Mamacita.
Now it's your turn.My turn?
Yeah, to say
the love word.Um, no.
No?No.
Why?Well, if I said I loved you,
then we'd end up--
And?And Miguel would
take away your restaurant.
True.
Your ex-wife won't give you
any money for a new restaurant.
Listen, Cat, I know
I'll probably lose everything
I used to think was important,
b-but I don't care
about that anymore.
I will mow lawns for a living
if it means coming home to you.
Whoa! Oso, I still
can't trust you.
Catalina, trust me, please.
Listen to
the music of your heart.
Oh, I can hear
the music to my heart, but...
the music to your heart
might change in the morning.
Just do me one small favor.
Just come back
to my bungalow with me.
- Is sex the only thing
you can think of?
- No!
I-It's pretty high on my list
but that's not why
I want you to come back.
- I bought you a present.
- Ah! So now you think
you can bribe me.
Something like that.
You coming?
Hmm, yes. But we'll
keep the door open.
Oh, Donald.
[ Chuckling ]
So what's this gift
you wanna give me?
Well,
it's a surprise.
Surprise!
- That wasn't the surprise
I had in mind.
- You're a very sick man.
I don't know how to explain
what just happened in there.
I don't think I can.
All I want to say
is just trust me.Trust you?
If you care about me at all
just trust me, please.
Give me one good reason
why I should.
I'll give you two.
I'm in love with you.And two?
I haven't given you
your present yet.Better be a damn good one.
Oh, you're gonna like it.
Just give me two minutes
with her.
I give you one minute
and my clock is ticking.
Thank you.
Oh, Donald. You almost
had me fooled.
Then I found
the wedding dress.
And somehow you figured
the dress was for you?
Well, you are already
married to that
Mexican woman.
The only thing I can't
figure out is...
what made you so sure
I'd follow you here?
Uh--Oh!
Barbie, why don't we
slip you out of this dress, and
we'll have a nice little chat.
You want me
to take off the dress?
More than
you could ever guess.
[ Chuckles ]
That's what you want.Yes, that's what I want.
- Time's up.
- ♪ Do, do
- [ Screams ]
- [ Ripping Sound ]
Donald, what are
you doing? Donald!
You do remember how to swim,
don't you, Barbie?
You wouldn't dare!Watch me.
[ Screams ]
[ Laughs ]
I'm beginning
to like that man.
Come.
Stay.I'm just leaving
the door open.
Don't. Our friend out there
might consider it
an invitation.
Oh! I hate this place!
Here.
This is the first part
of your present.
Shoes.
You got me new shoes.
They were supposed
to go... with this.
Barbara was taking too long
so I kind of had
to rip it off her.
Well, it can be fixed, but--
This is a wedding dress.
I know.
You wanna get married?
[ Laughs ]
We're already married.
I mean, really married.
In the eyes of God,
in a church, by a priest.
Come on, Cat.
Make me an honest man.
Oh, Donald, I don't know.
This is so sudden and--
What are you talking about?
We've been walking down
the aisle since we said "I do."
No, but Miguel--
Forget about Miguel.
This is about you and me.
You really do love me,
don't you?
I love you too.
You just said
the love word.I know.
They're here!
Gracias.[ Spanish ]
Aunt Catalina!Hey! Oh!
Come here, little man.Oh, I missed you.
I will never forgive you
for not letting me
give Catalina away.
Would you have
given her to me?
Probably not.
Welcome to the family,
Donald.
I'm so happy
for the both of you!
Just wish that Miguel
wasn't so upset with us.
Miguel--
I'm only angry
at myself.
I've been a fool
playing dictator with
the people I care about.
I hope you guys
will forgive me.
Apology accepted.
I don't suppose
this means, uh,
I can keep my restaurant?
Sorry, Donald. I've
already given the papers
to the new owner.
I didn't think so.
Are we gonna
stay out here all day
or what? Huh?
I'll get your bags.[ Spanish ]
[ Laughs ]
Hey, Miguel.
Donald and I will be staying
in the same bedroom now.
I know. I know.
But first, there's
something I gotta show you.
It's a surprise.Surprise?
Come on. You'll see.
Come on, you guys!Come on.
Surprise!
[ Chattering ]
The first wedding reception
was for Catalina.
This is for
the both of you.
And I have a very special
wedding present for you,
Catalina.
The keys to
Oso's restaurant.[ Gasps ]
It's in your name now,
sweetheart.Miguel!
Gracias.♪♪ [ Latin ]
I love this song. Come, Oso.
Dance with your wife.Yes, dear.
Whoa! Easy!
I'm coming. I'm coming.
♪♪
♪♪ [ Spanish ]
♪ But I don't mind
♪ I don't mind
♪♪ [ Spanish ]
♪ Sometimes life seems to be
♪ So confusing
♪ Out of control
♪ You've got your reasons
♪ For leaving me
♪ I'm still waiting
for a second chance ♪
♪ 'Cause I don't mind
♪ I don't mind
♪♪ [ Spanish ]
waiting for you ♪
♪ I don't mind
♪♪ [ Spanish ]