Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
(♪♪♪)
(Dog barking)
(Driller whirring)
(♪♪♪)
(Sirens wailing in distance)
(Chair squeaks)
You got sad eyes.
Not my usual pick-up line, but...
I just sensed you are a man
running from shadows.
What's your usual pick-up line?
When I see a guy
alone at the bar
at 3:00 in the morning,
I lean in real close
and whisper in his ear:
"For 510 bucks,
we can spend an hour.
For 1,000,
we can spend a night."
Why 510?
'Cause the ATM
only spits out 20s.
I've never had a john ask me
to break a note.
That's actually smart.
So?
(Indistinct chatter
in background)
(♪♪♪)
(Indistinct radio chatter)
(Indistinct chatter)
See that?
(Grunts)
FREEMAN:
Gasoline Alley...
Jimmy Jayne.
(♪♪♪)
(Car whirring)
JIMMY:
You sure about this?
YOUNG WOMAN:
I'm sure, I'm sure.
Okay.
Who's Shelby?
She rocks my world.
You're a lucky gal.
Yeah, we both are.
Right there?
Hold on.
James Jayne?
Yeah.
That's what it says
on my license.
Detective Freeman.
This is Detective Vargas.
Hi.
JIMMY:
Okay.
Yeah, your old man
was on the force, wasn't he?
14th precinct.
Hmm, how's he doing?
I don't think
he's doing much of anything.
Spends his days
at the Fitzgerald Cemetery.
He was a good cop.
Damn good cop.
Always paid his tab.
Did you ever consider the force?
Yeah. You ever think about it?
No, never.
That's yours, right?
I mean, it's my shop's lighter.
Right.
James... sorry,
may I call you, "James"?
The reason that we're here
is we need to talk to you
about the four dead girls.
Okay?
What's that have to do with me?
The lighter,
it was found at the crime scene.
What's your point?
What was it doing there?
I don't know what it's fucking
doing there.
I once found my lighter floating
in a urinal at a Duke's.
Am I a suspect?
VARGAS: You were seen
with one of the victims
at Rocka's, okay.
Thing about Rocka's,
it's over on the other side
of town
and there are 100
good watering holes
in between here and there,
right?
Yeah.
Yeah, again, again,
what's your point?
My point is why drive
all the way over there
like I was saying,
it's a long ways away.
Sentimental reasons.
VARGAS:
Such as?
My mother used to work there.
Okay. Behind the bar?
No, not behind the bar.
Oh.
Uh, Jimmy, excuse my partner.
He still doesn't know what side
of the bed to wake up on.
VARGAS:
He's right.
We have some photos,
maybe you could uh, ID
some of the victims.
That'd be helpful.
Holy shit,
you don't even know their names.
James, we're gonna need to talk
to you in private, okay?
The sooner, the better.
All right, give me an hour.
I got a customer.
No, we need to talk to you
right now,
so the tramp stamp
will have to wait.
How you doin', darlin'?
What you gonna get, a unicorn?
(Chuckles)
(♪♪♪)
FREEMAN:
I hope you can be discrete.
Last thing we need
is a media circus.
Yeah, he's right,
'cause if that happens,
then the D.A.,
he puts pressure on us
to pin it on some poor schmuck.
All right. I'll go ahead
and get started, right, boss?
- Yes.
- Okay.
For the record,
I'm Detective Vargas.
That's Detective Freeman.
And we're conducting
an interview
with Mr. James Jayne
concerning case V-7-7-4-3.
They suffer?
What do you think?
I think it's a fair
fucking question,
that's what I think.
Yeah, they suffered.
I imagine
you already questioned
the guests, staff?
Since 5:00 a.m. this morning.
63 rooms.
VARGAS:
Yeah, nobody suspicious.
Nobody caught our attention,
except you.
Security cameras?
They didn't have any
at the rat trap
they found 'em at,
but they're on camera
leaving the bar.
Then you're on camera
a few seconds later
following 'em out the door.
I had a drink, and I left.
FREEMAN:
What time?
2:30. Give or take.
Talk to anybody
while you were there?
JIMMY:
Yeah.
VARGAS:
What were you doing there?
(Sighs) I was fucking guys.
- FREEMAN: Easy.
- It's just juries,
they don't look real favorably
on uncooperative witnesses.
- Right?
- Right.
Look, why don't you just
show me the pictures?
'Cause something tells me
somebody told you
I was with the girls that night.
You want to see the pictures?
Sure,
we'll show you the pictures.
Pretty sordid.
Let me just start back
at the beginning here.
Here we go.
Huh, pretty gnarly, right?
Gnarly?
Recognize any of them?
Boom, boom, boom,
what you think?
That's pretty bad.
JIMMY:
Go back.
- That's Star.
- VARGAS: Huh.
JIMMY: That's what she told me
her name was.
You ever seen
these girls before?
Not before last night.
You talked to Star,
what about?
- Business.
- What?
- Tattoos or movies?
JIMMY:
She was an actor.
Aspiring actor.
Am I the only suspect?
FREEMAN:
Person of interest.
VARGAS: So Star, I'm assuming
she was a working girl.
Yeah.
Did she make you an offer?
JIMMY:
Of course she did.
VARGAS:
Did you take her up on it?
Or did you try and bargain
with her?
Maybe when you tried
to bargain with her,
you kind of made her feel
a little cheap...
JIMMY:
Fucking what?
VARGAS: Then she said
something nasty, who knows?
Maybe that hurt your feelings,
and then you thought,
"Hey, I'm really gonna let her have it."
- (Overlapping speech)
- Double fucking talk.
Did you hook up with her?
No. I told her I was meeting
with somebody after.
FREEMAN:
And who is that?
This girl I run around with. Christine.
- Okay.
- Are we done here?
No. So I'm just trying to get
all this straight in my head,
- maybe you can help me, boss?
- Yeah.
- So the bar, it closes at 2:30.
- FREEMAN: Right.
VARGAS: That gives you 45 minutes
to kill 'em.
Stage 'em.
Then mosey on over
to this Christine girl.
And you asked,
"Did they suffer?"
Their necks were broken.
All four of 'em.
Of course,
that's not real difficult.
When you got poor helpless girls
all whacked out on
junk and blow,
God knows what else.
Now the only
suspect description we got
is of a Caucasian shitkicker.
You seen any of those lately?
Get the fuck out of my shop.
I actually think we're done here
and we probably don't need
to tell you this,
but don't leave the country,
hell, don't leave the county.
We can haul you in
on a Ramey warrant
anytime, okay.
So yeah, you're still a suspect,
got it?
Don't worry,
if you get found guilty,
we'll walk you down
to the electric chair ourselves.
It's like that
old gospel number,
You'll Never Walk Alone.
Let's hit it, boss.
Good talking to you.
Nice spot.
(♪♪♪)
(Grunts)
Fuck!
(Indistinct chatter
in background)
Christine.
Hey.
One sec, come here.
You get my text?
Cops calling on me at work
ain't a good look, Jimmy.
They wanted to confirm you
were on your way to see me
last night.
What'd you say?
I told 'em, yeah.
The bald one,
he thought I'd be all bent
about you flirting
with those poor girls.
I told 'em, nah,
it ain't like that.
He flirts with everybody,
that's what makes him Jimmy.
Attagirl.
The other one,
he acts all best friends
bonding shit,
wasn't shy about doing
a little flirting himself.
Fuckin' asshole.
(Laughter, chatter
in background)
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Whoa, whoa.
- Oh God.
- Whoa.
- All right.
- Whoa, whoa.
(♪♪♪)
ANCHORMAN 1 ON TV:
Coming up on Eye Witness News,
the DEA have discovered
another tunnel connecting
Tijuana to a residence
in San Diego,
the longest yet at 4.2 miles.
More on the investigation
into the Four Beauty murders.
Police are searching
for answers.
Those stories and more
coming up.
(Exhales)
DISPATCH OFFICER 1 ON PHONE:
Precinct.
Yeah, Detective Freeman please.
It's Jimmy Jayne.
Connecting.
(Woman coughs)
(Cellphone vibrating)
DISPATCH OFFICER 1 ON PHONE:
Precinct.
Vargas, please.
Jimmy Jayne.
Connecting.
VARGAS:
Hey, James.
JIMMY ON PHONE:
Where's Freeman?
Yeah, Freeman's at a deposition
right now.
What do you want?
Anything more on the four girls?
VARGAS:
No comment.
JIMMY ON PHONE:
So you got nothing.
VARGAS ON PHONE:
It's an ongoing investigation.
And no other suspects but me?
Let's just say
you're a person of interest
and we'll leave it at that.
Okay?
You think I did it?
Hey, the evidence
says what it says.
I'm gonna text you my number
and if you think of anything,
well, don't be a stranger.
That cool? Good.
MAN 1 ON TV: Coming this fall,
blockbuster story continues
Sunday night, 7:00 p.m.
Starring Faith Hope
and Dennis Bourke.
American Siege.
BOURKE ON PHONE: JJ, the man,
the myth, the legend!
What's good, bro?
I need to see you.
Of course, bro,
anything for you.
You want to uh,
meet up next week?
No, today would be better.
Uh, I'm on set, bro.
All right, text me the address,
call your security,
let 'em know I'm coming by.
Okay, tight.
Uh hey, hey, bring your kit.
Yeah, all right. Whatever.
All right, dope.
(Gun blaring)
(♪♪♪)
Wait, cut! Cut the fucking shot.
Can someone get this asshole
out of my eyeline?
Again, dude. It happened again!
Fucking day,
it's something else.
Jesus, what the fuck...
(Indistinct chatter
in background)
Goddamn rookies.
What's up, big dog?
See me looking like a badass,
shooting these fucking guns.
They should let me shoot
a real one, huh?
Ain't gonna make the show
easier to watch.
(Chuckles)
I know you didn't just come here
to bruise my ego.
Rub your paycheck on it,
that'll make it feel better.
Yeah, that's good.
All right, Jimmy,
what's the favor?
You're in the scene, right?
I do okay. It's not really
your vibe though,
if that's what you're asking.
Don't use that tone of voice
with me.
Remember who kept you safe
on the inside.
Yeah, I know.
You know how grateful I am that
you protected me
when I was in there.
I bet your friends think
you're tough
doing three months hard time
for a fucking DUI or whatever.
I wonder what they'd say
if they find out
you cried yourself
to sleep every night
worried Kratos from Cell Block E
was gonna make you
his little fucking bitch.
I'm grateful
that you fucked him up for me.
How grateful?
Anything for a friend, Jimmy.
Got your kit?
Yeah.
Okay.
Yeah, all right.
Come on.
Heard they're already planning
a rip-off episode
about the dead girls.
Bullshit.
I swear to God.
The writer's PA with the fat ass
told me last night.
That is tasteless.
I knew one of 'em.
From where?
Some party.
Whose?
Persi Muleeney, something.
Get the fuck outta here.
That's a made-up name.
I swear to God, man,
she was all over me.
What was her name?
BOURKE: She didn't tell me
her real name.
Don't tell me.
"If you forget..."
BOURKE:
"...you just gotta look up."
- JIMMY: Yeah.
- BOURKE: You knew Star?
Briefly.
Tell me about the guy
running the party.
BOURKE: Persi? I... I didn't know
it was his party.
Finds girls on OnlyFans
and Craigslist,
turns 'em into porn stars
and escorts.
They float around the scene
for a little bit
then they just disappear,
that's all I know.
What do you mean disappear?
BOURKE: I mean they go back
to bumfuck Idaho
wherever the hell
they came from.
Man, this J-bird
fucking with you?
No, man, we're all right,
aren't we?
- Are we?
- Yeah, we're good.
BOURKE:
This is Jimmy Jayne.
This guy's a motherfucking
legend right here.
- True genius.
- Pleasure to meet you.
Oh, so you guys inside together?
- How'd you know?
- Come on, man.
'Cause all your other friends
that come here,
look like Ken dolls.
No offense.
BOURKE: Yeah, fucking right
we were in.
This dude did half the art
in San Quentin.
Why don't you tell him
about the time
I fucked up Kratos in the yard?
You know the story.
Yeah, I remember that, sure.
He was uh... he was fresh meat.
Wouldn't let anybody
fuck with him, so he beat a man
unconscious on his first night
with his bare hands.
Yeah.
Bullshit.
- That's a fucking lie.
- It's a lie.
ROY:
Hey, but you're a great friend
to try to make this
punk-ass look good.
Hey, you can't talk to me
like that, bro.
You're a fucking set mechanic.
I'm number one
on the call sheet, all right.
Calm down, kid. Calm down.
You took this gig for money
just like everybody else.
We're making art, all right.
- Art?
- Yeah.
This show makes a dumpster fire
look like Citizen Kane.
Yeah, well, this show
is number one in the country,
we are number one.
That says more about society
than the quality of your show.
Hey, listen,
I have a 66 Chevelle
that's got a bum clutch.
- You got a card?
- Yeah.
- Here man, call me anytime.
- Thank you.
- You guys good?
- Yes, sir.
Where you wanna do this?
Well, I want 1-1-7 right here.
It's how many people watched
last week's episode.
117?
Million, yeah.
I know, I can't believe people
pay to watch this shit either.
Let's go in my trailer.
FILM CREW MEMBER 1:
Action!
(Thud)
- Dennis!
- Hey, dude.
Dennis, up!
Oh, shoot!
(Gun blaring)
Fuck you, motherfuckers!
(♪♪♪)
Hi.
Now what?
Well, found your fingerprints
on your lighter.
JIMMY:
Who'd have thought?
And?
We got motive, we got access,
and we're one hair follicle away
from writing your warrant.
How'd you find me?
VARGAS: You got a GPS
in your pocket, buddy.
(Vargas chuckling)
You need a warrant
to track a phone.
You know you're actually correct
about that.
But the thing is judges
these days, they're real busy
and they know
we're the good guys.
So they kinda let it slide.
Now, you gonna offer me
a cigarette or what?
No, it's cool, I actually quit.
Here's the deal.
Everybody I talk to
across the board,
they all say
you're a stand-up guy,
except for the five years
in the pen
for putting a guy
in a wheelchair.
I didn't start that fight.
But you sure ended it,
didn't you?
And I bet you'd do it
all over again.
Came at me with a screwdriver.
Screwdriver.
Shit, that's a deadly weapon.
You know a guy named Persi?
I don't remember his last name.
Fucking Persi something,
whatever.
Why?
Used to run with Star.
You playing detective now?
Just concerned citizen.
I like that.
You know, uh, I found out
why you hang out at Rocka's bar.
Should have just told me
your mom was a working gal.
There's no shame in it.
Detective Freeman,
he told me that was her spot
until, you know,
she went missing.
And of course, your dad,
he lost his mind
trying to find her.
I'm just saying, you know,
I... I get it.
I understand why you feel
so connected to the case.
Sure do have a way with words.
Hey pal, James, Jimmy,
I uh... you know,
that's as close
as you're gonna get
to an apology from me.
Yeah, fine, well...
I have to go.
Just, hey, take it easy.
Let us do our thing.
Detective Freeman,
he's a great cop
and me, I'm the best thing
that ever happened
to the Robbery-Homicide Unit.
How many cases
you close last year?
You want my numbers now?
You want my stats?
I mean, if they were any good,
you'd be squawking about 'em.
Oh, come on.
You speak to Star's family?
Tell 'em what happened?
Well, they disowned her
a long time ago,
but they're raising her kid
as their own.
How old?
4. Actually the same age
as my boy Terry.
James, just don't go kicking
the hornet's nest.
'Course not.
- You understand?
- Yes.
Okay. I'll catch you later.
(♪♪♪)
(Engine rumbling)
(Gun blares)
(Car revving)
(♪♪♪)
(Gun blares)
(Engine rumbling)
(♪♪♪)
ROY:
Hey man, don't fuck that paint.
I can't be assed with an
L & D form.
(Cellphone ringing)
You got Roy.
Roy, it's Jimmy.
I met you on set.
Hey, buddy, what's going on?
Someone tried to run me down
just now.
No shit.
Someone tried to kill you?
Yeah. (Indistinct speech)
That's not
what makes it personal,
so much as they fucked up
my ride.
Holy shit, man!
You know who it was?
If I did, I wouldn't say so
on the phone.
You know what, it's nothing.
It don't sound like nothing
to me, man,
but what's it like to be you?
It was a Rover Wagon.
It was super charged.
Had some real fucking
balls to it.
Still not the smartest way
to try to kill somebody.
Yeah, maybe they're smarter
than you think, man.
Random ex-con cut down
on the side of the road?
Who'd give a shit?
Yeah, that's one way to put it,
I guess.
Rover's a lot bigger
than a bullet though, bro.
Oh no, they came at me
with those, too.
Listen...
I got this feeling that
you might be able to uh,
you know, get me
some sort of protection.
You know what I'm talking about?
10-4, good buddy.
I know you're a kindred soul
of the heathen brethren.
I'm gonna take that as a yes.
Of course it's a yes, man.
Send me the address.
I'll text it to you.
VARGAS:
So this doesn't add up.
How does Jimmy go
from felony assault
to multiple homicides?
I don't get it.
- The old days...
- Yeah.
You told me about, you'd just
taken a telephone book to 'em.
Now I gotta actually
question people
- and go fucking by the book.
- Right.
(Vargas chuckles)
- Yeah.
- Pain in the ass.
- Well...
- Mhmm.
I guess I'll take care
of this here,
- you gonna hit the game?
- Yeah.
VARGAS:
Who is it this week?
- Malibu.
- Right.
If they don't beat them,
who can they beat?
- Yeah.
- (Chuckles)
Exactly.
I'll take care of this,
all right.
- All right.
- I got it.
I hope they win.
(Sighs)
I didn't think you'd show.
Every brother needs a keeper
from time to time.
Are you sure you want this?
I got someone trying to pin
a bunch of murders on me.
I'm not going back inside,
especially not for something
I didn't do.
Easy, new friend, easy.
The fuck am I into?
Show business, son.
It's the most gangster game
out there.
You got family?
No, not since my dad died.
Hmm, how'd he go?
Bottle.
Hmm.
Come here, let's do this.
Your dad teach you how to shoot?
All right.
You got six rounds in there.
There you go.
How much do I owe you?
Nothing, man.
Just a favor down the line.
All right.
Anytime.
Yeah, I'll hold you to that.
But you be careful, man.
- See you.
- Thank you.
(♪♪♪)
(Sighs)
I may have to get out of town.
We should go somewhere.
Huh, I got that ticket
to Berlin, baby.
What ticket?
I didn't tell you?
I would have remembered.
I'm leaving Monday.
Sandy is there as an au pair,
we'll hang,
I hear it's a good scene.
Berlin?
It's in Germany.
Yeah.
(Chuckles)
You live in the moment, Jimmy.
Yeah.
Fucking Berlin.
(Chuckles)
(Slurping)
Jimmy Jayne.
What's up, buddy?
- How you doing?
- Good.
I need a favor.
(Scoffs)
You know I can't get back
into the evidence locker.
They won't let me back there.
- It's not that kind of favor.
- What is it?
I need you to run a name
through IVIS.
What's the name?
Oh fuck.
Uh...
Peter Mul...
Persi Mul, something or other.
Mul something.
What is that?
Persi Muleeney?
That's it.
(Scoffs)
Man, he lives up on Mulholland.
He's got an office down
on Skid Row.
You know him?
Yeah, everybody knows him.
He's a popular guy.
Give me a current address.
(Pete sighs)
Look, man, is this something
that's gonna come back
- and bite me in the ass?
- No, never.
- Yeah.
- Absolutely not.
Yeah, I believe you again, huh?
Look, man, you know
I'll lie on the stand, right,
say you had a gun to my head.
That's why I love you, brother.
You really are LA's finest,
huh?
Aww, that's sweet.
Fuck you, too.
(Jimmy chuckles)
Can you tell me
what he's driving?
Seems his 2011 Land Rover
was reported stolen yesterday.
You didn't get that from me.
He's having a party
up at his place tonight.
Lot of cops gonna be there,
'cause we get in free.
Yeah.
Seems he knows what lives
matter most.
All right.
Stay lucky, buddy.
Next time have the decency
to buy me a fucking coffee.
(♪♪♪)
(Car engine revving)
KAISER:
Private party tonight.
I'm on the list.
You a cop?
Yeah, 14th.
Where's your badge?
It's in the car.
(Sighs)
(♪♪♪)
(Water splashes)
STAR:
Want to hear a bad joke?
A bad joke?
A really bad one.
(Jimmy chuckles)
I do want to hear a bad joke.
Shoot.
What are the three words
to ruin man's ego?
to ruin a man's ego?
Is it in?
(♪♪♪)
(Snorting)
(Sniffles)
PERSI:
So it's like '88, '89.
We're driving to Barstow
like 3:00 in the morning, right.
We're sweating like bullets,
and we run out of cocaine
and I mean me and Tai,
we're sweating. We're sitt-
Only thing I know is
we're gonna go meet
a one-armed dope dealer
with a good...
Yo. You Persi?
I don't even know your name,
friend?
Jimmy Jayne.
Mind if I have a minute?
Mind if I have a...
Yeah, well, I mind.
I'm sitting here telling a story
to all my friends.
Is this about a job
or something?
Yeah, I'm sorry.
Go ahead, finish your story.
You were with a couple of dudes
or something?
So it's Barstow. Three-
Barstow! Holy shit,
I love Barstow.
You do, you love...
They had the swap meet
down there, you ever been?
I been to Barstow,
I never been
to a fucking swap meet.
- Street rods mostly.
- Yeah.
JIMMY:
I'm sorry.
Go on. Finish your story.
It's like 3:00 in the morning,
going into Barstow...
JIMMY:
Wait, wait, wait.
Going into the Torches Motel...
JIMMY: Wait, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa.
You're ruining my story.
One thing,
they got this red-headed mayor,
I'm fucking telling you,
she's got big fucking tits.
And man, she loves to ride.
She loves to ride, huh?
Who the fuck invited you
to my party?
I invited me.
I was hoping to have a minute
in private,
but suit yourself.
Gisella, Lana, and Star.
You ever heard
those names before?
I'll give you a hint.
They're not fucking race horses.
Kaiser, get this motherfucker
out of here.
JIMMY:
Hold on, Kaiser.
You ever met 'em?
No, I can't say I have.
You like jokes?
Yeah, who don't like
a fucking joke.
If this is a joke,
I don't find it funny.
JIMMY: I'ma tell you...
I'ma tell you a joke.
Three words to ruin a man's ego?
"Is it in?"
Now get the fuck out.
You heard that one before.
Yeah, I heard,
I'm the one who wrote it.
'Cause this girl told it
to me the other night.
PERSI:
What girl?
Same girl
you said you never met.
She heard it in my movie.
I just told you,
David Cop-A-Feel. It's...
Anybody who watches pornos,
watch... knows the fucking line.
It's famous.
Now get the fuck out of here!
Of course it is.
Night, guys.
Is that coke?
And they're fucking passed out?
PERSI:
Yeah, I got fucking coke.
JIMMY:
Can I rip a line of blow?
You get the fuck
out of my house,
you can't have none!
Oh to be you, huh.
Small dick motherfucker.
- You really a cop?
- No.
I seen them here, those girls.
Come with a sista I knows.
Eleanor Rogers.
She's one, uh,
20 feet from stardom types.
Backup singer.
Preacher's daughter.
Why you telling me this?
The fuck?
Motherfucker, I'm telling you.
Leave it at that.
Get the fuck outta here.
Thanks.
(Car engine rumbling)
(♪♪♪)
(Indistinct singing)
(Humming)
That was you singing, huh?
Guilty.
It's a recording studio?
I'm looking for Miss Rogers.
Miss Eleanor Rogers.
Why?
Our mutual friend Kaiser says
we should talk.
About?
About something
we're both involved in,
we shouldn't be.
I'll be at Shay's on 3rd, okay.
Hey, you got a light?
Yeah.
Don't lose it.
There's already enough
of those floating around.
ELEANOR:
You don't mean Persi Muleeney?
Nah, he ain't got it in him
to murder any girls like that.
He ain't that slick.
But he knows some fucking cats
doing some fucked up shit.
What cats?
He likes to strut
with a scary crowd
with his tail all up in the air.
But as much as he likes to be
on this gangsta shit,
they just take his money
and laugh at his dumb white ass.
Drug people?
Fuck yeah.
Cartel hookup.
Why's someone like you
hanging out
with someone shady like Persi?
Someone like me?
He told me
he'd put up all kinds of money
to help me put out a solo album.
And did he?
No.
Said if I could fuck like
I could sing...
Well, I'm not even gonna
tell you the rest of that
'cause I don't want
my father's ghost
hearing that
come out of my mouth.
Persi said
he never met the girls.
Oh, honey, no, no, he lied.
What else?
Those girls, I mean,
oh my God,
the way they were found
like that, I mean,
that was somebody sending
a message.
You said that wasn't
Persi's style.
No, no.
I think it was...
it was like those people
I was talking about earlier,
the ones that likes to use
Persi's house like it's theirs.
"Scary crowd".
Shit, you ain't heard this
from me.
That scene is a blackhole.
Girls come up missing
all the time,
guys always trying
to take advantage
of the situation.
There was this one creeper
at a party one night.
Late like 4:00 in the morning.
Silver-haired dude.
Now we were gonna go
to the patio and get high.
Anyway, the silver-haired dude
was inside
and I saw him talking to some
girls who had been there,
I'd seen them a couple of times
and they were giving him money.
About a week later,
I'm pulled over
for not using my turn signal,
and it was him,
the silver-haired dude.
He's a fucking cop.
- Is he a stocky guy?
- Yes, yeah.
Uh, Flosso.
Officer Flosso,
that was the name on the ticket.
JIMMY:
Right, right.
ELEANOR: The girl said
he was a cage fighter.
Our friend Kaiser,
I need to talk to him again.
Well, I'll give you his number,
but, you know,
don't expect much.
He's a moody motherfucker,
like you.
Oh, one more thing,
and maybe it's nothing
but the silver-haired guy,
I saw him take some money
and then give it to this guy,
the "Doc".
Well, we called him
"Dr. Feelgood",
because, you know,
he was giving out
pills like it was candy.
Big beard
and the curly-ish hair,
deep voice, like...
I don't fucking know,
that also happened.
I don't know if that helps.
I wish I'd met you a week ago.
Oh, what do you do?
What do I do?
Yeah?
Um, uh, a lotta this, lately.
No, when you're not creeping
on singers outside of studios.
Did you say creeping?
I...
Um, what do I do?
- I do uh, I do tattoos.
- Hmm.
And uh... motors.
- Hmm, rock 'n' roll life.
- Yeah.
- Very cool.
- It's right.
It's good people mostly.
- Yeah.
- You got any ink?
Oh man, no.
I never found anything that
I wanted to stay with me
for life, you know.
Oh.
Sometimes a tattoo
is just a tattoo.
Okay, well then how come
most girls get a rose
or a dolphin?
Fucking angel wings.
- How trashy is that?
- Touché.
- It's so trashy, right.
Yeah, well, you know
times are... times are tough.
Ink is ink.
Oh, and that's when you do
those kind of tattoos.
I draw the line at tramp stamps.
- Oh.
- (Laughing)
Well, it is good to know
there's a line.
Yeah, there is.
No, they all mean something.
- It's not gonna run out on you.
- No.
That's a different story,
probably a different tattoo.
(Cellphone dings)
Oh, I have to go.
That is my 15.
I've got an audition.
Mm?
Uh I hope that this helped.
Changed my day around.
Oh, fine.
Maybe I'll see you around.
- Good luck on your audition.
- Thank you.
You're welcome.
(♪♪♪)
Meet me behind the station.
I have something to show you.
(Snorting)
(Cellphone ringing)
(Coughs)
Yo.
Yeah, we've... we've been
shooting all night.
Jayne busted into my party
the other night,
asking me about Star
and the others.
Nah, I didn't tell him shit.
The asshole ruined my high.
You gotta be cool, bro.
There's some girls here.
(Snorts, coughs)
(Knocking on door)
Yeah, I still got 'em,
come on up.
Okay, cool.
(Knocking on door)
Hey, yo, what...
what are you doing here?
You don't... you can't just come
over to my office like this.
(♪♪♪)
(Grunting, moaning in distance)
ERASMUS: Looking for Persi?
All the way down to the left.
(indistinct speech)
Bye, Juicy.
(♪♪♪)
(Screams)
Hey.
FREEMAN:
What is it, Jimmy?
You're gonna wanna see this.
FREEMAN:
What?
You need to move your car
before we get it towed.
Yeah, I could move it.
I could drive it
right to the morgue.
What are you talking about?
Who's pulling the strings?
Who could throw the body
of a giant in a trunk
without nobody seeing?
Whoever did it,
picked the locks
in the parking lot on Franklin
where they threw the body.
In broad daylight?
They did it sometime
in the morning
while I was having breakfast.
You've been tracking my cell,
you know
I couldn't have done this.
VARGAS:
I don't know, buddy.
I think somebody's seriously
fucking with you, big time.
Or warning me.
Maybe they knew Kaiser
was trying to help me.
Yeah.
Now don't you think
the smart thing to do
would have been to tell us
about this when the Land Rover
first tried to run you down?
I've never been accused
of being smart.
Right.
What about your visit
to Persi's party?
Persi had nothing to do with it.
He's just a bad host.
If I were you,
I would check the people
at the Chateau party,
that's where I'd start.
Sorry, buddy,
afraid we have to keep the car.
Okay. Well, don't scratch it.
Don't fuck with the radio.
No scratch, no problem.
Who's driving me home?
I'll drive you home.
Hey, no smoking in the cruiser.
It's regulations.
All right,
have a couple of puffs,
I'll wait.
What a fucking day, man.
Yeah, me too.
Persi's dead.
Yeah, I know,
a real loss to humanity.
How'd he go?
VARGAS:
Snapped neck.
Now look, I'm only gonna
tell you this once,
I don't think you're involved
in this
any more than somebody
wants you to be.
Okay.
I'm next.
I think you're right.
JIMMY:
How's that?
You know something
you don't even know you know.
Or somebody wants you to know
something, you know.
Let's hit it.
Put that out.
(Vargas grunts)
(Birds chirping)
So this how you live?
Yeah,
Dad left me the house.
Mortgaged to get the shop,
couldn't make the payment, closed,
told the family moving in that this
is a separate property.
So what, they can kick you out
anytime they want?
I don't know, James.
All right, concerned citizen,
why don't you tell me
who you think's involved?
Flosso.
Flosso?
JIMMY:
He's an ex-fighter.
Huh.
He'd certainly know how to
break their necks clean enough.
So this preacher's daughter,
your source,
she for certain it was him?
Yeah,
he's working for somebody.
Well, that makes sense,
'cause Flosso,
he's a real dumb shit.
He wouldn't be able to do it
on his own.
I'll look him up,
I'll see what I can find.
Hey Vargas,
how well you know your partner?
Why you ask?
'Cause I think he's dirty.
I think he found my lighter
and thought I was an easy mark.
You're reaching, buddy.
And you better be careful
what you're saying.
He have an alibi?
Matter of fact he does.
He was half in the bag
over at the Montello.
How're the cameras at the
Montello Lounge?
- They're good.
- Yeah?
Yeah.
If you check the video footage
and you see him
leaving between 2:00 and 2:30,
then I was right.
And if I'm right,
I just wanna know about it.
No. All right,
no more cowboy shit.
I'll take a look at the tapes,
but I can already tell you
what I'm gonna find, okay.
And by the way,
you're all wrong about Freeman.
He's a good guy,
he's my kid's godfather.
Hitler loved dogs.
Huh.
What's your point?
My point is
some of the most evil people
in the world
still have great smiles.
That's interesting.
Just do me a favor.
Stand down, all right.
You done enough, okay?
It's depressing.
(♪♪♪)
JIMMY:
What's your name?
STAR:
Star.
If you forget, just look up.
(♪♪♪)
(Sighs)
(Bike engine rumbling)
The shit's vegan, right?
Makeup? It's vegan?
Go check.
It's in my contract,
vegan makeup!
(♪♪♪)
Don't fucking say anything,
I'm mic'd.
Okay, you know
what it looks like... I'm fr...
Shut the fuck up!
Shut up!
You lied to me.
You lie to me again,
I'll break your fucking face,
you understand?
- You understand?
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
- Okay.
Tell me about Persi.
Fuck, man.
I was embarrassed to admit
that I was hanging with Persi
'cause he is a fucking scumbag,
okay.
But it's not illegal to drink
his booze and eat his food,
not to mention, fucking pussy
flying around that place.
I mean, anything goes there.
Like what?
Some local cops there
hanging out now,
playing poker in the back.
That's not all that's going on
back there.
Yeah, I heard a few pimped
some girls,
but that's none
of my fucking business.
I had nothing to do
with those dead hookers.
Star and her friends,
did they go to this party?
Yeah, man, I said that,
I seen them there a few times
but there's 50 fucking girls
there every night.
You wanna talk to someone?
Talk to Erasmus.
Am I supposed to know
who that is?
Erasmus Alcindor.
He's a screenwriter.
He's a fucking hack,
looks like a ferret.
He used to date Star.
Look, I don't know
why they dated either,
she's a fucking beautiful girl
messing around
with some fucking creep.
He used to lie to her
and say he'd put her in movies.
He talks to that cop Flosso,
all the time.
Where can I find him?
Erasmus?
He lives in those shithole apartments
in Persi's studios.
I swear to fucking God, man.
Fuck God,
I swear to you, okay?
He knows everything about
their operation.
Everything.
I swear to you,
I swear, I swear, I...
Listen, listen,
you little bitch.
- You gonna lie to me again?
- No.
- No, I'm not gonna lie again!
No!
(♪♪♪)
Erasmus?
Go away!
Are you fucking deaf?
He's not here.
This can go one of two ways.
You watch who you're throwing insults
out of your word-hole to,
you... you...
the wrong person hears it,
and you'll be in a fucking
cheap hotel room dead,
you hear me?
(Grunts)
ERASMUS:
Fuck, man.
I'm a pacifist!
Fuck.
I'm not.
You going somewhere?
Babylon has fallen,
can't you see
it's the last days of Rome?
You want to know what I see?
I see a piece of shit
who's in way over his head
who's gonna tell me
all about his girlfriend.
Which one?
You know which one.
Fucking Star.
Star's not my girlfriend,
you sperm-less testicle,
she's my friend.
Alright, women, I'm not a threat
to them, they trust me,
they bare
their midnight fantasies,
their hopes and dreams.
(Grunts in pain)
Alright, I'm telling you
that she was an angel! Star.
They should've called her
"The-Whole-fucking-Galaxy".
Who killed her?
It's not that simple, man.
She was...
it's not that simple.
She was blackmailing us...
them, them!
That's not an admission
of guilt.
- She was blackmailing them.
- Who?
I tried to stop her,
but she brought the others
- in on it.
- Who?
All the girls, man.
Persi used to run drugs
up from Mexico.
He had to find a way
to launder the money,
so he got in the film business
and then he started
trafficking girls,
all the girls
who wanna be in his movies.
Didn't ask for a fucking resume.
Tell me who killed Star.
ERASMUS:
Flosso, man.
They always used Flosso to keep
the girls in line.
Don't fucking lie to me.
- (Indistinct speech)
- Don't fucking lie to me.
Half the fucking precinct
is in it, man.
How you think they wear
such nice suits?
I want names.
Goddammit, Flosso is a name!
Flosso is a name.
Who ordered the hit?
Who ordered the hit!
He'll kill me.
I'll fucking kill you.
Who ordered the hit?
ERASMUS:
Freeman.
- Detective...
- Don't fucking lie to me, man.
ERASMUS:
I'm telling the truth, man.
I overheard him
and Persi talking.
It's... it's not killing women
to them, man.
It's more like clearing out
rotten inventory.
Like difficult women
make bad hookers, man.
And you were...
you were the perfect fall guy.
You screwed everything up,
man.
Now Flosso's in the wind
and they want us all dead.
How are you involved?
Me, I'm just a writer, man.
I schedule the girls.
I make sure
they have a good time.
I take care of the girls,
that's it.
And Vargas?
You seen him around?
Freeman keeps him in the dark,
man.
Vargas is the worst detective
in the city.
(Cellphone ringing)
I'm going to my mom's.
I should have never left
Glendale.
Yeah.
Just pulled up.
What are you talking about?
To the parlor.
Rent here on Melrose
must be outrageous.
Wait, what?
Jimmy, you just texted me
15 minutes ago
- saying to meet you here.
- No. No, hey run.
Get out of there.
Get the fuck out of there.
(grunting)
JIMMY ON PHONE:
Hey? Hey!
(Cellphone ringing)
- JIMMY ON PHONE: Vargas?
- Hey, where are you, Jimmy?
Freeman's mixed
into this for sure.
Yeah, fuck, I know that.
Look,
I just went to The Montello.
They already handed over
their tapes to guess who?
Yeah.
So listen, Star, she worked
the concession stand
at this old movie theatre.
She sent an encrypted file
to her boss.
Forensics, they're trying
to unlock it right now, okay.
Hey, that source
I told you about,
the preacher's daughter,
she somehow got a text
from my phone.
I was talking to her
when she was abducted.
Hold on, okay.
We're gonna get an APB out.
Also a bystander ID'd Flosso
leaving the scene
where Star and her friends
were found.
You understand that?
You speak to your captain
about the tapes?
Look, I haven't talked
to anybody yet.
Where was she?
She's right outside my shop.
Okay, listen,
I'm gonna roll units over
right now.
Do not go inside, Jimmy.
- You hear me?
- Oh no.
Do not engage.
Okay.
(♪♪♪)
(Grunting)
(Flosso shouts)
(♪♪♪)
(Both grunting)
(Flosso shouting)
(Grunts)
(♪♪♪)
(Sirens wailing in distance)
VARGAS:
Cuff him.
(Indistinct radio chatter)
Fuck you!
(Flosso grunting)
(♪♪♪)
(Cellphone vibrating)
(Breathing heavily)
(Telephone ringing)
Farry.
VARGAS ON PHONE:
Captain.
You alone?
- Yeah, what's going on?
- All right.
It's Freeman,
gotta bring him in.
He's dirty.
Just busted Flosso.
He was trying to kill a witness.
Got it?
Fuck, he just left.
(Indistinct radio chatter)
(Spits)
What's your hurry, Bill?
(Gun blares)
So stupid.
Where they take her?
FLOSSO:
I don't know.
I could drive this thing
into the Pacific,
or you can give me an
exact address.
You're gonna die anyways.
Now you can lie to me,
I can make it real slow,
or you can tell me the truth
and maybe I'll make it fast.
Maybe.
I didn't want any of this.
It was Freeman.
Fucking Freeman caught me
with a gram.
One gram.
Told me he'd get IA
to take my badge away
and put me away for three years
if I didn't work for him.
You killed Star?
Yeah, I did.
Where's Eleanor?
San Diego.
They got a restaurant,
a fridge leads to a tunnel.
JIMMY:
What's this tunnel?
The kind of tunnel that connects
San Diego with Tijuana.
Freeman runnin' the operation?
FLOSSO:
Fuck no.
It's some broker, Dr. Feelgood.
He's a dangerous cat
though, man.
He's got eyes everywhere.
- Hey.
- Hmm.
I tell you where they are,
I'll take you to 'em,
you gotta let me go.
It's a fair trade, right?
Yeah.
Okay.
- Hey!
- Stop that car!
POLICEMEN:
Hey!
(Indistinct shouting)
Okay, took a left.
(♪♪♪)
I told you to be ready.
I do not work to your schedule,
detective.
Where's Flosso?
As soon as we get safe,
he's next.
She's doped up
and ready for transport.
Buyers pay well
for American girls, age aside.
Just make sure I get my cut.
(♪♪♪)
This the place?
Yeah.
Fridge's in the back.
Now you're gonna let me go,
right?
Man of your word.
Yeah.
(Grunts)
(Flosso yells)
(Grunting)
(♪♪♪)
Stop, stop!
- Stop!
- (Gun blares)
In here!
(Gun blares)
(Men shouting)
(♪♪♪)
(Eleanor grunting)
JIMMY:
Freeman, you prick!
Hey, I can get you
whatever you want.
Money, girls.
FREEMAN:
You motherfucker.
You know the damage you've done?
I have an idea.
I have a family.
I worked for my life.
Kill!
(Guns blaring)
(Grunts)
Hey, hey.
Don't... don't... don't...
don't you do it!
FREEMAN:
You motherfucker.
(grunts)
(Body thudding)
(Freeman breathing heavily)
(Grunting)
Jimmy.
(Taking deep breaths)
It's okay.
Wasn't supposed to...
(Freeman coughs)
...to end like this.
(Exhales)
Say hi to my mom.
(♪♪♪)
FREEMAN:
Please don't do it.
Not this way.
I'm sorry, Jimmy.
(♪♪♪)
Who is that?
Identify yourself!
Where's Freeman? Huh?
Where's Freeman?
What happened out there?
Your son's gonna need
a new godfather.
(Eleanor grunting)
JIMMY: What are the three words
to ruin a man's ego?
Is it in?
- I know it's funny.
- Yeah, no.
- 'Cause it's true.
- I bet, I bet.
Where you from?
Very far away from here.
JIMMY:
You here for the movies?
Real movies.
But I just arrived.
I worked in a theatre,
but they don't show
the kinda movies I'm in now.
Oh?
The theatre manager was such
a nice guy.
Not like my new bosses.
They are,
how do you say... pigs.
You like that work?
No.
(Indistinct chattering
in background)
Can you work a front desk?
Can you type?
Why?
My secretary left
with my business partner.
- Things happen.
Things happen.
(Indistinct chattering
in background)
Be there tomorrow,
you got a job.
I mean no pressure.
Jimmy Jayne.
JIMMY:
Thanks for being
such a good guy.
I don't know about that.
Persi wants us.
He has a car outside already.
Yeah.
Hey, what's your name?
Star.
If you forget, just look up.
Hey. Bye Star.
(Indistinct chatter
in background)
Star...
(Sighs)
Thank you.
(♪♪♪)