Looking back on the horrific events
that happened on your family farm,
do you ever worry that
they never found the body?
It's a fear I live with every day.
Hmm.
Speaking of fear, do you also fear
that he may come after you?
You know, for some type
of revenge or retaliation?
I personally don't.
Total random act of violence.
- Mm-hmm.
- Could have been anyone.
Just so, it happened to be us.
Wrong place, wrong time,
but totally random.
You know, there is a big hysteria
about what happened to you guys
And Adam, it's, it's
interesting that you talk
about random acts of violence.
It wasn't long ago, I
was reading some material
that talked about out,
sometimes violence incites more violence.
Do you think that the
actions of Colin Miller
would inspire more acts
of random violence?
I would hope that wouldn't be the case,
but in today's society,
people do tend to feed
off negative energy.
- Mm.
- So while I hope
that doesn't happen, I
could see where others
could tap into the darkness
that possessed Colin Miller.
It's a scary world we live in.
This is it. Don't be chickenshit.
Come on. We've talked
about this for days.
Myles, you're scared of
your own fucking shadow.
I am not, Maddy.
No going back now.
No going back.
I wonder if there'll be a lot of blood.
Hopefully.
Is it necessary to
always make that noise
every time you brush your teeth?
What's up with the kids?
What do you mean?
Eh, there's something off.
Look who their father is.
There's always gonna be something off.
They barely said a word all evening.
Yeah, they're probably
just tired from playing.
Maddy.
Shit! I almost my pissed my pants.
Why aren't you in bed?
Maddy?
Are you okay?
Never better.
That's it.
Myles! Maddy!
Honey?
Oh my God!
J.P? Oh, oh my God!
911. What's your emergency?
Somebody's killed him!
Please!
- Ma'am, I need you
to stay on the line.
- Please help me!
Attention all units we have a...
1034 in progress.
Ma'am, ma'am,
are you all right?
I need to know where you are.
- Maddy!
- What should we do with her?
- No!
- Hello?
Make her squeal like a bitch.
Rita Wanayo with Channel 26,
and we are standing in front of the home
on Poplar Bluff Road in the
small town of Carpenter Falls,
where police have just taken into custody
two young children who
have allegedly committed
a series of ritualistic murders.
Sadly, this is not the first time
this town has seen tragedy.
I am being informed by authorities
that these crimes may have been influenced
by those of Colin Miller,
a notorious serial killer
known to many as The Wicked One.
Minnesota.
Dad, we stopped playing miles ago.
Well it still counts.
Just cuz you guys are so
losers doesn't mean anything.
This drive is taking forever.
If the Nova was a busted,
I could have been there hours ago.
Is that complaining I hear back there?
Yeah, I do believe it is.
And how many times
did your father tell you
to stay up-to-date on your oil changes?
It's so lame that at 17 years old,
I have to get a ride
with my parents to a gig.
But honey, we love
taking you to your gigs.
- It's embarrassing.
- Not for us.
I'm gonna tear Valentine's
head off when I see
his Joey Ramone wanna-be ass.
Daniel, there is no way that Valentine
would've known that your
car was gonna kerplunk
because of your negligence.
Do you think GG All in ever had to drive
to CBGB's with his parents?
Well, considering his
father was a religious freak
who named his son Jesus Christ,
uh, you know, beat him,
threatened murder and bury him in cellar,
I'm gonna have to take
a wild guess and say no.
Impressive knowledge of
punk rock there, good sir.
I'm not as old
as lame as Daniel thinks I am.
Mm, nah, you're still pretty lame.
Hey, don't forget who taught you
the chords to "Holiday in Cambodia."
Yeah, yeah.
How much further?
About 22 more Taylor
Swift tracks, honey.
- Daddy?
- Yes, Snoops?
Did Taylor Swift's dad
threaten to kill her too?
No, hon.
The music world is not that lucky
I'm gonna go get the key.
All right.
This definitely isn't the Four Seasons.
You know your
father, anything to save a buck,
but we are a mile from the venue,
so you know, that's good.
- We're a mile away?
- Yeah.
And there's cell service. Thank God.
Oh, let's go to the vending machine.
Okay, we'll be back.
Hello, Earth to Mother.
Can you pass me in my bag?
Your bag, yeah. Here.
You're still staring
at the board, hey, Burke?
Tromer. Come on in.
I was just dropping off the
report you requested, sir.
Hmm? Oh, desk's fine.
What's it say?
Sir?
The report.
Oh, uh, some lady on the
outskirts of town called in
and said that some homeless man
was going through her trash.
And then she changed her
story and it was a Bigfoot.
Mm-hmm, and what do you think?
Ah, if I had to guess,
I'd, I'd say a bear.
Do you know how many people have died
at the hands of Colin Miller?
- Colin Miller is dead.
So show me his body.
It's been 10 years.
Four murders in the past 24 months,
nine missing persons cases
from surrounding counties, all unsolved.
And all unrelated, different motives,
different causes of death.
Hell, we caught the guy
who did one of them.
It was the boyfriend.
That one was circumstantial
and you know it,
All of these crimes
encircle Carpenter Falls.
He's out there.
Where, I don't know, but he's out there.
Today, we have got a marvelous guest.
Oh, I'm just so excited.
I wanna talk about the best
selling author with her hit,
The story of Colin Miller."
Yes, look, The National Book
Club, an official selection.
Whoop-whoop!
- Thank you.
- Oh yes, I'm just...
- Thank you for having me.
Yes. I just wanna dive right in.
Can we just do that?
- The story of Carpenter Falls
- Mm, yes.
- Is a tragic one.
- Mm.
- Okay, this is a town
that has been marred
with horrifying events
and there are a lot of
unanswered questions.
- Ooh.
- My book
- Mm.
- Dives deep into the story
and uncovers facts about the occult,
the ritualistic blood sacrifices.
Turn it.
What are you doing?
- Getting into character.
- Those people online
were right, you are a poser.
- Uncovered the truth about
- What?
- The disappearances.
- Someone said I was a poser?
Kendall, cool it with the jumping.
I think it's best if you not do that.
Am I the only one who thinks
going into a terrain
- Poser.
We know nothing
about without any knowledge
of its conditions or schematics,
- Okay.
- A little bit
intimidating?
- Yeah,
you know, I'd follow you into hell...
But with this...
Um...
How do I look?
- Honey, it's...
- My Mom will kill me.
Well, as it turns out, we might
have a guide.
- Revealing.
Mia Bates,
Helen Bates's daughter.
- Oh my God.
- We're gonna track her down.
Daniel, are you ready?
Ready as I'm ever gonna be.
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Slow your role, guys.
Where are you going?
- I've seen this movie before.
We're gonna get attacked by
some backwoods hillbillies.
Well, we're just gonna
walk it to the venue.
Now? But it doesn't
start for several hours.
Right.
The band's already there
and we have rehearsals.
But I wanted us all to go
get something to eat tonight.
This seems
legitimately dangerous.
Oh, Mexican? We need more queso.
- Oh God, no queso.
- Come on guys.
You stick your grubby
little fingers in it,
nobody can have any.
Yeah, pass.
- Fuck it.
- I'll just get
something at the venue.
- Let's do it.
I'm sure they'll have concessions.
Yeah, I'll probably
just grab a Power Bar.
Don't eat anything to big
before my performance.
- Be careful.
- Of course.
It's cool. We get it.
You two be careful.
I am not comfortable with this.
Geez, Mom, we're 17 and 18 years old.
And 17 And 18 year olds go
missing all the time, Daniel.
Alex.
Fine, but straight to the venue.
Do you understand?
- Mm-hmm.
- Yep.
- Yeah.
They'll be fine. They got each other.
The three of us will go
get something to eat.
Someplace with queso?
Child, you're obsessed.
Stopped answering my calls
and you clearly didn't take my hint.
They'll be good. Okay?
Look, I
know what you're thinking,
and no, I don't live here.
It's just somewhere I come
when I need to get away.
Clear my head.
- Boo, you suck!
- Well, well, well.
I thought I was gonna have to Phil Collins
this shit tonight.
Hey, hey.
- Hmm.
Do you even know who that is?
Of course I know who that is.
- Hmm.
- "No Jacket Required"
was required listening in
my household growing up.
The old man loved that Limey bastard.
Dude, the Nova totally keeled over.
- Fuck.
- Hopefully we have
a decent crowd tonight.
I could use the fucking money.
- Mm.
- And by the way,
thanks for leaving me behind, dick.
Well, don't be so damn late.
I don't know, man.
The dude said the pre-sales
were actually pretty rad,
so we might have a full house tonight.
Ooh, don't tell him that.
He's had the bubble
guts the whole way here.
Well, I didn't think you
were even gonna be here,
work or something.
- Mm, totally charmed
my way out of it.
- Mm?
- Mm-hmm.
- Well you picked
a pretty good one.
I can feel it coming in the air tonight.
Yes, that is an intentional
Phil Colland reference.
- Mm.
And the only pretty girl is
gonna be showing some support.
- Holly.
- Hi.
- Hey, how are you?
- Good.
Thank God we made it.
If I had to hear Holly mention
Daniel's name one more time,
I was going to slip my own throat.
How you doing today? You good?
Good. Are you nervous?
Yeah, Pike said it's
gonna be a full house, so...
That's good for y'all, though.
- Yeah.
- It'll be fun, it looks like
a good venue.
- Yeah, it's really cool.
I love all the lights.
It's cool. I'm excited.
Me too. Thanks for coming.
Yeah, I mean, Jenna would have killed me
if I didn't come, so...
- Yeah.
- I'm glad you came.
- Yeah, uh, me too.
You know, I've driven more crazies
across the Midwest than I care to mention.
Hell, I'll be happy when
they transfer my ass
in a couple weeks.
- You and me both.
Having to listen to your crabby-ass
on these trips is excruciating.
Uh, come on, man. Twisted clown killers.
Crazy ex-lovers.
Just about every other flavor
of insane you could imagine.
It's like a Baskin-Robbins for loonies.
So do you actually think
that these two did it?
What, kill their folks?
- Yeah.
- I mean,
the rumor is that Miller
fuck made 'em do it.
The kids were scary.
Gives me the heebie-jeebies
even thinking about it.
I have nightmares all
the time about my son
- killing me in my sleep.
- I would too.
That creepy little bastard.
Ever since I seen him,
I knew you were fucked.
Oh, shit!
Oh, holy fuck, man! Was that a woman?
Shit! Wait in the van!
Jesus.
What happened to you, lady?
Hello?
What the fuck?
They're dead!
Oh!
That's the most terrifying
thing I've ever seen.
No, you, you go ahead and finish it.
I like my cheese dip finger-free
and less strep-throated.
Honey, you okay? You want something eat?
No, I just don't feel like eating.
You can have something.
You wanna go find me
a good, stiff drink?
Look, I once heard it
said that you can't conquer
what you can't confront.
Did you get that out
of a fortune cookie?
- So, no.
- Mm.
It's still good advice.
Are you sure you don't want anything?
Not unless you wanna get a big bag
of those fortune cookies in case
I need some more good advice.
Mm-hmm.
Did you get enough?
The darkness takes
you, Makes you do things.
Corrupts your soul.
One moment, I was all happy
and the next,
Horror, terror.
- Chief wants to see you.
Once the darkness has
you, there's no escaping it.
Chief, you wanted to see me?
Come on in, Burke.
Close the door behind you.
Do you mind telling me what's up
with the Colin Miller shrine
hanging on your wall in your office?
Just research.
Research?
Yes, sir.
Look Burke, I like you.
You're one of my best officers.
So I'm not gonna sugarcoat this for you.
Your boys are worried about you.
They think you're taking
this Miller obsession
a little too far.
Chief, I, I just...
This has brought a lot of
eyes onto Carpenter Falls again.
Everything we do is under
the microscope, overanalyzed.
Now the last thing we
need is a media shit-storm
on how a police officer
believes the boogeyman
is still out there biding his time,
preparing to attack again.
The blow-back from that
would be catastrophic.
Public panic, media surges.
Have you ever seen evil, Chief Ellis?
I know you have a personal
connection to this case.
Dammit! It was my fault that he escaped!
He did it on my watch!
And that's, that's a fuck
up no one can ever fix.
It is time to move on, Burke.
Colin Miller is long gone.
Now I am asking that you
take the contents down
off your wall and put them away.
Are we clear?
We're gonna kill something.
I'm getting too old for this.
That's obvious.
Our boy's killing it though.
I know. I'm so proud of proud of him.
I'm proud of you.
Um...
Is it...
I'm gonna go to the bathroom.
Okay.
Kendall, sweetie, do you
need to go to the bathroom?
No way. This is my
favorite of Daniel's songs.
Watch her. I'll be back.
Get a grip, Alex.
Get a fucking grip!
Liv?
You shouldn't have come here, Alex.
I don't understand.
You, your family.
None of you are safe
here in Carpenter Falls.
Leave this place, Alex.
I gotta get outta here.
I need to go. Keep an eye on them.
Wait, what happened?
Mommy, you're hurting my arm.
Alex.
What in God's name is going on?
I gotta get outta here.
I thought I could do this, but I can't.
Mom?
Guys, I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
I know I've let you
down, but I, I'm trying.
I just can't do it.
I'm just gonna get
her back to the motel.
Yeah, that, that's okay.
We'll just catch a ride back with them.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah.
- Okay, good.
- I wanna stay too.
Uh...
Hey, rascal.
I need you to do me a solid
and go to the hotel with Mom.
Well why do I have to do that?
Why can't I stay?
Don't tell Jenna, but you're secretly
their favorite child.
Well, I already kind of knew that.
For me?
Please?
Fine.
It's gonna be, it's gonna be fine.
I'm so sorry, Daniel.
I know I've let you down. I'm so sorry.
Mom, it's okay.
You get a pass.
You go. I'll be fine.
I'll catch up with you guys
back to the motel later.
Okay.
It's okay.
Come on, hon. Let's go.
Come on. I'm sorry.
It's okay.
You guys be careful.
Okay.
Every time you perform, it's like
I can't control myself.
Because I'm fucking awesome.
I want you so bad.
Not as much as I do.
You're gonna kill me.
Oh my God. Don't tell
me you forgot a rubber.
What? No.
I just gotta piss real bad.
- Seriously?
Just hold it or I can
go join Greg in shower.
Shut the fuck up.
Here
Uh, better hurry or I'll
have to handle myself.
Don't you fucking dare.
Come on, fucker. We're
gonna have fun tonight.
What, what is up?
Holy fuck, you scared
the shit out of me.
I should be going now.
The room's all yours.
I wanna play with you.
Shh.
God, no!
Yes!
Kill her for daddy! Kill her for daddy!
You fucking freak.
I wanna look pretty too.
Help!
Wait.
- Right here.
- What's this? No.
Yeah, I think it's...
I'm an agony.
She's killing me.
I'm beat.
You know what the beautiful thing is?
In some alternate universe,
she's totally my girlfriend.
Yeah, and then in another
universe, she's totally not.
She's blown two other dudes.
She's the girl in my dreams.
Time. Speaking of dreams.
So last night I had this dream.
I go to college and I'm in my dorm
and standing there is Carrie
Fisher, butt-ass naked.
And I know she's dead and all,
but it's like this weird social situation.
I mean, she is Princess
Leia, for fuck sakes.
But at the same time, it's
like, I'm fucking a zombie.
You boned her.
Tonight's the perfect night to make
a move on her though, dude.
And I mean, if that doesn't
work, you can always
slip her one of those pixie sticks
and get that wet leg going.
Tonight's the night.
I'm gonna do it.
Need some tips, bro?
I can show you a thing or two.
Fuck off.
Hey, man. It's all in the hips.
All right, on that note,
let's get the rest of this shit packed up
before he starts humping my guitar case.
What about Pike and Blair?
They left like 20, 30 minutes ago.
Probably booty banging out
in the parking lot right now.
Typical, the least
reliable asshole I know.
Besides this asshole's Nova.
- All right, fuck you guys.
- All right.
I'm out.
I feel so bad about Daniel.
He understands.
I wish, I wish that made me
feel better, but it doesn't.
You gotta stop beating
yourself up over this.
We all knew it was a bad decision
for you to come back here.
I tried to tell you, but you're stubborn.
One of your better traits by the way.
Well you were right.
How does that taste
coming outta your mouth?
Fucking terrible.
Look, it's all to be expected.
What we went through was unimaginable,
but none of it, your fault.
Chris, Quentin, Trevor, Olivia.
Honey, they're all gone.
And Olivia, I will never
forgive myself for that.
You gotta let that shit go.
That's the bad shit that's happened to us.
You gotta focus on the
positive, all the good.
Your family adores you,
your kids think you're over the moon.
You got three amazing kids.
Daniel's in a band and
stays out of trouble.
Jenna goes to school and works,
and she still wants to be at home.
Kendall's funny. Cute.
A little terrifying when she eats.
And they all look like they're dad.
So I'm calling it a win.
You're lucky I love you.
And I love you.
Now let's get your mind on something
a little bit more stimulating.
Like what? Oh, okay.
Oh!
Mm.
Quit it. We gotta be quiet.
Well I'll be quick and quiet.
Besides, she's in a queso coma.
She's not waking up anytime soon.
- What's wrong?
- Nothing.
I can't believe we actually
just did that, but...
But what?
It's just a tad awkward with my sister
and Valentine in the backseat.
I mean, if the car starts
rocking, I'm outta here.
There's a trail over there.
Do you wanna go for a walk?
What is it?
You and hiking seem
like kind of an oxymoron.
I was a girl scout for nine years.
You were a girl scout?
Sure was.
You still got one of those vests?
We could totally role play.
So Daniel Lawson fantasizes
about little girl scouts?
No, I'm fantasizing
about you and your vest
trying to sell me your cookie.
Oh, so now you want my cookie, huh?
Maybe even your brownie.
Stay away from my brownie.
We can go for that walk though.
Hey, where y'all about to go?
- We'll be back.
- Yeah, you know
black people don't belong in the woods?
Everybody getting laid and shit.
Guess it's time to loosen up the wrist.
- So I'm serious now.
- Mm-hmm.
Have you given more thought
to, um, getting our own place?
You know, leaving the
nest and getting a place
with your boy Valentine?
Of course I have.
I just wanna make sure the time is right.
It's just the time is right.
I mean, all right. Think about this.
We could fuck like jack
rabbits all day and all night.
- Yeah?
- And not have to worry
about your schizo mother walking in on us.
What?
Be nice.
But she is.
- Oh my God.
- I'm sorry.
Listen, listen. Hey, hey.
I just, I want
you more in my life,
and in my bed more, and in my car more,
- Mm?
- And in my shower more.
- Mm-hmm.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Take it off. Mm.
- Wait, wait.
- What?
Is Weezer still out there?
You know he's a perv and
he's fucking blending.
What?
Are you serious?
Gonna get you wet like a gremlin.
So what's the deal with
your mom and this place?
She kinda flipped her shit earlier.
It's not really something we talk about.
You're gonna make me tell you, aren't you?
I mean, I'm not gonna make you tell me,
but I would kind of like to know.
Jenna and I were just kids.
My parents and some
friends decided to head up
to a property here for a
weekend away in Carpenter Falls.
Some crazy dude from
here went on the warpath
"Helter Skelter" style and
carved up their friends.
My parents
were the only survivors.
Okay, yeah, I can see
why that would be something
you don't wanna talk about.
It messed mom up pretty bad.
Apparently the dude was
into some cult-like stuff.
Killed his parents as a boy and shit.
Claimed some demon made him do it.
That's awful.
Dad seemed to have gotten over it fine,
but mom, not so much.
Look.
Oh, jackpot.
What do you mean jackpot?
This is creepy as shit.
It's abandoned.
Don't tell me you're actually afraid.
I mean yeah, kind of.
- It's an old, empty house.
- Exactly, old, empty house.
It's probably full of
snakes and spiders and rats.
Come on. I'll protect you, princess.
Smells like mildew and bacon.
It's not that bad.
I really hope you don't think
you're getting laid in here.
Why not?
I'm joking. Chill.
Oh, come on.
I knew I shouldn't
have listened to my ma.
"Don't get the guitar, Weezer.
Play the drums, Weezer.
Girls dig the drummer, Weezer."
Fucking piece of shit.
Maybe if I got that guitar, I wouldn't be
in these hillbilly-ass backwoods.
I wouldn't be about to jerk off
and I'll probably have any bitch I want.
You gotta be fucking kidding me.
A graveyard?
Kasie Miller.
I blaze here today in your honor.
I hope you were at least a
bad bitch when you were alive,
because before this night's over,
I'm gonna cover your grave
with my baby gravy.
It's all a fucking pathetic
I'm really about to beat
off to a dead bitch.
It's a damn shame.
Naughty girl
No!
- Naughty girl.
- No!
Let me go!
- When he was reviled,
he did not revile in return.
When he suffered,
he did not threaten, but entrusted.
He who would judge him just.
Fuck you, shoelace bandit.
Shut the fuck up!
What the fuck do you people want?
I said, what the fuck do you people want?
Bill, watch out!
Bill, no!
Bill!
Don't worry.
We'll take good care of her.
I always love checking
out abandoned houses.
If these walls could talk,
I bet they have plenty of stories to tell.
Yeah, somehow I don't think
this would be a good one.
Oh, shit, Kasie. Fuck.
I'm tired about this fucking
band getting no pussy.
Making me bust up on a fucking grave.
Oh shit. Fuck!
Oh yeah. Here it comes, Kasie.
Okay. That's enough
creepy for one night.
Can we just go back to the car?
Listen. Someone's coming.
Okay. Turn the light off.
Jenna.
Daniel, what are you gonna do?
- They have my sister.
- Yeah, no shit, Sherlock,
but you can't just run out there.
They'll kill you.
- Holly, that's my
fucking sister.
Daniel, you can't, that's suicide.
Shit, fuck.
Here I come!
Whee!
Shh.
Boo!
Daniel, don't open the door.
Daniel, we can go call
somebody then can come back.
Please, let's go.
I can't leave her.
There isn't much time, Alex.
What are you talking about?
Jenna?
Alex.
To save them, you'll have
to face your darkest fears.
Your call has been forwarded
to an automatic voice message.
Fuck.
What the hell is that?
Look. Get a load of this.
Maybe they hit a deer.
You don't suspect foul play, do you?
Maybe.
- It's him.
- It's who?
The guy I was telling you about earlier.
We have to find Jenna.
Alex, what are you doing?
Kids aren't back yet.
Think something's wrong.
Maybe not. They're just
out doing what teenagers do.
It's 2:00 AM, Adam.
They should have been
back long before now.
I can't get either one of
'em on their cell phones
plus this dream or
warning or I don't know,
call it whatever you wanna call it,
but she's trying to tell me something.
Who's trying to tell you what?
Look, I know that
this sounds crazy, okay?
But ever since we got back here,
I've been seeing her and I know
it's not just a coincidence.
Hey, you're gonna have
to help me out here.
I'm not following.
Olivia.
Olivia. As in dead, Olivia?
Look, I know how it sounds.
No, I don't think you do
She showed me the kids
at the old Miller house.
- Alex.
- I know, okay?
I know that this is
insane. Believe me, I do.
But something is wrong. I can feel it.
Is this is what we talked about earlier?
No, dammit, this,
this has nothing to do with that.
Then this is nuts
then. That's what it is.
You're talking
to a ghost and shit, it's gotta stop.
I have to protect them.
From who? He's dead.
I have to be sure, Adam.
Fine.
You wanna be chained to Colin Miller
for the rest of your life, go ahead.
I refuse.
- And what is that
supposed to mean?
- It means look at what
this is doing to your children.
They shouldn't have to see
the mom going through this.
If you can't get past it for yourself,
get past it for them at least.
But what if I can't?
I don't know how!
Come here. Come on.
You act like like if I
wasn't even there with you,
like I didn't go through
the same shit you did.
When I look in the mirror
every day, I see the scars.
I know what that monster
did to our family,
but I made a choice to move on
because my kids need me,
and goddammit, I need my kids.
I know.
I know. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. This is total bullshit.
I just want this to be over.
I want you to be okay.
Okay.
I'll try harder, I promise.
Look, I think I'm just
gonna go for a walk.
I just wanna go clear my head.
Get some air, maybe a cup of coffee.
You, you want one?
I wouldn't say no to a cup of coffee
or whiskey at this point.
Okay. Okay.
You want me to come with you?
No, no.
I just wanna be alone.
Plus, I don't want you to wake up Kendall.
I'll be fine.
Okay.
I love you.
I love you too.
We love
because he first loved us.
I promise you'll love her.
And I would say you're
a nasty Carrie.
Do you ever hear the voices?
Hmm? You hear the voices?
You do.
You do, you do, you do.
- No.
- You do!
Because, because we all hear the voices.
Even, even you.
Oh, you turn your back on the voices.
Why? I don't know why.
You need bloody listen!
- No, no!
- Huh?
Oh, and they want me to do
No, please.
Horrible, horrible things.
Do you, uh...
Oh, you're so warm.
Don't fight.
- No.
Don't fight, don't fight.
Please, please.
No, don't fight.
No, no, no.
- It'll hurt less.
- No!
No, no!
Please, please don't.
It's Jenna.
No!
Fuck!
- Ow.
- Daniel here.
- It's okay.
- You okay?
We're gonna get you out of here.
Come on. It's okay.
You're okay.
Yay, new lovers!
Officer, I need your
help. My kids are missing.
Ma'am, what's going on?
They, they disappeared and
I think they're in trouble.
Oh, okay. How long they've been missing?
I, I don't know. A few hours.
Okay. 48 hours is typical
for missing persons report.
Fuck that!
I need your help now!
And I need you to calm down.
Fine.
Listen, I know that this
is gonna sound crazy,
but I think they're at
the old Miller house.
The Miller house?
You fucking listen to me!
I need your help now!
And I need you to take
your hands off of me.
Alex, Alex Curtis?
Lawson.
Yeah, whatever. What the
hell is going on out here?
No idea, she came
barging through the door,
said her kids were at the Miller house, I-
Look, my kids are missing, and I think
they're at the old
Miller house in trouble.
Have you taken her statement?
- No, I haven't.
- Yeah,
hard to believe, right?
Look, before we do anything,
we're gonna have to sort through-
We don't have time to
sort through shit, okay?
We need to go, please!
Look, you can do this with my help
or you can do it on your own.
It's up to you.
Daniel. Daniel!
Can you hear me?
Where are we?
I don't know.
I'm gonna hurt you, Colin Miller?
Hi kids.
Yes.
Don't you fucking touch her.
Oh, you are so dramatic.
Ooh, look at 'em, look at 'em go.
What are you gonna do to me?
I'm just gonna get you all clean.
Oh no. Don't cry.
If you cry then I'm gonna cry.
Oh, this is so much fun.
All clean.
All clean for daddy.
I should be home in bed.
Not dealing with this.
Chief, you didn't
have to come down here.
I could have handled this.
Excuse me. When can I see my wife?
Thank you for coming down, Mr. Lawson.
Just give us a few with your
wife and we'll get back to you.
Thank you.
What are we gonna do with her?
You tell me, kiddo.
Alex, long time. No, see.
Chief.
I'd say it we're good
to see you if it were
under any other circumstances.
All right.
Why don't we start with you telling me
why you are back here in Carpenter Falls?
It doesn't matter why I'm back.
My kids are missing.
Okay. When did they go missing?
After the music thing downtown.
I think they're at the old Miller house.
We actually found a
car tonight abandoned
about a mile from the Miller property.
It was a white Toyota.
Had the back window broken out.
Oh my God, that's them.
They were with friends.
Okay, Alex, I
shouldn't be telling you this
given your connection to this case.
Telling me what?
The Mathis siblings escaped during
a transfer this evening,
people were killed.
Now we don't know this for sure,
but there's a chance they could be
heading back to Carpenter Falls.
Oh my, oh my God.
Now we have every
available officer in town
looking for them, and
we don't know for sure.
I have to find my kids!
Okay. And we're gonna help you.
Then quit fucking around
and get me to the old Miller house.
I'll take her. I mean,
I'll accompany her.
Not alone, you won't.
Tromer, you go with Burke.
See if you guys can locate the kids.
You get lost on your
way to the coffee shop?
What the hell's going on?
It's the kids.
They found Valentine's car out
by the old Miller property.
What?
Adam, the Mathis kids escaped.
There's been murders.
We have to find Daniel and Jenna.
We're gonna go out there now.
Me and those officers.
Okay, well I'm coming with.
Can I come?
Baby bug.
Oh, here. Let me save you some time.
"Kendall, you can't go with us."
Correct.
Where we're going is dangerous.
What's going on anyways?
Where's Daniel and Jenna?
Sweetie, we're going to
get them right now. Okay?
Are they gonna be grounded?
For life.
I wanna come with you guys.
I know. I'm sorry.
But we won't be gone very long.
Stay here, watch TV, eat
donuts, drink coffee.
We'll be back soon.
Love you, girl.
I love you, baby bug.
We'll see you in little bit. Okay?
Go with this nice lady.
Yeah. Yeah.
I better get rewarded for
this, like major rewarded.
Anything you want.
It's gonna be expensive.
I'd expect nothing less.
All clean.
Holly.
Please don't hurt her. Please.
Please, please.
And I thought you knew how
this would end for each of you.
But who goes first?
Holly, Holly, Holly, Holly.
You can do whatever you
want to me, just let her go.
Please?
- Daniel, no!
Shut up, Jenna!
Please.
No, stop!
Colin, stop.
Please, just stop.
Colin, please stop!
Just stop, Colin, please,
just stop!
He can't save you. You're all alone.
And it's telling me to spill
your putrid fucking guts!
Fuck yes!
Hmm.
Holly!
No!
Holly.
I did it. Killed her.
I killed them all.
Oh fuck, I'm a killer.
I'll be fucking damned.
So this is what it feels like.
I said I fucking killed
them! They're all dead!
Daniel? Jenna?
Oh God.
- Kids!
Daniel! Jenna!
How far is the Miller house from here?
It's less than a mile.
Oh, oh, Holly! Oh, Holly, Holly!
Holly, Holly, Holly!
- Don't you fucking touch her!
- Don't you touch her!
- I'll fucking kill you!
He might kill me.
Oh, do it. Come on, come
on, come on, come on.
- I'm gonna fucking do it!
- No, Holly, oh, poor Holly.
Oh, where you going? No.
Get off!
You wanna know what
Holly tastes like?
No, no!
Taste her, taste
her, see what she tastes like.
Jenna! Jenna!
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
- Jenna, run!
- Oh yes.
- Go!
- No, no,
no, Jenna, really.
Jenna, bad, bad girl.
- Jenna, just go.
- You better run.
Jenna, run.
Oh Holly, do you miss Holly?
Look, here's Holly right here.
Did you ever taste Holly? Oh.
She really, she tastes
good, doesn't she?
Mm.
- Oh.
- Jenna, run!
One, two...
You're so cute.
Let's go.
The basement, Alex.
There ain't nothing here.
They're here, Adam.
This is exactly what she
showed me in the vision.
Check the door.
Burke, the basement!
Mm.
Alex.
Just be careful firing
that thing down there.
Could cause an explosion.
Okay.
Oh, are you worried
about your big sister?
You can't imagine the
things that I did to her.
And my sister,
oh, she's gonna do so much more.
I thought your freaks
were supposed to be mutes.
You talk too much.
You hurt my little feelings,
but it's okay,
because everything that
I did to your sister,
I'm gonna do so much worse.
Fucking try it, Buffalo Bill.
Oh, tastes like Holly.
Holly, mm, Holly.
Yeah, there he is!
No!
Drop the knife!
Jenna. Jenna.
It's okay.
They killed everybody.
Jenna, Jenna, baby, where's you brother?
They have him.
Have to get her up.
Adam, she's really hurt.
Can, can you walk?
My legs.
This is Burke. This is,
I need, this is Burke.
I need to back up. Goddamn,
I can't get a signal.
Me either.
Look, I know you wanna find your son,
but we need to get her out of here.
She needs medical attention.
- No, I am not
leaving here without my son.
Alex, he's right. She
needs to go to the hospital.
Tromer, you go with Mr.
Lawson and his daughter.
When you get to service, call for backup.
Alex and I will find your son.
No, Alex, you take her.
No, I can't. I can't carry her.
She's too heavy. You have to do it.
I'm not leaving you down here.
I am not leaving here
without both of our children!
All right. Come on.
Goddammit, Alex.
Go.
Uh, I am the boogeyman.
How many are left? Check that.
Shit.
There's no bullets.
What is that?
Shit.
Yeah.
It's okay, baby, it's okay.
You guys wait here. I'm gonna
make sure everything's okay.
It's all right, sweetie.
He's gonna check it out.
The coast is clear.
- Fuck.
Come on, come on!
Keep going.
- Dad, I can't!
You stay the fuck away from my son!
Danny.
- Mom.
Burke, help me get him up.
Baby, baby, are you okay?
- Yes.
- Yeah?
We're gonna get you outta here. Okay?
- Yeah.
- Okay, okay we're gonna go.
Okay. Let's go, let's go.
Daniel, Daniel, come on. Let's go.
It's my fault.
What?
It's all my fault.
No, no, baby.
This is not your fault.
They're all dead because of me.
Honey, you didn't do this?
This is not your fault.
- Yes, I did!
If I hadn't have booked
that stupid fucking gig,
none of this shit would've happened!
It's not, no.
Baby, no.
You know how sometimes
people will look at you
and they'll say they know how you feel
when they really don't?
Dammit, Daniel, look at me!
I know how you feel.
I do. Okay?
Okay.
But right now you have
got to listen to me.
Your dad and Jenna are waiting.
We've gotta get the
hell out of this place.
Okay?
- Mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
Okay? Okay, come on.
Stop hitting me!
No, get out!
Oh, dispatch?
I need to report a murder.
Whoo.
Good day to you, officer.
You fuck.
Oh, fuck.
Dammit.
Huh?
Fuck.
Ha-ha! Oh.
Where are you?
Where are you my little sweet, oh, oh, oh!
Oh, all this killing
people makes me so thirsty.
I'm just so parched.
Shit.
Daniel.
Daniel! Daniel!
Get off of me!
Get off him.
Nice little brother, huh!
Daniel! Daniel!
Myles!
'Tis a flesh wound.
No.
I know what it's like someone.
What is this place?
Home.
This is where you grew up?
Yeah.
We don't have much time.
Come on, babe.
I got ya, I got ya.
- Thanks, daddy.
Alex.
What are we gonna do?
We're gonna set a trap.
A trap?
Find something you can use as a weapon.
- No.
- What's wrong?
Just a lot of bad memories here.
Well, they weren't all bad, right?
No, no, baby, they weren't all bad.
Found it.
We got one shot at this,
so let's make a count.
He's coming.
Uh!
Come and get me, motherfucker.
No, no, no!
No!
Colin.
Colin!
Mom!
Mom.
Dad!
Get off of him!
- Get up!
Hit him!
Dad, Dad, Dad, get up, get up.
Come on!
Fuck.
Alex.
How does it feel to be scared?
How does it feel to be threatened?
To no longer have control?
I never had control.
Die! Die!
Okay. It's all right.
Let's go.