(MultiCom jingle)
(dramatic music)
(bird chirping)
(soft music)
(child yelling)
(apple crunching)
- Hungry?
- [Veronica] Don't start with me, Ted.
- God, I got a faculty meeting
in three and a half hours.
- Then what are you doing up?
- After you climbed over me on your
hundredth trip to the toilet,
I couldn't get back to sleep.
- You came in here to make
fun of my weight admit it.
Hey, that's my ice cream.
- What you don't have enough there.
I just want a couple of spoons.
- Well, it's mine give it to me.
- [Ted] I'll have a couple of spoons,
and then I'll give it to you.
- No, you give me the whole thing,
and I'll give you a couple of spoons.
- No.
- Don't you trust me?
- The mother of your child?
- No.
- You're gonna eat your baby's food.
- Okay, here.
- Sucker.
- [Ted] I knew it.
- Bring a spoon.
Ted, you know I don't know what's wrong.
I can't stop eating.
I look like a 200-pound
sack of bird seed, don't I?
- Yeah, you do.
- Thanks.
- It's only temporary.
What are we out of mayonnaise?
How can you eat this without mayonnaise?
- Maybe not, Ted.
- [Ted] I don't see any I think we are.
- Maybe it's not temporary.
Maybe I won't lose the weight.
- Can I tell you something?
You'll lose it it's temporary.
It doesn't matter.
It doesn't matter because
I can let myself go
and we can live in the kitchen.
(soft music)
- I'm so damn tight.
- How's buster?
- We bred a kick boxer champion.
- Oh, good, we can take
in early retirement.
- Ted.
- Huh?
- You love me?
- Of course I love you.
- Even like this?
- Especially.
- As always we appreciate
the good work, Malcolm.
If there's no new business,
I suggest adjournment,
so that we might all return
to the task of making money.
(men chuckling)
All in favor.
- [Men] Aye.
- Opposed.
This meeting is adjourned.
- Thank you, son, for your presentation.
You did a terrific job.
- We're a good team.
- I'm very proud of you.
Listen would you see
that Charlotte gets this.
Carter, before you leave,
I have something I'd
like to share with you.
- Oh, thank you.
- I thought you had quit.
- He did.
- Don't start sounding like your mother.
This is an auspicious
occasion, my third grandchild.
- I suppose that means you'll
be looking for another raise.
- Well, you're lucky, Mr. Hughes.
This time I'm just the uncle.
- No, this is Veronica's it's her first.
- Oh, yeah, that's right.
Well, congratulations to you both.
- Thank you, sir.
- Thank you.
- Boy or girl?
- Well, we don't know yet.
It's not expected for another week or two.
- You're jumping the gun, aren't you?
- Well, the full board doesn't meet
for another three months,
and by then the kid will
be entering Harvard.
- Full scholarship no doubt.
- There better be we're
in a recession, you know.
- Come on.
Aren't you gonna offer me one of those?
- You know how much these things cost?
- That's why I want one.
- JD, what are you doing hanging out?
Give Mack a hand with those two by fours.
- Charlie.
- We haven't got all day.
- Ladies, ladies.
What do you want from me?
We're doing the best job we
can under the circumstances.
- Charlie, you're making
decisions about materials
without consulting us.
- We couldn't get copper.
We got galvanized sheet metal.
- It rusts out.
- Works just as well.
They all will rust out eventually.
- Charlie, we expect
copper in this fountain
because it lasts longs.
With galvanized sheet metal
it's gonna rust out in no time.
You really wanna replace the stuff
in two years instead of 20.
- It's the best galvanized
sheet metal.
- It's wrong, Charlie.
- It's top.
- Wrong.
- What do you want from me?
We're just trying to get the job in
by deadline under budget.
(cellphone ringing)
- Great now just
through in correctly and we're all set.
Talk to Joni she has a cost points.
- Hello.
Yeah, she's right here.
It's your mother.
- More advice.
Everybody's a critic, Charlie.
- We couldn't get copper.
- Yes, mother.
I'm in the middle of a
meeting can I call you right--
- Darling, I just wanted to
remind you about the vitamins.
You know how important they are.
I was reading this article.
- Yes, thank you, mother
I'm already taking them.
Now I've really gotta.
- I know, dear, you're busy as usual.
Just don't push too hard
for the baby's sake if nothing else.
- Bye, mother.
I'll call you later.
I have really got to go.
- Bye, dear.
- Bye.
- Charlie has agreed to replace
the materials as ordered.
Take the cost over on
that out his own pocket.
Honesty lives.
- Stupidity lives.
Any ways, we'll stay in closer touch
from here on in, okay?
- Great, listen guys I've got to get to
an appointment in about five minutes.
- I thought we had nothing--
- I was wrong, sorry, take care, Charlie.
- See you later.
- Excuse me, I had some other things--
- This is it, Joni, the
real thing I know it is.
- Why didn't you say so?
- Are you crazy.
Charlie Singleton thinks
women belong in the kitchen.
Today we made progress.
You think I'm gonna give it up
by reminding him that women have babies.
- Now you are the back
bone of the labor force.
- Don't make me laugh.
- Come on.
Just relax.
Start breathing in, okay, good.
Alright breathe, breathe.
- [Ted] Welcome to paradise.
Welcome to the modern world.
- I got her.
I got her.
(telephone ringing)
- Hello, you have reached
the hospital room of Jacqueline Ricci.
We're resting right now.
- This is your grandfather speaking.
- Malcolm, what a surprise.
We haven't heard from you and
Clair for at least an hour.
- I cannot be responsible
for my wife, Ted.
That's something you yourself
will discover someday.
Actually, I just wanted to talk to
my daughter alone for a couple of minutes
while my wife is at
some committee meeting.
- Um, she's resting right now.
She'll call you back in about 15 minutes.
- Relax will ya I'm babysitting Christy.
Let me just say a quick hello to her,
and then I'll speak to her
tomorrow from the office.
Thank you, Ted.
- All right.
- Hi, dad.
- Hi, sweetheart.
I won't keep you I just
wanted to say that...
I just wanted to tell ya that I love you,
and you're still my little girl.
Goodnight, sweetheart.
- Goodnight, daddy.
- You want me to read that to you?
- Uh-huh.
- Where did you get this book?
- You gave it to me, grandpa.
- I did I don't remember that.
- Well, hello.
- Hey.
- Hi, Christy.
- Hi.
- Hi, Michael.
(people conversing)
- Hey, beautiful.
Where's the baby?
- Outside with Ted.
Put that down we'll get that upstairs.
- Yeah.
- There she is.
- There's dad.
- Hi, Malcolm.
- Look at that face she looks
just like you, Veronica.
- Well, I hate to admit
you're right, Clair,
but she does look like her mom.
- [Ted] Yeah, secrets out
it was a virgin birth.
- Well, I think she has Ted's mouth.
- Oh, I don't agree.
- Oh, absolutely not.
- Well, she dances just like
me though no doubt about that.
- Can I see?
- Sure come on over.
You too, Christy, come on.
Jacqueline, meet your
cousins Michael and Christy.
- Can I touch her?
- [Veronica] Sure, but do it very gently.
- She's so little.
- Well, yes, but you were that
little once too, you know.
- Yeah, and so were you.
- Alright, my angel for you.
A family tradition
all my little girls get
horseys, don't they?
(birds chirping)
- Wanna see the waterfall?
- [Michael] Okay.
(soft music)
- Well, why don't I take
our things upstairs.
(crickets chirping)
- Tomorrow we'll go
take a look at the boats
on the lake would you like that?
Okay, that's tomorrow's agenda.
Give me a kiss.
Sleep well.
- [Michael] Okay.
- And sweet dreams my angel.
Give grandpa a big kiss.
When we get home on Sunday,
you and I will do something
special all right.
All right.
- All right.
- Goodnight.
(gentle music)
- Ted.
- Yeah, Ted, the one who looks
nothing like your daughter.
What are you doing?
- I couldn't sleep.
I (stammering).
I was just up here looking for something.
- Anything in particular
maybe I could help?
- It's not important.
- [Ted] Then why are you looking?
- I honestly don't know.
Come on let's go back to bed.
- Actually, you know,
as long as we're here.
- Oh, Ted.
- Door is closed your
parents wouldn't hear.
- No, no, come on, come on, don't.
- Veronica.
- What?
- Do you really think she has my mouth?
- Yes, I do.
Let's go to bed.
(crickets chirping)
I don't know ever since
the first day, nothing.
She just won't nurse.
- I understand your
concern, Veronica, I do,
but I've checked her out
entirely and she's just fine.
This is not that usually.
Remember she's learning too,
so I really don't think there's
anything to worry about for now.
Just keep trying.
I have some brochures over here
if you'd care to read them.
- I don't know it just feels wrong.
- I think V's trying to
take on a little too much
between the baby and the job.
I think you should give it some time.
I'm not worried.
- Well, I am, okay.
Isn't there anything we can do?
- Just give it some time
and I'll see you in two months, bye, bye.
- Here.
What's wrong with me I'm so edgy.
I feel so disconnected.
- Hey, I love you, Big V.
(baby cooing)
Oh, the baby's horsey.
♪ Da, da, da, da, da, da, da ♪
(dramatic music)
(engine revving)
Honey, don't let this breast
feeding thing get to you.
It really doesn't matter.
You know I wasn't breast fed as a kid.
It wasn't the done thing.
Doctors actually preferred
formulas then to breast feeding.
- Stop the car.
- [Ted] Huh?
- [Veronica] Stop the car.
- What's the matter, what's wrong?
- Just please stop the car.
- Okay, okay.
(dramatic music)
Veronica.
(car horn honking)
(baby crying)
Veronica.
Look out.
(car horns honking)
(tires squealing)
(tense music)
(car horns honking)
(breaks squealing)
- You crazy.
- I do, I do understand
how important it is to him.
I'm just saying I don't wanna leave
Jacqueline with a babysitter.
- Have you forgotten what the
Preservation Society represents, Veronica?
They've only presented this
award twice in 15 years.
Now every person of
stature in this community
will be in that room to honor your father
at our own country club.
- I'm aware of that, mother.
It's very flattering to dad.
- Your brother's giving
the toast, you know.
- [Veronica] I'm sure he is.
- And what's that supposed to mean?
(baby crying)
- Nothing, mother.
Jacqueline's crying and I've
gotta give her, her bottle.
- Alright, all right.
Just call us soon,
Veronica, with good news.
- I will, mother, goodbye.
- Bye.
(baby crying)
- You hungry, Jacqueline, huh?
Here, sweetheart, come here.
Come here let's have some food.
Let's have some food.
(baby cooing)
Hungry, huh?
Here.
(baby crying)
(heavy gasping)
- What's the matter?
What's the matter?
- I can't breathe.
I feel like I can't breathe.
- Alright, alright you're okay.
Nightmare again?
It's okay.
Breathe.
What was it the blood?
- I don't know if it's
blood it's just red.
It's just a sea of red so much red
until it's smothering me.
Oh, god it's so awful.
- It's all right.
It's all right.
I'll hold you.
It's okay.
I wish I could come into your dream.
I'd protect you.
- Ted, I think I'm losing it.
I'm so nervous.
- You're not losing it.
- I walked out in the middle of traffic.
I could've been killed.
- It's part of that postpartum depression.
- Don't give me that
postpartum depression crap.
This is different I know it is.
- Alright, okay, relax tell me what's--
- If I could relax, it wanna be a problem.
Don't you get it?
- I get it.
I get it.
Tell me what you want
I'll do anything you want.
What do you want?
- I don't know.
- You know I still don't understand
why you couldn't get Mrs. Foley's niece
to sit with Jacqueline?
This is no place for a baby.
- Because, mother, I don't like handing
my new baby over to strangers
and I already told you that.
- Ladies and gentlemen,
I'd like to introduce to Mr. Tom Worth.
- Every once in a while,
the Preservation Society
uses its annual fundraiser
to honor one of its fellow members.
The board felt that one individual
had so distinguished himself
with his efforts toward the
preservation and the restoration
of the city landmarks
that he must be paid tribute.
I turned them down, however.
(audience chuckling)
I suggested that they
honor my father instead.
Who better to introduce Malcolm Worth
than the kid he groomed in his own image.
My father has dedicated himself
to ensuring the security
and the saving of the historical landmarks
and legacies in this city.
He did all this in his spare time
when he wasn't balancing
the ledger at the bank
or when he wasn't tending lovingly
to the needs of his family.
So, dad, congratulations.
(audience applauding)
- Oh, thank you, son.
That's very kind of you.
Your check's in the mail.
(audience chuckling)
This is indeed an honor to receive this.
(baby crying)
Thank you, Jacqueline, my
youngest granddaughter.
She's very proud of the old man.
Ted, you sure you know
how to change diapers.
- I'm learning, grandpa.
- I would like to thank, first of all
my family for their love and support
and patience over the past few years.
We can all be very proud
of what we have achieved
in our city in the last five years.
We've taken some of the great old homes
that were about to fall
down and we have made them.
Thank you, Kathy, I'm
glad you could be here.
- [Clair] This is just lovely.
- I think it's super
that your whole family
turned out for this, Malcolm.
- Yes.
- Well, it was a pleasure to see you all.
And congratulations again.
- Thank you, Winston.
- Bye.
- Whole family except for one
renegade, ungrateful daughter.
- Well, I'm sure she has her reasons, dad.
- Oh, really I wonder what they are.
- Malcolm, do you have my coat check?
- All I'm saying is she's
not here to defend herself.
- Exactly she's not here.
- Hey, hey dad, dad come on now.
It's been a terrific day,
so don't get all charged up on us, okay.
- Well, thank you, Tom for your loyalty.
And Veronica my little girl.
- Don't.
- What?
- What's the matter with you, Veronica?
- Nothing, nothing all right.
- What, darling?
- Don't, please don't.
- What's up, V?
- I need to get out of here.
- I don't know.
Hold the baby I'll be right back.
Veronica.
V, what happened?
What happened?
What?
- I don't know.
I don't know.
- [Becky] It's just a little weird
that's all I'm telling you.
- I just thought it was
time that we talked.
- Talk about what?
- Just in general.
- So what you're taking some
kind of psych course at night
you get to the part of sibling guilt?
- That's not fair, Beck.
I haven't exactly heard from you lately.
- No, you haven't.
- So it's a two-way street.
- Alright, you're the one
who took the train down here.
You start.
- Look, if you're gonna
be a wise ass about this,
I can get right back on the
train and go home, your call.
- Still got that temper, huh?
Sure.
I'm sorry.
It's just a little out
of the blue, you know.
- Yeah, I know.
- Dad missed you at the banquet.
- Oh, I'll bet.
- He did.
Then he...
He just got angry.
- What a surprise.
- Becky, I've been having these dreams,
these nightmares ever
since Jacqueline was born.
- [Becky] Isn't that normal?
- I don't think so.
See it's pretty much the
same dream all the time
only I can't make it out.
But I think that you're
in the dream somehow
even though you're not.
- What do you mean?
- I mean you're there but you're far away
and I can't get to you.
There's this red
like blood only not
really just a lot of red.
- [Becky] Well, maybe
you should talk to your
doctor about it.
- Yeah.
Becky, when we were kids,
did we have any favorite stuffed animals?
- Sure, who didn't?
- No, I mean specifically.
Like a stuffed horse.
- You got me.
I blocked most of those years out.
You know, they weren't a
lot of fun for me, you know.
- I remember, but I
I don't know why really.
- Well, some other time maybe.
I've got a five o'clock shot,
so I'm gonna have to cut this short.
If I had a little bit more notice.
Why don't you call me first next time.
- I will.
Soon.
I'd like for you to meet Jacqueline.
Maybe come visit?
- Why not.
I gotta fly.
- No, it's okay.
- I'm really sorry.
- No, no it's all right.
I'm glad that we got
to talk even this much.
I don't get to the city that often,
and I thought why not, right.
- It was good to see you.
- Good to see you too.
Bye.
- You're my husband, Ted, not my father.
- You wanna translate that for me?
- It means you can't tell me what to do.
- I'm not telling you I'm begging you.
It's not a good idea.
You said yourself the
other night I'm losing it.
Why would you wanna go back to work
and add the extra pleasure?
- Because I need to get out.
I need to get on with my life.
- Oh, right, because you're spending
oh, so much time with
your daughter, right.
- What's that supposed to mean?
- You act like you don't want her.
- What because I wanna go back to work?
It's not my fault she won't breast feed.
The doctor said so even you said so.
- I am talking about
basic maternal instincts.
- What about them?
- You don't appear to have any.
- Get out of my sight.
- No, I live here.
Although you may not
have noticed that lately.
Might as well sleep in the garage.
- So that's what this is about?
You're feeling neglected.
- What I'm feeling is that
I don't have a wife anymore
in the house or in my bed.
Where are you?
Where the hell are you?
(soft music)
- What do you want me to say?
- I want you to tell me what's wrong,
so we can fix it.
(gentle music)
- Is that what you think, Jacqueline
that I don't want you?
You mean everything to me.
Everything.
- So, welcome to the wonderful
world of working motherhood.
It's great, isn't it?
- Which we minds me the
last time we ate here
I couldn't get close enough to
this counter to reached carrots.
- Have some of this.
It's been hell without you.
- Oh, why didn't you say so?
I've been on the phone
with you nearly every day.
- I didn't wanna worry you.
- Oh, great, saving it
up for one big chat.
- No, one big lunch.
I think if we get all the bids
in by the end of this week,
we can probably finish this
by the end of this month.
What do you think?
- Great, compared to motherhood
it's a piece of cake.
Which reminds me do they still have that
white chocolate mousse thing?
- I hope so.
So how are you really?
- I'm driving my husband crazy.
- He's tough he can take it.
I was the same way.
I was so certifiable for three
months after Lilly was born.
It's totally normal.
- So I keep hearing.
- Yeah, but nobody really
understands, do they?
- No.
- Is there anything I can do?
- Split the chocolate
mousse thing with me.
- Waiter.
(gentle music)
- Veronica, you can't
just show up like this
in an hour's notice.
(gentle music)
"Let's play ride the horsey,"
that's what he would call it.
He would take me into his
study and lock the door,
and there was a couch,
a cold leather couch.
It had a blanket,
a big old soft blanket covering it,
and he would do it to me there.
- The blanket.
What color was it?
- Red.
- So it was you in my dream.
But how could I know that?
- Who knows you must have seen it sometime
and not known what it was.
"Ride the horsey."
- [Veronica] I'm sorry,
Becky, I'm so sorry.
- How could he do that to me?
- I don't know.
I don't know it's over.
It's all over.
- I really feel bad about this.
My wife knew that we had a
7:30 appointment with you.
I guess she got stuck at the office,
which is the reason we need to hire you
so she can get stuck at
the office more often.
Anyway, she should be here any minute.
Can I get you some more coffee?
- No, thank you, that's fine.
(crickets chirping)
- Sorry.
- Sorry, that's it.
Sorry end of story.
- Listen, Ted, I'm beat I gotta go to bed.
- No, no you listen.
A: You missed an appointment
with a perspective nanny
that was scheduled at your request,
and B: when I called your office,
they told me you went home early.
I didn't hear a word from you.
So I gotta figure either you're
dead on the road somewhere
or what having an affair?
- Is that what you think?
- I don't know what to think.
- That I'm having an affair.
- No, I don't think
you're having an affair
but at least it's an explanation.
Where the hell have you been?
- I went...
I can't talk to you when you're this way.
- Fine, that's okay, no, no, no.
So what do you wanna do you
wanna play a little Cribbage?
Should we watch some TV,
or you wanna just jump
into bed call it a day
no questions asked?
- That doesn't help, Ted.
- Well, what does really I'd like to know
because I spent my whole term break
taking care of my daughter
so that you could go back to work earlier.
God forbid we should all
spend sometime together.
It's not enough for you what do you want?
I am your husband not the hired help.
- I know, I know.
I am sorry.
I'm sorry I am just
under a lot of pressure.
- Well, how would I know that?
See you don't talk to me anymore.
I can see you going through something.
But wouldn't it make
sense to share it with me?
I mean isn't that why we got married
so that we could ease
the burden a little bit?
- I'm going through something so scary
I can't talk about it.
- [Ted] You can tell me anything, V.
- I can't not this, not yet.
- Then why are we together?
Why did we have a child?
- Oh, Ted, this has nothing to do--
- It has everything to do with it.
- Just stop.
I need to sort this out alone.
Can't you understand that?
- No.
No.
I gotta get out of here.
You think you can take care
of Jacqueline till I get back
or do you want me to call a sitter?
(baby cooing)
(soft lullaby music)
- This isn't gonna be done in time.
Hello.
Where are you?
- Sorry.
I don't think I'm gonna
make a full day, Joni.
You mind if I cut out
early I need to lie down.
- Sure, you know I think you pushed it
a little coming back so soon.
Why don't you take a little more time?
- I needed to be back here.
We actually hired a nanny.
Starts Monday.
- Okay.
Well, have a nice weekend.
- I will.
Ted.
- Me.
I'm sorry, honey.
I was trying to be as quiet as I could.
Blame your father for this.
This was his idea.
I love fishing but even the trotter
are a sleep at this time.
Besides, I don't relish
driving an hour and a half.
- Ted, don't go.
- Oh, right.
- I'm serious.
- I'm only exaggerating, you know.
I mean once I'm out there
on the river in the boat,
it's all okay.
- Please, don't go.
- Oh, right you want me to call
Malcolm Worth the third at dawn
and tell him that I'm gonna
cancel the fishing trip
that he's planned for
a whole month no way.
- I'm asking you not to go.
- Besides, you know, your
brother's going now too.
It's a whole big thing.
- I don't care.
- What's the matter are you sick?
- No.
I just don't want you
spending time with my father right now.
- I have to.
I want to.
You know I need a break.
Besides, your father and I
we have a good time together.
You should be happy.
- Don't talk to me like that.
- Like what?
- Like I'm crazy.
- Well, when you get like this
you know, I think you are crazy.
Hey, it's four o'clock in the morning.
Go back to bed.
- No, not until you deal with this.
- Deal with what?
Some irrational
middle-of-the-night decision that
all of a sudden I shouldn't
go fishing with your father.
What the hell is wrong with you?
I am going, got it.
I'll see you tonight.
(glass breaking)
I don't know what to do?
I don't know how to help you.
I think we need some professional help.
'Cause otherwise there's not
gonna be anything left to save.
- I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
(engine revving)
Hi.
- [Ted] What time is it?
- About 4:30.
Where's Jacqueline?
- Nap time.
You're home early.
- Yeah.
I wasn't feeling well.
What's new, right?
- You said it not me.
- I'm sorry, Ted, I really am.
I love you, you know.
- Yeah.
If it wasn't for you,
I don't know what my life would be like.
(soft music)
- Oh, I miss this.
(telephone ringing)
- Don't get it.
That's what answering machines are for.
I wanna talk.
- Hello, sorry went can't
get to the phone right now.
(baby crying)
I guess that's what fathers are for.
(machine beeping)
- Hi, little girl it's daddy.
I was just thinking about you.
I hope all is well with you.
How's my granddaughter?
I've got my hands full here
babysitting my other little pride and joy.
Here.
Say, hi, Christy.
Come on, darling, say hello
to your Aunt Veronica.
Never mind.
Well, alright we've got to go now.
We'll see you all.
- Dad.
- [Malcolm] We're
unavailable at the moment,
but leave a brief message
and we'll return your call.
- Becky, it's me can you talk?
I think something terrible is happening?
- What is it Jacqueline?
- No, not Jacqueline it's...
Oh, god, I think...
I think dad's doing it to Christy.
- [Becky] What?
How do you know?
- I just know.
I mean I don't know for sure.
It's just a feeling.
- [Becky] Veronica what I
told you about me and dad
happened a long time about.
I think maybe you're letting
this get out of hand.
- [Veronica] What if I'm not?
What if it's true?
He's spending a lot of time with her.
- It can't be true he's too...
I don't know he's too old.
It's in the past.
It happened to me not you.
I've moved on you gotta do the same.
Are you listening to me?
- Yes, I'm listening.
- Life goes on, okay.
Like you told me it's over.
It's all over.
There's nothing to worry
about anymore it's over.
(gentle music)
- You got my wife's number.
- Yes.
- Doctor's numbers by the phone.
- I got my beeper you can beep me anytime.
- We'll call, but everything's okay.
Nothing's gonna go wrong.
- Okay, okay right.
- Hi, Joan, bye Joan.
- Bye.
- Thanks for your car.
I didn't wanna wait for the Auto Club.
Not today I don't wanna be late.
- Then don't be late.
- Bye, Jacqueline.
Olivia.
- You be good for Olivia.
- We'll be just fine, yes, we will.
- She ate.
- Okay.
What a morning.
New nanny, Ted's first day back teaching.
When he came downstairs this morning
and found that flat
tire he nearly flipped.
Thanks for picking me up, Joni.
- No problem.
Well, you and Ted don't look like
you're ready to kill each other anymore.
Just maim.
That was a joke.
You remember jokes?
What is it Olivia and Jacqueline?
It's gonna be fine.
Woman is a natural.
- I know, I know.
- Why do you look like
you just left your baby
with a child molester.
- Why would you say that?
- What?
- Why in the hell
would you say something like
that about a child molester.
It's not funny.
- I didn't mean it.
Are you alright?
- No.
- [Joni] Can I help.
- I can't talk about it.
- Come on.
Does it have something to do with
what you and Ted are
going through in therapy?
- We don't need therapy, Joni.
I'm the one with the problem not Ted.
- No, the two of you are married,
which means you got a lot of stuff
you gotta work out together.
- Joni, my father raped my sister
when we were kids repeatedly in our house.
I just found out.
- So that's what's been going on with you.
- I don't know what to do.
- Does Ted know?
- No.
- Sweetie, he's your husband.
You gotta tell him.
- I'm so ashamed.
- You gotta tell him.
You gotta give him a break.
You gotta let him know what's
been going on with you.
- I know.
(soft music)
- Malcolm Worth.
Malcolm Worth.
It's unbelievable.
Malcolm Worth are you sure?
- Yes, I'm sure.
- It's hard to believe.
But Becky's always been a
little bit on the dramatic side.
You know, all I'm saying is that--
- She's not making it up.
She's telling the truth.
- Why all of a sudden?
- 'Cause she's been hiding it.
Why do you think she never comes home?
- The only reason I'm saying this is
because, you know, thinks get embellished.
You know, I mean when I was a kid
my father was the old
school, a disciplinarian.
You know, the back of the hand, the belt
all that old crap, you know.
But never thought about it being abuse.
It's just the way it was.
- Ted, hitting a kid is abuse.
I don't care what culture or day in age.
I mean can you imagine taking a strap
or the back of your hand to Jacqueline?
Can you?
- No.
No.
- I don't know what to do.
- What can you do?
It was 30 years ago it's over.
- But it's not over.
I think he's still doing it.
- What?
- To Christy.
I'm paralyzed.
I can't stop thinking about it.
I just can't let it go.
- [Ted] Nobody's asking you to.
- Oh, Ted, come on you are in a way.
- I just want you to be happy.
- Well, so do I.
I feel like I should
find out about Christy.
- I agree.
- So,
do I confront my brother?
My father?
(liquid pouring)
I feel sick.
Yes, I feel nauseous.
My head is spinning just
like when I was a kid,
just like when.
(soft music)
I wanna stop it
the pain,
my pain.
Christy's.
- How do you know Christy's in pain?
- I can see it.
Now when I look back
and I see her
especially when she's with him,
she has that lonely,
lonely look of fear.
Like she's the one
he's chose to hurt.
It's the most awful feeling.
- Veronica,
how do you know?
How do you know what Christy's feeling?
How?
(somber music)
- No, no, no, no daddy no.
(engine revving)
(soft music)
It's been a week since I've known, and I
I still answer his phone calls.
I still feel the need
to try and please him.
I still haven't had the
guts to confront him.
- Veronica, you're not even sure
in the legal sense that
he is abusing your niece.
If he is, we have to report it,
which means you have to be sure
in your mind about your own experience.
It's all part of one process.
- Yes, I know but what I can't figure out
is why I let it go on.
- [Walter] Christy.
- Me.
- Oh, what alternative did you have?
You were what seven, eight years old.
- I should have been able to do something.
- What, a child.
What?
- I was afraid of the room itself.
Until the other day when I went back there
and I realized that it was just a room
and I could've gotten away.
I could have runaway.
- To where?
- Who knows somewhere anywhere.
Who knows.
- Is Christy to blame?
- What.
- Do you blame your niece?
If indeed this is happening
to her, do you blame her?
- Of course not, no.
- Well, then why do you
blame yourself and Becky?
He was an adult and he was your father
what possible power could
you have had over him?
You were no different
then, than Christy is now.
No different at all.
- No, we're different Christy and I.
She has me.
- Are you nuts?
Where do you come up with this stuff, huh?
I mean what do you do sit around all day
watching talk shows.
I mean dad you're crazy.
- Tom, it happened.
It happened to me and Becky.
- And you both just happen today remember
exactly the same moment in
time because you're so close.
- No, no Becky has known.
That's why she's never around.
- Yeah, Becky, there's a source, boy,
a woman who up until three years ago
at the ripe old age of
37 couldn't keep a job
or stay with a guy for more than a week,
who in the course of her sordid life
has ingested more drugs
than a laboratory rat
and you're gonna believe what she says.
- Tom, will you keep voice down.
The kids will hear you.
- Oh, yeah, right, Jan.
It's okay for my sister to walk in here
telling us their grandfather
raped her when she was eight.
That's okay for them to hear.
- Just lower your voice.
- I'm not gonna lower
my voice not when she comes in here.
- Tom.
- What.
- What I really came here
to talk to you about--
- Wait you mean there's more, Veronica.
Well, gee, what now?
You found out mom's a terrorist.
Dad's running guns for the PLO.
- Tom, I have reason to believe
that dad's abusing Christy.
- What are you talking about?
- Okay, one, two.
One, two.
Okay, do you have any aces?
One.
You don't then go fish.
Here you go.
- Hi, sweetie.
- Hi.
- Aunt Veronica just wanted
to stop by for a minute.
She can't stay long.
- Hi, Christy, how you doing?
- Good, how's the baby?
- Oh, she's fine.
You know I know that
she would just love it
if you'd come by and play
with her would you like that?
- Can we?
- Sure, sometime soon.
- How long will she be a baby?
- For a while you've got time.
Listen how would you like it
if grandma and grandpa came with you?
No.
- Why not, Christy?
- So, what are you playing?
- School I'm teaching her to play Go Fish.
- Oh, that's your best game.
You always beat me.
- I beat daddy too.
- Yep, it's true.
- And you even beat grandpa
when you play it with him,
and he's good at games.
So, what's your favorite
game in the whole world
besides Go Fish?
- Swings at the park.
- Oh, I knew that.
'Cause you like to go so high.
And what's your least favorite?
Oh, come on you can't fool me.
If you have a best favorite game,
you have to have a least favorite right?
You can tell me, you know.
No matter what it is you can
always tell mommy and daddy.
It's okay to tell I promise.
So what is it?
- I hate the horsey
with grandpa.
- You know if you just telephoned,
I could've arranged to
have lunch with you,
but as it is I've gotta
be at the Athenaeum
in a meeting at 2:30,
well, 3:00 if I stretch it.
- It's alright, mother,
I don't need lunch.
I just wanted to talk.
- Everything alright at home, Ted, baby?
- Fine.
It's me I wanted to discuss actually.
- Oh, so now we go into a
discussion instead of a talk.
Well, that sounds serious have some tea.
- No, thanks.
- Mother, when we were kids,
you were out of lot, right?
- Veronica, if this is
gonna be one of these
mother/daughter sessions
where you inform me
that I neglected you as a child,
I have to tell you my conscience is clear.
Martha Richards has just gone through
a similar thing with Catherine.
She's 45 years old for God's sake.
- Would you listen to me, mother.
For once just listen.
(soft music)
You did neglect us but you know that.
You were never around but that's...
That's not the point.
It's what happened while you
were gone that's at issue.
- And what was that?
(soft music)
- Did you ever notice
that daddy treated us
Becky and me
differently?
- No.
I don't know what you're talking about.
This is not the time
to discuss this, honey.
- Daddy raped us, mother,
repeatedly
when we were small
children and you were away.
Did you hear me?
- Yes, I heard you.
- That's it.
You're walking away that's your response.
My god, mother, what is wrong with you?
- Nothing's wrong with me.
I am respectful of your father.
I will not give one iota of credence
or attention to such vile
accusations as you've made.
Whatever mental torture
you're putting yourself through, Veronica
as a result of whatever
fashionable therapeutic analysis
you happen to be going
into, it's your business.
I don't have to be a part of it.
- But you do, mother.
If you knew about it and
you allowed it to happen,
then you are just as sick as he is.
- All I ever observed was your
and your over-sexed sister
flirting madly with every man
who set foot in this house
including your own father.
(telephone ringing)
- Mother, we were children.
- [Clair] Hello.
Christy, oh, my god.
I'm coming right over.
- What happened?
- It was your brother.
You evidently spread your vile
poison over at his house yesterday.
- What about Christy.
- She's runaway.
- Oh, my god.
- [Christy] No, way I
don't wanna come down.
Daddy, make them go away.
- Oh, my god, Christy.
- Christy, honey, please talk to me.
- Christy, whatever's wrong
we're gonna fix it, okay.
I promise everything
is gonna be just fine.
Mommy and daddy are gonna fix everything.
- Honey, stay right where you are.
- Will you stay out of this please.
- I will not stay out of this.
- Please.
- Mommy, I'm afraid.
- [Janet] Why are you afraid now, Christy.
- It hurts.
- [Janet] What hurts?
- The game.
- What game, honey?
- Ride the horsey it hurted me so much.
I don't wanna play it anymore.
I don't wanna play.
- Honey.
Honey.
Honey, if I can promise you
that grandpa will never hurt you again.
- [Male] Watch you step there, sir.
- And that he'd never play
that game with you ever again,
would you come down and come
back home with us, honey?
- But he'll get mad at me?
- No, no honey he won't.
Look I'll talk to him, all right.
He'll listen to me he's my dad.
I listen to you don't I, sweetie?
I'm listen to you right now.
I promise you I'm gonna fix it
so that you never have to play
that stupid game ever again.
Okay.
- Okay.
- Okay, now is it alright
if I come over there,
and get you so that we can go home?
- [Male] Take it slow, sir.
Take it slow.
- Okay.
Hold on tight, honey.
- [Male] Take your time.
(board breaking)
(people gasping)
- Grab the board, grab the railing.
- He's alright.
- [Male] That's it.
- I'm alright, honey.
I'm okay just step, just step.
Alright I got you, sweetheart.
I got you, you're safe.
You're safe, Christy, I promise you.
With all my heart you're safe.
I love you sweetie.
- [Male] Don't try to
come back with the girl.
We'll come to you.
(somber music)
(screen door squeaking)
- Clair, where have you been?
What's going on are the kids alright?
- Malcolm Worth, sir?
- Yes, I am what the
hell is going on here.
- You're under arrest for
the rape of Christine Worth.
You have the right to remain silent.
Anything you say can be used
against you in a court of law.
You the right to talk to a lawyer.
- Clair, call the lawyer.
- [Clair] I will.
- [Officer] If you want a lawyer before
or during questioning.
- Oh, Malcolm.
- [Officer] One will be appointed
to represent you at no cost.
- I don't intend to sell
you a bill of goods.
The situation you've
all found yourselves in
is undoubted painful,
so I want to be real clear
about what lies ahead.
We've got two distinct cases here.
With regard to Becky and Veronica,
there's a very real possibility that
we'll never even got
as far as a court room
because of limitation statutes.
This all happened quite sometime ago.
- I read somewhere that if you can show
a present effect that you can
sometimes get around that.
- Sometimes is the
operative word so is effect.
It can get pretty dicey.
Now the fact that both of you
want to cooperate can only help.
As far as the case with
Christy, I'm going to be honest.
I'll need everyone's cooperation
to bring a successful prosecution.
- What kind of cooperation?
- A man like your father
is not likely to roll over and play dead
neither are his high-priced lawyers.
If Christy is our only witness,
it will be more difficult.
- But she is the only witness.
Nobody else was ever present.
- Right, but what happened to
Becky and Veronica is so similar
down to the phrase, "Ride the horsey"
that their testimony as well as yours
and Janet's as to what
your daughter told you
how she behaved around her father etcetera
will all be essential
in convincing a jury.
- What if...
What if we decide not to prosecute?
- You don't really have that option.
This is not technically
a crime against Christy.
It's a crime against the state,
and it's up to my office to
decide to prosecute or not?
- And when will you decide if you want to?
- I've already decided.
I want to.
Having intercourse with
a five year old child
is a heinous crime any way you slice it.
My only question is whether
I've got a strong enough case
to proceed should you all
decide not to work with us
in which instance I may proceed any way.
I think Malcolm Worth is a dangerous man.
- Alright, alright hold on.
- Mr. Worth, I know this
is difficult to hear.
But I am involved on a daily basis
with children who are sexually
and physically abused by adults.
It ain't pretty as they say.
I know a thing like this
can tear a family apart.
But truth be told the damage
has already been done to all of you.
The point now is to protect this child
and any other child from
suffering the same abuse.
So,
I am asking for cooperation
from all of you.
Why don't you use our
conference room to discuss it.
- We can't just slap
his hand and walk away.
I think we should cooperate.
- What do we get out
of it in the long run?
Revenge.
You think that's worth it?
- This has nothing to
do with revenge, Becky.
It's like she said.
It's a heinous crime.
It could happen again.
- So what do you think dad's gonna
hang around the school yards.
We just keep him away
from Christy that's all.
- We have a daughter too, Tom.
- Yeah, so what are you saying?
- I'm saying it's not
as simple as you think.
- Well, sure he's not your father.
- Well, he's my father.
- Excuse me, but we owe this to Christy.
I'm not gonna let her go
through this by herself.
What's wrong with you, Tom?
- What's wrong.
What kind of a son testifies
against his father?
What's kind of a son would I be?
- What kind of a father
would you be if you didn't?
- Tom, you were the first one
down at the police precinct.
Remember how you felt?
If we don't do this for Christy now,
we're just as guilty
as dad, maybe more so.
- Maybe this was not the
best place for us to come.
- It doesn't matter, mother.
Thank you.
- Thanks.
I'm told that you still haven't
decided whether or not to go
through with this prosecution.
I'm asking you not to.
- It's not up to me, mother.
It's up to the DA.
- Do you know that the bank
has asked your father
to take early retirement
starting next month?
Do you know that this country club
where he's been a member for over 30 years
has not invited him back?
- You still don't get it do you?
- Get it, I'm living with it.
- You think this is about dad,
about what happens to dad.
What about Christy, what
about five-year-old Christy?
You think she deserves to suffer?
- No.
No, I do not and I blame you.
A five-year-old child does not come up
with vile accusations
such as this on her own.
She has to be coached.
- Coached.
You don't believe that, mother.
Why would I do that?
Why would I do something like that?
- It is revenge, Veronica,
pure and simple and it's perverse.
- What dad did to me and
Becky was bad enough,
but now for you to twist things around
that's what's perverse.
- Your father's an old man, Veronica.
It is in your power to ruin,
devastate what's left of his life.
But I must ask you where
is the joy in that?
- It's late do you wanna go to bed?
- Huh?
- Wanna go to bed?
- No, you go ahead, honey.
I've got some more I've gotta read here.
- You don't have to.
You're not the lawyer.
It's not your job you don't have to.
- What are you saying, Ted?
- Never mind I'll see you in the morning.
- Ted, come on please.
Don't do this.
- I'm very sorry for what happened to you,
and I wish I could make it
all go away, make it better.
But we have a life together.
We have a family of our own,
and it would be nice if
we could get back to it.
Move on that's all.
- Move on.
- Yeah.
- Ted, I am stuck in it.
You think now because it's out in the open
it gets any easier.
If anything it gets worse.
It didn't happen to you.
- That's right, didn't happen to me.
Other things happened to me.
- Yes, but what what happened
to you didn't make it
impossible for you to
function normally this does.
Ted, I'm sorry.
I wanna come back to our life,
to our marriage, Jacqueline.
It's all I can think about some days.
It just seems so far away.
- We're right here.
We're right here.
- I know you are.
(telephone ringing)
- Hello, sorry, we're unable
to take your call right now.
Machine will get it.
- [Clair] It's mother.
We're at the hospital.
Dad's had a heart attack.
- It's me what happened?
Of course, tonight.
- How bad?
- They don't know.
- What?
- She asked me if I was satisfied.
(soft music)
- [Female] Dr. Gerald Steiner
please call the OR two.
Dr. Gerald Steiner please call the OR two.
Dr. Peterson radiology.
(soft music)
(heavy breathing)
- [Female] Dr. Copeland,
Dr. Robert Copeland.
- I forget if you said real sugar or fake.
- Neither.
- I got both.
- Is there milk?
- I thought you said black.
I'm sorry I'll go get some.
- No, no, it's okay this is fine.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- [Female] Dr. Coleman, Dr. Sarah Coleman
please call the surgery unit.
- You know, I've been thinking.
Seeing dad like this, you
know, with the tubes and all
I just feel like this is all our fault.
I know what you're gonna say,
and there's a part of me that just wants
to see the old bastard suffer and die.
But then there's another part
that knows he's just sick mentally.
I just feel like maybe
we've punished him enough.
- Punished him.
Tom, it's not our fault.
This isn't about punishment.
It's about recognition.
I think we have to go through with this
or where will it stop.
- Veronica, look I...
I am truly sorry for what
happened to you and Becky.
I mean...
I mean I blame myself.
- You had nothing to do with this.
- Will you let me finish please?
I mean where was I?
Why didn't I see?
I'm your brother.
I'm your guy's older brother.
I was supposed to look out for you two.
- You were just a kid.
- But what about now, huh?
I mean how could I let
this happen to Christy.
I'm her father for god's sake.
- Oh, Tom.
Oh, Tom.
Why should I be the one to
feel the anguish over this?
I lived it.
I lived with it.
And now I have to live with the knowledge
that I'm destroying his life.
Why because I made it all up?
- Is that what you think
that you made it up?
- No, no I just can't
let myself off the hook.
- [Walter] What hook?
- That I should have never
brought this out in the open.
- Well, what was this alternative
to let your niece be permanently injured
the way you and Becky were?
- No, no, Walter I know that.
I am just angry.
I am just so damn angry I could scream.
Who are you so angry at
by the way, yourself?
- No.
My father.
- Then maybe it's time you told him.
- We have nothing to say to each other.
- Yes, we do.
- My lawyer's handling this.
You can face it with him.
- No, daddy.
I have to face this with you.
- What the hell do you want from me?
- An explanation.
- For what?
- An admission.
An apology.
Something.
Anything.
- I have nothing to apologize for.
I've done nothing to you.
If you insist on going forward
with these trumped up charges--
- You raped me, daddy,
why did you do that?
- I don't know what you're talking about.
- I looked up to you.
Why did you wanna hurt me?
Did you hate me that much?
- Hate you.
I loved you.
Both of you.
You were all I had.
My little girls.
You were my pride and joy.
- Don't you know what you did to us?
- I don't understand you, Veronica,
and I want you to stop this.
- I can't.
- Well, then you can consider
me your father no longer.
- You stopped being my father
the first time you forced
me to have sex with you.
- Veronica.
You disappoint me, deeply.
- It won't work, dad.
I'm going to see that you're prosecuted.
- Then you are no longer my daughter.
- I can understand about Becky.
I can't believe that you would
actually go through with this,
and Tom is going along with you.
- Yes, Tom is going along with us.
- Why.
- Because we all feel
that we have to, mother.
- Oh, that's a load of crap, Veronica.
It is hateful and it is selfish.
It's unnatural and it
is crap, do you hear me?
Why?
Why in your sordid little
mind do you believe
that you have to go through
with this wretched thing?
- So that Becky and I can go on from here
and restore some kind of a life,
and so that Christy has a chance at one.
I hope someday you'll understand.
(soft music)
- I should've gone in with you.
I couldn't.
- I know.
It's okay.
- No, it's not.
It's not okay.
(soft music)
- I sat on the couch, you know.
And for the first time ever
I didn't wanna vomit.
- It's a start.
- Yeah.
(engine revving)
(baby cooing)
It's gonna be difficult for a while
with the trial and all.
It's not over yet.
Can you stand it?
- With a good looking woman like you
and a baby like this I can stand anything.
(soft music)
There we go.
Look who's here and it's
time for the bottle.
Come on here we go.
Up we go.
- Let me.
Hi, Jacqueline.
Hi, sweetheart.
I wanna try again.
Come here sweetheart, come here.
Oh, sweetie.
(soft music)
(MultiCom jingle)