(FILM REELS)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
It's night.
Everyone, close your eyes.
Mafia... open your eyes.
Mafia... kill someone.
Mafia... close your eyes.
Doctor... open your eyes.
Doctor... save someone.
Doctor... close your eyes.
It's morning. Wake up.
Last night,
the Mafia killed someone.
The Doctor didn't
guess correctly.
And who was killed...
Sara.
Oh come on,
Doctors (INDISTINCT).
(LAUGHING)
Let's take a vote.
Who says, Babak?
(LAUGHING)
Look at her. She's delighted.
Okay.
Who thinks it's, Mohsen?
You're making a mistake.
Raise your hand.
You'll see.
Who thinks it's, Farhad?
Who thinks it's, Neda?
Come on.
Neda, defend yourself.
You're making a mistake.
One of you guys is a citizen.
You're making me
out to be the Mafia.
You're letting them win.
Anyone buy that?
Thank you very much.
Sorry Neda.
You've been condemned to death.
Your last words.
My last words?
Babak, look after our baby.
I lost the game.
It's just a game, sweetheart.
Don't worry about Shabnam.
I'll find her a sweet mommy.
My ghost will find you
and pluck your eyes out.
You're giving me goosebumps.
Not funny.
The Mafia is the winner.
Neda and Sara were
both citizens.
See, I told you.
But you two are so good at lying.
It's hard to believe a word you say.
Who was it then?
Obviously it was, Babak.
Babak and Mohsen.
I told Farhad but he's too
stubborn.
Come on.
Let's get some shots.
Forget this.
Where did you put it?
It's in the freezer.
Neda, check on Shabnam.
Make sure she's not up.
She's asleep.
The monitor is in my pocket.
I guess I'll get the
barbecue ready.
I know this brand.
It doesn't sit well.
You'll be fine, give it up.
Makes me throw up.
Where are your glasses?
Ladies. Who's up for a shot?
I'm breastfeeding.
It's good for you.
It'll keep the baby asleep all night.
- He's crazy.
- Want one?
I'll take one.
Anyone else?
You know Mohsen and
I don't drink.
You guys are party poopers.
So it's you, me and a
little for Sara.
Don't go overboard
and get drunk.
Don't be like that.
Just a couple shots for
my toothache.
I'm serious.
I don't want to deal with it.
Just take it easy.
We need someone
to take care of you.
Where are the kids sleeping?
(CHILD LAUGHING)
They're in the
room with Shabnam.
Guys. Come on out.
What are you doing?
Come on, she's awake.
Don't wake her up. Let
her sleep.
Is she awake?
Sweetheart.
My pretty girl.
Sleep. Sleep my love.
What is it?
What happened?
Why are you looking at
me like that?
Sleep.
Sleep, sweetheart.
(CAT MEOWS)
Maryam. Open your eyes.
Look at me, call me.
It's daytime. The sun is out...
We have to learn this
before we can teach you.
You'll have to learn it.
We have to learn it.
Do these.
You're welcome.
Like this?
No. Put it through the middle.
You've never done this before?
Like this.
Yes, that's better.
I'm learning a little bit.
Well done.
You know last week for the
first time I made gourmet subzi
and Farhad was very impressed.
Bravo.
Very nice.
Thanks.
Have you guys decided
on a second baby?
One is enough.
When Barbod grows a
little I'll have my second.
That's a handful.
An only child becomes spoiled.
I don't want him to
be alone. It's not fair.
I wouldn't mind another one,
but it's really hard.
Just one has been a struggle.
Shabnam's a good baby.
What would you do
if you had a boy?
Shabnam is a quiet child.
We're the ones who are on edge.
It was good you
waited before you had her.
Why?
You were alone in
Iran while Babak was here.
It would have been difficult.
That's true.
Yes?
Can I get a skewer?
Yes, dear.
What is it?
I just got it today.
Look at you.
I didn't know you got a tattoo.
I wanted the swelling
to go down first.
- Do you like it?
- Yes.
Does Babak like it?
The other half is on his arm.
How fancy.
I know.
I wanted one like yours.
When we both decided
to get it, I put it here.
What is it?
I really don't know.
It was in the tattoo
artist's book.
You don't know?
You're special.
Well, it's very unique.
What is it?
This toothache's been
killing me all night.
I could have brought you
something from the hospital.
It came on so suddenly.
Have you quit?
Sort of.
Neda's sensitive to it.
She's asthmatic.
I don't smoke in the house.
Neda okay? Is she settled?
We got into it again.
She's homesick.
She's trying to like it
here for Shabnam's sake.
Are you two happy?
She's happy, and I'm happy.
That's great.
You're hardly around
these days, Doctor.
Since I was transferred
to emergency...
...my job has become difficult.
How hard could it be?
You stick people with needles.
What do you know?
Ever been in a situation...
...where someone is brought
to the ER under your watch,
and as hard as you try
to save them...
...there is no way?
This morning, a young girl came in at
3:00 a.m.
She was my last patient.
Did you know her?
You two are at it again?
Mohsen says dinner is ready.
Okay.
Come on. Let's go have dinner.
Guys, it's freezing.
Don't come out.
Spend the night.
I know, but it's better we
get back.
Thanks for everything.
Mohsen, thank you.
We had a great time.
My pleasure.
- Thank you so much.
- Bye, Elahe.
Take this too, thank you.
You okay?
Yeah.
I'll get it for you.
(CAR ALARM BEEPING)
You didn't finish your story.
It's nothing, never mind.
I told you a hundred times.
Say it all,
or don't mention it at all.
I wanted to say something but didn't
want it to ruin our night.
Talk later.
Take care of yourself.
We'll talk later.
Farhad, it's been our pleasure.
Likewise.
It was a great evening.
Good night dear, thank you.
I'll drive.
Why?
You want to drive like this?
Why not?
Because you're drunk.
Give it to me.
Better than having a
suspended license. Get in.
Come on, the baby is going
to wake up.
(CAR DOOR CLOSES)
(CAR ENGINE REVVING)
(SOFT MUSIC)
What was Farhad talking about?
What's your deal with Farhad?
You're both the same.
You know how he is.
He didn't look well.
I asked, but he said nothing.
(PHONE RINGING)
Hello, Mohsen.
Yes, brother?
Forget it. Nothing I can do now.
No, I'll get it when I see you.
Okay.
Thanks, it was a fun night. Bye.
What did he say?
I left my phone charger.
Good you don't leave
yourself behind.
Let's head back and sleep there.
I said we wouldn't stay.
I won't go back.
I want to sleep in my own bed.
(GPS RECALCULATING)
Are you paying attention?
What is it doing? It's
going crazy.
(GPS RECALCULATING)
It says to turn right.
Go straight.
Wait, let's see
where it's saying to go.
(CHILD CRYING)
Be careful!
(BRAKES SCREECH)
You woke the baby.
Move your hand,
I want to go backwards.
What for? You can't...
There's no U-turn ahead.
You can't reverse.
Go straight.
Stop talking.
Oh, god.
(CAR HONKING)
(CAR BRAKES SQUEALING)
It's acting crazy.
Keep your eyes on the road.
(GPS MESSAGE)
There's something
on the road. Be careful!
(CAR BRAKES SQUEALING)
You ran it over.
What are you talking about?
Just look where you're going!
Don't drink if you can't
handle it.
You know how to ruin the night.
You nag too much.
Why are you sitting? Go check.
What? Go check what?
Go see what you did.
What have I done?
It's just a cat, so what?
Why is everything such an issue?
(CAR DOOR CLOSES)
What happened?
Nothing.
What do you mean, nothing?
Nothing happened.
What was that sound, then?
Take a look for yourself
if you don't believe me.
Give me Shabnam's bag.
Hi, baby.
Sweetheart.
Throw this in the trash.
(COUGHS)
(CAT MEOWS)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC)
Come on.
Please let me drive.
Will you stop?
What difference does it make?
We should go back to
Mohsen's house.
I said we're not going back,
so why should I go back?
You're so stubborn.
You won't let me drive,
you won't go back.
I don't want you to drive.
You're not well.
What's wrong with me?
You don't pay attention.
If you have it all figured out why did
you lose your license to the police?
What does that have to do with
it? I didn't have my insurance.
Let go of getting behind
the wheel.
'My license wasn't with me.'
Just leave it.
You tell me, what should we do?
- Tell me...
- You reject everything I say.
You tell us what to do, my love.
I don't know. Let's go
to a hotel.
For a half hour drive?
Half an hour ago you said,
'half an hour.'
We've been driving around
in circles for two hours.
Think of the poor baby.
Where are you going?
You said go to a hotel.
So let's go.
- What can I do?
- Do whatever you want.
(SIREN WALING)
Is this it?
Yes.
Don't you want to go to
a more crowded one?
This was the closest one.
It doesn't make a difference.
Give me my sweatshirt.
In the back.
Wait. Let's go together.
Bring Shabnam's bag.
(CAT GROWLS)
(INDISTINCT MUMBLING)
(KNOCKING ON WINDOW)
(BUZZER HUMS)
(GROAN)
Stay back, what are you doing.
Why did you do that?
You okay?
(SPEAKING PERSIAN)
Forget him, let's go.
What?
Let's go inside.
Good evening.
Welcome to the Hotel Normandie.
Hi. How are you doing?
Good. Thanks.
Who's the man
by the front door?
I'm sorry, I
didn't see anyone.
What, did something happen?
He harassed my family.
Oh, dear!
I'll make sure, I look
into that, don't worry.
How many nights
will you be staying?
Tonight, just tonight.
Oh, well you know we only
have a suite available.
That's fine. Good.
What's your name?
Babak Naderi.
N-A-D-E-R-I.
Could you please sign
in right there on the pad?
As you probably saw, we keep
the doors locked at night.
So if you ever would like
to go out, just let me know
and I'll open up
the doors for you
and your own room key, will
let you in from the outside.
Just please. Don't
ever push the door.
And here's your room key.
Thank you.
That is on the
fourth floor room 414.
And the elevator is
right around the corner.
Welcome to the Hotel Normandie.
- Thank you.
- Thanks.
(ELEVATOR BELL DINGS)
(MUSIC PLAYING IN BACKGROUND)
(SIGHS)
Where's Shabnam?
I changed her clothes
and put her in the other room.
Is she sleeping there?
Yes, it's comfortable.
I'll take a shower, you
get to bed.
Okay.
(SHOWER RUNNING)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC)
(WATER DRIPPING)
(BABY LAUGHING)
Neda.
The baby is awake.
Get up please, see what
she wants.
What is it, my love?
What is it?
My love. What is it?
Sleep, my love. Sleep.
(BABY CRYING)
Don't. Don't, my love.
LITTLE BOY: Mommy!
Mommy!
(DOOR OPENS)
Hi.
Are you lost?
WOMAN: Hey.
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
(CRYING)
(DOOR CLOSES)
Sleep, my love. Sleep.
(LOUD THUD)
What is it...
It was nothing...
Here, my love. Take this.
Sleep.
(WATER DRIPS)
(LAUGHING)
(CRYING)
What is it, dear? I'm here.
Let's go downstairs.
Come here, my love. Come here.
What is it?
(CREAKING FLOOR)
(DOOR OPENS)
(DOOR CLOSES)
Sit here.
Yes, my love. Let's go.
Let's get you some milk.
It's okay, my love.
(ELEVATOR BELL DINGS)
(SMOOTH LOBBY MUSIC)
Sir. Hello.
Hello.
Can I help you?
I need to get some
hot water, please.
- Of course, follow me.
- Thank you.
- Oh, let me.
- Oh, may I?
- Sure.
- She is so cute.
- Thank you.
You know I met
Bobby Kennedy once?
You know who that was?
No, I don't.
He was the Attorney
General of the United States
under his brother, President
John Fitzgerald Kennedy.
They were both assassinated.
Oh yes.
I've known a lot of people
and I've been to many places.
Paris, nightclub shootings.
Puerto Rico, where a hurricane
killed over 2000 people.
Las Vegas in the Hotel Bellagio.
I was here last week when that
little African-American boy
was shot and killed.
And the ghost fire where the
warehouse burned 40 people
to death in front of my eyes.
Oh yes.
I've seen a lot of
death. All sorts of it.
But the worst, the worst.
It's the death of a child
that is very painful.
Sometimes there's
just no way out.
You know, it's like quicksand,
the more you struggle,
the deeper you get in.
Oh, I'm terribly sorry if
my words disturbed you.
Have a peaceful night.
(BACKGROUND MUSIC)
(INAUDIBLE CONVERSATION)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
What are you doing here?
When did you come downstairs?
I came to get hot water
for the baby.
You can go.
I'll put her to sleep.
I said, you can go.
I don't know why she's
acting this way tonight.
She's happy.
She likes to play, I guess.
Isn't that right?
Go upstairs and sleep.
I'll put her to sleep and
come up.
Are you sure?
Did she sleep?
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
What is it?
What's wrong?
Where's the baby?
What do you mean, 'where's
the baby?'
What happened?
Why is Shabnam here?
You took her from me!
I was asleep.
You left the baby alone
and came up?
Give her to me.
Give her to me!
- Leave her alone.
- Give her to me!
Have you gone crazy?
I handed her to you!
What are you talking about?
What if something had
happened to her?
Have you gone crazy?
My sweetheart.
Go upstairs.
Let's go.
I'll bring her myself. You go.
Mommy's here.
Neda...
What's happened now?
Nothing, sorry.
Call if you need anything.
Go to bed. I'm coming.
(DOOR CLOSING)
(SLOW FOOTSTEPS)
(FILING NAILS)
What are you doing this
late at night?
Is Shabnam asleep?
Yes.
Babak...
Why did you leave me?
What?
What are you saying...
...this late at night?
(FILING INTENSIFIES)
(WHISPERING)
Babak...
(GHOSTLY MUSIC)
(SOFT THUD)
Babak, open the
door if you're awake.
What?
What's the matter?
Why are you acting like this?
I had a hard time
getting her to sleep.
I'm talking to you.
Why are you staring like that?
Give me the baby.
You've lost it. I'm not
letting you drink again.
Give me the baby!
Where were you?
Where was I?
Where was I? Have you
lost your mind?
Where were you just now?
(CRYING)
I can't even talk to you.
You're being ridiculous.
It's nothing sweetie, sleep.
Turn off the light.
It's nothing, my love.
Just go to sleep.
Sleep, my love. Sleep.
Sleep my love.
Babak, what's with you?
I'm tired of this.
Where were you, just now?
What do you mean, 'where was I?'
I was downstairs.
Weren't you just sitting
on that chair filing your nails?
Babak, what are you
talking about?
I don't know what to...
(RUNNING FOOTSTEPS)
What's that?
I heard it before.
What's going on in this dump?
(PHONE RINGING)
Where the hell is he?
- Where are you going?
- I'm going upstairs to check.
(LAUGHTER)
Excuse me.
Hello.
(ELEVATOR DOOR CLANGS OPEN)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC)
(TENSE MUSIC BUILDS UP)
(DOOR CLICKS OPEN)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC)
Sleep, sweetheart. Sleep.
Sleep, sweetheart.
Take a look.
What is it?
I didn't take this picture
of Shabnam.
You probably took it by mistake.
You think I'm an idiot?
I wouldn't forget taking a picture of
Shabnam with my flash.
You check on her with your
phone's flashlight all the time.
You touched it by mistake.
What else could it be?
Someone came into our room and took a
picture of her with my phone.
What was up there anyways?
Nothing, it's the roof.
Just a bunch of pipes.
It's the pipes then...
You exaggerate.
(DRAGGING NOISES)
Does that sound like pipes?
(DOOR KNOCK)
Who is it?
Who was it?
Who was that?
No one.
Give me the phone.
That's ridiculous.
Do hotels have stalkers?
Who are you calling?
Hello, I wanted to report
that my family is in a hotel
and someone keeps disturbing us.
There are no hotel staff around.
We called.
No, they haven't
stolen anything.
They're just disturbing us.
No, I haven't seen anyone.
We're staying in
Hotel Normandie.
My name is Babak Naderi.
B-A-B-A-K N-A-D-E-R-I.
We're waiting, thank you.
(PHONE BEEPS)
(SPEAKING IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
What are the police going to do?
We didn't see anyone.
Let's go.
What do you mean?
Let's go downstairs.
Leave her,
she was just falling asleep.
What's with you tonight?
Why are you acting like
this, Babak?
Come, get up.
My head is exploding.
Can I take a 10 minute nap?
(CRIES)
Let's go.
(DOOR CREAKING)
LITTLE BOY: Mommy... Mommy?
(RUNNING NEARBY)
Did you hear that?
Yes.
I'll go check.
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC)
(DRIPPING)
(DOOR CREAKS OPEN)
I'm drunk and hallucinating,
what about you?
I don't understand...
...what's happening now.
It was very close.
Who was he calling ‘mommy'?
How would I know?
I'm not even sure
I heard him correctly.
He called out ‘mommy' twice.
How can you not be sure?
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
Were you the ones that called?
Yes.
Are you surprised to see me?
Weren't you
expecting the police?
Oh yes.
How did you get in?
The door was open.
It should be locked.
How did you find our room?
The check-in book.
It seems you're the only guests.
Oh, really?
May I come in?
Sure, please.
(DOOR CLOSES)
So how can I help you?
Someone's been
disturbing us all night.
Can you explain
exactly what's happened?
The first time I was in
the lobby, a woman came.
When I went back, she was gone.
I don't understand.
I mean, there was
someone in the lobby,
but they disappear.
They vanished.
I don't know.
Maybe. And second time
there was a woman
in our room right there.
The same one that vanished?
I didn't see her
in second time.
Can you confirm this?
I'm not sure.
Are you sure you
weren't imagining this?
No, it's happened twice.
Are you taking anything?
Like what?
Just answer the question.
Yes or no.
Of course not.
I don't do drugs.
What's the smell
on your breath.
It's just my mouthwash.
It has alcohol in it, you know?
I have a toothache.
Is there something that
you're not telling me?
No. Ask my wife.
Someone was making
noise on the roof.
Someone's been
knocking on the door.
Did you see them?
No, there was no one there.
Look it's five in the morning.
And you want me to find
somebody knocking on your door?
Who ran away in a hotel?
They didn't run away.
They vanished too.
You came all this
way to make fun of me?
No, I'm not making fun of you.
You're the one
that's fooling me.
I'm done.
Look, please, sir,
it's long night.
Babak, stay calm. Don't get mad.
Okay. I'm sorry.
My wife is right.
Before you came.
We heard a child calling his
mother from the bathroom.
She heard it.
Yes. True.
So what about the child?
The child wasn't there.
Let me get this straight
just like all the others.
May I?
Sure.
(BABY COOING)
Yes, my love.
Sweetheart.
So this is your only child?
- Yes.
- I thought you had another.
Well, what do you mean?
You said a child
called out to you.
I can see that your
daughter's just a baby.
No, he didn't call me.
He just said mommy.
Excuse me, sir.
It seems you didn't
understand exactly.
No, I understood completely.
You said you heard sounds,
you said you saw
people disturbing you
but they're not here now.
This isn't a police matter.
You guys need to find
yourself a ghost hunter.
Ghost?
Yeah.
If he can catch it,
and doesn't scam you.
Are you messing with us?
No, I'm not kidding.
We deal in facts.
Things we can see,
not hallucinations.
But I'm telling the truth.
Your baby's beautiful.
May I hold her?
Yes.
Come, my love.
Oh thank you.
Oh she's adorable.
Take care of her.
Do you have children?
I did, a daughter.
What do you mean "Did?"
She was run over by a car.
I'm sorry.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
Who is that?
I don't know.
It's probably my
partner, let him in.
(GHOSTLY MUSIC)
(CRYING)
Wasn't he just here?
(DOOR OPENS)
(TENSE MUSIC)
(CAT GROWLS)
What happened?
What...
Come on.
(BUZZER HUMS)
(PANTING)
What is it?
Your keys?
Shit! Shit! Shit!
Let me come, too.
Stay, I'll be right back.
(DOOR BUZZES OPEN)
(HINGES CREAK AS DOOR CLOSES)
(SOOTHING LOBBY MUSIC)
(CAT GROWLS)
(MUMBLES)
(GASPS)
Sir what do you want?
(SPEAKING PERSIAN)
(PANTING)
(SOMBER MUSIC)
They hear the truth,
morning comes.
You...
You speak Farsi?
Say it.
What...
What should I say?
Neda, neda.
Get in the car.
(CAR DOOR CLOSES)
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
(METALLIC CLINK AND ROLLING)
(WOMAN HUMMING)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC)
(WATER DRIPS DOWN)
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
(SCREAMING)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
(GROANS)
(ELEVATOR BELL DINGS)
(THUD)
(PHONE RINGING)
(KNOCKING ON CAR)
(GASPS)
LITTLE BOY: Mommy?
Let me play with my sister.
(MYSTERIOUS MUSIC)
(CRYING)
(SIGHS)
(ELEVATOR STOPS)
(KNOCKING DOOR)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
(UPBEAT MUSIC)
Remember.
(ELEVATOR BELL DINGS)
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
(DOOR BUZZES AND UNLOCKS)
(SOBBING)
What happened?
Water... give me water.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Get up.
Let's go.
(DOOR RATTLES)
(BANGING THE DOOR)
(WHISPERING IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
(GROANS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Hey!
Come here.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
Let's go upstairs.
Where?
Get up.
Get up!
(BANGING ON DOOR)
(DOOR CREAKS OPEN)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
What are you waiting for?
Do something.
What do you want me to do?
I don't know, call someone.
Who?
I don't know...
Farhad... Mohsen.
Hello... Hello, Farhad...
Hello, Farhad, how are you?
Farhad, sorry. I know
it's 5:00 a.m.
We came to a hotel...
Hello...
Farhad!
Damn it!
He's not answering?
(PHONE BEEPING)
Hello...
Hello, Farhad?
Farhad?
Farhad, we need help.
Hello... do you hear me?
It didn't ring... and you didn't
answer Neda's phone.
I don't know where my phone is.
Maybe I left it in the car.
I think Neda's phone is in
the car. Listen to me.
What's wrong with you?
We came to this hotel,
but something's happening to us.
We can't figure it out.
Hotel?
What are you doing in a hotel?
I don't have time to explain.
We needed to spend
the night somewhere.
We ran out of gas... it
doesn't matter.
Get here as soon as you can.
Now?
Yes. Now.
Why?
There are people doing things...
harassing us... I don't know... I...
Who? Are you okay?
I don't know. They're
stalking us.
I don't know what's going on.
I don't know what's happening.
Please get over here.
Stop asking so many questions.
Did you call the police?
What about the receptionist?
Yes, we did.
No one is doing a damn thing!
Please come, Farhad.
Come!
You said calling the
police was useless?
Now you're calling me.
For what?
What do you want me to do?
What's he saying?
Let me tell you something...
...put both of your minds
at ease.
Stop looking.
There's no way out for you two.
What're you saying, Farhad?
Are you high?
What are you talking about?
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC)
There's no way out.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Babak, could it be because
of these?
Because of what?
These tattoos.
Are you out of your mind?
Don't talk nonsense.
I don't know, maybe it's
some kind of a curse.
What's that got to do with it?
Please don't start with
any of your nonsense.
What time is it?
Why doesn't the sun rise?
(COUGHS)
Babak, what happened to you?
LITTLE BOY: Mom... Mommy...?
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
Mommy.
Why aren't you
telling dad what you did?
Say it.
(SCREAMING)
(CRYING)
What's the matter, Neda?
What's wrong?
I didn't keep my baby.
What?
What are you talking about?
The baby is okay sleeping there.
What are you saying?
Neda, talk to me.
Five years ago...
when you came here...
...I realized I was pregnant.
I hadn't heard from
you for a while.
You were supposed to return...
...but you didn't.
I didn't want to have
a child without a father.
I had an abortion.
Why didn't you tell me?
Where were you?
You weren't there.
I didn't think you'd come back.
(BABY CRIES)
Get up, the baby is restless.
Let's get out of here.
The power is back.
Get up, Neda.
Let's get out of this shit hole.
(BUZZER HUMS)
(RATTLING DOORS)
(GRUNTS)
You...
(GASPS)
What are you hiding from me?
What... what are you
talking about?
The man at the door...
...said, if they hear the truth,
it'll be morning.
As soon as I told the truth,
the power came on.
What are you hiding from me?
This damned door's lock
is busted.
We just have to get out of here.
That's all.
Stay here until I return.
Don't go anywhere.
Where are you going?
Stay there.
(CLOCK TICKING)
(BANGING ON DOOR)
I found another way out.
Wait there until I come back.
(DOOR CLOSES)
SOPHIA: Why are you
running away from me?
Sophia.
(GRUNTS IN PAIN)
SOPHIA: You
said you loved me.
You lied to me.
You lied to me
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
Why didn't you leave her?
You did this to me.
You did this.
There's no way out.
Say it.
- No please.
- Say it.
Please, I'm sorry.
- Say it!
- Sorry, honey.
SOPHIA: Say it!
(SLASH OF KNIFE)
(GASPS)
Neda!
Shab...
Shabnam...
Shabnam, what?
Let me see, what happened?
Let me see.
Let me look at you!
- Shabnam...
- Shabman, what?
Go...
...find Shabnam.
Where is she?
(CAT GROWLING)
(CRYING)
Go!
Go...
...Shabnam.
Shabnam.
(BABY CRIES)
(CAT MEOWS)
(WAILING)
(HINGES SQUEAK)
(CRYING)
(CAT MEOWS)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
(COUGHING)
OFFICER VOICEOVER:
Is there something
that you're not telling me?
SOPHIA VOICEOVER:
There's no way out.
RECEPTIONIST VOICEOVER:
Sometimes,
there's just no way out.
You know it's like quicksand.
SOPHIA VOICEOVER:
Come with me.
RECEPTIONIST VOICEOVER:
The more you struggle.
- There is no way out.
- The deeper you get in.
SOPHIA VOICEOVER:
There's no way out.
Come with me.
(ELECTRONIC HUM)
Come on.
You can do this.
(ELECTRONIC HUM)
(CLOCK TICKING)
(BABY WAILING)
SOPHIA VOICEOVER:
Come with me.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(OPENS DOOR)
(SPEAKING PERSIAN)
From the darkness of night...
...to the keeper of morning.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
From the darkness of night...
...to the keeper of morning.
(TERRIFYING MUSIC)
(SLASH OF BLADE)
(SCREAMING)
(GROANS)
(KNIFE CLATTERS TO THE FLOOR)
(CLOCK CONTINUES TICKING)
(BABY WAILING)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
(MUSIC STOPS)
(WATER DRIPS)
(GASPS)
(FLICKS LIGHT SWITCH)
(DRAWING THE CURTAINS)
(SPITS)
(WATER DRIPPING)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
(HAUNTING MUSIC)
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
(SOMBER PIANO MUSIC)
(SINGING IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE)