(ominous music)
(electricity buzzing)
(tinkling music)
(ominous music)
(speaking foreign language)
(tense music)
(hammer bangs)
(soft pop music)
- Damn.
(putty thuds)
What the hell?
- [Man] You patch that hol?
- I'm working on it.
- Oh yeah, that always does it.
- Why's that?
- I've worked this unit every
year, and it's like clockwork.
Tenants never stay long, and
that hole is always there.
(lighter clicks)
- We can smoke in here?
- No, Chad, I can smoke in.
- Man.
- Now listen.
I did hear this story.
That cavity in the wal?
It's alive.
It's waiting.
It's hungry.
And if you stare at
that long enough,
it becomes a glory hol.
(both laughing)
- Man, stop playing with me.
- Listen.
Sun's down, scrape out the
damp, cover it with wallpaper,
and I'm not paying overtim.
- I need at least another hour.
- No, we'll do it tomorrow.
We need to drag this ot
a few more days anyway.
So just go home.
You need a ride?
- My girl's meeting me.
- All right.
Well, lock up before
you leave, all right?
- You got it, boss.
(eerie music)
Man, this is fucking bullshit.
(ominous music)
(tense music)
(Chad gasps)
What the fuck?
(tense music)
- Hey, Mister.
Sorry I'm late.
- Look who finally showed up.
- And look what I brought.
- Is that a four-pack?
- Two might've disappeared
on the way over here.
- Yeah, sure.
Thanks.
- Oh, wow.
- That's cool, right?
- Hmm.
- Okay.
Wait, wait.
I got something for it.
(tense music)
- You got that for me?
- Yeah.
Here, turn around.
Let me see.
- Hmm.
Do you like?
- I love.
And you need another beer.
(Chad laughs)
(glass shatters)
(tense music)
(Lena groaning)
- Lena?
Baby, you okay?
(dramatic music)
Lena!
Oh, fuck.
Stay with me, stay with me.
Look at me, look at me.
Lena, baby, no, no, no, no.
Help, somebody!
Look at me, Lena.
Please help!
Oh, fuck!
Okay, I'm gonna get help,
okay, I'm gonna get help.
(tense music)
(solemn music)
- You're making a huge mistake.
- She's a bad influence on you.
You step out that door,
don't come back to us
asking for help.
- Kim!
- Hey.
- This place is lit, right?
- So cool, I love the floor.
- Where's your mom and dad?
Still not a fan of mine, huh.
- Not a fan of either
of us right now.
I'm just happy
you're here with me.
- I'm just happy to
ride out your coattails
when you become like,
a famous journalist.
Or if I make it before
then, I'm gonna give yu
an exclusive article
on how fabulous I am.
(both laughing)
(women chattering)
- Hi.
- I like your hat, man.
- I'm Ronan, the landlord.
You're moving into
room 203, right?
- That's us, yeah.
(woman chuckles)
This is the same
building, right?
- This was an old
commerce building.
The bank was on the first ,
the other floors were
converted to apartments
during the Depression.
We take first, last,
plus damages, cash onl,
for tenants like
you with no credit.
That's how it's done.
There's no parking included.
No smoking, no loud
noise after nine p.m.,
no cats, no dogs,
and the basement
is off limits to residents.
This is the last floor to be
renovated in the building.
The other units on
this floor are empty,
so it's just yours
here that's available
and mine back over there.
All original
pre-war furnishings.
Utilities are included
in the monthly.
All furnishings are required
to remain in the apartment.
- Wow.
Oh my...
Yes!
This'll do.
This will do just fine.
- It's better than the photos.
Definitely vintage vibes.
You concur?
- I concur.
(gentle music)
Whoa.
This is beyond.
- It reminds me of
that messed up play
that you did freshman year.
- "Murder at the Cathedral."
- Don't touch that!
This is an historic building,
and under no circumstances
can that be damaged.
- Got it, dude.
- Are we good here?
(tense music)
(both laughing)
- Yay.
(hammer tapping)
(ominous music)
(knocking on door)
- Hey.
She said this was
the only picture
where her hair looked nice.
- Her hair always looked good.
- Yeah.
(gentle music)
- I call wheelbarrow.
- No.
- That was your mom's rules.
Sad girl goes in
the wheelbarrow.
Wheelbarrow.
(both chuckling)
Let's go!
(both laughing)
Whoa!
- Blood surging to my head.
(both laughing)
(head thuds)
(gasps)
- Sorry.
Dang.
Fuck, I'm dizzy.
Oh, you know what
I just remembered?
- What?
- It's a margarita Thursday.
- That's not a thing.
- Why?
I just made it a thing.
It's margarita Thursda.
- I can't.
I have orientation day
the day after tomorrow.
(blender whirring)
(upbeat music)
♪ Found me on the Gold Coast ♪
♪ Take me where I wanna go ♪
♪ I'll be in your pokey show ♪
♪ Ooh, oh ♪
(women chattering)
♪ You can call me Marianne ♪
♪ Tell me I'm your favorite ♪
♪ Yeah, gotta give
me what you got ♪
♪ The sun goes down ♪
♪ We stay awake ♪
♪ You got that shine ♪
(woman singing indistinctly)
♪ I'm in your dreams ♪
♪ You're getting tired♪
- Mine!
- I'm only gonna borrow it.
- Borrow it?
I bought it!
♪ Yeah ♪
(women chattering)
(ominous music)
(machine clicks)
- [Samuel] Hello, you've
reached Samuel and Anne White.
Please leave us a
message after the tone.
(voicemail beeps)
- Hey, it's me.
I just want to let you know
that we got all moved in
and the place is really good.
And I'm happy.
Okay, I'm gonna try again
tomorrow after my first day.
Love you.
- Hi.
- Good morning.
- I think I dreamt I peed
on the roof last right.
- Wait, no, I think you did
pee on the roof last night.
- Round two tonight, baby.
That's not what I'm saying.
What I'm saying is that
99% of college students
go to orientation
with a hangover.
I think it's like
a rite of passage.
- If I even look at tequila
tonight I'm gonna vomit.
- Dude, just drink win.
Ew!
- I know, I tried to hang
the mirror there last night,
but the nail didn't hold.
Found it on the
floor this morning.
Ew, it's fine.
We'll just ask Ronan to fix it.
- I think I see something.
(tense music)
- Izzy, don't, you know
you're just gonna mess it up.
- No, hold on.
- Don't.
- Oh no, it's fine.
(Izzy gasps)
(suspenseful music)
- Izzy!
(Izzy whimpering)
(Izzy laughing)
- You're kidding!
You're... (sighs)
Asshole.
- I told you I was
gonna be a superstar.
My pictures everywhere and
everyone knows my name.
- Was that in the wall?
- Yeah.
- Let me see it.
- Finders keepers.
- Well, I don't want to ke.
There's probably mold
on it or something.
- Oh, whatever.
This is vintage, and Im
the queen of vintage.
- Mm-hmm, more like
queen of tetanus.
- That's a good one, actually.
- Thank you.
- Get ready, we're
going out tonight.
(ominous music)
- Okay, so, your mom ad
dad, wouldn't let you
hang in high school,
and then what?
They disown you now, o?
- They don't disown me.
They're just really strict.
- It's 'cause I went to rehab.
- Oh.
Damn, well...
- Not for alcohol, you jackass.
- Well, then for what?
- None of your
business, stranger.
- My name is Steve.
- Oh, well good for you, Steve.
- Anyway, we're roommates now,
and I start at the
college tomorrow.
- Okay, cool.
All right, so you guys
are going to college.
That's cool.
- Not me.
- Well, what are
you gonna do, then?
- Oh, you know, just
probably thinking
I'm gonna drink a lot here.
- She's an actress.
- Thanks babe.
- Man.
You're so fucking so hot.
- Don't.
- What?
- Dude, what are you doing?
- Calm down, we're all just,
we're hanging out here, right?
Bitch.
- Shit.
(Izzy laughs)
(Izzy laughing)
(tense music)
I'm sorry, we'll be quieter.
(door closes)
(man sighing)
- You know, I didn't
tell you how much
that punch turned me o.
- You know, we could
try something like that
if you want, huh?
You can slap me or...
Look, we don't have to
if you don't want, but...
(Izzy snoring)
Hey.
(man sighing)
Man, what the fuck?
(izzy snoring)
(eerie music)
(man sighs)
Holy shit.
(Kim breathing heavily)
What the fuck?
(tense music)
(bottle thuds)
(zipper buzzes)
(urine trickling)
(tense music)
(flesh squelches)
(man gasps)
(suspenseful music)
(ominous music)
(door opens)
(door closes)
(floor creaking)
(door opens)
(solemn music)
(Izzy snoring)
- Morning, sunshine.
(Kim groaning)
It's orientation day.
I told you I wouldn't fail you.
(Kim sighs)
- I heard some weird
noises last night.
- Oh dude, I didn't hear shit.
And that guy must've left.
What's his name?
- Tony?
- Tony!
Dude, I totally forgot.
But yeah.
- How's your hand?
- Oh, you know, it's all good.
(Kim chuckles)
- What time is it?
- It's only 11.
- Shit!
- What?
- God.
Orientation already started.
(tense music)
No!
(knocking on door)
Excuse me?
I'm here for the orientation.
Please?
- You're late.
Orientation ended
15 minutes ago.
I was giving the orientation
tour, so in exchange
for an extra hot non-fat
sugar-free vanilla latte,
I'll give you the
exclusive Ian tour for one.
- Really?
That's your drink?
- Yeah.
- I'm kidding.
You got a deal.
- Need your name first.
- Kim.
- Ian.
- I got that from the tour.
- It's all about the web p.
You'll access the live
lectures, round tables there.
Has its own social network.
I'm not really giving
you any gold here.
You don't have to
write it all down.
What are you
majoring in, anyway?
- Journalism, but I
want to minor in psych.
- Nice.
Yeah.
I'm a junior now.
I'm doing journalism
too, but I'm focusing
on video journalism.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Just it's the future.
Information's become
democratized on the we.
- Yeah.
I think that's part of
the problem, though.
I mean, any idiot with
an internet connection
can take a video of
themselves and call it news.
- Touche.
What about you?
- Call me romantic, but
I think there's something
special about the written word.
Like I...
I don't know.
I think there's something
special about the process
of real journalism,
and it helps people.
- I hate to break it
to you, but that means
you're gonna be taking a couple
courses with Dr. Phillips.
- Is that bad?
- Dude is a complete ass.
- He was must've given you a C.
- C minus.
(Kim laughing)
So you came here
for spring semester,
and your friend came
to pursue acting?
- Yeah, but we just
wanted to get away.
I was being suffocated
by my mom and dad.
But Izzy...
She was struggling aftr
her mom passed away.
So I wanted to help her,
and it kinda helps me too.
She's like family, so.
- There's a story for Dr.
Phillips' class right there.
You could write about
how you help a friend
cope with loss, you know?
Anyway, you're lucky to have
a friend that's like family.
- Yeah.
It's cool. (chuckles)
And we found this
amazing apartment.
I mean, it's amazing
and creepy, kind of.
But we can afford it, so.
- I've actually got ths
little protest today
I'm gonna cover.
(gentle music)
See you on the portal.
- Thanks for the in-person
lesson on isolated education.
(phone beeps)
- Hey.
Just getting back.
Haven't heard from you.
Gonna go to bed soon.
(ominous music)
Izzy?
(door closes)
Hey, what's with the smell?
Izzy?
(match strikes)
(blows out match)
(object clattering)
(tinkling music)
(keyboard clacking)
Living...
In the wake...
Of an accidental overdose...
Doesn't always feel like l.
(solemn music)
It's more like surviva.
Like you've been kissed
by death and the shadow
that looms in the aftermath is
a reminder that you're next.
I watch helplessly as t
stalks my best friend.
It has come close.
The shadow gave her
a fistful of pills
on a beautiful of
Fourth of July.
But the subsequent fireworks
that burst inside her
didn't finish the job.
She refuses the call to
the other side, but...
The shadow is patient.
(mysterious music)
(Kim sighs)
(paper rattling)
(suspenseful music)
(Kim breathing heavily)
What the fuck?
(slow, heavy banging on door)
(tense music)
(suspenseful music)
Izzy.
What are you doing?
(tinkling music)
(ominous music)
(gasps) Izzy!
Hey, wake up.
Wake up, Izzy, please?
I'm here.
It's okay.
- She's still with us.
(tinkling music)
I can feel her.
- Shh.
(music box closes)
(ominous music)
(solemn music)
(tools clattering)
(Kim sighing)
Well, I had two
visitors last night.
An imaginary bird, then you.
- Was the bird cute?
Was I cute?
I'm sorry, Kim.
I put the two and two together
when I woke up in your bed.
But I don't remember anything.
- Izzy, last-
- You liked your
smoothie, right?
- I like my sleep more.
- I used to sleep
walk when I was a kid.
It'll stop.
And if it doesn't,
you won't even know,
'cause I installed a lock.
(liquid pouring)
- So what were you
up to last night?
- I've met someone.
- Hmm.
What's his name?
- Her name.
- Congratulations?
- Sandy.
Her name is Sandy, and I met
her last night at the bar.
She is a casting
assistant to this lady.
And guess what?
She's getting me an
audition for this TV show
that she's doing.
- Congratulations!
(Izzy laughing)
- When I get the part, taking
you to your first strip club.
- Mm-mm.
- Mm-hmm.
(both laughing)
- I was gonna tell you
about it last night,
but I met someone too, a guy.
Ian.
And I like him.
I think I'm gonna let
him take me on a date.
- What?!
- Oh, are you okay?
- Yeah, sorry.
My cramps are really
kicking my ass today.
- Okay.
There's aspirin in the
cabinet over the stove.
Drink more water, less tequila.
- Whatever.
- The SPJ code of ethics
is a great place to start.
You should always run through
the checklist to ensure that
you are delivering your
content in a way that
you're both proud of and that
will stand up to scrutiny.
My office hours are
available as usual.
Thank you, everyone.
- Excuse me, Dr. Phillips?
- Yes.
- Yeah, I just...
I wanted to ask a questiont
my personal experiences ar,
because what I'm writing about
isn't technically about me,
it's about my friend and
her personal experiences,
some difficult situations and
how I've seen it affect her.
And I think it'd be important
for me too, just be cathartic.
I'm not gonna say
her name or anything,
but I was wondering if youk
I need to get her permission.
- You should act
independently here.
As long as you aren't
putting her in any danger
or betraying her trust.
- Yeah, I just feel
it's important.
I don't think she'd
understand right now
what I'm trying to do with it.
- As long as you
leave her anonymous,
I think you'll be fine.
Good luck.
- Thank you, Doctor.
(computer beeps)
I was just getting some
help from the professo.
- So the audition's
today, and then
Sandy's taking me
out for drinks after.
- Casting couch.
Nice.
- Please.
You should go see that boy.
Give your mom and dad a big
fuck you by fucking him.
(Kim chuckles)
(ominous music)
- All right, I'll see you .
- Good luck, love you.
- Love you!
(gentle music)
(hammer tapping)
- Stay.
(Kim laughs)
So then she punched this
guy in the face. (laughs)
I think he was knocked out.
- Remind me not
to piss Izzy off.
She sounds cool, I just don't
want to go down like that.
(Kim laughing)
How'd her mom pass awa?
Sorry, I shouldn't
have asked that.
Sorry, it's the
journalism thing,
it's ruined my social etiq.
- No, no, it's fine.
She just...
It was an overdose.
And the thing about
it was I think she was
the happiest person that I.
I mean, I loved
Leanna, and I had just
no idea that that's wht
she was going through.
And I think she was
going through that
and she was just this
light in our lives,
then what does that
mean for the rest of u?
- Sorry.
Just can't imagine.
- It crushed Izzy.
The worst part about
it is that I let
my parents run my life.
They wouldn't let me
over there to see her.
They thought I'd overdose
by osmosis or something.
So I couldn't go to the fu.
When she needed me
most, she called me
and asked me to be
there, I didn't show u.
And then the next
thing that I heard,
she was in the hospita.
She tried to...
She took a bunch of pills.
So.
I just promised myself that I
would always be there for her.
Sorry.
- Don't apologize.
Come on.
I'll take you for a ride.
- You don't have a car.
- Yeah, I know.
When's the last time you
rode on a pair of handlebars?
(Kim laughs)
(Kim laughing)
This is better
than a car, right?
- It's kinda scary!
- I know.
- How fast are we goin?
- Fast!
Five miles per hour.
(Kim laughing)
- Woohoo! (laughing)
Woo!
- You almost got me killed.
- You almost got you killed.
- I'd invite myself up, but
actually really sweaty now.
- Good, 'cause I
would've said no.
Go shower.
- Can I see you again?
- Uh-huh. (laughing)
(door closing)
(gentle music)
(mysterious music)
(door closes)
(keyboard clacking)
- [Samuel] Hello, you've
reached Samuel and Anne White,
please leave us a
message after the tone.
(voicemail beeps)
- Hi, it's me again.
I just want to tell you
how it's going here.
I like my classes.
We're doing good.
I guess call me back
if you have time,
or want to talk,
(glass shattering)
Shit!
Oh...
(Kim sighs)
(eerie music)
(door opens)
(door closes)
- I had a really good
time with you today.
I really wanna kiss yo.
- Yeah?
Well why don't you do it?
(glass crunches)
(Kim grunts)
(eerie music)
(tinkling music)
- Izzy?
Izzy?
Hey.
Are you okay?
Are you awake?
(metal crunches)
It's me, Kimmy.
Izzy?
(Izzy screaming)
Hey, are you...
(tense music)
(Kim gasps)
Izzy, wait.
(door closes)
(elevator beeps)
Fuck. (groans)
(door opens)
(door closes)
(mysterious music)
Izzy?
Izzy, please?
It's me.
Izzy, please.
Please, where are you?
Izzy?
(tense music)
(Kim gasps)
(person choking)
(tinkling music)
Izzy?
(person choking)
Izzy, where are you going?
Izzy, wait!
(door closes)
(tense music)
(tinkling music)
(ominous music)
Hey.
Izzy.
It's okay.
It's all right, Izzy.
You're gonna be safe.
Okay.
You're gonna be all right.
Shh.
(suspenseful music)
(Izzy groaning)
(urine trickling)
(solemn music)
I'm here.
- I don't understand.
- It's okay.
I think you just
need to stay in bed.
You need rest.
And please don't drink.
I don't know what that was
last night, but it scared me.
- I'm not gonna drink.
I have a call back today.
- Drink this.
- My head really hurts.
- I think it might
just be stress.
Can you see a doctor?
- I don't have insurance.
And like, I don't know,
but they're not gonna
let me take sleeping pills.
- No, that's not
what I was saying.
I don't want that.
- Do you ever feel like
you're watching your dreams,
but you're not part of them?
- No.
- Well, that's
what it felt like.
(solemn music)
- [Kim] I feel like
I'm talking crazy.
- No, no, you're not.
This is real.
You weren't sleepwalking,
you were awake.
- Well, what do I do?
I need to do something.
- Dig.
- What?
Research, investigate.
That's what we're
supposed to do, right?
There's always an answer,
you just have to dig.
- Right.
Yeah.
- Just can't judge what we.
- We?
- You'll need like a
research assistant.
- Will you come to
the apartment with me?
- Finally, you're
inviting me up.
- Just don't talk to hr
about it though, pleas.
I just want you to
see the place first.
Maybe there's like
radon poisoning
happening or something.
- I don't think radon makes
you sleepwalk yourself
down to the basement.
- What the hell?
(ominous music)
- Is she gone?
- I don't know.
(dramatic music)
- Can I help you?
- Do you know this guy?
- [Kim] He's my landlord.
- I came to treat the glass.
- Oh, okay.
Can you let me know in
advance when you're gonna be
coming into the apartment?
- You went down to the bas.
The basement is off
limits to residents.
Don't go down there.
- Your landlord's
kind of a dick.
- Yeah.
(door closes)
- This thing is horrifying.
You ever seen stained
glass like this?
- No.
- Me neither.
(camera clicking)
- Last night Izzy was
just staring at it.
It was weird.
It was like she was
hypnotized or somethin.
- That symbol is weird.
It looks like kinda Irish
or Celtic or something.
- Hmm.
- What else?
- What else what?
- You said she was
holding a music box?
- Yeah, I found it in that
little cabinet over there.
All the stuff is just
like stuff left behind.
- From other renters or what?
- I think so.
I don't know.
One second. (laughs)
- [Ian] Look at these.
This is the music box?
- Yeah.
- It's not making
any music sounds.
- It was last night.
I'm not crazy, it was, I swear.
- To my dearest Karen,
always yours, L.M..
(door closes)
- Hey, I'm Ian.
- Hey.
- How's your call back?
- Sandy didn't even
show up, so I guess
it kinda just went like that.
- I'm sorry, hon.
I'm sure it went better
than you think it did.
And there's always
gonna be more.
- There is gonna be more.
I get another chance to
get rejected tomorrow.
So.
- My sister's an actress.
They made her be the spoon
in "Beauty and the Beast."
- Spoon.
That's great.
- Sorry.
(camera clicking)
Why don't you cover that up?
- I tried.
- Smells kinda weird.
- I know.
And the necklace that
Izzy found was in ther.
- What?
Out of the hole?
- Yeah.
She just reached her hand
in there and found it.
- Okay, but that's gross.
Does Izzy eat gum
off the sidewalk too?
- Shut up.
No, no, really,
that's fucking crazy.
Why would that be in there?
Why would you wear it?
Okay.
Moving on.
All right.
I'll look into anything
I can find on the window.
You look into the apartment.
(solemn music)
(zipper buzzing)
(keyboard clacking)
Okay, this is definitey
a Celtic mark,
it's called a triskele.
It's like a druid pagan symbol.
- Hmm.
Liam McNally.
Look at this.
It's Karen.
It's the name from
the music box.
- L.M..
That's crazy.
That's their music box, right?
- It has to be.
(keyboard clacking)
- Damn.
Look at this.
- "Bank manager
murders pregnant wife."
Jesus.
Milton Briggs.
(keyboards clacking)
"He was last known to
be in his apartment..."
203.
They all lived in
this apartment?
- I don't know, some of
the articles don't say.
(solemn music)
(Kim chuckling)
(tense music)
(Izzy breathing heavil)
(eerie chanting)
(tense music)
(Izzy panting)
(woman whispering
foreign language)
(Izzy panting)
(woman whispering
foreign language)
(Izzy gasping)
(Izzy hyperventilating)
(voices whispering indisti)
(Izzy gasps)
(woman whispering
foreign language)
(ominous music)
(paper rustling)
(Kim sighs)
(suspenseful music)
(bird caws)
- What happened?
Are you okay?
- There was this bird,
there was a fucking bid
and it flew at me.
(tense music)
- It's just a dream, all right?
It's okay.
(mysterious music)
(door closes)
- Can I help you with some?
- Excuse me.
Are you Kim White?
- I'm her roommate.
- Okay, great.
Here.
- Thank you.
(door closes)
Kim?
Kim, I got your paper.
Oh, fuck.
(solemn music)
(doors open)
(doors close)
(phone beeps)
- I'm just here in
St. Mark's Cathedral.
As a lifelong atheist, I
don't have much experience
with stained glass
windows, so I wanted to see
these in person,
make some comparisons
between the windows
in the church
and the stained glass
window in Kim's apartment
at the commerce building.
So far, what I'm seeing
here are depictions
of religious events, you know,
probably biblical symbolism.
Or they're totally decorative.
Either way, the tone
is about reverence.
They're generally uplifting,
and generally pretty.
In contrast to the
window in room 203,
I don't see any maker's
marks or symbols
that appear to be Celtic.
(phone beeps)
(tense music)
(mysterious music)
(door opens)
(car door closes)
(solemn music)
(knocking on door)
(door opening)
- Hi.
Can I help you?
Are, are you Milton Briggs?
- When I can remember
my own name I am.
Did I forget to pay
a bill or something?
- No, no, nothing like that.
I go to college here
and I'm actually doing
some research for an article,
and I was just wondering
if I could talk to
you for five minutes
about Liam and Karen McNally
and the night that they died.
- Why would you want to
write an article about that?
They've already wrote everything
there is to say already.
- I just wanted to
hear it from you.
- I haven't had to talk
about that in about 50 years.
I don't want to
dredge up the past.
- Please.
Five minutes.
I live in that same apartment,
and I just need to know.
- You live in room 203.
- Yes.
- That night I was
working the graveyard,
and I heard some footsteps.
I figured it was Larry,
the other janitor,
had come back 'cause
he had forgot his keys,
but then I heard more
footsteps, and crying.
So I stepped out to
see what was happening.
And that's when I saw him.
Chasing his wife
into the boiler room.
- Who?
- Mr. McNally.
(tense music)
He was after his wife.
And she was screaming.
So I ran after them and chased
them into the boiler room,
and that's when I saw the .
- Blood on who?
- Mrs. McNally.
She was clutching her
stomach and crying out.
It was everywhere.
And then the crying stopped.
And I just froze.
I've never been so ashamed
of anything in my life.
I stood there, and
when he got up,
he just walked right past me.
He had a look in his eyes
I'd never seen in a man.
It was like I wasn't even .
Like I was a ghost.
I felt like I
floated Mrs. McNally.
I just wanted to
stop the bleeding.
All of a sudden,
I heard a gunshot.
- He shot himself?
- I guess.
I couldn't think
of what that was.
My mind just wasn't
ready for it yet.
At that point, all I could
hear was the baby crying.
- What?
The baby survived?
- He did.
A little boy.
- What happened to him?
- Nobody told me.
I went into shock.
And I've never stepped foot
in that building again.
(solemn music)
- Hey.
- Hey Kimmy.
- Where are you going?
- Out.
- Can you stay for a
few minutes, please?
I need to talk to you.
- I've got plans, kid.
- Izzy...
- Wanna talk about thi?
This whole fucking
thing is about me.
My life.
- Izzy, I'm sorry, oka?
I didn't say your name
and I kept it anonymou.
I was just trying to help.
- Help who?
Yourself.
- No, no...
I was trying to-
- You didn't have
to say my name.
It's obvious who
you're talking about.
You took my tragedy, ripped it
open, and put it on the page.
Congratulations.
You made me your guinea
pig just so you can
get a fuckin' A?
- No, please, Izzy, don't,
it wasn't like that, okay?
I need you to listen to me now
because it's really important.
- Like I needed you.
I buried my mom.
Where the fuck were yo?
(solemn music)
- Izzy, I'm sorry.
- No.
- No, I am sorry!
- No, no, no, no, no, no!
If you were there,
you wouldn't have had
to write this fucking
paper just to make
yourself feel better.
I mean, did you
even ask yourself
why I was so fucked up after?
Bro, you were the
only family left.
And you left.
- Izzy, I'm sorry.
I am, I'm sorry,
Izzy, please stay.
- I just wanted you
to fight for me.
- Izzy, please.
(Kim crying)
(door opens)
(door slams)
- Druids worshiped Pagan gods.
(tense music)
"Goddess of revenge, war, .
Known as 'fury.'"
Often takes the form of a crow.
(tense music)
The mark of the Morrig.
(Kim panting)
(suspenseful music)
(Kim grunting)
(banging on wall)
(dramatic music)
(Kim hyperventilating)
(door closes)
Kim.
Okay, just the facts,
and the facts are weir.
I found something on
the stained glass windw
in your apartment.
I was researching...
Anyway, whatever.
I just need to tell you
about it as soon as possible.
And maybe you shouldn't
be there right now.
If you are there.
Okay.
Call me back as soon
as you get this.
I'm coming over.
(ominous music)
(door closes)
(Kim breathing heavily)
(Kim whimpering)
- That was the last picture
taken of my parents.
Do you recognize anything?
(Kim crying)
My mother's necklace.
Morrigu chooses
who wears it next.
She's with her now.
And she needs to feed.
(Kim crying)
feed her children.
If I don't satisfy
the crows soon,
she's going to come after me.
Like she did my
mother and my father.
Normally, it would
be done by now.
But your friend is fighting it.
The others were quicke.
I'm telling you this...
Because you're about to
join them in the walls.
(suspenseful music)
(Kim grunting)
(elevator beeping)
(muffled shouting and banging)
(knocking on door)
- Hello?
(door closes)
Kim?
(tense music)
Shit!
Oh, shit.
(window creaking)
(heavy breathing)
(bird caws)
(tense music)
(suspenseful music)
Izzy, Jesus.
- Ian, right?
- Yeah.
Is Kim here?
Do you know where she is?
- She'll be back.
For now you can sit here...
And wait.
- Kim's...
- Shh.
(ominous music)
(muffled screaming)
- I don't have a choic!
Morrigu has been trapped
in the glass for centuries.
She's a part of my family.
I found my father's journal.
He taught me about the curse.
He taught me how she feeds.
How the souls she
takes leave a totem
and allow her to
cross into our realm.
My parents thought
they could ignore it,
and she found a
way to get to them.
She won't get to me.
(Kim crying)
(speaking foreign language)
(suspenseful music)
(bird cawing)
(speaking foreign language)
Take this offering.
(ominous music)
Feed on her soul.
(Ronan grunts)
(both grunting)
(Ronan shouting)
You little bitch!
(suspenseful music)
(door closes)
(Kim crying)
- Izzy?
Izzy, where are you?
We need to leave,
we need to go now!
(knives clattering)
(solemn music)
(Kim crying)
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
(ominous music)
(Ronan panting)
(tense music)
(door closes)
(suspenseful music)
- Kim.
Kimmy?
(tense music)
You can't save her now.
(ominous music)
(tinkling music)
(Kim gasps)
(suspenseful music)
(Ronan grunts)
(both grunt)
(Ronan panting)
(tense music)
(Ronan growling)
(person choking)
(Kim gasps)
- Izzy?
(person choking)
It's me.
Please.
It's Kim.
(ominous music)
(person choking)
(Kim shouts)
(tense music)
(person choking)
(suspenseful music)
Please.
Just let me save her, okay?
Just let me save Izzy.
I'll go with you.
(gun clicks)
Just please, okay?
I saw him.
I saw your father's face.
- That means she's her.
It's time.
- Don't.
Don't do it, just...
Don't do it.
- It's my responsibility.
(Kim crying)
(Ronan grunts)
(Ronan gasping)
(suspenseful music)
(gunshot bangs)
(Kim screams)
(feedback ringing)
(body thuds)
(Kim whimpering)
(tinkling music)
- Izzy?
(Kim grunting)
Izzy?
(tinkling music)
(music box closes)
- Help me, Kim.
I need you.
- That's why I'm here.
I'm gonna help you, okay?
I just need you to take
off the necklace, okay?
Take the necklace off, Izzy.
(Izzy groaning)
(Kim gasps)
- Can you get me home?
Please.
- I love you, Izzy.
(Izzy laughing)
I won't let her have you, okay?
I won't.
(tense music)
(Izzy shouting)
- Help me, please help me.
(eerie music)
Help me.
(Izzy laughing)
Kimmy.
I need you.
- Take the necklace of.
(Izzy laughing)
(suspenseful music)
(Izzy shrieks)
(Izzy laughing)
(Izzy snarling)
(Kim whimpering)
(Izzy shouting)
(Kim grunting)
(Kim shouting)
(Izzy laughing)
Izzy, I won't let you go.
- She's mine.
- Izzy, don't leave me.
Izzy.
(Kim whimpering)
(Izzy roaring)
(Izzy shrieking)
(birds cawing)
Don't leave.
I love you, Izzy, okay?
(knife clatters)
Please, I love you.
- Are you okay?
- Fuck.
It's okay, I'm okay.
I'm okay. (crying)
- Let's get the fuck outta.
- No.
Not yet.
Not until we destroy
that fucking window.
(solemn music)
(Izzy crying)
(suspenseful music)
(banging on window)
(birds cawing)
Fuck, Kimmy, just
do it and leave!
Come on, Kimmy, just
Kimmy, please.
(glass shatters)
(Kim whimpers)
It's okay.
Come on.
We gotta go.
(Kim crying)
(solemn music)
(door closes)
- [Kim] When you're one
of those left behind,
you understand that the
shadow will always exist.
There's no doomsday clock
ticking away your countdown.
It's more of an appreciation
for every single morning.
That's why I'm grateful
to be here with her.
She appreciates me
simply for existing.
She loves me because
I fight alongside her.
If the shadow wants
to knock on this door,
it'll have to take us both.
(ominous music)
(voices whispering indisti)
(tense music)
(birds cawing)
(dramatic music)
(solemn music)
(rocks slamming)
(upbeat music)