The United Methodist
Church is one
of the largest Protestant
denominations in the US,
with about 8 million members.
And, like the rest
of the country,
it is bitterly divided
over gay marriage.
He is the minister willing to
give it all up for his son,
even if it means
being forced out
of the priesthood of the
United Methodist Church.
Law changes but religion
doesn't have to change.
Religion has its own rules.
Religion does not have to
recognize same sex marriage.
There are lots of forms of sin,
and this isn't the only form
but it's one that we've
been asked to acknowledge
as normative when it's not.
This is our church, too.
Stand your ground.
This is our table.
Charges have been
brought against me
and I will be in a church trial
to determine whether or not
I have violated the
integrity of the church.
This case has demonstrated
how divided we are
and what a challenging position
that we're in as a church.
When you performed
your son's wedding,
did you think that the
road would end up here?
This could be entitled,
Lord is coming, Maranatha.
Actually, I have seen
a picture like that.
Maranatha the Lord is coming,
and then the clouds like that.
I did think of becoming a
minister, actually, early on,
but I always thought
that I couldn't just go
to Bible school, just because
I had an interest in this.
The way I was raised
and taught was that this
is a calling from God.
I always interpreted that
to be like a booming voice
from heaven and
that didn't occur,
so I decided to follow
in my father's footsteps
and become an engineer.
After a couple of years,
I wasn't getting anywhere.
I felt like this is
not really my calling.
In fact, the way I described
it to Brigitte at the time
was like, every time I sit
in class, it's like darkness.
I experience
darkness and I can't
see myself doing this
for the rest of my life.
And something very
incredible happened.
I had a dream.
And I dreamt that I was
transported back in time.
I saw myself as a senior in high
school saying to my best friend
then, I'm going to
do an apprenticeship
but what I would really like
to do is go to Bible school.
And at that moment, it was like
God was standing next to me
and was saying, "Who
do you think put
that desire into your heart?"
And it was like, wow.
There's my booming voice.
There's my calling.
I was actually not too surprised
but I wasn't too thrilled.
Did you think it was going to
affect your life in a bad way?
Yeah, I had my thoughts.
About what?
About you going back to
school and us having kids.
What do I love about
the Methodist Church?
Well, I'm a cradle Methodist.
Generations before
I was born, there
were Methodists in my background
on both sides of the family.
So it's sort of like my
mother's milk, you know?
The Lord be with you.
And also with you.
Lift up your hearts.
The United Methodist
Church, for me,
is a place of connectedness
in the community,
the beloved community of God.
This denomination is broad
and inclusive in its scope.
It has always occupied
a kind of middle ground
in American culture.
I love my church.
My church has helped
make me who I am.
My church has given
me the privilege
to do things no one could have
ever imagined a little country
boy from Clinton,
Louisiana ever doing.
United Methodism,
Methodism in general
has always been steeped
in a love of God
and love of neighbor.
It's in our DNA to be loving.
I mean, conservative, centrists,
liberals, you just count.
United Methodists are
among of the most loving,
gracious, caring
people on the planet.
That's why you find
us in soup kitchens.
us working down
on the border with
immigrant children.
That's why you find us
leading all the social efforts
in most communities.
It's just kind of strange
that the same church that
works so hard against injustice
is also doing injustice
with its members.
After I was ordained in the
United Methodist Church,
I got assigned to a church
in Lebanon, Pennsylvania.
I think the bishop thought
this German pastor would
fit perfectly into the heartland
of Pennsylvania Dutch country.
I though I could
just speak my German
and I could understand
the Pennsylvania German,
but I was wrong.
I remember when that
first person walked up
in my church who tried his
Pennsylvania Dutch on me,
he said and
I said Gesundheit.
I was really active
in the church
during my high school
years, in particular.
So I had served on a
couple of the boards,
I was active in the youth group.
I played the drums
in the worship team,
I sang in the choir.
I would even preach on youth
Sundays and things like that.
So not just church, but my
faith was really important.
And I had gone one year with
my dad to an annual conference.
I was always interested
in law and in politics.
And he thought this
is, essentially,
a legislative body, so you'll
find it really fascinating
how they vote on legislation.
It just so happened,
in that year,
there was a debate on the
floor about homosexuality.
An LGBT related piece
of legislation came up
and there was really some
tough debate around that.
I'd say 80% of those
who were speaking
were against the issue.
And there was some
pretty harsh language.
I remember feeling
pretty down about myself
because it was during a
time when I was trying
to figure out my sexuality.
So, to me, that sent a
message, really, that who I was
was against church teachings.
I had read this was a
phase that a lot of boys
regularly go through.
They grow out of it.
I guess, at the time, I was kind
of just waiting for that phase
to be over, and when
that didn't happen, year
after year, I really
started to pray to God,
just make me normal.
Let this phase and
I'm going through end.
A lot of times, I
would end up just
crying myself to sleep because
I was so distraught over it.
I remember kids at school
asking me, is your brother gay?
And I had never
thought about it.
And I just said
I don't think so.
I mean, I guess he could
be, but I don't know.
He was withdrawn, at that time.
He kind of went from school,
straight up to his room
and he didn't really talk.
And before, we always hung out.
And I thought, well, it's
just being a teenager.
He just needs this
time by himself.
I had seen a friend of
mine come out to his family
and his family kicked
him out of the house.
His mother even said to him,
when I look at your face,
it makes me want to throw up.
It makes me so
sick to my stomach.
And there was always
that fear that what
if my parents have a problem
with it and they kick me out?
Where would I go?
I certainly didn't want to
come out and be this freak
and bring shame on my family
or on my local church.
I had started
thinking of some ways
that, the easiest way,
the least painful way,
really, to just kill
myself and end it.
I had actually climbed onto the
roof of the parsonage one day,
because it was up
about three and 1/2,
four stories and honestly
thought if I dove off,
I would probably
break my neck and die.
My daughter came home
from school one day,
and she was very
upset and crying.
Tim was telling her that
he thought he was gay
and he was considering suicide.
I felt strongly that the
parents should be notified,
so I told my daughter that
I could go to a public phone
booth and make the
call from there,
so that it couldn't be traced.
I was in my office,
it was the year 2000.
I received this phone call.
I said my daughter was
friends with his son.
He was gay and that he believed
that being gay was wrong
and he was suicidal.
And I heard these words and
they instantly transported me
into this surreal place.
It was almost like an
out of body experience.
I was like-- I couldn't
think, I couldn't breathe.
I was shocked.
And I remember driving home to
my wife, sharing it with her,
and she had a similar reaction.
Do I really not
know my children?
I would know this.
I would somehow know.
Both of my parents were
sitting in the living
room, very serious
expressions on their faces.
And my dad said, "Tim,
can you sit down,
because we have to talk
to you about something
really important."
I thought somebody had died.
Is it true?
Are you gay?
I had this phone
conversation with this lady.
I must have hesitated
for quite a while,
and I was going over
my options in my head.
I can tell them the truth or
I can laugh it off and lie.
And I had thought,
you know what?
I'm just going to tell them.
We embraced him that night.
And we just, and I remember
there were a lot of tears.
We were all in tears,
all three of us.
And then we said,
you know, please
know that we will always
love you, no matter what.
He had struggled all this time
and I never knew about it.
And he was all alone in this.
It wasn't that I was
gay that had upset him.
It was that I felt
I couldn't share
with them a part of who I was.
I do remember asking him why
he didn't feel comfortable
talking to us.
And what did he say?
I think was more worried
about it coming out in church,
for your sake.
The simple wedding
ceremony in this church
has turned Methodist
against Methodist.
When Jimmy Creech defied church
guidelines by administering
vows to a lesbian couple.
I'd been doing covenant
ceremonies since 1990
and I had done 12 or 15
or more, because I believe
that was a part of my ministry.
Wedding ceremony was on a
Sunday and, on Monday, all hell
broke out of the United
Methodist Church.
I was aware that trials take
place in the United Methodist
Church, but I never knew of
one in any kind of detail.
I didn't know anybody who had
ever gone through a trial.
Creech argued the ban
on homosexual unions
was a guideline,
not a church law.
Thus, he should
not be disciplined.
Eight persons voting guilty,
five persons voting not guilty.
He was acquitted by
a jury of his peers.
I was extremely excited.
I thought this was going
to be a significant victory
for the whole church.
I thought this was
going to set clergy
free to be pastors to everyone
in their congregation.
Well it didn't
turn out that way.
In April of 1999, I conducted
a wedding for Larry and Jim.
The bishop had charges
filed against me
and a judicial
process was initiated
that resulted in a trial that
took place in November of 1999.
What I decided to do was sort
of a non-violent resistance
to the whole process.
I decided that I would
not ask for legal counsel.
I wouldn't enter a plea
one way or another.
All I would do would be to
answer the church council's
questions honestly.
Then, at the end, make
a final statement.
My hope was that I
could convince the jury
to not vote either way,
and say to the church,
this is a corrupt
and invalid process
that we are not going
to be complicit with.
It was not a shock that
the verdict was guilty,
but I was surprised that
it was a unanimous verdict.
At the end of that
trial, I was no longer
ordained clergy in the
United Methodist Church.
What had been given to me
back in 1970, my ordination,
had been withdrawn.
The trial belongs
to everyone here.
This is their witness.
It's their pain
and it's their hope
that change can
take place that's
really going to make it
possible for the future.
When I was first
appointed to Zion of Iona,
my second church in Lebanon,
before I even got there,
before I even met
anybody from the church,
there were already rumors flying
around that I had to gay son.
And that was a problem
for some people.
I knew that there were going
to be certain cities I could
go to where I was going
to be more accepted,
and so I really chose Boston.
I met Bobby, actually,
shortly thereafter.
We met, actually, through my ex.
It got serious pretty quickly.
I would say, right
after our freshman year,
he and I had our first
apartment in Cambridge.
Marriage was something we
had talked about for a while.
So it was, for me,
kind of a no brainer.
I was actually the one
who proposed to him.
Tim just surprised me
one day and he actually
had something else planned, but
he had the ring in his pocket
and couldn't wait any longer.
So he just kind
of blurted it out
while we were in his dorm room.
We had talked about the
option of just going
to a justice of the
peace, but for me, it
was important to have that
religious aspect to it.
I remember calling my dad
and saying Dad, I'm engaged.
We've been talking about
it a lot and both Bobby
and I would really like to
have you perform the ceremony.
There wasn't even a hesitation.
I said, absolutely, son.
And I remember just feeling
very joyful and honored
that he would ask me.
When two people love each other
so much, like Tim and Bobby do,
whoever says that
such love cannot be?
Tim and Bobby, are you ready?
This is the point of no return.
I, Tim, take you, Bobby--
I, Tim, take you Bobby--
To be my wedded partner.
Tim, I give you this ring.
As a sign of my vow.
In the name of the Father--
And of the Son.
And of the Holy Spirit.
Amen.
It's a very special
privilege and honor
to announce Tim
and Bobby, married
for the very first time.
It was truly a family
affair and family event.
It was beautiful.
He has made Tim so happy and
I can't imagine one of them
without the other.
I wish Tim and Bobby a
wonderful, fabulous, long
life together
Of course I knew that United
Methodist Church did not
allow ministers to
perform gay marriages.
Ministers had been
defrocked over this.
I decided I will perform
this wedding for my son,
even if it meant that
I was fired and lost
my job, my career in the
United Methodist Church.
My dad called me
almost six years
to the date of the marriage.
He said you're not
going to believe it,
but a complaint was filed.
I just was stunned, because
almost six years had gone by
and we hadn't heard anything.
It was so weird that it
was just coming up now.
The complaint was filed
26 days before the statute
of limitations expired.
There's a six year
statute of limitations.
He was trying not to get
caught and, at the 11th hour,
he got caught.
He officiated at
his son's wedding
and it may cost this
local minister his job.
The trial of Reverend
Frank Schaefer
is taking place at a Methodist
retreat in Chester County.
Dozens of people, many from
Lancaster and Lebanon counties,
have come to the trial to
support Frank Schaefer.
It was really cool to
see all the support.
There were signs everywhere
and banners and rainbow stoles
and hundreds of people.
We shall overcome.
We're here to say
we stand with Frank.
This was my first trial ever.
I had a pretty good
idea what's happening
in criminal court or
the civil court, even,
but I had no idea what to
expect about this church trial.
Keep in mind, this is a trial
with a bishop for a judge
and 13 Methodist
pastors as jurors.
The actual trial was set
to be in a gymnasium.
The church set it up to look
exactly like Law and Order.
It had a judge at the bench,
it had a defendant's table
and a prosecution table.
It had a witness
stand and a jury box.
And it had the gallery
for the spectators.
What other way could you
set up a church trial?
I wondered if there might
be a way to set it up
so you could actually
have a conversation?
If you or I are employed
and my employer tells me,
I'm given a handbook,
and my handbook,
it says I'm not
to do these things
or there are consequences.
Frank's given The
Book of Discipline.
They filed two charges.
The first charge was performing
a wedding of a same sex couple.
And the second charge
is in the Discipline
as a chargeable
offense, disobedience
to the order of the Discipline.
Knowing that he was
disobeying the Discipline
is undermining the
covenant of the church
and harmful to
the body of Christ
in the United Methodist Church.
It's kind of a quirk
of the trial system
that we could acknowledge that
Pastor Frank had performed
that wedding and still found
him not guilty of performing
that wedding.
We never denied
that Frank did this.
I really believe that a
father's love for his son
preempts The Book of Discipline.
The Book of Discipline is a
covenant that binds us together
as United Methodists.
It's a book that contains
our doctrinal standards, that
explain what it is that we
believe as United Methodists.
And then it contains lots of
different rules and regulations
about how the Church
is to function.
United Methodist
Church, probably more
than any other denomination,
has this process
of discernment of what is God's
will for the denomination that
is a very democratic process.
General Conference
happens every four years.
It's the international gathering
of United Methodists, where
we vote on the polity doctrine
and direction of the Church
for the next four years.
The Book of Discipline
is the outgrowth
of all these generations
of General Conferences,
writing laws and
making adjustments
and adding and subtracting.
Good morning, bishop,
General Conference visitors
and volunteers.
It's time to turn in our
discussion to an issue
that I know matters for
many here and in our church
and in our world.
I was a delegate to the
1972 General Conference.
And during that time is when
the issue of homosexuality
sort of came out.
And we made a statement
somewhat similar to the one
that we have now, saying
that heterosexuals, as well
as homosexuals, are
persons of sacred worth
and are entitled to their
human and civil rights.
But when the entire thing came
to the floor, from the floor
there was an amendment that
basically turned the meaning
of everything on its head.
They proposed inserting,
right in the middle
of that, a statement that said
"the practice of homosexuality
is incompatible with
Christian teaching."
And the people
adopted it and we've
been living with that
incompatible with Christian
teaching language since 1972.
People are being
harmed by the church,
by the use of the
incompatibility condemnation
language.
I am a lesbian and
a child of God.
I think people,
at that time, had
little idea of
what fruit would be
reaped from the seed
that was planted
in that little statement.
That's led to a ban on the
ordination and appointing
of clergy, a ban on clergy
performing marriage ceremonies
or unions for same sex couples.
The cumulative weight, if you're
a queer person in the church,
is to see that every four years,
something gets worse for you.
Friends, we're going to
be moving toward a break.
God's love is for everyone!
Let's be in order, please.
God's love is for everyone.
Even if we have to
remind the church.
When they took that
action about clergy
could not perform
holy union ceremonies,
I said that one will
come back to haunt us.
The first phase of the trial
was guilt or not guilt.
And each side was only
allowed one witness.
Our witness was Frank.
The church's witness
was the complainant.
Jon Boger took the
stand and I don't even
know how to describe it.
He was very
emotional, although it
was a little hard
to figure out what
he was being emotional about.
Then he started crying and I'm
like, what is wrong with you?
It was very embarrassing.
So none of us liked
him, from the start.
I mean, you could hear
grumbles behind me.
Just.
We were not impressed
by him at all.
Jon is in the military and is
accustomed to following orders.
Even orders you might not
agree with or understand,
you're supposed to follow them.
Reverend Schaefer did baptize
at least one of his children
and so Jon had put a
lot of trust in Frank
and he felt like that
trust was violated when
Frank disobeyed the Discipline.
He said that the
Reverend's decision
to officiate the marriage was
both a lie and broken covenant.
I didn't actually
know him that well
because, during my 11 years of
ministry at the Iona church,
I had maybe seen him
about once a year.
Because he was in the Navy
and he never lived in Lebanon.
So he was never a
regular attendee.
The only way I knew
Jon was that we
had prayed for him as
part of a youth group,
because he served
in the military.
So I was very confused
as to how this
affected his spiritual life.
But was it knowledge that
there had been multiple staff
issues with his mother?
Absolutely.
He denied that this
was a vendetta.
He said it just so happened that
he found out about the wedding
and he was appalled and
decided to file a complaint.
There was no vendetta.
It was just simply
the straw that
broke the camel's back was the
marriage certificate that Frank
conducted the same
sex marriage for Tim.
And Frank can twist
it anyway he wants to,
but that's the bottom line.
The man that filed
the complaint,
a member of Schaefer's
congregation, said little.
What would you say to the folks
that are watching out here?
Sir, I have no comment.
There were other issues
involved besides the wedding.
I felt that it was almost
a minor issue compared
with some of the
other issues that
were going on in the church.
I met Frank when I was
a seminary student.
The church had advertised for
an open position for a youth
pastor.
We hit it off right away.
We had a lot of the same visions
and hope for the community,
for the church to grow.
We started a second service and
that was very much necessary
because we had grown from about
140 in worship to over 200,
and the room was just too small.
The contemporary service had
an incredible rock group.
The traditional service
was equally powerful
but in a quieter way, older
folks, more traditional
in their background and
their understanding of faith.
We attracted more
and more people.
We had lesbian
couples and gay men
come and join us
in our ministry.
We attracted people of color.
Everybody was welcome.
We were homeless and that's how
we got affiliated with the Iona
church.
There was just something
about Iona that struck with me
and I stayed there, especially
with Pastor Frank Schaefer.
He was probably the most
genuine person I've ever seen.
We're going to take
the joy of the Lord
and we're going to take that joy
with us into our daily lives.
We're just going to start today.
We do some refreshments,
so please stay a while
and have some fellowship and
some refreshments and see you
all next week, same
time, same place.
People are drawn to that
and that's why we grew.
At one point, the second
service was doing so well,
the attendance started to
exceed the first service.
That is when we began
to see some of the pain
and the struggle and the
attacks that this story has.
I started to see
a change in Frank
and his message and the
way he conducted himself.
It would appear as
if he didn't prepare
for that traditional service.
He was late for services.
It seemed as if
he would have been
content to let the traditional
service pretty much
go by the wayside or die.
It wasn't the second
service saying we
don't like the first service.
We don't fit in.
It was the first
service saying we
don't like all the attention
the second service is getting.
They really wanted
the status quo
of the way the church had been,
for many of them, from the time
that they started
there as an infant.
He self-taught himself
how to play guitar.
He kind of pretty much wanted
to be a rock star type guy.
I learned about the
concern that some people
had at the Iona church
over me having a gay son.
I stood in the presence of
two people that literally
said what is he doing wrong?
Why can't he fix his kid?
And so that mindset translated
to, he doesn't do this right,
he doesn't do that right,
the service started late,
his hair wasn't combed, his wife
doesn't wear dresses enough.
And it just snowballed.
Things were really
starting to pile up
and there was some maybe
animosity between Pastor Frank
and the choir director
at our church.
It kind of got through the
church and to the choir
that Frank had
requested her dismissal.
That did not sit well with
a whole group of people.
My hypothesis is
that a group forms
and they're known as
the concerned group.
We were a concerned group.
The group probably consisted
of about 30 people maybe.
They were about how do we get
rid of this man and his family?
What can we do?
So the very next day, after I
had this talk with the choir
director, the very next
day, I received a phone call
from my DS.
I had been accused by Jon Boger,
the son of the choir director,
of having had a sexual affair,
in the church's bathroom,
with a former male staff
member of the church,
and that the janitor of the
church had walked in on us
and seen the whole thing.
Is it true?
Did this happen,
the DS asked me.
I said absolutely not.
Absolutely not.
Why don't you call the janitor?
I have her number right
here in my cell phone.
I said I don't know what
you're talking about.
I didn't find Frank or
anybody doing anything.
The previous allegation that
I investigated about Frank
turned out to be totally
specious and without merit.
But once a rumor
starts, there's always
lots of rumors that
stay out there.
And it's in the
community then, too.
There was an attempt to try
and uncover those things.
But, in defense of, Frank,
it was never substantiated.
Nothing was ever proven
one way or the other.
About three weeks after
the initial accusation,
there was a complaint
filed against me.
The complaint was about having
performed Tim's same sex wedding
One of the members of
the church at the time,
and it's no secret, Jon
Boger, researched it
and we found proof through
the marriage certificate.
This had nothing to do with
homosexuality or homosexuality
bashing, as the
LGBT would see it
or as Frank or other
people at the church
would see it at the time.
It was about what was right
with Frank, Frank presiding
over Tim's same sex marriage.
It was illegal.
He couldn't do it.
Hi, I'm Rob Renfroe,
President of Good News
and this is Tom Lambrecht,
our vice president
and general manager.
Well, Good News'
mission and purpose
is really to help the
church to maintain fidelity
to scriptural Christianity.
We try to keep the
church centered
on Christ and faithful to what
God has revealed in the Bible.
I think it's very
important that we
maintain the content
of Christianity
and not change or adapt
the content to fit whatever
whims of culture and intellect
happen to be at the moment.
I'm speaking to
you today because I
am concerned about our
United Methodist Church.
More and more United
Methodist pastors
have begun to perform
same sex services.
One bishop said that she thinks
we want a gay free church,
and nothing could be
farther from the truth.
What we want is the church to
be open to all people, no matter
our sin, no matter our desires.
You are a person of sacred
worth, but what you do is sin.
You know, love the
sinner, hate the sin?
That's a kind of craziness
that asks a person
to live a dichotomous life.
You are who you are.
You are who God
created you to be.
So to say that it's
OK that I'm gay,
that I want to have
sex with another woman,
but it's not OK that I
actually have sex with her,
that makes no sense.
And, even if it did, it
would be cruel to say
that this portion
of the population
should be deprived of the
basic human need for love
and intimacy.
Our church has been taken
over by the religious right
and politicized the church
to where we are now.
This is a matter of
power and control.
It is to maintain the
status quo and it's
to deny the freedoms of a
particular group of persons.
It became clear to some
of us that the only way
change was going to happen
was from the bottom up.
And so we borrowed a model
from the Presbyterians
and decided that we would begin
a network of United Methodist
congregations which
would publicly
declare that they welcomed
all persons, regardless
of sexual orientation.
We have a large body of people
in the United Methodist Church
who are committed together
for full inclusion.
And they're sending a
message to the denomination
by saying we're reconciling.
In that statement,
they're saying
we disagree with
the formal policies,
current practices that
maintain a stance
of exclusivity,
and we are working for change.
Are we really two churches,
pretending to be one or are we
one church that just simply
cannot find a way to live
together?
I wish we never had to
talk about this again.
And if the other side would
not make this their agenda,
if this is not what they pushed
over and over and over again,
you wouldn't hear
anything from us.
If you go to McDonald's
and buy a hamburger,
you know that, no
matter whether you're
going to one in Alabama or Maine
or California or Wisconsin,
you're going to get the
same hamburger everywhere.
If you go into a United
Methodist Church,
you don't know what you're going
to get, in terms of theology.
So taking the witness stand,
I wasn't actually sure
how much I was
allowed to get in.
My counsels had a great idea.
They said why don't we
start with introducing you
to the jurors, because
the jurors didn't know me.
Who is this person you're
accusing and are considering
whether he can continue to be
a United Methodist minister
or not?
And I started to tell the story
from the beginning and a very
curious thing happened.
I kept telling more and more
about the story of my son, Tim.
Tim was very sick
when he was born.
He had a heart lung problem.
They duct just didn't close.
I remember the
doctor telling us,
he's not going to live
through the night.
And I mean, that
was devastating.
Our faith played a really
important role at that time.
And I remember the whole
church was praying for Tim.
He survived the night
and then we just
visited every single day.
And the only way we could touch
him was through the incubator.
He had an operation
and it was successful.
And then we could take him
home for the very first time
a few days after that.
And that was amazing.
When your little kid's like
that, you bond even tighter.
And he was Frank's little
miracle, his whole life.
And so, when he was struggling
with this, of course
they're going to gather
around him and say it's OK.
I even quoted scripture.
I brought in the parable
of the Good Samaritan
and actually got in a defense.
He admits that he did
it, but he doesn't
admit that he's guilty
for anything by doing it.
He's not guilty.
And I told the jury
that I could not
ignore my son, who was like this
man in the parable of the Good
Samaritan, who was beaten up
and bleeding in the street.
And I couldn't pass
by on the other side,
like the Levite
and the priest did.
I had to help my son.
He was hurt by the
doctrine of the Church,
and he asked me for help.
And I couldn't refuse him.
It was an act of love.
I felt, for the first time
in the trial, a real sense
of lightness in the courtroom.
It just seemed to be this
acknowledgement and an embrace
of a father's love for his son.
I don't agree with The
Book of Discipline.
But, at the same
time, I'll uphold it.
But it was his son.
And while I say I'll uphold
it, my kids are four and two,
but what if, by the time my
children are marrying age,
my daughter comes to me
and says, "I'm a lesbian
and I want you to
officiate at my wedding?"
What am I going to do?
Growing up in a
rather conservative
evangelical environment,
in my family, in my church,
I definitely remember
thinking that homosexuality
was a sin at that point.
Hey, willkommen.
Come on in.
This is actually the apartment
that we used to live in
in Germany, in Wuppertal.
Dining table here.
Dining table.
And a sofa was over there.
And the sofa was
over here, right.
But the palm tree did really
well because of the light here.
So it was a huge palm tree.
And remember, one Christmas,
we decorated that?
Decorated the palm tree and
your mother thought, what?
You don't have a Christmas tree?
Said that's our Christmas tree.
She wasn't convinced.
She didn't like it.
This entire apartment
building is actually
owned by my mother-in-law and,
at the time, my father-in-law.
There's just a lot of
diversity in this building.
People from other
countries and among them
were several gay couples.
They were friends with
one particular guy
who was super nice.
That was the first time I
ever talked to a gay person.
And I have to say,
he was really nice.
And I was really
intrigued by that,
because I had been taught
that gay people are different
and it's sinful and
they're going to hell
and all these things I'd heard.
And then so I met
this guy, I was
surprised by how nice
he was and how close I
felt to this person,
just talking to him.
It was like we had a connection
and it really changed my life.
OK, in preparation to go up the
highest mountain in Germany,
you've got to put on
some extra clothes.
I thought that because being
gay was so statistically rare,
my brother had used up all
of the gay in our family.
It would be so unlikely
for two of us to be gay.
First, I thought,
well, I'm bisexual.
I like guys too, but I
just also like women.
I told Kevin first.
He thought I was
joking around with him.
I had already arrived at the
conclusion that I was gay
but I was holding out
on telling anyone,
just to be extra sure
before I came out.
We made this agreement to come
out to our parents together,
but then I ended up
just telling them.
She said I think I might
think I might be bisexual.
And we said, OK.
Well, I guess you have to
find that out for yourself
and whatever you
are, we love you.
I think, in the back of my mind,
I knew I was gay all along,
but I just didn't want to
let go of the idea of getting
married to a man,
having a family,
living the, quote,
unquote, normal life.
And I realized that that
was never going to happen,
that I was only
attracted to women.
I don't even remember
my coming out very well.
It was such an
insignificant moment.
It wasn't a big deal
because we really, frankly,
we knew about it.
He was different from
other kids in the same way,
really, that I was
different from other kids.
We wouldn't play the same.
We would play more
with the girls,
rather than with the boys.
They didn't have to say
like, we love you.
We still love you or
anything like that.
It felt like a
non-issue and I think
that was probably the best
thing that could have happened.
I was wondering, are
all our kids gay?
Yeah.
That had began to--
We had to ask Pascal.
Yeah, for a while we kind
of wondered about Pascal.
I kind of just hinted to them
for a while, I'm not gay.
He thought we, as
the gay siblings,
would be upset if
he were not gay.
Yeah, there was some
pressure, right,
because you have to follow the
precedents of your siblings.
So, yeah, I guess there
was kind of a coming
out of me being straight.
Continuing coverage now of
Reverend Frank Schaefer's trial
in the United Methodist Church.
Tonight, we have the verdict.
Because I felt I
had been able to put
in a pretty good
defense on my behalf,
I felt optimistic
about the verdict.
Because I really
believed I could
be acquitted at this point.
We had heard word that the
jury had reached a verdict.
We reconvened in the
gymnasium, the courtroom.
As the jurors were walking
in, I looked over to them
and I noticed that they were
all avoiding eye contact with me
and I knew that
wasn't good news.
Reverend Frank Schaefer
will learn his exact penalty
tomorrow.
Tonight, he learned
that he was convicted
of breaking the rules of
the United Methodist Church.
And I was devastated.
I thought I had prepared
myself for a guilty verdict,
but there's no way that
you can prepare yourself
for something like that.
I wasn't emotionally prepared
for hearing those words spoken
by a representative of the
entire church, telling me
I had violated the
order and the Discipline
of the entire church.
It felt horrible to
be in that space.
Trials are not something that
we look forward to or want
to have, but it is
the last resort way
that we have of holding people
accountable to the promises
that they made when
they became pastors.
When we have a church trial,
because somebody dared
to minister to a gay person
or because, God forbid,
somebody is gay, and we
put them on trial for that,
it brings to the surface the
ugliness that lies beneath.
I loved being a minister.
Every day was packed with
work that was very meaningful.
But I felt more
and more isolated,
being an ordained minister
but being in the closet.
I was sad and frustrated
and unhappy, personally.
She was our associate
pastor and was much loved
and was just a wonderful pastor.
I started to think coming out
is something I need to do,
and I need to do it here
because this is a church that's
already inclusive.
This is a church where my coming
out will not divide or upset
the congregation.
So I decided to come
out on April 27, 2003.
I know that by telling
the truth about myself,
I risk losing my credentials
as an ordained United Methodist
minister.
But I have realized that
not telling the whole truth
about myself has been
holding me back in my faith.
Here I am, for this Sunday
at least, and perhaps
for many months to
come, your openly
lesbian, fully credentialed
United Methodist pastor.
Nobody wanted to have a trial.
It was much more a matter
of Bishop Weaver believing
that, in his role
as a bishop, he
had an obligation to uphold
church law as currently written
The presiding Bishop, the
judge, said this trial is not
about The Book of Discipline.
This trial is not
about the Bible.
The only thing that
we're determining
is whether Beth Stroud did
violate paragraph whatever
of The Book of Discipline.
The verdict hinged
on the question
of whether I was a self-avowed
practicing homosexual.
It hinged on some very
painful and embarrassing
personal questions I was
asked in the courtroom
that I don't care to repeat.
The report of the trial
court is that the credentials
of the respondent
are to be withdrawn.
The vote was seven to six,
meeting the required vote
for the penalty.
There weren't really a lot
of other opportunities for me
after that, in the
United Methodist Church.
Our top story, a
Lebanon County pastor
convicted of
violating church law
could learn his
punishment today.
I was in a different mindset on
day two than I was on day one.
I have to admit, I was angry.
I was angry at the
church for ignoring
the good ministry I had
provided for more than 20 years.
And when I walked
into that courtroom,
I was not as intimidated
as I felt the first day.
It's been a full
day of testimony
from witnesses in the
sentencing phase of this trial.
We wanted to present
to the trial court
the impact of Frank's actions,
the impact on the church.
Former congregation members
testified about a split
in the church.
Honestly, to not defrock him
sends a message that I think
would be hurtful
in the long run.
William Bailey testified,
quote, "The impact on my family
was devastating.
The impact on the
congregation was devastating.
People left, and left
with their wallets."
A lot of the
testimony was dated.
It wasn't even accurate.
We were suffering financially
when the recession happened.
when we began to have attacks.
Some good people left
because of these bullies.
I do think that there
were some crocodile tears.
People weren't sworn in.
Maybe if they were
sworn in, they
wouldn't be saying these things.
Well, I felt the way things
were handled was way out of line
and over the top.
But my worry was Tim.
Schaefer's son Tim
is here and will
testify in his father's behalf.
They put you in a
little waiting room,
and the waiting room essentially
was a custodial closet.
I just remember
thinking, how ironic
is it that I'm being
put into a closet
by representatives
of the church,
in preparation for testifying.
It was very difficult to
listen to Tim's testimony,
because he was really sick
about this whole thing.
But he did so well.
I was so proud of him
for sharing his story
in front of a hostile court.
And yet he told it with
so much passion and grace.
There was one question
in cross examination.
And the question was
really a clever way
to bring in my divorce.
Bobby and I were going
through a divorce
and it hadn't been
finalized yet.
We did keep the fact that we
were separated from the media.
We thought that,
if people found out
that we were going
through a divorce,
it would change the trial.
The question was not asked to
shame Frank or Tim in any way.
The question was asked
to point out the fact
that, if there was a divorce,
there could be another marriage
and that Frank might
feel like he needed
to perform another wedding.
The first line of
defense, on either side,
is to question the
integrity of your witness.
This was a private affair
that was nobody's business.
I mean, it's one thing if
they want to talk to me
and reprimand me, but to
pull in my whole family
into this, and in front of the
whole world, that's an affront.
During the lunch break,
I sensed that I could not
go through with the
testimony that I had
coordinated with my counsels.
I was supposed to evade.
I was supposed to make
blanket statements.
I was opposed to redirect.
I wasn't able to say all
that because it wasn't what
I felt in my heart.
What I felt in my
heart was I needed
to let them know where I stood.
So I went into my
room and I prayed.
I remember saying to God,
can I take the stand?
What will I do if
I get defrocked?
What about my career?
What about my paycheck?
What about my family?
What about health insurance?
And it was in that
moment when it
was like God was saying consider
what I have done for you.
Jesus gave up
everything, not just
his career and his paycheck.
He gave up everything.
And all of the sudden,
I knew what I had to do.
And I got really nervous
and I remember actually
feeling sick to my stomach.
I just wasn't sure whether
the words would come out.
And I had no script.
And I sat in the stand and
I remember looking over
to my family and,
behind my family,
I saw all these people in
rainbow colored stoles.
And I remember thinking, wow,
there are a lot of supporters
here in this room,
and somehow, I
felt strength coming back into
me and my confidence came back.
And I heard myself say words
that were just incredible.
These were words that
were given to me.
I want you to know
that, if I'm going
to be United Methodist
minister tomorrow,
I will not discriminate
against anybody based
on their sexual orientation.
I will not refuse
ministry to them.
We are treating our LGBT
brothers and sisters
as second class Christians.
The hate speech has to stop.
We are harming beloved
children of God.
And then I remember
taking out this stole.
And I said to the
trial court, you know,
I don't think things
happen by accident.
I was given this
stole yesterday.
I'm wearing the stole as a
visible sign of my commitment
to be an advocate for
the LGBT community.
And that I can no
longer be silent,
but that I have to speak.
And that is all I have to say.
It was really emotional.
I heard some gasps behind me.
I was more proud
of my dad than ever
before when he pulled
that out and put it on.
It was almost, for me,
a relief and, really,
like a burden off me.
Counsel for the church had their
moment of cross examination.
I could tell that he
thought that's it.
He just made my case.
Frank, you have been found
guilty by this court.
Do you repent?
No, I cannot.
Will you from, this
day onward, promise
to uphold the
Discipline and never
perform a gay marriage again?
I cannot make that statement.
And that was the end.
And it was like a huge load had
been lifted from my shoulders.
And I was free.
I didn't care, at this
moment, whether they
were going to defrock me.
In fact, I would have rejoiced.
I felt like I had done
what God had sent me to do.
And then Jon Boger
came back to the stand
and said something like, did
you just hear what he just said?
Did anybody in this room
hear what this man just said?
And I found myself smiling.
All around the deliberating
room, every single one
said if he hadn't
made that speech,
they would've been
more merciful.
Well, the penalty phase
wrapped up tonight, Janelle,
and the jury came back with
a very interesting decision,
suspending Pastor Frank
Schaefer for 30 days.
He has 30 days to
consider whether he
will remain in the
United Methodist Church
and agree to uphold
the entire Discipline.
My first thought was wait, so
they're putting this on me?
We didn't want to become
part of the story.
We just wanted our decision
to be our decision.
We didn't want to be
part of turning Pastor
Frank into a martyr or a hero.
So they loaded the weapon, they
put a round in the chamber,
and they said you
have 30 days to decide
to kill your whole career.
And then we'll get back to you.
And, by the way, don't
perform any gay weddings
over the next 30 days.
It was brilliant.
He gets to choose.
It'll be his
responsibility whether he
can live within the covenant.
I remember other jury members
being happy and feeling
like a weight had been lifted
off their shoulder because they
felt that the burden of the
verdict wasn't on them anymore.
It was on Frank.
But I knew.
I knew from what he said that
we were forcing him to hand
in his ordination credentials.
And so it was us.
It wasn't him.
Supporters immediately
flipped over their chairs
and started singing in
support of the Schaefer
family following Tuesday
night's penalty hearing.
I just, I was like in a daze.
I was like in a dream.
And then, next thing
I knew, I was grabbed.
Frank, you need to do communion.
You need to give us communion.
This is the cup,
the cup that Jesus
raised at the end of
the Passover meal.
This is a new
covenant, a new time,
when everybody could come
to him, to his table.
And everybody could receive
grace and unconditional
love because of his sacrifice.
Thank you, pastor.
We decided we were going
to take this church camp
and reclaim it for
Christian purposes.
So it's up to me.
I have 30 days.
I'm here to tell you of that
I will not change my mind.
What I said tonight is the
truth and the full truth,
and so we'll see how
the church is going
to deal with it in 30 days.
It's hard to sort of
watch the whole world
advance around LGBTQ inclusion
and, as a church, not go along
with it on some level.
General Conference
meets every four years
and, every four years,
we try earnestly, we
bring these petitions and we
say, please change these rules,
please listen to
our story, please
affirm our basic
humanity and the fact
that God didn't make a
mistake by making us gay.
And they say no.
What happens is,
from our side, we go
and we think we know
that we're going
to win these and the
first one comes up
and everybody's on
pins and needles
and holding your breath.
And then our side wins.
It's thank God.
And then you see the
other side's hurting,
and they do some kind of
demonstration or whatever.
And the way that it works is
that this issue comes up three
or four other places and
gets voted on three or four
other times.
And now, you know,
it's like hey Tom, bam,
we got a guy last time.
Hold him up again.
We're going to get a
chance to hit him again.
Boom.
This is going to come
up two more times.
Hold him up.
Boom, boom.
And you know that
every time these people
are hurt all over again.
You do not feel like
you're some kind of victor.
You feel like this is
terrible, this is awful.
I don't want to be a
part of this anymore.
I don't want to see
people hurt any longer.
Can't we find some way not to
have to do this to each other
over and over and over?
I was at General
Conference 2012.
I was there with the horror
of being called animals
and pedophiles and people
who wanted to molest children
and all kinds of
horrible things that
were spoken on the floor
of General Conference 2012.
And the bishops who
were leading seemed
impotent to make it stop.
It was really quite--
it shook people up
and the homophobia in
particular was really bad.
So it was a very difficult
General Conference.
The only thing that kept
it from being even worse
is that, on the
penultimate day, a group
of LGBTQ activists
and some supporters
basically shut the conference
down with a civil disobedience
action at the altar.
For us, it was important
for someone to make it stop.
And making it stop had to
come in the form of protest.
That's not unusual
here in America.
Making injustice stop comes
in the form of protest.
I understand that struggle
because I have been through it,
not as a gay person,
but as a black person.
Bishop Talbert spent
three days in a jail cell
with Martin Luther King in
the 1960s, an experience that
changed his life forever.
When black people were
treated the way they were,
that was discrimination.
It was wrong.
When women were
treated the way they
were in the church, that was
discrimination and is wrong.
And when people, because of
their being gay or lesbian,
are treated this way, that's
discrimination and it's unjust.
In light of the actions taken
by this General Conference,
I believe that the time has
come to call and invite others
to join in what I'm calling
an act of biblical obedience.
Based on the twofold
commandment of love,
you shall love the Lord, your
God, with all your heart,
with all your mind,
with all your soul
and with all your strength,
and your neighbor as yourself.
This is our biblical
marching order.
It was an aha moment.
Biblical obedience.
And what do we obeying?
We are obeying the
love of Jesus Christ.
I declare to you that
the derogatory language
and restrictive laws in
The Book of Discipline
are immoral and unjust
and no longer deserve
our loyalty and obedience.
An unjust law is no law at all.
We're tired of waiting.
We're not going to accommodate
this faithlessness.
This is about having
biblical faith.
And then he gave
us, essentially,
his Episcopal blessing.
I call on the more
than 1.100 clergy
to perform marriages
among same sex couples,
and to do so in
the normal course
of their pastoral duties.
That was like, stick a
fork in me, I'm done.
That was the moment.
And so biblical
obedience is nothing more
than choosing to do the
right thing, no matter what.
And obviously people
will argue with me
and say how do you know
you're doing the right thing?
I could be wrong.
But I doubt it.
I doubt it.
They won.
They have their four walls.
They won their property.
They're down to
one service, which
is what they always wanted.
And they won in the
sense that they'll never
see Pastor Frank in
that pulpit again.
But then the Lord kind of
wins, because now they'll
see Pastor Frank on CNN, on the
cover of a book, in a movie.
The world will now
see his ministry.
We're only going to keep
him to just Lebanon County.
The Reverend Frank Schaefer.
It is such an honor to
be here this morning.
My calendar is pretty full.
For a defrocked minister,
I have an awful lot
of preaching to do.
In fact, all of my
Sundays are taken.
We continue to call
him Reverend because we
believe his ordination
stands in our midst.
People want to hear
me share the story
and I am more than
willing to do it
because I think sharing my
story will bring healing
to the church.
We've been taken into
a homophobic captivity
and it's been more than
40 years that these rules
and that this language has
been a part of our Discipline.
And it has cost us.
I really believe that we
are at a tipping point.
I believe we need to do
everything in our power,
as United Methodists,
to take our church back.
This is not about doctrine,
this is not about theology.
It's about the life of people.
Thank you so much
for your witness.
It's an honor to meet you.
I'm grateful for what
you did for your son.
We're backing you
a thousand percent.
It's been, actually,
healing to be
invited to these churches,
that are open and affirming.
I hadn't really
seen that before.
Jimmy's been like a father to
me through this whole process.
Beth like a sister, so thank
you for your encouragement.
I thought to myself,
you know what?
I'm not so sure that, once I get
through this, that I will ever
set foot into a church again.
God asked me to risk
it all and I did.
But look how faithful God is.
Because God said, I'm
not finished with you.
I'm not finished
with Frank Schaefer.
I have more to do.
Frank needs to take
responsibility,
which, in my opinion
and a lot of others,
he's never done that.
He's never taken responsibility.
He's never said I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, United
Methodist Church.
I'm sorry, Iona.
I'm sorry for those
that I've hurt.
He has just simply moved on.
He's the rock star now for
reconciliation, I guess.
What's next for you?
You going to stay in Lebanon?
Hell no.
No, we're not going
to stay in Lebanon.
We've been offered a place
of ministry in Santa Barbara.
It's very exciting,
not only because it's
in sunny California and
it's a great church,
but because our son
Kevin is there as well.
I'm excited to have him there.
It'll be really cool to be able
to see them and go for hikes
or wine tasting or whatever.
I have mixed feelings,
because three of our kids
are still here on
the east coast,
so it's going to be
a little hard for me.
It's been 18 years
in Lebanon County
and we've made a lot of
friends, but there's also
been a lot of disappointments
and very stressful times
for me and my family.
So I think it's time
for us to move on.
We'll miss you so much.
We'll come see you, I hope.
Absolutely.
OK.
Just don't forget about us.
My gosh.
No, no, no, no, no.
I just got this yesterday.
I haven't even opened it yet.
Wow.
My goodness.
I love it.
There you go.
One for you, too.
How neat.
That's beautiful.
Some of the back story's
in there, some of the dirt.
The concerned group.
I'm going to vomit.
He'll always be my pastor,
my pastor in my heart.
You know, that's the
way I think of Frank.
He'll always be my
pastor, wherever he is.
Don't you think?
Yeah.
I think a lot of
people think that.
Yeah.
When we kids, my parents would
talk a lot about California, as
like the place that
they wanted to end up.
To me, it's a beautiful,
beautiful place.
It's like paradise.
I think we sort of deserve this,
because we went through hell.
And we're going to end up in
paradise, at least for a while.
So California here we come.
Our guest is Frank Schaefer.
He was defrocked in 2013 by
the United Methodist Church.
He was reinstated on an
appeal in June of 2014,
but that reinstatement
is being appealed
before the denomination's
highest court today.
This is our Supreme
Court, so to speak,
of the United Methodist Church.
So it's a very big day.
There's no appeal
possible after this.
This is the final word.
This case is no longer
about LGBT issues.
The trial court's findings
of guilt were not appealed
and the other
aspects of that issue
are properly the work
of General Conference.
Some have suggested that this
is a decision that is ultimately
going to split the church.
We've seen other churches
go through this, too,
sort of around the world.
Is there really a threat
here of basically two
Methodist Churches
emerging from this?
If left to stand,
the appeal decision
will do harm to the
church because it clearly
communicates that it's
OK to ignore and violate
the Discipline.
When Bishop Carcano
invited Frank Schaefer
to come to California
and serve in ministry,
she was essentially
undermining the whole covenant
of United Methodism.
We simply cannot feel good about
being in a church that allows
its pastors to promote something
that we believe to be sinful.
Churches need to change
from the bottom up.
That's been a major focus
of the work that we do,
but it does need to
change at the top.
No people will continue
to allow themselves
to be discriminated against.
During the long process
that led up to his trial,
Frank began to see all of the
ways in which our church is
doing harm to our gay, lesbian,
bisexual and transgender
brothers and
sisters, and decided
that he could no longer remain
silent in such circumstances.
The future has to
be our willingness
to live with our differences.
I'm not trying to convert
all of those who are
evangelicals to be progressive.
They can make their witness
but let me make mine too
in my church.
This is as much my
church as it is yours.
Rather than hurting
each other, rather than
damaging the
church, why don't we
set each other free
to pursue what we
believe God would have us do?
It just may be that more
work for the cause of Christ
would be done if
we didn't use so
much of our time, our
resources, our finances
to fight this battle that's
never going to be resolved.
Thank you very much for your
thoughtful and prayerful
consideration of this matter
and the church rests with that.
I don't think I would be
ready for another defrocking.
But I know that
I'll get through it
because, if there's
one thing I've
learned through this
whole experience,
it's that if you
do what is right,
God is not going
to let you down.
And it's been incredible, the
support has been incredible.
So I'm not afraid of it.
I know it's going
to be devastating
if it does indeed happen,
but I'm not afraid of it.
Our top story, the
United Methodist Church
has ruled in the case of former
Lebanon County pastor Frank
Schaefer.
This case has gone
back and forth,
but the decision that
was announced today
is the final one and the United
Methodist Church's highest
court has ruled that
Frank Schaefer can remain
a minister in the church.
The judicial council
reinstated him as a clergyman.
Upheld a decision to reinstate
Reverend Frank Schaefer.
I'm so glad it's over and done
with and I'm still a reverend.
He plans to continue to
fight for inclusion of gays
and lesbians in the church.
They reinstated me as a
United Methodist minister,
sending a very clear signal
that things are changing
in the United Methodist Church.
And that is my
commitment, I want
to continue to change
things from the inside out.
This afternoon, a
spokeswoman for the church
said the next General Conference
is in 2016 and, at that time,
legislation could be
brought up to change
their stance on homosexuality.
In the past, I
had really thought
I should go into
the ministry myself.
And now those feelings
are all coming back
and now there's a
different component.
I would love to be within
the Methodist Church
and continue to fight
for what my dad has
started to fight for.
Reverend Schaefer,
the people who
reinstated you know that this
is something you might do again.
Absolutely.
I mean, I was very
clear on that.
I never made it a secret.
I said I will perform another
gay marriage if I'm asked to.
We met on Facebook
through friends.
I asked him to go and have
coffee with me at Starbucks
and kind of went from there.
John and I are very compatible.
We want the same
things out of life
and we have the same values.
So this is a keeper.
John and I are engaged and
my dad, the first thing
that he said when I called
him, after my mom had told him
we were engaged, my dad said,
do you have something to ask me?
I haven't officially asked my
dad, but he knows it's coming.