[intense mysterious music]
[tense music]
I will talk to you of art,
for there's nothing else
to talk about,
for there is nothing else.
Life is nothing
but a homeless traveler
on the RTD of art.
Burn gas on the freeways
and whip your sour cream
of circumstance,
flip at your channels
and plod at your monitors.
Creation is, all else is not.
What is not creation is
meatless sausage and rice cakes.
Let it all crumble
to feed the artist.
The artist is,
all others are not.
A canvas is
a canvas or a painting.
A rock is a rock or a statue.
A sound is a sound
or it is music.
A preacher is a preacher
or an artist.
Where are John, Joe,
Jake, Jim, Jerk,
dead, dead, dead.
They were not born
before they were born.
They were not born.
Where are Leonardo, Mozart,
Shakespeare,
alive, alive, alive.
They were born.
Bring on the multitudes
and the multitude of fishes.
Feed them
that you will be satisfied.
Nourish the artist,
stretch their skin
upon an easel,
crush their bones into a paste
that he may mold them.
Let them die.
And in their miserable death
become the clay in his hands
that he might form
an ashtray or an ark,
that he might take you
in his magic hands
and wring from
your marrow wonder,
all that is comes through
the eye of the artist.
[fingers snapping]
All the rest are blind fish,
swimming in the cave
of aloneness.
Swim on, you mortals
and muddling maddened souls,
and dream of that one bright
and sunny island.
Some artists will bait a hook
and let you bite upon it,
bite hard, and die.
And in his stomach,
you will feed creation!
[audience applauding]
[jazzy music]
Bravo, Maxwell, bravo!
Hi, Walter.
[man] Walter,
what are you doing?
Oh, uh, I was actually just
looking at Carla's picture.
Well, that's not what
I pay you for, now is it?
No, Mr. DeSantos,
I'm sorry, Mr. De--
Don't be sorry.
Be a bus boy.
A busy bee busboy.
Yes sir.
- Hi, Carla.
- [Carla] Hello, Leonard.
Ah, your new headshots.
- Si.
Oh, very nice.
Very, very nice.
Leonard, why do you have to
be so mean to him?
Excuse me, sir.
[music continues]
Nice talking to you.
I got to go.
[people chatting]
[people shushing]
Who can make the monkey laugh?
- [mechanical chattering]
- I can.
Who can make the monkey laugh?
- [mechanical chattering]
- I can.
Who am I?
Mm. You don't know me
but I know you.
I've been looking after you.
You, when you weren't chosen
for the little league team,
you, little baby, went home
and cried.
[whiny crying]
You should have called on me.
I was there waiting,
watching after you.
Who am I?
I'm your patron saint of anger.
A-N-G-E-R. R-A-G-E. R-A-G-E-N.
Raging in anger.
Rage in anger.
[door creaks]
How ya doin'?
[man] All right man,
how you doin'?
[poet continues indistinctly]
[smacks lips]
[man] Later.
What do you got?
Nothing yet.
There's definitely
a lot of drugs around here.
I've been keeping a low profile
but I just can't figure out
who's dealing,
at least not yet anyway.
[mechanical chattering]
Who can make the monkey laugh?
- [mechanical chattering]
- I can, I can.
I am your patron saint of anger.
[audience applauding]
Brava, brava, brava!
Ergo, what do you think
of these, huh?
Tell me what you think.
Perfectly adequate,
much like the performance
of St. Anger over there.
I don't think anyone could
comprehend what I was saying.
Their blank faces staring,
mute, unfeeling.
Oh, I liked it very much,
Mr. Brook.
I liked it very much.
Well, I'm overjoyed.
"Let them die.
And by their miserable death,
become the clay
in his hands that he might form
an ashtray or an ark."
Yeah, that's a word for word.
Is it? I've forgotten.
Man, you mean you don't even
remember your own poems?
That's so Goethe.
I refuse to say
the same thing twice.
Repetition is death.
[man] What do you mean?
Teach me.
When you repeat something,
you relive a moment, wasting it,
looking at a shed skin.
I only want new impressions,
new sensations.
But I thought you said, "Life is
as like a homeless traveler
- on the RTD bus."
- I know that, I know that!
Walter, Leonard,
he is looking at you again.
Man, that guy is such a...
losery type of guy.
[music continues]
We heard that you could pick up
some really cutting edge pieces,
if you know what to look for
around here.
I'm looking for something
for my den,
something unusual, something
je ne sais quoi.
Do you know what that means?
Yeah, uh, well perhaps
these might interest you.
These are from
our roadkill series.
I take the pictures.
I do the research.
Oh, they're sort of
like Les Crim's.
- [artist] Sorta.
- Yeah, exactly.
And as a matter of fact,
we actually do
the driving as well.
Well, I don't know, dear,
what do you think?
- Maybe--
- Oh good Christ, no!
We have friends
that are members of PETA.
[man] Of course, you're right.
I'm sorry,
I'm afraid we're looking
for more of
an investment possibility.
Hey, look, man, this is not
a supermarket, okay?
There are no aisles here,
right?
There's no 10 items or less
express checkout.
- I'm sorry.
- Yeah, investment potential,
that's a real dead soul
way of looking at it.
Nonsense!
Why, we've developed
great rapport
with many young artists.
We love artists.
We support artists.
We're very supportive.
[Walter] "All that is comes
through the eye of the artist.
The rest are blind fish
swimming in
the cave of aloneness."
Oh, that's very deep.
[Walter] "Feed them
that you will be nourished.
The artist is,
all others or not."
Where did I just hear that
someplace?
Are you a poet, too?
[both laughing]
[chuckles] Ah, no.
Well, what do you do?
[stammers]
I've been working,
I've been working
on something, but I'm...
um, I'm just not finished yet,
yeah.
Oh, and what is it?
A crying clown?
[laughs]
Look, man, why don't you
get out of here, okay?
We are trying to
negotiate a deal.
I am working on something.
[Leonard] Walter.
You're startin' to
piss me off.
Come on,
let's get back to work.
Sorry about that folks.
Is he, um, retarded?
No, he's just a bus boy.
[all laughing]
Get your feet off the chair.
See, I spelled the word feel
with an extra E
to emphasize exactly
- how much--
- [Walter] Excuse me,
is Carla done with her coffee?
I don't know, Walter,
take a risk.
And also
I spelled the word closet
with a K, but that's for
something different.
Uh, you know,
to paraphrase Moliere,
takes one to know one.
[laughs] You know,
if you've seen Tartu.
- [key clicking]
- [dog barking]
[gate squeaking]
Hello, Walter.
Hello, Mrs. Swicker.
I wanted to tell you,
the super fixed
those leaking pipes
and sealed up
that hole in the wall.
Oh, okay.
Walter, you look awfully pale,
what'd you have to eat today?
I had a salami sandwich,
Mrs.--
Oh Walter,
if you were my son--
Walter, Walter,
why don't you let me fix you
a nice hot bowl of soup.
It won't take but a minute.
That's okay, Mrs. Swicker.
I--I can fix myself something.
I...I have something important
to do.
Oh, by the way, Walter,
did you happen to see Frankie
out here by any chance?
No, I didn't see him at all.
Oh, what's got into that cat?
[stammers] Well,
if you do see him,
would you tell him
that I have a nice fat piece
of ocean-fresh halibut
for him?
Okay, Mrs. Swicker.
Good night, Walter.
Good night, Mrs. Swicker.
[door closes]
[mysterious music]
[can opener grinding]
[music continues]
[cans rattling]
[gas whooshing]
[music continues]
Oh, Carla.
Now I have my muse.
[cat mewing]
Frankie?
[intense music]
[heavy breathing]
[cat mewing]
Frankie?
[music continues]
[frantic music]
"A canvas is a canvas
or a painting.
A rock is a rock or a statue.
A sound is a sound
or is music."
[music continues]
Now, I gotta make her nose.
God.
Come on.
[music continues]
[cat mewing]
No, no, no, no, no!
- [cat mewing]
- Frankie?
Frankie, are you in there?
- [scratching]
- [cat yowling]
The super must have
sealed you up by accident.
- [cat yowling]
- [scratching]
Okay, don't worry, Frankie.
[cat yowling]
Old Walter's gonna
get you out of there.
[cat yowling]
[tense music]
Hold on, Frankie.
[cat yowls]
Oh, Frankie, Frankie,
are you still there?
Frankie?
[mysterious music]
[cracking]
[frantic music]
[dramatic music]
[mysterious music]
[Walter]
"And by their miserable death
become the clay in his hands."
[light fixture squeaking]
[tense music]
[Carla] I'm trying to find
a style of my own.
What do you think, huh?
You like them?
Oh yes.
Very, very nice.
[Carla] Hi, Walter.
Hello.
What are you doing here
so early?
[Walter] Well,
I brought something.
What is it, your laundry?
Don't worry about him.
What have you got?
[tense music]
A thing I made.
Wow.
Leonard, look at this.
[Leonard]
Where'd you buy that?
I didn't buy it.
I made it.
You made that?
[hissing]
- Yeah.
- [Carla] I've never seen
anything like it.
Maybe Segal, but nothing
with such a dichotomy.
It's very good, Walter.
- Honest?
- [mysterious music]
Well, what's it called?
Uh..."Dead Cat."
Well, it certainly
looks dead enough.
You wanna buy it
and put it in the club?
[laughs nervously]
It'll scare people away.
Don't you feel it?
[both] Feel what?
Way it's giving off
it's presence.
[speaking Italian]
Come, take a closer look.
Look at the detail.
It's so alive
and yet it's so dead.
Look at the expression
on his face.
Why'd you put a knife in it?
- I didn't mean to.
- Ah.
Got carried away, huh?
All right, I'll tell you what.
I'll put it in the corner
of the alcove, uh...
if it sells,
we'll split it 50-50.
- How's that?
- Bene.
Sure.
Wow.
I guess I am an artist
after all.
Maybe so.
Yeah, I wouldn't quit
your day job.
"All that is comes through
the eye of the artist."
Yeah, don't lose your ear,
Van Gogh.
Why don't you
start with the toilets?
[woman]
You won't take me seriously.
I'm just a stupid girl.
This piece is entitled,
"Sexist Transportation."
[cello playing]
[violin playing]
Do you like my cat?
Yeah, it's like out there.
You understand
what I'm saying?
[strings playing]
Wanna buy it?
No, no man, I...
I don't have the funds
to be buying
various pieces of artwork.
You understand
what I'm saying?
[Walter] Sure.
- Good luck, though.
- Yeah.
- [clangs]
- Ow.
[music continues]
[violin playing]
[zipper whirs]
[cello playing]
[strings playing]
[audience applauding]
Hey Walter, hey man, congrats.
Your cat is fat.
Yes,
everybody's talking about it.
- Attention,
attention everyone!
- [people shushing]
[jazzy music]
As you pass through
the portals of
this elegant chamber,
I'm sure you noticed
on the right,
a small plaster figure
and assumed this transfixed
effigy to be the work
of a master sculptor.
Indeed, it is.
And that bright new creator
is in our midst.
He's none other than
Walter Paisley,
our very own busboy.
[man whispering]
Which one's Walter?
[Maxwell] Who's undiscovered
hands of genius
have been carrying away
your empty cups
of frustration.
Remember his name,
Walter.
[ice clinks]
- [speaking Italian]
- [audience applauding]
Bring me a gimlet.
Oh, hey, Walter.
Congrats on the cat, man.
We're just wondering, uh,
where you got the idea
for dead animals.
Yeah, Walter,
can you say plagiarism?
Don't listen to them, Walter.
I get it.
You get what?
Your work,
the layers of irony.
- [man] There's Walter.
- Paisley, congratulations.
That is just the most amazing,
amazing work.
[crowd chattering]
I can get you representation
with one phone call.
If you need studio space,
call me.
I understand it, man,
I hate stinkin' cats.
[detective]
What the hell is going on?
Everybody wants to meet
the bus boy.
[man] You know what this means
for your career?
I'm outta here.
See ya. [exhales]
What's going on over there?
[sighs] I don't know.
And where our
double latte macchiatos?
Service around here
has really gone to hell.
You!
We ordered 20 minutes ago.
20 minutes ago.
Terribly sorry,
I'll be right with you
and I'll make him triple it,
no extra charge.
I found five dollars so
I can buy your cat.
I have a gallery on Melrose
with free parking.
I always knew it would happen,
Walter.
What's next, "Dead Dog"?
- [crowd chattering]
- [music continues]
[man] They all say that
Generation X is cliché,
but I have never thought
that in my life.
Actually, who does your hair?
Is it Doyle Wilson?
All right, folks, show's over.
Come on, drink your latte,
eat your muffins.
Do you think
I look like a beatnik?
Darling, you reek of Bohemia.
[music continues]
Did you hear that,
Mr. DeSantos?
People seem to
really like "Dead Cat."
Yes, yeah, they do.
Don't they, Walter?
Look, why don't you
take the rest of
the night off, okay?
You look tired.
Well, I'm not tired.
No, look, it's okay.
You know, you came in early
and besides you're creating
an incident.
When people are applauding,
they don't order anything.
I'm sorry.
No, look, Walter, okay,
go home. Okay?
Work on something.
All right? Make another cat.
Okay.
Good night, Walter.
Good night, Mr. DeSantos.
Wait, Walter?
Hello, Mayolia.
You really did something
to me tonight with your work.
With "Dead Cat"?
With "Dead Cat."
[chuckles] It was like
a breath of fresh air.
Oh, I could just babble on
about it for hours.
- Really?
- Yeah. I really could.
[sensuous music]
It's like, um,
you've turned on.
- Turned on?
- Yeah.
A white, hot bulb
is burning inside of you.
Oh, I want to be warmed
by it, Walter.
That's really nice
of you to say, Mayolia.
Oh, let me enter your world,
Walter.
Let me enter that white hot,
inspired world of yours.
I can't, I gotta go home.
Well, I'll go home with.
No, Mrs. Swicker will
start asking questions and...
Let me give you something then.
maybe this will give you
some inspiration,
change your perception
of reality.
I want you to have it.
There's something in here
for you.
Gee, thank you.
Let it inspire you Walter.
Maybe it will let you
think of me.
[dog barking]
[tense music]
[locket clicks open]
[mysterious music]
[tense music]
[dog barking]
[music continues]
[dog continues barking]
Why, yes, I...I do think
"Dead Cat" is a masterpiece.
- [gun clicking]
- [music continues]
What's that, Carla?
Oh.
Oh, I love you, too.
[knocking on door]
[door creaking]
Hello, Walter.
Hi.
I know you...
from the Jabberjaw, right?
Yes, can I come in, Walter?
Sure.
[door shutting]
Nice basement you got here.
[chuckles]
I was just fixing some pancakes.
You can have some, if you like.
Oh, I don't think so, Walter.
[tense music]
Did you see my cat?
Yeah, I saw your cat
and I also saw the girl
give you this.
Oh, that was Mayolia.
She's a nice girl.
She's kind of strange though.
[music continues]
You like chasing the dragon,
Walter?
- Chasing the dragon?
- Yeah.
[laughs nervously] What do you--
what do you mean?
Ah, let's cut the crap.
I'm a police officer and
you are in deep shit,
pal, whether you know it or not.
Possession of narcotics
isn't something we take lightly.
You understand.
But I got a feeling
you are gonna cooperate with me.
You wanna tell me
about your connection?
- Connection?
- I'm not trying to pinch you.
I don't care about you
or the girl,
but if you want to
save your ass,
you better start telling me
what I want to hear.
Telling you what?
Who's the head honcho?
Who supplying the smack?
Smack.
God dammit, Walter!
Where ya from, the moon?
Haven't you ever heard of smack,
horse, junk, heroin?
Oh, I--I have heard of that.
I've never really seen it,
though, I mean...
I've heard it's very expensive.
Oh, yeah.
It can be very expensive.
[music continues]
Wow. [sighs]
Geez, wasn't that nice
of Mayolia to...
to give me some expensive smack?
Who do you think
you're dealing with?
I'm trying to
cut you a break, kid.
- You are?
- Yeah,
but you got to drop
this mild-mannered bit
'cause it doesn't fly with me,
Walter.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
All right,
you're coming downtown with me.
- What did I do?
- Make it easy on yourself,
dummy.
That was Mayolia.
She gave it me,
I didn't even ask her for it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I've heard
that song and dance before.
Now just save your breath.
You're comin' downtown with me.
I told you
I didn't do nothing wrong.
Now don't get me mad, Walter.
We're just going to take
a little drive, all right?
I'm not going anywhere with you!
Turn around!
Back up and turn around!
Please, put that away, please.
Come on, please,
- can you put that--
- What, are you deaf?
- Now turn around.
- Don't shoot me, please.
Just relax, Walter.
- Sir, could you please--
- Shut up and relax.
Would you please put that
down? Sir, please?
Just relax.
- [whimpers] Please, sir.
- Shut up.
- [metal banging]
- [grunts]
[body falling]
[Walter panting]
- [blood pattering]
- [eerie music]
[knocking on door]
[Mrs. Swicker] Walter?
Walter, are you all right?
I thought I heard
someone shouting.
[objects clattering]
- [knocking on door]
- Walter?
Walter, I'm coming in!
[door creaking]
What is all the noise in here?
Noise, Mrs. Swicker?
- What noise?
- Don't you tell me
I didn't hear a racket.
I am an older woman.
I don't need to be upset and
disturbed in this manner.
Yeah, I understand.
I was just
straightening up the place.
Straightening up, indeed!
Are you sure you're alone?
I'm always alone, Mrs. Swicker.
You know that.
Walter, have you been
talking to yourself again?
Well, I...I guess I have,
Mrs. Swicker.
Somebody's got to.
Oh, Walter.
You know what you need?
A girl, and
she doesn't have to be pretty.
Just so she'll take
good care of you.
Oh. I take real good care
of myself, Mrs. Swicker.
Oh yeah, I can see that.
Look at this place.
[dramatic music]
It's terrible.
Don't you ever clean it up?
Walter, are you listening to me?
Um, Mrs. Swicker, I have to go
meet some friends.
So I have to take a shower.
[Mrs. Swicker] Well, why don't
you clean up this dump?
I will, Mrs. Swicker,
I will, goodnight.
Walter,
what is the matter with you?
I don't know.
- [door shutting]
- [deadbolt locking]
[exhales loudly]
[frantic music]
[heavy breathing]
I didn't mean to hurt you, sir.
Just think, if you had shot me,
you'd be picking up
my blood now.
[pattering]
[whispering] This is crazy,
this is crazy, this is crazy!
I didn't know
you had it in you, Walter,
I didn't know you had it in you.
Mr. DeSantos said,
"Make something, Walter,
make another cat."
I don't have another cat.
[blood pattering]
[eerie music]
[man over phone] Good morning,
Third Precinct.
Yeah, this is Detective Lane.
Has my partner checked in yet?
[man over phone]
Um, no, not yet, sir.
Damn.
He's probably putting a little
cream in someone's coffee
but let's put an APB out on him
just to be safe.
Oh, and don't send anyone
to the Jabberjaw.
It'll blow my cover.
[man over phone] Okay, yeah.
Are you sure sir?
Yeah. I'm sure. Bye.
[receiver clanging]
[phone ringing]
Jabberjaw for coffee,
art and personal growth.
"Dead Cat"?
[bright music]
Yes, it's for sale.
Well, the artist isn't here
just now, but I am the agent.
Well, we've had quite a few
calls on this piece.
What were you
interested in paying?
[chuckles] Well, that may seem
like a fair price to you
but, uh, we're talking about
an exciting new artist here.
Uh, yeah, that sounds more like
the right ballpark. Uh.
Look, uh, can I get back to you?
Uh, the piece needs to be fixed,
uh, mounted.
Can you call back later?
Ask for Leonard.
- [phone beeps]
- [tense music]
Walter, you naughty boy.
What do you want?
Well, as long as you're here,
you might as well listen.
I got something to say
about wanting and not getting,
but I don't talk with my mouth.
I hope that's okay.
[heavy metal music]
- See that guy's
doing something.
- Hm?
- That's good, what he's doing.
- Yeah.
[Cuff] I mean the fact that
even if you don't get
- what he's trying to say--
- I do get it.
Okay. But I'm just saying
if you don't--
- [Link] I totally get it.
- [Cuff] Fine, you get it
just like me,
I'm an artist, right?
- I know that, so am I.
- That's what I have to do.
- [Link] Right.
- Okay, that's the whole point,
I have something to say
legitimately,
unlike people like Walter,
right?
- Oh, right!
- Who just steals
other people's ideas
and concepts.
He has nothing to say
for himself.
Hey, hey, hey, hey,
it's that guy again.
[music continues]
[Cuff]
What's that guy's story?
You know, I see him around here
all the time.
He's always like lurking,
you know?
I think he's a narc
or something.
Yeah, he's pretty cop-like.
[Link] Yeah, yeah,
maybe he is a cop,
maybe he's here
looking for Walter
'cause he know Walter's a thief.
- [Link] Absolutely.
- [glass clinking]
Geez, take it easy, Walter.
I'm sorry, Mr. DeSantos.
That's all right, Walter,
come here.
I want to have a little--
little chat.
- [music continues]
- [whimpering]
See that?
The clumsiness of guilt, man.
That's how they got Oswald,
he was staggering.
[thudding]
[audience cheering, applauding]
Put the tray down, Walter,
and have a seat.
I thought I wasn't supposed to
sit in customers' seats.
Why shouldn't you, Walter,
things are different now.
- They are?
- Of course they are.
You've arrived.
You've been recognized.
You're a talent.
Leonard, what are you doing?
- Hi, Carla.
- Hi, Walter.
What am I doing?
I'm trying to tell Walter
I want to be his agent.
- Really?
- [speaking Italian]
Why the sudden interest
in Walter's work, huh?
Because I have faith in you,
Walter.
Now I can't make any promises,
but I think
I can sell "Dead Cat."
Now I'm gonna have to hustle.
So I'll expect
to make something off it too.
That sounds fair.
Hey, you know what this proves?
What, Mr. DeSantos?
It proves I've underestimated
your ability.
Walter's work, well,
it has enormous realism.
You can hardly tell it
from the real thing.
The question is,
what are you gonna make next,
Walter?
Oh, I already have a new one.
Really? What is it?
Well, it's a full-length,
life-size figure.
What is it called?
"Murdered Man."
[eerie music]
"Murdered Man"?
"Murdered Man," "Dead Cat,"
Sounds a little bit like
the Warhol Mayhem series.
Exactly, exactly.
Very unoriginal.
[music continues]
Leonard, you all right?
[shakily] Oh, yeah, I'm...
I'm fine.
You don't look so hot.
Probably had some of the food.
[chuckles]
- [phone dialing]
- Oh, there you are.
I tried to contact you
on the phone.
Excuse me,
I have to make a call.
I want the cat.
I'll give you
1,000 dollars cash.
I can't talk right now.
How much do you want?
2000, 3000?
No look, I'm busy.
I won't be overbid. [chuckles]
I am a very wealthy man
and I don't mind paying
for what I want.
[woman over phone]
911 emergency.
Yes, give me Homicide.
- If you ensure me the cat...
- [woman] Transferring.
...I'll give you
5,000 dollars cash.
[man over phone]
Homicide. Hello? Hello?
Uh...
I don't have the cat right now,
but I'll be getting it back
in a few days.
5,000 dollars, right?
Right, thank you.
I consider it a bargain.
[chuckles]
Here's my card,
when you're ready.
Good night.
Leonard, you feeling better?
[rock music]
Yeah, uh,
I'm feeling a lot better.
Listen,
I'm going over to Walter's,
after the place closes.
I want to get to look at
"Murdered Man."
Do you want to come along?
Come on, Walter,
take off the sheet.
[eerie music]
[dramatic music]
Do you like it?
Like it?
It's a masterpiece.
Um...
I have to sit down.
[tense music]
Can you feel it?
In all its eloquence,
can I, huh?
Modern man in all his self-pity.
How did you ever find it
all inside yourself, Walter?
It wasn't easy.
What's the matter with you,
Leonard?
Hmm? Nothing, nothing.
Nothing at all.
Well, what's your opinion
of it, huh?
[Leonard mutters]
Then admit it,
it is a work of genius.
I admit it.
We can bring it down
to the Jabberjaw.
No!
[sirens wailing in distance]
Why don't you cover it up,
Walter?
[Carla] What's wrong with you?
Why do you want to hide it?
Well, um, I never realized
the true depth
of Walter's talent.
It's something very precious.
You are right, Leonard.
And it's something so precious,
we should not keep it
to ourselves, huh?
We should give Walter a show.
What?
How about Sunday?
[stammering] No, no, no,
no, no, no.
No, that's--that's not possible.
Uh...
It would take years to make
enough statues to put on a show.
What kind of agent are you,
Leonard?
Don't you understand
I want to feature my work?
You will, but
these things take time, Walter.
And right now,
you've got to break out
of this one avenue you're on.
Carla and I will--
will guide you,
help you develop
and evolve your work,
maybe lead to something
more abstract.
Abstract,
with his talent for realism?
You see the direction
his realism takes?
It's unhealthy.
You said I was a genius.
If I'm a genius,
I don't want to be a busboy.
You know, you may
have a point there, Walter.
You shouldn't keep working
at the Jabberjaw.
Look, "Dead Cat's" practically
money in the bank.
I talked to a man today and
I think he's going to buy it.
So here's your half in advance.
25 dollars.
Now, if you need more,
I've got it.
I have faith in you, Walter.
Carla, look,
25 dollars for something I made.
- [door creaking]
- Let's go.
Now you're a professional.
Goodnight, Walter.
What about my show?
[door closes]
Oh, hey, look,
get a load of this.
[upbeat jazz music]
[whispering]
He's such a bad boy.
What have we here?
Excuse me.
Looks like "Dead Cat"
- gave Walter some confidence.
- Mm-hm.
[woman giggling]
Hi, Carla.
Hello, Walter.
[music continues]
Cappuccino or something?
Yes, please, I'd like a double
latte macchiato, please.
Sure.
Walter.
The rewards of achievement
have come your way.
Maxwell.
Yeah, well, I'm starting to see
some success
- with some of my pieces.
- Excellent.
Yes, I was, uh, just suggesting
to Walter
that he experiment with
more abstract things,
right, Walter?
Why would you suggest
anything to Walter?
Are you the spokesman
for society,
come to poke
your stifling finger in his eye?
Hi!
Maxwell, Walter,
how goes it, gentlemen?
Who invited these two
down from the clouds?
[woman] Maxwell!
[sexy jazz music]
Clear the floor and
bring me a bowl.
I may be sick.
[Cuff]
Well, if it isn't Alice Ziobro,
here to spread a little cheer.
So Alice, where you been?
We missed you.
Well, I was up in Seattle,
working on a new video.
[Link] Oh yeah?
For who?
Petroleum Function.
- No way.
- And it's for their new CD.
So was it any good?
[scoffs] It was awesome.
Hey, don't you work here?
- Not anymore.
- Yes, Walter has sold
- his first sculpture.
- Oh, really?
Alice, this guy's a total clown.
He ripped off our concepts.
[Alice] Oh yeah?
You know, someone should
really burst his bubble.
So what project looms
on the horizon, Walter?
- I don't know.
- [Alice] You know, I do
life modeling.
Would you like to do me?
I just might.
[Alice] Well, I'd be more than
happy to help...
for 50 bucks an hour.
[both laughing]
Never mind that, Walter's going
to try something abstract.
There you go again.
May take my business
to the Snake Pit.
Do you know, I was
going to suggest to Walter,
that he try female figure.
It might be nice, Walter.
If you like, I will model
for you, for free.
Oh no, not you.
I couldn't do that.
Would you, uh, pose for me
for free?
You know, Walter, if you wanna
be a legitimate artist,
man, you gotta do nudes.
[chuckles]
- I mean, nudes, nudes, nudes.
- Yeah, that's right.
No major body of work
would be complete
without at least some nudes.
Please, can't we just
change the subject?
I am so sick of hearing about
sculpture this
and sculpture that.
[scoffs] No one even knows
how to do it anymore.
Especially the bus boy
from the Jabberjaw.
Who do you think
you're talking about?
You. Look at you!
Who do you think you are?
You're just a poser trying
and failing
to fit into the scene.
Much the way
your breasts fail to fit
into your crimson frock.
Oh really?
Well, I think this whole bit
about him being
a discovered sculptor
is a bunch of bull.
That's not true.
- I am sculptor.
- Oh really?
Prove it.
[lips smacking]
Make something out of this.
[music continues]
How about...
"Flying Cake"?
[spitting]
Oh, my God.
[tsking]
You disgust me.
If you were a real artist,
you would have
created something,
but you're a fake and a phony.
And let me tell you something.
I see right through you.
I'm going home.
Good.
Good night, dark prince.
[tense music]
[siren wailing in distance]
[music continues]
What do you want?
I just wanted to apologize
for being nasty tonight, Alice.
All right, fine.
So you apologized.
Now get lost!
[tense music]
Look, schmuck.
I thought
I told you to get lost!
But I wasn't finished
talking to you, Alice.
Well, I'm done talking to you.
I decided to make
a female figure.
I want you
to pose for it, Alice.
Oh yeah?
You got the money?
Uh-huh. 50 dollars
an hour, right?
Yeah, that's right.
50 bucks an hour.
[dog barking]
I live down here.
What, you mean you live
in the basement?
Yes.
[scoffs] Nice.
- [dog barking]
- [cricket chirping]
Good for you, Walter. Mm-hmm.
You know, could use
a little heat in this dump.
[thumping]
Well, it's bad for the clay.
[tense music]
[Alice] I'm almost naked.
[music continues]
Just sit there.
So. Do you like what you see?
Yes.
Hey, that doesn't look like
very much clay.
It's enough.
Are you, um, nervous, Walter?
No.
When's the last time you had
a totally nude girl
in your room?
Without a stitch of clothing on,
sitting, facing you?
A girl with a body like mine.
You're breaking
my concentration, Alice.
Can I ask you a question,
Walter?
What?
[laughing]
Are you still a virgin?
For crying out loud, what does
that have to do with anything?
It's just an innocent question.
And I just want to clarify
your intentions, that's all.
[frantic music]
Look, let's forget about
this pose,
it's all wrong.
Okay. I'll pose any way
you want me to.
Thanks.
Would you put this
around your neck, please?
[music continues]
[dramatic music]
- [whooshing]
- Would you like to do me?
- [Walter grunting]
[Alice gasping]
Nervous, Walter?
[choking]
[music continues]
Do you like what you see?
[Alice struggling]
[Alice laughing]
Are you still a virgin?
It's just an innocent question.
[laughing]
[crackling]
[intense music]
[Carla] Here you go, enjoy.
What's this sauce?
I'm lactose-intolerant.
Is nondairy sauce,
made with soy milk.
- Ah.
- [doorbell rings]
- I'll get it.
- [operatic music playing]
Well, if it isn't
Mr. Plagiarism.
Good morning, Walter.
- Hi.
- Walter, what's up?
Well, I brought you something
and I...
I wanted to show you.
Is it "Murdered Man"?
It's better.
Man, this is heavy.
Yeah, what is this,
Murdered Elephant?
When did you make this, Walter?
Last night.
Doesn't take me very long.
Well, Walter,
unleash your vision.
[operatic music continues]
Walter, I can't believe it.
She's beautiful.
It looks like Walter
finally did his nude.
Yeah, and it's pretty good.
Walter,
I'm honored to know you.
Do you think she's better than
"Murdered Man"?
It's really good, Walter.
They're both great.
[Maxwell] I'm moved.
I'm moved to write.
Tonight at the Jabberjaw,
I will recite a new poem
and we will celebrate
in your honor.
Yes, Walter.
- [kiss smacks]
- [spring boings]
[Lane]
All right, let's split up.
[upbeat music]
Try to keep a low profile.
You hear anything,
you let me know.
I'm getting' to
the bottom of this.
Attention, attention everyone!
I have something to share.
- Order, order!
- [people shushing]
Thank you.
[chuckles]
[Maxwell] Walter,
Walter,
the bird that flies now
pays later
through the nose
of ambidextrous apathy.
Hmm.
Necrophiles may dance
upon the placemats
in an orgy of togetherness.
[chuckles]
And in the deep freeze,
it is the children's hour
and no one knows
that Duncan is murdered.
And no one knows
that Walter Paisley is born.
Duncan knows.
Tuesday, sunrise knows,
and alley cats and garbage cans
and satellite dishes
and you and I,
and the nude
descending the staircase,
and all such things with souls,
we shall hear
that Walter Paisley is born.
[Walter belches and laughs]
And the soul becomes flesh,
and Walter Paisley is born!
- [audience applauding]
- [crowd chattering]
Man, Maxwell,
that was magnificent.
Yeah, you were so eloquent.
[Maxwell] Walter deserved
every word of it.
Oh, man, that wasn't brilliant.
That was powerful stuff, man.
- Eh, it was all right.
- Hm?
What do you mean,
it was all right? You just
don't get it, that's all.
- Oh, I get it.
- You don't get it.
[stammers] Why do you keep
asking if I get it or not?
- I get it.
- Oh, if you get it,
then who's Duncan?
Macbeth killed Duncan.
Who?
Look at Walter down the bubbly.
[chuckles]
Drunks make great lovers.
They try harder.
[Carla]
Congratulations, your majesty.
[music continues]
Did you hear what he said?
It was all about me.
Yes, Walter.
It's true, isn't it?
Every word.
[chuckles]
- [Leonard] Thanks for coming.
- [man] Thank you.
[Leonard] Good Night.
[man] Go get the car.
[door closes]
You might want to hold off
on the bubbly.
[tense music]
Yeah, why?
You might talk too much.
[scoffs]
And what would I say?
[music continues]
You two grinders ignoring us?
Oh, no, not me, Maxwell.
I wouldn't ignore you,
because I know what it's like
to be ignored.
So, Walter, what are you
going to do next, huh?
[tense music]
[somber music]
[banging]
Alley cats,
garbage cans.
They know Walter Paisley
is more.
What are you gonna do next,
Walter?
Oh, I don't know,
what are you gonna do next?
I better do something quick.
Before they forget about...
I know what it's like...
to be ignored.
[machine whirring]
[saw whining]
[baseball announcer speaking
indistinctly on radio]
Who the hell are you,
what do you want?
Life...
is nothing...
but a homeless man...
on the bus of art.
Huh?
Let them all crumble so that
they might feed the creator.
[chuckles] Beat it, ya drunk,
before I call the cops,
all right? Huh?
Before you get hurt.
Yeah, move along, pal.
- [saw powering up]
- I'm sorry.
All else is rice cakes.
Get outta here,
you friggin' freak!
[crashing]
Son of a bitch!
[saw whining]
- [punch landing]
- [grunting]
[dramatic music]
[man groaning, screaming]
No!
[man screaming]
No, no!
No!
- [sawblade whirring]
- [squelching]
- [Walter panting]
- [body thudding]
[tense music]
Hello, Leonard.
It's a beautiful morning,
isn't it?
It was.
Wha...what've...what do you have
in the box, Walter?
Oh, Leonard,
wait till you see this.
[dramatic music]
What's the matter, Leonard?
[eerie music]
Leonard?
[laughs] You made a bust.
Yeah,
isn't it wonderful?
What's the matter, Leonard?
Listen, Walter.
Okay.
All right.
I don't want you
to make any more statues.
Okay, Walter?
Do you understand, Walter?
I don't--no more statues.
Why--why not?
I have to make statues, Leonard.
You heard everybody.
They want me to make them.
[tense music]
I can't go back to being a bus--
Look, Walter.
Okay, now listen to me.
You've got to stop this now,
okay?
I'm beginning to feel
a little responsible.
You are responsible, Leonard.
You're my agent.
You're the one who started
the whole ball rolling.
Oh, jeez, Walter.
[music continues]
Hey, do you think
I have enough pieces
for a show, Leonard?
Uh--Walter, n...
Wait a minute, Walter.
You know what?
It's not such a bad idea.
Listen, when Carla comes by,
I'll--I'll have her make up some
nice invitations, okay?
And she'll get them printed up.
- Really?
- Yeah.
And--and we'll send them
to the critics and
the art collectors.
And we'll tell them...
Tell them what, Leonard?
We'll tell them
that this is going to be
your first and last show.
Why?
Uh...
It'll drive up the price.
[chuckles]
We'll both become rich
and you won't ever have to make
another statue again
because you'll be a legend.
[operatic music playing]
Well, I don't understand
why we can't go.
Mr. Leonard DeSantos is afraid
to have you come.
You, who buy his coffee,
his potables, his food.
You who are the heart and soul
and meat of the Jabberjaw.
He has slighted you.
You got an invitation?
I did not, but I'm going anyway.
Not to drink his champagne,
but to witness Walter's triumph.
After that, we shall go no more.
Walter,
I won't wish you good luck.
Why not?
That would imply that
you could not succeed
on talent alone.
- [toilet flushing]
- Ciao.
Walter, you look very handsome.
So do you.
I mean, look so pretty.
Thank you.
[Walter] Are you ready?
Ready?
We have plenty of time.
I know,
but I--I wanted to talk to you.
Okay, we can leave right now
if you want.
Well, goodbye, my friends.
Have a great show, Walter.
[door shutting]
What are you trying to say,
Walter?
[tender music]
Carla, I don't want to
make statues any more.
You don't?
No.
I want to get married...
to you.
Walter,
how long you think about this?
Oh, for a long time,
ever since you first
came to the club.
You were the only one
who was ever nice to me.
I didn't even know you loved me
until you kissed me.
Walter, I really do like you.
And I did kiss you,
but this was for your work, huh?
There's more to love
than just this.
[tense music]
What do you mean,
you don't love me?
I'm afraid
that's what I'm saying.
You gotta love me!
Walter, [speaks Italian],
I'm sorry.
Yeah, I don't want you
to be sorry.
I want you to love me.
[speaking Italian] Calm down.
Let's go back in there.
And then when the show
is over, maybe then we'll talk.
No. [stammers]
I want to talk about it now.
Walter, I don't want to
hurt your feelings,
but there's not going to be
a time
where you and me
are going to be together.
Do you know what that mean?
[gentle music]
- Why not?
- Because we are just friends.
That is all, just friends.
[tense music]
I'm going inside.
- [Waitress] Champagne?
- [Maxwell] Ah.
- [classical music playing]
- [people chattering]
You are too kind.
[Waitress] Champagne?
Walter,
why are you wearing
the mask of defeat?
I don't know.
Haven't you heard the things
they've been saying?
They'll give you 50,000 dollars
for those pieces alone.
I thought
you didn't care about money.
Well, I don't, but it's 50 thou.
[crowd chattering]
Thank you.
Excuse me.
- Hey, Leonard, great champagne.
- Mm.
Very nice little soiree,
my friend.
Looks very well attended.
A little too well.
- Whoa!
- Get out,
you weren't invited.
[chuckles] What?
- Get out, I said,
get out, come on, let's go.
- Are you serious?
- Are you throwing us out?
- Out the back so no one
will see you, come on.
- He's serious.
- Fine, we're going.
What's the attitude for?
Let's go, you bums,
get outta here.
Oh, bums, how are we bums?
And be specific.
Just make a road kill,
all right.
[crowd chattering]
I'm sorry about
what I said to you before.
Ah, forget it, Walter, eh?
I've been thinking.
Would you let me
make a statue of you?
Would you really like to?
Bene.
Okay.
[dramatic music]
[crowd chattering]
[mysterious music]
[tense music]
Where are you going, Carla?
Walter, there's a body
in the sculpture.
Oh, well, that's Alice.
[intense music]
Let them become the clay
in his hands
so that he might mold them.
Walter, stay away from me.
Don't you see, Carla?
I made them immortal.
I could do the same for you.
Get away from me, Walter!
[door opens, shuts]
[dramatic music]
I love your articles.
I read them every week.
Thank you
art is to be appreciated.
For example, this work,
the artist is...
Well, I'll be.
There's another work
inside this one.
My God, it looks just like
a real finger.
[critic] It's unparalleled,
it's reality encased
in a shield of whiteness.
No, it's just a finger!
- Excuse me.
- [frantic music]
It's reality, all right.
[Walter] Carla!
[gasping]
[music continues]
[dramatic music]
Oh, God, Lou!
Precisely what are you doing?
Stand back, asshole!
- [plaster breaking]
- [crowd gasping]
[dramatic music]
Oh, my God!
Paisley!
There's a body in there!
- [crowd screaming]
- [glass breaking]
Carla!
Oh, God!
Call 911,
get a patrol car down here now!
- What happened?
- Walter Paisley's a murderer.
I had no idea.
Hey, we just saw that freak,
Walter,
chase Carla down the street.
- He looked whacked.
- I'm going after him.
Well, I'll go with you.
Be careful, he's a genius!
[tense music]
Carla!
[Carla panting]
Walter!
You get away from me, huh?
What is the matter
with you, huh?
What's the matter with you?
Get away, get away!
- [grunts]
- [smacking]
[body thudding]
[Carla panting]
[intense music]
- [exclaims]
- Are you all right?
It's Walter, he's gone crazy.
He tried to attack me.
- [Lane] Where is he?
- He was going that way.
- [Lane] Let's go!
- [Carla] Come on!
- [all shouting]
- [Carla shouts in Italian]
[music continues]
- [trash cans crashing]
- [Mrs. Swicker gasping]
- [dog barking]
- Walter?
Walter!
[latch locking]
What are you gonna do now,
Walter?
[dramatic music]
Hey, get in here!
He's down there
and he's gone crazy!
Come here! Hurry!
[dramatic music]
I don't want him in my house
one more minute,
he's really scary!
- [Link] Come on, Walter!
- [Lane] Open the door!
[paper rattling]
[all shouting indistinctly]
Wait a minute! Here! Uh...
There, here, use this!
[all shouting]
Open the door!
All right, stand back!
[all shouting]
[door breaking open]
Oh, no, Walter!
Unbelievable.
This will command
a small fortune.
- [somber music]
- [rope creaking]
He would've called it
"Hanging Man."
His greatest work.
[dramatic music]
- [camera shutter clicking]
- [upbeat music]
[camera shutter clicking]
- * Little boy
- [camera shutter clicking]
* Longs to fly
* Father gives him wings
- * And says goodbye
- [camera shutter clicking]
* Little boy takes to the air
- * Hoping he would find
* Happiness up there
[camera shutter clicking]
[tense jazzy music]