CHILDREN: * Dina, Dina bo bina
Banana fana fo fina
* Fee fy mo mina
* Dina
* Andy, Andy bo bandy
* Banana fana fo fandy
* Fee fy mo mandy
* Andy
-WOMAN: Hi, Dina.
-(ALL LAUGHING)
DINA: Hi.
MAN: Hi, Dina.
DINA: I saw a butterfly.
Here, doggie.
LINDA: That's her.
DINA: I'm going to work.
MITCH: She's pretty.
I've been observing her
for quite a while now.
Music.
Music!
MITCH:
What's her mental capacity?
LINDA: I can't tell
without testing her,
but emotionally, she
acts fairly well adjusted.
What do you think?
I don't know. She looks happy.
We can make her happier.
-(SQUEAKING)
-(BOTH LAUGHING)
GIRL: Claire!
Let's do Gina.
* Gina, Gina bo bina
Banana fana fo fina
-(KIDS CONTINUE SINGING)
-DINA: Fina!
* Gina!
Let's do Susie!
* Susie, Susie bo busy
Banana fana fo fusy *
(CONTINUE SINGING)
Hey, Dina.
Yes.
(CHILDREN SINGING)
Can you give this
to that man over there?
-Yes.
-Okay.
Popcorn?
Dina!
* Dina, Dina bo bina
Banana fana fo fina
* Fee fy mo mina
DINA: Uh-oh.
It's clean.
(CHILDREN CONTINUE SINGING)
Hi.
Hello.
-Hi, Dina.
-Hi.
Bye.
MITCH: Over the entrance
of the temple of science
are written the words,
"Ye must have faith."
It's a quality the scientists
cannot dispense with...
(CAMERA CLICKING)
...and it is a quality upon
which our current endeavor
is based.
Ladies and gentlemen,
meet Laverne and Shirley.
(CHATTERING)
Their story
is the result of years
of scientific research.
My father,
Dr. Fredrick Conlon,
won the Nobel prize
for pioneering
the molecular
biological revolution
back in the 1950s.
Soon afterwards, he founded
the Conlon Institute,
which I'm happy to say
remains at the cutting edge
of current genetic therapy.
Until his death last year,
my father drove forward
the groundbreaking
research that we
reveal here to you tonight.
But first, I'd like
to introduce our
resident researcher,
Dr. Linda Ryan.
Linda came to us
three years ago
with Laverne and Shirley.
She's been caring
for them since their
natural mother abandoned them
and she oversees
their training,
their education
and their medical status.
In other words, she's Mom.
(ALL LAUGHING AND APPLAUDING)
(SHRIEKING)
As you can see,
they're a handful.
Girls, sit down!
(SHRIEKING)
During routine DNA research,
while testing a tropic virus
meant to boost
the immune system
of our laboratory animals,
Frederick Conlon discovered
a most startling side effect.
The elevation of their
innate intelligence.
(ALL CHATTER)
That is what brings
the esteemed
Dr. Elisha Swan to us today.
A scientist specializing
in learning disabilities,
he represents the Behavioral
Studies Foundation
in Washington D.C.
Dr. Swan will guide us
in the application
of our finding.
Looks like Dr. Swan's
plane got in a little late.
(ALL APPLAUDING)
Based on the Institute's
research to date,
the FDA has given us
the green light
to begin testing
a human subject.
ALL: Doctor, Doctor...
Do you expect...
Doctor, isn't there
a moral issue here?
Yes, many. Gender selection,
the right to privacy,
genetically, are we
creating a master race.
Yes, those are
very important issues.
But medical benefit
is our goal here.
We are morally responsible
to enhance the quality
of life for future generations
if we can.
Isn't that the same...
You say... You say you can
make a human being smarter.
Yes, that's true
and possibly
reverse conditions
of mental deficiency.
How do you address
those people picketing outside
who say what
you're doing is immoral?
We respect their
right to an opinion,
but wonder if they
understand what we
hope to accomplish here.
But a human guinea pig,
isn't that crossing the line?
Aren't you playing God?
LINDA: Absolutely.
We have to play God.
If that's how they
choose to say it.
Tell that to those people out
in front of the Institute.
Oh, they're always out front.
We can't be concerned
what other people
think. We're scientists.
Now, wait a minute.
How we're perceived does
affect our livelihood, honey.
Yes, but our pledges
for the fundraiser
are higher than last year.
And that's only
half our funding.
Think what we can
gain from the publicity.
Think of what I can
gain from just being here.
(LAUGHING)
Hey, when are you two
getting married?
In six months.
Right after
our grant presentation.
Don't worry about the grant.
If this thing works,
every pharmaceutical company
in America will be after you.
Now, don't start talking
to me about drug companies.
They're businessmen.
They're not scientists.
So all they're concerned about
is their pocketbooks
and their glory. That's it.
Well, what's wrong
with a little glory?
Jonas Salk didn't call
the polio vaccine
the Smith vaccine.
And you've heard
of pasteurized milk.
Louis Pasteur and his wife
didn't seem to mind.
Your dad was on his way
to a second Nobel prize.
To us.
This is gonna win him
that prize.
ANDY: This just might
win your first prize.
I like prizes.
Leave it for now.
Come on. It's time to eat.
How do you want your eggs?
On my plate.
-Scrambled okay?
-Yes.
Breakfast!
I like breakfast at night.
Makes twice this week.
It's fun.
Little too much fun.
Need to go grocery shopping.
Okay.
No, not right now, Dina.
Tomorrow.
Okay.
We need to make a list first.
If I could buy you
one special thing
what would it me?
-Red.
-What?
For my rainbow, I need red.
(CHUCKLES)
This place sure
brings back memories.
I expect your father
to walk through
the door any minute.
To tell me how I should've
handled the press conference?
Your father would
be proud of you.
Not likely.
Yes, he would.
We're finishing
the work he started.
MITCH:
We're not finished yet.
He's not happy
unless he's worried.
So what's the plan?
I want to follow the progress
of one subject hands-on.
You know, build 'em
from the ground up.
DINA: Breakfast!
Here, Tuna.
You be good.
Okay.
8:20...
This one.
Andy!
(THUDDING)
Stay!
Linda is bringing Swan
up to speed on her
research with the chimps
and how we plan
to implant...
DINA: And the butterfly
stood on the mountain.
And
the butterfly had wings.
Big wings.
With colors.
And they saw her fly.
Fly high in the sky and...
Hi.
Hello.
I know you.
-GIRL: Come on, Dina.
What's next?
-BOY: Yeah!
GIRL: Come on!
And...
It's upside down.
I can't read good.
The butterfly...
-The butterfly landed on...
-(CHUCKLES)
...a big leaf.
And he...
GIRL: Come on, Dina.
-BOY: What happened?
-DINA: ...landed next
to a caterpillar...
LINDA: Self recognition
measures a special
kind of intelligence,
the sense of self.
Most animals just see
another animal
when the look in the mirror.
Laverne and Shirley
know they're looking
at themselves.
Not only are the chimps
healthy as horses,
so to speak,
but since taking
injections, they're smart
as whips.
Leonard. Leonard, come here.
This is Leonard Takawa.
He's our senior
lab technician.
Graduated MIT
cum laude at 18.
Leonard, this is Dr. Swan.
Nice to meet you, Leonard.
LINDA: Would you boot up
the computer game
please, Leonard?
We're gonna get him
to talk one of these days.
(LAUGHS)
Who wants to show off
for Dr. Swan?
(SHRIEKING)
LINDA: Not yet, you!
(BOTH LAUGHING)
-Make yourself
at home, all right?
-Thank you.
Just don't go near
Mitch's desk.
It could go at any second.
Computer games geared
for a third or fourth grader.
Laverne has it down.
First thing we noticed
was a rapid acceleration
of their IQ.
Linda's monitoring, of course.
Physiologically,
they're stable.
Blood test
consistent and normal.
What's interesting
is the degree to which
they crave stimuli.
I mean, the more the better.
New puzzles, games,
color, movement.
They make a fuss
when we leave at night.
Hmm, interesting.
Any other side effects?
-Yes.
-What?
Hairy palms.
Ah! (LAUGHING)
Hi.
(BOY CHUCKLES)
Hi, dummy.
-(CHUCKLES)
-Can't you say hi?
Hi.
Oh.
Your shoe.
(CHUCKLES)
You got paint on your shoe.
It's pretty.
Yeah, it's pretty messy, huh?
-Yes.
-(LAUGHING)
Why don't you try
to get some paint
on the picture, uh?
I do. I get paint
on the picture.
-Look, I got it.
-(LAUGHS)
(SCREAMS) Hey!
Hey!
Come on!
Rip it up!
(SCREAMS) Hey!
Come on!
Give it to me!
Want a ride? Hop on!
(BOYS LAUGHING)
(GROANS)
(BOTH LAUGHING)
Hey, can't you read the sign?
(LAUGHING) You retard!
(BOYS LAUGHING)
I saw her again today.
She was with that
group of kids
who really seemed to love her.
I was observing her
motor skills and, uh...
This logical progression
of thought
she uses to tell stories...
We've seen abstract reasoning
through her ability to express
herself with her paintings.
Mmm.
I gotta tell you
something. I...
I have to admit
I can't stop
thinking about her.
LINDA: Let's bring
Swan to the park tomorrow.
See what he thinks.
MITCH: Okay.
Let's have Swan meet her.
-Hi.
-MITCH: Hi.
-How are you?
-I'm busy.
Can I have some
coffee, please?
Yes.
And one of these cookies.
How much?
Andy can do change.
I can't do change.
Uh, that comes to $2.35.
Let me introduce myself.
My name is Dr. Mitch Conlon.
Doctors make me
take my clothes off.
I'm Andy Chase.
This is Dina.
Would you happen to know
how we can get in
touch with Dina's family?
I'm it. She's my aunt.
And my right-hand gal.
I'm a right-hand gal.
She came to work for me
when I bought the place.
I can't read good.
Perhaps we can help.
This is Dr. Linda Ryan.
We're with
the Conlon Institute.
We're involved
with genetic research.
Oh, so you're the guys
in that big institute
up the street.
I've read about you.
-This is Dr. Swan.
-Hello.
MITCH: He's a teacher.
Can you make me read good?
Well, maybe we can.
Can you make me read
signs in the grass?
ANDY: Dina, please.
Mr. Chase, we have
every reason to believe
that we can enhance
Dina's mental capacity
to some degree.
How?
With your permission,
we'd like Dina to come
to the institute.
We'll give her
a complete physical
and a battery of tests
to see if she qualifies
for our program.
If she does?
She'll stay with us.
We'll administer
injections daily.
Keep an eye out
for secondary responses.
-What do you mean?
-Side effects.
That sort of thing.
Nothing that would
surprise us.
I like her fine
just the way she is.
I'm sorry.
We're not interested.
Mr. Chase,
Dina would receive
long-term medical care
for her participation.
And we'd put her in school.
Dr. Swan...
-I want to go to school.
-ANDY: Dina.
-I want to, Andy.
-Dina, Dina, please.
I want to go to school!
No!
-Like my friends.
-Dina, be quiet!
The worst that could happen,
Andy, is nothing happens.
She might not even qualify.
MITCH: You've got
nothing to lose.
Dina suffers
from microcephaly.
Since she's had
no formal education, uh,
her IQ's a little difficult
to pinpoint at this time.
We have to completed
some standardized tests.
Measure her against
grade school children,
but I'd place it somewhere
between 50 and 60.
Certain parts of her
cerebral cortex never
fully developed, so
she has a problem
completing higher
order activities,
cognitive functions...
Real people talk, please.
Scholastically,
she's not in
the first grade yet.
(BUZZER BEEPS)
ANDY: What's that?
That's the way
we measure advances.
The game targets
eight-year-old abilities.
Dina failed.
When and if she masters it,
we'll know the injections
are working.
We should see chemical changes
within 48 hours.
Blood test normal.
Stats normal.
She passed with flying colors.
ANDY: Dina, they want me
to sign this paper.
They say
they can make you better.
But God made you
the way you are.
I don't know what's right.
Do you even know
what I'm talking about?
I want to read.
(KNOCK ON THE DOOR)
-I brought you some things.
Can I come in?
-Yes.
First night in new place
is kind of strange, isn't it?
Yes.
I got a colorful picture.
Might cheer up your room.
I like paint.
Those are flowers.
-Yes, they are.
-I like them.
This is the computer game
you tried before.
I tried that game before.
Tomorrow, school starts
full-time.
-With my friends?
-No, Dina.
This isn't a place to play.
Learning is like work.
We have rules.
-But there'll be games
and classes...
-I like games.
Good.
It's time for your
first injection.
Well, Dina, this is our lab.
This is a where we do
our tests,
and it's also the home
to two of our favorite
peoples.
(CHIMP PANTING)
Oh, good girl.
Four seconds faster.
Good.
-This is Laverne.
Laverne, this is Dina.
-Hi.
Hi.
And that's Shirley.
Your turn.
Sit down.
LINDA:
Can you turn it on, Dina?
The computer.
(BEEPING)
(VIDEO GAME CLOCK TICKING)
AUTOMATED VOICE: (OVER P.A.)
Your attention, please.
It is now 7:45.
Any personnel requiring
evening security clearance,
please report to the
night supervisor.
Attention.
It is now 7:45.
DR. SWAN:
Maybe this isn't for her.
LINDA: Her blood
tests are normal.
No secondary reactions.
How'd she doing
in class?
She seems completely
overwhelmed.
Well, we'll give it
a little time.
If she can't do it,
we'll have to get
someone else.
(DIALING)
Andy,
I thought you wanted to
hear my voice.
Andy?
I'm scared.
Bye.
MAN: If she's scared,
it won't work.
It's this place.
She came to work for me
when I bought the snack shop.
That's when she moved
into my house.
Now, even though I shop
for her, pay her bills,
she still feels independent.
This must feel like a
step back for her.
Maybe this isn't for her.
No, she really wants it.
She just needs to relax.
-Let me take her home.
-No, that won't work.
We need her in a controlled
environment.
But a sense of family is
important for her.
-She need to come home with...
-With us.
She'll stay with us.
We can control
her environment.
And besides, she needs
a woman's influence.
If this works out,
she'll be living in a
whole new world.
She'll have to be prepared.
She needs a woman.
Plain and simple.
Well, here we are.
Come in. Come in.
-Welcome.
-Welcome. I'm Dina.
(LAUGHING)
I'm Jeanette.
Welcome home, Dina.
Let me show you to your room.
DINA: It's big.
(CHUCKLING)
Here you go, Dina.
Your new home.
(CHURCH BELLS CHIMING)
Oh, excuse me.
Well, Dina,
what do you think?
-Will this do?
-It's pretty.
(CHUCKLES)
And you can do anything
you want to make it home.
-Here's your computer game.
-Yes.
-Andy!
-(CHUCKLES) Thought you
might need a friend.
(SIGHING)
-Jeannette went all out
tonight, in your honor.
-In my honor.
Cold cucumber soup.
-My own recipe.
-I like cold soup.
(CHUCKLES)
(SPOON CLANGING)
No, Dina.
Dina, you have to wait.
I have to wait?
Yes, until everyone is served.
And you have to use a
soup spoon.
That's the big spoon.
(SPOON CLANGING)
-I have a big spoon.
-Good.
Bread?
-Would you like some bread?
-Yes.
(CHUCKLING)
-Thank you.
-Bread.
(CLOCK TICKING)
-(VIDEO GAME PLAYING)
-DINA: Uh-oh.
Oh... No.
Oh...
Testing
session.
Day 9.
Dina, I want you to take a
look at these pictures
and tell me which one
doesn't belong.
DR. SWAN: Dina?
Pay attention.
-How many cc's?
-Seven.
Secondary reactions?
None.
There you go.
Good night, Dina.
Good night, Linda.
Okay...
-Everything all right?
-I'll do better tomorrow.
Good.
Good night, then.
(COMPUTER BEEPING)
-I just don't get it,
what are we doing wrong?
-Uh-uh.
Subject's last blood test
and MRI show the physiological
changes that we anticipated.
At this point, she should be
showing signs of improvement
in dexterity
hand-eye coordination,
comprehension of tasks,
etcetera.
I think it must have something
to do with body mass. I'm
going to up the dosage again.
Swan suggests we start
testing another subject.
We don't see improvement
by Monday, he is going to
contact Andy Chase.
(GASPS) Aw!
Andy...
Come on, Tun.
Shh!
(SOBBING)
Going home!
(EXCLAIMING IN ALARM)
Tuna!
Aw...
(MOANING)
Tuna!
(LINDA MOANING)
(MOANING CONTINUES)
(CHIMP SCREECHING)
(CONTINUES SCREECHING)
(COMPUTER GAME MUSIC PLAYING)
(SIGHING)
Ah!
(CHUCKLING)
Oh, my!
Mitch! Oh, my!
Mitch!
I did it.
Oh! Mitch?
Oh!
I did it.
-What?
-I won.
-Great.
-I won! I won!
Good girl!
-(CROWD CHATTERING)
-Hold them up...
Are you the people doing
the testing on that woman,
Dina Blake?
Look, she's put you on
the front page of the paper
but there's no mention of
-how she's doing.
-Our work is going very well.
Thank you very much.
You call it work?
How is the person doing,
Doctor? How is Dina Blake?
Mitch.
The operation was a success,
Doctor, but the patient died.
LINDA: Mitch, Mitch, come on.
Come on.
Dina's latest results.
Her IQ is testing about
30 points higher.
-And her capacity to learn
is improving.
-Great.
-You just bought this pizza
for $8.35.
-Yes.
You gave me this ten.
How much change
do you get back?
$8.35.
$8.40.
-$8.50.
-Yes.
Eight...
Um...
I'm not hungry.
Dina, it's okay
not to get it the first time.
It happens to everybody.
It's okay to try it again.
MITCH: Try it again
and remember, enunciate.
DINA: What?
MITCH: Speak clearly.
I speak clearly.
"At."
Bat. Did I do good?
Hat.
Did I do it better?
-(CAT MEWING)
-Ca...
Look.
-Dina, pay attention.
-I'm paying attention.
-"Cat."
-Don't tell me.
You have to look at the word.
Don't tell me.
I can do it.
Subject seems to have
trouble focusing...
I can do it!
I can do it! I can do it!
DINA: I can do it!
WOMAN: Dina!
What was that all about?
Simple. She was comfortable
with failure. That's all
she ever knew.
What did I do wrong?
You got your bedside
manner from your father.
You're too worried
about results.
Lighten up. If you have fun,
she'll have fun.
You don't have a temperature.
I can't go to school tomorrow.
I think you can.
I want you to.
Okay?
I like it when you smile.
DR. SWAN: She's come
a long way in a month.
LINDA: We're seeing
physical improvements now.
Her speech and writing
are getting better.
Keep her an extra hour
from now on.
I don't want to push her
too hard.
No, the injections
are working.
I want to see how far
she'll go.
(CHUCKLING)
Perfect. Continue.
(KEYBOARD CLACKING)
I'm here.
I'm ready to read.
In a minute.
Look at me.
I'm writing
a note to Dr. Swan.
Look at me.
He's right here.
Yes, yes, I know. I know.
But, uh, this is faster.
You talk to machines
more than you talk to people.
Okay.
Open the book.
MITCH: Books by great authors
are the best teachers
in the world.
They can instruct you
on anything you need to know
in life.
The way to make reading
meaningful
is to find stories and books
that interest you
and reflect the way you're
thinking and feeling.
That way, they come alive
and it sticks in your mind.
They create mental pictures
that you can hold on to.
Books about history can
make you a part
of what's gone on before
and, oh... Poetry.
Poetry speaks to your soul.
Connects you to another being.
At the checkout counter,
the clerk says,
"That'll be $17,
33 cents, please."
You give her a $20 bill.
What change do you get back?
I'll take this cookie too.
Okay.
The cookie is $1.35.
That makes it
$18.68.
So I get
$1 and
cents.
I'm right, aren't I?
I made change!
-I made change!
-(PEOPLE CHUCKLING)
I made change!
"Congratulations!
Today is your day.
"You're off to great places.
"You're off and away.
"You have brains in your head.
"You have feet in your shoes.
"You can steer yourself
any direction you choose.
"You'll be on your way up.
You'll be seeing great sights.
"You'll join the high fliers
who soar to high heights.
"Wherever you fly,
you'll be best of the best.
"Wherever you go,
you will top all the rest.
"Oh, the places you'll go!"
ALL: Bye!
Bye, bye.
DINA: Wait for me.
(CHUCKLES)
Looks like Dina has a crush.
LINDA: Oh, that's natural.
Mitch is responsible for a lot
of her happiness right now.
She's like a teenager.
It'll pass.
Don't you see what's
happening? She's falling
in love with you.
-Andy, you're exaggerating.
-No, you think you're the guy
-in My Fair Lady.
No, in this situation...
-Hey, hey, hey.
Simmer down here,
you're overreacting.
I'm not Professor Higgins.
No, you're a doctor!
She has no experience
with life,
you should know that.
Her therapy
is going very well.
Dina's more important
than your little
experiment here.
I want you to take a look
at her. She's learning,
she's reading,
-she's happy.
-She's a person.
I don't want
to see her getting hurt.
She's fine.
I'm Dina's mentor right now.
She looks up to me. That's it.
You should see
the way you look at her,
Doctor.
(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
WOMAN: It was wonderful.
-Hi.
-Hi, Dina.
Hey.
Mitch! Hi, Linda.
-Hey, slow down.
-Hey, there.
-Goodbye.
-(LAUGHS)
Oh, she isn't maturing
as fast as her mind, is she?
-No, not quite.
-Charming, though.
Yes, it is.
-Hi.
-DINA: Hi.
MITCH: I kinda hate
to see her grow up.
-We're gonna use it.
-What do you mean?
-We'll introduce her
at the fundraiser.
-Introduce her?
Yes, we'll show her off.
A picture's worth
a thousand words, right?
We've got four months.
How do you do this
without looking down?
LINDA: Just keep
your head up,
don't cheat.
-You'll get the hang of it.
-Oh, God!
(LAUGHING)
Mitch, come here.
We have a problem
with the spelling lesson.
-DINA: Let's do Leonard.
-(LAUGHING)
* Leonard, Leonard bo beonard
Banana fana fo feonard
* Fee fy fo feonard
* Leonard
Who's teaching
what around here?
DR. SWAN: We've been
Dina-ised. (LAUGHS)
Come on, you. Come on.
We don't have time
to play games right now.
Hey, hey. Stop it.
Calm down. Stop it. Hey!
What's that all about?
-Looks like you need
an attitude adjustment.
-(SHRIEKING)
The Institute's fundraiser
is to coincide
with the presentation for our
research branch this year.
We are, at last,
seeing success.
Dina's progress
is consistent throughout
all of the academic subjects.
She shows a marked interest
in the arts.
Probably because
that's the world
she has always understood.
Van Gogh, Starry Night.
It's one of his best works.
I have to remember that.
Starry Night by Mr. Gogh.
The best
of the Post-Impressionists.
Notice the movement
on the canvas.
The use of color
to underline the mood.
How each brush stroke affects
the turbulence
in his tortured soul.
The madness in his genius.
I like it.
You like it.
I feel it here.
Me too.
LINDA: It was a very
thoughtful gift, Mitch.
Well, she's never had
oils to work with before.
She's doing so well.
In so many ways.
(DINA HUMMING)
-(CHIMPANZEE CHATTERING)
-DINA: Shirley!
(CHIMPANZEE CHATTERING)
-(SHRIEKING)
-DINA: Laverne!
Stop it.
Oh.
Hold it down, you three.
Sorry. Come on, you two.
Come on, get down.
Get down.
-Shirley!
-(SHRIEKING)
Oh!
-What happened?
-Shirley scratched me.
-No, you were teasing her.
-I didn't.
No, now, listen.
Now, you got them riled up.
I didn't tease her.
Dina, you have to admit
when you're wrong.
-You are not a child anymore.
You are a grown woman...
-I'm not... I'm not wrong.
You have to start
acting like one.
-April 13th, subject
was playing with Shirley...
-Look at me.
I am not Subject.
I am a person
and I have a name.
It's Dina.
(CHILDREN LAUGHING)
GIRL 1: Hey, there's Dina!
ALL: Dina!
We missed you!
I missed you too.
GIRL 2: Can you play with us?
GIRL 3: Yeah.
Well, I...
What's wrong?
Nothing. Uh, nothing's wrong.
You look different.
I am different.
You look like my mom.
-(CHUCKLING)
-DINA: I do?
I do.
So, come on, play with us.
Come on. Come on, let's go!
Let's do Dina.
ALL: * Dina, Dina, bo bina
Banana fana fo fina
* Fee fy mo mina
* Dina
Do you know where Dina is?
ANDY: No, I don't.
Why don't you know
where she is?
(CHILDREN CHATTERING)
(INHALES DEEPLY)
(PANTING)
Nice day, huh?
I love the sunshine.
Yeah.
(EXHALES DEEPLY)
I'm David.
I'm Dina.
(EXHALES) I like to jog here.
Jog?
Yeah, I run here every day.
-(INHALES DEEPLY)
-Oh!
I run too,
with Laverne.
Oh, is she here?
No, she's...
She's back in her cage.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
I, uh... I haven't seen you
around here before.
I'm... I'm usually with them.
DAVID: Oh,
is one of them yours?
No, but I'm like her mom.
Are you married?
No.
Got a boyfriend?
We had a fight.
(SIGHS) Been there.
That's why I'm free and easy.
Sometimes, it's better.
I'm free and easy too.
Uh...
I hope you don't mind me
saying this,
but you have amazing eyes.
Oh.
And mouth.
Hey! Hey! Get away from her.
-Hey! Who are you?
-Get lost!
Get out of here!
-Stop it!
-What did you do to her?
-What's the matter with you?
-MITCH: Get out of here.
Hey, some education
you're giving her, Doctor.
-How are you going to
explain this to her now?
-Stop it!
Stop it. Both of you.
(PANTING)
-David was nice.
-Mmm-hmm.
He made me feel good.
I liked him.
And... And it's natural
to feel that way.
But some men are gonna
come on to you
when you're just
being friendly.
What's coming on?
They're gonna say
nice things to you. They're...
They're gonna kiss you.
-I like kissing.
-(CHUCKLES)
That's fine.
But not everybody is
as nice as you are.
So you have to know
how to say, "No."
I know how to say, "No."
(SIGHS)
-Mitch?
-Yes?
It's okay to like
some people, isn't it?
When you find the right
person, it's okay to have
all the feelings you want.
When you find somebody
who really cares for you,
who you really trust.
You save those feelings
for that person.
And you'll know in here.
-Then it's okay?
-Then it's okay. (LAUGHS)
Mitch...
I...
Trust you.
(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
She really gets into things,
doesn't she?
Can't we just buy her
the brochure?
(LOUDLY) Now I know
why you love it.
(LAUGHING)
(SIGHS)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
Dina?
What's this?
Poetry.
"Look at me
"In life we sing
a strange duet
"The adult
and the child within
"And holding hands
"the two have met
"They know where
they have been
"But if they never look at sky
"Sun dancing on golden beams
"Then inside
they'll surely die
"as though they've never been
"Look at me"
Did you write this?
It's a gift.
Well, uh...
I'm... I'm very proud of you.
The end of World War II began
with the splitting
of the atom and a series
of atomic explosions.
-The first was
July 16th, 1945 at...
-Good!
Shakespeare, Hamlet,
Act One, Scene Three,
line 78...
"This above all,
to thine own self be true.
"And it must follow,
as the night the day.
"Thou canst not then
be false to any man."
Physics. Who was Max Planck?
The Nobel Prize winning
German physicist,
born 1858, died 1947,
who said,
"Over the entrance
to the temple of science
"are written the words,
'Ye must have faith.'"
Can you, uh, explain to me
the functions of microchips?
What type?
Central processing chips?
-ROM? RAM? What?
-Wait a minute. Whoa.
Where did you learn
these things?
-Those books.
-Those books?
-I read them.
-Isn't she something?
Where is this going to end?
At the fundraiser.
We won't just introduce her.
We'll have her give a speech.
We'll have her
answer questions.
She'll be the presentation.
That's a lot to expect
from her.
-I don't think so.
-I think it'd be great.
You can't expect her to
perform like a trained seal.
DINA: Wait a minute!
Isn't anyone gonna ask me?
I can do it.
One and two and three and four
and one and two
and three and...
(SYMPHONY PLAYING)
(SIGHS)
Just Dina.
-She's up again.
-Mmm.
(SYMPHONIC MUSIC
CONTINUES PLAYING)
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
(CHUCKLES)
Dina! It's two o'clock
in the morning.
Oh! I'm sorry!
I... I couldn't sleep.
Music...
Music relaxes me.
You need to get some rest.
Try... Try a little warm milk.
-Good night.
We were in bed, Dina.
We were trying to sleep.
If you're gonna be up, study.
You're a little behind
with your physics.
I am studying.
I'm teaching myself
music composition.
Well, study something quieter,
like physics.
(SCREECHING)
(OBJECTS CLANKING)
(OBJECTS CLATTERING)
(SCREECHING)
(GRUNTING EXCITEDLY)
-Mitch...
-Did Dina get to bed
last night?
-Who knows.
-I don't know if she's getting
enough rest
-ever since we talked to her
about the presentation.
-Mitch...
She seems so keyed up.
Dina! Dina! That's all you
ever talk about anymore.
-Wait a minute. Wait...
-You wait a minute.
You better keep your eye
on the ball. It's the project
that's important here.
-You're getting
too personally involved.
-What?
What are talking about?
We have a lot invested here.
A little too much,
if you ask me.
What does that mean?
-What's going on there, Mitch?
-Going on?
-Nothing's going on.
-I call that classic denial.
Well, I call that
a cheap shot.
-You're invited to a party.
-What?
Saturday night, eight o'clock.
It's your birthday.
Jeanette told me.
-Can I bring Andy?
-Sure.
It's formal.
Can you teach me
how to do that?
(WOMAN ANNOUNCING ON P.A.)
(SIGHS)
-What the hell?
-Oh, my God.
-(CHIMPANZEES SCREECHING)
-Are you okay?
-No. This... This is...
Are they okay?
-Yeah, I think so.
(CHIMPANZEES SCREECHING)
-What happened?
-I don't know, vandals.
Maybe teenagers?
-Someone looking for drugs?
-I better call security.
No, uh, let me do it.
You better start
Dina's lessons.
You don't want to worry her.
-If only they could talk.
-Security?
This is Dr. Ryan.
We've had a break in. Mmm-hmm.
What's the matter with you?
Are you having
trouble sleeping?
What are you doing in here?
I was just
thinking about the party,
and I... I was just
-pretending.
-I don't care.
These are my things.
You didn't ask permission.
Get out.
(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
JEANETTE: Dr. Ryan, would you
like an hors d'oeuvre?
Oh, no. Thank you, Jeanette.
But they look delicious.
-Are you all right?
-Yes.
I just want to be hungry.
I know what's coming.
All right. All right.
So, I give up...
So, how many scientists
does it take
to screw in a light bulb?
(CHUCKLES) Four.
One to screw in the bulb,
one to write the report,
and two to apply
for the grant.
(BOTH MEN LAUGHING)
(SOFTLY) Dina.
You look beautiful.
Thank you, Andy.
DR. SWAN: Dina, look at you!
Hello.
DR. SWAN: Very elegant.
DINA: Andy spoiled me.
MITCH: Well,
you're worth it.
DR. SWAN: You're 90 years old,
minus a day.
-(ALL LAUGHING)
-MITCH: This is great!
JEANETTE: Thank you, sir.
The meal is
wonderful, Jeanette.
Well, we wanted the best
-for Dr. Conlon's birthday.
-Yes.
DR. SWAN: Dr. Conlon is
a lucky man.
Very lucky.
I'm going to get
the birthday cake ready.
All right.
Interesting new report
on the link between DNA
and the tanning process.
-MAN: Really?
-Oh, what's that?
LINDA: Boston University
reports that
a so-called healthy tan
is actually strong evidence
that the DNA in the skin
is been severely damaged.
(SCOFFS) We already knew that.
Yes, but the report states
that the tan
is actually the result
of damaged DNA.
No, that's not exactly right.
The tanning process
is actually triggered
when the body begins
repairing the DNA damaged
by ultraviolet radiation.
-Oh, really?
-Well...
(SCOFFS)
Actually it is a series...
The repair process initiates
the production of melanin
and a small DNA fragment
called dipyrimidine
dithymidylic acid
can actually cause
the damage...
Isn't it fascinating
how our little project here
has graduated from
monosyllables
to scientific prose.
-Linda.
-Linda, I only meant...
LINDA: And what an education
for our honored guests,
who undoubtedly came
from universities all
over the world
to study at the knee
of a coffee clerk.
You are way out of line.
How the hell would you know.
I think you owe Dina
an apology.
I don't think so.
(SIGHS DEEPLY)
Excuse me for a minute.
(SOFTLY) Excuse me.
What's going on, Mitch?
Dina.
You've gotta move back home.
Now, you can go to
the Institute during the
day for your injections.
No, Andy. I'm staying.
Dina,
this is not good for you.
I'll be fine.
How could you talk
to me like that in front
of our guests?
It was hard not to.
Hanging on her every word.
I enjoyed her enthusiasm.
Seeing things the way
she sees them with...
You're acting like
a smitten school boy, not
a scientist. It's ridiculous.
-I'm proud of her.
-Proud?
I've seen you look at her
in ways I've only
dreamed about.
I don't think
you even realize it.
I am looking at who she is!
What she is. She's just there,
no strings.
Pure and simple.
Do you hear
what you're saying?
I have never, ever, ever
known that before.
Not with you,
not with my colleagues,
and certainly,
certainly never
with my father.
-(ZIPPING)
-I need some time to think.
Oh, really?
And you better
sort things out too.
What does that mean?
It means I'm leaving.
(SIGHS) Are you in love
with her mind?
Is that what it is?
Anybody can be a genius.
We've proven that, haven't we?
Just add our formula and stir.
(CLOCK CHIMING)
DINA: Mitch...
I...
I, uh,
got some milk.
I...
Love you.
So...
I know
in here.
(DOOR SHUTS)
(WHISPERS) I love you too.
-Oh!
-(SHRIEKING)
How did you get out?
I changed the combination.
(SHRIEKING)
What's the matter
with you two?
Hey! Come here. Come here!
(CONTINUES SHRIEKING)
Hey!
Stop it! Come here!
Come on, yeah.
That's a good girl.
Come here.
That's it, come on. That's it.
Come on, yeah. Stay!
-(MONKEY PANTING)
-(SIGHS)
You aren't sleeping. Why?
(SHRIEKING)
Damn, you picked a fine
time to have a reaction.
I have to take you off
the formula.
Linda.
I'm sorry.
Seven cc's. Reaction...
"None."
Leonard,
if you lowered the temperature
and added a 17% solution of
beta-Mercaptoethanol...
It's fine. Study.
Or better yet,
first extract the DNA with,
uh, a phenol chloroform.
-It's fine. (SIGHS)
-You'd get a better yield.
With the DNA isolation,
you get less digestion.
Dina.
I've done this 1,000 times.
DINA: I just read it
yesterday in
volume 11, page 139.
-Let me do my job.
-One second.
Never mind. I'm finished.
It's late. I'm going home.
You should too.
I can't.
I have some studying to do.
Get some rest.
Here it is. Leonard!
TEACHER: (ON TAPE)
Where is the library?
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
TEACHER: The library is there.
Come on, come on.
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
-Are you going there now?
-(SPEAKING FRENCH)
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
-Yes, I have to look
for a book.
-DINA: Oui.
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
Come on. (SIGHS)
Merde.
(TAPE REWINDING)
(VOICE DISTORTING)
(SIGHS)
Damn.
(MONKEY VOCALIZING SOFTLY)
MAN: (CHANTING)
What's at stake?
Join us.
-Come on, join us.
-ALL: What's at stake?
What's at stake?
What's at stake? Dina Blake.
You look tired.
Can't stop studying.
You should slow down a little.
Can't. Just not enough
hours in the day.
You need to relax.
Don't have the time.
The fundraiser's coming up.
What fundraiser?
I have to make a speech and
raise money.
No, they've got you
on a treadmill.
No, they need me.
You're proof
their experiment worked.
They're using you.
No, they're not.
I have to be prepared.
That's all.
ALL: Dina! Dina! Dina!
Come see our dance!
-I really don't...
-We copied it off
a music video.
-Not right now, all right?
-Can we show you?
No! I'm talking to Andy.
Sorry.
Let's go.
Come on, guys.
That's not like you.
Don't lecture me.
-You came here to talk.
You don't want to listen?
-Andy drop it.
No, you can't even see it,
can you?
-You and Svengali,
so high and mighty...
-Don't criticize Mitch.
They gave you a brain.
You're not using it.
I'm going back
to the Institute.
ANDY: You even know
why you're doing this?
DINA: I'm doing it
because I love it.
You're doing it
because you love him!
(SIGHS)
I'm doing it because
I'm ambitious,
something you wouldn't
understand.
(SYMPHONY PLAYING)
My, my, my. There's just
no end to your talent,
is there?
You scared me.
The Van Gogh?
It's Mitch's favorite.
And a heart of gold, too.
You're just too good
to be true.
Let me give you
a little word of advice.
I wouldn't be wasting my time
on painting if I were you.
I'd be planning
for my future.
What does that mean?
You're so naive.
You think you just took
the world by storm,
don't you?
You're only a clinical
curiosity, honey.
Mitch doesn't really care
about you.
He's created you in his
own image.
He's in love with himself.
Just perform your little
tricks at the presentation.
That's all we need from you.
Let Mitch show you off.
Then you can go back
to your little world.
I thought you should see this.
It's from Decauer
and some of the others.
They're concerned about Dina.
She's edgy,
she's over-tired...
Ah, well, everybody's edgy.
We all are before
the presentation.
-It's... It's normal.
-No.
Don't explain this away.
Dina looks to you
for approval,
for reassurance,
for her identity.
She'll do anything for you.
Let her leave and get on
with her life.
I'll talk to her.
After the presentation.
This isn't about winning
prizes anymore.
(SIGHS)
LINDA: Hang in there, girls.
Just for a few more days.
Then the fundraiser
will be over.
They'll renew our grant,
and Dina can go away.
(MUSIC PLAYING)
(SIGHS)
(MONKEY SHRIEKING)
MAN: Ladies and gentlemen,
it is with great pleasure
that I introduce to you
our hosts for this evening,
Dr. Mitch Conlon
and Dr. Linda Ryan.
(CROWD APPLAUDING)
Good evening,
ladies and gentlemen.
On behalf of
the Conlon Institute,
I would like to welcome you
and thank you
for your continuing
and enthusiastic support
of our work here.
Mitch, why are you hiding?
-(AUDIENCE LAUGHING)
-I want you at my side
where you belong.
As the annual report
tells you, it has
been an exciting
and promising year.
Mitch.
Our presentation this year
holds considerable
significance.
We've made some
groundbreaking discoveries,
we've pioneered some
exciting new applications,
but of course, we couldn't
have done it alone.
-(CHIMPS CHATTERING)
-Linda, would you bring
them out here.
-(CHIMP SCREECHING)
-You're next.
(AUDIENCE APPLAUDING
AND CHEERING)
This is Laverne and Shirley.
(AUDIENCE LAUGHING)
As members of the species
evolutionarily closest
to humans,
they share 98% of our genes.
Their contribution to our
research has been invaluable.
As result of our work
with them,
a very special person
represents the Conlon
Institute tonight.
Good luck.
Ladies and gentlemen,
Miss Dina Blake.
-(AUDIENCE APPLAUDING)
-(SIGHS)
Well, girls, it's past
your bedtime
-(CHIMPS SHRIEKING)
-(AUDIENCE LAUGHING)
When we first met Dina,
she was far from the person
that we see here tonight.
Her mental capacity
was that of a kindergartner.
We put Dina
on the same formula schedule
as our chimps
and then we instituted
the same learning regimen
to see if she could achieve
the same level
of cognitive function.
MITCH: She did, and then some.
At our last evaluation,
Dina's IQ was placed at 172.
She's a genius.
Ladies and gentlemen,
Miss Dina Blake.
(CROWD APPLAUDING)
Who would have believed
it possible?
Take a strand of DNA,
a genetic messenger
that is tissue-specific,
and tell it to
go to the brain,
and it does.
It breaks through the barrier
between the brain
and the blood system,
something that has never been
done before, by the way.
These brilliant scientists
who stand before you,
-asking for your dollars
and cents, I might add...
-(CROWD LAUGHING)
...have made history.
They've reached
into the brain cell itself
and they transformed it,
and they created
me.
The ramifications for
the future of genetic therapy
are staggering.
Once, I lived in a world
where I couldn't express
how I felt,
but I did.
Look.
And when they found me,
I knew I wanted something,
but
don't we all?
Isn't that natural?
Don't...
I'm your right-hand girl.
Mitch?
Let me do it again, okay?
Yes.
It's Dina.
Dina!
(SOFTLY) Andy!
(CROWD MURMURING)
Dina.
(SHOUTING)
Why did Dina Blake collapse?
Was their irresponsible
behavior on the part
of the institute?
REPORTER:
Was Dina's health jeopardized?
-A press conference is being
scheduled. No comment.
What's Dina's future now?
Is she gonna be all right?
JEANETTE: Good day, Dr. Swan.
Dr. Conlon is upstairs.
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
How is she?
She's sleeping.
When you tread
on moral grounds,
you get your shoes dirty.
Your father never told you
that, did he?
-(KNOCK ON DOOR)
-(DOOR OPENING)
Hey.
Feel like some company?
Yours.
Oh.
-I'm sorry.
-No, no problem.
I'm just glad you're okay.
-I never meant...
-Shh. No.
I'm sorry too.
I was scared.
Not just for you,
for me.
I was afraid
you wouldn't need me anymore.
Oh, Andy.
Oh, wait a second.
What?
Voila.
You always liked
having breakfast at night.
Scrambled eggs.
(CHUCKLING)
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
Yes.
We had no right to put
so much pressure on you.
Things have happened
that I didn't expect,
reactions we couldn't
have predicted.
Yes.
For me too.
Mitch,
kiss me.
Please.
I need to get some air.
(EXHALING)
Well, I guess we
owe you an apology too.
Here.
What's wrong?
Are you not hungry?
Huh? (CHUCKLES)
What's wrong with you guys?
"Two cc's placebo.
No formula."
What the hell?
What's going on here?
They were having
secondary reactions.
I think the formula invaded
the limbic system,
threw off their body clocks.
It's like they
were burning out.
Burning out?
They weren't sleeping.
They hated the dark.
Light stimulated them.
One became passive,
the other aggressive.
So I took them
off the formula.
They're in withdrawl.
They'll be fine.
How could you possibly
keep this a secret?
I kept it a secret to
get us through
the presentation.
The presentation?
What about Dina?
You put her life in danger!
How could you do that?
I took her off
the formula too.
That may be why she fainted.
We are talking
about a human life!
You're a scientist
for God's sake!
What about your
code of ethics?
Oh, I could ask you
the same question.
She trusted you!
She trusted me!
I trusted you too.
"Ye must have faith."
I did!
In you!
I thought I could have it all.
The Conlon name,
the recognition
for our good work.
That's how I saw it!
I thought you did too.
But you are never
gonna be your father.
I didn't have to be.
You were.
I never meant to hurt her.
Linda.
What about her prognosis?
You'll know in six months.
Where are you going?
I am a scientist.
When one experiment ends,
I look for another.
My father used to say to me,
"The end is all,
"no matter the cost."
And this institute
was built on
that very precept.
I never questioned it.
Not until recently.
My father was wrong.
Science is a two-sided coin.
It can be good
or bad.
The progress that
man has made
in research
has unleashed
an awesome power.
It has given him
the insight into the miracle
of creation itself.
The scientist must recognize
the responsibility in that.
He holds human life
in palm of his hand.
The scientist has been given
the power to play God.
If he chooses to play God,
then he must
have his conscience.
DINA: Goodbye.
I once stood
across the street,
looking back at the Institute
And I realized
what I had gained.
And what it had cost.
You created me.
Now I have to find me.
LINDA: I need time.
Don't leave.
You gave me a gift.
If I stay,
it would be like
giving it back.
Don't make me give it back.
You haven't asked me
what will happen to you.
No.
I'll be fine.
No matter what.
I love you.
LINDA: "And the beautiful,
multi-colored butterfly
broke free and flew away,
"catching the sunlight in
the many colors of its wings.
"And the people gasped
at its beauty."
(CHILDREN EXCLAIMING HAPPILY)
So, what does that story mean?
(ALL CLAMORING)
LINDA: Okay, Leanne?
That there's beauty
in all of us?
If we look for it,
there's beauty in all of us.
Let's go!
-(ENGINE STARTS)
-(CHILDREN LAUGH)
GIRL: Let's do Dina.
ALL: * Dina, Dina bo bina
Banana fana fo fina
* Fee fy mo mina
Dina *
(CHILDREN LAUGHING)
* Dina, Dina bo bina
Banana fana fo fina
* Fee fy mo mina
Dina *