[water running]
[water running continues]
♪♪ [humming]
[burbling]
[gargling]
[snarls]
♪♪ [whistling]
- [water stops]
- [man sighs]
♪♪ [whistling]
[man snoring]
[coughing]
Hey. Good morning, bro.
It’s 3:00
in the afternoon.
Weren’t you gonna look
for an apartment today?
[coughing]
Okay. I will. I will.
I just cleaned this.
God! You weren’t
such a pain in the ass
when we were kids.
Why are you all dressed up?
I have a date.
You have a date?
What, the one
I fixed you up with?
From the Internet?
Yep. And if she is
as great as she seems,
I might even forgive you
for posting that ad.
Uh, Todd, you never did
exchange pictures, huh?
Nope. It’s just
a coffee date.
Besides, she says she’s
above average in appearance.
"Above average."
I-- I warned you about
Internet inflation, right?
Inflation?
If they say "average,"
that means homely.
Now "V.G.L."--
very good looking--
that means average.
What about people
that really are V.G.L.?
Well, good luck finding them
on the Internet.
[coughing]
- Good luck.
- [door closes]
Hi.
Uh, I was wondering,
are you--
- What? Watch it.
- Sorry.
- I thought
you were this guy.
- No. No.
Well, okay.
[chuckles]
You’re not my type anyway.
Oh, um--
Sorry, this is my table.
You don’t have a drink
or anything.
Okay. This is ridiculous.
You can’t just steal
another person’s table.
You’re not gonna make
a scene, are you?
You people are so dramatic.
"You people"?
[scoffs]
And by "you people"
do you mean gay people
or Latino people
or specifically
gay Latino people?
Look, I apologize.
That came out wrong.
I’m really sorry.
Uh, how about--
- We’re both waiting
for someone, right?
- Yeah.
Whosever date shows up first
gets the table?
All right.
That sounds fair.
Well, scoot over.
There’s no chair.
[chuckles]
- Does that bother you?
- No. No, of course not.
Mmm!
Do you want me
to get a chair?
Would you?
Thank you.
[exhales]
- Hey, hon.
- Hey.
Nice catch.
I’m not a catch.
Oh, and modest, too.
We like that.
Actually, he’s not
my date, Marco. He’s--
- Straight. Totally straight.
I’m straight.
- Straight.
Mm-hmm. So was
my last boyfriend.
He went straight
to the next man, honey.
[laughing]
[whispering]
That must be her.
- You’re dating a lesbian?
- She’s not a lesbian.
- Hi, hon.
- Hey.
- How are ya?
- Great.
[Marco]
Hey, what can I get
for you ladies?
[woman]
Uh, I’ll have
a double cappuccino.
[chuckling]
How can you be so sure?
Oh, gaydar.
You know, straight people
can develop gaydar if they
spend enough time with queers.
I’m guessing you haven’t
done a lot of that.
No, I know some qu--
gay people--
some of the other
programmers at work.
But you hang out with
the straight boys, right?
Not really.
Most of them are techno-geeks.
All they know is
what’s in front of them
on their computer screen.
They even watch movies
on a computer screen.
How can you watch a movie
on a computer screen?
You need to watch it
on a big screen, you know?
Wait. You’re a movie buff?
Totally.
I’m a bit of a fanatic.
Me, too.
I mean, major fanatic.
- Really?
- Yeah. Who’s your
favorite director?
- Milos Forman.
- Oh.
- Mostly for Amadeus.
- Amadeus?
You’re crazy. I mean,
if we’re talking Forman,
what about
People vs. Larry Flynt?
or Cuckoo’s Nest?
- That’s a classic.
- Cuckoo’s Nest is, yes,
but Flynt?
Nah, it’s not even in
the same league as Amadeus.
Amadeus has the costumes,
the music, the performances.
Are you sure
you’re not gay?
[scoffs]
I’m positive.
Oh, my God.˯
You think
that’s your date?
Of course not.
I’m-- I’m not delusional.
But, God.
He’s beautiful.
Yeah? I--
I don’t like that.
Too groomed and pretty.
You’re telling me
you wouldn’t wanna look
like that if you could?
Never.
Okay. All right.
What’s your ideal body type?
You’re looking at it,
my friend.
No, seriously.
- All right.
- [chuckles]
Uh, all right, that guy.
See? He looks like a man.
Ah, yes. Muscle boy.
I can see that.
- He is hot, isn’t he?
- I’m not saying
I’m attracted to him.
I’m just saying, you know,
objectively speaking,
he’s masculine.
I mean, not that
I like masculine.
Okay, okay. Yeah.
Spare me the homosexual panic.
I mean, even if you were
attracted to him, so what?
I mean, I thought
that lesbian you were
trying to pick up was sexy.
That doesn’t mean
I’m straight.
I didn’t know gay guys ever
felt that way about women.
Well, some don’t.
I mean, it’s not like
we come off some assembly line
in Taiwan, you know.
[chuckles]
[sighs]
You know, I, uh--
I think my best friend
in junior high
might have been gay.
Really?
- Yeah.
- You guys ever fool around?
Would you--
Why would you say that?
I’m not gay.
No. It has nothin’ to do
with gay or straight.
All kids fool around
if they get half a chance.
All right.
Define fooling around.
You did, didn’t you?
Nothing serious.
We were 11.
We were curious.
Okay. I mean, I’d ask
for all the gory details,
but this is obviously
making you uncomfortable.
A little bit, but mostly
I gotta take a leak.
So go.
Oh, please.
Please get over yourself.
Nobody’s gonna jump you.
[fly unzips]
[urinating]
[urinal flushes]
[water running]
[urinating]
Oh, hey.
Um, table opened up.
I-- I thought
I’d better grab it.
- Oh.
- I mean, you’re more
than welcome to join me.
I’m enjoying the company.
I just thought you might
want your own table.
Once my date shows up.
- Okay.
- Looks like it’s
thinnin’ out anyway.
- Yeah, right?
- [clears throat]
[both chuckle]
So how long are you supposed
to wait for somebody on one
of these coffee dates anyway?
Why are you askin’ me?
I’m no expert.
I guess I just assumed
you’d done your share of these.
Oh, you think because
I’m gay, I can’t sustain
a serious relationship?
You think I’m out
every night partying
and screwing my brains out?
Whoa. I not trying
to be offensive.
Remember what I was saying
before about being dramatic?
Oh.
[chuckles]
- I guess I kind of have been
on a dating rampage lately.
- Oh.
But before that,
I was in a monogamous
relationship for five years.
At least
I was monogamous.
- Ouch.
- Yeah.
I know that story.
I was married once,
although we sure as hell
didn’t make it any five years.
Technically, it was two,
but that’s only because
the divorce took six months.
Oh. Sounds ugly.
Yeah. I was a total wreck.
I’m just now
pulling out of it.
So, are you looking to score
with your date tonight?
I mean, assuming
she ever shows up.
Or are you looking for something
a little more substantial?
Substantial--
that’s a good word.
Yeah. I guess that’s
what I’m lookin’ for.
Me, too.
I mean, I don’t know.
Maybe I’m getting old,
but sex just isn’t the big deal
it was in my twenties.
Don’t get me wrong.
I’m still a big fan.
It’s just, there are times
when I’d gladly
trade in a good fuck for
a little decent conversation.
I know what you mean.
I did the whole singles bar,
one-night stand thing,
but after a while,
I just got so bored.
Some of the women I took home
actually seemed to be offended
- when I just wanted
to talk to them.
- Like about movies.
Exactly.
This one woman--
she had her clothes off
before I could shut the door.
And she’s staring at this poster
I have of Amadeus,
so I say, "Do you
like Milos Forman?"
And she says, "Well, I’ll try
anything, but usually
I like to be on top."
[laughing]
I hope my date turns out
to be half as entertaining.
To tell you the truth,
I’m kind of nervous
about meeting him.
We really seemed to connect.
I mean, granted,
it was only through e-mail.
But I don’t know.
He seemed special.
Did you exchange pictures?
No. I mean,
I didn’t want it
to be about that.
I mean, I know
it sounds corny, but we
actually talked about
life, people, ideas.
He’s very funny
and bright.
And unlike most people
on the Internet, he can actually
write and punctuate
a coherent sentence.
And plus, he’s
another movie nut.
What’s his name?
His name is Todd.
Oh, my God.
[laughing]
You’re Kelly, aren’t you?
Yeah. Hi.
- [laughing]
- Jesus.
Goddamn it.
My brother did this.
He posted the ad.
In the men-seeking-men
section?
He’s probably laughing
his ass off right now.
What a son of a--
What a prick.
Well, I guess
you won’t be meeting people
through the Internet anymore.
I don’t know. I mean, other
than you being the wrong gender,
you seem great.
And you didn’t even inflate.
Excuse me?
I mean, you were honest
about your appearance.
You are above average.
Oh.
Thank you.
That’s very sweet.
Listen, since you are
technically my date,
can I buy you
a cup of coffee?
Oh. Thanks.
That’d be nice.
- Black, no sugar, right?
- [chuckles]
Uh, low-fat latte
with whipped cream
and chocolate shavings.
Very good.
I’ll be back.
Okay.
Kelly.
Yeah?
There’s an Ingmar Bergman
double feature playing tonight
at the New Beverly.
I’m not asking you out
like a date kind of thing.
I really just don’t know anyone
else who might enjoy Bergman.
[woman on TV]
Oh, yeah! Oh, my God!
[moaning]
[door opens]
[TV switches off]
Bedroom’s this way.
[chuckling]
[laughs]
[Todd moans]
[Kelly]
Oh, it feels good!
[sniffles]
Morning.
What-- What are you
doin’ up?
Where’s your, uh--
[whispering]
Where’s your friend?
He left.
Listen, about last night--
I’m your brother,
and I love you, but...
yeah, I can’t
stay here anymore.
- Uh, no offense.
- You’re leaving?
Yeah, I-- I gotta go.
I’m sorry.
No, no, no, no, no.
That-- That’s okay.
I understand.
I wouldn’t want my lifestyle
to make you uncomfortable.
I’ll give you a call
in a couple days
and let you know
where I end up.
Okay, well...
- good luck.
- Yeah.
- So, take care of yourself.
- You, too.
No. I mean,
take care of yourself.
I don’t want you
getting the-- you know.
Nothing to worry about.
I promise.
Good.
I’ll, uh, catch you later.
Yeah.
Yes. Thank you.
[door closes]
[quiet chatter]
Hi, Todd.
Ask her out.
She’s not datin’
that jerk anymore.
She’s not
interested.
She’s available.
Besides, we work together.
It’d be awkward.
Well, suit yourself.
- Hello?
- [Todd]
Kelly.
- Hey.
- Listen.
That little joke we played paid
off better than I’d imagined.
My brother was so freaked,
he actually moved out.
Can you believe it?
Free at last.
Thank God almighty,
you’re free at last.
- Amen.
- Well, good.
I’m glad I didn’t
disfigure myself for nothing.
I scratched my hand
climbing out your window.
- Oh, I’m sorry.
- Oh, I’ll pull through.
Hey, listen. You wanna
catch a movie tonight?
I can’t pronounce it--
that German film that made
such a splash at Sundance.
Yes. I’ve been
dying to see that.
Jesus. You scared
the hell out of me.
I’m not staying.
I just-- I forgot
a couple of things.
- Yeah. A couple of my things.
- Oh, but I get so thirsty.
Oh, the toaster?
I need you to pick up Mom
at the airport.
She gets in around midnight.
Here’s all her flight info.
What are you talking about?
Mom doesn’t fly.
Well, she does now.
I had to tell her, bro.
She’s your mom.
She has a right to know.
Barry, you jerk!
I am not gay!
I was just
yanking your chain.
Please.
You are gay. Look at you.
Look at the way you dress.
Look how you decorated
your apartment.
Look at those light bulbs.
That’s a gay light bulb.
- The sconces?
- See?
I wouldn’t know that ordinarily,
but my friend is a decorator.
- Oh.
- It’s a girl.
- Ready to go, handsome?
Oh, hello.
Oh.
Wow. I gotta go.
Don’t forget about Mom.
- Barry--
- Bye.
He’s cute.
Are we having toast?
Ooh, whiskey.
Fantastic.
[laughing]
It’s not funny.
I’m sorry.
I’m sorry. It’s just--
[laughing]
- It’s not funny.
- It’s hysterical.
No. You don’t
know my mom.
I mean, when she gets
an idea in her head,
she’s like a Chihuahua
with a chew toy.
Look, once you explain,
she’ll understand,
and you’ll have
a nice relaxing visit.
The only way this is gonna be
a relaxing visit is if she
stays somewhere else.
- I don’t suppose you have
a guest room?
- Uh, no.
And I don’t think staying
at my place is gonna convince
her of your heterosexuality.
Good point.
It was great, wasn’t it?
Brilliant.
So, do we have time
to grab some coffee,
or do you need
to go get your mom?
Yeah, I should go.
If I’m not there when
she gets off the plane,
she’ll take a cab
and then spend
the rest of her visit talking
about how much it cost.
[chuckles]
Sounds like my mother.
Are you sure she’s not Latina?
[chuckles]
I think it’s a mom thing.
It transcends race,
creed and color.
[chuckles]
Well, thanks for
going out with me tonight.
I had a good time.
Okay, but we didn’t go out,
you know. We went out.
Well, we came out.
We didn’t come out.
We-- We physically went
to the movies together.
- But not together.
You know, just--
- [laughs]
Wow. And we almost
made it through the evening
without a gay panic moment.
I’m sorry.
In fact, I’m sorry
about the whole night.
I feel like I spent
the entire time
complaining about my mother.
I don’t mind listening.
That’s what friends are for.
I guess I don’t have
a lot of friends.
Cheryl and I had
couple-friends,
but she seems to have gotten
custody of most of them.
Right. It’s hard
meeting people in L.A.
Well, thanks for listening.
You’re a good guy.
I’m a great guy.
- It’s too bad
it’s wasted on you.
- [chuckles]
Yeah? Well, I’m still
trying to get over the fact
that you’re not a woman.
I think I was
half in love with you.
I mean, with the woman
I thought you were.
Really?
You give great e-mail.
Stop.
You’re gonna
make me cry.
Okay. Time to go.
[laughs]
Quit being so straight.
A hug is not
going to kill you.
Okay.
Oh, that’s very nice.
- Good night.
- Good night...
sweetie.
Oh, honey!
[crying]
Oh, baby.
Mom, I’m fine.
Everything’s fine.
Oh, of course you’re fine.
I just wish you’d
told me sooner.
That’s just it.
There’s nothing to tell.
It was just a misunderstanding.
I’m not gay.
You don’t have to hide anymore.
Your brother told me everything.
Mom, I was just playing
a joke on him.
Remember?
Like when we were kids?
Well, I remember when I caught
you with that Robert naked,
and I-- I tried to tell myself
nothing was going on
and all little boys
are curious.
Nothing was going on.
All little boys are curious.
Yeah, well, your father warned
me that I coddled you too much.
- Do you think that was it?
- Mom, you did not coddle me.
Right, right.
So it’s just genetics.
That’s what
everyone is saying.
I mean, that no one blames
the mother anymore.
There’s nothing for you
to be blamed for, Mom.
Right, because
being gay is okay.
Really, nobody is to be
blamed for anything.
Although I do wish
that your father,
God rest his soul,
could have turned off
the television for five minutes
and played with his son!
Mom, you are not listening.
Okay?
Let’s go
to the baggage carousel.
I have two large bags.
How long are you
planning to stay?
For as long
as you need me, honey.
Okay.
All right.
Mother, about this
whole misunderstanding--
- [snoring]
- Oh, my God.
- [phone rings]
- [Todd’s voice] Frankly,
my dear, I don’t give a damn
if you leave a message.
[beeps]
Hey, Mom.
Are you there? Pick up.
Okay, well,
I’m gonna try to get off work
early so we can talk.
Honey? Todd?
This is Mrs. Orsini.
She has a boy like you.
A programmer?
You don’t have to
pretend with me, Todd.
Mrs. Orsini is the head
of the Los Angeles PFLAG--
Parents and Friends
for Lesbians and Gays.
She and her husband marched
in this year’s parade.
We march every year.
Did you march, Todd?
Could you excuse us
for a moment? Mother,
I’d like to talk to you.
What are you doing
bringing her? I told you I was
gonna explain everything later.
I just thought it would be
helpful to have someone here
who’s been through it before.
She hasn’t been through
this before. Trust me.
Todd, please don’t be
upset with your mother.
Now, this is a very
hard time for her.
She’s really
trying to understand
and support you.
I appreciate that,
and I’m sure PFLAG is
a wonderful organization--
Honey, maybe I didn’t
see the signs.
- Maybe Cheryl
turned you against women.
- I have nothing against women.
Ever since Cheryl, there’s
been no one special in his life.
He hardly dates anyone anymore.
I date.
I just don’t necessarily
tell you about it.
That’s very common among
closeted men who are
just coming to terms
with their sexuality
in mid-life.
I’m not clo--
What do you mean "mid-life"?
You’re 35, honey.
I mean, the life span
of the average American male--
All right, whatever!
I am not gay,
closeted or otherwise.
It’s best not
to force the issue.
Wait till he wants
to talk about it
and comes to you.
I am talking about it.
I’m just not gay.
- Feel free to come to our
meetings while you’re in town.
- Oh, thank you.
And I will contact you
with the information
for your local chapter.
Oh, that’s very helpful.
Thank you so much,
Mrs. Orsini.
Oh, well,
I remember how hard it was
for my son and me.
Good luck.
- Good afternoon.
- Good afternoon, Mrs. Donovan.
I just want to tell you, you
have nothing to be ashamed of.
My nephew’s gay.
What?
I said my nephew is gay.
Shh!
You know,
you should meet him.
Honey, he’s a dentist.
No, thanks.
Oh, right.
You’re seeing somebody.
Oh, well,
I hope it works out.
But if it doesn’t,
my nephew is very sweet.
Is there something
I can help you with?
Yeah.
Uh, I’m looking for Kelly.
Does he work here?
He owns the place.
Do you have
an appointment?
No, I’m, uh--
I guess I’m a friend.
You guess?
Could you just
tell him Todd’s here?
- Yeah.
- Thanks.
What are you doing here?
[gasping]
Man-scaping? Quick trim?
Massage?
- Brazilian wax?
- You have to talk to my mother.
[gasps]
So soon? Are we asking
for her blessing?
This isn’t funny.
Nothing I say seems to
convince her that I’m not gay.
And you think talking to me
is gonna help?
Maybe if you explained
what happened,
she’d see the whole thing
was a joke.
All right.
Sure. I’ll try.
- Really?
- Yeah. Why not?
Can you come by
tonight after work?
Well, I was
going out, but--
All right.
If it’s that important
to you, I’ll be there.
Thanks.
You’re a pal.
You’re welcome.
[chuckles]
- I’ll see you tonight.
- Okay.
I’m just gonna take this.
Oh. Okay.
Hey, Bonnie.
Hey, baby.
You know,
that is so funny.
I was just sitting here
wishing there was
a half-naked man in the room.
You think about sex more than
any woman I have ever known.
- You know I’m a gay man trapped
in a straight woman’s body.
- [laughs]
Why the mad rush?
Got a hot date?
I told Todd
that I would help him
with a little problem
he’s having with his mother.
Todd?
Yes.
Excuse me?
Todd, the straight guy?
Yes.
- So, what,
are you dating him now?
- No.
You know I don’t
go after straight guys.
- Mm-hmm.
- I don’t.
- Shut up.
So, what, you don’t find him
the least bit attractive?
I didn’t say that.
And that’s beside
the point.
- Oh, what is the point?
- The point is that I can have
friends I don’t sleep with.
I have you, don’t I?
Yeah, you had me,
remember?
That was 10 years ago,
and you took advantage of me.
And I still
let you be my friend.
So my point still holds.
Well, my point is that I don’t
want to see you get hurt.
Bonnie, I’m a big boy,
okay?
I’m not gonna fall for him.
What do you think?
Hat? No hat?
I think you’re a freak.
What the hell is that?
- [laughs]
Shut up. I love you.
- Love you.
- Don’t wait up.
- I won’t.
Don’t get drunk.
[scoffs]
That’s boring.
Men.
I’m not ready
to meet your boyfriend.
Mom, the whole reason
he’s coming over
is to establish
he’s not my boyfriend.
Of course, I would meet
anybody that you care about.
Really, I would.
It’s just that...
this is so new.
Mom, the only
new thing going on
is that I have a gay friend,
not a lover, a friend.
Gay people are so sensitive
about terminology.
[ sighs]
[knock at door]
Whazzup, whazzup,
whazzup?
- How you doin’?
- Okay, I think
you misunderstood.
We don’t need to convince
her that you’re straight,
just that I am.
Oh, thank God.
It was all too La Cage
Aux Folles for me.
- Oh, you must be
Mrs. Mull-er.
- Myoo-ler.
Myoo-ler.
Mull-er, Myoo-ler.
- So sorry.
Such a pleasure to meet you.
- It’s nice to meet you, too.
Well, I really
can’t stay, but--
Oh, that’s so sweet.
Okay. Todd wanted me
to come by and explain
about the other night.
There’s nothing to explain.
I understand.
I’m an adult.
Well, nothing happened.
Your son was a perfect
gentleman... damn it.
- Kelly.
- What?
I’m sorry. I thought I was
up to this, but I’m not.
Please excuse me.
Mother, wh-where
are you going?
I’m sorry.
- [door closes]
- [Todd]
Mom!
- Mom!
- [knocking at door]
Mother!
You know, I just thought
a little levity might
lighten the mood.
- [knock at door]
- Mom. Oh, God.
It’s not your fault.
She’s a lunatic.
No, no, she’s... sweet.
- [pounding on door]
- Mom. Mom, I’m serious.
- Would you please
open this door?
- Let’s put a mirror in here.
- Mom!
- Listen, I’m
going to go see...
that new Woody Allen movie
tonight with some friends.
- Do you want to come along?
- We have to see that.
Friends?
Yeah, friends,
a group of gay men.
You’d be the token
heterosexual.
Scared?
No. But...
I don’t know.
Maybe I should stay
here with my mom.
All right, yeah.
I understand.
- I’ll talk to you later.
- All right. Wait.
She’s probably going to
be in there all night.
Let’s just go.
This is the best you
could do for straight?
- I love her.
- Come on.
Do we have to see
this Woody Allen thingy?
A new Tom Cruise
movie’s playing.
You get to see his butt.
You’ve seen that movie
five times already.
He’s crazy now,
but I think he’s
still kind of hot.
- Not as hot as you, baby.
- Yeah.
- Todd! Is that you?
- Clayton.
Hi. How’re you doing?
Good to see you.
You remember
my partner Andy.
Andy! What’s up?
- You’re hurting him.
- Sorry, sorry.
- Nice night, huh?
- Oh.
Oh, yeah.
Um...
This is my friend Kelly.
Friend.
And these are his
friends, um, uh...
- Matt and, uh--
- Anthony.
- Nice to meet you guys.
- Nice to meet you.
So are you here to see
the Tom Cruise film?
Yeah, yeah--
Uh, no, Woody Allen.
Yeah, Woody Allen.
He shows his butt
in this one.
I mean, Tom Cruise does,
not that I know that.
I just, uh...
Or care.
I don’t even...
Well...
- have fun.
- [Matt]
You, too.
- Bye.
- Nice to meet you.
Bye.
He’s going to tell
everyone in the office
that I’m gay.
- What do you care?
- I don’t know.
- It’s just weird.
- I know what you mean.
People are always
thinking I’m straight.
It’s so annoying.
- [Kelly laughs]
- What?
I’m serious.
It happens.
- [Kelly]
Yes.
- Oh, my god.
Sorry I’m late.
I was getting my hairdo.
Whatever.
I just want to get tickets
so we can get good seats.
- I’m so hungry.
- I know. Me, too.
- This place is great, though.
- Yeah?
- [horn honks]
- Fuckin’ faggots!
- Asshole!
- Fascist little punks!
[Kelly]
Are you okay?
- I’m bleeding.
- Oh, my God,
you’re bleeding.
Okay, wait.
Let me see.
It’s not deep.
You’ll be all right.
An inch lower, and you
could’ve lost your eye.
- Did somebody see
their plates?
- What for?
They’re just kids.
The cops won’t
do anything.
Now you know
what we go through.
Being gay isn’t
all about disco music
and sparkle dust.
But this is
your part of town.
Apparently, somebody
needs to be better
about border patrol.
God.
- Is it still bleeding?
- What do you think?
It looks fine, but we
should go inside and put
some iodine on it.
It’s fine.
I can do it myself.
[sighs]
What--
- You’re still a little shaken.
- I don’t want to
wake my mother.
Yeah, I’m a loud queen,
but I do know how
to whisper, you know.
- It’s not necessary.
- It’s going to get infected
while we stand here arguing.
Let’s just go inside
and fix your face.
It’s fine.
I can do it.
[whispering]
Sit down.
Where are the Band-Aids?
- In the top drawer.
- Okay.
Let me see.
I hope this cut didn’t ruin
the evening for you.
It’s not the cut.
I know.
We weren’t doing anything.
It’s not like we were
holding hands.
And that would have
made it okay?
Well, I mean,
I can see how
that might make some
people uncomfortable.
People?
Not you?
Well, discomfort’s
one thing,
but how do you get from that
to throwing bottles?
People deal with discomfort
in strange ways.
Maybe this kid
is actually gay,
and this is his way of
fighting those feelings.
God, what
a depressing thought.
Well, not everybody is
as accepting as your mother.
Don’t remind me.
I still need to straighten
out that whole mess.
What you need is
a good night’s sleep
and a hairstyle.
What do you mean?
I like my hair.
Really?
You’ve got to be completely
honest with me, okay?
- What?
- Am I losing my hair?
You are not losing
your hair.
- Look right there.
- I’m looking right there.
I see hair.
- You saw hair?
- I saw hair.
You need
a little product.
No, I don’t want to
gay it all up.
Is gel gay, huh?
A little dollop.
Dollop sounds gay.
It does sound gay.
Hey, Todd.
How was that movie
last night?
It was great.
Yours?
So-so. We did get to
see Tom Cruise’s ass,
so it wasn’t a total loss.
Listen, you want
to grab some lunch?
- Oh, my God, what
happened to your eye?
- Uh... scratched it.
It’s nothing.
Oh. You want to go
to that new Indian place
down the street?
That sounds good.
Yeah.
Oh, love the hair.
[Indian sitar music playing]
Okay, listen.
There’s something
I need to explain.
Kelly seems really nice.
How long have you
been seeing him?
He is nice,
but we’re not dating.
Oh, so you’re still
in the market?
Andy works with
this really great guy.
The two of you would hit it off.
Okay, I’m not
making myself clear.
I am straight,
heterosexual, 100%.
Okay, tofu tikka masala.
Can’t a guy go
to the movies
with a group of gay men
without being gay?
- Is there some sort
of law against that?
- Mm-mm.
Of course not.
Happens all the time.
You still
don’t believe me.
It’s fine.
You’ll come out
when you’re ready.
No, seriously,
I’m straight.
- Do you swear
on Judy Garland’s grave?
- What?
Now, see that...
would make perfect sense
to a gay man.
- [phone ringing]
- [computer keys clacking]
This is Todd.
[Kelly]
You want to get
a drink after work?
There’s this little
place right near here
makes a great mojito.
You’ve had those, right?
Trendy, but who cares?
- It goes down easy.
- Kind of like you.
[laughs]
Aren’t you feisty today?
Don’t believe everything
you read on bathroom walls.
Ah, I’m glad you can
laugh about your ex.
I’m not quite sure
I’m at that point yet.
Well, I can only laugh about it
because I know he’s miserable.
If he was living happily
ever after with that twink,
I’d be a tad bitter.
Yeah.
So you didn’t tell me
this was a gay bar.
- You didn’t ask.
- Do you only go to gay places?
I mean, the movie theater,
the coffee house.
I suppose you shop
at a gay supermarket.
Obviously.
Supermarkets are great
places to pick up men.
I’ll bear that in mind.
- Thank you.
Sure. You guys
are a cute couple.
- How long have you
been together?
- We’re not.
- Two years.
- We’re not a couple.
He’s joking.
Well, whatever.
You look happy together.
Thank you.
We are.
- [laughing]
- Just--
- Hi, Todd!
- [guffaws]
I didn’t know you knew about
this little watering hole.
I didn’t.
Kelly invited me.
Yeah.
We met last night.
I remember.
[laughs]
So I just wanted
to say hello.
I guess I’ll leave
you two alone.
Judy Garland’s
grave, my ass.
Mom? What are you doing?
Are you okay?
Oh, yeah.
There’s a message for you.
[answering machine beeps]
[Clayton] Hi, Todd.
I forgot to mention,
there’s a group you
might be interested in.
It’s called GLIPA--
Gay and Lesbian
Programmers of America.
I’ll e-mail you next time
we have a meeting.
Bye.
- [beeps]
- So...
you’ve come out at work,
but you still can’t talk
to your own mother.
I have not come out at work.
He’s just confused.
Freud called that
projection.
Mom, I realize
this looks bad--
No, honey, not at all.
There’s nothing bad
about your being gay.
- It’s just what you are.
- But it’s not what I am.
Darling, I never
told this to a soul,
but I knew you were gay
when you were a little boy.
You didn’t enjoy sports
like the other boys.
I liked sports.
Well, let’s say
you liked reading more.
Mom, I was smart,
not gay.
Of course you were smart,
and you were sensitive,
and you loved the theater
and music and movies.
God, you’re right.
I do sound gay.
And when I saw you
with your friend Robert,
well, you know.
Do you know
a couple of months ago
Robert came with his
life partner to visit?
What a lovely man.
They’re so happy.
They’ve been together
10 years now.
Isn’t that wonderful?
Yes, that’s
wonderful for them,
but not me
because I love women.
Of course you love women.
It’s just a myth
that gay men hate women.
But that’s not
what this is about.
I’ve been doing some
reading, a book called
Loving Someone Gay.
Mom...
I love you so much,
and I know you love me
and you mean well,
and you’re so sweet
and supportive.
And if I were gay,
I’d be so lucky
to have someone
like you, but I’m not.
And I don’t know
what else I can say
or do to convince you
that I’m straight.
This was just
a huge misunderstanding.
I was just trying
to get back at Barry.
Oh, well, Barry’s
a little uptight.
You know,
he’ll come around.
He’s a good boy.
[dance music playing]
Another one, please.
Thank you.
I’m just going to
throw this out there.
Are you alone?
Yeah.
That sucked.
Hey.
Me?
Hi.
- You got one.
- [laughs]
Why don’t I just
pull this off?
[woman moaning]
It’s okay.
It sometimes happens
to older guys.
I need to go.
Well... maybe...
maybe you could try
that Viagra stuff.
I really need to go.
[sighs]
Bye.
[knock at door]
[pounding on door]
Who the hell are you,
and why are you pounding
on my door at 3:00 A.M.?
- I was looking for Kelly.
I thought--
- He’s not here.
You have the right place.
He’s just not here.
Oh.
Doesn’t mean he’s out
with another guy.
It’s fine if he is.
That’s not-- We’re not--
[locks clanking]
You’re Todd,
the straight guy.
Uh, yeah.
I guess that would be me.
Oh, hi. I’m Bonnie,
Kelly’s fag-hag.
- Hi.
You wanna come in?
I’d better go.
It’s late.
Well, I’m already up.
You might as well come on in.
But I don’t even
know you.
And you never will
standing out there.
Come on.
Thirsty?
Uh...sure.
So, Todd,
what is this
all about?
You can’t tell me you were
just in the neighborhood
at 3:00 A.M.
Um, I just need
to talk to Kelly.
About?
It’s between us.
[giggles]
Kelly tells me everything.
We’ve been best friends
for years now.
Hey, is this about
your mother?
You know about
my mother?
Just the broad outlines.
Kelly says she’s really sweet.
In a demented
sort of way.
Well, at least
she’s not a bitch.
You should meet mine.
So you and Kelly
live here together?
Mm-hmm. We have
for a couple of years now.
He never mentioned you.
You know, I think
he’s been keeping us apart,
probably afraid that we’re
gonna end up sleeping together,
and then, you know, things
will get a little awkward.
You pretty much say whatever
pops into your head, don’t you?
Pretty much.
Does that bother you?
I’m not sure yet.
You know, Kelly is right.
[rings]
You are really cute.
[giggles]
I’m not gay.
Well, nobody said you were.
Everyone says I am,
but I’m not.
Well, makes
no difference to me.
Some of the best sex
I’ve ever had
has been with gay men.
- What?
- Mm-hmm.
How do you think
Kelly and I met?
Maybe I’m still asleep
and hallucinating
this whole conversation.
Maybe.
Chamomile?
We’re gonna fuck,
aren’t we?
- Ah!
- Oh, oh, my gosh!
I’m so sorry!
Here, let me get
something cold.
Oh, that was bad.
I’m so sorry!
Oh... is that better?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Because sometimes I say
things to shock people,
and it’s fun, but I need
to learn not to do it
when they’re holding
sharp objects
or scalding liquids.
So you were just
trying to shock me?
No, no, I really do
wanna have sex with you.
It’s just, in retrospect,
maybe I could have had
a more subtle way
of signaling
my interest, huh?
Perhaps.
Yeah.
You’re probably not much
in the mood now, huh?
Yeah.
I better go. I...
have to get up for work
in three hours.
You want me to leave
Kelly a message?
No. I’ll catch him
later.
- [groans]
- [door closes]
[car engine starts]
Bonnie?
What?
Did I hear someone
leave?
[giggles]
You don’t usually let
your tricks slam the door.
That’s because
it wasn’t one of my tricks.
- It was one of yours.
- What?
My tricks don’t leave.
It was Todd.
My Todd?
Mm-hmm.
Why didn’t you
come get me?
Because it is
3:00 in the morning.
And...
well, because
he’s really cute.
Yeah. He is, isn’t he?
And you know he’s
straight, right?
Yes.
Of course.
Totally.
Okay.
- Good night.
- Night.
♪ Am I foolin’ you ♪
♪ Are you foolin’ me ♪
♪ Can you see in my eyes ♪
♪ What you want to see ♪
Hey, Todd.
Didn’t mean to scare you.
Not that you don’t
deserve it.
What?
All this time,
you’ve been holding out on us.
What are you talking
about, Melissa?
It’s okay.
You don’t have to
hide anymore.
Clayton told us
everything.
Oh, yeah. I guess
that was inevitable.
I’m just hurt
that you didn’t think
that I would understand.
I mean, I may be straight,
but I’m not narrow.
No, it wasn’t that--
Listen, if you’d like to,
uh, get together sometime--
Diana, hi!
Todd, if you have a minute,
I would love to see you
in my office.
Of course.
By the way,
happy birthday.
I want you to know
that this company
is behind you 100%.
Thanks. But...
this isn’t even
a milestone birthday.
Oh, anybody
can have a birthday.
But a committed
gay relationship?
That’s a political
statement.
That’s worth celebrating.
What?
This company recognizes
domestic partnerships.
I mean, that’s presuming
you and your partner
want to take
that step sometime.
This is unbelievable.
Doesn’t anyone around here
have anything better to do
than talk about
my personal life?
This is a family
here, Todd.
That’s the only kind
of company I like to run.
That’s great, but--
Todd, we’re excited for you.
I mean, coming out
at this age?
That’s not
an easy thing to do,
especially not in this
political climate.
That’s why it’s so important.
Now, if you need
any help from me,
you just go to my assistant,
and she’ll let me know.
That’s very thoughtful, but--
Anyway, I think we should
get back to work, don’t you?
- We all have deadlines.
- Yes, absolutely.
But the-- the thing is,
Diana, I’m not--
I don’t think you understand--
Scott-- Oh, I’m sorry.
I mean Todd.
You can call me Scott.
I am so looking forward
to meeting your partner
at the company picnic
next month.
I hear he’s a stud!
No, he-- he’s--
That’s the thing
I wanna make clear.
- He’s not my partner.
- Oh, uh, Todd.
Would you do me a favor?
I would like you to look into
the Nordlinger account.
Just e-mail me an update.
That would be great.
Absolutely.
I will do that.
- You have a good day.
- You, too.
The thing is-- he’s not--
I wanna just be--
Oh, hi! I’m so glad
I ran into you.
I need your advice.
About what?
I have a few questions
about, you know,
backdoor issues?
We’re on the fifth floor.
No, no, no, no, no,
silly.
The back door.
Back door?
Carl and I have been
experimenting,
and it’s really
working out great.
At first when he
suggested it, I thought,
"Oh, no, he’s gay!"
But that’s not what
it’s all about.
It’s totally perked up
our sex life.
Um...
So we’re just using
regular lotion.
But I know that there’s
a million products
out on the market.
What do you think of
the stuff that heats up?
Is it hot,
or is it just hot?
I’m not gay, and I have
no expertise in this area.
Well, maybe you could
ask your boyfriend
and get back to me.
I kinda want to surprise
Carl this weekend
with something fun.
Thanks!
You’re such a doll!
Okay, bye-bye.
- [knocks]
- It’s only me.
Sorry I’m late.
Hi, honey.
Hi.
Happy birthday.
Thanks.
Darling,
here’s your dinner.
I invited your brother.
I hope that’s okay.
That’s actually
perfect.
And here’s some butter
for you all.
You know, my doctor says
I shouldn’t have saturated fat.
But if you all want...
Mom, Mom, it’s fine.
Everything looks perfect.
Why don’t you sit down?
I sure missed
your home cooking.
Me, too, Mom. I’m sorry
I haven’t been around more.
Oh, don’t be silly.
I arrived in town
unexpectedly,
and you’re starting
a new relationship.
And I may be old, but I remember
how exciting that was.
Can the three of us talk
as adults?
Sure, honey.
Well, as long as you
don’t get too... graphic.
Look, um,
I’m sorry if I haven’t been very
open about my personal life.
I guess I’m a pretty
private person.
And I can see how you might
misinterpret that
and think that I had
something to hide.
It’s okay.
I understand it now.
Mom, please, let me finish.
The truth is, I don’t have
any exciting secrets.
I mean, up until recently,
the most titillating thing
in my life was cable television.
And I guess that’s why
I fell for it
when Barry took
an uncharacteristic interest
and seemed to be trying
to fix me up--
Hold on. Are you saying
this is my fault?
Are you blaming me?
That’s not what
I’m saying, Barry.
[doorbell rings]
I’ll get it.
- He’s blaming me.
- Barry.
He’s a homo,
and he’s blaming me.
I’m not blaming you, Barry.
Will you shut up?
Who is it, darling?
It’s the police.
Oh, shit.
Mr. Muller?
Yeah...
I have something for you.
[dance music]
♪ Come on, everybody ♪
♪ Par-tay ♪
♪ Get into the groove ♪
♪ Make your body move ♪
♪ Baby, if you want me ♪
♪ Oh, whoa, yeah ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Come on, everybody ♪
Happy birthday, big boy,
from all your friends
at the office.
Um...
I gotta go.
Barry, sit down
and eat your dinner.
♪ Whoa ♪
Uh, I kinda lost
my appetite, Mom.
♪ Par-tay ♪
Aren’t you gonna tip
the nice young man?
What?
That was very nice.
Thank you.
Hey, here’s my card.
Gimme a call.
I do all sorts of occasions.
[Mrs. Muller]
Bye.
Well...
I just saw you
kiss a man,
and I’m okay,
I’m really okay.
Aren’t I progressing?
I’m progressing, right?
Christ, this has gotten
so out of hand.
[knock at door]
- Hey!
- We need to talk.
What’s wrong?
I think, just for right now,
we shouldn’t see
each other for a while.
Thought you actually
had to date someone
before he could
break up with you.
We are not breaking up,
because we were never a couple.
I think we should just
back off a little bit.
That’s such
a break-up line.
Oh, my God, you’re right.
Okay, climb off the ledge.
What’s going on?
Tonight a man with bigger
tits than my ex-wife
did some sort of birthday
striptease--
Happy birthday!
- And then kissed me!
- How old are you?
Forget about my birthday.
He kissed me!
Look, as life catastrophes go,
an unwanted kiss
isn’t up there with, say,
cancer, or--
Okay, so my problems
don’t amount to a hill of
beans in this crazy world.
Fine. They’re still
my problems,
and my life still feels
totally screwed up!
Okay, what’s the real
issue here, huh?
You don’t like people thinking
you’re gay when we’re
not doing anything?
- Exactly!
- Well, that’s easy to fix.
Kelly!
What? I just think it’s a shame
that the only action going on
is in the minds
of your friends and family.
But sleeping together
isn’t gonna solve anything.
What is that?
Oh, night firming cream.
It’s my own special blend.
I sell it at the store.
You want some?
No, I don’t need night
firming cream right now.
Actually, you do.
Anyway, look.
You already have
the stigma of being gay.
You might as well experience
some of the fun.
But it wouldn’t be fun
because I’m not into guys.
You’re telling me
you didn’t enjoy
any of the fooling around you
did when you were 12?
11, and that’s not
the point.
At that age, brushing
against a tree is exciting.
I guarantee I’m more fun
than a tree.
The answer is still no.
Um, can you stir this?
And don’t stop.
- Just keep stirring.
- Yes, yes, yes!
The only reason why
you’re not willing
to have a little fun
with me
is because of what
it might mean about you.
Kelly, I’m not
attracted to you.
Really? Stir.
I mean, not in that way.
It just-- I love
spending time with you,
but that’s not
the same thing.
How do you know?
Not stirring.
Apples and oranges.
You’ve never heard the theory
that we’re all
a little bit bisexual?
Yes, and maybe
it’s even true, but--
What are you doing?
You-- You’re crazy.
I’m outta here.
[door slams]
Orange.
[door opens]
Hi, Todd.
How have you been?
What are you doing here?
Barry called me.
Yeah, he had some very
interesting questions
about our sex life.
I am going to kill him.
He thinks I
turned you gay!
Is that true, Todd?
Are you gay now?
It’s none of your damn business
if I’m sleeping with sheep.
I’d like you to leave.
I asked her to leave, but she
insisted on speaking with you.
We’ve spoken.
Now go.
I don’t believe it.
Even if you were a fag,
I don’t think you’d have the
guts to do anything about it.
[knock at door]
Hey--
See? Nothing.
Well, hello to you, too.
I didn’t find that
the least bit arousing.
Well, neither did I.
It felt like you were
trying to bash my teeth in.
- Oh, sorry.
- Do you wanna come in?
I think we’ve given
the neighbors enough
thrills for one evening.
What the hell’s
going on?
What if I’m just
fooling myself?
I mean, everyone
thinks I’m gay.
Maybe I’m just in denial.
- You’re not gay.
- Can you tell?
I mean, how can you
be sure?
Do I set off
your gaydar?
I’m sure
because you’re sure.
But, I-- I’m not sure!
I mean, I was sure.
I don’t know anymore!
Even my own mother thinks
I’m a closet case!
Well, your mother
has issues.
Tell me about it.
I can only think of
one way to settle this.
Oh, no.
No, no, no.
You’re not gonna make me
listen to Barbra Streisand,
are you?
I can’t believe
you just said that.
That is
such a stereotype.
Okay, you know what?
She’s the world’s
greatest living singer
and criminally underrated
as a director.
And Yentl was the only
decent movie musical of the--
I see your point.
What were we talking about?
The one sure way to know
whether or not I’m gay.
Right.
We have sex.
And that’s gonna prove
that I’m straight?
Well, then you’ll know.
I mean, it’ll either be
the most incredible
experience of your life
or it won’t.
What if you’re
just a bad lay?
No.
Okay.
So... we have sex...
Mm-hmm.
And if it doesn’t
send me over the moon,
then I’m straight?
Pretty much.
What if I do like it?
Well, then,
you’ve lucked into
a pretty amazing boyfriend,
if I do say so myself.
I-- I don’t think
I’m broad-minded enough
to go through with this.
Well, you’ve already
kissed me,
and you didn’t turn to stone
or drop dead
from a heart attack.
But it wasn’t much of a kiss,
as you already pointed out.
All right.
Well...
Let’s start with that.
What are you
so afraid of?
Hmm?
There.
That was a real kiss.
That wasn’t...
gross.
[laughs]
High praise, indeed.
I mean, I thought
I’d wanna throw up...
but I don’t.
Okay, stop.
You’re making me blush.
I-- I need a drink.
Yeah.
So do I.
[chuckles]
I can’t believe
I might actually do this.
What if it’s a mistake?
Finding out who you are
is never a mistake.
Do you trust me?
’Cause I trust you.
I really care about you.
If we do this,
and I don’t like it,
you have to promise me
that you won’t
fall in love with me.
[laughs]
Listen to you.
Look, if it’s one thing
gay men are good at,
it’s sex that’s
only about sex.
That and decorating.
[laughs]
Well, your sense
of humor’s coming back.
That’s a good sign.
Shall we?
[moans]
Was that a good moan
or a bad moan?
It was good.
It felt good.
If I do something
you don’t like, you tell me.
You’re talking
too much.
Right. Okay.
Can-- Can we turn
the lights out?
Yeah. Whatever you want.
[whispers]
You have chest hair.
[laughs]
Is that a bad thing?
It’s definitely different.
[rustling]
[Todd]
Ow.
[Kelly]
Sorry.
You could put an eye
out with that thing.
[laughing]
How much of that bottle
have you had?
Enough, I guess.
Mmm.
Morning.
I have to go.
I knew you’d freak out.
I’m not freaking out.
I just have to...
go to work.
Was I that good?
Can we not talk
about this?
Look, if it makes you feel
any better, in Latin America,
guys aren’t considered gay
for having sex with other guys,
if they’re on top.
Well, that’s a relief.
So I’m straight as long
as I move to Ecuador.
Look, you can be straight here
if that’s who you really are.
I’ll call you.
What are you
doing up so early?
Oh, I couldn’t sleep.
A lot on my mind.
Join the club.
You all right, honey?
I don’t wanna talk
about it.
[inhaling]
I love that scent
that Kelly wears.
What’s it called?
What’s the scent
that Kelly wears--
How the hell should I know?
Eternity.
Fag Forever.
Something like that.
You and Kelly had a fight?
Mom! No!
Oh, honey, there’s this thing
called couples counseling.
Your father and I did it.
Mom, we are not a c--
You and Dad?
Yeah. It was in the ’70s.
We learned a lot
about communication.
I really think it would
be good for you and Kelly.
Mother, listen to me.
I don’t know how many times, in
how many ways, I can say this.
He is not my boyfriend!
Well, whatever he is,
you care a lot about him.
He’s nothing to me!
Look, I may not have a genius
IQ, but I’m not a moron.
Don’t bullshit me!
I need to get ready
for work, Mother.
You want breakfast?
[door slams]
[woman]
Ask him about
the stripper.
Hey, Todd,
how’s it going?
Hey.
Did you enjoy the birthday
gift we got you?
The whole office
chipped in.
Clayton...
Look, are you and Kelly gonna
be at the Happy Hour tonight?
There is no me and Kelly, okay?
And I’m not gonna be
a Happy Hour tonight, or ever.
I’m not gay!
Whatever.
Todd had a little spat
with his boyfriend.
Oh, so is that why
you weren’t at the meeting?
There is no boyfriend,
and there was no spat.
What meeting?
Project meeting.
Been scheduled for a week.
Oh, my God, I forgot.
Hey, are you okay?
You don’t look so good.
I’m fine.
Some of us girls are going
out for drinks after work.
Come along.
We’ll cheer you up.
I appreciate that--
I won’t take no
for an answer.
Party.
[woman]
You’re not gonna be there,
dragging my ass down!
[woman #2]
Finally!
Did you kick him out?
Not exactly.
He has nowhere to go,
okay?
But I told him he’s gotta be
out by the end of the month.
Ann, you’re crazy.
Now you’re never
gonna get rid of him.
Tell him you’re gay--
surefire way to get rid
of unwanted houseguests.
No, that’s not gonna work
because men get all
turned on by lesbians.
Well, men-- Okay, they think
they want two women.
Oh, please.
Do the math.
Five minutes
divided by two?
Not even worth
shaving your legs for.
[woman #2]
Exactly.
I just think
it’s really weird
that men want
to watch that.
Like, I don’t know.
I just-- I don’t get it.
I totally get it.
Haven’t you guys ever seen
two men having sex?
[woman #2]
No. Why would I
see that?
It’s hot.
Okay, you are officially
a freak.
Girls, come on,
back me up!
No, I’m sorry.
I’m with Sarah
on this one.
I just think it’s
disgustingly, ugh, gross.
I mean, sorry,
no offense.
None taken.
I feel the same way.
[woman #3]
What, do you
rent gay porn?
No, no, no, I--I--
I’m just saying that
with the right two guys,
it’s really sexy.
I would just settle
for one man
if he knew what
he was doing.
Thank you.
- Can I get an amen?
- Amen.
[Ann]
Angelo, he couldn’t even
find my g-spot
if he had a flashlight
and a map.
I’ve completely given up
on having orgasms during sex.
If my shower massage
had a dental plan,
I’d fucking marry it!
[laughing]
I didn’t realize...
I just didn’t realize
girls talked like this.
[woman #2]
Like what?
What are we supposed
to talk about?
You know...
- Love...
- relationships.
Oh, such a pretty
story.
We talk about
that shit, too.
Yeah. Todd’s having trouble
with his boyfriend.
Oh. Is that fucking asshole
cheating on you?
Kelly’s not like that.
And he’s not my boyfriend,
you know?
Last night was the first time
I’ve ever had sex with a man.
[woman #3]
Oh...hey.
Oh!
Oh, my God.
It’s okay.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
I’ll see you guys
bright and early
tomorrow morning.
I’m not going to work
tomorrow.
Uh... I don’t think you
should be alone right now.
Come with me.
[Melissa laughing]
This is amazing.
You didn’t know it could
be like this with a woman, huh?
I never expected this
to happen between us.
I never realized
you were interested in me.
Well, I never knew
the real you.
What do you-- What do you
mean, the real me?
Oh!
Well, I thought you were just
another boring straight guy.
You mean you weren’t
interested in me
because you thought
I was straight?
Well, I never realized
how complex you were.
So because I slept with a man,
suddenly I’m complex?
Well, yeah!
Wait a minute.
You’re not interested
in me at all, are you?
I’m just a challenge.
Of course
I’m interested in you.
No. No.
We wouldn’t even be here
if you didn’t think I was gay.
Look, do you wanna
fuck or not?
Of course I do,
because I’m a straight man
and I’ve been lusting after you
from the first time I saw you.
I think you better go.
But--
[beep]
Uh, hi. It’s Kelly.
You didn’t pick up at work,
so I thought
I’d try you here.
Just thought
I’d make sure you’re okay.
Call me.
Maybe you should call.
Maybe you should just
mind your own damn business!
I did not bring you up
to speak to me like that.
I’m sorry. I’m just
a little on edge right now.
Well, honey, you hungry?
Let me make you some chicken.
- Mom, I’m not hungry.
- Chicken parmesan?
[knocking]
Hello!
Oh, Mom.
I’m so glad you’re still here,
because I have to say something
to the both of you.
I should say so.
We’ve both been waiting
for your apology.
Mom...
I’m gay!
Yeah, I finally realized
I’m gay, just like him.
That’s why this whole thing
has been bothering me so much.
[chuckling]
You just can’t stand
to let your brother be
the center of attention,
can you?
I remember
on his tenth birthday,
you deliberately
crashed your bike
so that we would have to get
you to the emergency room,
and Todd’s party
was ruined!
My bicycle?
No, no, that was an accident.
Darling, I am so sorry
if I’ve neglected you.
But your brother
needs me right now.
[shouting]
Ma, did you hear
what I said?
I’m gay!
You are not gay!
Yes, I am!
I’m gay!
But I’ve been suppressing it
all these years,
mindlessly, aimlessly fucking as
many different women as I can,
hoping that it would
somehow change me.
But it’s no use.
I am what I am.
How dare you say the F-word
in front of your mother!
Are you listening to me?
I had an epiphany!
And I don’t have to fight it
anymore because I’m gay!
I’m gay, I’m gay,
just like my brother Todd.
I’m not gay.
Oh, yes, you are.
You are gay,
my little brother,
and you’re very,
very good at it.
- You’re gay, and I’m gay.
- I am not gay!
Why can’t we just be
gay together?
There’ll be no together
with the gay!
Shut up, both of you!
You’re my boys.
I know my boys.
Barry, you are not gay,
and that’s that.
But, Ma, no fair!
I am gonna go lie down.
You boys are putting me
into an early grave.
But how come he gets to be...
all gay all the time?
[door slams]
You believe me?
Yes.
Okay! We got one sane
person in this whole family.
So, what do you say you,
uh, hook a brother up
with any of your
hot gay friends?
Okay, I support you,
I accept you unconditionally.
I’ll even march with you
in Gay Pride.
But, Barry, please,
don’t ask me to pimp for you.
All right.
Fine. Just trying
to get a little love.
Jesus, is that so wrong?
What do you got to eat?
You exhaust me.
♪ Sometimes at night ♪
♪ Where angels fly
and devils play ♪
♪ It feels so right ♪
♪ And I don’t know
what to say ♪
♪ I’ll admit ♪
♪ I was not pure of heart ♪
[telephone rings]
[ringing]
Todd?
Are you all right?
What?
You look terrible.
What’s going on?
I’m fine.
Everything’s fine. I--
- Look, just come with me.
- Why?
Just get up, walk this way.
You’re in Clayton’s hands.
You, out.
- What?
- Now!
No!
Take the fashion disaster
with you.
All right.
Come and sit down.
Right over here, honey.
There you go.
And tell me everything.
Go on.
I’m unshockable.
I...
had sex with a man.
You cheated on Kelly?
No. It was with Kelly.
I mean, I had sex
with Kelly.
I mean, my first time
ever with a man.
And it didn’t work out.
Oh, honey.
Sometimes the first time
is painful.
- You have to learn to relax.
- It’s not that.
It’s just...
I’m not gay.
I’m just... not.
Oh. Seems like you have
the whole thing figured out.
Why so miserable?
I don’t know.
I can’t eat.
I can’t concentrate.
My whole life
just feels off.
I’m no shrink,
but it sounds like you have
some unresolved issues.
I know you think I’m gay.
So does my mother,
my brother,
pretty much
everyone I know.
Look, in my experience,
sexual identity
is not decided by the masses.
Right.
So I’m still straight,
no matter what people think.
Well, there’s still
this matter of sex with Kelly.
It was an experiment
to prove I was straight.
Did it work?
Yes.
I mean, I don’t feel
any different.
I’m still attracted to women,
and I’m still not
attracted to men.
But you were able
to have sex with one.
Yes.
After a few drinks.
Do you know what that makes you?
What?
Normal.
How do you figure?
My grandmother
always had a saying.
"A stiff prick
has no conscience."
Your grandmother?
Yeah, we’re all able to get off
in a variety of ways.
And our sexuality,
our deepest feelings
about another human being--
that’s in our hearts
and our minds...
not our jolly Rogers.
Let’s say I buy that.
Why do I still feel
so lousy?
Oh, can’t eat, can’t sleep.
Sounds like love to me.
I thought that we just
established that I’m not gay.
There are
all kinds of love.
Not all of them
have to do with sex.
Now, look.
I don’t think we’re gonna feel
better until we talk to him.
I mean, you talk to him.
Hi.
Ow! What was that for?
For not calling.
We just had tea.
Not me, you idiot.
Kelly.
Oh, well, that’s what
I came to explain.
He’s not home yet.
Is he furious with me?
What do you think?
He didn’t keep
his promise, did he?
What promise?
Not to fall in love.
Oh, you know what?
Don’t flatter yourself,
Casanova.
He just doesn’t
appreciate being used.
It wasn’t like that.
Oh, really?
Well, what was it like?
Hi.
Well, this is a surprise.
I didn’t figure
I’d ever see you again.
I’m sorry for not calling.
I... just needed some time
to sort things out.
Hmm.
So what’s the verdict?
Did I rock your world,
or did you have to close your
eyes and think of England?
Could we talk inside?
Alone?
I’ll gong you
if I need you.
I’ll be out here
hoeing.
[laughs]
Okay.
Well?
Well, on a purely
technical level,
you get high marks.
But...
I can’t explain it.
And I don’t want
to hurt your feelings.
It’s just...
on some level
I didn’t feel...
engaged.
That’s because
you’re straight.
Really?
You think so?
Absolutely.
So... have I totally
screwed up our friendship?
Well, the bitchy queen in me
wants to punish you.
But...
But I missed you.
Yeah.
Me, too.
So where does that
leave us?
I mean,
how can we be friends
if we can’t even look
each other in the eye?
Truthfully,
this is hard for me.
I-- You’ve seen a side of me
nobody else has ever seen.
And part of you wants
to forget that side exists
and forget me, too.
Yes.
Is that really
what you want?
I don’t know.
Well, then,
so why did you come here?
I couldn’t leave things
like they were.
I had to explain.
I had to...
make sure you were okay.
I’m fine.
But I’d be lying
if I said
there wasn’t a part of me
hoping that you’d discover
your inner faggot,
and we’d...
live happily ever after.
But I-- I knew that
wasn’t gonna happen.
Really, I did.
You know,
maybe you should go.
I’m so sorry.
I screwed everything up.
No, no.
I think on this one,
you had some help.
Should I call you...
I-- Look, I don’t know.
Just--
Just go.
[sobbing]
[Mrs. Muller]
Okay, hurry, hurry.
Help!
I gotcha.
Come on.
Yeah, get those--
get those bags.
[man]
Good afternoon.
You don’t want to let her
miss this flight.
She misses the flight,
she stays another night.
I love ya, Ma!
- Me, too.
- Watch the spikes.
Oh, okay. Love you!
Okay, Todd, now,
now, it’s not that heavy.
It’s just a few dresses.
- Hi.
- Hey.
- Oh...Tom.
- Tom.
Nice to meet you.
- It was good to see you.
- I love you.
And maybe next time I come,
maybe there’s grandkids.
- What?
- Well, I mean, no rush.
You and Kelly
take your time, of course.
Mom, do I need to give you
a birds and bees talk now?
Don’t play dumb with me.
Look, there’s adoption,
surrogacy, the gay-by boom.
I know all about that.
Mom, you know Kelly and I
are not a couple.
What, this whole visit
you’re trying to tell me
there’s nothing going on
between you and Kelly?
I don’t think so!
I’m just waiting for you
to stand up
and say, "I’m gay,
and I’m proud of it."
I’m gay.
I’m proud of it.
Todd’s just confused.
Honey, let it go.
You are not gay.
Oh, I am gay,
I am so gay,
I even got
my nipples pierced.
Look, let me
show you, look--
- No, not here!
- See, it’s got a tight
little clamp.
You do not have to be gay.
It’s not a competition.
I love you as much
as I love your brother.
Mom, you should go.
I love you.
Okay.
Bye, honey.
- Bye, Mom.
- Bye.
- Safe trip.
- Let’s go.
I’d love the kids’ names
to be Rosie and Henry.
Okay.
Happy Hour?
I wasn’t sure
you’d come.
[laughs]
Yeah, neither was I.
I’m glad you did.
I ordered your favorite.
Thank you.
My mom thinks
we should adopt a kid.
[laughs, coughs]
Oh...
Well, I’ve always
wanted children.
You’d be a great dad.
Thanks.
You, too.
So is this okay
with you?
It’s a little sweet.
Not the lattes, fool.
The two of us.
It’s not gonna be
too weird between us?
Weird, yes.
Too weird?
My boundaries on that
have been expanding.
What about you?
I’m okay... now.
I guess I let my feelings
get a little out of control.
Feelings have a way
of doing that.
But I’m over it.
You won’t have to deal with
any more hysterical crying jags.
I wasn’t worried.
Well, I was...
for a while.
I’m not going to be doing
any of that
"Scarlett pining
for Ashley" crap.
In fact, I already have
a new personal ad
posted on the Internet.
You should check it out.
And this time,
I posted a picture.
Smart move.
You should do it, too.
No, I’ve already met
someone I’m interested in.
Oh, really?
Someone at work?
No. Someone
at your apartment.
Oh, my God.
How weird.
- You’re right, forget it.
- No, no.
It’s not that.
It’s...
I was gonna ask Barry out.
My brother?
Well, he is cute.
And I already know
he comes from a good family.
We can double-date.
It would be a hoot.
You think my coworkers
are confused now?
Are you still trying to convince
them that you’re straight?
No, I gave up.
I mean, really, who cares?
Besides, technically,
I’m bisexual, right?
Uh, no.
You’re straight.
If you were bisexual, you never
would have resisted my charms.
Listen to you.
Hey, I’m a hot package.
You’d have been lucky
to have me.
I know.
Drink your coffee.
♪ What’s the other
half coming down
What’s there ♪
♪ It seems so good
that I can’t trust it ♪
♪ No, I never felt this ♪
♪ No, I felt this before ♪
♪ I wanna pick up
the phone and call you ♪
♪ Although I try,
I just can’t ignore you ♪
♪ No, I felt this
No, I never felt this ♪
♪ Before you ♪
♪ What did I do
with my time, my money ♪
♪ Who’d I spend it on, honey ♪
♪ I know you
from the inside out ♪
♪ I can’t eat, I can’t sleep ♪
♪ Does it sound like love ♪
♪ ’Cause it sounds
like love to me ♪
♪ I can’t feel anything ♪
♪ Does it sound like love ♪
♪ ’Cause it sounds
like love to me, yeah ♪
♪ But I have a mind
to retry and try it ♪
♪ I’ve gotta know
before I deny it ♪
♪ ’Cause I never felt this ♪
♪ No, I never felt this before ♪
♪ The clock, it strikes 12:00
kinda funny ♪
♪ But I intended to run, honey ♪
♪ No, I never felt this ♪
♪ No, I never
felt this before ♪
♪ You don’t plan
these kind of moments ♪
♪ Try not to show it,
won’t it, baby ♪
♪ It’s just once
on this merry-go-round ♪
♪ I can’t eat, I can’t sleep ♪
♪ Does it sound like love ♪
♪ ’Cause it sounds
like love to me ♪
♪ I can’t feel anything ♪
♪ Does it sound like love ♪
♪ ’Cause it sounds like
love to me ♪
♪ I can’t eat, I can’t sleep ♪
♪ Does it sound like love ♪
♪ ’Cause it sounds
like love to me ♪
♪ I can’t feel anything ♪
♪ Does it sound like love ♪
♪ ’Cause it sounds
like love to me ♪
♪ And you ♪
♪ It’s a story without end ♪
♪ What to do ♪
♪ When you’re less than a lover
and more than a friend ♪
♪ I can’t eat, I can’t sleep ♪
♪ Does it sound like love ♪
♪ ’Cause it sounds like love ♪
♪ I can’t feel anything ♪
Closed-captions byCAPTION FILES
˯www.captionfiles.com