That guy, he had extras.
It's, like, 15 cents.
You got that for 15 cents?
I don't have 15 cents.
- 50 cents?
- I paid 50 cents for...
- Where did you get 50 cents?
- You got ripped off.
How much further is it?
It's just up here,
at the very end of the block.
He doesn't
even know where we're going.
I know, I've... we've told you,
like, ten times.
You've been here, like...
What, like, two years?
I've been, like,
doing this for, like, four.
I'm the Reaper,
baby, I'm coming for your spot.
- Whatever, like, still.
- The Reaper?
If he's like a new kid,
then maybe he should be
- the one in charge.
- Damn right.
Are you crazy?
He doesn't even know
where the corner is.
No, that's the logic
that you have, like...
'Cause this is my first
time at this corner.
I've been to
the corner on Fifth twice.
I'm not assuming, I know.
You were, like, screaming
in the fucking street.
Is there a cop car?
You know, you guys are idiots.
There's certain
places that you can't live
unless you've, like,
worked your way up there.
Like Town Avenue is
the crack and heroin dealers,
and, like, unless you're, like,
one of those dealers,
you can't live there.
And then if you're... you're
working for someone,
like, helping with runs
you can, like, live near
where there... they... they live
and they, like, protect you,
and you wanna be protected.
You wanna be part of one
of those, like, gangs
in a way, you know?
Do you think you'll ever leave?
Mm.
I mean, I'm sure, yeah, one day.
- What?
- No.
Moved the pickup location.
Ah, Jesus Christ,
and he's sleeping.
Need to get him up right now.
Gabriel!
Wake up. Gabriel,
wake up, we have to go.
Come here.
Come on,
get up, big payday today.
This is gonna be a good one,
so we gotta go, guys, come on.
Just be good tonight, all right?
Just be good.
- For once.
- Where's the car?
It's up here,
they changed the spot.
Move it!
I wait all night.
Gabriel,
you're with Tom tonight,
and he paid holiday prices,
so she told me to tell you, uh,
you know,
be good.
Gabriel, be good to Tom, okay?
I heard you the first time.
Gabriel, you okay?
Gabriel.
Yeah, one second.
All right, I've been waiting.
Hey, Gabriel.
Yeah?
What are you doing in there?
Just a minute.
All right, I've been
waiting for you a while.
Yeah, ju... just a second.
What are you doing?
Nothing.
So, you all set, all good?
Yeah, all good.
Okay.
You wanna come out?
- You all right?
- Yeah, mm-hmm.
You into kissing?
Sure.
Okay.
- Did you steal my wallet?
- No.
- No, I...
You are lying to me.
- You are lying to me.
- No.
You have my wallet.
I wanna see your pockets.
- I don't have your money.
- Empty your goddamn pockets.
I don't have your money,
- I don't have your money.
- You have my wallet.
- Empty your goddamn pockets.
- No.
- Empty them.
- I'm leaving.
- I wanna see your pockets.
- Empty your pockets.
- I don't have your money.
Trying to scare
off the girls with those nails?
What?
Are you trying to scare
the girls off with those nails?
No.
Uh, everyone.
I don't blame you.
Why's a handsome boy like you
waiting for the Metro
all by himself?
Why are you still here?
You look like you
could use some company.
I'm good.
Good, I'm glad, I'm Martha.
Hey, Martha, um, I'm on my way
to see a client right now, so...
A client?
I sleep with people for money.
Oh. Oh.
You're still here.
Women or men?
Why, do you want to pay?
I'm a married woman, young man.
Where's your husband?
Well, he's no longer with us.
Oh, I'm sorry.
You know what my favourite
thing about him was?
He would leave
little origami swans for me
every day in secret spots.
He knew how much I loved swans.
I miss those swans.
This is, uh...
This is my train coming.
Good luck with everything.
Do you ever get paid
just to spend time?
None of that other
stuff required.
Come in.
A Christmas tree.
It's Christmas Eve, after all.
I forgot.
I put up the tree
a couple of weeks ago.
This is a nice place.
Thank you.
Would you like some water?
Oh, no, thank you.
Wasn't expecting guests.
Do you like music?
Uh, yeah.
Do you sing?
Uh, no, ma'am.
I hate being called ma'am.
What would you be
doing if I wasn't here?
Well, I'd probably be
listening to music and reading,
nothing too crazy.
What type of music?
Oh, I don't think
you'd like my music.
Try me.
Okay.
Could I have one?
Are you old enough?
Thank you.
Do you need to be that
drunk to be here with me?
I think I just need to
be that drunk in general.
You don't need to stay.
I can give you some money
and you can leave
whenever you'd like.
I think I'll stay.
More?
Yes, please.
It's not water, my boy.
Who likes Scotch?
Apparently, you do.
Remind me to get Scotch later.
Scotch?
I always drink
scotch at Christmas.
Thanks for last night.
I'll see you later.
Don't be late again.
I have to go to the bathroom.
Hey, Gabriel, it's Mom.
It's cold here today.
I hope Los Angeles is warm.
I know you can't call often,
but I'd love to hear
from you soon.
And if you can send
some more money,
that would be really great.
They cut my shifts
at the vocational school.
I'm praying for you.
Merry Christmas,
and call your mom soon.
I love you.
Who were you talking to,
Gabriel?
Nobody.
This isn't what
I'm paying you for.
- Is that the police?
- No.
Ow, stop.
Come on.
Where are you going?
Your loss.
How can I help you?
I need to send all
of that to Illinois.
Okay, uh, we can do that
through a cashier's check
or wire transfer.
Um, how much is this?
A lot.
[faint dance music
playing in club
Can I bum one?
Thanks.
Got a light?
What do you want?
Are you guys hiring?
No.
Wait, I'll sweep the floor.
Can you stick
around for one song,
and I'll have
a job for you after?
Yeah, okay.
Okay.
Come on, I'll buy you a drink,
but only because it's Christmas.
Wait, what's the job?
Are you coming or not?
[soft classical
music playing faintly
Merry Christmas.
You have a visitor.
Santa, you look skinny.
Santa's on a diet.
What have we got?
I like it.
I'm just trying
to, um, tie this part,
and that part is the leash.
It's the leash, 'cause
we're gonna walk Pat-pat.
Fist.
High five.
Middle. Side.
Side, side, side.
Low. Too slow.
Low.
Good job.
Thanks.
You stay safe out there, okay?
You got it.
What's your name?
I'm Gabriel.
Come back to the bar,
I'll see if they can give you
a bar backing job or something.
Thanks.
Okay.
Now, go on.
Wait, gimme my outfit back.
Mrs. Wynn, there is
someone here to see you.
Tell them I'm busy.
Uh, he says his name is Gabriel,
and he would like
to speak with you.
How did you find
my office address?
A lot of research.
Very proactive of you.
Hey, look what I got.
What's that?
You bought my book?
Well, I didn't buy it.
You stole it.
No, I just
borrowed it from the shelf.
I'm gonna return it,
don't worry.
What was that other journal
at the bottom of your bag?
Oh, nothing.
You write?
No. I mean sometimes.
But not important
stuff like you.
Just stuff that happens.
Writing about your
experiences is important.
Hey, would you wanna do
this, uh, same time next week?
Well...
I'm sorry,
I shouldn't have asked that.
No, it's not that, it's, um,
I'm moving to Tuscany next week.
Tuscany.
- Italy.
- I know.
I'm going to our house there
to... to write one last book.
Last?
You look thinner,
are you hungry?
Yeah, always.
I should get going.
Get yourself cleaned
up and get a good meal.
Martha?
Yes?
I forgot what I was gonna say.
Take care of yourself, Gabriel.
LA seems like this
really friendly place,
but as soon as you need help,
you're pretty much on your own.
So, you have nowhere to go,
and then some dude approaches
you and offers you a job.
I got approached at a... a...
A fucking taco stand for...
700 bucks to
get naked on a camera.
I'm never gonna leave here.
Yes, you will.
I mean you will, I won't.
Why?
It's the only thing I'm good at.
Hey.
Luke, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Hey, hey.
Hey, hey, hey.
Hey, look at me, look at me.
Luke, Luke.
Hey, hey, hey.
Hey, hey, Luke, hey.
- Is he okay?
- He's fine.
- You should call someone.
- I said, he's fine.
Look at me, look at me.
Look at me.
Hey, hey, hey.
Breathe, breathe, breathe.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Can we talk to the doctor?
- Where's the doctor?
- You're not helping us.
He is with the doctor right now,
and if you could please
wait in the waiting...
- How do I get back there?
- If...
Where is he?
Just tell us where he is.
You cannot go back
there right now.
- Where is he? Which room?
- Tell us where he is right now.
I have told you
that he is in the ICU,
he is with the doctor and the...
How did you get past security?
Can I come in?
Are you all right, Gabriel?
Scotch.
Excuse me?
There's a perfect bottle of...
Of whiskey, and I pick Scotch.
Mm-hmm.
Have you been drinking?
Have you?
Can I get you a glass of water,
Gabriel?
Why do you always ask that?
Because you look like
you could use some.
Can I sit down?
Of course.
That's pretty nice
that you have a beautiful home.
Thank you.
That's okay.
What is?
You'll be happier in Italy,
and I think that's pretty cool.
Mm. Well, guess what?
My doctors say I'm not
well enough to go to Italy.
I'm here for another
round of treatment.
Oh. Oh, I'm sorry, Martha.
You have nothing
to be sorry for.
Hey, do you wanna go
somewhere that looks like Italy?
What?
So, do you want to?
- Gabriel, that's crazy.
- Hey...
Hey, what does Italy look like?
It's beautiful.
There are some hills up
the coast near Santa Barbara
that resemble parts of it,
but no, we're not going
anywhere.
Okay.
Mayb... maybe tomorrow?
Gabriel.
Okay.
Absolutely not.
Hybrids are economical.
They're great on gas, and much
better for the environment.
I'm serious.
Guess how many times
a month I fill up this tank?
Once. Just once.
Can you believe that?
If you ever make money,
want to keep it,
don't go buying fancy cars.
Means we're almost there.
When you receive bread,
you say grazie.
What does that mean?
It means "Thank you."
And then I reply, prego.
- Prego.
Hey, have you ever
looked at a sunset upside down?
What?
Yeah, you do a handstand, watch.
No, no, no, no, not that one.
- Shit, okay.
- R is reverse, not stop.
You need to take your
foot off the accelerator
- Okay.
- And put it on the...
Ah, ah, how do I stop?
Gabriel, Gabriel, hit the brake.
How do I stop, how do I stop?
Oh, my God, one more time.
- Oh, my gosh.
- How was that?
You're going
to give me a heart attack.
That was... that was
pretty good, though, right?
That was a pretty good turn?
Yes, you're
a fast learner, okay.
I'm gonna freshen up.
Can we get more wine?
Are you hungry?
Always.
Order room service,
anything you like,
and wine too.
Are you going to order food?
Yeah, sure.
Is everything okay?
Yeah, everything's fine.
Do you want me to make the call?
Who's this?
What were you doing in my purse?
Who is it?
Give me the photo, Gabriel.
Not until you tell me who it is.
My son.
The photo is of my son.
You didn't tell
me you had a son.
I don't have a son.
He looks like you.
Yeah.
That first night I saw you,
you looked so much like what
I imagined he might look like.
He drowned.
My husband was supposed
to be watching him,
but he got distracted
for two minutes.
That's all it took.
I tried to forgive him, but...
I don't think I ever really did.
I'm sorry, Martha.
Everyone says they're sorry,
I don't want you to be sorry.
I miss Luke so much.
Who's Luke?
My friend.
He couldn't handle it all.
Do you think
you can handle it all?
I don't think so.
Maybe he was warning you.
You believe that?
They don't ever really leave us.
Why don't we order
that room service?
Hey, Martha.
Hmm?
Can I sleep in your bed?
Of course.
You sure you want
me to let you off here?
Yeah, this is fine.
Well, okay, then.
So, what's happened?
Hey, Martha, it's, uh, Gabriel.
Just wanted to, uh...
Just call me back
if you get this voicemail.
Hey, Martha,
it's, uh... it's Gabriel again.
You haven't been
answering your phone,
so I just wanted just
see if you're okay.
Okay, uh...
What's going on, Gabriel?
Where you going this time,
Gabriel, huh?
I asked you a question.
Got any wallets on you, Gabriel?
Got any more wallets on you,
Gabriel?
- Huh? Got any more wallets?
- No, no.
- Answer me.
- No.
Got any wallets?
Fucking punk.
It's okay, it's okay.
I think I broke a rib.
Where are those bruises from?
I don't wanna talk about it.
Oh, you don't have to.
What are you writing?
I just have to take some notes.
Have you consumed any alcohol
or drugs in the past 24 hours?
No.
- No?
- I hate drugs.
Why is that?
Drugs killed my best friend.
Oh.
I'm so sorry to hear that.
It's a very painful situation.
Well, I'm glad to hear that
you're steering clear of it.
Um, have you ever
been paid for sex?
No.
No?
Um, you were brought
in from the district
that has a high
level of prostitution.
Do you wanna tell me the truth?
No.
All right.
Gabriel,
I know you feel so alone,
and I know it's a dark path,
but I want you to
know that I understand.
I've been down that path
and... I'm gonna
do everything I can
to get you
in a better place, okay?
Okay.
So... have you ever
been paid for sex?
- Okay.
- Yeah.
Thank you
for telling me the truth.
And where does that money go?
I send most of it
to my mom in Illinois.
Hmm.
You still care about your mom?
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
I'm sure she misses you.
Have you... have you called
her to talk to her?
No.
Is your mom in a situation?
The State of California
makes you ask these questions?
They don't make me ask anything.
I just...
I just want you to be better.
- Okay.
- Okay?
Okay.
Do you have any
employment prospects?
Yeah.
- You do?
- I have one.
Oh, that's fantastic.
You excited?
- If I get it.
- Yeah.
How could they
not give it to you?
- Oh, thanks.
- Hmm.
Well, it's a great first step.
I hope so.
This is for you, mademoiselle.
Thanks, Gabriel.
You got it.
I got you.
Gabriel.
Hey, how can I help you?
You look good.
Thank you, so do you.
You got a job.
Martha's assistant.
I knew I knew that face.
How is she?
Can... can I talk to you?
- Okay.
- Um...
Outside, please?
Okay, okay, gimme five,
I'll meet you out back.
Okay.
You good?