(tense, funky music)
(zipping)
(clicking)
(fist thudding)
(zipping)
♪ She tops the chart ♪
♪ She sings the best ♪
♪ The press will never let her
rest ♪
♪ She's famous ♪
♪ But this is just a face we see
♪
♪ She has one more identity ♪
♪ But hush ♪
(shushing)
♪ Leather boots and bustier ♪
♪ Is what she wears to get her
way ♪
♪ She's hot ♪
♪ Fighting crime and villainy ♪
♪ To save the music industry ♪
♪ She's tough ♪
♪ Sexina ♪
♪ She has the boobs ♪
♪ And the brains of a queen ♪
♪ She's every man's dream ♪
♪ And when you look in her eyes
♪
♪ You're hypnotized ♪
♪ Karate and tae kwon do ♪
♪ She'll kick your ass
before you know what hit ya ♪
(woman shouting
♪ She's wicked cool and that's a
fact ♪
♪ So evildoers watch your back ♪
♪ She'll get you ♪
♪ Sexina ♪
(upbeat pop music)
♪ Numero uno lover ♪
♪ You better run for come ♪
- This Lance Canyon song is so
cool!
- I know, totally.
- (laughs) Oh no,
look who's heading this way.
- [Girls] Vera.
- Hey guys.
- I think there's something
wrong with my ears.
I could swear that nerdy Vera
was trying to talk to us.
- Her breath always
smells like bacon bits.
(laughing)
(gasping)
- I was just going to ask you
guys
what you're listening to.
- We're listening to Lance
Canyon,
he's the coolest singer out now.
- No, he's not.
Sexina is the coolest singer out
there.
- How would you know what's
cool?
- Yeah, you suck.
Beat it porkchop!
(laughing)
(dramatic music)
- Stop laughing at me!
- Sexina, I'm glad you're here.
I need to talk to you.
- If it's about the incident
in the limo, I can explain.
- We have bigger problems than
that.
- What?
- I just watched an advance copy
of the new Lance Canyon
video, and it is hot.
- How hot?
- Piping hot.
- That hot?
- Hotter than my sweaty balls.
- I want to see it.
(wood thudding)
- Lance Canyon, you are
accused of the crime
of being totally awesome.
How do you plead?
- Guilty.
- In that case,
I'm giving you a life sentence
to party!
(upbeat music)
Yeah!
Lance, you're sexy for life!
- Don't you want to see the rest
of it?
- I think I've seen enough.
- Sexina, I don't think
you realize the impact
this video's gonna have.
Every teenager in the country
is going to want to buy his
album.
If you're not careful,
you could become yesterday's
news.
- You said the same thing two
years ago
about Sir-Stabs-A-Lot,
and his last album hardly made
the top 20.
Don't worry.
Lance Canyon, he'll come and go.
- Yeah, but I have a feeling
that when Lance comes,
he'll come with the thunder.
(thunder roaring)
- Yes, I am so close
to perfecting my ultimate
creation.
I must make sure that this time
it doesn't fall into the wrong
hands.
Who are you?
This is private property.
- Don't act stupid, professor!
How long did you think
you can hide from us?
- I see.
I'll tell you the same
thing I told your boss.
I quit.
- You can't quit!
The boss needs you.
And I'm here to take you with
me.
- Never.
Now, leave so that I can finish
my work.
(dramatic music)
- So, this must be your
daughter.
- Put that down!
- She looks barely legal.
She could have a long life.
Of course, that's if you
cooperate.
- Oh, dear.
- [Girls] Hi Vera!
- Hello.
- Don't be scared, Vera.
We just wanted to know if you
wanted
to have some breakfast with us.
- Really?
- We feel really bad about
yesterday.
- And we want to make it up to
you.
- Okay.
I would love to have
breakfast with you guys.
- I hope you like eggs!
(laughing)
(shrieking)
(crying)
(sad music)
- Why, oh, why?
(laughing)
- That was such a great idea,
Crystal.
- That was so funny!
- Oh, what can I say?
I'm beautiful and smart.
(laughs)
- [Girls] You so are!
- So Sal, how's it going with
the contest
I asked you to set up?
- Oh yeah, remind me about that
again.
- The one where I perform
for free at a high school.
- Why would you want to do that?
- Come on.
Can you do it or not?
- Relax, the posters should be
at all the high schools
around the country today.
- Oh.
(phone ringing)
- Hello?
- Sexina, it's Sara,
I need to talk to you.
- Okay, one sec.
- Hey, Sal, do you mind
giving me a second alone?
- Sure.
- Thanks.
(tense music)
- Okay Sara, what's up?
- Have you ever heard of
a Professor Van Bunson?
- Yeah, he was the lead singer
in the Van Bunson trio in the
'60s,
and then he just gave up
music to pursue science.
Actually, I think he's the
world's leading scientist
in robotics now.
- That's him.
His daughter just called me.
He's missing.
She wants us to track him down.
- Alright, I'm on it.
You get as much information you
can
from Van Bunson's daughter,
and I'll talk to my informants,
okay?
I'll be in touch.
- By the way, what are
you wearing right now?
- Why do you want to know that?
- Just curious.
- Okay.
(cheerful, dramatic music)
- Hope you're ready for the
big game against Madison.
- I'm going to give 120% coach.
- Atta'boy.
(grunting)
- Coach, I got a math
test in a few minutes.
I've gotta go look over my
notes.
- Math, huh?
Atta'boy.
- Coach, I really can't talk
right now.
- Alright, Zach, I'll see
you at practice tomorrow.
- [Zach] Alright, Coach.
- Atta'boy.
(metal thudding)
- Hey honey.
Where's my kiss before third
period?
- I got it right here,
beautiful.
(lips smacking)
- God, ugh.
I hate that boney bitch.
I would love to show her up.
(sighs) How?
(dreamy music)
It says here that the person
who writes the best essay
and gets the most signatures
from other students
will get to see Sexina
perform live at their school.
And get to spend an entire day
with her!
(sighs) This is it!
If I get Sexina to sing
here everyone will like me.
(zipping)
(tense, jazzy music)
(lighter clicking)
- What's up, Jay?
- Oh, man.
Every time you come around
you need something from me.
- What are you complaining
about?
You know I pay you.
- You want a hit off this?
- No, you know I don't smoke.
- That's a damn shame
'cause this some good shit.
This stuff could knock
Tommy Chong out for a week.
- Come on, enough small talk.
Let's get down to business,
I need some information.
- You're all business, alright.
Let's get to it.
- I'm looking for a missing
scientist.
Professor Van Bunson, have
you ever heard of him?
- No, what's he look like?
- Here, here's a picture.
- Yeah, I have seen this dude
before.
My memory's not so great on
account
of I'm such a pothead and all,
but...
Oh yeah, it was over at Glitz
Records.
I was over there selling some
he rb to Lance Canyon, and, uh.
- Wait, was the professor
doing at Glitz Records?
- He was working.
He's got his own office and
everything.
That's all I know.
- Alright.
Thanks for the info.
- Stay gold.
- See you later, Jay.
(tense music)
(grunting)
- [Boss] Oh, be gentle,
don't damage the goods.
Good, we have you back
in our grasp once again.
Back where you belong, at Glitz
Records.
- Please, listen to reason.
What you've been doing is wrong.
- [Boss] I don't care about
that,
all I care about is money and
boy bands.
Try to not to think about
it morally, numb nuts.
Just do what I tell you.
You know who will be
punished if you don't.
- I'm only doing this
to protect my daughter.
- [Boss] Whatever.
As long as you do it.
- I have one more thing to say.
That Lance Canyon album is
really hot.
- [Boss] Oh yeah, yeah, yeah,
Lance is pretty hot. (laughs)
I mean, his album's pretty hot,
but I'd like to see hotter.
It is your genius that will make
me
the richest CEO in the music
industry,
and no one can stop me.
- So how often do you look
at yourself in the mirror?
- Oh, not often, around 40 hours
a week.
- Why do you do this?
- I like to look at myself.
You know, sometimes I
wonder what it would be like
to be in someone else's body,
so I know how it feels
to have sex with me.
- Your song, You Need That Extra
Deep Love
got you in a lot of trouble
with the church groups
because the way you described
your penis.
- Look, I don't understand
why they're mad.
I mean, my penis was
touched by God. (chuckles)
They should just worship it.
- Your album is really,
really hot right now.
Do you think it will outsell
Sexina's latest album?
- Look, I think it's my
destiny to outsell that album.
I mean, Sexina was pretty good
in her day,
but it's time to move on.
People are ready for the next
big thing and, (chuckles)
that would be me.
(chuckling)
- Hey Lance, baby.
- Hey, What's Your Name.
(upbeat blues guitar music)
- Hey Stevie, how you doin'?
- Maude, it's great to see you.
- (shushing) Your voice.
I don't want anyone to know my
real name.
- Oh, maybe now you're
Sexina the famous pop star,
but to me you'll always be Maude
Jenkins,
the little girl I used
to bounce on my knee.
- I'm sorry I don't come
and see you anymore Stevie,
just after my dad died
I've just gotten so famous
I hardly have time for anything
else.
- Your father would be
proud of your success.
I wish he was here to see it.
- Me too.
You know, he's the one that
deserves all the success I have.
He was one of the best blues
guitar players in the world,
until the record company ripped
him off.
In all those years of playing
music
and he ended up penniless.
That's why I'm here doing what
I'm doing.
Stopping corruption and
evil in the music industry.
- And you're doing a great job.
It's good to know that
there's someone like you
sticking it to those fat cats.
(chuckling)
I know that you're a hard chick,
but I worry about you.
I promised your dad that
I would look after you.
Did he ever tell you how
we ended up raising you?
- Yeah, he told me all
about how my parents
were eaten by cannibals.
- (laughs) That's not the truth.
He told you that to make you
feel better.
You want to hear the real story?
Well, one night he was
walking home after a show.
(humming)
(baby crying)
- Was that a baby?
What you doing in there baby?
(retching)
(spitting)
(baby crying)
I'm sorry, baby.
I promise I won't do that again.
I wonder what happened to your
parents?
You really are beautiful.
Guess what?
You are coming home with
me tonight, little mama.
- And from that day on he's
raised you
like you're his own daughter.
- Why didn't he ever tell me
that?
- He'd rather have you think
that your parents were eaten by
cannibals
rather than know that they
tossed you in the trash.
He told you that because he
loved you.
- (sighs) Anyway, Stevie,
I need your help, okay?
I'm looking for a missing
scientist
whose name is Professor Van
Bunson.
He used to work at Glitz
Records.
Do you know anyone who works
there?
- I know somebody who works at
Glitz.
I'll have him call Sara,
and she can make an appointment.
- Thank you, Stevie!
Thank you for everything.
- It's no problem.
I'd do anything for Maude.
- What is she doing?
- Hey, would you sign this list
to get Sexina to sing at our
school?
- [Girl In Blue] Yeah,
sure, that sounds cool!
- What a lame attempt to
get people to like her.
- [Vera] Thanks.
- [Girl In Blue] No problem.
- How pathetic.
- I know, really.
- Hey beautiful.
- Hey gorgeous.
- Oh, cool, that girl is trying
to get Sexina to come here,
I'm gonna go sign up.
- Zach, I need you to take my
books
to my remedial math class.
- Sure.
- Now.
- Anything for you.
(dramatic music)
- I want you to know that we
have
our best person on the case.
She is tough, smart, and very
sexy.
She also the coolest
walk and a great smile.
(sighs) Anyway, we are very
dedicated
to finding your father.
- It feels so good to hear that.
The police haven't been much
help.
- Were you aware that your
father
used to work for Glitz Records?
- I know he was working
on a secret project,
but he wouldn't tell me for
whom.
Isn't Lance Canyon on Glitz
Records?
- Yes, he is.
- His album is really hot.
- Yes, very hot.
Does your father have any
enemies that you're aware of?
- He's a very sweet man.
Weird and nerdy, but sweet.
I can't imagine anyone hating
him.
- We think he might have been
kidnapped
by someone who wants to get
their hands
on his secret experiments.
(mysterious music)
(zipping)
- (gasps) Oh my God, Jay, are
you alright?
(dramatic music)
(gasping)
- It is unfortunate for
you that you're here.
I cannot let you leave alive.
- If anyone's going to die here
today,
it's going to be you.
- Women are not meant to fight.
They're meant to cook my
food and massage my feet.
- Oh, I'm going to fuck you up
twice as hard for that
statement.
- You cannot defeat me.
I'm a martial arts master.
(tense Asian music)
(glass shattering)
(grunting)
(intense music)
- Alright, tough guy, I
need to know who sent you.
- No, I won't tell you!
- Wrong answer!
- You will never know!
(groaning)
- Feel like talking yet?
I can break your balls for
hours.
- Okay, I was working for Glitz
Records.
- I need names!
- I would rather die than talk.
I will be dead in one second.
- Damn it!
Poisoned himself.
(tense music)
- [Boss] So, professor,
how's our little project coming
along?
- It will be finished in a few
days.
I must admit, it is my best
work.
- [Boss] Good, we're ahead
of schedule for once,
and I'm looking for some sexy
results.
The world will be amazed when
they see what we've done.
I will rule the music industry
thanks
to your newest and greatest
achievement.
No one will be able to oppose
me.
(upbeat music)
(audience applauds)
- In case you've just joined us,
I am talking to the pop
music sensation Sexina.
(audience cheering and
applauding)
So, I hear you're doing a big
contest.
Can you tell me a little about
it?
- Sure, Lauren.
Well, it's a contest for
high school students.
- Mm?
- The winner gets to
spend the day with me,
and then I perform for
free at their high school.
- I think that's terrific.
I always think it's good to
give something back to the fans.
Don't you agree?
- [Crowd] Yes!
(audience cheering and
applauding)
- Sexina, Lance Canyon's
album is climbing the charts.
Some people think that he's
gonna outsell your last album.
How do you feel about that?
- I'm fine with it.
I really think there's plenty of
room
in pop music for more than one
performer.
- [Crowd] Aww.
- I have to ask you this,
because everyone wants to know.
Are you seeing anybody?
- [Crowd] Ooh!
- No, I'm not.
- [Crowd] Oh.
- Really?
Such a beautiful girl with no
boyfriend.
- Well, I don't really have
time to go out and meet men,
I'm always working.
- That's sad.
- [Crowd] Oh.
- Anyway, it's time to take a
call
from one of your biggest fans.
Hello, you're on the air.
- Sexina, I think you are so
beautiful.
My question is would you ever
kiss a girl?
(crowd gasps)
- Sara, is that you?
(phone clicking)
(dial tone ringing)
- Well.
You really are a great talent,
th anks for being on the show.
- Thanks for having me.
- Our next guest is a man.
(audience jeering)
But he's an author who wrote a
bo ok
about how much he loves his
wife.
- [Crowd] Aww.
- But he loves watching
football.
(audience jeering)
- But he loves giving foot
massages.
- [Crowd] Whew!
- But he's cheap with money!
(audience groans)
We'll have him next after
this commercial break.
(upbeat music)
- [Man] We're clear!
- I can hardly believe
that such a beautiful girl
doesn't have a boyfriend.
- I know, it's just hard
for me to find a man
that really does it for me, you
know?
Someone that isn't
intimidated by my strength
and my intelligence, and
really has the same interests.
It's hard.
- I know just the guy for you.
He is a friend of my
husband and the two of you
could hit it off.
- Thanks Lauren, I appreciate
it,
but you know, I just don't
have the time right now.
I'm working on a huge case,
record,
and I'm just too busy.
- I am Lauren, and I don't
take no for an answer.
- [Man] And we're back in five,
four.
(slow jazz music)
- So, Ralph, what do you do for
a living?
- I'm an agent.
I represent Tom, Julia, the
Pitt.
All the big names, you know.
- Cool, do you like it?
- I have two summer homes, three
Bentleys.
What's not to like?
- I asked you if you like your
job,
not if you like the money.
- Isn't that the same thing?
(sighs)
- Do you listen to music?
- No, I don't listen to music.
- You don't?
I thought everyone listened to
music.
- Not me.
I like talk radio.
- Well, music is my life.
- Good for you.
- Hey, Sexina, what are you
doing here?
- Hey Sara, I'm on a blind date.
This is Ralph.
- Yeah, hi Ralph.
Um, so, I didn't know you were
dating.
- I'm not really, this is
just something Lauren set up.
- Lauren, huh?
- Uh, Sara, do you know
where the bathroom is?
- Yeah, it's at the back of
the restaurant on the left.
- Thanks, excuse me a second,
Ralph.
- No problem, I'm not going
anywhere.
- So, Ralph, is it?
- Yeah.
Um, I don't think you want to
date Sexina.
- Why not, she's hot?
- Yes, she is hot, but
she also has herpes.
- Really?
- Yes really, and not just
regular herpes,
we're talking hardcore, raging
herpes.
- Wow, thanks for telling me.
- No problem.
(patrons chattering)
- Sorry about that.
So, are you ready to order?
- Actually, something
came up, very important,
and I'm going to have to go.
- You can be honest with me
Ralph.
You're not my type either,
I know it's not working out.
- I'm not your type?
Who are you to talk?
- What's that supposed to mean?
- You can keep your herpes!
- What?
What the hell does that mean?
- I received an invitation for
you
to go to Lance Canyon's big
party tonight.
I think you should go.
You'll get a lot of free
publicity there.
- Sounds good, what time?
- Uh, it says get there at
eight,
so I would arrive about
midnight.
(upbeat jazzy music)
(crowd chattering)
- Do you think I'll get to
beat somebody up tonight?
- We're here to have fun
Chainsaw,
not to beat people up.
- Beating people up is fun.
(chuckling)
- Well, well, Sexina, glad
to see you could make it.
- I wouldn't miss this party,
Lance.
Especially when your album's so
hot.
- Oh, what can I say?
I got the goods.
- Such modesty.
- (chuckles) So um, who's your
friend?
- The name's Chainsaw.
- He's my bodyguard.
- Well, make sure you keep him
on a leash.
(growling)
- Relax, Chainsaw, relax.
And uh, who's your friend?
- Oh, her name is not important.
What's important, she's
a first rate skank.
(giggling)
- You really think I'm first
rate?
- Oh, yes baby, yes you are.
(speaks foreign language)
- Oh, you are so sweet.
(laughing)
- And the Bush twins are here
tonight,
have you ever met them before?
- No, I haven't.
- Oh girl, you should.
The two are magnificent whores.
(snorting)
- Anyway, Lance, um,
how do you like working at Glitz
Re cords?
- It's the best record label in
the world,
what's not to like?
Nah, I'm sorry guys,
but I must attend to my other
guests.
(laughing)
- Just say the word and I'll
give him
the beating of his life.
- Yeah, really.
That's alright Chainsaw,
it's not necessary.
Didn't Lance Canyon do a public
service
announcement against drugs?
- Yes he did.
I remember the slogan.
Lance don't need weed to
succeed.
(sighing)
Pee-ew!
- What a scumbag.
- Hey, everybody.
Let's have a round of applause
for the man
who's throwing this great party
tonight.
Lance Canyon!
(cheering and applauding)
Share some words with the good
people.
- I want to thank you all
for attending my party.
Hey, there's still
plenty of weed, cocaine,
and ecstasy for everyone.
As well as heroin, crystal meth,
horse tranquilizers, vicodin,
xanax,
modern igloo, yellow
jackets, black beauties.
You guys name it, and we got it.
(laughing)
- [Man] Yo, I love this guy,
he's awesome.
- You know Chainsaw,
as much as I can't stand
the guy, he is kind of cute.
- Oh, I hate cute.
- Now, I want you all to give a
big,
big round of applause for
another big star
that's in the house tonight.
The one and only Sexina.
(applauding)
Sexina, I am so glad that I can
tell you,
and everyone else here the great
news.
My brand new album has just
outsold yours.
(applauding)
I am now the biggest star in pop
music.
(laughing)
- Chainsaw, I've had enough.
Let's get out of here.
- And, fellas, I'm going
to do your ladies tonight.
(laughing)
- Pick me, Lance!
- Me first!
- Thank you!
- Hey.
I wanted to sign your list.
- Great, umm.
(tense music)
Here you go.
- I'm so glad you're doing this.
I am such a big Sexina fan.
- So am I.
- I've seen you around.
What's your name?
- I'm Vera.
- My name's Zach.
- I know. (laughs)
You're quarterback of the
football team.
- I hope you don't think
I'm some dumb jock.
- No, I don't think that at all!
- That's good to hear.
Everyone thinks I'm
this big football hero,
which is fine and everything,
but,
I wonder if anyone will ever
know
that I have this fondness
for French poetry,
or how passionate I am
about animal rights.
- I think it's great to
have lots of interests.
- Thanks.
You know Vera, you're pretty
cool.
- I think you're pretty cool
too.
- I'll see you around.
- See you around, Zach.
- Zach, you've been working out,
huh?
Atta'boy.
- Vera like, mm.
- Mm, Coach like.
(tense music)
- [Boss] Good, you're here, have
a seat.
- You needed to see me?
- [Boss] Yes, I have a job for
you.
- What is it?
- [Boss] I want you to
take care of the man
we hired to kidnap Van Bunson.
- What do you mean, take care of
him?
- [Boss] Oh, don't act so naive,
Lance.
I want you to kill him.
- Hey, hey, hold on, alright?
Hey, I'm a musician, not a
killer.
- [Boss] You'll be
anything I want you to be.
- I won't do it.
- [Boss] Lance, Lance, testicle
brains,
don't forget that I'm the
one who signs your checks.
I am the one who owns
your houses and your cars,
and I can make those things go
away.
And if those things go away,
the women will go away too.
- Hey, hey, hey!
Not the women, not the women.
Fine, I'll do it, but I don't
like it.
- Hey, uh, Lance.
Thanks for having me over.
- Uh, yeah, cool man.
Hey, you want something to
drink?
- Yeah, sure, I'll have a drink,
thanks.
- Huh, yeah, yeah, cool man.
Um, do you know by any
chance why you're here?
- No, the boss just told me to
come over.
- Oh, well, you did such
a good job kidnapping
Van Bunson that he asked me
to take care of you, man.
- Really?
- [Lance] Yeah.
- We going to get some
hookers or something? (laughs)
- (chuckles) Well, not exactly.
- No hookers?
- Not today.
(grunting)
(dramatic music)
(coughing)
- Would you stop strangling me?
(dramatic music)
How many times are you
going to strangle me?
- I thought you'd be dead by
now!
- Well, I'm not.
(dramatic music)
(heavy breathing)
(coughing)
(dramatic music)
- Well, why didn't you use
that in the first place?
- Sorry man, I'm new at this.
(gun firing)
(upbeat pop music)
♪ Sexina ♪
♪ Dangerous Sexina ♪
♪ Dangerous ♪
♪ Undercover ♪
- Oh, cut!
♪ Sexina ♪
- Sal, come on, I can't do this.
- What's the matter?
It's going so well.
- You think this is going well?
This video is fucking stupid.
- Hey, listen, watch your
language
in front of the Jesus, okay?
- That's another thing.
Why is Jesus in my video?
- 'Cause Jesus is hot right now.
Jesus sells.
- (sighs) But it makes no sense
why he's on the beach with me.
- He's just doing a couple
rap verses for your video.
- I don't want a rapping
Jesus in my video!
- Why not?
Listen, people love rap.
People love Jesus.
Put the two together, and I
smell a hit.
- I smell your bullshit.
- Alright, just listen
to the guy, alright?
Come here.
(sighing)
- Do that rap part.
- Come on!
♪ Yo, everywhere I go ♪
♪ The people love me ♪
♪ I'm the dopest of them all ♪
♪ I'm the rapping JC. ♪
- Sal.
Jesus doesn't rap.
Jesus doesn't build a sand
castle,
and Jesus would never, ever wear
a thong.
This video is so over, I'm
leaving!
- Sexina, wait!
- Who the hell does she think
she is?
I'm Jesus Christ, bitch!
(phone ringing)
(loud sipping)
- Hello?
- Hey Sara, it's Stevie.
- Hey Stevie, what can I do for
ya ?
- Actually, it's more like
what I can do for you.
I know a guy who works
down at Glitz Records,
and he's got some information
he'd like to share
with you and Sexina.
For a price of course.
- That's great news.
I'll let her know right away.
Thanks so much, Stevie.
- Just remember to tell her
to meet him at Rosco's Chicken
Pit,
tomorrow at noon.
She'll recognize him because
he's the guy
with the eye patch.
(dreamy music)
(upbeat rock music)
- So you the man I'm supposed to
meet?
- Yes, I am.
I wasn't expecting such a
beautiful woman.
- Enough with the flattery.
I came here because I was told
you could give me what I need.
Let's get down to it.
- Wow, you move really fast.
Don't you think we should
slow down a little bit.
I mean, get to know each other
fi rst.
- Why do you want to get
to know each other first?
- Because it's the polite thing
to do.
- You know what I'm here for.
Are you going to give it to me
or not?
- Of course I'm going to
give it to you. (chuckles)
I can't wait to give it to you.
Where do you want to do it?
I mean, we could go to a hotel
or we could go to your place.
We can't go to my place,
because I still live with my
parents.
- Why do you want to go
somewhere else?
Why can't we just do it right
here?
- You want to do it right here?
- Yeah.
I want to do it right here.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah, I'm sure.
Come on, enough with the small
talk.
Let's get down to business.
- Do you want me to
show you what I've got?
- Do you have something to show
me?
- Oh yeah. (chuckles)
Oh yeah, I've got something to
show you.
Do you want to see it?
- Yeah, I want to see it.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- Right now?
- Right here, right now.
Come on, show me what you got.
- Okay, alright.
- Wait, what are you doing?
No, what, ugh!
Ugh, what are you doing?
- I'm giving you what you want.
- I don't want that.
- Hey, over here.
- Who the hell are you?
- Aren't you Debbie, my blind
date?
- No!
- Then where's my date?
- Are you Phil?
- Yeah, I am, are you Debbie?
- You're sick, and tiny.
(laughing)
- I'm a grower, not a shower.
Hey, wait!
(tense music)
- So much for being
inconspicuous.
- Alright, so what have you got
for me?
- First things first.
Where's the money?
- What happened to your eye?
- Nothing.
I just wear this to look
cool for the ladies.
- Okay.
So what do you know?
- I saw the professor at Glitz
Records.
He came out of the president's
office.
- What do you think they're
using him for?
- Cyborg robots.
- Why on earth would
they want him for that?
- I don't know, that's
up to you to find out.
- Do you think Lance Canyon is
involved?
- Lance is definitely involved.
He's tight with the boss,
and he has access to the
professor.
Also, his album is really,
really--
- If you say really hot,
I will break your nose.
- Okay, relax.
I guess you're not a Lance
Canyon fan.
- Have you ever actually seen
the president of Glitz Records?
- No, he never leaves
his penthouse office.
- That's so strange.
Why would a CEO of a major
record label
keep such a low profile?
- I don't know,
but only a select few
have actually seen him.
He moves in the shadows.
- It's very suspicious.
(tense music)
I broke into Lance Canyon's
house
looking for some more clues.
Since he is Glitz Record's
golden boy,
I wanted to know how involved
he's been
in Van Bunson's kidnapping,
and what the hell this is all
about!
(dramatic music)
(door creaking)
- Hm.
I guess I'm hearing things.
- [Woman] Lance, come back to
bed!
- Okay, but I hope you're ready
for that
all-you-can-eat Lance buffet.
(tense music)
- Hey Vera.
How's the contest going?
- Well I got all the signatures
I need.
- That's great news.
- Yeah, except now I have to
write an essay about myself,
and I'm having a hard time with
it.
I mean, how much can a person
write
about Paula Abdul and unicorns?
- Yeah, it's hard to look
deep down inside yourself.
I know it is for me,
but you're a really cool and
smart person.
I'm sure you'll be able
to write a great essay.
- Thanks, Zach.
- No problem.
(sighing)
I have to go.
I almost forgot, I have
to carry Crystal's books
to her remedial English class.
See you later.
(dreamy music)
- I know exactly what I'm
going to write my essay about.
I'm a student at Britney High
School.
I'm what most people
would describe as a loser.
I don't drink or smoke.
I am not a beautiful
cheerleader.
I don't have any friends.
Actually, I spend most of my
time learning
and trying to get into a good
college.
There's this popular girl named
Crystal
that always makes fun of me.
She calls me names like
fatty and lard-ass.
I really hate the way she
and her friends treat me.
There's also this boy I really
like.
His name is Zach.
I think he could fall in love
with me,
but he's dating that total bitch
Crystal.
Please pick me as the winner
so I can teach that snobby bitch
and her friends a lesson.
Oh, and I really want to see
Zach naked.
And have sex with him.
- I think we found our winner.
(tense music)
- I have accomplished
wh at you asked of me.
- [Boss] Very good,
we're ahead of schedule.
- Lance, listen to me.
You must not be a part of
this diabolical scheme.
- Sorry professor, but I
care about money and women.
(chuckles) And you offer me
neither.
Hey boss, I've got to leave,
man.
I've got to meet Paris in ten
minutes.
I've got some boning to do.
(groaning)
- Please, I beg you.
Don't do this--
- [Boss] Enough!
Do I have to remind you
what I'm capable of?
- Here they are.
(dramatic music)
I call them Top That.
They are the ultimate
in cyborg technology.
You can program them to sing,
dance,
act, or speak in any way you
want them to.
Never again will you have
to find real human beings
to mold into stars.
They will follow your every
command,
and learn a song or a dance move
with the flick of a switch.
They are the ultimate pop group.
- Oh, you've really outdone
yourself, professor.
Tell me about each member of the
group.
- Dustin is the young, cute one.
Then there's Jake, he's a bad
boy.
The one with the dreadlocks is
G-Dog,
he loves reggae, so you know
he's down.
Then there's Anarchy Al,
he's a punk rocker who
hates authority figures.
- [Boss] Mm, they look yummy.
Especially that Dustin.
I want to see them in action.
- Okay boys.
Hit it.
(upbeat pop music)
♪ My love for you is so deep ♪
♪ It's deeper than the deep blue
sea ♪
♪ Ooh baby do you understand ♪
♪ That you and me equals we ♪
♪ We, we, we ♪
♪ No one can stop the two of us
♪
♪ We, we, we ♪
♪ In you girl, I do trust ♪
♪ We can listen to punk
on the school bus ♪
♪ We, we, we ♪
♪ You and me equals we ♪
- Word to life, boo.
- [Boss] Oh, they're perfect.
Especially Dustin.
Everyone from teenage girls
to horny Catholic priests will
love them.
I'll start informing the
press about them right away.
The world has been craving
a group like Top That.
More than crack.
- Good God, what have I done?
(dramatic music)
(dreamy music)
- Zach!
What are you doing?
- Oh, nothing.
- Tell me how beautiful I am.
- You're the most
beautiful girl in the world
- You're right.
I am the most beautiful girl in
the world.
- I think I'm going to be sick.
- I just decided that I'm going
to let you
take me out to an
expensive dinner tonight.
- I don't have the money
for that, maybe next week.
I have an idea.
Let's make a picnic basket
and eat underneath the stars.
- (sighs) I don't think so.
Find a way to get the money
and pick me up at seven.
Okay, toodles.
(upbeat dance music)
- Hey, what's up everybody?
Welcome to Cool TV.
I'm your host Onski,
and today I'm going to introduce
to you
the next big thing in pop music.
From the people that
brought you Lance Canyon
comes this amazing new group,
Top That!
Yeah!
(audience cheering)
I want to introduce you
first to the members.
Dustin.
- I'm just a sensitive guy who's
looking
for the right girl to give my
love to.
- Aw, what a sweetie!
And next, we have Jake.
- You girls, you don't want
to get too close to me,
'cause I'm a heartbreaker.
- Wicked man, yeah.
Yo, yo, yo, give it up for
G-Dog!
- Ya mon, I like smokin'
the trees and reggae beats.
- Whoa.
And finally, Anarchy Al.
- I don't give a shit about
you, or this fuckin' show.
- Yeah!
This is it, the guys of Top
That.
We here at Cool TV think
th ey're totally crunk.
In fact, they crunked in
at a 10 on our crunk meter.
So tune in tomorrow for the
world premiere
of their crunktastic new
video, Love on the Deep End.
- Oh my God!
That group is going to be the
biggest thing in musical
history.
We need to do some damage
control, quick.
We have to make sure that you're
twice as cool as Top That.
- But there's something
strange about them.
I can't put my finger on it,
though.
- All I know is those guys
could put us out of business.
- Anyway, I'd rather
talk about the contest.
I picked a winner, her name is
Vera,
and she goes to Britney High.
- Great, I'll inform the school.
- Okay, thanks.
- Sexina, you're going to have
to face Top That eventually.
They're sexy and they know it,
and that's a lethal combination.
- Don't worry, everything will
be fine.
Top That has got nothing on me.
(dramatic music)
- [Zach] Hey Vera.
- You probably think that
note was pretty lame.
- No, actually, I thought
it was pretty sweet.
- Where's the but?
- But I have a girlfriend,
so I can't date anyone.
- Can't you just be honest
and tell me you don't want to
date me
because you don't find me
attractive.
- Vera, that's not true,
I do find you attractive.
I just happen to be in a
committed relationship.
I really enjoy your company,
and I want us to be friends.
- Okay, that sounds cool.
We can be friends.
- Good.
I have to go.
I volunteer at this animal
shelter.
I think of all those cute little
animals that need my help.
(sighs) It just tears me apart
inside.
I've gotta go.
See you later.
- Later, Zach.
(sigh) Friends, my ass.
I'm gonna get me a piece
of that sweet booty.
(upbeat blues rock music)
- I'm really glad to see
you're still in one piece.
- Come on, I'm a tough
chick, you know that.
- I know.
I've got a bad feeling about
this case.
I think you're in a little over
your head.
- I know, but I can't quit now.
- I knew you'd say that.
- I got really good
information from your guy
at Glitz Records, thank
you for arranging that.
- I'm glad I could help.
Do you remember when me and your
dad
tried to get you to listen
to some Robert Johnson,
but all you cared about was
Madonna?
(laughing)
- He would get so mad at me.
I wish he was here with us right
now.
- Me too.
Can I get you a beer?
- No, no, no, I've got to go,
thank you.
- Oh, I understand.
You're a busy woman.
(dramatic music)
Please, consider giving up this
case.
I don't want anything happening
to you.
- [Sexina] I'll be fine.
- Maude, down!
(dramatic music)
- Not you Stevie!
(dramatic, funky music)
(gasping)
(grunting)
(bear roaring)
(groaning)
- No, bear!
Stop, please!
I have great respect for your
kind.
I give thousands of dollars
to Save the Bears every year,
please stop attacking that man,
I need to get information from
him.
(roaring)
No, please!
(screaming)
Step away from my witness!
This bear is killing my witness!
- Mom, you should knock
before you come into my room.
- I'm sorry honey, I
got so excited I forgot.
- What is it, mom?
- There's a boy here to see you.
- What?
- And he's cute.
- Who is it?
- His name is Zach.
- Zach?
Is here now, in my house?
- Yes!
I'm going to send him right up.
- Oh, just don't embarrass me.
- Here you go Zach, this is
Vera's room.
- Thanks.
Hey Vera.
- Hi.
- Well, I'll just leave you two
alone.
- She's great, my mom is the
same way.
- Have a seat.
- Well, I came by because we
have
this big math test tomorrow,
and I thought maybe
you might be able to help me
study?
- Yeah, of course.
- Oh, I didn't know you
were into French poetry!
- Yeah, I love it.
- That is so cool!
- Yeah.
I have to go downstairs
and get my math book.
- Oh, do you have a
calculator I could borrow?
- Oh sure, there should be one
in my desk.
- Thanks.
(laughing)
(buzzing)
- Hey Zach, atta'boy.
(gasping)
(sighing)
- I brought you my, vibrator!
Soda pop?
Vera?
(phone ringing)
- Hello?
- Sara, it's me.
Did you get the results
of the fingerprints?
- They belong to a guy
named Richard Flack.
He did five years at San
Quentin for kidnapping.
- I knew it.
He kidnapped professor Van
Bunson for Glitz Records,
and then they had him
killed so he wouldn't talk.
The president of Glitz
Records must be the one
that's pulling all the strings.
Sara, an assassin just tried to
kill me.
- Oh no, Sexina, are you
alright?
- I'm fine, but the assassin's
dead.
He got mauled by a bear before I
could
get any information out of him.
- Fucking bears!
- Sara, he killed Stevie.
- Oh my God, Sexina.
I'm so sorry.
But listen, we have to act fast.
Van Bunson's daughter is getting
worried
that we're not going to find her
father.
- I know, I have to come up with
a plan.
I need to meet with the
contest winner today,
but I'll call you after that.
- Should we inform the police?
- Don't say anything, we have
to handle this ourselves.
They could be on the Glitz
Record payroll.
Just tell Rachel we're very
close
to getting her father back,
okay?
- Be careful.
I don't know what I would do if
anything
happened to that hot body of
yours.
- Congratulations, Vera!
- Congratulations for what?
- Didn't you hear?
They just announced it in the
cafeteria.
- I never eat in the cafeteria.
- You won the Sexina contest.
- Really?
- Yes, and she's coming here
this afternoon to meet you.
- That rules!
- Oh, I can't believe that total
pig Vera
is talking to your man, Crystal.
- Yeah, she better check
herself.
- Looks like I have to
teach bacon bits a lesson.
(grunting)
- I can't believe I'm going
to get to meet Sexina.
- I knew you could do it.
- Zach, what are you doing?
- Oh, I'm just talking to Vera.
You know her, right?
- Yeah, I know her, but I
don't actually talk to her.
- Why not?
- 'Cause she's a loser!
- [Girls] Duh.
- Hey, that's mean.
- Don't be stupid, Zach.
You know she's pathetic.
Why do you think she sits
out here for lunch every day?
Because nobody likes her.
- I'm sorry about this, Vera.
She's totally out of line.
- It's okay, I'm used to it.
She talks to me like this every
day.
- Is that true?
Answer me, is that true?
- Of course it's true.
I mean, just look at her.
- I think she's pretty.
- [Girls] What?
- Are you serious?
She's so ugly!
- Right now, you look like the
ugly one.
- Yeah, you ugly bitch!
- Yeah, consider yourself
dumped, Crystal.
- Are you fucking kidding?
- You heard me, it's over.
- Ugh, you are so going
to regret this, Zach.
- Why don't you go home
and cry yourself to sleep?
- You know what, have fun with
lard ass.
Be careful, she just might eat
you.
- Isn't it time for you
to go throw up your lunch?
(screaming)
- [Crystal] God!
(tense music)
- Man, I can't wait to
until I start my world tour.
I'm going to be knee deep in
pussy.
And with Top That opening up for
me,
it's going to be the
biggest tour in history.
- [Boss] Oh, Lance, yes, yes.
It'll be the biggest tour in
history,
but I have some changes in mind.
- What kind of changes?
- [Boss] Top That is going to
headline it,
and you're going to be the
opening act.
- What?
How dare you, huh?
I'm Lance Canyon.
The hottest singer and the
best piece of ass in pop music.
- [Boss] Oh, hey Lance.
Dustin has twice the ass you do.
- My ass cannot be topped.
I'm number one, you got that?
Numero uno.
I open up for no one.
- [Boss] You're right, Lance.
You're number one, today.
But once Top That's album comes
out,
you're going to be yesterday's
news.
- Hmm, no, you're wrong.
I'll be number one forever.
- [Boss] Oh, Lance.
Your stupid mind doesn't get it.
Top That is the next big thing.
Today I'm going to have them
crash the free Sexina concert.
When they upstage her at her own
show,
the media will be all over them.
Top That will be ten times
bigger
than you are Lance, baby.
I'm afraid your 15 minutes are
almost up.
You should consider yourself
lucky to
open up for newest pop
sensation.
- That wasn't part of our deal.
- [Boss] I'm changing the deal,
and if I were I'd pray I
don't change it any further.
(heavy breathing)
- Hi, you must be Vera.
- I love you, I'm your biggest
fan!
- Nice to meet you, too.
This is my bodyguard, Chainsaw.
- Hi Chainsaw!
- Oh oh!
Touch me and I'll kill you.
- Is he always like this?
- Yes, he is.
So, would you like to go to
lunch?
- Would I?
(upbeat music)
This is so cool.
I can't believe I'm having lunch
with you.
(laughing)
- Thank you.
- Hey Sexina, can I have
your autograph please?
- Sure.
- [Waiter] Thanks.
- So tell me about you, Vera.
- What do you want to know?
- Is there a boy at school that
you like?
Oh, so there is a boy.
- Yeah, his name is Zach, and
he's so hot.
- Sounds awesome.
Does he know that you like him?
- Yeah, but he's really popular,
and he was dating the
coolest girl in school.
- Was dating?
Wait, is he single now?
- Yeah.
He broke up with his girlfriend
today.
- Well now's your chance.
- I know, but oh no, he
would never want to date me.
Guys never want to date me.
- Vera, listen to me.
I have to be honest with you.
I personally read your essay.
I already know about Zach
and the mean girls at school
and how they're always bullying
you
I picked you, Vera, because I
admire you.
- You admire me?
- Yeah, it took so much
courage to write that down
and express how you feel.
You're stronger than you think,
Vera.
- Maybe I am, but I still
wish Zach wanted to date me.
- Whew, stuffed!
You know what?
I have an idea.
You know what cheers me
up more than anything?
- Your dildo?
- No, shopping!
(upbeat pop music)
♪ Two girls out on the town ♪
♪ Their feet won't touch the
ground ♪
♪ Heads are turning all around ♪
♪ New clothes, new clothes ♪
♪ We'll take a break from school
♪
♪ Buy a dress that looks real
cool ♪
♪ Having a vagina rules ♪
♪ There's no stopping ♪
♪ Two girls shopping ♪
♪ New clothes make the world go
'round ♪
♪ There's no stopping ♪
♪ Two girls shopping ♪
♪ New clothes make the world go
'round ♪
♪ Shop ♪
♪ Shop until we drop ♪
- Wasn't that fun?
- Yeah, but you didn't buy me
anything.
- Vera, listen to me.
You don't need a new
dress to look beautiful.
You're already beautiful.
Just the way you are.
- But you bought like, 20
dresses.
- I'm talking about you, not me.
Alright, I'm just kidding.
Here you go.
Zach will not be able
to resist you in that.
- Thanks Sexina, you rule!
(tense music)
(car horn honking)
(brakes screeching)
(metal crashing)
- When am I going to be
released?
- You'll be released
when the boss says so.
- Please, have some mercy,
I want to see my daughter.
- I've heard enough from you,
so shut up or I'll shut you up.
(thudding)
- Come on professor, I'm
getting you out of here.
(crowd chattering)
- Today is the great day.
Sexina is about to perform for
all of you.
(audience cheering)
As your principal I must
stress that everyone
must behave in a civilized
ma nner.
This is a school and we want to
show
that all of you are mature young
adults.
- [Boy In Audience] One, two,
three.
- [Boys] These nuts!
(audience laughs)
- Very funny.
Please give a round of
applause for our opening act,
Boaz.
(upbeat dance music)
(cheering)
♪ I'll be yours tonight ♪
♪ Tell me if you're feeling down
♪
♪ The music going to lift you up
♪ Funk you up, turn you 'round ♪
♪ Every time you hear that sound
♪
♪ Music going to lift you up ♪
♪ Funk you up, turn you 'round ♪
♪ Crazy 'cause it feels so good
♪
♪ Like a remedy, it's a cure ♪
♪ Workin' like it should ♪
♪ Come on DJ, play my song ♪
♪ Catch the melody, feel the
beat ♪
♪ Turn me on ♪
♪ Dance with me if the rhythm's
right ♪
♪ Take a chance with me ♪
♪ I'll be yours tonight ♪
♪ Dance with me if the feeling's
strong ♪
♪ Take a chance with me ♪
♪ I'll turn you on ♪
- Sexina, I can't tell
you how happy we are
to have you here.
- My pleasure.
This is my bodyguard Chainsaw.
- Nice to meet you, Chainsaw.
- I want you to know that if
any of your students act up
I'll be more than happy to
take care of them for you.
- I might actually take you up
on that.
I wish all of students
could be like our Vera here.
- Thanks Principal Matthews.
- She is the one that
made all this possible.
- You told me you were
close to finding my father.
- We are, we just need a little
more time.
- You have had enough time.
I want my father found now,
and why are there pictures
of Sexina all over the walls?
- (gasping) Daddy!
- I love you, Princess!
- I have been so worried about
you!
- The president of Glitz
Records kidnapped me.
He made me build a cyborg boy
band.
- Do you mean Top That?
- Yes, they're robots.
They have been scientifically
cr eated
to be the ultimate boy band.
- Yeah, we must destroy them
before they take over the world.
- Aren't you in on this plot,
Lance?
- He was, but then he helped me
escape.
- How do we know we can trust
him?
- Look, I know I've
been an ass in the past,
but I changed.
I don't want to be a criminal no
more.
Criminals go to jail,
and chicks in jail have penises.
- How did you find us, father?
- I had a chip implanted in the
back
of your head when you were a
child,
so that I would always
know where you were.
- Wow, dad, that's pretty
creepy.
- What did you expect?
I'm a scientist.
- Come on guys, we've got to
get down to the high school.
- Why?
Is Sexina in danger?
- Look, Top That's going to
crash the show
and try to outperform
her, and if that happens,
they'll be impossible to stop.
♪ Dance with me ♪
♪ If the rhythm's right ♪
♪ Take a chance with me ♪
♪ I'll be yours tonight ♪
♪ Dance with me ♪
♪ If the feeling's strong ♪
♪ Take a chance with me ♪
♪ I'll turn you on ♪
♪ I'll be yours tonight ♪
(audience cheering and
applauding)
- Wasn't that great?
Today reminds me of when
I was in high school
and the Osmonds came to perform.
- [Boy In Audience] Lick
my balls, you jackass!
(audience laughs)
- Chainsaw, would you take care
of that?
- My pleasure!
- Now, without further ado,
the one and only Sexina!
(audience cheering)
- Sexina!
- What is up Britney High?
(cheering)
Now before we get started,
I want to bring out a friend of
mine.
She is the reason that I'm here
today.
Everyone, give it up for Vera!
(audience cheering and
applauding)
(groaning)
- Alright, now it's time to get
busy.
(audience cheering and
applauding)
(dramatic electronic music)
- Yo, I don't think so, Sexina.
- Look, it's Top That.
(audience cheering and
applauding)
- Top That?
What are you guys doing here?
- We'll show you.
♪ Whoa, whoa, whoa oh oh oh ♪
♪ Sensitive romantic ♪
- I'm a wild stallion you can't
tame.
- I want to kill my parents.
- I really wish I was black.
- [Audience] Aww.
- Well I'm too hot for you guys
to handle.
- That's enough!
(audience cheering)
- Lance Canyon!
- So you came here to
help your friends, huh?
- No, I'm here to help you.
And trust me, you're going to
need me.
- I don't need your help.
I can handle these chumps on my
own.
- Yo, are you with us
or against us, Lance?
- I'm with Sexina, and you know
what?
I think it's about time
people knew about your secret.
- You wouldn't dare, biotch.
- Oh yeah?
- Well not only is G-Dog
not really from Jamaica,
he's also a robot.
(crowd gasps)
(crowd screaming)
(electricity crackling)
- So that's why the
professor was kidnapped.
To create a boyband made out of
cyborgs.
- That's right, biotch.
- One thing I don't get though
is,
why would you help me, Lance?
- Well, because Top That could
become more popular than me.
- You really betrayed us, Lance,
and that really hurts my
feelings.
- Yeah, so we're going to
have to kill all you fuckers.
- Chainsaw, you have my
permission to kick some ass.
- I want a piece of the
bodyguard.
- Finally I get to beat someone
up.
(upbeat jazzy music)
(fist thudding)
(grunting)
- Oh, not my face, my beautiful
face!
- God I love hitting you!
(whimpering)
(grunting)
(groaning)
- If you want Sexina, you're
going to have to go through me.
- Vera!
- Okay.
- Quick, someone throw me a
football!
Thanks!
(grunting)
(screaming)
- Oh shit!
- Vera, are you okay?
- I'll be alright, keep
fighting.
- Don't worry Sexina,
I'll take care of her.
- You're a good man, Zach.
(dramatic music)
- Sexina!
- What, Sara?
- I need to tell you something.
- I love--
(electronic beeping)
(electricity crackling)
(buzzing)
- I'm too sensitive for this!
- Pretty boy.
- It's time to die now.
- Quick, somebody get me a
guitar.
- Here you go, dude.
- Thanks, man.
I'm going to rock you
harder than a hurricane.
(intense electronic guitar
music)
- You're next in line for
an ass whooping, pretty boy.
- No, I beg you, please don't
hurt me, no!
- Shut up.
- I'm not ready to rock.
- Hurting you makes my dick
hard.
- Rock overload.
(electricity crackling)
(buzzing)
- Hell yeah!
(audience cheering)
- Looks like we took care of Top
That.
- I've got it, dude.
- Thanks, man, here you go.
- Amazing, you guys defeated Top
That.
- Professor, how did you escape?
- Lance broke me out.
Thanks to him I've been reunited
with my lovely daughter.
- I'm never going to let you
out of my sight again, daddy.
- That's so nice, Lance.
Guess I was wrong about you.
- Look, I know now that
what I was doing was wrong.
I'm going to fight on the
si de of good from now on.
(fists thudding)
- Good to hear that.
- Was that good for you?
It's good for me.
- Chainsaw!
(electricity crackling)
Chainsaw, you can stop now,
I think he's dead.
- But I wasn't even tired yet.
- Sexina!
- Oh, Sara, are you okay?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
I'm just glad to see you alive.
- I'm glad to see you're okay
too, Sexina.
- That's so sweet, Lance.
(dramatic music)
- That was very brave
of you to stay and help.
- I had to.
You see Vera, I realized
something today.
- What is it, Zach?
- I know now that I love you.
- Oh, Zach!
I love you too.
- [Audience] Aww.
- Zach, I can't believe my ears!
Have you lost your mind?
You're supposed to be my man!
You're supposed to be loving me,
remember?
I'm hot and I won't let you dump
me
for this fat, stupid loser.
- You know what Crystal?
I have had enough of you.
(grunting)
(crowd murmuring)
How do you like me now, bitch?
(audience laughs)
- She got beat down!
(peaceful music)
- Wow Vera, I'm really glad
yo u stood up to her like that.
- Yeah Vera, that was a
first rate ass kicking.
- Yeah!
- I really do love you.
- I know.
- See, Vera, I knew you'd get
your man,
because you were--
- Yeah, beautiful all along, I
get it.
- I've been wanting to do this
all day.
(crowd whistling and cheering)
(moaning)
(mellow, funky music)
(crowd shouting)
- They're in love, huh?
That's what I really want,
Sexina.
To be just like the two of them.
- I thought all you really
wanted was
to have sex with any
woman that would let you.
- I just did that to fill
the empty void in my heart.
All I really want is to fall in
love.
- I avoid falling in love
by working all the time.
- Maybe we're not as
different as you think we are.
- Maybe not.
(crowd cheering)
- Sexina, why would you kiss
Lance?
- I can't explain it, Sara,
I just feel a connection with
him.
- So do I, Sexina.
You're my soul mate.
- But what about me, Sexina?
- Don't worry Sara, you'll
find a man of your own one day.
- Ooh!
- I've had enough.
(dramatic music)
Do you really think I'd let
you get away with this, hm?
You've destroyed my plan to
take over the music industry.
Top That with sweet, sweet
Dustin,
was gonna take the world by
storm
and provide me with
power beyond imagination.
Now that you've killed my dream,
I must kill all of you.
Starting with my daughter,
Sexina.
(crowd gasps)
- What?
- Who would have thought the
little girl
I threw away in a garbage
can all those years ago
would grow up to trash all my
pl ans.
- You're lying.
- I killed your mother,
but I didn't have the
heart to kill you, Sexina.
Of course, I would live to
regret that.
I have to admit though, I was
proud of you
when you became such a big star.
I always kept track of you.
I guess I always thought
in the back of my mind
you would want revenge
for what I did to you.
- You can't be my father.
- Oh, search your heart Sexina.
You know it to be true.
- Then why did you kill my
mother?
- She never supported my
plans for world domination.
She wanted me to get a
nine-to-five job like a square!
So I shot her.
Just like I'm going to shoot
you.
- Kill me instead!
(crowd gasps)
- Settle down, brown eyes.
I'm going to kill all of you
Lance.
I'm sorry but my daughter
will have the honor of dying
first.
- If I really am your daughter,
I bet you won't be able to kill
me now
just like you couldn't do it
then.
- Oh, I'm sorry, but you're
wrong.
(gun clicking)
(crowd gasping)
(gun firing)
(groaning)
(crowd screaming)
So this is how it ends for me.
Shot in the back.
You win, Sexina.
(sighs) Now I have to face your
mother.
(crowd screaming)
- Looks like I showed up just in
time.
- Man, we didn't need you.
I was two seconds away
from killing him myself.
- You saved my life, Sal!
- Oh, hey, I'd do anything
for my favorite client.
- Hey Lance, looks like you're
going
to need some new representation.
- No thanks, man.
I'm retiring from the music
business.
- I can't believe my father was
evil.
- You're nothing like him,
Sexina.
You make the world better for
everyone.
- He was a second away from
killing me.
- Yeah, but today wasn't your
day to die.
You still have so many people to
help.
- You're right.
- Sexina, there is something
I have to tell you.
- What is it?
- I'm a robot.
(crowd gasping)
- Is that true?
- Yes, it's true.
I created Lance as a pleasure
robot.
He has been programmed with more
than 1,000 techniques to
bring a woman to orgasm.
- Really?
(chuckles) Well, sounds
like a happy ending to me.
- Can you make me one
of those robots, daddy?
(moaning)
- That's it, I'm leaving!
I'll see you at the office!
- What has gotten into her?
- I think she's just mad
'cause I forgot to thank her.
(mumbling)
- Hey, how 'bout you sing us a
song?
- I think it's a great idea.
- Let's rock this joint!
- That's right!
(audience cheering)
(upbeat pop music)
♪ We have waited all our lives ♪
♪ For a moment like this ♪
♪ Don't surrender 'cause this is
it ♪
♪ No, no, never quit ♪
♪ And never say die ♪
♪ You can't win ♪
♪ So don't even try ♪
♪ So fight back ♪
♪ Keep fighting 'til the end ♪
♪ We can win ♪
♪ With help from my friends ♪
♪ So stand up ♪
♪ And be counted as heroes ♪
♪ Losers lose ♪
♪ And that's how it goes ♪
♪ Victory is in the air ♪
♪ You can smell it everywhere ♪
♪ It feels like new underwear ♪
♪ Vera's got sexy hair ♪
♪ Everything is going to be okay
♪
♪ Today is a brand new day ♪
♪ Please get out of the way ♪
♪ If you're evil, you will pay ♪
♪ So fight back ♪
♪ Keep fighting 'til the end ♪
♪ We can win ♪
♪ With help from my friends ♪
♪ So stand up ♪
♪ And be counted as heroes ♪
♪ Losers lose ♪
♪ And that's how it goes ♪
♪ So fight back ♪
♪ Keep fighting 'til the end ♪
♪ We can win ♪
♪ With help from my friends ♪
♪ So stand up ♪
♪ And be counted as heroes ♪
♪ Losers lose ♪
♪ And that's how it goes ♪
(upbeat pop music)
♪ Numero uno lover ♪
♪ You better run for cover ♪
♪ Girl, you make me love you
like I can ♪
♪ I was made to please you ♪
♪ I am spicy and I always wax my
chest ♪
♪ When it comes to sex
I surely am the best ♪
♪ Numero uno lover ♪
♪ You better run for cover ♪
♪ Sex, sex, sex, sex, sex, sex,
♪
♪ Ina, ina, ina, ina, ina, ina ♪
♪ Sex, sex, ina, ina ♪
♪ Shooting to the top ♪
♪ Sex, ina, ina, ina ♪
♪ Dangerous ♪
♪ Undercover ♪
♪ Sexina ♪
♪ Shooting to the top ♪
♪ Dangerous ♪
♪ Sexina ♪
♪ Dangerous Sexina ♪
♪ Undercover ♪
♪ Sexina ♪
♪ Dangerous ♪
♪ Undercover ♪
♪ Sexina ♪
♪ Sex, sex, sex, sex, sex, sex ♪
♪ Ina, ina, ina, ina, ina, ina ♪
♪ Sex, sex, ina, ina ♪
♪ Shooting to the top ♪
♪ Sexina ♪
♪ Dangerous ♪