[Miles Lanson, Duffy Sylvander,
Mia Mayer "Christmas Spark"]
♪ I’ve wrapped my presents
And got my letters all sent ♪
♪ I like to think that I am
super damn well prepared ♪
♪ The seasons ready to go ♪
♪ Tell me your wishes
and send me kisses ♪
♪ And then listen to carol singers
Knocking on the doors till ten ♪
♪ We can go to bed
before it snows ♪
♪ So I follow the
brightest star ♪
♪ Except my own two feet
don’t walk that far ♪
♪ Right into your heart ♪
♪ I need a Christmas Spark ♪
[indistinct chatter]
All right, Mr. Barstow.
I have the reservation here for
you and Mr. Dickens in room 357...
Ooh, Dickens!
Thank you.
Dickens!
[telephone rings]
Merry Christmas.
You've reached the Hotel Fontaine,
your home for the holidays.
This is Georgia speaking.
How may I help you?
You can help me
by coming outside
and giving me a hand
with all of this stuff.
Kiki, great. You're here.
I will be right out.
- Ooh, Georgia!
- [gasps]
Florence! Did the
champagne arrive yet?
Oh, yes. All 20 cases.
- Great.
- You really got the good stuff, huh?
Christmas only
comes once a year.
- Yep.
- There you go. Thank you.
[gasps] Oh, uh, that goes outside by
the front door to the right, please.
Thank you so much.
- [screams]
- Oops.
- Oh, my God. Thank you, Milton.
- [laughs]
Who knew the Christmas rush
would be so hazardous this year?
[gasps] Oh! Oh, uh, the bedside
table lamp in 209 needs a fresh bulb,
414 needs fresh batteries in the
remote, and 327 has a leaky tub.
Leaky tub. Yeah,
I'm all over it.
- You're the best. Thank you, Milton.
- [phone chimes]
Uh-hmm. Thank you.
Ho, ho, ho, how
about a donation?
Ho, ho, yourself.
How about some help?
Well, if you give me a donation,
I'll give you some help.
Where is your Christmas
spirit, Santa?
Left it up north with
the other reindeer.
I'm so sorry it took so long.
I had no idea how hard it would be
to find a partridge in a pear tree.
So, I had to go with the macaw.
As my head concierge, you shouldn't
have to be schlepping all of this,
but with my extra holiday time
staff comes in tomorrow, hopefully.
Don't worry about it.
What are best friends for, if not
to schlep a little yuletide cheer?
Besides, I should
really be thanking you
for letting me organize this whole
Jingle Mingle party myself this year.
Jingle Mingle, what is that?
It's our annual Christmas Eve
party for singles who wanna mingle.
[Kiki] And also, for singles
who are not ready to mingle.
Basically, it's a
Christmas party for anyone
who doesn't have something
to do on Christmas Eve.
Where's my invitation?
Every party needs a Santa Claus.
Not one on the naughty list.
Hey, I see you when
you're sleeping, you know?
Creepy!
I'm Santa... I'm Santa Claus!
It was a Santa joke!
Just a whiff of
white truffle, chef?
Just a whiff.
Et voila!
[Victor] You know you go through a lot of
trouble making Georgia lunch every day?
It's not trouble. Besides,
it's not the point.
That is the point.
You've been working here
for over a year now.
And she still doesn't know
how you really feel, does she?
Victor, Georgia and
I are just friends.
Good friends.
All right, chef.
Just because you and
Anna are sneaking around
doesn't mean that we all are.
Uh, we ain't sneaking around. I
mean, you won't tell anybody, right?
Look, Anna just wants to keep
it on the down low, all right?
Your secret's safe with me.
Oh, hey, Anna. How you doing?
Luke, hi!
Little last-minute
Christmas shopping?
Oh. [chuckles] Yeah, sort of.
If it's for Victor, you better
hide it. He's right in there.
How did you... Victor
doesn't want anyone to know.
Know what?
[sighs]
Oh, my God.
Okay.
Wow.
Let me guess. Kiki
made the sign.
Her marketing
instincts are great.
She's just a little
heavy-handed on the glitter.
At least it is covering the
giant crack in the wall.
They say cracks
let the magic in.
[sighs] I'm afraid I
don't believe in magic.
- [Luke] Well, do you believe in lunch?
- [Georgia] Oh, my God.
You don't have to keep doing
this for me. You know that.
Hey, making lunch for you
is the highlight of my day.
Well, you making lunch for me
So take some time and eat.
[sighs] Oh, God.
There's just so much I have to
get done before Christmas Eve.
The lights. The lights on the
fifth floor aren't working.
I forgot to tell
Milton. Oh, my God!
So they can use candles.
It adds mystery.
This rug is ancient.
I have to change this rug!
Not ancient. Vintage.
Does that tree look
crooked to you?
[Luke] A little. I think it's
the weight of all the ornaments.
I wanted to get matching ones
this year, I just ran out of time.
No, I thought that was the
whole point of our tree.
People bring their
own ornaments.
Makes it feel like home.
[chuckles] Hey, not bad.
Not bad for a seven-year-old.
I remember it took me a
whole week to make that.
I guess I always knew I was
gonna grow up to work with food.
What's the matter? Is it cold?
No, no. It's perfect.
It's just...
I'm so lucky to have you.
You're such a good chef.
You know you could do a lot better
than this old hotel of ours.
I love this old hotel of ours.
And the way I look at it,
it's not always the
place that's important.
Sometimes it's the people.
[crowd chattering]
Oh, my God! Now what?
Thank you.
Ugh, glitter.
[Jimothy] Hey, enough photos.
Enough photos. Stop with the flash.
No. No, you do not
have a release.
Thank you. Move, move, move.
Not the cameras. Not the cameras,
please. No flash. No flash.
[upbeat music playing]
Welcome to the Hotel Fontaine,
your home for the holidays.
[Jimothy] We have a reservation.
Of course. And the name is...
Seriously?
This is Pandora.
You probably heard
her last release.
Love, Love, Love is
All Couture to Me.
[Pandora chuckles softly]
Never mind, Jimothy. Nobody did.
That's why we're here.
Guru Peterson. That's my
life coach, Guru Peterson.
He says I need a simple zen space
to ground myself for the holidays.
Okay.
Of course. Here you are. We
have you in a queen room.
Avenue view, it's very
simple, very cozy, very zen.
Cozy sounds... small.
How about a king?
Hmm.
Okay.
Uh, junior suite?
Hmm, hmm, hmm.
Okay. How about the
presidential suite?
- [breathes deeply]
- We'll make it work.
Great. We will have your
bag... s brought right up.
[Pandora] Uh-hmm.
Loving life.
♪ We wish you a
merry Christmas ♪
They don't sing
all night, do they?
[Carolers] ♪ ...and
a happy new year ♪
♪ Good tidings we bring ♪
♪ To you and your kin ♪
♪ We wish you a merry Christmas
and a happy new year ♪
Ah, there. That should do it.
Well, thank you so much, Milton.
Oh, you're welcome. [sighs]
Funny thing about this
sink, you know what,
that's the third time that faucet
has come loose in the past week.
You'd almost swear somebody
is doing it on purpose.
Well, that's crazy. Why would
anybody wanna sabotage my sink?
- Yeah. Weird.
- Weird.
I thought I told
you to stop that.
Checking in.
[Georgia] Of course.
And your name is...
Prince Raymond. Hello.
Welcome to the Hotel Fontaine.
It is an honor to have you here.
Thank you. It's just
Raymond though, no Prince.
Right. I knew that.
I just read about you
giving up your title.
Yes. And I'm trying to keep a
low profile, you understand?
The Hotel Fontaine is famous
for its discretion with guests.
Instead of two turtle doves, what
if I went with a couple of rabbits?
- Prince Raymond.
- [Georgia] Kiki.
What? This is Prince
Raymond of Caspernia.
Not anymore. He quit.
Oh. Well, so then you're not
in town looking for a princess?
Please, forgive my associate.
She has inhaled too
much Christmas glitter.
[sighs]
Stop.
I'm sorry about him.
He's taken my
abdication rather badly.
He refuses to quit.
I don't even think the earpiece
is attached to anything anymore.
[both chuckles]
So your, um, not Royal Highness?
Just Raymond is fine.
Just Raymond. Is this your
first time visiting in New York?
Yes, actually.
I want to get as far away from my family
this year for the holidays as possible.
Well, my name is Georgia.
I am the hotel manager.
And if there's anything at
all that I can do for you,
please, don't hesitate to ask.
Yes, we are all yours.
Thank you for your help.
No.
Kiki, what was that?
You are not going
to believe this.
But I dreamt about
him last night.
This has to be
some kind of sign.
- I mean, look.
- Yes.
It's a sign that you should
stop reading that stuff.
There is some kind of
Christmas magic happening here.
The prince and I are
obviously meant to be.
Kiki, I hate to break this to you
but there's no such thing as magic.
So how do you explain the prince walking
through the front door of our hotel?
[phone chimes]
Kiki, will you keep an eye on
the front desk for me, please?
Yes. Wow! Thank you!
Kiki, just watch the front desk.
All right? Don't move.
Okay. But don't be
surprised if you come back
and I am suddenly Princess Kiki.
[whispers] Okay.
[exhales deeply]
[strident music playing]
[Milton grunts]
I should have this fixed
for you in no time, Georgia.
Get that water
working on 310, too.
Great. Thank you, Milton.
Um, is it possible for you to
maybe come back a little later?
Sure. Yeah, I mean,
you're the boss.
[grunts] Yeah. Everything okay?
Yes. Yes.
- Totally. Everything's fine.
- Yeah.
Yeah, I have to make a
phone call. That's it.
- [Milton] All right.
- Yeah. Thank you.
Well, yeah, if you need me, you
know where to find me, yeah?
- Sure do!
- [both chuckle]
- You okay?
- I'm okay.
Yeah, thank you.
All right. Great. Thanks.
[exhales heavily]
[Fontaine] I must say, Georgia.
You present a very
persuasive argument
and, uh, the design you sent for
the proposal, they look magnific.
So innovative, so modern.
Thank you, Madame Fontaine.
The problem is...
I hate modern.
That's why we keep Hotel
Fontaine to preserve the past,
the elegance, the way of life.
Right. But you wouldn't
have to give any of that up.
The Auberge Moderne would
be the Hotel Fontaine's
cool modern counterpart
right here in New York City.
I understand all
of that, Georgia.
But, uh...
Oh, merci, Jean Luc.
This sounds like a great
big deal of extra work
and I hardly have time to
spend on my yacht as it is.
That's the beauty
of my proposal.
You wouldn't have
to do anything.
I would take on full responsibility
as the executive director
while you continue to
travel as much as you like.
And all I'm asking
for in return is...
Forty-nine percent
of the ownership.
I think that's fair.
[laughs]
Oh, your ambition reminds me so
much of myself when I was your age.
And I must say, you've
done a wonderful job
over the past two years
for me with the hotel.
And I often say you are
the daughter I never had.
Really? Does this
mean you'll do it?
No.
Oh. Uh, okay.
Well, thank you anyway.
And Madame, would you
please not mention this
to any of the staff
here at the hotel?
I wouldn't want them to know
I was thinking about leaving
and it might rub
them the wrong way.
Wait, what if...
I invest half?
Half?
You come up with the rest
and we'll see if we do.
Madam Fontaine, you know I don't
have access to that kind of money.
Oh, but I know you to be
a very clever young girl.
And I suspect that when you
put your mind to something,
there is nothing you can't do.
Merry Christmas, Georgia.
[cheerful music playing]
[Luke] You're too
early, you know...
for Santa.
He's not due for
another four days.
How do you always
know where to find me?
Lucky guess.
Plus, Kiki told me you were
going somewhere to think.
And this is where you
always go to think.
Christmas toast?
[glasses clink]
You know me really well.
I know when something's
bothering you. What's up?
Nothing. [sighs]
Nothing. Just a plan
that didn't work out.
What kind of plan?
Actually, Luke, do you mind
if we don't talk about it?
Yeah. Yeah. We don't have to talk
about it if you don't want to.
Thank you.
I just don't wanna end up like
my parents. You know what I mean?
Like, they worked so
hard their whole lives.
They came to this
country with nothing,
and they didn't even get
to own their own home.
I just... [inhales deeply]
I want to have something
to call my own.
We're not talking
about it, though.
- Sorry.
- [both chuckle]
No problem.
Is there anything
I can do to help?
Not unless you got a big pile of
cash somewhere you wanna loan me.
You know I would if I did.
[glasses clink]
How do rich people
get so rich anyway?
Oh, that's easy.
- They never spend their own money.
- What do you mean?
Well, if they wanna buy something,
they find someone else to pay for it.
[thoughtful music playing]
[jaunty Christmas pop playing]
[indistinct chatter]
Dickens?
Dickens.
Dickens!
[carolers] ♪ Deck the halls
with boughs of holly ♪
- Dickens?!
- ♪ Fa-la-la-la-la, la-la-la-la ♪
Oh, excuse me.
Have you seen my dog?
It's a little black
Chihuahua, about this big.
His name is Dickens.
He got out of his harness and ran
off. Have you seen him at all?
That depends.
Care to make a donation
to the candy cane fund?
Okay.
Fine. Here.
Little dog, black and tan
with happy waggin' tail?
[chuckles] Yeah, that's it!
Nah, I haven't seen him.
Dickens! Dickens!
Well, if it isn't my
favorite little elf.
Are we feeling more
charitable today?
Why don't you go back to the North
Pole and stop bothering people?
Ooh. You know, if
you're not careful,
you'll end up with a lump
of coal in your stocking.
Look, I realize that I
don't have the funds.
I just...
No, no, I don't own
any of my own property.
I just...
Is there anybody else in the
loan department I could talk to?
Maybe like a supervisor
or... You are the supervisor.
Merry Christmas to you, too.
[Kiki] I had to hit five
different pet shops today,
and most of them had never
even heard of French hens.
- [chicken clucking]
- Still sticking with the whole
12 Days of Christmas theme, huh?
[Kiki] Yeah. You know what happens
when I set my mind to something.
Speaking of...
I dreamt of Prince
Raymond again last night.
Kiki, you know you're not
supposed to bother the guests.
I'm not gonna bother him.
I'm just gonna let him know that
we are destined to be together.
I hope he doesn't think I'm
just after him for his money.
I mean, he is a prince, right?
He's probably got billions.
Cream and sugar? Right.
There you go.
[singing] ♪ Jingle bells, jingle
bells, jingle all the way ♪♪
From your secret love...?
[whimsical music playing]
Ooh...
Wowee
[clears throat]
[chuckles]
[singing] ♪ Jingle bells, jingle
bells jingle all the way ♪♪
- [man] Here they are!
- [man] Prince Raymond!
Great! Over here!
[Reporter] Your
highness, right here!
Why are you here?
[Paparazzi clamoring]
[crowd murmuring]
I am so, so sorry,
Mr., uh, Raymond.
I will personally make sure
that that never happens again.
You know, I'd rather hope
that being an ex-royal
would mean I'd have some
privacy now and then.
Now it seems I can't
even leave the hotel.
Come with me.
I cannot believe I didn't
think about this sooner.
Not many people know
about these stairs.
The hotel uses them for deliveries,
but it's not that pretty.
[Raymond] Oh, it's
absolutely fine.
Do you have any
idea how bored I am
withe people bowing and bloody trumpets
going off every time i walk into a room?
This is a very nice
change of pace.
It isn't quite the New York that
tourists see, but it's private.
And here, you can use this
during your stay with us.
I very much appreciate
this, Georgia. Thank you.
Of course. If there's anything else that
I can do for you, please just let me know.
Actually, I do need some
help navigating your city.
I don't suppose you know
anyone who's up for the task.
[singer] ♪ I was hanging with
my gals when you came up to me ♪
- [whistle blows]
- ♪ It's not like I was... ♪♪
[radio DJ] And Pandora's latest single,
Love, Love, Love is All Couture to Me
continues to plummet and
the once hot singer's career
flies into oblivion.
Let's just turn
this off, shall we?
I need Guru Peterson, Jimothy!
I called him six times.
It just keeps
going to voicemail.
Christmas must be the
busy season for gurus.
[sighs deeply] Besides, you
know, he'd probably just tell you
that the reason
your album flopped
is because you've lost
touch with your fan base.
You're just not relatable
to normal people anymore.
What do you mean
by normal exactly?
You know, people who
carry their own luggage.
- Oh.
- [Jimothy] People who wear khakis.
People who eat soft
serve ice cream.
[gasps] Please, never say
"soft serve ice cream" again.
You know what I need, Jimothy?
[Jimothy] Another makeover?
[Pandora] No.
A make-under.
[gasps]
Kiki? I'm heading out for lunch.
Can you watch the front desk for me?
I should be back in
about an hour or so.
Actually... make that two.
[hopeful music playing]
- Oh, there you are.
- [Georgia gasps] Luke.
Hi. I...
I am heading out
for my lunch break.
Wait, wait.
You are going on a lunch break?
Well, it's Christmas. [chuckles]
Wait. Before you go, I want
you to try this new eggnog
I was thinking of serving
at the Jingle Mingle.
I'd love to.
[Luke] It's my own recipe.
I have an in with the dairy
farmer at the Christmas market.
Oh, my God. This is incredible.
Thank you.
I have to go. I'm sorry.
Oh. Where are you headed?
Out.
Perfect. I'll come with you.
I wanted to grab some stuff
from the market anyway.
No.
No. I...
I don't wanna get in your way.
You're not gonna get in my way.
You're just saying that to
be nice. I'll see you later.
Bye.
[Georgia] So you've been
a prince your whole life?
That is generally how
monarchies work, yes.
Yeah. I knew that.
[chuckles]
Oh.
Force of habit.
He's also my food taster
back at the palace.
- [chuckles softly]
- Oh.
Oh, I got it. Thanks.
So, um, why did you leave?
Well, that's a good question.
I suppose I just
got tired of it all.
I just wanted a
change, something new.
Then of course there's my father,
he was in charge of my life.
[scoffs] It's like he's
the king or something.
I guess the real truth of it is
that I just got sick and tired
of sharing everything with
11 brothers and sisters.
I wanted something
that was just my own.
Raymond, I have an idea.
[elevator bell dings]
[exhales deeply]
[Kiki] You have hoops? Five
of them? And they're golden?
Thank you. I will
be right there.
Can I help you?
You don't know who I am?
Should I? Are you a guest here?
I'm Pando... um...
Pam?
Oh, wait. Are you one of the temps that
Georgia hired for the Jingle Mingle?
- Uh...
- The Christmas Eve party?
[Pandora] Uh, yes. Yes.
Uh, yes. Yes, that's it.
I'm a temp. An absolute
normal, everyday temp.
Great. That's perfect.
We got to go because we've got to pick
up something from the Christmas market.
Uh, don't you have
people for that?
Yeah, us. Come on.
[sighs]
Oh, what, uh, what's this for?
[clicks tongue] Milton,
by the power vested in me
by the Innkeepers
Association of America,
I am officially putting you
in charge until I get back.
[Milton] Wow.
Come on.
[chuckles]
[telephone ringing]
[Milton] Oh. [sighs]
Bonjour. Joyeux Noel.
This is the Hotel Fontaine,
your home for the holidays.
How may I help you?
[crowd murmuring]
- Let's go.
- Oh.
Where's Santa's little helper
going off to this time?
-It's a Christmas secret, Santa!
[bell ringing]
[Pandora] I wonder what he
looks like under the beard?
Dickens... Dickens!
Dickens!
[flowing waltz playing]
You don't even have to lift a
finger if you don't want to.
You bring the capital.
I'll be the executive director, and
we will split the 49% ownership stake.
To be honest, I'm not exactly looking
to get into the hotel business.
Why not?
Okay. Look down there.
Did you know that during
the holiday season,
an average of 800,000 people pass
through Rockefeller Center every day?
[inhales sharply] You know, my father
built an indoor rink at the palace once.
First time I tried skating,
I broke my ankle. [chuckles]
The point is, all of those
people need somewhere to stay.
And modern hotels are the fastest growing
segment of the hospitality industry.
I very much appreciate that,
but I don't know why I would
put any roots down here.
I don't know the city at all.
And I'm planning to leave
the day after Christmas.
Which gives me just enough
time to show you around.
- But I...
- Will you at least give it a chance?
Look, if I don't convince
you that this city
is a good investment
by Christmas,
you can hop on your jet and fly
off to anywhere else in the world.
But...
if you fall in love
with New York...
I must warn you.
I was a prince, so I'm
pretty difficult to impress.
Clearly, you've
never met New York.
Deal?
[chuckles softly]
So you've seen my jet?
[joyful marketplace chatter]
[Kiki] Do you think these like
geese need to actually lay the eggs
or do you think they can kind
of just sit on top of them?
I feel like it's gonna
be kind of hard to...
[sighs] ...do you remember
how excited you used to get
about Christmas
when you were a kid?
Actually, I don't.
Wow. Christmas buzzkill.
Come on.
[Pandora] Honestly,
there wasn't much time
between the dance rehearsals,
and singing classes,
and piano lessons.
You know, like,
like any normal kid.
Well, in that case, we need
to make up for lost time.
We start with the head first.
Oh, no, I can't.
That is nothing but
sugar and baked lard.
Yeah, that's basically
what Christmas is.
Come on. I know the best hot
chocolate stand in the city.
[chuckles softly]
[flustered hubbub]
[barking]
Hey, buddy. You lost?
Dickens...
Well, it is Christmas.
Okay, Dickens, let's
find out where you live.
[Georgia] They say that a million
kids visit this market at Christmas.
In fact, over 60 million
tourists visit New York City
- every year, all year round.
- [chuckles]
And you just have this
information at your fingertips?
I have been working on this proposal
for a really, really long time.
- I have done my research.
- Yes, I can see that.
This new hotel isn't just a real
estate investment for you, is it?
No...[exhales deeply] no.
It...
it means the world to me.
Look, Georgia, I
appreciate your enthusiasm.
And New York is obviously a
massive tourist destination.
But... [sighs]
the truth is, I'm just not sure
I'm looking to invest
in a business right now.
I see.
Do you mean right now, right now or
do you mean right now as in never?
You know what? Why don't we
discuss this over dinner?
I would like that.
I've never had dinner
with a real prince before.
Well, then we're even,
I've never had dinner
with a real hotel
manager before.
[Georgia chuckles softly]
How about 8:00?
And seeing as you're the
authority on all things New York,
I'll leave the where
of it up to you.
That is easy.
I just happen to know
the best chef in town.
[Luke] A prince?
He used to be.
He used to be?
I didn't know you could
"use to be" a prince.
The thing is, he doesn't want
anybody to know about it.
So we need to eat
somewhere private.
There will only be two of us.
Well, three of us, technically,
but I don't think his
bodyguard eats anything
but protein shakes and
the occasional cow.
How did you end up having
dinner with this guy?
You know, it's kind
of complicated.
Can we just do 8:00, please?
Yes, we sure can.
You're the best.
Thank you so much.
- How's the broth, chef?
- Good, chef.
Oh, also, remember
he is royalty,
so I need you to make us something
that's really going to impress him.
He's back to being a prince now?
No problem, G.
Bring him to the roof at 8:00.
The roof?
You said private?
Well, yeah but...
Don't worry about a thing, okay?
I am making the best
dinner he's ever had.
What would I ever do
without you, Luke?
Thank you.
What are you looking at?
Come on. We got
dinner to make, chef.
[sighing]
[bell ringing]
We still need to get the inflatable
pool for the swimming swans
and, of course, the swans,
so we better get an
early start tomorrow.
I will see you in
the morning at 8:00.
[scoffs] Don't be silly.
8:00 doesn't come
in the morning.
Does it?
[Georgia] Kiki,
what are you doing?
- Didn't Milton tell you?
- Tell me what?
I put him in charge
of the front desk.
I gave him the badge
and everything.
[Georgia] Kiki, I love Milton,
but he already has a job.
This hotel will literally
fall apart without him.
He doesn't have time to
be checking in guests.
Okay. But he's doing a
great job at the front desk.
Kiki, that's not the point.
The point is that this isn't how
you're supposed to run a hotel.
Okay, Georgia, you know the
Fontaine isn't like other hotels.
You're right.
It isn't.
[sighs] I can't wait
to get out of here.
Can't wait to what?
Georgia.
Georgia, wait.
- Are you Kiki?
- Yeah.
Sign here for you geese.
Oh.
Thank you.
[squawks]
[swinging Christmas
rock playing]
[Luke] Thanks, Milton. I could
never get these things to work...
[dreamy music playing]
Wow.
Do I look okay? You
look more than okay.
You look...
more than okay.
You look... you
look more than okay.
Thanks.
I really wanna make
a good impression.
Yeah, of course. I mean,
he's a prince, right?
It's not like you're having
dinner with some commoner.
[chuckles]
I'll see you upstairs.
Yeah. Yeah, see you upstairs.
I think it's a bit of a pity
you're not dining together.
Yeah. We're just
friends, Milton.
What makes you think
we should be together?
Oh, I don't think you
should be together.
Everybody thinks you
[chuckles]
[sighs]
Where have you been all day?
I went to a Christmas market.
Excuse me?
I even ate a gingerbread man
that I'm almost 100%
certain was not gluten-free.
So why can't I come
up with a new song?
Maybe this will inspire you.
Look.
I bought you more nice, normal
clothes for you to wear for Christmas.
Oh.
Ho, ho, ho!
[sighs] This is a disaster.
If I don't have a new hit
song soon, my career is over.
What am I gonna do? [sighs]
[Holiday vibes playing]
Hmm...
Just, um, put that on my bill.
Good evening,
mademoiselle, and monsieur,
and monster.
Welcome to Restaurant de Luke.
Follow me.
Prince, sorry, Raymond,
allow me to introduce
you to Chef Luke.
Pleasure to meet you, Chef.
And you...
you are welcome here.
Welcome. Thank you.
Please.
- [clears throat]
- Raymond is visiting New York City
for the first time, Luke.
- Oh, is he?
- Yeah.
And yet it seems as though he's
made himself right at home.
[clears throat]
- Well, it's an easy city to love.
- [Georgia chuckles]
- Not if it doesn't love you back.
- [Georgia] Chef Luke.
I'm sure you have things
to do in the kitchen.
Don't let us keep you.
Yes. Yes, of course.
Enjoy your wine.
Yeah.
Do you know who that is?
- Georgia said he was a prince.
- Yeah.
He's also the guy that was
with her this afternoon.
What does that matter?
They're just having dinner.
[stammers] This
isn't just dinner.
Look at this.
Okay. Well, whatever it is,
the lobster appetizers
are ready to serve.
You want me to fire
up them fillets now?
The fillet?
No, no, no, no, no.
There's gonna be
a change of menu.
To our partnership.
[Prince Raymond] Let's not
get ahead of ourselves.
I haven't made my decision yet.
Right.
My father always says it's
best to discuss business
on a full stomach.
One of the few things
we actually agree on.
You know, I would
really appreciate it
if we could keep all of
this between the two of us.
I'm not ready to tell the
hotel staff about it yet.
[chuckles]
We'll keep it between us then.
Your secret is safe with me.
Thank you.
It must have been fun
growing up in a palace?
Not always.
There are very strict
rules, curfews,
elocution lessons,
apparel guidelines.
You know, I've never worn
sweatpants in my life.
- [gasps] Criminal.
- [chuckles]
[Georgia] No wonder
you ran away.
I'm aware of how that sounds.
No, actually, I...
I really, really get it.
When I moved to New York,
it was like the first
independent thing I ever did.
It was like I finally
owned my own life.
And now, you want to
own your own hotel.
[Luke] Dinner is served.
Oh, fantastic.
I'm obviously famished.
[Luke] Tonight's specialty of the
house is an old New York City recipe
that's been passed down in
my family for generations.
We only use farm to
table ingredients
that have been handcrafted with
artisanal attention to detail
and served at a perfect
temperature of 104 degrees.
I present to you...
- Pizza.
- [Prince Raymond] Pizza.
Yes. Well, we also
have a selection
of curated toppings.
I would recommend...
the, uh, cracked
pepper, of course,
simpler is always better.
Don't you agree?
Chef Luke, may I have
a word in private?
- Of course.
- Excuse us.
After everything we spoke
about and you served him pizza?
I thought you said you
always liked my pizza, G?
Are you trying to
ruin this for me?
This? I... I don't even know what
this is because you won't tell me.
I can't, okay? I'm
sorry. Not yet.
It's just... it's
really important to me.
Yeah, well, it must be. You
spent the whole day together.
What? How do you know that?
Because I saw you.
- Are you spying on me?
- [scoffs]
Spy... don't try to change
the subject, all right?
I saw him kiss your hand.
He's a prince.
That's what they do.
Besides what difference
does it make to you anyway?
Oh, nothing... none, none.
It makes no difference to me.
Raymond. Hi.
Sorry. There was an
emergency in the kitchen,
but I will be right
back at the table.
Well, you better hurry up.
There's not gonna be any left.
I was never allowed to
eat pizza at the palace.
They say it wasn't
fit for a prince.
But this, Chef Luke. Hmm.
This is incredible.
This is one of the
most delicious meals
I think I've ever tasted
in my life, so bravo.
Uh, thank you. Thanks.
[Prince Raymond] If this is any
indication of New York City cuisine,
might've stick around after all.
I have to get back to the table.
My pizza's getting cold.
G. [sighs]
Sorry, brother.
Come on.
- Let's go.
- [Luke sighs]
No, it's okay.
Yeah. I love you.
Everything okay, Flo?
Yeah. Oh, yeah,
everything's fine.
Just my son and my daughter-in-law
aren't gonna be able to make it in
for Christmas dinner
after all, so...
I'm sorry.
Yeah. Which leaves me with a whole
lot of turkey for one person.
- [chuckles]
- [Milton chuckles]
So you done for the night?
Yeah. Uh, pretty cold out there, so I sure
am glad I have this beautiful new scarf.
[Florence] Oh, yeah. Well,
it's very becoming on you.
[laughs] Oh, thank you.
[sighs]
Well, good night, Milton.
Well, have a good night, Flo.
Good night, Anna.
Good night.
Oh...
Oh, no.
My gift for Victor...
[solemn guitar playing]
[Prince Raymond] You know, I don't
think your Chef Luke like me very much.
No. I wouldn't
say that. [laughs]
Luke is just passionate.
You know how chefs are.
So you've known him
for a long time then?
I've been friends with
Luke for a very long time.
I can't even imagine
the hotel without him.
Just friends?
Oh, my gosh. I love
that window. [chuckles]
[toy train whistling]
[giggling]
You know, I heard that there are
over eight million mechanical elves
in New York City
on a given moment.
Ha-ha.
[Prince Raymond] You're not the only one
with information at their fingertips.
[Georgia] I am just trying to help
you make a sound business decision
based on facts and logic.
The truth is, I haven't made
many big decisions in my life.
My last one, abdicating the throne,
wasn't based in logic at all.
I guess that's going to be
true of my next decision, too.
Are you serious?
[chuckles] Very.
I looked at your proposal.
I think you'd be a
great business partner.
You're not kidding, right?
He's not kidding, right?
No.
Not kidding.
Oh, my God. Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you.
- [laughs]
- [Prince Raymond] Careful.
You know, there are
paparazzis hiding.
We don't want anyone
to get the wrong idea.
Sorry.
This is going to be the
best Christmas ever.
[both chuckle]
[Georgia] So the Prince has
agreed to invest half the cost
But I heard that Prince
Raymond has left the throne,
didn't want to be a part of
the royal family anymore.
Silly boy.
Well, yes, but he is looking
to expand his interests.
The thing is, he is leaving New
York right after Christmas, so...
So in that case,
I suggest...
Jean-Luc, I'm thirsty.
Yes. What do you suggest?
[Madame] I suggest you
open a bottle of Champagne.
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you, Madame Fontaine.
Thank you so much.
Oh, don't thank me.
Thank your prince.
Now, go find us a
shiny new hotel.
Okay.
[carolers] ♪ Deck the halls
with boughs of holly ♪
♪ Fa-la-la-la-la, la-la-la-la ♪
Hey. Hi.
I'm in the lobby.
Where are you?
[Dickens barking]
Dickens...
Hey. Thank you.
Hey, I missed you so much.
[Hunter] You must have
been worried sick.
Yeah. Do you have a dog?
No, my apartment is too small.
Even my plants complain.
[laughs]
He never used to run away.
But he's been acting out ever since
his other daddy and I broke up.
[chuckles]
I hope you don't mind. It
was pretty cold out there
so I, uh, got him a coat.
There are matching boots too,
in case you ever
want the full outfit.
Uh, I'll think about it.
- How much do I owe you?
- [Hunter] Forget about it.
Think of it as an
early Christmas gift
from one divorcee to another.
- Well, thank you.
- You're welcome.
Uh, I hear this Jingle Mingle party they
put on every Christmas is pretty fun.
If you're still in town,
maybe we could check it out.
Oh, um, thanks.
But no, I... I can't.
Oh, okay. I understand.
I... I mean, I have work stuff
that I got to get
done, you know.
[chuckles]
No problem.
[sighs] Well, take care
of your dad, Dickens.
It was nice meeting you, AJ.
You too.
Merry Christmas.
What?
[carolers] ♪ Fa-la-la-la-la,
la-la-la-la... ♪♪
What do you think he
meant by sticking around?
Probably means he's
gonna stick around.
You saw the way he and Georgia
were looking at each other.
You dropped the ball
on this one Luke
and prince charming was
right there to pick it up.
Victor, I told you.
Georgia and I are
just good friends.
Nobody believes that
except for you and Georgia.
And the only reason why she does
is because you haven't told
her how you really feel.
Maybe I don't know
how I really feel.
I do.
You feel like you wanna
make lunch for her
every single day for
the rest of your lives.
And if that ain't love, brother,
I don't know what it is.
So, what am I supposed
to do about it?
I'm no Prince,
retired, or otherwise.
You're gonna go down there,
you're gonna give
her this sandwich,
and you're going to
tell her the truth.
The truth.
You got this.
[Kiki] Hey, I need to hire
eight more temps for the party
and they have to
dress like milk-maids.
Sure. Okay.
Thanks.
And I'm really sorry about
not being here yesterday.
Don't worry about it.
Milton did a great job.
- Oh, so, you're not upset.
- No. Of course, I'm not.
Oh, I thought you were mad, when you said
"I couldn't wait to get out of here."
Oh, that, that's just
a figure of speech.
Um, I have to run and do
some Christmas errands.
- I'll be back later, okay?
- Okay.
Oh, wait. I also
need nine ballerinas.
"Executive Director
Georgia Clark"?
- [Luke] Georgia. Georgia.
- Oh, Luke.
Sorry, I have to run out
to go to lunch. I don't...
Oh, going out to lunch
again, getting to be a habit.
Look, I'm sorry, okay,
about last night with
you and the prince.
I behaved immaturely and
I wanted to apologize.
- It's okay, really. Don't worry...
- No, it isn't.
It isn't, really.
The thing is, I acted
like that because I...
we, you know, you
and me, we... uh, us.
- Yeah.
- Ah, there you are.
- Hi.
- Chef.
- The car's waiting for us.
- Oh, I'll be right there.
Luke, can we pick this
up later? I have to run.
Yeah. Yeah. Of course.
You, you got things
to do, busy-bee...
Hey.
Everything okay?
Yeah. Everything's fine.
Here, you want a sandwich?
- Yeah, it's just...
- Oh, okay. Sure. Yeah.
- And, uh, the spices for it, so.
- Okay.
Oh, okay.
That's, uh, Ms. Kelly, room 304.
- Oh, Anna. Good.
- Uh-hmm.
Uh, apparently, uh, some
of our guests have spotted
some goose droppings
in the East Corridor.
- Well, if you can tidy that up, please?
- Sure.
But, Milton, I have to talk
to you about something.
Oh, dear, that sounds important.
It is. Uh, it's actually
about your scarf.
Oh, do you like it?
A secret admirer left it
for me in the supply closet.
Confidentially, I
think it was Florence.
- Florence?
- Uh-hmm.
You know, actually, Anna,
I could use your help.
I wanna do something
nice for her,
but, well, my dating
game is a little rusty.
It's, uh, been 12 years
since my wife passed
and, uh, well, it's been some time
since I've had to do anything like this.
Do you have any ideas?
Actually, Milton.
The scarf was from me.
What?
I bought it for Victor.
I was hiding it in the supply closet
to give to him on Christmas Eve.
But I found it first.
- I am so sorry.
- Oh, no, no, no.
Anna, this is not
your fault at all.
Silly of me, anyway.
Imagine me having a
secret admirer at my age.
Well, uh, back to work.
You're one lucky dog, Dickens,
being found by such a nice guy.
[Dickens mewling]
Oh...
He's even got good
taste in clothes.
[Kiki] I just can't believe
Georgia wouldn't tell me
she's planning to
leave the hotel.
Maybe she wanted to
keep it a secret.
People keep secrets from each
other all the time, right?
Even when they're supposed
to be best friends?
I don't know.
I never really had
time for a best friend.
Well, I am in the market for a
new one, if you're interested.
Thanks.
Come on. You're gonna
help me with these.
Um, what am I supposed to do?
Oh, we're gonna
decorate the cookies
and then put them on the
tree for the Jingle Mingle.
Oh, no, no, no. I better not.
Why not? It's
Christmas tradition.
But what if I don't do it right?
What if my cookies
are a huge flop
and nobody likes them and I never
have another hit cookie again?
Who cares if no one
likes your cookies?
Listen, some people
don't like gingerbread.
Some people don't
like shortbread.
Some people don't even
like cookies at all.
So you really can't worry what
other people are gonna think.
Sometimes, you just gotta
make the cookies for yourself.
Get to work.
Oh.
[Prince Raymond] You know, when
I said I wanted to see New York,
I didn't mean to see
it all in one day.
So far, we've seen a property
that look like a prison.
One, like a subterranean bunker,
and there was that
hole in the ground
that I was actually
beginning to consider
until we were attacked
by feral pigeons.
I have to admit so far, Georgia,
this isn't very encouraging.
No, I know. Okay.
Just... just wait
until you see this one.
Do you have a key?
Better.
I have an app.
[Georgia] Look at this place.
The realtor is starting
to stage it for Christmas.
- Oh, this is...
- Beautiful.
You took the words
right out of my mouth.
Look at that.
That, now, that is
a Christmas tree.
Now, this...
This is a proper
restaurant for our hotel.
The Viridian is the hotel's five-star
award-winning dining experience.
I know just the chef
to do it justice.
Chef Luke.
Chef Luke?
Erm... [chuckles]
He's great at making pizza.
I was thinking more along the
lines of Otto Hans Becker.
Has a Michelin star
and he's the spoke chef to
World Hunger Foundation.
[Georgia] Chef Luke
likes to help people too.
Look, Georgia. I know that
he's your friend, but...
Our new hotel will need someone
with reputation. Gravitas.
Luke just isn't that.
[discouraged music playing]
So partner, what do you think?
I think we found our hotel.
Hey.
Hi. Excuse me.
I was wondering if
you had matching boots
to go with this jack... et.
Hi.
Hey.
You work here?
Actually, I own the place,
and another uptown and
one at the airport.
Got 'em in the
divorce. [chuckles]
How do you own pet
stores but not a dog?
I do.
About 30 of them,
every day, right
through that door.
Hi, Dickens.
[Dickens barks]
- About yesterday.
- If it's about the money,
- don't worry about it.
- No.
I actually have something
I wanna ask you.
I would...
I would really like to go to the
Jingle Mingle at the hotel with you.
And that is if you
still wanted to go.
Hmm, do I wanna go to the
Jingle Mingle with you?
Let me think about
it. Yes, I do.
[chuckles]
What changed your mind?
Nothing. It's just, um,
I've only been single for
about six months, you know?
And I still get a little...
skittish with, you know, this.
Well, if it makes
you feel any better,
I've had about two
years, and I still squirm
every time someone asks
for my phone number.
What do you think?
Should we try them on for size?
[Dickens barks]
[bell tolling]
[SATV Music "Almost Christmas"]
♪ Now, it's that time of year ♪
♪ When magic's in the air ♪
♪ That's when you know
It's almost Christmas ♪
♪ Chestnuts roastin', champagne
toastin' Frisky in the snow ♪
♪ Children wishin', lovers
kissin' Under mistletoe ♪
♪ It's almost Christmas ♪
Look what just got here?
Green, if you're single and red
if you're not ready to mingle.
[Luke] I guess you won't be
needing either of those, huh?
What does that supposed to mean?
Well, just means
why settle for pizza
when you can have filet mignon?
- Yeah.
- What?
- Or a brand new hotel.
"Welcome to Auberge Moderne,
Executive Director
Georgia Clark."
Okay. Can you just
let me explain it.
Wait... you're leaving
the Hotel Fontaine?
I wouldn't say leaving exactly.
But you're going to
work at another hotel?
Well, sort of, but...
Actually, she's gonna be
working for her own hotel.
Can we please just
do this later?
Georgia is going
to be a part owner
of our new Auberge Moderne.
Oh, let me guess.
This was your idea?
No. Luke.
It was mine.
Look, I'm sorry to surprise
everybody like this.
It's just... I've always
really wanted to own something,
you know, and the... And
the chance came up and...
anyway,
I hope you guys all
really understand.
Yes, I am leaving the hotel.
But not tonight.
And we'll always have
the Jingle Mingle.
Yeah. We can just make it
into a going away party.
Congratulations,
Georgia. Really.
It's a great opportunity.
Yeah. Besides, you, you, you shouldn't
stay in one place all your life.
I mean, look at me.
Oh, just stop it, Milton.
I think it's wonderful, Georgia.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Luke.
I'm really sorry
I didn't tell you.
I just didn't think
it was gonna happen.
No. Don't worry about it.
Maybe you'll need a chef
for the new place, right?
Yeah. Yeah. Who knows.
Got it. Right hotel, wrong chef.
Well, I, uh, should head
back up to the kitchen.
Got a lot to prep for tonight.
You're gonna be there, right?
Yeah.
Um, singles only.
Congrats, G.
Kiki.
Kiki. I'm sorry. I
wanted to tell you.
- I just didn't know how I...
- [Kiki] Don't worry about it.
It's not like we're best
friends or anything.
Don't say that.
I've got to go.
I still have to find eleven
pipers and twelve drummers
and the party is less
than six hours away.
I have to admit, though,
you finally convinced me.
About what?
Doesn't matter how much
glitter you throw around.
There really is no
such thing as magic.
[exhales sharply]
[indistinct chatter]
[clears throat]
Well, the guests should be
arriving in a couple of hours.
Flo, anything I
can help you with?
Oh. Actually, there is.
Have a seat, Milton.
Oh, all righty...
So, with it being
Christmas Eve and all,
and you and I being
friends all these years.
I thought, well... I... uh-hmm.
- For me?
- Yeah. Well, read the tag.
Oh.
- Yeah, that's me. [laughs]
- [chuckles]
Okay. Go ahead.
Open it already.
Okay. Sure. Sure.
Well, this is... Oh,
it's sweet of you.
Oh, Flo.
Well, you know, you looked
really good in the red one,
but I just thought that this
went with your eyes better.
Hmm.
Ah. Great.
Thank you.
But I didn't get you anything.
Oh, well, I've already
thought about that.
Remember I told you that my
son and my daughter-in-law
can't make it this Christmas?
So, I was wondering if you
would like to come to my place
and help me eat all that
goldarn turkey that I bought.
Flo, I would like
that very much.
- [chuckles]
- Great.
I need to get back
for the mingle, soon.
But I really want to show you
my idea for the lobby first.
So I'm thinking we redo this
whole reception area here.
Oh, shoot.
Madame Fontaine, I
forgot to charge my phone
so I might lose you,
but what do you think?
Whatever you like, Georgia.
Okay. Great.
Are you sure you don't
wanna ask Jean-Luc?
Jean-Luc is not here.
He's found a more
amusing way to vacation.
There's got to be charger
in here somewhere.
Of course.
[exhales sharply] Oh, the party.
[groans]
What? Oh, the app.
Oh, my God. No,
no, no, no, no.
Hello?
[mouthed] Can anybody
hear me? Hello?
Help!
Hello?
[indifferent city bustle]
[Christmas party music playing]
[Kiki] Has anyone seen Georgia?
I've been calling her
for like the last hour
and it just keeps
going to voicemail.
What about the milkmaids?
Them too?
Great. That is just great.
[laughs] If it isn't
Little Miss Edwina Scrooge.
You know what? Not
tonight, Santa, okay?
I've got no pipers,
my drummers cancelled,
and my lords 'a' leaping are
stuck on the train from Brooklyn,
along with the rest of
the 12 Days of Christmas.
I don't even have a...
Hey, Santa.
How'd you like to go to a party?
Thought you'd never ask.
[upbeat music playing]
Well, Merry Christmas.
Are we, uh, single or
not yet ready to mingle?
Um, single I guess.
[chuckles] Single,
it is. Enjoy.
Thank you.
Stop fidgeting.
You look just fine.
Now, this is a nice, normal party
full of nice, normal people.
[gasps] Thank you.
This is going to be just
the inspiration you need.
[glasses clink]
Something's wrong. I know it.
This isn't like her.
Perhaps, she changed
her mind about coming.
Georgia wouldn't do that.
This party was her idea
in the first place.
She loves the Jingle Mingle.
Well, maybe she doesn't
love it anymore.
[Prince Raymond] Listen, I
think I know where Georgia is.
- [knocking]
- [Georgia] Help.
Please, help me.
Hello? Hi. Hi.
[silence]
Help, please. Help
me get out, please.
[silence]
[groans]
[sighs]
[party swing playing]
[man] I own a
frozen yogurt store
and our signature
flavor is vanilla.
In my free time, I collect vintage khakis,
you know, from different eras in history.
Some people believe that
khaki originated in 1930s,
but you can actually trace the
origin of the pants to the 1840s.
[chuckles]
Excuse me.
[sniffs] [sighs]
If this is normal, I quit.
[sighs]
Look, I'm sorry.
I'm just not ready
to do this yet.
Sorry, sir?
Oh, just talking to the dog.
Oh.
Well, that's everything then.
You're not joining everyone
for the Jingle Mingle tonight?
No, I'm not.
Besides, what's so great
about mingling, anyway?
[barking]
Dickens! Dickens!
[excited barking]
Dickens!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
[panting]
[elevator dings]
"Good girll pose," Amazing.
Perfect. Those are some
real Santa selfies.
You know where to find me
afterwards if it gets too cold.
Oh, speaking of...
Thank you. Thank you.
Santas are supposed to be
having milk and cookies.
Yeah, but this Santa
wants champagne
because I've been working
incredibly hard for this.
- I'm not dropping it.
- [Kiki] Drop it! Drop it!
- [thuds]
- [sparks]
[startled hubbub]
[barking]
Dickens.
Just look at what
you did, Santa.
Santa!
Dickens!
Hi.
Going somewhere?
Um...
I'll, uh, I'll go check the
fuses, you keep them calm.
- [clears throat]
- What? What?!
Hey, everyone.
Wow. [laughs]
What a Christmas surprise! I
should ask Santa for new wiring!
[dramatic music playing]
[Luke] No, I thought that was
the whole point of our tree?
People bring their
own ornaments.
Makes it feel more like
home. Look at that.
Not bad for a seven-year-old.
Hey, making lunch for you
is the highlight of my day.
[Kiki] It doesn't matter how
much glitter you throw around.
There really is no
such thing as magic.
[dramatic music playing]
[groaning]
[knocking]
Oh, my God. [chuckling] Yes.
Hi. Hi. Yes. Thank
you. Thank you.
Hi. Oh, my God. Um, uh,
can you get the app?
[silence]
You need to get an app for
the building to open the door.
There's that.
[Kiki] All right, everyone. Lights
will be back on in just a minute.
Have some more champagne, right?
Luke. Everybody's leaving.
Can you get them to play
some music or something?
With what? The
power is still out.
My party-giving reputation
is going to be over
before it even started.
I'm sorry.
I really thought I
could do this, but...
Hey. Breakups are hard.
You know?
But you can't let it
define your whole life.
So how do you get past it?
Maybe you don't.
Maybe you just go through it.
Sounds easier than it feels.
Well, there's no rule that
says you have to do it alone.
[indistinct chatter]
How long do you think it's gonna
take to get the power back on?
Beats me. Some things
just take time, you know?
Victor, I thought you
didn't want anyone to know?
I thought you didn't
want anyone to know.
Come here.
Victor, people are looking.
Good, because I want
them to see this.
Anna...
I know this is only our
first Christmas together,
but I know I wanna spend all
the rest of mine with you.
Oh, he's doing it.
Will you marry me?
Yes. Yes.
[applause]
Woo!
[playing piano]
♪ Hmm ♪
♪ Mm-hmm ♪
♪ I've seen glittering
lights on cold wind tonight ♪
♪ And snow that falls
soft as a kiss ♪
♪ All those
last-minute shoppers ♪
♪ With brightly
wrapped packages ♪
♪ Checking off their
Christmas lists ♪
♪ Crackling fireplace ♪
♪ Family gathered ♪
♪ Stockings all hung in a row ♪
♪ Cookies are baking ♪
♪ Memories making ♪
♪ Oh, how I love it so ♪
♪ Because I want my
very own Christmas ♪
♪ I want carols and
toys on the tree ♪
♪ I know that somewhere
you're out there ♪
♪ Please won't you share
Christmas with me? ♪
♪ No mistletoe kisses ♪
♪ No presents from Grandma ♪
♪ I've never trimmed
my own tree ♪
♪ I love to read
stories to little kids ♪
♪ Dreaming of the Santa
They're hoping to see ♪♪
I thought you
weren't gonna come.
I almost didn't make it.
It's a long story,
but I don't know.
Maybe modern isn't all
it's cracked up to be.
All I wanted was
to get back here.
Seriously? Look at this
place, the lights don't work.
[clicks tongue]
The candles have mystery.
Then we need to change
that ancient rug.
Ancient? I think
you mean vintage.
There are cracks in the wall.
Cracks add the magic in.
I thought you didn't
believe in magic.
Maybe it's time to start.
[Pandora] ♪ Please won't you
share Christmas with me? ♪
♪ Yes, I want my
very own Christmas ♪
♪ I want carols and
toys on the tree ♪
♪ I know that somewhere
you're out there ♪
♪ Please, please ♪
♪ Please won't you
share this Christmas ♪
♪ With me? ♪♪
[applause]
That was a beautiful song.
Thank you.
I wrote it a long time ago and I
never thought anybody wanna hear it.
Oh, I love everything
you do, Pandora.
How'd you know?
I'd recognize your
voice anywhere.
You're very big in my country.
In fact, it was your song,
"Hey, You Get Off My Throne"
that gave me the courage to drop
my title and to go my own way.
Wow.
Single version or the dance mix?
Dance mix.
Um, excuse me, everyone.
Merry Christmas.
I'm sorry that I'm late.
And I'm sorry about
the electricity.
This is a really,
really old building.
- But, we love it.
- We love it.
Yes. Yes, I do, too. I just...
I didn't realize exactly
how much until tonight.
I guess I'd forgotten that
there's magic in this place.
You just have to believe in it.
Raymond,
I don't wanna own the
Auberge Moderne, I'm sorry.
I truly thought that I did,
but it turns out owning isn't
as important as belonging.
I think I belong here.
My Christmas wish to all of you is that
you find the place where you belong,
whether it's family,
or friends...
[chuckles]
or an old building.
Merry Christmas.
[all] Merry Christmas.
And a very Happy
New Year. [sobbing]
- [applause]
- Thank you. Thank you.
[hopeful music playing]
[Georgia] I thought these
would make you laugh.
[Prince Raymond] Sweatpants...
They're perfect. Thank you.
No, thank you for everything.
I'm truly sorry everything
didn't work out.
Oh, but it did.
Turns out my last release was a
huge hit in Caspernia, who knew?
The Prince, I mean, Ray-Ray,
is putting together a big
tour for me over there.
And the plane leaves in two
hours, so, Merry Christmas.
Merry Christmas.
Merry Christmas!
Bye.
Oh, I'll catch up.
[Kiki] Job's perfect. And
then I got all of these.
This ended up being fine.
- This is...
- Kiki.
Hi.
It's me.
Pam?
[chuckles] Actually,
I'm Pandora.
Wow!
This is amazing.
I'm sorry that I couldn't
tell you the truth.
But well, I just
wanted to say thank you
for showing me Christmas.
Honestly, you're the closest thing
to a best friend I've ever had.
Merry Christmas, Pam... Pandora.
Merry Christmas,
Kiki. [chuckles]
Wow. So she was
Pandora all along.
[laughs] How about
that Pandora?
[Kiki] Gosh.
Yeah. Who's, uh, Pandora?
[indistinct chatter]
Madame Fontaine, what
are you doing here?
When we were cut off
from talking yesterday,
I realized something.
There, I was on a yacht
alone at Christmas and why?
So, I decided to get on the first
flight and tell you something in person.
Actually, um, I have something
I have to tell you, too.
- The deal is off.
- The deal is off. What?
I don't want another hotel.
I want this hotel
with you in it.
I want you to be the Executive
Director of the Hotel Fontaine.
There will be a salary
increase, of course,
as well as another
little incentive.
Would you accept
49% ownership of
the Hotel Fontaine?
- What?
- I just think that
everybody deserves something
extra at Christmas.
I'll let you decide.
Are you at the hotel?
Let me show you to the bar.
Um, did you just hear that?
Uh-huh. I guess I'll be coming to
you about a raise after the holidays.
I have a better idea.
How would you like the events
and marketing position
at the Hotel Fontaine?
There is no events and
marketing position.
There is now.
That is, if you'll forgive me.
Oh, my gosh. Of
course I forgive you.
What are best friends for?
But do you think you could
keep an eye on the concierge
desk for me for just a minute?
I do have to drop these
swans off before noon.
Hand it over.
Thank you.
Oh, Georgia, I, uh, forgot
to give you this back.
Actually, Milton, why
don't you keep it?
No, no, no, I, I couldn't.
I'm not the, uh...
Sure you can. It goes
with your new job.
What? Really? [chuckles]
Merry Christmas, Milton.
Thank you.
Merry Christmas.
Wow.
- So, Manager, huh?
- Yeah.
- [laughter]
- Oh.
- Here. Can I help you with that?
- Oh, please.
- Yeah.
- Yeah. All right.
Well, I guess I'll need to get a new
blazer to go with my green scarf.
Oh.
So, Milton, I have a
confession to make.
You do?
Yeah. You know the bar sink that
you always start with sabotaged.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
It was.
It was?
Merry Christmas, Flo.
Merry Christmas.
[chuckles]
- It was?
- Yeah.
[Hunter] So, when do you think
you'll be back in New York?
[AJ] Oh, probably tomorrow.
What?
Yeah. This is a staycation.
I live in New Jersey.
Geez, Santa. Come on.
Don't you take
Christmas Day off?
Well, that depends.
What are you doing for
the rest of the day?
["For the Holidays" by Shenna]
♪ ’Cause in colder weather ♪
♪ We'll stay warm together ♪
♪ All I want is you
for the holidays ♪
I heard the good news.
- Congratulations.
- [Georgia] Thank you.
Oh, Luke, I actually don't have time
for lunch right now, but thank you.
Who said anything about lunch?
Our first selfie.
Farfalle dyed with fruit juice.
I graduated from macaroni.
[Georgia] Oh, it's perfect.
I have a lot I wanna say to you.
But for now, will
Merry Christmas do?
Merry Christmas
will do just fine.
♪ We're fa-la-la-la-la-la,
Falling in love ♪
♪ Fa-la-la-la-la-la-la-la,
♪ To the bells, as they play ♪
Well, tree is still crooked.
You know what?
I think I like it
better this way.
♪ All I want is you
for the holidays ♪
♪ We're fa-la-la-la-la-la,
Falling in love ♪
♪ Fa-la-la-la-la-la-la-la,
♪ To the bells, as they play ♪
Falling in love ♪
♪ Fa-la-la-la-la-la-la-la,
♪ To the bells, as they play ♪
♪ All I want is you
for the holidays ♪
♪ 'Oh, the snow
is falling down ♪
♪ And the lights
shine all around ♪
♪ The memories we make ♪
♪ Are gifts our
hearts will save ♪
♪ Fa-la-la-la-la-la-la-la,
Falling in love ♪
♪ Fa-la-la-la-la-la-la-la ♪
♪ Oh, we’re fa-la-la-la-la-la,
Falling in love ♪
♪ Fa-la-la-la-la-la-la-la,
♪ To the bells, as they play ♪
♪ All I want is you
for the holidays ♪
[upbeat music playing]
[singer] ♪ Jolly
old St. Nicholas ♪
♪ Lean your ear this way ♪
♪ Don't you tell a single soul ♪
♪ What I'm going to say ♪
♪ Christmas Eve is coming soon ♪
♪ Now, you dear old man ♪
♪ Whisper what
you'll bring to me ♪
♪ Tell me if you can ♪
♪ When the clock
is striking 12:00 ♪
♪ When I'm fast asleep ♪
♪ Down the chimney
broad and black ♪
♪ With your pack you'll creep ♪
♪ All the stockings
you will find ♪
♪ Hanging in a row ♪
♪ Mine will be
the shortest one ♪
♪ You'll be sure to know ♪
♪ Johnny wants a
pair of skates ♪
♪ Suzy wants a sled ♪
♪ Nellie wants a picture book ♪
♪ Yellow, blue, and red ♪
♪ Now I think I leave to you ♪
♪ What to give the rest ♪
♪ Choose for me
dear Santa Claus ♪
♪ What you think is best! ♪
♪ Choose for me
dear Santa Claus ♪
♪ What you think is best! ♪♪