(MultiCom Jingle)
(dramatic music)
- [Boy] Okay freshmen, you've
got two minutes to run.
Then we come and get ya!
Go!
Did you see 'em take off?
They just get dumber every day.
- [Boy] Yeah, genetic weakness I betcha!
(laughing)
- [Boy] Yeah.
- [Boy] Hurry up, load 'em up!
Coming to get you, Kimball!
(laughing)
Kimball, Kimball the thimble.
Alright, that's two minutes.
You ready?
- [Boy] I'm always ready.
- [Boy] Let's go.
You better run!
(laughing)
Hey it's survival of the fittest, Kimball!
This is awesome!
- [Boy] Come out come
out wherever you are.
You might as well give up you freshmen!
We'll be easier on you!
- Guys, can we make a deal?
I got two Snickers in my backpack!
- [Boy] No way, we ain't
making no deals man.
- Please!
- [Boys] No!
- [Boy] That's right
Kimball, you better run!
(exciting music)
Don't make us madder than we already are!
(laughing)
(howling)
- Hurry up, catch him!
- Run, run!
I smell fresh meat!
Almost.
- Lazy shot, dude.
- [Boy] Come on!
Hey Kimball, hey Kimball!
Paging Dr. Kimball!
(laughing)
Ah man.
Run little piggy, run!
- [Boy] Can't you run any faster?
(laughing)
Hands up, piggy!
- Okay guys, I give up.
- [Boy] Gotcha Kimball.
- [Boy] We got you now.
(laughing)
- Not bad, huh?
A noble effort.
- For a shrimpus maximus.
- Any last words?
Guess not.
- [Boys] Three, two, one.
- Ready, aim, fire!
(paintball guns firing)
(crying out)
- [Kimball] Man, you messed up my clothes.
(laughing)
- School colors!
Blue and gold!
- Welcome to Washington High.
- Freshmen.
You guys are the same every year.
- My mom's gonna kill me about this shirt.
- You know Kimball, you're
not such a bad guy after all.
And to show you what good guys we are
we'll let you shoot some
pellets so you'll be ready
when you're a senior.
Go set these targets up, past that tree.
(laughing)
Moron.
- Yeah.
(eerie music)
- Guys.
Soldiers.
- Yeah, I know they're soldiers.
I got them at Walmart, moron.
- No!
I mean real soldiers!
- What?
- [Kimball] Hey guys, how about a ride
on the back of your bike?
- [Boy] You're on your own, man.
- Thanks for nothing!
- Run!
(dramatic music)
(screams)
- Whoa.
What are you doing?
- You're coming with us.
- [Kimball] No, no!
- This is a disaster.
- Come on guys, let me go.
I've got two Snickers in my backpack.
Come on.
- Make sure the perimeter
is secure, that's an order.
This little event could
severely compromise the project.
- Well, at least we know it works.
- Works!
It was supposed to make them invisible,
not send them off into some new dimension.
Can we get them back?
- Back?
I'm more concerned about
what we're gonna do with him.
- Me?
I didn't see a thing!
Well I saw something, but
it was so unbelievable
that I couldn't have seen it.
And by the way, did I
mention that I've got
two Snickers in my backpack?
- Sorry kid.
Chocolate makes me nauseous.
- No, no!
(zaps)
- Alright gentlemen,
let's make our other problems disappear.
Move out!
(booming)
(exciting music)
(gentle music)
- Where's this one go?
It's not labeled.
- Andy, just set that down, I'll get it.
- I don't mind.
- It's fragile Andy, I'll get it.
- Dad, Dad, Dad!
- Whoa, whoa, whoa!
You better be careful
there, you little wild man.
I gotta check in at work.
- The pizza's on its way.
- Well I'm sorry hon,
you'll have to save me
a few slices.
Andy.
Now listen, you know I
appreciate your help.
I just don't want you to touch
any of the unlabeled boxes.
Okay?
- Okay.
- Okay?
- Fine, yeah.
(roaring)
Come on Cameron.
You can help me destroy the upstairs.
Go on, I'll meet you up there.
Here, let me help you with that.
- Oh, you're saving my life.
How do you like the place?
- I like the old place better.
- I know, but your dad
couldn't pass up this job.
- John's not my dad.
- He adores you and Cameron.
You know that, don't you?
- He adores Cameron.
I mean I'm just another troublesome teen.
- That's unfair, Andy.
I understand how you must feel,
but you've got to try to see things
from John's point of view.
(mysterious music)
- We're ready for the
sequencing demo, Boyd.
Let's start with level
one but build it up slow.
- Righty-o.
(beeping)
- Alright, let's go to
level two, reach stability.
Alright.
Well well.
Oh Boyd.
You lied about quitting smoking.
And your lunch looks like something
that might make a repeat appearance.
- Privacy.
A thing of the past.
- We're destabilizing.
Try level three right now, hurry.
Hurry!
(beeping)
Oh, we were so close!
(clapping)
- Bravo, John.
That's the nearest we've ever
come to stabilizing the image.
How'd you do it?
- I just replaced the old processors
with self-cooling crystal chips.
Just declassified by military.
- How'd you get that so fast?
- Friends in low places, I guess.
- You've been with us less than a week
and you've already
accomplished more than we have
in six months.
Isn't that right, Boyd?
- Oh yes sir, Mr. Baker.
Old John's a real achiever.
We make a good team.
- Get me a cup of coffee would you Boyd?
- I don't remember seeing coffee jockey
listed in my job description.
Is that a cream with two sugars?
- Absolutely.
John, I want to thank you
for relocating so quickly.
- Don't mention it, I
appreciate the opportunity.
And the family's adjusting
okay, with one exception.
- Ah, you've got a teenager.
(chuckling)
- And how.
My stepson, his name's
Andy, he's a sophomore.
We pulled him out of school mid-September.
He left his one best friend,
four potential girlfriends.
You do the math.
- Not too happy a lad, I take it.
- Oh Mr. Baker, you're a
master of understatement.
- I might be able to help.
I'll call the science
teacher at Washington High
and arrange a field trip to the labs.
Your stepson can see where
you work, his chums can see
how cool you are, instant popularity,
end of adjustment problem.
- You can arrange that?
- Well it does help to be on good terms
with the president of the school board.
- Let me guess, you.
- Modesty forbids.
- Hey butthead.
Hey, you don't show me much.
- I got nothing to prove.
- 'Cause you've got nothing!
(laughing)
- You got something to say?
- Ha ha ha.
(honks)
- Andy, it's a school day tomorrow.
Come on, come on home.
- Now in lateral magnification for rays,
the rays coming from an object point not
on the object axis is called a coma.
Now if a coma is present
light from a point
is spread around into a family.
Guys guys please please.
So can anyone here name other
electromagnetic radiation
that cannot be seen by the naked eye?
Sam, can you give somebody
else a chance please?
- Like who?
- [Teacher] Anybody?
- Okay how about microwave and infrared.
- That's a good start.
Iris.
- The other side of the spectrum.
Ultraviolet radiation, x-rays, gamma rays.
- Well I'm glad somebody
does her homework here.
(giggling)
(clears throat)
Mr. Carver.
Can you tell us the range on the spectrum
where the visible light falls?
You just moved here from Chicago, right?
- Yeah.
- Let's imagine you could
cut the country in half.
Chicago would fall roughly in the...
- In the middle?
- So the range of visible
light would fall in the...
- Middle of the spectrum?
- Nicely done.
Light from the sun that's white light
can be refracted through a
prism into all wavelengths
of light.
- [Boy] It's the rainbow.
- Kind of like the album cover
of Dark Side of the Moon.
The album Dark Side of the Moon?
Pink Floyd?
- Dude!
Yeah dude!
- You know guys, there was rock and roll
before The Offspring, huh?
(school bell rings)
Wait wait wait.
Listen, before you leave,
make sure make sure make sure
you get your permission slips
signed for the field trip
tomorrow, we're going to VectreComp.
Okay?
(gentle music)
- [Girl] Hey, there's the new kid.
- Hey, where's Carver's buttcrack?
In the middle!
(laughing)
- At least I'm not a Neanderthal.
- Smarter than he looks.
- Mm hmm.
(growling)
- Hmm, who replaced my son with Godzilla?
(laughing)
(door shuts)
(whistling)
- Hi Dad.
- Hi.
- What were you doing in the basement?
- Oh, nothing exciting I'm afraid.
So, how's the new school?
- Good.
- Thrilling.
- Any girls?
(laughs)
- I have to go finish unpacking my room.
- Andy.
Andy.
(laughs)
(dog barking)
(soft music)
(knocking)
- [John] Can I come in?
- Yeah.
- It's gonna take a long
time, Andy, getting used
to the death of someone that you loved.
- Used to it?
- Yeah, you know.
Well you hear people talk
about getting over it,
but I don't think that's what happens.
I think you just adjust and you endure.
- You know my science class
is going on a field trip
to VectroComp tomorrow.
- Yeah I know, looking forward to it.
You know what I wish?
That I could have met your dad.
- John.
- Yeah.
- I'm looking forward to it also.
The field trip.
- Good.
Good night.
- Good night.
(light music)
- Hey Jerry.
- Oh thanks
for letting us do this.
So kids, come over here, we need to get
your ID badges on you.
Yes you too.
- Here's one for you.
Young lady.
And you.
- [Teacher] Please keep
your ID badges on you
at all times, okay kids?
- Hi, hey.
- God, security wasn't
like this on the field trip
to the dairy farm.
- Oh well it's the alien spacecraft.
We keep it in the basement.
- It was a joke, Agent Mulder.
- There is truth behind every joke.
- [Woman] John Carver, please come to
the third floor conference hall.
- Uh oh.
- [Woman] John Carver, please--
- Bad news?
- We'll see.
I'll catch up with you later, alright?
Go on, get up there.
(beeping)
(whistling)
(buzzes)
(beeping)
(whistling)
(buzzes)
Wrong.
(beeping)
(whistling)
(beeps)
- We've reached the
halfway point in our tour.
The public relations liaison
will be right with you.
Come.
Come on.
Please have a seat.
Somebody will be right with you.
- Hi Andy.
- Hi.
- You know, I knew
you were our connection
the minute I saw you.
- What is he talking about?
- The UFO.
- Huh?
- Reverse engineering of
alien technology Andy,
that's what we're talking about.
Now that guy you were talking to?
- My stepdad.
- Oh good, good, good,
then you guys are close.
What kind of information
can you get out of him?
Come on Andy, don't play
coy with us, we know
what's going on here,
we've heard the rumors.
VectroComp has connections
with every black ops division
in this government.
I mean everybody knows
that they were behind
the disappearance of
those kids four years ago.
- You know, down by Lake Cloverfield,
the secret government installation?
- Right.
- I've been down there.
All I've seen is an old
abandoned power plant.
Oh, you mean the secret
old abandoned power plant.
That's where my stepdad sells human women
to the alien overlords.
(laughing)
(mocking laughter)
- Laugh while you can, monkey boy.
The power plant is just a coverup.
Everything's underground.
Talking about miles and
miles, subterranean caverns,
underground tunnels.
Probably connected to this place even.
Why don't you ask you
stepdad about the spy?
- The spy?
- Oh!
Yeah.
Rumor has it that one of
the seven new employees here
at VectroComp is not
exactly what he seems to be.
(dramatic music)
- It's fragile Andy, I'll get it.
I just don't want you to
touch any unlabeled boxes.
(whistling)
- Corporate espionage, Andy.
- Are you guys up for some exploring?
- Maybe you didn't see our name tags?
They say limited access.
- [Andy] Come on.
- Hey loser, where are you going?
- Hey, who cares?
(mysterious music)
- It's a code lock, what now?
(beeping)
(whistling)
(beeps)
- Did I mention that you rock?
- You know I just, I don't
know where to go from here.
You're leading us in circles, Boyd.
Why can't I shake the
feeling that you simply
don't have the slightest
idea what the problem is?
- I do know what the problem is, Malcolm.
The crystal is unstable.
- Yes, I understand,
you've been telling me that
for three days now.
Are you with us, John?
- Sorry Malcolm.
(mysterious music)
- I'm sorry.
I shouldn't be apologizing
to you, both of you.
Been pushing too hard.
Somebody's looking over
our shoulder on this one.
It's got me on edge.
We need a solution.
Which is why I'm putting you in charge
of the project, John.
It's time for a new vision.
We'll go back to diagnostics,
we're going to run
that program again.
(mysterious music)
- [Sam] We're gonna get caught.
- Don't worry about it, relax.
- Okay what now brain boy?
No way is it gonna be
the same code we used
to get into the corridor.
(beeping)
(whistling)
(beeps)
- Whoa.
- Oh yeah, awesome.
- Hey, check this out.
We became outlaws for
this lame Star Trek prop?
- Hey, there's nothing
lame about Star Trek.
The original series.
- There's gotta be something
cool about the glasses,
otherwise why all the security?
- To throw people like us off the trail
of what really goes on here.
All we've gotta do is find the right lab.
(beeping)
- Dark Side of the Moon.
(keyboard clicking)
- What are you doing?
- This should be--
- Andy, I don't think you should--
- Look come on, you're gonna
get us all landed in jail, alright?
- This should be a three.
Three.
(beeping)
- Whoa.
Awesome.
(beeping)
(whistles)
(beeps)
- After you.
- Get away from there!
What do you think you're doing?
- How'd you get in here, Andy?
- You know this young man?
- He's my stepson.
- Well you better have a good lawyer
because I am calling security.
- Hold it, hold it.
Hold on.
You're not calling anyone, Boyd.
- But--
- John.
Take a look.
- Malcolm, it works.
- Yes.
- What did you do?
- Well I, there was a
slight error in the math.
An eight instead of a three.
It must have been a typo.
- Like this kid can correct my math.
- I'm afraid he has.
Would you like to take a look?
Alright.
- Oh here, Andy, use the remote.
Now push right here, controls
the level of the x-ray.
- [Andy] Whoa.
Cool.
Oh yeah.
Man.
- Hey, whoa there super boy!
- Alright, alright.
There.
Like 'em?
- Are you kidding?
- Boyd, I want these locked in the vault.
No one signs them out without
my permission, understood?
- Yes sir.
- Let's take the afternoon
off to celebrate.
Then we'll get to work
refining the controls,
especially the cloaking system.
Young man, while I certainly don't approve
of the way you went about
it, you've made a major
breakthrough for us and I thank you.
Now I'm afraid it's
time you got your butts
out of my top security laboratory.
(mysterious music)
- I forgot my backpack.
- [Boyd] Forget something?
- Thanks.
- Let me guess, they caused
some kind of trouble.
- Oh no no, far from it.
- Sam.
- Come here.
Andy, you know I find
myself strangely torn.
You broke into a top secret facility.
Last time I checked, that
fell in the category of bad.
Oh man.
But I am proud of you.
See you tonight.
- Okay, moms go rest, nine
year olds get ready for bed.
- Go.
- Scientists and spies do the dishes.
Come on.
- Well.
Guess we'd better get to
it, especially with all
the unpacking we've got to do.
Oh.
(dog barking)
(sighs)
So I'll wash, you dry, okay?
- Okay, okay.
John?
- Yeah?
- Why do you always keep
the basement locked?
- Well I got some equipment down there.
You know those boxes I
asked you not to mess with.
- What kind of a equipment?
- I'll show you when I get
it all unpacked, alright?
Hey, grab those dishes
over there, would you?
- Honey, I'm home.
(gentle music)
Hello dear.
- I didn't hear you come in.
- I've got some news.
The glasses.
They work.
It's only a matter of
time before we refine them
so that they work across
the entire spectrum.
And then I'm going to take
you outside and show you
the world.
What do you think about that?
(laughing)
- [Wife] Wonderful.
(dramatic music)
- Why don't you just cut
a path with a chainsaw,
might make less noise?
- Lieutenant Biddle.
- Give me some good news.
Alright, let's change our tactic then.
Give me any news.
- Glasses work and I managed
to smuggle them out of the lab.
- And the cloaking device?
- Let's just say that it's not 100%.
- Let's have them.
- You see that's where we
get into this whole gray area
between good news and just news.
(sighs)
- I am beginning to think that
you were put on this earth
expressly to punish me!
Take a stab at the gray area, Mr. Russell.
- A kid has them.
- A kid?
- It's not just a kid, it's the son, well,
it's the stepson of the new
scientist at VectroComp.
See I used him as a mule
to smuggle the glasses
out of the lab but he's also
the reason that the cloaking
device hasn't been perfected.
I deliberately screwed
up the math that controls
the shield of the prism inside the glasses
to buy more time to work on the cloak
and then this punk kid comes
in and corrects my math.
Oh I'm glad you're amused by this.
- Oh far from it, Mr. Russell.
You know very well the
success of our mission
depends on that cloaking device.
I could care less about the x-ray vision,
the military applications are minimal.
But invisibility, now
there's an offensive weapon.
And since you failed
so miserably to develop
the technology on your own,
I risk personal discovery
to set you up at VectroComp
so you could simply
steal what we need!
And you failed at that too!
- Not yet.
- Use what has been
given you, Mr. Russell.
The boy, his stepfather,
and bring me those glasses.
(ominous music)
- Back soon Mom, going to the park.
- [Grode] Yo Ritchie,
check out who's coming.
(rock music)
(laughs)
- Well well well, if it
ain't Robbie Knievel, huh.
- Hey Moe, hey Curly.
- That's funny, we're the two stooges.
You gonna put on another
daredevil thrill show for us?
Impress the girls?
- Why not?
- Think you can jump the bear?
- Oh come on, even you
could jump the bear.
- You're just a laugh riot, aren't you?
- Grode, make a ramp.
- Okay.
- [Richie] Come on, you chicken.
(mimicking chicken)
(laughing)
- Hey, don't worry, there's
a payphone down the street
and we'll call you an ambulance.
(mimicking chicken)
(shouting)
(laughing)
- Oh man!
- Woo, come on let's go
to the Crunchy Freeze.
Grode's buying.
- Oh, you bet.
Come on, let's go.
- [Richie] Shotgun!
- Oh no.
This is not good.
(dramatic music)
Wow.
Whoa.
- This oughta be like
taking candy from a baby.
- Oh man.
- You know what?
I think I'm beginning
to get a clear picture
of what this alien abduction
stuff is all about.
The Kennedy assassination.
- Wait a minute.
- Oh no no no no.
Extraterrestrials, the
grays, were in league
with Kennedy's rivals in the government,
not to mention, you know, the mafia.
I've been over and over this,
it's finally obvious to me
that Lee Harvey Oswald and
Jack Ruby were both abductees.
Ruby killed Oswald to
prevent him from revealing
the alien implant in his brain.
The same implant that
transmitted the extraterrestrial,
you know, signal ordering Oswald
to kill President Kennedy.
- [Andy] Guys!
- Oh thank god.
Finally.
- Some frequency, Kenneth.
- You guys aren't gonna believe this.
- You stole the glasses?
He stole the glasses.
- Andy!
- Boyd, Boyd, Boyd--
- He stole the glasses!
- Boyd, in my backpack.
I need to talk to you guys, just--
- Oh no no no oh no.
I'm not going to jail for you, Andy.
- Come here, come on.
- Alright.
- Look, Boyd, he must
have slipped the glasses
in my backpack and I think
that my stepdad's involved too.
- That's crazy!
- I know, but something's going on.
(ominous music)
There's some shady action
going on in the basement.
He keeps it locked and
acted very suspicious
when I asked him about it.
- Has he ever been abducted by aliens?
Okay, alright fine.
Let's take the investigative approach.
What would your dad and this guy Boyd
want with some goofy looking glasses?
- I dunno, they want to join Devo.
- Would you stop making jokes Andy?
This is serious!
- Better listen to him, Andy.
This is very serious.
Just give me the glasses, Andy.
I'll see to it the
authorities never find out
what your stepfather has done.
Come on Andy.
Just give me the glasses.
Andy.
Gimme the glasses!
- [Iris] Run, run!
- [Sam] I got him, I got him, I got him.
(dramatic music)
- Alright kid, you made your decision.
I hope you like not having a father.
- Wait wait wait wait.
What's going on?
Uh oh, this is not good.
- Why don't you put the
glasses on and find out
what's going on inside?
(snaps)
- I see about five or six figures.
I think that's my mom.
- Andy?
- What?
(buzzing)
- The glasses.
They're, uh, they're gone.
- Then why am I counting your ribs?
- No, I'm telling you,
they're completely invisible.
- Hey, I can't get 'em loose.
Oh no!
This is not good.
They're taking John away.
What are we gonna do?
- I dunno.
- Guys guys guys guys!
Hey guys, I was afraid that
Boyd had caught you guys!
- They arrested John.
- What?
- Yeah, and the glasses,
they're invisible.
- And I can't get 'em off my face.
- No.
- Oh great.
What else could possibly go wrong?
- Look, just give me the remote and maybe
we can power them down and
I can reverse the process.
- Yeah.
- Uh oh.
- What do you mean uh oh!
Sam!
Jeez!
- I must have lost it.
- Let's go let's go.
- God!
- Okay look, whatever's
causing this invisibility
must be creating some
kind of magnetic field.
- Are you saying that my head is magnetic?
- Okay who am I, Spock?
I don't know how these things work!
(groaning)
- I can see in the basement.
- What is it?
- It's real hard to make out.
I'm kinda seeing through it too.
It looks like lab equipment maybe.
We're gonna have to break in.
We gotta see what John's been up to.
- So that's where you went.
I'm always losing the remote.
- Perhaps I should pursue
a career in criminal arts.
- Guys?
- Alright, you tell me,
what is all this stuff?
(mysterious music)
- Whoa.
- It's your birthday present.
Your dad was gonna
build you a science lab.
- I didn't do it, Malcolm.
You have to know that.
- Do I?
I've known you about a week, John.
Our people are put
through the most intense
security measures
possible, but maybe, maybe
you slipped past us.
I'm afraid I don't know
what kind of a man you are.
What I do know is that your stepson,
a 15 year old boy, somehow
managed to break into
a high securance laboratory,
a lab that you know
the entrance code to.
And while in that lab, he
was able to solve a problem
that's been plaguing
this project for months.
And now that project has been stolen.
I didn't design those
x-ray glasses because
I wanted to change the world,
John, or to give the military
some swell new weapon.
My wife has been blind
since she was a little girl.
My hope is that the
technology can be improved
to the point that she'll
be able to see again.
- I can't believe I lost the remote.
I'm such a loser.
- I'm not just a loser,
I'm a big suck loser.
- You know if there were
a royal family of losers
we would be the inbred mutants
forced to live in the basement.
- Yeah and eat rats.
- Mm hmm.
- Man cry me a river.
Look.
We can either sit here and
whine or do something about it.
- Mm, whine.
- It's almost time for Buffy.
(buzzing)
(shouts)
- Hey!
- What is it?
- The effect, it's getting weaker.
Your flesh and muscles are coming back.
- Hey, don't go exploring, Columbus.
(buzzes)
(shouts)
- The effect, it's getting stronger now!
It's freaking me out!
- I think someone's using the remote.
- Maybe the person who's
using it is still in the park.
- Alright look, sit down in
here, just stay here okay,
we'll be back in a few minutes.
Alright, let's go.
- I can see through my eyelids!
(suspenseful music)
- Come on, this way.
- I can see through my eyelids.
Stop this!
Oh.
(groaning and shouting)
- [Sam] Where is it?
- Man am I an idiot.
The solution has been right
in front of me the whole time!
All I've gotta do is go
see Malcolm and tell him
what happened.
(mysterious music)
Wow.
(doorbell rings)
- Hello, is someone there?
Yes?
- Um, hi, is Malcolm in?
- No I'm sorry, he's not.
He had some business to take care of.
- Could you tell him that
Andy Carver came by please?
- Of course.
- Tell him that I have
something that belongs to him.
- Is there anything else?
- No, thank you.
- [Wife] Okay then, good night.
- Did you find it?
- No.
Alright look, if you were a
remote, where would you be?
- Definitely not in this forest.
- I can't believe this.
Just forget it, okay, just forget it.
I'm a loser, alright?
- And the fact that you lost the remote?
Yeah.
Otherwise, you're a
perfectly acceptable guy.
So knock off that loser stuff.
I mean, don't get me wrong, I still think
you're certifiably insane.
(dramatic music)
Duck!
Duck duck duck!
Boyd.
What does he want now?
- Maybe he's got the remote.
Okay, let's go.
- I have some good news and I have some,
well I don't know what the good news is,
but I have it.
Lieutenant Biddle, how are you?
- Let's cut the niceties.
News, good, bad, whatever.
- I set up the stepfather.
He's sitting in a jail cell right now
and that should buy us some time.
- You were actually doing
pretty well until you said that.
You don't have the glasses.
- The kid still has them.
You want some good news?
The cloaking device works.
The bad news is we haven't
been able to make it work right
which means the glasses are
bonded to the kid's face
unless of course we can
wire him to a computer
and shut 'em down using
the failsafe codes.
- And that's why you haven't
brought the glasses to me yet?
You're still not thinking
these things through, are you?
- What do you want from me?
The glasses are stuck to the kid's head.
- Then bring me the kid's head.
- We better go get Andy.
Look, he made that easy.
- [Sam] Oh my god, what's he doing here?
He's supposed to stay at home.
- [Iris] I dunno.
- Andy!
- I'm at one with the universe!
- Wow, he's totally freaking out.
- Andy, Andy, Andy are
you alright, you okay?
- I can see the eye of god.
- Andy, that's the Texaco sign.
- Okay, alright Andy, Andy, come on,
it's time to snap out of it, okay?
Pull yourself together, come on!
- These glasses are freaking me out!
Hey, are you slapping me?
- Look, Boyd is gonna do
a lot worse than slap you
if we don't get those
glasses off your face.
- No but you heard him, we can't do that
unless we hook him up
to the computer again.
- [Iris] What about the lab?
- Oh, okay, yeah great,
great, let's just break into
VectroComp again, that's a good one.
- No no no, the lab in Andy's basement.
Why don't we just make a new remote?
- Wait, we can do that?
- I don't see why not.
Come on, let's go!
- Hey guys, guys, help me, help me.
(mysterious music)
On the shelf.
- Come on baby, where are you?
Ah, gotcha.
Universal TV remote.
We'll see about that.
- Huh.
(machines whirring)
- Alright, screwdriver.
- Check.
- [Sam] Soldering iron.
- Various electronic gizmos.
- Check?
- Brow.
Brow.
- Check.
- Ah.
Right tools for the right job.
- Right tools for the right job.
- You know it actually
looks like a model car
I built in the fifth grade
and subsequently blew up
with an M80.
- This is never gonna work.
- Could you be a little
bit more optimistic please?
- Shh.
Did you guys hear something?
- I can't see anything.
- Alright, let's start with
turning off the cloaking device.
Yeah?
(buzzing)
(crying out)
Okay okay okay okay okay.
So what I meant to say was
I'll decrease the level
of the x-ray effect.
- It's working.
It's working!
- Shh, shh!
(suspenseful music)
Okay, maybe I'm just nuts,
but I think there's something
creepy going on upstairs.
- What do you mean, like
parents making out creepy
or like serial killers
on the loose creepy?
- There's definitely something up there.
It could be a cat but
the glasses are really
out of control.
- That's no problem.
(bleeps)
Captain, please turn the phasers on stun.
- Come on.
(buzzes)
(cries out)
- [Andy] What'd you do?
- Same thing I did last
time, didn't it work?
- [Andy] You zapped me.
- Shh!
Shh!
Am I the only one who is
a little bit concerned
about the cat or whatever it is upstairs?
- You're not really
afraid of a cat, are you?
- He said it might be a cat.
Operative word might.
- There's definitely
something up in the carport.
If it is a cat, it's really big.
- Like how big?
- Who cares?
Look, we know that the
remote control works
so I say we play with it later.
Come on, out the window,
better safe than sorry
I always say.
- I've never heard you say that before.
Here here here, let me
dial it down some more.
(buzzes)
- Ow, you shocked me!
- Wait wait wait.
Okay, let's go over what we're gonna do.
So what's the plan?
- We take the fight to them.
- Oh, and the insane guy
says take the fight to them.
And everybody laughed and laughed.
- We've got to go out
to the old power plant.
I mean with the x-ray
glasses I can find the secret
entrance to the base.
Maybe then we can find
the information we need
to shut these guys down
and clear John's name.
- Hey!
Wanna make this interesting, huh?
Okay I'll play.
I'll play.
- Richie, we're not supposed to be here,
it's government property.
- Nobody tells me where to go.
- Guys guys guys.
I can't do it.
- What?
- I can't, I can't go on.
- [Andy] Why not?
- Do you even know what's out there?
I'm telling you, more than
the truth is out there.
Okay scary stuff is out there, alright?
- Look, Sam, we've been
friends a long time, right?
- Yeah.
- Wasn't it me who comforted
you when you found out
your sea monkeys couldn't drive Cadillacs?
- Yes.
- And wasn't it me who
calmed you down right after
you found out that your ant
farm would never grow crops?
- Yes.
- And wasn't it me who saved
you from extreme embarrassment
by pointing out that
the middle kid in Hanson
is a boy not a girl and that
maybe it wasn't a good idea
to send him a mushy fan letter?
The main thing is that
I'm your friend Sam,
and I'm not going to let
anything happen to you
that wouldn't happen to us.
Right Andy?
- Couldn't have said it better myself.
- Alright, okay, point taken.
Alright, you're right.
Let's go.
(owl hooting)
- Hold it, hold it.
Got two bogeys.
- That just sounds gross.
- 10 o'clock, behind the oak tree.
Two males, teenagers, maybe,
I think it's Richie and Grode.
- That's just fabulous.
You think they been following us?
- Initiate plan B.
- Right.
- Plan B?
What the heck is plan B?
Okay that's for leaving
me out of that one guys,
that's great.
(shouting)
(laughing)
- Nice boxer shorts, Richie.
Mama's little stinker?
- It's laundry day.
Hey, how did you know what I was wearing?
- My god.
- You freak, I'm gonna pummel you.
- You know you're trespassing here.
This is government property.
We can have you arrested.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- Why don't you go do that then.
Why don't you tell the
president of the school board
for all I care?
That'll get us in big trouble.
- We'll see.
Come on Grode.
- Hey, was he really wearing
mama's little stinker
underpants with the cartoon skunk?
- Yeah.
- Oh man.
I used to have a pair of
those in second grade.
You know, novelty item
to amuse the parents.
I used to put them on my head
and used to dance around--
- Too much information, Sam.
- Whatever.
- Let's go.
- [Man] Trespassers in area 102.
No no boys, you did the
right thing calling me.
- [Richie] That'll teach those idiots.
(laughing)
- Guys guys.
This is it.
This is where those kids
disappeared four years ago.
- This is area 102.
- Area 102?
- Twice as scary as Area 51.
- I better scan for
surveillance equipment.
Power me up to level two.
- Level two?
- Yeah, it just sounds cool.
- [Andy] I got some good
news and I got some bad news.
- Bad news.
- There are tons of laser
beams crisscrossing the ground.
- Good news?
- I don't know, I was just
trying to cushion the bad news.
Iris, put your arm around me.
- Hey look, I like you and
all, but I'm not that--
- Alright, just move when I move.
Three two one.
Okay, okay, this way, this way.
(suspenseful music)
Again, on three.
Two, one, and jump.
Okay straight, okay three, two, one, jump.
- Hey hey hey.
That's the power plant over there.
That means there must be an
entrance around here somewhere.
You know they have all these
for emergency evacuations.
- How do you know that?
- Standard covert military procedure,
read it on any website.
Okay look around at the trees
for any hairline fractures
or unusual root patterns.
- Hey, I see something.
Look.
Three two one and jump.
Alright, alright.
Foot over and jump.
We're clear.
- Oh that's cute.
So the masterminds behind this whole thing
are the Keebler elves?
- There's a chance we
could have just triggered
some kind of warning mechanism.
- How good a chance?
- I'd say at least 50/50.
- Sir, I'm showing
activity in quadrant six,
probably a glitch on the system.
- There's no such thing as a glitch.
Cross check everything, always.
(suspenseful music)
- [Iris] This is amazing.
- This is exactly like the
pictures on conspiracy.com.
Our tax dollars at work.
- You don't even have a job.
- Okay, my dad's taxes then.
This is a transcendent moment.
All my paranoias proven, justified.
My life has meaning and a purpose.
- Sam, save it for a
tell-all book and Springer.
- Springer?
Are you kidding?
60 Minutes or nothing.
- Guys, can we get back to
the matter at hand here?
We have to find the nerve center.
Take the fight to them, remember?
- Hey, footprints.
- They're not military tracks.
- The humidity and low
level lights are really
affecting these glasses.
It's hard to make out anything.
- Do you see any laser traps?
- No.
- Would you guys keep it down?
This place is probably wired for sound.
(suspenseful music)
- Hey, here's a door with no handle.
- Looks like a combo lock lateral slide.
Standard issue.
It's a pretty tricky tumbler.
Yeah.
Oh yeah.
- We're in.
- [Iris] Whoa.
- Sweet.
(dramatic music)
This is all from the corps of engineers.
- Hey, these are the
blueprints to this power plant.
And the overlay for this
underground construction.
- The whole power plant
was just a cover up
for these underground networks.
Divert the public's attention,
the old magician's trick.
- And to think the government
would deceive the public.
- Hey guys, look at this.
- Oh man, oh man.
Do you know what these things are?
God, I can't believe I
didn't bring my camera.
This is in my book for sure.
- What's so special about 'em?
- I mean all the pieces fit,
this just proves everything.
Don't you see?
These are the bikes that
those kids who disappeared on
were riding.
Stu Bryant, Delden Swanson, Kimball Pike.
Two were on bikes, one was on foot.
Look, they were playing paint wars.
Paintball guns.
Must have kept them here as evidence.
As cover up.
- Uh, do you have any other
questions you want answered?
- Yeah, like where are they.
(alarm blaring)
- Well you can ask the
three soldiers coming down the tunnel.
As for me, I'm outta here.
Iris?
- [Iris] I'm so gone.
- Look, get on the bike.
- I never learned to ride.
- What?
- Oh what you didn't get that?
Great, then it gives me a second chance
to humiliate myself by
telling you I never knew
how to ride a bike.
- Well get on the pegs.
- No no no, I'll just slow you down.
Look, look.
You guys go this way and I'll go this way.
Divert their attention.
We'll meet up where we came back in.
- You do realize the one that goes alone
always gets caught?
- It's just a cliche.
- Remember, we're a team, always.
- Right.
(dramatic music)
- Move it, move it, move it!
Down corridor three, now, now!
- Well well, fancy meeting you here.
- I can explain.
- Oh, I guarantee you will explain.
When I'm through with
you, you will explain
why you chose the breakfast
you ate on the last Tuesday
of 1993.
Was it an omelet?
Maybe Pop Tarts.
- Sorry guys.
- Guess cliches are cliches for a reason.
- Look, I'm the one you want.
Let Sam and Iris go and
I'll do whatever you say.
- Touching.
You know I'll just chalk that up
to the stupidity of youth.
From what I can see, I'm
holding all the aces.
You, you're just a joker in the deck.
Card analogies.
They are so vivid.
Move out!
- Ow!
- Move it kid.
Let's go you two, keep up with us.
Hey, guess what.
You got a date with my boss.
Have a seat.
- You may be wondering
why you're still alive,
or at least not blindfolded.
The fact is
I'm just so gosh darn
proud of my work here
I simply had to show off.
Especially to an interested,
albeit captive, audience.
(chuckles)
- I'll take supervillains
for 400 please, Alex.
- You may be interested
in knowing the origin
of what you're seeing here,
all this precision labor,
sweat, glory, excellence.
It's all a byproduct.
Technological byproduct.
Ah.
(snaps)
Okay, here's an analogy
that you children may
be able to relate to.
Just like the chicken nugget.
The chicken nugget was
actually the excess of a failed
chicken sandwich, but some
forward thinking executive
recognized that he could
sell that byproduct.
And of course, naturally,
inevitably, it became
more popular than the original!
Which is precisely what's happening here.
We were siphoning
technology from VectroComp.
- Through a carefully placed
operative in the company.
Little old me.
- And the byproduct of the x-ray device
was the possibility of a cloaking device.
Rearrange molecular structure
to create invisibility.
- I know someone I'd
like to make disappear.
- We were getting
information from VectroComp
at a good rate but not
(snapping)
fast enough.
Funding from our sources had dried up
due to a rather unfortunate,
really quite tragic situation.
The end of the Cold War.
Our project was at risk
so I planted Boyd here
to help with the development
of the x-ray device
so that we could catch up here and we did.
Until the unexpected popped
up to make things really
interesting, you.
You were the X factor
that we could not predict.
The mathematic variable.
Let's take care of the glasses.
- We should have visual
confirmation of the glasses
very soon.
Power up the cloaking turbine!
(dramatic music)
(buzzing)
- What about the three
kids, what happened to them?
- Oh they're here, just
not in this dimension.
Their molecular information
is stored in this device.
So they do exist.
- What are you gonna do to us?
- I think that those three
children need some company.
After all it has been four
long years for crying out loud.
(alarms blaring)
Your friend Mr. Carver has
provided the final piece
of the puzzle.
The energy from the
crystal of those glasses
has been absorbed into the mainframe.
A very new age concept.
(humming)
You know what I see?
I see a scared little boy who is not long
for the third dimension.
Boyd!
- Yes sir.
- Prepare for dimensional cloaking.
(dramatic music)
- But sir, I--
- There is no I in team.
Everything, everything for the
greater good of the project.
- But I--
- Just do it!
(snaps)
(alarm blaring)
I'll make your photos on the milk cartons
look suitably flattering.
Goodbye, children.
- [Soldier] This way, kids.
(zapping)
- I've got two Snickers in my backpack.
- [Biddle] What the?
- Andy the plate, push
Biddle onto the plate!
- I got your back.
(zapping)
(screaming)
It's alright, the police are
surrounding the place outside.
They won't get far.
- But how did you?
- You know I have had blueprints and specs
on a machine like this for months.
I never had the resources though.
It's a bipolar device.
It's an amazing machine.
- I mean well you just about
earned your own chapter
in my book, you know, not to
mention part of the royalties.
- Yeah Mr. Baker, impeccable
timing I must say.
- Well you can thank your
hoodlum friends for that.
They called me and
convinced me that they were
telling the truth.
Now I'm afraid I have a
lot of apologizing to do
to Andy's stepfather.
- My dad.
I mean you can call him my dad.
Boyd, where do you think you're headed?
- Malcolm?
Malcolm!
(chuckling)
I am so glad that you came when you did.
You have no idea what
it is like to be forced,
forced to do something against your will.
Now, now I know what
Patty Hearst felt like.
There were guns--
- Can it, Boyd.
I heard, saw, and
recorded more than enough.
You've been tripped up, or in
parlance you'll understand,
you got jail.
(laughing)
- [Andy] Come on, the food in
the slammer couldn't have been
that bad, could it?
- I'll miss those jailhouse cabbage rolls.
(laughing)
Mm.
It's good to be home.
- It's good to have you home, John.
You've got a heck of
a son there, you know.
- And I have got a great
pitch for a TV series.
World's wildest conspiracies.
Gonna blow that bogus alien
autopsy thing out of the water.
- Andy, I can't thank you enough.
You know, what you saw
when you visited Nancy
it was a nodule pressing
against her optic nerve.
All the conventional
x-rays she's had missed it.
So we're going to the
Mayo Clinic on Friday
and we don't know exactly
what the results will be
but we've got a lot of hope.
- I see enough to know
you're a special boy.
- Uh, could you excuse me for a minute?
- Sure.
- So back to school tomorrow.
Seems kinda dull now huh?
- Not for me.
- I mean, you'll probably
be too busy with schoolwork
and other stuff to hang out much, huh?
- Busy, yes, stupid, no.
We still got that date coming, right?
- You know it.
- Besides, I only have x-ray eyes for you.
- That was pretty bad.
- I can see clearly now?
You're a sight for sore eyes.
How about--
(swelling music)
(dramatic music)
(MultiCom Jingle)