I DON'T KNOW,
IT MAY BE A LOCAL LEGEND.
I'VE NEVER SEEN IT,
BUT--
NO!
ANOTHER HUGE
TIDAL WAVE HAS HIT LAND,
THIS TIME
IN PUERTO VALLARTA, MEXICO.
WHAT YOU WILL SEE
IS AMATEUR VIDEOTAPE
TAKEN LAST NIGHT
BY A SURVIVOR.
OUR ANN WINSLOW
IS ON THE SCENE.
FRANK, WORDS CANNOT
DESCRIBE THE DEVASTATION.
WHAT WE SEE HERE
SPEAKS FOR ITSELF.
10 DAYS AGO, A WAVE
DEVASTATED HONSHU, JAPAN.
THIS ONE WAS WORSE.
PEOPLE ARE SCARED
AND STARTING TO ASK
WILL THERE BE MORE?
AND, IF SO, WHERE?
THANK YOU, ANN,
FOR THAT REPORT.
WE HAVE
THIS INFORMATION NOW,
COMING FROM
THE TSUNAMI WARNING CENTER.
A TSUNAMI HAS BEEN GENERATED
WHICH COULD CAUSE DAMAGE
TO PORTIONS
OF THE PACIFIC COAST.
TSUNAMI WAVE HEIGHTS
CANNOT BE PREDICTED
AND MAY BE AS A RESULT OF WAVES
WHICH COULD BE DANGEROUS
FOR SEVERAL HOURS AFTER
THE INITIAL WAVE ARRIVAL.
HEY!
HEY, WHERE WERE YOU?
I LOOKED
ALL OVER FOR YOU.
WHERE WERE YOU?
BIG UPSET WHEN YOU GO
WITHOUT HIM, DOC.
HEY, HE WASN'T AROUND.
I LOOKED FOR YOU, CODY,
HONEST.
SO WHAT'S IT DOING
OUT THERE TODAY?
SAME AS ALWAYS.
KEEPING ME HAPPY.
HEY, DOC, YOU'RE
A SCIENTIST, RIGHT?
NOT ANYMORE.
THESE TIDAL WAVES, MAN.
THINK YOU COULD, LIKE,
TELL IF ONE WAS COMING?
NO ONE CAN, CHICK,
NOT REALLY.
'CAUSE THAT WOULD BE
THE ULTIMATE KICK,
IS TO SURF ONE OF THEM.
HEY, CODY! COME HERE.
COME HERE!
HEY, I LOOKED FOR YOU,
I DID.
COME ON.
YOU HUNGRY?
CONFOUNDING THE PUNDITS
WHO ARGUED AGAINST THE MOVE
INTO TREASURY BONDS
AND NOTES,
DIVIDENDS ARE MUCH HIGHER
THAN EXPECTED,
THE SELECTED COMMODITIES
CURRENTLY UP
FROM A YEAR AGO.
THIS IS AN AREA
WELL WORTH A SECOND LOOK.
FOREIGN STOCK MARKETS
STILL SHOW LITTLE CHANGE
FROM YESTERDAY,
BUT LOCAL EARNINGS ARE UP.
I KNEW THAT.
THE WORLD'S TOP
DEEP WATER SPECIALISTS
HAVE BEEN CALLED TOGETHER
TO MEET HERE
AT THE FAMED AQUATRONICS
RESEARCH INSTITUTE,
FUNDED IN PART
BY WASHINGTON'S NATIONAL
SCIENCE FOUNDATION.
NOW, WITH THE SECOND WAVE
HITTING,
THIS MEETING BECOMES
EVEN MORE URGENT.
OH. DR. AGAMO.
DR. AGAMO, EXCUSE ME.
UH, YES.
YES. COULD YOU TELL US,
AS A SEISMOLOGIST,
DO YOU BELIEVE THAT
UNDERWATER EARTHQUAKES
ARE THE CAUSE
OF THESE TIDAL WAVES?
THE TSUNAMI. UH,
IT'S TOO EARLY TO TELL.
WELL,
2 IN A ROW LIKE THIS,
ISN'T THAT UNUSUAL?
YES, YES,
MOST UNUSUAL.
EXCUSE ME, PLEASE.
BUT--DOCTOR, EXCUSE ME.
THE INVITED SCIENTISTS
ARE BEING MET
BY THE INSTITUTE'S
ASSOCIATE RESEARCH
DIRECTOR...
DR. WAHL?
I'M MARLAN CLARK.
THIS IS FRANK BRISICK.
HOW DID YOU KNOW
WHERE I WAS?
OH, WE'VE ALWAYS KNOWN.
MORE OR LESS.
WELL, YOU CAN
GO BACK AND TELL THEM
I'M NOT INTERESTED.
I'M...BUSY.
RIGHT.
SURF'S UP.
GO AWAY, FELLAS.
I MEAN IT.
YOU'RE COMING WITH US,
DR. WAHL.
AND WE MEAN IT.
YEAH.
JOHN WAHL?
PUT ON YOUR SEAT BELT.
TSUNAMI STAFF,
REPORT TO AREA 6, SECURITY.
UH, LET ME JUST SEE
WHO'S HERE REAL QUICK.
"DR. HIROSHI AGAMO...
DR. JULES BERNARD."
GOOD.
"DR. JOHN WAHL?"
CAN YOU BELIEVE IT?
WHY THEY HAULED HIM IN
ON THIS I'LL NEVER KNOW.
THE MAN'S BEEN
OUT OF IT FOR YEARS.
THEY SHOULD
HAVE LEFT HIM OUT.
THAT'S A LITTLE HARSH,
DON'T YOU THINK?
COME ON. HE WAS THE TOP
IN HIS FIELD, AND HE QUIT.
YEAH, B-BUT THE MAN
MADE SOME, UH,
PRETTY IMPORTANT
CONTRIBUTIONS IN HIS DAY.
I HATE QUITTERS!
DR. WAHL.
JULES BERNARD.
YOU'RE ACTUALLY HERE.
YES, SIR. INDEED I AM.
I...I AM HERE.
DR. JESSICA WEAVER,
JOHN WAHL.
WHY AM I NOT SURPRISED?
NICE TO MEET YOU,
DR. WEAVER.
PLEASE STAND BY
FOR AN IMPORTANT MESSAGE.
TSUNAMI STAFF, REPORT
TO AREA 6, SECURITY.
SHE'S CHIEF
OCEANOGRAPHER
AT AQUATRONICS.
SHE HOLDS 2 MASTERS
AND A Ph.D. IN HER FIELD.
THE NAVY PUT HER HERE.
AND SHE'S STILL
A LIEUTENANT COMMANDER.
WELL, MAYBE NEXT TIME
I BETTER SALUTE, HUH?
SECURITY, AREA 5.
IMMEDIATELY.
I'M EDGAR PURCELL
FROM THE NSA...
I should have known
you'd be here.
I DON'T KNOW ALL OF YOU
PERSONALLY,
BUT, UH,
I KNOW YOUR REPUTATIONS.
WE'RE HERE BECAUSE,
AS OF TODAY, 2 WAVES
HAVE KILLED 97 PEOPLE
AND CAUSED WORLDWIDE DAMAGE
ESTIMATED AT OVER
A BILLION DOLLARS.
OUR GOVERNMENT...WANTS
TO KNOW WHAT CAUSED THEM.
WAS IT A, UH...
SERIES OF TECTONIC
PLATE SHIFTS, DR. AGAMO?
MAYBE CAUSED BY OCEAN FLOOR
THERMAL VENTING DISTURBANCES?
OR ARE THERE
SOME KIND OF, UH,
WAVE RESONANCE PROGRESSIONS
WE SHOULD BE LOOKING AT,
SOMETHING WITH
A MATHEMATICAL SEQUENCE TO IT
THAT WE CAN PREDICT?
PREDICT?
NOT THIS, NO.
NO IS A WORD
WE DON'T WANT TO HEAR.
WHAT WE WANT,
WHAT WE NEED, SOON...
IS SOMETHING DEFINITE.
THE JULY 1st
OFFSHORE DISTURBANCE
WAS GENERATED IN THE AREA
MARKED IN RED.
95 MINUTES LATER,
A 30-FOOT TSUNAMI
HIT HONSHU, JAPAN.
THE JULY 10th DISTURBANCE
WAS A RICHTER SCALE 6.5,
GENERATED...HERE.
ONLY 55 MINUTES LATER,
A TSUNAMI HIT
PUERTO VALLARTA,
AND THE WAVE WAS SEVERAL
FEET LARGER.
WE CAN CONFIRM THAT
THE WAVES WEREN'T CAUSED BY
VOLCANIC ERUPTIONS.
HAVE YOU CONSIDERED
AN ATOMIC BOMB?
SEISMIC READINGS ON BOTH
DON'T INDICATE A BOMB.
IN ANY CASE, ONE ALONE
COULDN'T DO THIS.
JIMMY DOOLITTLE
THOUGHT IT COULD.
STANLEY!
YOUNG JOHN.
GOD, I MISS SEEING YOU.
HEY, I DIDN'T SEE
YOUR NAME ON THE LIST.
WELL, MY LIST.
I PUT IT TOGETHER.
HOW'S THE FISHING?
HOW'S THE SURFING?
GREAT.
YOU MENTIONED A BOMB,
DR. SCHIFF?
NOT JUST A BOMB.
THE BOMB.
2 OF 'EM.
THE WAR
WAS WINDING DOWN.
WE WERE GONNA WIN.
BUT AT WHAT COST?
JIMMY DOOLITTLE HAD
DONE HIS RAID ON TOKYO.
PRETTY SHAKY
OPERATION, BUT, UH,
PSYCHOLOGICALLY...
HE KNEW WE HAD THE BOMB.
HIS IDEA WAS TO DROP ONE
IN TOKYO BAY.
GIVE THE JAPANESE PEOPLE
SOMETHING THEY WOULD
UNDERSTAND, SOMETHING
THAT WOULD REALLY
GET THEIR ATTENTION.
A TSUNAMI.
DID THE GENERAL HAVE PLANS
FOR A SECOND BOMB?
OH, YEAH, HE SURE DID.
HE WANTED TO DESTROY JAPAN'S
MOST ENDURING SYMBOL...
MT. FUJI.
WE'RE IGNORING METEORS.
JOHN LOUIS SAID THAT
MOST OF THEM HIT THE OCEAN.
HE RAN COMPUTER SIMULATIONS
ON THE IMPACT TSUNAMIS
CREATED THAT WAY
AND GOT AN AVERAGE
CASUALTY READING OF
100 KILLED, 1,000 INJURED.
ON TOP OF WHICH,
ANY COLLISION LIKE THAT
GIVES YOU A RICHTER SCALE
READING THAT LOOKS EXACTLY--
I-I'M SORRY,
BUT I DON'T BUY IT.
NOT THAT I WANT TO DISAGREE
WITH LOUIS. HE'S GOOD.
IN FACT, I'M A LITTLE SURPRISED
THAT HE'S NOT IN ON THIS.
BUT MY POINT IS THAT
THERE HAVE BEEN 2 WAVES,
ALMOST IN A ROW.
THAT IS WAY BEYOND
ANY PROBABILITY SCALE.
SO WHAT'S YOUR THEORY,
DR. WAHL?
THE BOMB?
THERE ARE SOME PEOPLE
WITH ENOUGH MONEY
TO BUY AS MANY BOMBS
AS THEY WANT
WITH CHANGE TO SPARE.
I GUESS THAT
LEAVES YOU OUT.
THANKS.
LOOK, YOU PEOPLE WANT MY HELP,
I'M GLAD TO HELP,
BUT THIS
IS A WASTE OF TIME.
YOU WANT METEORS...FINE.
FIRST, GET THE GOVERNMENT
TO DO A SATELLITE SCAN
OF THE OCEAN FLOOR FOR ANY
NEW IMPACT CRATERS.
ME? I GOTTA GO, UH,
DISPLACE A LITTLE WATER
OF MY OWN.
AQUATRONICS IS
A NONSMOKING FACILITY.
NO SMOKING, PLEASE.
CHARMING.
YEAH. TALK TO ME.
MR. WAHL,
I'M NOT SURPRISED
THEY BROUGHT YOU
IN ON THIS.
IN ON WHAT?
WHO IS THIS?
METEORS! THAT IDIOT.
WHO THE HELL IS THIS?
THAT IDEA OF
GENERAL DOOLITTLE'S.
IMAGINE
WHAT A TIDAL WAVE
COULD HAVE DONE
FOR OUR BOYS ON
D-DAY AT NORMANDY.
THINK OF
ALL THE LIVES SAVED.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
TOO BAD WE CAN'T
CONTROL MOTHER NATURE.
HAVEN'T YOU BEEN
WATCHING THE NEWS?
WE CAN.
YOU THINK THAT'S FUNNY?
ARE YOU LAUGHING?
ALL RIGHT, WISE ASS,
WHAT'S GOING ON?
NOTHING...YET.
MR. WAHL...MR. WAHL...
WHAT?!
YOUR BEER'S
GETTING WARM.
VALERIE, THANK YOU
VERY MUCH FOR COMING IN
AND JOINING US TODAY.
AND FOR YOU THINKING
ABOUT THAT FIRST HOME,
MARTY HAS SOME VERY GOOD TIPS
THAT YOU MIGHT WANT TO STAY
TUNED FOR. MARTY?
WE INTERRUPT
THIS PROGRAM TO BRING YOU
A SPECIAL REPORT.
20 MINUTES AGO,
A 40-FOOT TIDAL WAVE HIT
THE NORTH SHORE OF HAWAII.
REPORTS INDICATE THE WAVE
WASHED 1/4 OF A MILE INLAND,
LEAVING VAST DEVASTATION
IN ITS WAKE.
WE'LL BRING YOU A LIVE REPORT
AS SOON AS POSSIBLE.
WE NOW RETURN TO YOUR REGULARLY
SCHEDULED PROGRAMMING.
STAY TUNED...
I TOLD THEM
NOT TO PUT YOUR PHONE CALLS
THROUGH TO ME ANYMORE, ALAN.
BECAUSE WE HAVE
NOTHING TO TALK ABOUT.
WELL, ALAN, I REALLY
DON'T CARE WHAT YOU THINK.
ALAN...ALAN, THAT'S WHY
THEY CALL IT A DIVORCE.
DAMN IT, ALAN,
I SAID NO!
UH, YEAH, HI.
IT'S JOHN WAHL--
SIT! CODY!
UM...JUST A MINUTE.
HI.
TO WHAT DO I OWE
THE HONOR?
UH, CODY, THIS IS
LIEUTENANT COMMANDER
JESSICA WEAVER
OF THE UNITED STATES NAVY--
STAY HERE, CODY! SIT!
I'M ALSO VERY BUSY,
DR. WAHL.
EDGAR IS CLIMBING--
HAWAII.
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
I NEED TO GET BACK
INTO AQUATRONICS.
REALLY? YOU WERE
THERE EARLIER.
YOU DIDN'T SEEM
TO LIKE IT MUCH.
C-CODY!
RIGHT AFTER I GOT
BACK THIS MORNING,
I GOT A PHONE CALL.
A MAN. HE MENTIONED
DOOLITTLE'S PLAN,
AND THEN THIS ARRIVED.
WHAT'S THIS
SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
OH, COME ON,
DR. WEAVER.
NO, YOU COME ON,
DR. WAHL!
YOU COULD HAVE SENT
THIS TO YOURSELF.
THEN I CAME STRAIGHT HERE
BECAUSE YOU'RE MY PERFECT
CHARACTER WITNESS!
WHY NOT?! IT WOULD BE
THE SMART THING TO DO.
WE BOTH KNOW
YOU'RE NOT DUMB.
DR. WEAV--MA'AM!
THOSE WAVES ARE
BEING MANUFACTURED.
I BELIEVE IT,
YOU ALMOST BELIEVE IT,
AND THAT'S THE REAL REASON
THAT CONFERENCE WAS CALLED.
THAT'S WHY EDGAR PURCELL
AND THE NATIONAL
SECURITY AGENCY
NEEDED ALL OF US
IN THE SAME ROOM.
I SUPPOSED YOU'D
BETTER COME IN.
IS, UH,
IS THAT ALL RIGHT?
WELL...HE'S
ALREADY THERE.
CODY!
COFFEE?
UH...YEAH, YEAH.
NICE PLACE.
SOME OTHER TIME, WAHL.
YOU AND MR. PURCELL
SEEM TO HAVE A VERY
SPECIAL RELATIONSHIP.
YOU NOTICED, HUH?
I THINK EVERYBODY NOTICED.
SO YOU THINK
WHOEVER CALLED YOU WAS
IN THAT ROOM WITH US.
I'D PUT MY MONEY ON IT.
REALLY? SO WHO IS IT?
BERNARD?
NO. HE'S TOO NICE.
HO HO.
WELL, THAT ELIMINATES
HIM RIGHT AWAY.
WHAT ABOUT SCHIFF?
YEAH, RIGHT. YOU'RE
TELLING ME THE MAN
WHO TAUGHT ME
MOST OF WHAT I KNOW
IS PULLING SOMETHING
LIKE THIS?
YOU SAW HIM.
HE'S A STRAIGHT-
FROM-THE-SHOULDERS GUY.
ALL RIGHT,
THAT'S 2 DOWN,
WHICH LEAVES AGAMO.
TOO DEDICATED.
HE'S THE CLASSIC
LABORATORY MOLE
WHO BLINKS AT NIGHT-LIGHTS.
THE MAN KNOWS A LOT ABOUT
DEEP CANYON THERMALS.
HIROSHI AGAMO'S BEEN
SURFING THAT HORSE
FOR THE LAST 20 YEARS.
WHILE YOU ONLY SURF
THE REAL THING.
LOOK, DAMN IT,
ALL I'M TRYING
TO PROVE HERE--
NO, YOU LOOK!
NO, NO, NO, WHICH
LEAVES ONLY YOU.
AND YOU.
I THINK YOU CAN PUT MONEY
ON IT BEING A MAN.
I MAY NOT LIKE
WHAT A LOT OF PEOPLE
ARE DOING TO THIS WORLD,
BUT CREATING
GIANT KILLER WAVES
IS NOT REALLY MY STYLE.
OK, FINE. WE JUST DID
A NIFTY LAUNDERING JOB
ON EVERYONE WHO WAS
IN THAT ROOM,
BUT YOU'RE STILL SAYING
IT WAS SOMEONE IN THERE.
MY MONEY'S
RIDING ON IT.
YOU GOTTA STOP
TALKING ABOUT MONEY,
OR I'M GONNA
THINK YOU'RE RICH.
ARE YOU?
HOW DO YOU PAY
YOUR BILLS, WAHL?
I PLAY THE STOCK MARKET.
SO YOU'RE
INDEPENDENTLY WEALTHY,
AND A MYSTERIOUS PERSON
IS CONTACTING YOU,
SENDING YOU CARTOONS.
WHY?
I DON'T KNOW.
LOOK, I CAN'T GET
INTO AQUATRONICS.
I NEED YOU TO DO THAT.
DO WHAT?
I WANT YOU TO RUN EVERYONE
WHO WAS IN THAT CONFERENCE
THROUGH THE LATEST
NAVY SECURITY PROFILES.
INCLUDING ME.
OH, I'D START WITH YOU.
WHAT, TOO STRONG?
JUST A BIT.
HAVE A LITTLE SUGAR.
NO.
NO?
HAVE YOU SEEN MY DOG?
CODY?
CODY!
WAHL?
YEAH.
WHAT IS IT THAT
I'M LOOKING FOR?
ANYTHING THAT DOESN'T
MAKE SENSE--CODY!
YOU DON'T MAKE SENSE.
HEY, I'M AN OPEN BOOK.
SO WHO'S ALAN?
I'M A CLOSED BOOK.
MY EX-HUSBAND.
HOW DO YOU DO IT?
DO WHAT?
GET ME TO TELL YOU
SOMETHING
WHEN I REALLY
DON'T WANT TO.
RELAX. YOU HAVEN'T
TOLD ME ANYTHING.
YET.
CODY.
MORNIN'.
SO, DOC, MAN,
THESE TIDAL WAVES.
HOW BIG WE TALKIN'?
OH, 50 FEET HIGH.
60, MAYBE.
60?!
TELL ME YOU WOULDN'T LOVE TO
JUST SHRED ONE OF THEM, MAN.
HEY, WHAT'S UP WITH CODY?
I MEAN, HE ALWAYS WAITS
FOR YOU TO THROW THE STICK.
WHAT'S GOIN' ON, DOC?
TIDAL WAVE.
A TIDAL WAVE?
TIDAL WAVE!
TIDAL WAVE! WHOO!
CHICK, FORGET IT, MAN!
IT'LL KILL YOU!
CODY! CODY, COME HERE!
CODY!
COME ON, CODY!
COME ON!
COME ON! HURRY!
HURRY UP! COME ON!
COME ON. GET IN THE BACK.
GET IN THE BACK.
OVER THERE!
HELP ME!
THIS WOMAN
NEED HELP!
IT'S GONNA BE
ALL RIGHT! RELAX.
HOLD ON. HOLD ON.
OK. GIVE ME YOUR ARM.
GIVE ME YOUR ARM.
HELP!
CODY?
CODY...
WE'RE HERE!
COME ON. COME ON.
FORGET ABOUT IT. COME ON.
LET'S GO! LET'S GO!
YOU LOOK LIKE
YOU GOT BANGED UP
QUITE A BIT THERE, SON,
WHEN THE WAVE HIT.
YOU GONNA BE ALL RIGHT?
EXCUSE ME. EXCUSE ME.
CHECK OUT MY BUDDY,
WOULD YOU?
RIGHT AWAY.
WE GOT A CRITICAL!
J.T., CHECK HIM OUT.
YOUR ARM NEEDS TO BE
TAKEN CARE OF, TOO.
I'M ALL RIGHT!
NO, NO, NO. YOU NEED
TO SIT DOWN, SIR,
AND HAVE SOMEONE
TAKE A LOOK AT YOUR ARM.
RIGHT THERE.
THERE YOU GO.
HOVERCRAFT STAFF,
REPORT IMMEDIATELY.
A SURGICAL STRIKE.
LOOK AT THAT.
LOOK AT THAT. THE WHOLE
COASTLINE'S WIPED OUT.
A BLOCK AWAY, PEOPLE
ARE TOSSING STEAKS
ON THE BARBECUE.
AND JUST BEFORE
IT HAPPENS,
JOHN WAHL
DROPS IN ON YOU.
NOW, THAT'S INTERESTING.
YOU THINK
HE DID THAT?
THAT'S HIS HOME.
MAYBE HE'S THINKING
OF MOVING.
I'M GOING DOWN THERE.
YOU DO THAT.
BUT BEFORE YOU GO,
LET ME TELL YOU A FEW THINGS
ABOUT YOUR NEW FRIEND.
IN '81, HE HEADED
HIGH WEAPONS TESTING
AT RAT ISLAND
FOR N-RAT.
IN '84, HE GOT
THE NOBEL PRIZE
FOR HIS RESEARCH
IN HYDROTHERMAL GUIDANCE
SYSTEMS DEVELOPMENT.
I KNOW ALL THAT.
JUST LISTEN.
ONE YEAR LATER, HE BROKE
INTO A CONFIDENTIAL NETWORK,
FOUND OUT WE WERE
CONSIDERING USING
SOME OF THOSE WEAPONS
TO REARM IRAN,
LEAKED THE NEWS,
THEN MARCHED INTO THE OFFICE
OF THE UNDERSECRETARY
OF DEFENSE,
THE UNDERSECRETARY
TOSSED THE WASHINGTON POST
ON HIS DESK
SO HE'D BE THE FIRST TO SEE
WHAT WAHL HAD DONE.
THE SECRETARY CALLED HIM
A TRAITOR, WHICH HE WAS,
AND WAHL DECKED HIM.
THE UNDERSECRETARY
OF DEFENSE
WAS PLANNING
TO BREAK THE LAW.
ONLY PLANNING IT.
YOUR FRIEND DID.
THEN HE PULLED A HOUDINI
AND DISAPPEARED.
I THINK HE'S STILL
MAD AT THE SYSTEM.
I THINK HE DOESN'T CARE
IF PEOPLE DIE.
I THINK WE'RE
THROUGH HERE.
DON'T EXPECT TO FIND HIM.
SECURITY. SECURITY,
AREA 5, IMMEDIATELY.
I KNOW HIM.
HE COULD DO THIS
WITH HIS EYES CLOSED.
DR. WAHL!
MY GOD! YOU WERE
HERE WHEN--
GO AWAY!
I SAW EDGAR.
WAHL, HE'S CONVINCED
IT'S YOU.
YOU GOT A BAD SENSE
OF TIMING, LADY.
YOU ARE JUST DARING HIM TO
POINT THE FINGER AT YOU. WHY?!
JUST GET AWAY FROM ME!
YOU'VE GOT THE KNOW-HOW
TO MAKE THESE WAVES HAPPEN.
DO YOU THINK I WOULD DO
SOMETHING LIKE THIS
TO ANYONE?
MY DOG IS DEAD!
MY HOUSE IS--
I DON'T KNOW.
PICK IT OUT!
IS IT THERE?!
I'M LUCKY TO BE ALIVE.
YOU CAN DROP THAT IDEA
OF SOMEBODY USING ANY KIND
OF BOMB TO DO THIS.
WHAT MAKES YOU SO SURE?
WAHL! I'M STUMBLING
AROUND IN THE DARK HERE,
AND YOU ACT LIKE
YOU KNOW EVERYTHING.
I DON'T KNOW DIDDLY,
BUT I WAS INVOLVED
IN OFFSHORE NUCLEAR TESTING.
YEAH, WE WERE TRYING
TO MAKE A TIDAL WAVE.
AND I CAN TELL YOU THIS.
AN EXPLOSION,
ESPECIALLY A NUCLEAR ONE,
IS A BAD WAY TO DO IT.
IT'S ALL HEAT.
THE DISPERSED WATER
EVAPORATES.
THERE'S GONNA BE A WAVE,
BUT BY THE TIME
IT HITS THE SHORE,
IT'S GONNA BE
DOWN TO NOTHING.
IF IT CAN'T BE DONE,
WHY DO THEY THINK
YOU'RE RESPONSIBLE?
'CAUSE I WAS GETTIN' CLOSE
TO THE WAY IT COULD BE DONE.
COULD BE DONE,
DR. WEAVER.
NOBODY KNEW
HOW CLOSE I WAS.
I DIDN'T DO IT, WEAVER!
I GOT OUT!
I BUILT MYSELF
A NICE LITTLE SCENARIO.
I SLUGGED A GUY
AT DEFENSE,
I DUG MYSELF A HOLE,
AND I JUST DROPPED THROUGH.
I DON'T CARE ABOUT
ANYTHING ANYMORE!
THEY CAN ALL BLOW
THEMSELVES UP FOR ALL I CARE.
I GOT OUT...
AND I WANT TO STAY OUT.
HE WANTS ME
TO TRY AND FIND HIM.
WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
WHOEVER THE HELL
IS DOING THIS.
THE PHONE CALL,
THE LETTER.
IT'S AN INVITATION.
"FIND ME."
THEN DO IT.
GIVE ME SOME TIME.
I WILL.
MAYBE I CAN
BUY YOU SOME.
COME ON.
AQUATRONICS.
IT'S JESSICA WEAVER.
LET ME SPEAK
WITH DR. PURCELL.
PURCELL.
EDGAR?
I JUST CAME FROM THE BEACH.
JOHN WAHL'S MISSING.
HE WAS THERE, BUT, UH,
NOT ANYMORE.
WHO, EXACTLY,
SAID HE WAS--
LET ME SUGGEST YOU PUT
SOME OF THE OTHERS
UNDER THE SAME MICROSCOPE
YOU'VE GOT LOCKED ON WAHL.
WE ALREADY ARE,
DR. WEAVER.
THANK YOU FOR SHARING
YOUR THOUGHTS.
EDGAR, I HOPE YOU'RE
LOOKING FOR MORE THAN
HOW HE'S DOING IT.
GO HOME, DR. WEAVER.
THE BASTARD.
YEAH. WELL,
LET'S NOT FORGET THAT
HE'S THE TOP BASTARD.
OH, JEEZ.
YOU'VE GOT TO LET ME
LOOK AT THAT ARM.
HEY, HEY...
JUST DRIVE.
EARLIER TODAY,
THE PRESIDENT FLEW OVER
THE DISASTER AREA
AND LATER MET
WITH SURVIVORS
TO PERSONALLY EXPRESS
HIS SYMPATHY.
IN A SEPARATE STATEMENT,
THE WHITE HOUSE HAS ASKED
ALL AMERICANS TO REMAIN CALM.
THIS SO-CALLED
CONFERENCE, MR. CLARK,
WHY, EXACTLY,
DID THEY CALL IT?
MR. PURCELL
HAS ALREADY DECIDED
THAT JOHN WAHL
IS RESPONSIBLE
FOR WHAT IS HAPPENING.
I DON'T THINK HE HAS.
AH. SO IT'S NOT
JOHN WAHL.
IT'S ONE OF US.
YOU THINK
THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
ON THE CONTRARY,
EVERY ONE OF US HAS
CONSIDERED THE POSSIBILITY
OF CONTROLLING
SUCH A NATURAL POWER.
THIS PLACE, THIS AQUATRONICS,
RECEIVES SO MUCH MONEY
FROM THE GOVERNMENT
BECAUSE TO HARNESS THE OCEANS
WOULD MAKE EVERYONE
PAY ATTENTION.
SO IT IS QUITE POSSIBLE
THAT ONE OF US IS DOING IT.
NOT I, OF COURSE.
WOULD YOU RELAX, WAHL?
I KNOW WHAT I'M DOING.
I HAD
2 YEARS OF PREMED.
THEN WHAT?
TALK TO ME, COMMANDER.
ABOUT WHAT?
YOU ARE SUCH A SISSY.
YOU'RE AFRAID TO WATCH.
YEAH, WHEN IT COMES
TO ME, YES, I AM.
ALL RIGHT, YOU DID
A COUPLE OF YEARS PREMED,
THEN WHAT?
DON'T GIVE ME ONE
OF THOSE PRINTOUT RESUMES.
YOU KNOW,
"I WENT TO AFGHANISTAN
UNDER COVER OF BLAH BLAH."
OK, OK, I SEE
WHAT YOU'RE DOING.
WELL, MY FATHER
WAS NAVY...
KOREA?
MM-HMM.
I WAS BORN
AFTER HE CAME BACK
AND RETIRED.
HE WAS A LOT OLDER
THAN MOM.
I GREW UP
LOVING THE WATER.
OW!
OK. OK,
I'M FINISHED.
WHAT DID YOU--
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
JEEZ.
WELL, YOU WANT TO
TAKE A LOOK AT THIS?
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
IT'S NICE STITCHING.
THANKS.
YOU DO GOOD WORK.
WELL, WE BETTER GET
YOU SOME CLOTHES.
OHH...
THEY'RE ALAN'S.
I'VE BEEN MEANING
TO GET RID OF THEM,
BUT AREN'T YOU GLAD
I DIDN'T?
THRILLED.
IT'S A LITTLE...
SNUG FOR YOU?
HE ACTUALLY WORE
THIS STUFF?
LOOK, I THINK I'M
JUST GOING TO
WASH MY OWN CLOTHES.
YOU DO HAVE
A WASHING MACHINE
AROUND HERE, WEAVER?
YES, I DO,
AND THE NAME
IS JESSIE.
STILL GOT YOUR HUSBAND'S
CLOTHES, HUH?
I FIND THAT KIND OF
INTERESTING.
NO, IT'S NOT.
THEY'RE JUST CLOTHES.
NO.
THEY'RE
ALAN'S CLOTHES.
GUESS YOU STILL GOT
SOMETHING THERE
FOR HIM, HUH?
THERE IS NOTHING THERE.
YOU KNOW, EITHER WAY,
IT'S REALLY NONE
OF YOUR BUSINESS.
YOU'RE RIGHT,
I'M SORRY.
IT'S OK.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
FORGET IT.
I'M SORRY.
I'LL SEE YOU
LATER.
WHERE
ARE YOU GOING?
AQUATRONICS,
REMEMBER?
AND DON'T USE
THE PHONES.
YOU THINK
THEY'D BUG YOU?
I KNOW THEY WOULD.
TRY NOT TO BURN DOWN
THE HOUSE
WHILE I'M GONE, WAHL.
IT'S JOHN.
JOHN.
JOHN WAHL AND
JESSICA WEAVER.
HEY!
WE HAVE
THE SAME INITIALS.
CLEVER.
YOUNG JOHN WAHL
WAS BRILLIANT.
UNPREDICTABLE.
IDEALISTIC.
JUST YOUR
REGULAR SCIENTIST.
I WAS THERE
WHEN HE, UH...
WHEN THAT INCIDENT WITH
THE UNDERSECRETARY HAPPENED.
AND, UH, I DON'T KNOW.
IT'S JUST A FEELING I HAD.
AS A MATTER OF FACT,
I HAD THE SAME FEELING
AGAIN THE OTHER DAY
WHEN I SAW HIM.
WHAT FEELING WAS THIS,
DR. SCHIFF?
THE REASON WE THOUGHT
HE TOOK OFF AND QUIT.
NO, I DON'T THINK
THAT WAS IT.
I THINK IT WAS
SOMETHING ELSE.
I THINK...
I THINK IT WAS
SOMETHING HE FOUND.
SOMETHING HE WANTED
TO KEEP TO HIMSELF.
TO HIMSELF...
OR FOR HIMSELF?
I'M NOT COMFORTABLE WITH
THAT SUGGESTION, MR. CLARK.
I CAN'T EVEN GET CLOSE
TO THEIR FILES.
WAHL?
RIGHT HERE.
AAH! GOD...
SORRY. I'M SORRY.
ALL RIGHT, EVERYTHING IS
ALL CLEAR OUT BACK, I THINK.
WHAT HAVE YOU GOT?
ZIP. I THOUGHT I
COULD PATCH THROUGH
TO THE AQUATRONICS
MAINFRAME,
BUT
IT'S BLOCKING ME.
LET ME TRY
SOMETHING ELSE.
I COULDN'T GET
TO THEIR FILES
BECAUSE THEY WERE
RIGHT THERE ALL DAY.
EDGAR WALKING AROUND
LOOKING
OVER MY SHOULDER.
AGAMO WAS USING THE
MAINFRAME COMPUTER.
THE MINUTE
HE FINISHED,
BERNARD NETWORKED IT
OVER TO THE WAVE ROOM
TO USE IT.
ALL RIGHT,
LOOK AT THIS.
THE SURF
FROM THE OTHER DAY.
HOW'D YOU MAKE
THAT HAPPEN?
THE WEATHER SERVICE
HAS EVERY WEATHER PATTERN
TRANSLATED INTO
NUMBERED COORDINATES.
ADD AN ALGORITHM...
MM-HMM.
YOU GET IT IN PICTURES.
LOOK.
THIS MORNING'S WAVE.
SOMEWHERE...
THERE HAS TO BE
A GROUND ZERO.
I KNOW.
WELL, LET'S FIND IT.
NO. I MEAN,
THIS IS WHAT BERNARD
WAS WORKING ON.
HE HAD IT UP ON THE
WAVE ROOM MONITORS.
TODAY?
YOU'RE NOT LISTENING.
BERNARD WAS LOOKING
THROUGH THIS?
HE STILL IS.
HE STAYED BEHIND
BECAUSE HE THOUGHT
HE WAS ON TO SOMETHING.
MAY I ASK YOU
SOMETHING?
IF YOU'RE CREATING WAVES,
AND YOU WANT TO KEEP
ANYBODY FROM FINDING OUT
WHERE THEY ORIGINATED,
WHAT WOULD YOU DO?
FIND THE ONE COMPUTER
THAT WOULD SHOW YOU HOW.
BERNARD?
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
IT MAKES SENSE.
WHEN WE WERE WORKING
ON WAVES,
WE WERE WORKING FROM
MATHEMATICAL MODELS
THAT HE CREATED.
YEAH, BUT...
HE'S NICE.
YOU SAID SO
YOURSELF.
YEAH, HE'S ONE OF
THE REAL DARLINGS
OF THE THEORETICAL
SCIENCES, JUST LIKE ME.
BUT YOU STILL
SUSPECT ME...
DON'T YOU?
WELL, HE MUST BE GONE.
DO YOU SMELL SOMETHING?
LET ME TURN THE LIGHT ON.
SOMETHING'S BURNING.
WHAT...
WE'VE GOT TO CALL
THE POLICE.
WAIT. WE WILL.
FIRST, LET'S SEE
WHAT HE WAS WORKING ON.
LISBON.
JOHN, LET'S
GET OUT OF HERE.
GIVE ME
A FEW MORE SECONDS.
THE COMPUTER ROOM!
SEND SOME BACKUP!
HEY!
MAN, I GOT TO
GET AHOLD OF CHICK.
I GOT TO FIND OUT
HOW HE'S DOING.
THIS IS GETTING
VERY PERSONAL.
WHOEVER'S DOING THIS
DOESN'T JUST WANT ME BLAMED.
ONCE HE GETS ME,
HE WANTS ME DEAD.
FOR NOW, HE NEEDS ME
TO KEEP THE OTHERS BUSY
WHILE HE GETS READY.
READY FOR WHAT?
LISBON.
THAT'S WHAT
BERNARD WAS TRACKING.
1755, A TIDAL WAVE
HIT PORTUGAL,
KILLED 60,000 PEOPLE.
FOR A SECOND, I THOUGHT
THAT'S WHAT BERNARD
WAS PLANNING TO MAKE
HAPPEN AGAIN.
LOOK, I GOT TO GET
SOMEPLACE,
I GOT TO
GET BACK ONLINE,
I GOT TO START CHECKING
SOME THINGS OUT.
WE CAN'T GO
BACK TO MY PLACE.
THEY'RE
ALREADY CONVINCED
THAT YOU'RE MAKING
THE TIDAL WAVES,
AND NOW THEY'RE
GOING TO THINK
WE KILLED BERNARD.
HOW'D I GET
INTO THIS?
LIKE PURCELL SAID...
MY CHARM.
THANK YOU.
I'M ALMOST FINISHED.
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
AHH...
WELL,
THE PRESIDENT SAYS
THE GOVERNMENT IS
IN TOTAL CONTROL.
HMM. REALLY?
YEAH. AND THERE'S
THIS SURVIVALIST
WHO'S GOING TO BUY
HIMSELF A MOUNTAIN TOP
AND BUILD
HIMSELF AN ARK.
OH. I'M SERIOUS.
AAH.
I GOT THIS PAIN
THAT GOES STRAIGHT FROM
THE BACK OF MY NECK
RIGHT TO MY HEAD--
YOU NEED TO TAKE
A SHOWER.
OH. YOU TRYING TO
TELL ME SOMETHING?
AS HOT AS YOU CAN
STAND IT,
THEN CALL ME
WHEN YOU'RE DONE.
AYE, AYE, SIR.
OH.
SHH...
MMM.
THAT'S BETTER STILL.
SALT WATER IS VERY BAD
FOR YOUR HAIR, YOU KNOW?
YEAH, WELL, IT'S
A LITTLE LATE FOR ME.
I READ ALL ABOUT YOU
WHEN I WAS IN COLLEGE.
YEAH?
YOU WERE
SOMETHING ELSE.
YEAH?
I'M NOT THAT OLD.
WAHL?
HMM?
I'M JEALOUS.
OF WHAT?
OF YOU.
YOU DO EXACTLY
WHAT YOU WANT TO DO.
AH, IT'S NO BIG DEAL.
NOT YOUR USUAL
"WANTED" POSTER, ARE WE?
ARE WE GOING TO JUST
KEEP ON RUNNING?
WE HAVE TO.
THEY CAUGHT UP
WITH YOU LAST TIME.
I LIKE IT WHEN YOU RUB
THIS SIDE RIGHT THERE.
WORK YOUR HAND UP
OVER THIS WAY HERE.
OH, I'LL WORK
MY HAND UP.
YES, MR. PURCELL.
THAT'S THEM.
THANK YOU.
I KNEW IT.
I KNEW IT WAS HIM.
RIGHT FROM THE START.
I FELT IT.
WE JUST FOUND
WEAVER'S CAR
SITTING AT THE CURB
AT BURBANK AIRPORT.
WE FOUND THIS UNDER
THE REARVIEW MIRROR.
IT'S A MINIATURE
MICROPHONE.
WHAT ARE THEY
PLAYING AT?
SIR? YOU BETTER
TAKE A LOOK.
ATTENTION.
INTRUSION, AREA 2.
A BILLION DOLLARS?
"IF YOU WANT TO THINK
I AM KIDDING, BE MY GUEST,
"BUT SOON IT WILL SOUND
LIKE A BARGAIN.
I'LL BE IN TOUCH."
YOU ALL RIGHT?
OH, YEAH.
ALL RIGHT.
WHAT ARE WE
LOOKING FOR?
NOT "WHAT." "WHO."
I ALREADY TRIED GETTING
EVERYBODY'S
NAVY SECURITY PROFILE.
NO, NO, FORGET THAT.
WE'RE LOOKING FOR ANY
UNUSUAL TIDAL WAVE LINKS
TO ANYBODY WHO WAS
AT THE CONFERENCE.
THERE'S NO REASON
STUFF LIKE THAT
SHOULD BE CLASSIFIED.
ALL RIGHT,
I'M IN THE NATIONAL INSTITUTE
OF SCIENCE CENTRAL FILE.
NOW THEN...
REST IN PEACE, JULES.
WE KNOW IT'S NOT YOU.
YOU NEED A KEYCODE.
UM...TRY "TIDAL WAVES."
NO. NO, NO,
IT'S TOO GENERAL.
OK. UM...
"TSUNAMIS."
HELLO, DR. AGAMO.
AGAMO...
LET'S ADD
ANOTHER KEYWORD...
"SEISMIC WEAPONS."
"THERMONUCLEAR..."
YOU SAID
IT WASN'T A BOMB.
A TSUNAMI HAPPENS WHEN
THE SEA FLOOR IS ALTERED
EITHER BY AN EARTHQUAKE,
A VOLCANIC ERUPTION...
BUT WE CAN'T MAKE
THOSE HAPPEN.
AGAMO CONFIRMED THAT
HIMSELF.
BUT A TSUNAMI ALSO HAPPENS
WHEN THERE'S
AN UNDERWATER LANDSLIDE.
WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
WHAT IF
HE'S BLOWING UP MOUNTAINS?
LOOK.
3 LINKED REFERENCES
TO "TSUNAMI"
AND THE WORD
"THERMONUCLEAR."
"CRASHER." WHAT'S THAT?
IT'S A THESIS PAPER
FROM 1959.
"GENERAL DOOLITTLE'S
FUJI PLAN WAS SOUND
"AND WOULD HAVE ENDED
THE WAR AND SPARED LIVES.
"IMAGINE HOW MANY LIVES
WOULD'VE BEEN SPARED
"HAD A LARGE TIDAL WAVE
BEEN CREATED
AND CLEARED THE BEACHES
OF NORMANDY."
YOU SAID THIS
IN THE CONFERENCE.
NO. NO.
STANLEY SCHIFF
TALKED ABOUT DOOLITTLE'S
IDEA, REMEMBER?
I TOLD YOU THIS.
SOMEBODY CALLED ME
AT MY HOUSE
RIGHT AFTER
THE CONFERENCE.
THAT PERSON ALSO TALKED
ABOUT NORMANDY.
DR. SCHIFF...
"IS IT POSSIBLE
TO CREATE A TSUNAMI?
"IN THEORY,
ABSOLUTELY.
"BY COLLAPSING
A SEAMOUNT
"USING
A HYDROGEN EXPLOSION
THE DISPLACEMENT
OF WATER--"
OH...WHAT THE HELL
IS IT DOING?
WHAT?
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
WE'VE BEEN AMBUSHED.
HE MUST HAVE
A PROGRAM IN HERE
THAT SCANS EVERYTHING
USING HIS NAME
AND LETS HIM KNOW WHEN
SOMEONE COMES KNOCKING.
HELLO, STANLEY.
WHY DOESN'T HE JUST
ERASE THE ARTICLE?
STANLEY SCHIFF ERASE?
NO.
"WE HAVE TO TALK.
"MEET ME
AT NOON TOMORROW
"UNDER
LIFEBOAT NUMBER 2
"ON THE QUEEN MARY.
"IF YOU TELL ANYONE,
THE WAVES WILL NEVER STOP.
NEVER."
"HAVE CLARK MEET ME
ON THE QUEEN MARY
"UNDER LIFEBOAT
NUMBER 2 AT NOON
"WITH A SWISS BANK DRAFT
FOR THE MONEY.
"IF YOU TRY ANYTHING,
THE WAVES WILL NEVER STOP.
J.W."
WE TAKE OUT JOHN WAHL.
HE SAID
IF WE TRY ANYTHING,
THE WAVES
WILL KEEP HAPPENING.
ONE MORE,
WHICH SHOULD PROVIDE
VERY SUSTAINABLE LOSSES
IF IT MEANS WE NAIL HIM.
I'M NOT SURE IF THEY'VE
GOT 2 OR 3 PEOPLE.
WE HAVE THE SUSPECT.
YOU COCKY
LITTLE FREAK.
EVERYTHING
I TAUGHT YOU.
YOU THOUGHT
YOU CAN DO IT
WITH ONE HAND TIED
BEHIND YOUR BACK.
SURE, GUYS. PUSHING
THE BUTTON'S EASY,
BUT WHAT ABOUT
PULLING THE TRIGGER?
WELL, WATCH ME,
SONNY BOY.
HI! WE'RE OVER HERE!
WHERE'S RAY?
OH, I'M NOT SURE.
THIS WAY.
WHOA. WHOA.
WHAT ARE YOU
DOING HERE?
MEETING YOU.
LIKE YOU TOLD ME TO.
NO BILLION DOLLARS,
THOUGH.
TOUGH BREAK.
WHAT
BILLION DOLLARS?
OH, MAN, I SEE
WHAT'S GOING ON.
CLARK, YOU GOT TO--
TO LISTEN TO ME.
I KNOW WHO IT IS.
YEAH? SO DO I.
YOU!
NO! NO!
LOOK, I GOT
THE SAME MESSAGE.
THAT'S EXACTLY
WHAT HE WANTS.
LOOK, YOU GO--
MAN DOWN!
COME ON!
CLARK'S BEEN HIT.
HOLD ON, BUDDY,
HOLD ON!
COME ON! COME ON!
COME ON!
LOOK OUT!
GO! GO!
DOWN THERE!
I GOT THEM!
COME ON.
LET'S GO!
GET A BEAD
ON 'EM.
HOLD ON.
IN THE BOAT!
JESSIE, GET DOWN!
TSUNAMI ALERT.
YOU COPY?
COPY THAT.
THERE'S A TIDAL WAVE
COMING.
WE GOT ONE MINUTE.
GET EVERYONE
OFF THE SHIP!
MAYDAY!
MAYDAY! MAYDAY!
GO! GO! GO!
JOHN.
HOLD ON.
NO! LISTEN!
HE'S DOING IT AGAIN.
HANG ON!
ARE YOU CRAZY?
IT'S COMING AT US!
IT'S OUR ONLY CHANCE.
OH, NO...
COME ON!
COME ON...COME ON...
WE'RE GOING
THROUGH IT! HOLD ON!
HOLD ON!
COME HERE!
OH, MY GOD.
HE LOVES
WHAT HE'S DOING.
HEY. HEY.
ARE YOU SURE
IT'S SAFE IN HERE?
FOR NOW.
WELL,
I'LL MAKE A FIRE.
NO.
NO, WE DON'T KNOW
WHO'S AROUND HERE.
WELL...
YOU MEAN,
LOOKING FOR US?
JUST, UH...
DON'T START A FIRE.
I'M GOING TO GO
DOWNSTAIRS
AND GET US SOME FOOD.
SO HOW DOES THIS PLACE
FIT INTO THE JOHN WAHL
SCHEME OF THINGS?
MY EX-WIFE LIVED HERE
FOR A COUPLE OF YEARS.
EX-WIFE?
SHE USED TO LIVE HERE.
ALONE?
NO.
WITH THE GUY
I FOUND HER
IN BED WITH.
WHO'S THE GUY?
JUST...
SOMEONE.
YOU DIDN'T DROP OUT
BECAUSE OF SOME PERSONAL
ETHICAL CONFLICT.
IT WAS BECAUSE
OF HER, WASN'T IT?
WRONG.
THEY GOT ME STRAIGHT
OUT OF GRAD SCHOOL.
I LOVED IT.
FROM DAY ONE,
STANLEY HAD ME WORKING
ON HIGH-ENERGY SYSTEMS,
THINGS, BIG, IMPORTANT THINGS
THAT WERE GOING TO...
HELP THE WORLD.
NEXT THING I KNOW,
I'M DEVELOPING
LASER-GUIDED WARHEADS.
I KEPT THINKING,
IT'S STILL THEORETICAL,
IT'S EXPERIMENTAL...
BOY, WAS I WRONG.
ONE FINE DAY,
IN A SINGLE FLASH
OF LIGHT,
SOMETHING I DEVELOPED
KILLED A LOT OF PEOPLE.
I WAS FINISHING UP
MY STINT
WITH THE JOINT CHIEFS
OF STAFF,
AND EDGAR WAS
TRYING TO CONVINCE ME
TO RUN AN OPERATION...
HE CALLED TACTICAL EXERCISE.
HE GOT HIS WAY...
USING MY WARHEADS.
HE WAS IN CONTROL.
HE KNEW
WHAT WAS GOING TO HAPPEN
EVEN BEFORE HE DID IT.
HE ALSO KNEW HOW
TO IMPRESS THE BRASS...
WITH A REAL BODY COUNT.
JOHN, YOU DIDN'T
KILL ANYBODY.
EDGAR DID.
THAT'S FUNNY.
I KEEP THINKING
IT WAS ME.
THAT'S WHAT
YOU WANT TO THINK.
THAT'S THE PROBLEM.
THANKS FOR
THE INSIGHT, DOCTOR.
YOU'RE NOT
THAT COMPLICATED.
YOU KNOW
WHAT I LEARNED?
DO YOU KNOW WHAT...
REALLY SCARES ME?
NO. TELL ME.
ANYTHING
CAN BE JUSTIFIED.
SOME THINGS
YOU DON'T HAVE
TO JUSTIFY.
WHAT?
I WANT TO
BE IN CONTROL.
OH. SO DO I.
YEAH,
BUT SOMETIMES
YOU'VE GOT
TO LET GO.
WHAT IF I DON'T
WANT TO LET GO?
THEN I CAN ORDER
YOU TO.
I'M A LIEUTENANT
COMMANDER.
YEAH, BUT WHAT
IF I DON'T KNOW
HOW TO LET GO?
LET ME SHOW YOU.
MMM...
HEY.
YOU ALL RIGHT?
I HAD A DREAM.
ABOUT WHAT?
STANLEY SCHIFF.
HE WAS WORKING
ON A WEAPON.
I--I THINK I KNOW
WHAT HE'S GOING
TO DO NEXT.
JOHN, IT WAS
JUST A DREAM.
NO, IT--IT
WAS WHAT BERNARD
WAS WORKING ON.
THE LISBON WAVE.
WHO AM I
GOING TO TELL?
WHO'S GOING
TO BELIEVE ME?
WELL, WE'LL HAVE
TO STOP HIM.
WE CAN'T STOP HIM.
WELL, WE CAN
SLOW HIM DOWN.
OR WE CAN THROW HIM OFF.
UNBELIEVABLE.
THE WHOLE WORLD WAS
BEING HELD HOSTAGE.
I THINK IT STILL IS.
YOU THINK HE
SURVIVED THE WAVE?
I HOPE SO.
UNTIL I SEE HIS BODY...
I HAVE TO ASSUME
HE'S STILL OUT THERE.
DR. SCHIFF,
YOU HAVE TO ACCEPT
THAT HE'S DOING THIS.
JUST THINK OF THOSE
2 UNDERWATER WARHEADS
HE DEVELOPED.
I KNOW PERSONALLY
WHAT THEY CAN DO.
SO DO I.
BUT WH-WHAT
DOES HE WANT?
A BILLION DOLLARS.
HA HA HA!
THAT'S RIDICULOUS.
ALL RIGHT, WHERE'S
HE GOING TO SPEND IT?
HE'S A MURDERER
ON THE RUN.
POWER, DR. SCHIFF.
TO DO WHAT?
USE IT.
PLAY WITH IT.
MANKIND RUNNING
AROUND PANICKED,
WONDERING WHERE
THE NEXT MONSTER'S
GOING TO HIT...
YOU THINK
I'M GOING TO LET
THAT HAPPEN TO ME,
TO MY COUNTRY?
NEGATIVE!
YOU GUYS EAT, SLEEP,
AND DREAM SCIENCE.
I RESPECT THAT,
BUT THIS IS NOT
ABOUT SCIENCE.
THIS IS NOT
ABOUT POLITICS.
THIS IS NOT EVEN
ABOUT BUSINESS.
THIS IS ABOUT WHO
PULLS THE STRINGS.
IT'S ABOUT
CONTROLLING THE WORLD.
POWER.
OH, GOD.
IT IS YOUNG JOHN
AS GOD. I'M...
OH, I DON'T--
I DON'T THINK SO.
NO WAY.
SCHIFF HERE.
JOHN! HEY,
WHERE ARE YOU, MAN?
LISTEN, I DON'T KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE UP TO, BUT--
KEEP HIM TALKING.
HE'S ON NOW.
GET SCHIFF'S NUMBER
AND TRACE IT.
DO IT NOW.
LISBON? WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
BERNARD FIGURED IT OUT,
DIDN'T HE?
SO YOU KILLED HIM.
AND THEN CLARK.
HOW MANY MORE,
STANLEY?
YOU SHOULD
CONSIDER YOURSELF LUCKY.
M-ME?
HOW DO YOU FIGURE THAT?
MARLAN CLARK IS ALIVE.
CLARK IS ALIVE?
WHAT?
I KNOW YOU DON'T TRUST
THESE SPOOKS.
WHY DON'T YOU JUST
GIVE YOURSELF UP TO ME?
TO YOU?
STANLEY, WHAT--
HE HUNG UP.
GOD, I WAS WRONG.
ABOUT WHAT?
OH, HE FIGURED OUT A WAY
TO MAKE ONE OF
HIS WARHEADS DO IT.
IT'S MY FAULT.
I FORGOT.
FORGOT WHAT?
HOW WELL I TAUGHT HIM.
WHAT WAS ALL THAT
ABOUT LISBON?
HUH?
OH.
IN 1755, A WAVE
HIT PORTUGAL.
60,000 PEOPLE
WERE KILLED.
HE'S GOING TO MAKE IT
HAPPEN AGAIN.
OH...
"GIVE YOURSELF UP
TO ME."
THAT WASN'T
FOR MY BENEFIT.
SOMEBODY ELSE
WAS WITH HIM?
EDGAR?
PROBABLY.
HE REALLY NEEDS
TO BELIEVE IT'S ME.
SCHIFF CAN SMELL THAT.
HE CAN FEED HIM WHATEVER
HE NEEDS TO HELP NAIL ME.
WHAT IS IT BETWEEN
YOU AND EDGAR?
HE'S THE ONE I FOUND
IN BED WITH MY WIFE.
HE BROKE UP
YOUR MARRIAGE?
WAS THAT
HIS HOUSE WE W--
BOY, YOU GOT
A LOT OF GUTS.
HE SOLD IT RIGHT AFTER
MY WIFE LEFT HIM.
YOU NEVER SAY HER NAME.
IT DOESN'T MATTER.
WELL, I'D LIKE TO KNOW WHAT
IT IS IN CASE I MEET HER.
IT'S NOT GONNA HAPPEN.
SHE'S DEAD.
SHE DROVE OVER
A CLIFF IN BIG SUR.
EDGAR SAID
HE'D GONE TO SEE HER
TO TRY TO GET BACK
TOGETHER AGAIN.
HE SAID THAT SHE
HAD BEEN DRINKING.
THEY GOT INTO SOME SORT
OF ARGUMENT,
NEXT THING YOU KNOW,
SHE'S OFF IN HIS CAR.
CORONER CONFIRMED
THAT SHE WAS DRUNK.
HE COULD'VE GRABBED THE KEYS,
HE COULD'VE GONE WITH HER,
HE COULD'VE DONE ANYTHING,
BUT HE DIDN'T.
YOU KNOW WHY?
'CAUSE HE DOESN'T CARE.
HE DIDN'T CARE
ABOUT HER.
HE DOESN'T CARE
ABOUT ANYTHING
OR ANYONE BUT HIMSELF.
HER NAME WAS KATHRYN.
I GOT TO GET
TO YOUR LAPTOP.
MY LAPTOP?
I NEED IT
TO PROVE SOMETHING
TO THE ONLY PERSON
WHO MIGHT BELIEVE ME.
MARLAN CLARK?
HE KNOWS
I DIDN'T SHOOT HIM.
WELL, HOW ARE WE
GOING TO GET THERE?
WE CAN'T TAKE
ANOTHER TAXI.
OUR FACES ARE
ALL OVER THE PLACE.
STEAL A CAR.
STEAL A CAR?
STAND BACK.
ARE YOU SURE
IT'S LOCKED?
DR. MILLER,
PLEASE REPORT
TO SECOND FLOOR
NURSES' STATION.
DR. MILLER, REPORT TO
THE SECOND FLOOR
NURSES' STATION.
LOCALLY, IN THE MANHUNT
FOR JOHN WAHL...
YES. CAN I HELP YOU?
MARLAN CLARK.
OK...HE'S, UM,
DOWN TO THE LEFT.
ROOM 9.
HEH...
I THINK YOU GUYS
GOT THE WRONG--
WRONG ROOM.
OH, MAN...
I DIDN'T SHOOT YOU,
CLARK.
YOU KNOW
THAT I DIDN'T.
SO WHAT?
YOU CREEP.
YOU'RE MAKING
THOSE WAVES.
NO. WE CAN PROVE
JOHN ISN'T.
DON'T TELL ME.
TELL EDGAR.
NO. FIRST WE'RE
GONNA TELL YOU,
THEN YOU'RE
GONNA TELL HIM.
WHO IS IT?
I WANT YOU TO
SEE SOMETHING.
COME ON,
OPEN UP.
HERE,
TAKE A LOOK.
"IMAGINE HOW MANY LIVES
WOULD HAVE BEEN SAVED
"HAD A LARGE TIDAL WAVE
BEEN CREATED
TO CLEAR THE BEACHES
OF NORMANDY TO..."
SO DR. SCHIFF WROTE IT.
SO WHAT?
THAT PROVES NOTHING.
ALL RIGHT,
ALL RIGHT, UH...
LOOK, UH...
DO YOU REMEMBER
WHAT SCHIFF SAID
AT THE CONFERENCE
ABOUT DOOLITTLE?
SURE.
I THOUGHT HE HAD
MADE IT ALL UP...
UNTIL I CHECKED.
OH, GOOD FOR YOU.
CLARK, RIGHT AFTER
I LEFT AND WENT HOME,
I GOT A PHONE CALL.
THE VOICE ON THE
OTHER END OF THE LINE
SAID EXACTLY
THE SAME THING
THAT SCHIFF SAID
IN THE ARTICLE.
OH, WAHL...
STANLEY SCHIFF,
HE'S GIVEN HIS LIFE
TO WORKING FOR US.
YES. AND NOW HE WANTS
SOMETHING BACK.
LOOK, HE KNOWS WE
TRACKED DOWN THAT ARTICLE.
HE BROKE IN ON US
AND TOLD US TO MEET HIM
AT THE QUEEN MARY.
YOU'RE JUST
BLOWING MORE SMOKE.
WOULD YOU LISTEN TO ME?
I ONLY DESIGNED
2 WARHEADS
FOR UNDERWATER USE.
THE FIRST ONE
WAS A BUST.
THE SECOND ONE
WAS THE MARK-6,
A COMPUTER-GUIDED
THERMONUCLEAR
SUBMISSILE.
SCHIFF WAS THERE
WHEN IT WAS TESTED.
THE THING HAS A RANGE OF
9,000 MILES, CLARK!
I THINK SCHIFF
IS USING MY MARK-6
TO COLLAPSE
UNDERWATER MOUNTAINS.
THAT'S WHAT'S CREATING
THESE TSUNAMIS.
THANK YOU...
FOR TELLING ME
HOW YOU'RE DOING IT.
IT'S NOT--
IT'S NOT ME!
IF I COULD JUST GET
INTO AQUATRONICS,
I COULD USE
THE MAINFRAME.
I COULD DO
A THERMAL SCAN
FOR RADIATION
TRACKS.
OH, MAN, WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
EVERY THERMONUCLEAR
SUBMISSILE
LEAVES ITS OWN
FOOTPRINT.
I KNOW THE MARK-6.
IT'S MINE.
I KNOW
ITS WEAKNESSES.
SET IT UP, MR. CLARK.
CALL EDGAR.
HEH. HE WOULDN'T
HELP YOU GUYS...
EVEN IF YOU WERE DYING.
THERE'S GONNA BE
ANOTHER WAVE.
WHEN?
IT'S NOT UP TO ME.
DAMN YOU.
FORGET IT.
IT ISN'T HIM.
COME ON, JESSIE,
LET'S GET OUT
OF HERE.
GET YOURSELF
A SNORKEL.
YOU'RE GONNA NEED IT.
I GOT TO GET
TO AQUATRONICS.
WAIT. STOP.
YOU DON'T NEED
THIS ANYMORE.
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA.
WAIT, WAIT, WAIT.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I'M GONNA TAKE IT
UP TO CLARK.
I'M GONNA HOOK IT
UP TO THE NET,
AND LET HIM FIND OUT
WHAT YOU DID
ON HIS OWN.
LOOK, HE DOESN'T
TRUST YOU.
MAYBE HE'LL
LISTEN TO ME.
I--
HELLO, CLARKIE.
HOW YOU DOING?
MR. CLARK,
IF YOU COULD JUST--
MR. CLARK?
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
WHAT...
MR. CLARK?
WHAT HAVE YOU DONE?
CODE BLUE! CODE BLUE!
RESIDENT RIGHT NOW.
RIGHT NOW!
ALL RIGHT, THE MISSILE
HAD TO STRIKE LIGHTNING FAST,
BUT ITS ENGINE
IS NUCLEAR POWERED,
WHICH LEAVES BEHIND
A TRAIL OF RADIATION.
RIGHT. THAT'S WHAT
WE'RE LOOKING FOR.
ALL RIGHT.
I'M READY.
ALL RIGHT, START
THERMAL SCANNING IT.
I'M GONNA GO
BACK TO JULY 1st
WHEN THE FIRST WAVE HIT.
LET ME SPEED IT UP
A LITTLE BIT.
GOOD.
ALL RIGHT, THERE.
THERE, YOU SEE IT?
RIGHT THERE. THAT'S
OUR NUCLEAR BLAST.
UH-HUH. LOOKS
VERY LOW YIELD.
YEAH. STANLEY SCHIFF'S
SPECIALTY,
BUT HE COULDN'T GET IT
LOW YIELD ENOUGH
NOT TO LEAVE SOME
RESIDUAL RADIATION.
UH-HUH. LOOK.
THERE'S TIDAL WAVE
NUMBER 1
HEADING
STRAIGHT FOR JAPAN.
I'M GONNA
GO BACK AN HOUR,
SEE IF WE CAN FIND
OUR SUBMISSILE.
AH, THERE. YOU SEE RIGHT THERE?
THERE SHE IS.
KEEP BACKING IT UP
SO WE CAN SEE WHERE
HE LAUNCHED FROM.
THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
YOU SEE WHERE IT'S
HEADED BACK TO?
HE LAUNCHED IT
OFF THE COAST HERE.
WE HAVE TO SEE IF HE'S
BEEN LAUNCHING THEM ALL
FROM THE SAME PLACE.
UH-HUH...THERE'S
PUERTO VALLARTA...
IT'S THE EXACT
SAME SPOT.
WHERE THE HELL IS THIS?
LET ME SEE.
5 MILES STRAIGHT
OFF THE COAST.
WELL, THERE'S
NOTHING THERE.
THAT DOESN'T MAKE SENSE.
IT'S IN THE MIDDLE
OF NOWHERE.
WELL, IT COULD BE
A SUBMARINE.
STANLEY SCHIFF DOESN'T
HAVE A SUBMARINE.
EVEN IF HE DID,
IT WOULD STILL LEAVE
SOME SORT OF TRAIL.
JOHN...WHAT IF HE'S
NOT ALONE IN THIS?
HE IS. I'D BET
THE FARM ON IT.
YOU ALREADY HAVE.
ALL RIGHT, LOOK, LOOK.
WE--WE KNOW WHERE HE'S
LAUNCHED IT FROM.
LET'S SEE IF WE CAN
GET A LITTLE CLOSER.
CAN YOU ENHANCE IT?
YEAH.
MORE.
YOU SEE
WHAT I'M SAYING?
IF THERE WERE
A SUBMARINE,
IT'D SHOW UP SOMETHING
BY NOW. MORE.
OK.
WHOA. ALMOST THERE.
ONE MORE TIME.
THERE.
I'LL BE DAMNED.
YOU SEE, I KEPT
TELLING THEM,
BUT THEY JUST WOULDN'T
LISTEN TO ME.
EVEN WITH ITS ENGINE OFF,
MY MISSILE STILL LEAVES
A NUCLEAR TRAIL.
NOT A LOT, BUT SOMETHING.
JUST ENOUGH.
WHERE DID IT
COME FROM?
CAN YOU PULL UP A REGIONAL
TOPOGRAPHICAL MAP OF THE AREA?
UH, I THINK SO.
SOMETHING WITH CITY
AND COASTAL COORDINATES.
YEP.
GOT IT.
MY GOD.
WHERE IS THIS?
IT'S THE BOATYARD
RIGHT NEXT TO THE MARINA
AT KING HARBOR,
HOME OF STANLEY SCHIFF.
HE'S LAUNCHING
FROM THERE?
I DON'T--I--
I DON'T KNOW.
I GOT TO FIND OUT.
I GOT TO
GET OVER THERE.
SOMEHOW I GOT TO GET TO
THE COMPUTER GUIDANCE SYSTEM.
MAYBE I CAN
DISARM IT ON ROUTE
OR I CAN ABORT IT
WITH A SELF-DESTRUCT.
LOOK, I WANT YOU
TO GET EDGAR HERE--
GET EVERYONE HERE.
HAVE THEM TAKE
A LOOK AT THIS.
PUT IT UP
ON THE BIG SCREEN.
AND WHEN YOU'RE DONE,
GET BACK TO ME
AS FAST AS YOU CAN.
WHAT IF HE REFUSES?
NO CHANCE.
HE STILL WANTS
IT TO BE ME.
HE PUT UP
A HELL OF A FIGHT.
PURCELL.
WHO?
PATCH HER THROUGH.
JESSICA WEAVER
WANTS TO TALK TO ME.
THAT ONE CAUSED THE WAVE
THAT HIT JAPAN.
THAT ONE'S PUERTO VALLARTA,
AND THEY WERE ALL LAUNCHED
FROM THE SAME PLACE--
RIGHT THERE.
A BOATYARD
IN REDONDO BEACH.
LOOK! ANOTHER NUCLEAR MISSILE
HAS BEEN LAUNCHED.
LISBON.
WAHL IS CALLING
THIS ONE?
AREN'T YOU LISTENING
TO WHAT WE'RE SAYING,
OR IS YOUR OWN
PERSONAL AGENDA
MORE IMPORTANT
THAN THE TRUTH?
I DON'T KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
THERE'S ONLY ONE TRUTH
I WANT HERE--
THE MAN
WHO'S DOING THIS
AND YOUR
INVOLVEMENT IN IT.
THAT'S WHAT YOU SHOULD
BE WORRYING ABOUT.
OH, HEY,
UH, STANLEY SCHIFF--
HAVE YOU SEEN HIM
AROUND?
HE'S NOT
ON HIS BOAT.
YOU MIGHT CHECK
HIS SAIL LOFT.
THAT'S THE LITTLE RED BUILDING
AROUND THE CORNER.
ALL RIGHT,
THANK YOU.
STAND BY.
WE'VE GOT AN EMERGENCY
SITUATION DEVELOPING.
WHEN I KNOW WHERE IT IS,
I'LL TELL YOU.
WAHL IS SETTING US UP.
I KNOW IT.
IT'S LAUNCHED.
LATE FOR CLASS AGAIN,
MR. WAHL.
STANLEY...
THE MISSILE...
ON ITS WAY.
DON'T DO THIS,
STANLEY.
DON'T DO THIS!
DO WHAT, KILL YOU...
OR WIPE OUT SAN DIEGO?
SAN DIEGO?
NOT JUST 1 WAVE, BUT 2,
AND TOMORROW MAKES 3.
NOT EXACTLY YOUR YOUNG JOHN
GUIDANCE DELIVERY SYSTEM,
BUT IT WORKS.
A DRONE CARRIER.
OUT THERE
IN THE MIDDLE OF NOWHERE
SHE DROPS HER LOAD,
TURNS AROUND
AND COMES CHUGGING
SAFELY BACK HOME AGAIN.
JUST LIKE ONE OF
THOSE BATHTUB TOYS
WHEN YOU WERE A KID.
FOR GOD'S SAKES!
JOHNNY...
THEY GAVE YOU
THE PRIZE,
BUT THEY'RE GOING TO
REMEMBER ME.
ACTUALLY, THEY'RE GOING
TO REMEMBER BOTH OF US.
HOW DO YOU THINK
I GOT THE MISSILES?
I PULLED A TRADE.
MY SYSTEM...
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
UGH!
STANLEY, GIVE ME
THE CODE.
ARRRR...
GIVE ME
THE ACCESS CODE!
GIVE ME THE CODE!
YOU HOLD OR
I'LL USE THIS!
IT'S TOO LATE, JOHNNY.
THIS'LL GET
THEIR ATTENTION...
AND THAT AIN'T
THE HALF OF IT.
STANLEY...
DON'T LAUNCH IT.
I HAVE TO.
PLEASE STAND BY
FOR AN IMPORTANT MESSAGE.
STANLEY...
I'M BEGGING YOU.
DON'T DO THIS.
NO.
OK. ALL RIGHT,
ALL RIGHT!
EDGAR!
STANLEY...
COME ON, STANLEY.
EDGAR, YOU HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT YOU JUST DID.
STAY WHERE
YOU ARE, WAHL.
YOU'RE UNDER ARREST.
YOU JUST SEALED THE FATE
OF 100,000 PEOPLE, MAN!
THERE'S NOT GONNA BE
JUST 1 TIDAL WAVE.
THERE'S GONNA BE 2.
2?
LOOK.
MOVE AWAY
FROM THERE.
AND THERE GOES
OUR ACCESS CODE.
YOU SEE THIS?
YOU SEE THIS
RIGHT HERE?
THAT'S A MISSILE.
IT'S HEADED FOR ANOTHER
UNDERWATER MOUNTAIN.
WHEN IT HITS,
AND IT COLLAPSES THAT
UNDERWATER SEAMOUNT,
WE ARE GONNA HAVE
OURSELVES
ANOTHER TIDAL WAVE, AND
IT'S GONNA MAKE LISBON
LOOK LIKE
A GOOD SURFING DAY.
JOHN, YOU
GOT TO STOP IT.
I CAN'T.
MOVE THE HELL
AWAY FROM THERE!
EDGAR,
IF YOU'RE GONNA SHOOT ME,
YOU BETTER SHOOT ME NOW.
OTHERWISE, SHUT THE HELL UP.
FORGET IT. IT'S NOT
GONNA WORK, JESSIE.
UM, TSUNAMI.
TRY TSUNAMI.
COME ON, COME ON.
WAHL...
UM...WHAT ABOUT...
WAIT. FUJI.
IT'S USELESS.
OK, UH...
FORGET IT!
OH, FOR GO--
ALL RIGHT, HERE WE GO.
OH, FOR CRYING--
UH...
SELF-DESTRUCT ISN'T
GOING TO DO IT.
NO, I'M NOT TRYING
FOR SELF-DESTRUCT.
I GOTTA SHIFT
THE MISSILE'S COURSE.
CHANGE THE COURSE?
WHAT--
EDGAR...HE TOLD YOU
TO BE QUIET!
IF I CAN SHIFT THE COURSE
OF THE SECOND MISSILE
TO MAKE IT HIT ITS TARGET
FROM A DIFFERENT ANGLE,
I HAVE A CHANCE
OF MAKING A WAVE
THAT MUST JUST
HIT THE FIRST WAVE.
COLLIDING FORCES.
WHAT'S THAT--
SHUT UP, EDGAR.
IF JOHN CAN GET
A SECOND WAVE
TO HIT THE FIRST ONE,
THEY'LL NEUTRALIZE
EACH OTHER.
CAN YOU DO IT?
WHAT WAS IT.
WHAT WAS THE YEAR...
OK. I GOT IT.
UM, OK,
JOHN, JOHN, JOHN...
JUST STOP
FOR A SECOND.
STOP FOR A SECOND.
I KNOW. WE GOT
PLENTY OF TIME.
WELL, DO
SOMETHING, WAHL.
EDGAR, SHUT UP.
WHAT?
WHAT DID STANLEY
LOVE
MORE THAN ANYTHING?
AH, JESSIE--
COME ON, THINK!
ALL RIGHT, HE, UH...
HE LOVED SCIENCE.
HE WANTED FAME. HE--
THE NOBEL PRIZE.
NOBEL PRIZE...
USELESS.
OK, WAIT, STOP.
THINK A SECOND.
LOOK AT ME.
LOOK AT ME!
WHAT DID HE HATE?
HE HATED ME.
YES.
BINGO. BINGO.
HERE WE GO.
HIT THE STOP BUTTON
RIGHT HERE.
GOT IT.
OK, NEW COORDINATES
ARE IN.
WE ARE...ON TARGET.
WE'RE ALMOST THERE.
COME ON, BABY.
COME ON, DO IT.
DO IT, BABY.
DO IT.
4...3...2...
COME ON.
IT'S WORKING. 1...
BY MY CALCULATIONS,
WE SHOULD BE GETTING
A FRONT-ROW SEAT.
HEY, WHAT'S THIS?
THIS IS FOR YOU.
YEAH?
YEAH.
SO HOW'S IT GOING
OUT THERE?
SURF UP OR RISING
OR WHATEVER IT'S
SUPPOSED TO BE DOING?
I SAID IT WRONG.
NO.
WELL?
DO YOU LIKE HIM?
NO.
HEY...YOU LIKE SURFIN'?
WANT TO LEARN TO SURF?
OH, YEAH.
HE'S WONDERFUL.
LOOK AT THAT FACE.