[Instrumental music]
♪ By the way the land
is layin', ♪
♪ think I'd be safe in sayin', ♪
♪ that over the next hill
we'll be home ♪
♪ it's a straight and narrow
highway, ♪
♪ no detour and no byways, ♪
♪ and over the next hill,
we'll be home ♪
♪ from the prophets
I've been hearin', ♪
♪ I would say the end
is nearin', ♪
♪ for I see familiar landmarks
all along ♪
♪ by the dreams that
I've been dreamin', ♪
♪ there'll come
a great redeemin' ♪
♪ and over the next hill,
we'll be home ♪
[Instrumental music]
♪ By the turn that the tide
has takin', ♪
♪ I would say there's
no mistakin', ♪
♪ that over the next hill,
we'll be home ♪
♪ there's a place that
we are nearin', ♪
♪ that so many
have been fearin', ♪
♪ and over the next hill,
we'll be home ♪
♪ when we get there,
we're all hopin' ♪
♪ that we'll find the gate
is open, ♪
♪ and there'll be a refuge
from the comin' storm ♪
♪ for the way's been
long and weary, ♪
♪ but at last the end
is nearin', ♪
♪ and over the next hill,
we'll be home ♪
♪ over the next hill,
we'll be home ♪♪
Camera man: Shawna,
that light's too hot.
Shawna: This light?Camera man: That light.
Old Templeton: Go away.
Go away, get away, get away.
Shawna: Sir?
Old Templeton: Oh, it's good
to see you today.
Reporter: ...It was.
Old Templeton: But I thought
yesterday's interview was
very productive.
Shawna: I'm pretty sure
that we will be out of your way
by the end of the day.
Reporter: No, you're wrong. Old Templeton: Well,
I will miss you.
Porter: There's no dirt here Billy Graham. D Templeton:
Ll miss all of you.
Reporter: And even if there
was, I'm not gonna get it
out of this guy.
Reporter: He's a professional charmer.Old Templeton: Go away.
Go away.
Reporter: I'll call you back.
Reporter: Dave,
roll it.Old Templeton: Not now!
Camera man: Sound, speed,
camera one, camera two,
camera three... slate it.
Shawna: "The last hours
of decision" documentary.
Charles Templeton interview.
Take three...Common markers.
Reporter: Mr. Templeton.
Mr. Templeton.
You just said, "get away".
Who do you want to go away?
Old Templeton: I like talking
to you, I do.
Do you have to finish
the interview today?
Reporter: Well, we were...
No, of course not.
We, ah, we can come tomorrow.
You're such a fascinating
gentleman.
Old Templeton: Oh, that
would be marvelous.
Reporter: Great, now,
we'd like to know anything,
anything at all,
that you wanna tell US
about your friendship
with Billy Graham.
Old Templeton: You want
something juicy, don't you?
Reporter: No.
Old Templeton: Yes, you do.
[Laughing]
Well, Billy's life, Billy's life
was... was like a fairy-tale.
[Instrumental music]
Reporter: A fairy-tale?
Go on...
Old Templeton: I mean,
they weren't rich people,
but they certainly weren't
poor either, you know.
I mean, they had a dairy farm, you know.
Billy grew up in a Norman Rockwell painting.
And believe it or not,
all Billy ever wanted to do
was play baseball.
[Sports announcer
talking on radio]
Albert: You played a heckuva
game today.
Billy: Hey, thanks, Albert.
Morrow: When'd you start
wearin' lipstick, son?
Billy: Oh.
These are for you.
Morrow: Thank you.
[Men praying]
Billy: What is daddy doin'?
It looks like he let those men
sweet-talk him into usin'
our property again.
Morrow: Billy frank!
Now, your daddy has very
personal reasons for feelin'
the way he does.
And maybe someday he'll
share 'em with you.
But until then, son, I expect
you to be respectful.
You understand me?
Billy: Yes, ma'am.
Morrow: Go on and get
washed up for dinner.
And wash your face.
Frank: For what we are
about to receive, lord,
make US truly grateful.
In the name of our savior
and lord, Jesus Christ, amen.
Morrow: Amen.
Frank: Billy, you wanna
hand me that sweet tea?
Billy: What's this doin' here?
Don't tell me you guys are...
It's just that all these
evangelists are alike.
They're just "fleecers
of the flock."
Morrow: Billy...
Billy: I'm just sayin' the last
thing Charlotte needs
is another money grubbing
Elmer gantry.
Frank: God listens
to everyone, Billy.
Money or no.
Billy: Well, I'm just sayin'...
Frank: You sure have
a lot to say.
Billy: Well, I'm just sayin'...
Frank: I hear what you're
sayin', son... now eat.
Catherine: I like Dr. Ham,
Billy.
Albert: I like him too.
I'm going to see him tonight.
Come with me.
Billy: Two things
I'm never gonna be,
is an undertaker
and a preacher.
Frank: Son, how do you
come by all this,
"what you're just sayin'?"
Billy: Well, kids at school
were sayin',
"if you've seen one evangelist,
you've seen 'em all."
Frank: You've heard from some
people that don't know.
Maybe you need to hear
for yourself.
If not, you're just repeatin'
somebody else's ignorance, son.
Ignorance!
Not another word.
♪ Like a bird from these
prison bars has flown ♪
♪ I'll fly away... ♪
[Car radio playing]
Billy: Hey, t.W.!
[Radio static]
♪ They set the stage,
began to play... ♪
Albert: Are we gonna sit here
an' listen to the radio,
or go inside an' see US
a revival?
Billy: I can't believe I let
you talk me into this.
♪ ...joy will never end,
I'll fly away ♪
♪ I'll fly away, oh glory,
Albert: Catch ya on
the other side.
♪ When I die, hallelujah
by and by, I'll fly away ♪
♪ I'll fly away, oh glory,
I'll fly away [in the morning] ♪
♪ When I die, hallelujah
by and by, I'll fly away ♪
♪ when I die, hallelujah
by and by, I'll fly away ♪♪
[Applause]
Billy: I see men ready
to "fleece the flock,"
over there.
T.w: Enjoy the moment,
Billy.
You'll never see
nothin' like this.
Dr. Ham: As I travel
all throughout the south
and see the full effect of this
great depression upon our land,
I can understand why some
of you, maybe all of you,
wanna just "fly away"
one glad morning, just fly away.
[Applause]
Dr. Ham: Well, brothers
and sisters,
I've got some important news
for you tonight,
news that you might
not find so welcome,
news that's gonna make
you stop and think.
You cannot work your way
into heaven!
You cannot beg your way
You cannot buy your way
into heaven!
You cannot bribe your way
You cannot climb your way
into heaven!
[Applause]
Dr. Ham: Your best efforts,
your best efforts,
are filthy rags in the presence
of the almighty god.
Now, none of US is all good,
not a single one.
None of US is all bad.
We are each imperfect.
We are each wanting
in the eyes of the lord.
Sinners! Sinners!
Each and every one!
Well-dressed man: Who do think
you are, comin' into our town
and smearin' the good
name of our citizens?
Dr. Ham: Who am I, sir?
I am the messenger.
God told me that there
was sin in this town,
and he told me where.
I am the messenger!
[Applause]
Dr ham: Now, I ask a question
of all of you.
I ask a question of the young
men in back.
You, son, what brings you here
tonight, huh?
Your own two feet?
Ho, ho, ho... no!
Two thousand years
before you were born,
god planned for you
to be here tonight.
You think this is
an accident?
No, son, let me
tell you somethin'.
You got an emptiness
in your soul,
and you can't fill it
with a, with a fancy car
or, or a pretty girl.
No, it's there, and it's gnawing
at ya, and you can't fill it!
[Applause]
Dr ham: So, you ask yourself,
you say to yourself,
"well, how do I get into heaven?
I'm just an average man.
Sometimes I'm good.
Sometimes I'm bad.
Sometimes I've got love
bloomin' in my heart,
and sometimes it is dark
as the devil!"
Crowd: Amen!
Dr. Ham: "Sometimes I know
where I'm goin', and sometimes,
oh sweet Jesus, sometimes
I am lost, and I am lonely."
You will die in your sin unless
you do somethin' about it!
And guess what?
You are not alone!
[Applause]
Dr ham: Brothers and sisters,
brothers and sisters,
there is some good
news tonight.
There is some good news,
and here's what it is...
Our lord, Jesus Christ, cares
for each and every one of you.
He loves you, and he loves you,
sweet girl.
Sir, he even loves you!
And young man,
he loves you!
Remember, young man,
you follow Jesus
and he will never leave you
or forsake you... never!
[Applause]
Dr. Ham: My brothers
and sisters,
tonight Jesus offers you
forgiveness and purpose
for life.
If you want to free your soul
of heartbreak, of pain,
of doubt, of anxiety,
come! Come down!
Come show the lord,
Jesus Christ,
your total commitment!
Come on! Come down!
Show your commitment by walkin'
this well worn, sawdust trail!
Come on down!
It is not too late!
You are not alone!
Oh sing, my brothers.
Oh, sweet Jesus.
Forgive their souls.
Sweet Jesus, forgive
their souls.
Fill their hearts with love,
and with gratitude.
Just as I am.
Oh, sweet Jesus,
we bow before thee.
We give our life to thee,
sweet Jesus.
♪ Just as I am,
though tossed about ♪
♪ with many a conflict
with many a doubt, ♪
♪ fightings and fears
within, without, ♪
♪ oh lamb of god,
I come, I come ♪
♪ just as I am
and waiting not, ♪
♪ to rid my soul
of one dark blot, ♪
♪ to thee whose blood
can cleanse each spot ♪
♪ oh lamb of god,
I come, I come ♪♪
Morrow: Mornin', son.
Mornin', Albert.
Albert: Mornin', ma'am.
Morrow: You was out
pretty late last night, huh?
Have a late team meetin'?
Billy: I didn't go
to the team meetin'.
Morrow: Oh, where'd you go?
Albert: Um, I'll,
I'll just get these on up
to the top of the house.
Billy: Ah, I went to the, ah,
I went to the tent revival.
Morrow: You did?
Billy: Momma, did you tell
Dr. Ham anything about me?
Morrow: Well, let me think.
Uh, no.
Billy: He just said all
these things about me
in front of everybody.
Morrow: Well, I didn't say
a word about you to that man.
I, I didn't say one word
to that man at all.
Frank: Billy, get that milk
up to the icebox, boy!
Billy: Yes, sir!
Um, I got this
at the tent revival.
It's for the Bob Jones academy.
So, what do ya think?
Can I, can I, can I go?
Morrow: Oh son, I think
you know what I think.
Billy: What about poppa?
Morrow: Well, you're gonna
have to ask him for himself.
You know that.
Don't you forget, Billy, if you
wanna know somethin',
you ask questions,
and I don't care
who it is, okay?
Billy: Yes, ma'am.
Morrow: I'll take that for you.
Billy: You sure?
Morrow: Yeah. You go ahead
and ask your daddy yourself.
[Instrumental music]
Old Templeton: Would you
like to know
what my religious
conversion was like?
Reporter: Absolutely!
[Swing music]
Man: That'll teach you to mess
with my girlfriend, ya punk.
Young Templeton: Lord,
come down! Come down!
Old Templeton: I began to pray,
my face upturned
to the heavens,
tears streaming.
And in a moment,
a weight began to lift,
a weight as heavy as I.
It had passed through
my face, my belly, my chest,
my arms, my shoulders,
and lifted off entirely.
And I felt I could've
leapt over a wall.
An ineffable warmth,
a warmth began to suffuse.
A light turned on
in my chest,
and its refining fire
cleansed me.
I hardly dared breathe,
fearing I might end this,
or alter the moment.
And somewhere, somewhere
in that darkness,
I, I heard a still,
small voice, my own,
whispering softly over,
and over, and over again,
"thank you, lord!
Thank you, lord!
Thank you! Thank you!
Thank you!"
Old Templeton: Did I mention
to you, that Billy...
Reporter: Billy,
what about Billy?
Old Templeton: Well, the summer
before he went off to college,
he, he became quite
the door-to-door salesman.
[Bluegrass music]
Billy: Hello, ma'am.
My name is Billy Graham,
and I'm here to change
your life.
Housewife: And just tell me,
how are you gonna do that,
Mr. Billy Graham?
Billy: Well, I have here,
some of the very...
[Crashing sound]
Billy: Sorry ma'am.
Ah...
I am gonna show you the finest
brush Fuller has to offer.
And it's not this one.
Actually, it's not these
either.
Sorry, ma'am. Ah,
here it is, okay.
This brush here is the favorite
Fuller brush of every woman
in the county.
No, no, this Fuller brush
happens to be
the favorite brush of every
woman in the state.
Housewife: How much
do I owe ya?
Billy: Really?
[Bluegrass music]
Billy: Hello, ma'am.
My name is Billy Graham,
and I am here to change
your life.
Dr. Minder: You'll find
the basis of our teaching
here at Florida Bible institute
comes from our belief
in the inspiration
and the authority
of the word of god.
Now, our staff is here to help
you to inquire, to question,
to learn to think
for yourselves.
We're here to guide
and assist you
in this, at times, difficult,
but deeply satisfying journey.
Billy: Whoo-hoo!
Hey t.W, what'dya know
about Florida rain?
Dr. Minder: The term,
"evangelist,"
comes from the Greek word,
"evangelion."
Meaning, one who announces
"good news",
and giving rise to the word,
"gospel".
[Bell ringing]
Dr. Minder: Everyone, ah,
please remember to sign up
for the outreach program.
Emily: Hi.
Dr minder: Lots of opportunities
for budding preachers, Billy.
Billy: Preachin'?
Dr. Minder: Yes, would you like
to speak at the men's mission?
Billy: Speakin'?
Emily: Do you have
a problem speaking?
Billy: No, but...
Emily: I'm Emily.
Billy: I'm speakin'. Ah,
i'm, i'm, I'm Billy.
Charles: And i'm...
Charles: Charles massey.
Emily: Hello, Charles massey.
Charles: Hello, Emily.
And Dr. Minder,
if Mr. Speaking doesn't
wish to preach,
I would love to honor the lord
and share his word.
Dr. Minder: We'll see,
Charles.
Billy, don't worry, you can,
you can just serve dinners.
Billy: Well, dinners
or speakin',
you can count on me, Emily.
Ah... Dr. Minder.
T.w.: Smooth.
That went well.
Billy: I don't know the first
thing about preachin'!
T.w.: You know how you were
spreading the good news
about Fuller brushes?
Billy: Yeah.
T.w.: Well, preachin' is
spreadin' the good news
about god's love.
Easier sale, if you ask me.
Billy: Yeah...
For all who have sinned...!
For all have sinned
and fallen short of the glory.
And entered through
that narrow gate!
For wide is the gate
and narrow,
and broad is the...!
That's terrible...
What's stoppin' ya?
Will ya be saved?
And you! And you!
Well, if you burn in hell,
you don't blame me.
You were warned.
[Laughter]
Billy: Alright fine, I may have
crossed the line.
I'll let god decide who goes
to heaven and hell.
And what about you, sir?
Custodian: Honest opinion?
Billy: Well, yes, sir.
Custodian: Son, I've seen the
greatest preachers of the day.
They've all come through here,
and they all have one thing
in common... talent.
So, I can spot it
when I see it.
And, trust me when I say this,
son, you ain't got it.
[Laughing]
Billy: And broad is the road
that leads to destruction...!
I mean, this is all gonna take
about two hours, t.W.
[T.w. Snoring]
Billy: Great, I even
put him to sleep.
[Bluegrass music]
Billy: I can't do this.
T.w.: Yes, you can.
Billy: Okay... oh...
Nope, still can't do it.
T.w.: Billy, you can!
Billy: Well, I guess I did
get dressed up.
I did my hair.
How's my hair look?
T.w.: Your hair looks fine,
Billy.
Billy: You sure? Okay.
Billy: Nope... t.W: Billy!
Billy: Okay, fine. "And many
will enter through..."
[Footsteps]
Dr. Minder: Speak clearly.
You'll be fine.
Church leader: Well, let's see
who we got on the roster today.
Let's see here.
Comin' all the way from
Florida Bible institute,
to offer US words
of inspiration,
we have a Mr. William frank
Graham.
Billy: Ah, just Billy, sir.
Church leader: Okay. Folks,
welcome, just Billy.
[Crowd laughs]
Church leader: Uh, you
about ready, son?
Billy: Ready for what?
Oh! Yes... ready.
Dr. Minder: Go get 'em.
[Clock ticking]
Billy: Sin is missing
the Mark!
The Greek word for sin is,
metanoia, like an arrow,
aimed at a target,
missing the bulls-eye!
And we have all missed
the Mark with god!
And that's about all I know
about the 144,000.
[Clock ticks once]
Billy: And what about
David and Moses!
[Clock ticks once]
Billy: Is there anyone who
thinks they have not sinned?
You need Christ!
T.w.: Hallelujah! Amen!
T.w.: I'm gonna sit down now.
Dr. Minder: Billy, I can't wait
to see what god's got in mind
for you.
Billy: You mean that
in a good way?
Dr. Minder: Yeah, Billy.
I mean that in a good way.
Billy: Mind if I sit here?
Emily: Sure... do you eat
as fast as you preach?
Billy: Nah...
Oh, you were there?
Emily: I was sure
you'd noticed.
Billy: I did notice.
You were there,
most definitely there.
Emily: I thought...
Billy: Yeah?
Emily: I thought you did
a good job.
Billy: Really?
Emily: Yeah, really.
Student: So, being an evangelist is spreading the word?
Dr. Minder: Yes, Billy.
Billy: Dr. Minder, who becomes
an evangelist?
Is, is desire enough, or is it
a matter of devotion?
Dr. Minder: Well, for one,
Billy, you need to develop
good oratorial skills.
And it cannot, and must not,
ever be about money and fame.
It's about "the call."
It's about serving the one
that died for you.
It's about his message.
Florist: I know what
you want!
A, a corsage!
A corsage! Ha-ha-ha!
Corsages are 25 cents,
and 50 cents for something
extra special.
Billy: I'll take
a 50-cent corsage.
Florist: Special lady?
Billy: Special, as in?
Florist: Special!
Billy: Yes, very special.
Florist: Extra special!
♪ But if a man sings
in a forest, ♪
♪ nobody hears his song ♪
♪ but if somebody sings
for somebody, ♪
♪ sometimes somebody
sings along ♪
♪ come on and sit down,
sing some songs and then, ♪
♪ stand up and sing
some more ♪
♪ I hope you sit and stay ♪
♪ and like the songs
that I play ♪
♪ I'd be so very sad to see you
slip out the door ♪
♪ sit right down,
relax, unwind ♪
♪ you do your thing
and I'll do mine ♪
♪ I'm gonna sit down,
sing a song, and then, ♪
♪ stand up and sing
some more... ♪♪
Emily: Billy...
Emily: We need to talk.
Billy: I thought I was
bringing you to this.
Emily: Billy, I'm in love
with Charles.
Emily: He's going to Harvard.
Billy: So?
Emily: So, I wanna marry someone
who's going to do something
special with his life.
Billy: Special?
Emily: Look, you're
a nice fellow.
I like you, but...
Billy: But what?
Emily: I just don't think you're
going to amount to much.
I'm sorry.
♪ Sit right down,
relax, unwind ♪
♪ you do your thing
and I'll do mine ♪
♪ I'm gonna sit down,
sing a song, and then, ♪
♪ stand up and sing
some more... ♪♪
T.w.: Hey, lucky ducky!
Somethin' I said?
Ooh, corsage.
[Instrumental music]
[Applause]
Dr. Minder: William
Franklin Graham,
you are now ordained
as a servant of Christ.
Billy: Excuse me.
Oh, sorry.
Excuse me, I think
you dropped this.
Ruth: Oh, thank you.
Billy: You're welcome.
And you are...
Ruth: Late for class.
Thank you again.
Billy: You're welcome,
again.
Ruth: Well, bye.
Billy: Bye.
Billy: Oh, I'm Billy.
Billy Graham.
Ruth: Well, nice to meet you
Billy, Billy Graham, i'm...
Billy: Ruth...
You're Ruth bell.
Marjorie: He's been
eyein' you for months.
Ruth: I know.
Grady: Holy cow, do you
know who that is?
Billy: I know.Grady: Every guy
on campus...
Billy: I know...Grady: Holy cow.
Billy: I know!!!
Marjorie: Hello-o-o!
I mean you!
We're in anthropology
together.
I sit next to you?
Billy: Marjorie...
Baker.
Marjorie: Bostrom.
Close enough.
Billy: Bostrom.
Marjorie: Do you wanna study
together for the midterm?
I could use the extra help.
Is there something wrong
with my ear?
Billy: Your ear?
Marjorie: Is that a note?
Billy: [Scoffs] A note.
No.
Marjorie: You seem to have
a fascination with my roommate.
Billy: Ruth is your roommate?
Marjorie: So, tomorrow,
it's a date?
Billy: Well, I really look
forward to it.
Marjorie: I really bet you do.
[Instrumental music]
Marjorie: Are you gonna study
for the mid-term, or study Ruth?
Billy: Huh?
Marjorie: Is that
a note?
Billy: What note?
Marjorie: What, are you
in the fifth grade?
Billy: No! No! Marjorie: Gimme that.
Billy: No! No! No!Librarian: Shhhh!
Shhhh!
Billy: You don't have to
if you don't want to.
Ruth: [Whispers]
I'd love to.
Librarian: She said
she'd love to, now, shhh!
Marjorie: Now can we study?
Billy: Yeah.
♪ I would bet my life,
like I bet my heart ♪
♪ that you were the one,
baby ♪
♪ I've never been so sure
of anything before, ♪
♪ it's drivin' my heart crazy ♪
♪ I can't hold out,
I can't hold back now, ♪
♪ like I've done before ♪
♪ darlin', look at me, I've
fallen like a fool for you ♪
♪ and darlin' can't you see, ♪
♪ I'd do anything
you want me to ♪♪
Ruth: The way I see it is,
if you are not willin'
to live your life for something
greater than yourself,
then life's not worth livin'.
Billy: I believe that is
the most profoundly beautiful
set of words I've ever heard
strung together.
Ruth: What about you?
What do you wanna do
with your life?
Billy: I say...
Ruth: Mm-hmm?
Billy: What you said.
Ruth: What does that mean?
Billy: It means...
I believe god's callin' me
to preach the gospel.
Ruth: You mean,
as an evangelist?
Billy: Yeah.
Ruth: Then do it!
Billy: Really? Ruth: Yeah.
Billy: You think that'd
be alright by you?
Ruth: You need
my permission?
Billy: Well no,
but I'd like it.
Ruth: Well, you have it.
[Instrumental music]
Billy: How can one girl be so
beautiful and so spiritual,
all at the same time?
Grady: You're in way deep,
my boy.
[Instrumental music]
Billy: All right, Ruth,
keep your eye on the ball.
Don't let it hit ya.
It'll hurt.
Ruth: Okay.
Billy: All right. Okay.
Eye on the ball.
Yeah, great!
Ruth: All right, Billy, you keep
your eye on the ball.
Don't let it hit ya.
It'll hurt, okay?
Billy: Okay.
[Laughing]
Billy: All right, great.
Billy: Wonderful!
[Laughing]
Billy: Perfect!
Ruth: Thanks.
Billy: All right,
here it comes.
Ruth: All right.
That was a good one.
Billy: All right.
Bring the heat.
Ruth: All right.
Billy: Maybe we should
go eat now.
Let's go see what we got.
She's the most wonderful girl in the world, momma.
She's so smart,
and beautiful, and...
I mean, she's so compassionate, momma.
Morrow: I'm happy for you,
son.
Frank: You wanna tell Billy what
these long distance calls cost?
Morrow: Go on, honey.
Billy: I'm gonna marry her,
momma.
Morrow: Are, are you sure
she's, I mean, 'the one'?
Billy: She's the one,
momma.
There's no other.
Ruth: Ever since I was 12,
I've had my mind set
on staying single
so I could go be
a missionary in Tibet.
I couldn't ask a husband
or children to make
the same sacrifice.
Billy: Well, is there
anything wrong with being
a wife and a mother?
Ruth: It's the most wonderful
thing in the world for
some women, but not all.
Billy: I could go to Tibet.
[Instrumental music]
Billy: What's wrong?
Ruth: My sister's really sick,
and I have to leave school
to go and take care of her.
I just wanted
to tell you myself
why I won't be
seeing you again.
Billy: Marry me...
We could take care of her
together.
Ruth: Billy, I can't.
Not now.
Not yet, maybe not ever.
You think you know what
you want out of life,
and then all of
a sudden it's...
Billy: I just can't give up
on you... I love you.
[Instrumental music]
Beth: Tell me again.
Ruth: Tell you what, sis?
Beth: You know, about Billy.
Ruth: Billy?
Billy: And, no matter what
you may have done,
the lord watches over you.
He watches and he...
Cares for you.
Homeless man: I don't see
no lord watchin' over me,
preacher.
The lord want nothin'
to do with me.
Nobody wants me.
Nobody wants to have
nothin' to do with me.
Billy: But that's
not true, sir.
Homeless man: If you want money
for your preachin',
you done come
to the wrong place.
Billy: I didn't come here
for money.
Homeless man: Well, what'cha
come here for?
Billy: To do the lord's work.
Homeless man: Shouldn't you be
in your pajamas?
Tucked away in your bed with
your little Teddy bear,
drinkin' a glass
of cold milk?
Billy: You cannot be found
unless you are first lost.
And the lord can find you.
He can give you your life
back again.
Let him into your heart.
Homeless man: Can you
help me, preacher?
I mean, can you help me?
Billy: What is your name,
sir?
Homeless man: My name's Darryl.
Darryl's my name.
[Sobbing]
♪ Love is a changing river... ♪
Billy: Father god, Darryl
and I come to you today.
And I believe this was not
an accident.
I believe you had
this planned for US,
two thousand years before
Darryl and I were even born.
I believe, I believe.
Ruth: I believe, I believe.
♪ ...and stare at forever... ♪
Rosa: Sis, here's your tea.♪ ...Into the great,
wild beyond, ♪
♪ then I'm gone ♪♪
[Instrumental music]
Billy: She said yes.
She said yes,
she said yes, she said yes,
she said yes. She said yes!
She said yes!
Right here! Right here!
She said yes! She said yes!
Ruth, she said yes.
Grady: What in the world
are you talkin' about?
Billy: It's Ruth. She said yes!
She said she'd marry me!
Grady: Well, congratulations.
Billy: Yes! She said yes!
She said yes!
Mr. and Mrs. Ruth Graham.
♪ "Here comes the bride" ♪
♪ "here comes the bride" ♪
Old Templeton: Billy's life plan, at this point,
was nothing more than being
a pastor in a little church,
going into the army
as a second lieutenant,
perhaps being a chaplain and getting shipped overseas.
He would come home, become
a missionary with Ruth,
going to, possibly China.
But something, something always
stepped in and saved him.
Reporter: Hmmm.
Old Templeton: If you'd been
there and saw the two of US,
I, mean, I was so focused.
I had goals, I mean,
I was preaching in front
of 25-30,000 people at once!
I mean, I did it!
Now, Billy, on the other hand,
if it was left up to him,
he, he would have been content
to be your local pastor.
Adio: This is torrey Johnson coming to you from
"songs in the night,"
saying, may the good lord
always shine down on you.
[Phone ringing]
Ruth: Hello?
Ruth: Mr. Johnson? Yes,
of course we know who you are.
Ah, this is Ruth, his wife.
Ah, yes, he is!
Hold on just one moment, sir.
It's torrey Johnson!
Yeah!
Billy: And this is Billy Graham,
signing off from
"songs in the night,"
wishin' all of you loyal
listeners a terrific evenin',
and may god bless you always.
[Whispering] Goodnight, Ruth.
[Instrumental music]
Ruth: Oh, nice.
That was a great one.
Billy: Now I see why they call
it, "the house that Ruth built."
Let's get some of that
fresh lemonade you made.Ruth: All right.
[Song on radio]
George Beverly shea:
♪ almost pursuaded, ♪
♪ harvest is past,
almost pursuaded... ♪
Billy: Oh, please, allow me.
Ruth: Thank you.
♪ Doom comes at last
almost cannot avail, almost is but to fail... ♪♪
Billy: See, I need someone like
him for, "songs in the night."
Ruth: Well, why not him?
He's the best baritone
in the country, where is he?
Billy: Moody Bible institute
in Chicago.
And why would he wanna be
on my little radio show?
Ruth: Well, maybe you just need
to get your foot in the door,
Mr. Fuller brush salesman.
Radio: This is
George Beverly shea,
wishing you and yours a happy and peaceful afternoon.
[Bluegrass music]
Secretary: May I help you,
sir?
Billy: Yes, I'm here
to see Mr. Shea.
Secretary: I don't see
any appointments for him
at this hour.
Billy: I realize that, but I
drove all the way up here
from western Springs
just to see him.
Secretary: I'm sorry sir,
but he is busy.
Would you like to make
a proper appointment?
Billy: How 'bout right now?
Secretary: Sir! You,
you can't go in there!
Billy: Mr. Shea, my name is
Billy Graham, and I am here to,
to be honest, sir,
you could change my life.
George Beverly shea:
Well, it'd be a shame
to ruin such a spiffy
pair of shoes, come on in.
Billy: Thank you, sir.
Billy: Now, Mr. Shea, as I said,
my name is Billy Graham,
and I have a very little
radio show...
♪ ...and that thou bidst me
come to thee, ♪
♪ oh lamb of god,
I come, I come ♪♪
[Applause]
Billy: To all our loyal
listeners,
that was Mr. George
Beverly shea,
coming to you live, from western
Springs baptist church.
[Applause]
Torrey johnston: I'm puttin'
together a new outreach called,
"youth for Christ,"
and what I want is someone
who can preach the gospel
and invite people to Christ.
And not a seasoned pro,
but a, an up and comer.
Someone whose career
I can foster and grow,
and watch blossom.
Who I want, is you,
Billy Graham.
Billy: I don't know
what to say.
Ruth: The lord speaks
in strange ways.
Billy: Apparently.
Torrey johnston: You're gonna
need a team, have you got one?
Billy: Well, I got, ah,
t.W. And Grady Wilson,
men I've known since
high school.
I trust them like brothers.
Ruth: And he's got
George shea.
Torrey johnston: I think i'm
gonna send Chuck up there
with ya.
Billy: Chuck?
Torrey johnston: Chuck
Templeton.
Billy: Chuck...
Charles Templeton?
Torrey johnston: Chuck-
Charles Templeton.
Billy: Torrey, I'm just
a small time preacher.
Charles Templeton's big time.
Old Templeton: "Charles
Templeton is big time!"
[Laughing]
Old Templeton: They poured in
like floodwaters to see me.
I mean, I was the juice!
I spoke and they listened,
enraptured!
I mean, I could hold them
in the palm of my hand.
I could close my fist
around them,
and not let them go until
I led them to Jesus...
Young Templeton: Put
your faith in him.
He will not disappoint
the trusting heart.
The answer to man's dilemma
is found in Jesus.
[Applause]
Old Templeton: We traveled
together, we preached
together.
Was impossible not to like Billy... ha-ha-ha... yes.
Young Templeton: Since
this war has ended,
people all over the world have
been searching for answers.
The innocence of our time
has passed.
The simple life that america
has known is gone for-ever.
The simple answers have
given way to much more
complex questions.
However, let it be known tonight
that the ultimate answer
has not changed.
[Applause]
Old Templeton: Like a leaf
on the wind.
Billy: For the Bible says,
"for god so loved the world,
he gave his only
begotten son,
that whosoever
believeth in him,
should not perish,
but have everlasting life."
Billy: And this is not only your great hope,
but this is your salvation. It is your answer to life.
[Instrumental music]
Billy on radio: The holy spirit is dealing with your hearts.
You come... you give
your life to Christ.
[Applause]
Billy on radio: Come!
Billy on radio: Come down!
[Applause]
[Newsreel playing]
Newscaster: Today,
in the waning weeks
of the European war,
the world sees proof
of acts of savagery,
unparalleled in history.
The supreme allies
commander himself
views the Nazi murder mills
with his generals.
Ld Templeton: I let Europe nd the aftermath of the war wash over me.
But Billy, Billy's faith was
unshaken by what he saw.
How could that be?
And then we came back.
Billy: Ruth, I'm home!
I brought Chuck back
for dinner!
Ruth: I'm in your office.
Billy: Hi.
Ruth: I missed you.
Hello, Chuck.
Young Templeton:
Hello, Ruth.
Billy: So, what were you
doin' up there?
Ruth: Oh, just measurin'
for new curtains.
Billy: Oh honey, I don't need
any new curtains.
Ruth: Well, they're not
for you.
Billy: Who are they for?
This is my office.
Ruth: Well, not for long.
Billy: Honey, I have to have
a place to do my work.
Ruth: They're for
the nursery.
Billy: Well, I need a place
to write, and do my sermons,
and...
Billy: Nursery?Ruth: Mm-hm.
Billy: Nursery, like for plants?
Ruth: For babies.Billy: For baby plants?
Young Templeton: I think what
she's tryin' to tell you
is that you're going to be
a father... knucklehead.
Billy: You mean...?
Oh, oh... I'm sorry, sorry.
Ruth: Come and meet
your daughter.
Marjorie: Go on, hold her.
[Baby crying]
Billy: That is just the cutest
little ficus I've ever seen.
That's my daughter.
That's my daughter!
Young Templeton:
Congratulations, Billy,
she's perfect.
Billy: She's perfectly
wonderful.
[Instrumental music]
Old Templeton: How can there
be a god in this evil world?
You know, I had
profound doubts,
and I let my doubts
guide me to questions
that I could not answer.
Reporter: Go on... please.
Old Templeton: Dr. Reilly
was the president
of Northwestern Bible college.
He says, to Billy, "I'm an
old man, and I'm dying,
and I want you to take over
as president of my college."
Billy Graham, I mean,
president of a college.
Amazing!
I mean, he had
a bachelor's degree
from wheaton college
in anthropology.
I mean, that's it.
All of a sudden, there he is,
the youngest college president
in the United States.
[Phone ringing]
Laverne: Office of
the president.
Can you hold, please?
Mr. Wilson, can you field this?
It's them again.
T.w.: T.W.
Yes, mighty interested.
I'll, I'll get back to you
by close of business.
Thank you.
Billy: Is that Los Angeles?
T.w: It's their third call.
Laverne: Here's your
messages, Mr. President,
and your magazine.
Billy: Thank you, Laverne.
Tell Robert hello.
How much they have to offer?
T.w.: Two-thousand
for the entire event,
but I told them we need
at least 10,000.
Billy: We need 25,000.
T.w.: 25,000?
Billy: What about Charles?
Is he on board?
T.w.: No.
Billy: Then to do it right,
we need $25,000.
Reporter: Tell US
about the scandal,
Billy Graham and the picture
holding the sack of money.
Old Templeton: Oh, that.
In those days, the, ah,
the final offering in churches,
and tents, and halls-
I mean, they used to call it
the "love offering."
It would go to cover
the evangelists' expenses
and, and go on
to the next campaign.
And anyway, some ambitious
reporter takes a picture
of Billy with the money.
It was nonsense.
I mean, Billy made sure
that he was accountable
for every penny collected.
He was completely transparent.
One day, he said, "now boys, I,
I want you to go to your rooms,
and I want you write down
the things
that can cause the downfall
of an evangelist."
They all had the same items.
And Billy said, "alright fellas,
these are the rules:
From now on, no man
is to be in a room
alone with a woman
other than his wife."
He said, "we're not even
going to let there be
a breath of scandal
in this ministry."
I mean, Billy Graham is the most
scrupulously honest person
that I have ever met.
And when I needed a friend,
he was always there.
Young Templeton:
Bill, how can anyone
take the Bible as literal
word of god?
Billy: What do you mean?
Young Templeton: Jonah
and the whale.
Do you think that a whale
actually swallowed a man
and spat him out?
Or, or, or that god made
the sun stand still in the sky.
Do you honestly believe that
the earth stopped revolving?
Where is the hard science
to back these stories up?
And if the Bible is not true
in each and every case,
then doesn't that cast doubt
on all of it?
Billy: Charles, it's the word
of god.
Young Templeton: But what if
it's wrong, Billy?
Nothing more than feeble stories
written by men like you and me,
attempting to answer
the great questions of life.
If it's wrong, then what
about the rest?
Old Templeton: He went down
his path...
I went down another.
Young Templeton:
Good evening, everyone.
Thank you so much
for coming out tonight.
As I look out, I see a lot
of familiar faces.
I've known some of you since
you came into this world.
I have seen some of you
through times, good,
and through times not so good.
And it has been my honor,
my deepest honor,
to serve you.
But I am here
with heavy heart.
In me, you put your trust
for spiritual guidance,
and I realize the responsibility
and the honor of this.
I realize it to the center
of my core.
And so, it pains me,
but I must confess this.
I find that I can no longer
accept many of the tenets,
the fundamental tenets,
of the Christian faith.
I see now that there are
other truths-
that there are other paths,
other perspectives,
other ways.
So, to continue on this journey
toward greater understanding,
toward an ever-widening
search for truth,
I've accepted a position
at Princeton university.
[Instrumental music]
Young Templeton: And this means
that I am leaving this ministry.
Billy: Charles Templeton
is my best friend,
and there is nothing
dishonest in that man.
And, because of a crisis
of his faith,
he felt a moral imperative
to resign from his positions
to no longer preach that
which he could no longer
fully believe.
And that is not hypocrisy,
that is integrity.
And, I will not stand
with anyone
who will denounce my friend.
Instead, let US pray for him.
[Instrumental music]
[Knocking on door]
Laverne: Mr. Graham?
Mr. Graham?
Billy: Oh, I'm sorry, Laverne.
Laverne: Well, you've
been confirmed
at the forest home conference.
Billy: Forest home?
Laverne: You'll be
the youngest college
president speaking there.
It's very interesting...
Dr's Evan and Hamilton,
from Oxford will be there.
And so will your friend,
Charles Templeton.
Billy: Thank you, Laverne.
[Instrumental music]
Mrs. Meirs: Billy, how wonderful
to see you.
Billy: And you, Mrs. Meirs.
Ah, these are for you.
Mrs. Meirs: Always thoughtful.
Come inside, please.
I think you know Dr. Bob.
Dr. Bob Evans: Billy, so glad
you could make it.
Billy: I've heard such
great things, sir.
Mrs. Meirs: Charles!
Young Templeton: Thank you
so much for having US
to your home.
You remember my wife, Connie.
Bob, how are you?
You know, I, I just finished
reading your dissertation
on the Neo-orthodoxy
and the barth comparative study,
and I have to tell you,
it is brilliant work.
Dr. Bob Evans: Well,
thank you, Charles.
I'm afraid it probably created
more questions than it answered.
Young Templeton: Excuse me.Billy: Chuck, it's good
to see ya.
Young Templeton: Billy,
it's good to see you too.
Tell me, are you still
speaking for god?
Billy: Well, god speaks
for himself, Charles.
I just testify about what
the word has meant for me.
Young Templeton: Ha, ha, ha...
Billy, Billy.
The world has grown
so much more complex,
just in the last fifty years.
When people seeking the truth
can no longer accept
the simple rhetoric
that you were raised with
and preach with.
When are you going
to get that?
That old time religion,
it's not good enough for me.
And it's not good enough
for you either, Billy.
Connie: Charles.
Mrs. Meirs: Outspoken young man,
god bless his heart.
Young Templeton: No, no, no
Connie, actually,
I'm actually, I'm doing you
a big favor.
You see, people no longer
accept the Bible as being
divinely inspired.
There are too many
inconsistencies,
lapses, lacunae.
How could any of US presume
that a document written by men
is the sacrosanct,
inalienable word of god?
It is a fairy tale.
Billy: Well, 2.000 years ago,
the Bible prophesied
that god would gather his chosen
people from the four corners,
and reunite them in
their homeland, and...
Young Templeton: God didn't
create the state of Israel...
Man did.
The u.N. Did, after
six-million Jews,
god's own "chosen people,"
were burned and gassed
in the ovens of Hitler.
Six million people, Billy.
All praying to their
god to be spared,
and not one prayer answered.
Is that your loving god?
Can you find his face in
the ovens in Auschwitz, Billy?
Or the fire storms of Nagasaki,
or the bombs of dresden?
I'm asking you, how could
a loving god have done that?
Billy: Charles, god didn't
do that.
Man did...
Young Templeton: Well then,
he permitted it, didn't he?
He stood by and you're
out there, Billy.
You're out there preaching
the "good news."
What good news?
Billy: The good news that
god so loved the world
that he gave his only...
Young Templeton: Billy, Billy.
I believe that Jesus is
the most perfect moral being
in the history of the world.
I believe that Jesus is
the greatest teacher
in the history of western
civilization,
and I believe that Jesus
is the purest example
of all that is good
in mankind,
and, and I do not believe
that he is the son of god.
He's the son of a man.
I feel sorry for you, Billy.
What you call faith,
it is the death of intellect.
Bob Evans: Billy, you all right?
Billy: Yeah, yeah, thanks.
Morrow: Listen to me, Billy.
You're gettin'
all caught up in,
in man's prideful need to be
right about these things.
Let me ask you
a question, honey.
What is your "callin'?"
Is it to go out and prove
every word in the Bible,
or is it, is it to open people's
hearts and minds to the love,
and healing power of our lord
Jesus Christ?
Listen to your heart, Billy.
Billy: Maybe I'm just
not cut out for this.
Morrow: God is with you,
Billy frank,
and will never leave you
and will never forsake you.
[Instrumental music]
Billy: God, if you didn't
want me to preach,
why did you let me believe?
And if you want me to believe,
why can't you just give me
some proof?
There are questions in this book
that I just can't answer.
So, give me something!
Anything!
Where are you?
[Instrumental music]
Morrow: Billy, you will
hear his voice again.
Catherine singing:
♪ to rid my soul... ♪
Billy: I hear you, lord.
Frank: Billy, you will
hear his voice again.
Dr. Ham: Sweet Jesus,
forgive their souls
and heal our hearts...
Billy: I hear you... Dr. Minder: It's about serving the one who died for you.
Billy: I hear you, lord... Darryl: Can you help me preacher? Morrow: Listen to your heart.
Billy: I hear you, lord! Ruth: I believe.
K: On this day in Charlotte, e asking god to Grant his nation,
a voice for the gospel, to the ends of the earth.
By faith, we ask this in the name of Jesus, amen.
Billy: I hear you, lord.
It's by faith.
And from this moment forward,
I accept this work
as your infallible word.
By faith, because that is
what the Bible says.
By faith!
Thank you, lord.
Thank you...Thank you!
[Instrumental music]
Billy: I'm back.
Daughter: Daddy!
Billy: Hey, come here.
How are you?
Ruth: Hi. Billy: Hi.
Billy: I love you.
T.w.: Los Angeles called
back...
They raised the 25,000.
What do I tell them?
All right.
[Instrumental music]
Billy: I have a friend,
a dear friend,
who told me Jesus was a man,
nothing but a man.
Well, he was a man,
he was human.
Now, he was not a white man,
and he was not a black man.
He came from that part
of the world,
which touches Europe,
and Africa, and Asia.
And he probably had
a brown skin.
And christianity is not
a white man's religion.
And you don't let anybody tell
ya that it's white or black.
So who is this strange man who
marches his way across history?
Who can explain him?
There's never been anyone else
like him.
My friend, who is an atheist,
will tell ya that.
He only had a ministry
of three years,
and yet 2.000 years later,
millions upon millions,
on every continent, bow down
and worship him.
Why?
How is this possible?
Because he was made
to redeem US.
He went up onto that cross
And on that cross, he touched
the finger of god in one hand,
and in the other hand,
he reached out,
and he took your hand.
And in that moment,
on the cross,
he reconciled god and man.
And, I'm asking you tonight,
to commit your life to him.
It's tough, it's hard,
and there are those
who will mock you for it,
but there is a joy
and a satisfaction
in living that kind of life,
in following him,
a Serenity that fills
the emptiness in your hearts.
And once you have it,
you know where you are going,
and you know where
you have come from,
and you know what life
is all about,
and you know why
you're here,
and where you are going
when you die.
Now, I am going to ask you
to get out of your seat,
wherever you are,
and stand in front
of this platform,
and say, "by coming,
I know that I am a sinner.
I want to receive god
into my heart.
I want my sins forgiven.
I want to know that
I am going to heaven.
And I want a new life,
and I want it to begin
right here.
And I want it to begin
right now."
And you know what?
It can.
I don't care if you are
a movie star,
or the biggest drunk walkin'
the streets of Los Angeles.
God is waiting for you
right now.
Come down...
Come down and give
your life to Christ.
[Applause]
[Instrumental music]
♪ My steps were wandering,
my lips were hungering, ♪
♪ my heart was thundering
for something more ♪
♪ than all those things ♪
♪ my words were crying out,
my faith was darkened out ♪
♪ my life was lost without
this one amazing love ♪
♪ washing over me like rain,
conquering the fear and pain ♪
♪ my broken path
was not in vain, ♪
♪ glory hallelujah,
glory hallelujah, ♪
[Instrumental music]
♪ Washing over me like rain,
taking all the fear and pain ♪
♪ my broken path
was not in vain, ♪
♪ glory hallelujah,
glory hallelujah, ♪
♪ I lift my blinded eyes
to where those souls denied ♪
♪ and saw the one who died
for one amazing love ♪
♪ hallelujah, hallelujah,
hallelujah ♪
♪ this one amazing love,
one amazing love, ♪
♪ hallelujah, hallelujah,
hallelujah, hallelujah, ♪
♪ just one amazing love
hallelujah, hallelujah ♪
♪ this one amazing love ♪♪
♪ ...and when he comes
as he will come ♪
♪ with quiet eyes aglow, ♪
♪ I'll understand that
he's the man ♪
♪ I prayed for long ago ♪
♪ dear god, I prayed for love,
he gave me you ♪♪