[music playing]
Kick his ass.
[thrashing]
Come on, punk.
You wanna join us,
you gotta jump in.
Ugh.
Aw.
[whip sounds]
[guns loading]
[fighting]
You better fucking get up.
Come on.
Get up, man.
Come on you wimp.
[ominous music]
My collection appreciates
your business.
[ominous music]
[fighting ]
[loading guns]
[gun shots]
[police sirens]
[music playing]
[horn honks]
[glass shattering]
[police sirens]
[gun shots]
[explosion]
[police sirens]
Where were you?
Fuck all you.
[explosion]
I guess we were at
the wrong location.
[police radio chatter]
[music playing]
[crickets chirping]
Hey, what is this?
Are you playing games?
Turn out the lights.
What are you try
to intimidate me?
Is that it?
I thought we were going
around with each other.
Shit, Ricardo, after
six months you'd
think you trust me by now.
This is bullshit.
Turn out the lights.
(YELLING) I said, turn
out the God damn lights.
I'm warning you.
I said, I am not fucking around.
I said, turn them off.
You cramped my ride.
You don't go smashing
my lights out.
Why the hell did you
have them on, asshole?
I was staking you out, bitch.
Shit, Ricardo, you
were just dicking
me around to try to scare me.
I said, don't screw me.
Baby, I'd rather screw
a broken window, OK?
RICARDO: Who's the muscle?
It's my insurance policy.
You got the cash?
You think I'm here
for the company?
Then, let's have a look.
Cash for stash, asshole.
You're going to pay
for the lights, bitch.
Brand new ride, some
psycho, gun-happy bitch
comes in and does
a Hank Aaron on it.
That's how I know
you ain't a cop.
You too God damn crazy.
[crickets chirping]
Holy shit, Ricardo.
What'd you do?
Buy Colombia?
Let's just say, Santa Claus
has definitely come to town.
Where the hell did
you get all this stuff?
You have a new
collection, don't you?
Who is it?
What are we
playing 20 questions?
I ain't gonna tell you shit.
Kiss my ass.
Who's my connection, please.
Now, where's the green?
I said, the green, not the pink.
What we gonna do, get a peak?
Take a nice, long stare.
Asshole, you're under arrest.
Shit.
Freeze, goon.
Aw, man.
These streets are
definitely not safe anymore.
Move it.
Down.
Spread em.
OK, asshole.
Next to your buddy.
[struggling]
She's kicking your boys ass.
Nice.
Enjoy the show?
Oh, yeah.
So what's happening?
Why didn't you wait for
the sale to go down?
Look at the stuff.
It is bigger than any sale.
Where'd you get that
shit Ricardo, huh?
Who you working for?
Yeah, who's your connection?
Kiss my ass.
Come on, speak to me, asshole.
It's police brutality, bitch.
Owh.
Tony Casanova.
GILS: Zebra 5 for back-up.
Yeah, that's a 10-4 on Casanova.
GILS: Tell Weston to be careful.
I'll let her know.
GILS: Good work, guys.
All right.
I just off the horn with Gils.
He busted this guy,
Casanova, a few years ago.
He says the guy is a real
womanizer, a sex fiend.
He has six different
counts of rape against him.
The guy's an easy hook.
And I guess I'm
the bait, right?
[music playing]
You think he's our rapist?
If he rapes her
he's our rapist.
[laughter]
I guess so.
[music playing]
Oh, you like it rough.
You know something?
She too said, I love you when
you like it rough, darling.
[spanish]
CASANOVA: Did you know that?
Tell me about her.
She used to love me.
Now, you just get on your knees.
(YELLING) Get on your knees.
What else you gonna
do with that scarf?
CASANOVA: I'm gonna to show
you about a real man, darling.
I love a man in control.
Can you believe this shit?
You know, she
said she loved me.
She always said she love me.
Can believe this
douche bag slut?
Look at her.
Would you believe I
asked her out two times
and both times she
turned me down?
She brushed me right off.
Yeah, me too.
Made me feel like
shit, the bitch.
[moan]
[music playing]
Come up for air.
Woah.
Now, this is romance.
I think she's
enjoying herself.
I'll say.
Don't you--
[laughs]
Aw, shit.
You make any
noise, you scream,
I'm gonna make you bleed.
I'm gonna cut you.
You understand me?
Oh, Jesucristo.
You like this?
No, no, no, no, no.
Do you want me?
Tell me you want me.
I want you now.
Come in now.
[burp]
Oh, God.
Shut up.
Say it again.
WESTON: I love you.
I want you.
[moans] I love you.
I want you now.
Son of a bitch.
I thought she
was gonna bang him.
What are you crazy?
What are you doing?
Where the hell were you?
Stupid fucking bitch.
[laughs]
[music playing]
I love you.
[laughs]
[screaming]
[music playing]
[gun shots]
Get on the radio.
Get us some backup.
Did you hear me?
(YELLING) Did you hear me?
Shit.
[gun shots]
[music playing]
Son of a bitch.
[gun shots]
This is one Johnson 99.
Officer down.
Sniper on the roof,
backup requested.
Fifth and Cedar.
Cover me.
Are you going to cover me?
[gun shots]
[music playing]
[screaming]
[laughter]
[inaudible]
I want you.
I'm up here.
[gun shots]
(YELLING) Help me.
MAN: Come on.
HOSTAGE: Don't hurt me.
I won't hurt you.
Don't hurt me.
Don't-- don't please, please.
I won't hurt you.
I love you.
[laughter]
MAN: Come on, blue.
I'm not stupid.
I can smell ya.
Come on, fool, show yourself.
I'll kill a boo, I swear.
I swear my mother's
brain she's dead.
Dead if you don't
let me out of here.
Isn't she beautiful, blue?
Aw, isn't she beautiful?
I love this woman.
She got time, baby.
[mwah] Blue, where you at?
I want you now.
I know where you go, blue.
Your move.
[laughs]
[ugh]
[music playing]
Hey, hold on.
Malcolm.
[coughs]
[music playing]
MALCOLM: Damn it, those three
have gone too far this time.
And why aren't they dead yet?
DANTE: Listen, Malcolm.
I don't care how much you
want these people dead.
I can't just go out there and
kill three police officers.
It has to be done right
and that takes time.
Let me tell you something,
my friend, I don't pay you
and others like you
to take your time.
DANTE: You know, you have a
bigger problem down in Mexico
with Cesar.
He wants his million
dollars, and he's had
it with your sniper attacks.
My business with
Cesar can wait.
What's most important
to me is the revenge
of my brother's death.
DANTE: I know that, but I don't
think you understand that Cesar
has tipped off the DEA,
and they are now planning
a raid on the nightclub.
I think we should
deal with that first.
Maybe the three police
officers could be caught
in the crossfire of the raid.
MALCOLM: Fine.
But you listen to
me, detective Dante.
You make it happen
any way you want,
because if it doesn't happen,
I promise you, my friend,
I will personally see that
something happens to you.
[music playing]
[phone ringing]
Thank you.
[typewriter clicks]
Dante, DEA
[phone ringing]
STARK: I believe these
three will make the best
unit for your operation.
[phone ringing]
DANTE: These are my choices.
What do you want
a suicide mission?
Sloan, Cuff and
Weston have recently
been transferred
to this department
with active suspension papers.
I mean, there-- there's a
reason why the LAPD took
their guns out of their hands.
Why those three?
The DEA has gone
over your files.
My office feels that these
three individuals are
the best people for the job.
The DEA would appreciate
your cooperation.
Cooperation?
What the hell do
you want to know?
What do you know about
these people personally?
How all three graduated
from the top of their class
at the Academy.
They all went to
school together.
They all grew up in
the same neighborhood.
And Billy Sloan, he is
the most recent addition
to the precinct.
Sloan is a weapons
and explosives
expert, served a
tour in the Marines,
saw a battle, decorated.
He flew helicopter missions
to recover POWs, not married,
no family, expert marksman.
Cuff is an expert in all areas
of martial arts, karate, judo,
state kickboxing champion.
Most of his early years work
centered around gang activity.
The only family he
had was a younger
brother who was killed
in a drive-by shooting
two years ago.
Ali Weston graduated law school
before entering the Academy,
father was a cop.
She wanted to be a cop.
Father died in the line
of duty when she was 15.
The mother is in some
hospital on life support.
Other than her two visits
a week to the hospital,
she buries herself in work.
[typewriter clicking]
These three have had
the most active files
since they left the Academy.
These three I feel the
worse for your operation.
Since joining the
force, I mean, they've
had a following of dead bodies
everywhere they've gone.
Collectively, they've lost two
partners in the line of duty
and seven injured.
Thanks for your
recommendation, Captain Stark.
[typewriter clicking]
[music playing]
[telephone ringing]
Sit down, Mr. Cuff.
You have been chosen
as a surveillance
unit regarding a major drug
operation in this city.
The purpose of
your unit has been
based on your past records,
your friendship, and the fact
that this department has
found it virtually impossible
to assign any of you a partner.
So we've decided to let you
renegades work together.
Sit down Mr. Sloan.
I don't need this shit.
What shit is that?
SLOAN: This renegade shit,
this finding me a partner shit.
If you got an
assignment assign it,
but don't give me this shit.
Nobody else created
this shit, Mr. Sloan.
Sit down.
Nobody else in
the squad has more
partner casualties than you with
the exception of miss Weston.
Miss.
The department
issued you a gun.
You pulled the trigger.
Now, whether you like it or
not, this is the last stop.
Either you play by my rules
or you don't play at all.
It's up to you.
[phone ringing]
What's the matter
with you, huh?
You never tell these assholes
what you're thinking.
You know better than that.
You're right, Tommy.
You're always right.
Well, when you're
right, you're right.
And when you're
wrong, you're wrong.
Right?
What's it been, two years?
Two years.
Feels like two days.
Some things never change.
And some things do.
How's your wife, Tommy?
Great.
The only thing that's
missing is a couple of dogs
and a white picket fence.
How's your husband?
I'm not married.
Oh, that's too bad.
I'm sorry.
I'm not.
I missed you guys.
[chuckles]
Oh, boy.
What are we going to do, huh?
They got me stuck
behind a desk.
I'm going to go crazy if
I don't see some action.
I say we take it.
Can you take it, councilor?
I think we found our leader.
All right, let's get started.
OK, there'll be no
backup unit on this team.
That would only put
you in jeopardy.
Our sources inform us that the
shipment is leaving the country
in the next 24 hours.
Starting now that
you're on your own.
How you do this
is your business.
Dismissed.
[ominous music playing]
So you think they're
going to make it?
[music playing]
Good evening, ladies.
WOMAN: Wait 'til you
guys see this place.
It's a real trip.
Hello, ladies.
How are you?
I'm doing great.
Step right in.
Have a beautiful time.
- Hey, what's up?
- Nothing's up.
Just relax.
[music playing]
CUFF: Don't let it get
away from you, huh?
VALET: I'll try not to you.
CUFF: Busy night, huh?
VALET: Yeah, sure is.
CUFF: Here's a little
donation for the Bouncer's
Club of America.
LOUDMOUTH: Hey, there's
a line back here.
Hey man, I've been waiting two
hours to get in this place.
I'm going to give you a three
count to get your hand off me.
1, 2.
[fighting]
[inaudible]
WOMAN: Who was that guy?
[music playing]
Thanks for the compliment,
but, uh, I prefer blondes.
[music playing]
So do I. Your loss.
You still have a
thing for Billy, huh?
You had me, but you want him.
Go forward, Tommy.
Life moves forward.
OK, how many ducks?
Two at the bar.
Woman on the rafter,
one on the left.
[ominous music playing]
All right.
Let's rock and roll.
[ominous music playing]
All right.
That's enough.
We're moving.
Come on, move.
Come on, let's go.
Go.
[music playing]
[gun shots]
Come on, move.
[music playing]
[gun shots]
RADIO: Everyone stay sharp.
We've got badges in the house.
[gun shots]
[screaming]
Greencall, you copy?
Yeah, what's up?
RADIO: Undercover LAPD coming
out the front, captain.
[screaming]
[gun shots]
[music playing]
[screaming]
MAN: There goes the
dealer with the shit.
Hey, woah, woah, take it.
It's yours, man.
It's yours.
[gun shots]
[music playing]
[police sirens]
RADIO DISPATCH:
[inaudible] for a 128.
I don't appreciate being woken
up in the middle of the night.
My wife doesn't appreciate it.
She's a suspicious
woman as it is.
And I don't need shit from her.
I don't need shit
from you three.
Internal Affairs 7:00
AM tomorrow morning.
Stone and Dante want to ask
you three a few questions.
And don't be late, please.
Just a quiet place,
just the place to be.
What are you working at?
Get out of-- get out of my face.
[phone ringing]
Aw, fuck.
Internal Affairs, huh?
SLOAN: Yeah, that's
the least of it, pal.
So how many times you
call her in one night?
What?
You have baller, right?
What-- what-- what--
what is this, huh?
Hey, man, the chips are down.
I'm gonna a leak.
You OK?
(YELLING) Hey.
SLOAN: I'm good tom, tom.
Yeah, I don't blame him.
What am I getting
with this shit?
What am I getting from you?
What-- what--
Nothing, man.
Nothing.
Hey.
[music playing]
RADIO: What police
officials have described
as a tragic event has claimed
the lives of a dozen people
at club X in the
trendy warehouse
district of the city tonight.
Again, raising questions over
the use of excessive force
by members of the LAPD.
Tommy Cuff, Billy
Sloan, and Ali Weston
were officers
involved in what is
rapidly being described as
the massacre of the innocents.
Nine innocent patrons
of the club X nightclub
were gunned down
during the crossfire.
Top level officials are
claiming that the officers
were not on duty and were
acting on their own accord.
The three officers
have been suspended
pending an investigation.
Internal Affairs refuses
to comment on who
will be leading the inquiry.
What is this shit, huh?
Is this legal?
Anything's legal when you're
dealing with the people who
make the rules.
So what are we going to do?
Issue a statement before this
looks any God damn worse?
I don't know.
I really don't know
what to advise.
All that law school and
you're crapping out on us?
Hey, it's a chess game.
And we shouldn't
make a move until we
know who we're playing with.
So what, we wait?
Yeah.
[music playing]
WESTON: Don't Look at him.
Don't even look at him.
I'm not doing anything.
Anybody catch
the news tonight?
BAR CROWD: Yeah.
Yeah.
LARRY: Is today February 14th?
Hey, Tommy, is
today February 14th?
Come on.
You're not going to answer me?
I'm asking you a question.
Is today February 14th?
Don't answer him.
LARRY: Tommy Cuff, is
today February 14th?
Don't answer him.
What'd you like
in the 3rd one?
LARRY: Hey, Tommy, I'm
asking you a question.
Shove you're gold
bat up your ass, Larry.
SLOAN: There we go.
WESTON: That's great.
Batter up.
That will aid in
avoiding conflict.
Tough guy.
Cobody A cocktail
for my enemies.
We're celebrating tonight.
Keep the change.
[music playing]
Let it go.
Come on, let's get out of here.
OK, look, I just want to
thank your brother, Eric.
OK, really.
LARRY: Cheers, Tommy.
Larry, I really don't
want a drink from you.
Thanks anyway.
What's the matter?
Not celebrating Valentine's
Day with us after that massacre
you pulled?
I feel like Al
Capone still lives.
How many kids you make
orphans, huh folks?
Once an asshole,
always an asshole, Larry.
Tommy Cuff and the guy
that could shoot straight.
[gun noises]
Hey, pal.
Next time you start
your car, think twice.
You're another one, Sloan.
You fucking kook lover.
Tommy.
Huh.
My old man always said, there's
no room for slacks in blue.
[music playing]
[bar chatter]
LARRY: Fuck off you
mother fucking--
WESTON: Come on Larry.
CUFF: Fuck this asshole.
LARRY: Fuck you though.
SLOAN: What are
you gonna do, huh?
Oh.
Yeah, come on Larry, get him.
Yes, Larry.
BAR CROWD: Come on.
Don't let him get
away with it, man.
Larry, come on, man.
What's going on?
Stand up.
Stand up, man.
[fighting]
Fucking jerk.
Fuck off.
Hey, dickhead,
we're all cops here.
You really think you're
doing some work here, huh?
Shut up.
If you want to keep your job,
you'll a release officer Cuff,
go outside, get in your
car, and drive away.
OK?
Yes sir.
And I don't want to
see one scratch on him.
Yes, sir.
[music playing]
What was that,
our guardian angel?
Or the devil in disguise.
[music playing]
I just can't do this anymore.
Mr. Mitchell, we'll be
talking to each one of you
individually.
If I were you, I'd
clear your schedules
for the rest of the day.
Sloan, you're up.
[typewriter clicking]
William Sloan, James
D. Mitchell, FBI.
Your full name is Will
Marcelow, is that correct?
William Robert Sloan.
Can I call you Bill?
Can I call you Jim?
Tell us what happened, Bill?
Do you know how many
people got killed last night?
I've seen a lot of
people get killed.
So you mean you don't know.
Is that it, Sloan?
I've seen a lot
of people killed.
You've served in
the military, correct?
Navy seals.
Would you consider
yourself a trained assassin?
I did what my
country asked me to do.
You do consider
this your country?
Lately?
What do you mean, what
are you referring to?
The press being told that we
acted on our own last night.
No statement was
released from this office.
Well, sometimes
branches of government
have been known to do their
own thing to ensure the peace.
- We did get the bad guys.
- And some good ones.
CUFF: I guarantee you
that the bullets that
killed all those people all came
from called bags and security.
What happened to the money?
What money
$100 thousand.
I stuffed it down my bra.
Bullets were flying
every which fucking way.
I didn't see any money.
[music playing]
STONE: Officer Cuff,
it says in your report
you fought with a club
patron before entering.
CUFF: Yeah.
Well, this guy was
mouthing off in line,
and since I was undercover,
I thought it would
be appropriate to bust his ass.
Now, what does this
got to do with what
happened inside club X?
SLOAN: No, for the third
time, I'll telling you.
I heard small arms fire, which
sounded like 9 millimeter
semi-autos going off.
I turned and fired.
STONE: I'm running a check on
his military records right now.
I need a psych profile.
Right.
Sloan, William Robert.
Did you shoot the two officers?
I've seen a lot
of people killed.
What did you see last night?
There was a car crash.
CUFF: I was driving the car.
SLOAN: Chemicals that
were transporting
exploded in the car.
WESTON: The cars were on fire.
I remember people screaming.
Then, I heard shots.
Then, I heard shots
You're all
officially suspended
until this investigation
is concluded.
You have to undergo
psychological testing
and be available at all
times for questioning.
12 innocent people
have been killed.
An undercover DEA agent is dead.
$100,000 in government
funds are missing.
And two uniformed patrol
officers answering
a disturbance are also dead.
Until we get this
story straight,
one version, none of you
is to talk to the press
or any other outside agency.
To do so would incur
a suspicion of guilt.
And guilt in this
case, in this state,
could get you the gas chamber.
You're dismissed.
Any idea who could
have leaked to the press
about being their
being on their own.
How the hell do I know?
You know how the press is.
Hm.
[music playing]
[screaming]
What did you tell them?
Nothing.
I didn't remember anything.
Dead is dead.
Half the time I don't
even realize when I pulled
the trigger and when I don't.
I only remember the
fire burning, that's it.
What are you two gonna do?
I don't think we've got
much of a choice, Billy.
Just sit tight and
wait out the storm.
Ali, suspension is one
thing, but without pay.
Well, at least you
got the security gig.
You know, that's something.
Yeah, right.
Something.
Shit, what day is today?
Thursday.
I gotta go see my mother.
If you need anything call me.
Listen, I really
think that the best
thing is not to talk to anyone.
See you.
What a waste.
So what happened to you?
Who knows.
Take it easy with
that drink, Billy.
Listen, I'm going to go
and do some working out.
You want to come along?
[chuckle] No, man.
I got to go wherever the hell
it is I work, because, Tommy, I
need something.
Need A?
Few bucks?
Fuck no.
If you need some money,
I got some extra cash.
No.
Get out of here.
Look, Billy, come on.
Billy.
You all right?
Fine.
CUFF: You sure?
Life is fine.
CUFF: Call you later.
Hey, come by, huh?
Bring a little take out.
I got to talk.
[music playing]
Hey, Maddie.
This is for you.
Put the rest on the house, huh.
Please?
[music playing]
[baby crying]
And in the massacre
of innocence case,
police officials are
refusing to comment
on the actions of officers
Thomas Cuff, William
Sloan, and Allison Weston.
But on the other hand, the
victims' families and friends
are speaking out loud and clear.
She was just 17, I mean, she was
here celebrating her birthday,
and her friends
brought her down.
She didn't have
to die like this.
These cops have got to pay.
They can't just go around
shooting every damn time
they get a chance.
She was just 17.
All my husband ever
wanted to be was a cop.
Precinct 65 was his
home away from home.
He was a very good
provider, and he
would have made a good father.
He didn't deserve to die.
He didn't.
[music playing]
[crying]
He didn't deserve to die.
He didn't.
I'm not coming back, mom.
I can't stand to see
you like this anymore.
It's killing me.
I love you too much.
[music playing]
Tommy, it's Mary.
You'll be hearing from
my lawyer next week.
Look, I'm sorry.
I had to hit you all at once,
but it's got to be done.
Please don't call me.
If you have anything to
say, please just say it
through the lawyer all right.
[door bell rings]
Tommy, I've got a
message from precinct 65.
[music playing]
[fighting]
Hold him down.
If they don't find you guilty,
next time it will be loaded.
OK, fellas, let's go.
[music playing]
This is really arousing me.
Oh, God.
Obviously, you kept your key.
Stupid son of a bitch, what
the hell is wrong with you?
Look, I had no
place to go, OK.
Three men try to end my
thriving career to tine my home.
Yeah, by the looks
of my door, we're
all building a little fan club.
Drink?
No, thanks.
How about some ice, huh?
Florence Nightingaleing
it in that.
Never wanted to be.
ANSWERING MACHINE:
An eye for an eye.
We know where you live.
It's only a matter of time.
You date really strange men.
WESTON: Funny.
ANSWERING MACHINE: Murders
should be murdered.
I'm gonna be watching and
waiting for you, bitch.
WESTON: Obviously, I need
to get an unlisted number.
Well, maybe I would have
been safer at my own place.
SLOAN: Ali, you there?
Pick up.
It's all over.
It really hurts.
I'm sorry, Ali.
I don't mean to leave you guys
for this, but I have no choice.
I can't sit tight.
Tell Tommy I'm sorry.
[music playing]
Billy.
Hey, Billy.
What's up Billy boy?
Tommy?
CUFF: Yeah, it's me, Billy.
I'm glad it's Tommy.
Hey, I'm glad it's you.
Come on in.
Can't do that.
I'm not going to help
you blow your brains out.
What?
Hey, come on in.
Hey, it's not loaded all right.
I don't buy that.
SLOAN: Look, I've just
made some fresh coffee.
It's nice and hot.
Did you bring that
take out, man?
Come on.
Get your ass in here buddy.
You can't do this to us.
What the hell did
you bring her for?
Hey, we were going to discuss
this together, right buddy?
We're in this together.
So Ali, come on, huh?
Come on in.
It's not loaded.
Come on.
Don't be a stranger.
Get your ass in his solider.
Come on.
Hey, it's not loaded.
It's not loaded.
- I'm going in.
- No, you're not going in.
You believe him?
He said, it's not loaded.
I know what he
said, but he's sick.
I know him.
- (YELLING) No, I know him.
(YELLING) No.
Hey, Billy, you OK?
Hey, I know you.
Did you come buy me some coffee?
No I don't want any.
Empty.
Hey, Tom Tom, I
told you it was, huh.
If you can't believe your
friends, who can you believe?
What am I gonna do with this
guy, huh? (YELLING) What am I
doing with this guy?
Knock it off, Tommy.
Just leave them alone.
You stay out of this, OK.
Just stay out of it.
You want to die, Billy, huh?
I'll kill you myself, you fuck.
You want to leave us alone in
this mess, huh? (YELLING) Well,
Fuck you, man.
We're in this together,
all three of us.
Open your eyes,
all right, Tommy.
The ship is sinking.
We are going down.
That's what the
public want and just
because things are so
fucked up, that's what
the public are going to get.
One way or the other,
legal or illegal.
Now, asshole on the street
is responsible for my life.
This believe it or not
it's my own responsibility.
And if I so choose to blow
my fucking brains out,
this, I believe,
is my right also.
Shit, we're all
going to go down
if we don't make a move now.
STARK: I don't want to hear it.
How could you have let those
three handle this assignment.
STARK: Don't give me crap
about this shit, huh.
I told that pompous
ass Dante that these
were the worst three
for the assignment,
and he wouldn't listen.
You mean you didn't recommend
Cuff, Sloan, or Weston.
What are you crazy?
Look, this is your
problem, you handle it.
Oh, uh, by the
way, tell Dante he
made a great call on this one.
MALCOLM: What the hell
is wrong with you?
10 men armed with
assault rifles,
and you can't take
out these three.
There's a backup plan in effect.
- Backup plan?
What are you, an idiot?
Back up plan?
Your last play cost me 10
good men, half. $0.5 million
in damage to my club, and
$1 million in chemicals.
Carried out the same operation
before and nobody has survived.
Well, they did, all of them.
This will be
carried out legally.
Between the pressure of the
media and the department,
they're buried.
- I've taken care of it.
Oh, they'll be found guilty.
Where were you doing the riot?
What, am I supposed to believe
that a jury will convict
three LA police officers?
Charges will be
brought against them,
and they'll be convicted.
What about Caesar?
Damn it.
We hit Caesar's
operation tomorrow.
[gun shots]
[music playing]
[speaking spanish]
CAESAR: Sooner or later they
have to run out of bullets.
[speaking spanish]
MITCHELL: Where are they?
No shows, all three
of them this morning?
All of them?
All three missed their meetings?
Every one of them, yes.
What happened to the
tales we had on them?
Not enough men.
They weren't scheduled
until this morning.
Where's Dante?
I don't know, sir.
I've been trying to reach
him at home all morning.
Soon as you hear from him,
tell him I want to see him.
You got it.
Get me everything you
have of those three.
I want to eat,
sleep, and breathe
them till they're back here in
this office, you understand?
Yes, sir.
I swear to God, I will track
them down wherever they are.
CAESAR: I apologize for bringing
you down here like this,
but let's face it, if I would
have sent you an invitation,
would you have come?
I didn't think so.
This is my village
and my business.
What business are you in?
I import and export.
Marijuana and cocaine.
I am a man of my word.
I am not a liar.
And I consider a
lying man a dog.
I am in the drug trade,
but my drug operation
is also responsible for all
the people in my village
having jobs and being able
to support their families.
If taking out last
the bombing rates.
Excuse me, but how many people
is it worth losing to keep
your zero unemployment rate?
We don't force
people to take drugs.
They create their own hell.
You three have a serious
problem in and so do I.
What the hell do we
have to do with you?
We have a common enemy.
I used to have a
partner in the trade.
Greed has a way of interfering
with people's working
relationships.
This, um, guy, what
does he got to do with us?
CAESAR: Have either
of you been associated
with a name, Marshall Gumstock?
Never heard of him.
Sounds like a stockbroker.
Or the name, um, Malcolm?
Malcolm?
Aw, yeah, Mr. Sloan.
Never heard of him.
This man, Malcolm
owes me $1 million.
You bring me the million
dollar and him, you keep half,
I keep half, Malcolm.
I have never seen
so much shit before.
MITCHELL: Well, everything
can tell you something.
And the more
information we have,
the better chance we have
of saving their lives.
Saving their lives?
You think it's their fault?
When was the last time
we were in the field?
Well, I've never
been in the field.
I've just always
been in the office.
You know, when I was a kid, a
police officer in the community
got respect, believe it or not.
We used to wave to the
cop on the B. Today,
we get laughter instead of the
mornings, smart-assed replies
and slurs, instead of sir.
If I were on the street
today with the street having
more fire power than the
department in many cases,
I'm not so sure I
wouldn't shoot first
and ask questions later too.
I don't think it's
their fault. I think
we let him down, the system.
DANTE: With due
respect, I think we're
talking about three individuals
here who don't value life,
other people's or their own.
These aren't police
officers, they're cowboys.
Where the hell have you been?
Why don't you run a
credit check on bill Sloan?
Three eviction notices,
an apartment full of drug
paraphernalia, it's not a
stretch to think that he'd
be seduced by $100,000.
I've been running a cross-check.
Good.
MITCHELL: Trying to get
something new, but you
didn't answer my question.
DANTE: What's that?
Where have you been?
I had a dentist appointment.
You know, by the
look of their records,
these guys have taken out
some really strong people.
Why did you pick Sloan,
Cuff, and Weston for the job?
Because at the
time, I felt they were
the best people for the job.
That's not what Stark thought.
DANTE: What the hell
does Stark know?
He knows his men.
So why did you pick them?
Solidarity.
They were best friends.
Why didn't you just
look at the records?
They're born shooters.
That's what they are.
I mean, it's obvious.
You knew there was
DEA on the inside.
Are you suggesting that
I'd sacrifice one of own?
Did you?
I'm not answering
that question.
- (YELLING) Did you?
- Fuck you, no.
[phone ringing]
No.
I'm telling you,
it's not a good idea.
He's offering us
weapons, transportation,
and $0.5 million.
I don't like it.
Oh, you don't like it?
What do you know about
this guy, Malcolm?
He doesn't know anything.
Don't fuck around.
Who is he?
I don't know anything.
He said he doesn't
know anything.
Leave him alone.
- OK, he knows, OK.
I saw the look in your eye.
(YELLING) I don't
know anything.
Call me fucking stupid, OK.
Don't start this
shit now Tommy.
(YELLING) Billy, talk to me.
You shouldn't be
involved in this.
But you're hiding
something from me?
Malcolm, Malcolm,
Malcolm. (YELLING)
Who the fuck is Malcolm.
I had the drop.
He moved.
A man died in my arms.
So he's dead, but he
was connected the way
you guys are connected with me.
Malcolm wants one of us.
We all go in, we all die.
All right.
We're all in this together.
WESTON: So if we don't
take Caesar's offer,
what do you want to do?
I don't know, escape.
Way south to the beaches.
Return to Mitchell
and, uh, surrender.
What you think counselor?
No escape, no return.
Grab the cash, grab Malcolm.
New lives, huh, son.
What is your decision?
MITCHELL: Anything?
Why the hell wasn't
this on his record?
Look at date.
It happened two weeks ago and it
wasn't filed until last night.
Mr. Mitchell, What
you find out, Johnson?
Three suspects were taken down
to Ceaser Sanchez's compound
late last night.
You know Marshall Gumstock.
A.k.a.
Malcolm, who doesn't?
DEA has been after
him for years,
but we haven't been able
to make anything stick.
He's been feuding
with Cesar Sanchez.
I didn't know that.
What the hell does that have
to do with this investigation?
Sloan killed
Malcolm's brother.
He probably doesn't
even know that.
JOHNSON: The word is
Cesar has imported
Cuff, Sloan, and Weston.
He's seeking their employment.
You know, if my
feeling is right
our shooters are headed on a
direct course with Malcolm.
Johnson, Stone, come on.
I'll put out a warrant.
MALCOLM: I assure you that
Caesar Sanchez will soon
pose no threat to
your careers, so you
have nothing to worry about.
Thank you, Malcolm.
And how are you this morning?
Very good, thank you.
There's a phone call
for you in the study.
It's great.
When did he do all
this renovation?
Oh, I don't know.
It's gorgeous.
Beautiful.
Yes?
DANTE: Sloan, Cuff,
and Weston are loose.
MALCOLM: That doesn't
make me very happy.
I've also learned that
they were contacted by Cesar.
You, my friend,
are on my death wish.
You have made promises
you have not kept,
and you have put me in
a very bad position.
I'm sick and tired of
your threats, Malcolm.
I can't cover it anymore.
I'm out.
You'll be getting a
visit from the FBI soon.
The man's name is
Mitchell, James Mitchell.
Dante.
Why did you do it?
Money?
Yes.
For $1 million.
Malcolm wanted the three
kids and the DEA agent dead.
I was there.
There was no way they could
come out of that place alive.
I know with three
against 12, I--
they pull off a miracle.
Malcolm bet a million on
a sure thing and lost.
I gambled my career.
[gun shots]
MITCHELL: Detective
Edward Dante, you're
under arrest for the
murders of officers Kevin
Donaldson and Jack Silver.
Kindly surrender your weapon.
[music playing]
[gun shot]
[birds chirping]
[music playing]
[fighting]
[whistle]
[music playing]
MALCOLM: Sloan, Cuff and Weston.
[sigh]
[music playing]
[fighting]
Matthew, Alex,
come on talk to me.
He can't talk
right now, Malcolm.
Aw, so the three
little piggies decided
to hunt down the big, bad wolf.
Well, let the hunt begin.
You know, I heard somewhere
the more people a man kills,
the more of himself
he kills too.
Well, Malcolm, you
and I have killed
a hell of a lot of people.
And it all starts to add up
to one day some low-life scum
shoves a gun into an
innocent girl's mouth
and threatens to
blow her brains out.
Well, Malcolm, let me
tell you, your brother
was a pitiless, soulless
piece of dog shit.
Damn, he wasn't worth the
piece of lead I spent on him.
For some God damn reason,
second I pulled that trigger,
it suddenly hit me.
I pulled it on myself too.
Problem is my heart's
still beating.
MALCOLM: Well,
don't worry Sloan,
because I can fix that problem.
I'll take care of
your two partners too.
Lord knows, they've been a
pain in my ass for a long time.
SLOAN: You know what
your brother said
to me with his dying breath?
Hey, blue, tell Malcolm
he's an asshole.
(YELLING) You're
a dead man, Sloan.
[music playing]
[gun shots]
[fighting]
What the hell's going on?
You want me?
You want some of this?
Come on then, come on.
Come and get me.
Come on, Billy Sloan,
come and get me.
Come on.
Go for it.
[gun shots]
[music playing]
[police sirens]
[gun shots]
[music playing]
(YELLING) Hold your fire.
Take cover and hold your fire.
[music playing]
There's something I thought
they should know, sir.
We found burned fragments
of some material
in the mountains yesterday,
three separate bundles.
Bundles?
Has the lab checked
the materials?
Our preliminary is parachute.
Thank you.
So can I buy you a drink?
Thanks, but I think
I've got some things
to take care of before I
fly back to Washington.
I'd like a rain check though.
WESTON: Everything happened
so fast, so fast as
if it never happened.
Fire burning, the
smell of gasoline,
the hot fire on our faces,
the sound of attack.
[music playing]
All I want is to be free, but
how free can I be when I'm
in prison in my own freedom.
[waves crashing]
[music playing]