[chef 1] Come on.
Let's go. Marie?
[kitchen staff shouting]
The 6:30s are here.
The serving staff
is on the floor.
It's time.
Perhaps you should
say something?
Ordering one hamachi crudo,
two salad niçoises
and one striped bass.
Merde! Sebastian. Huh?
We eighty-sixed the bass
an hour ago.
Why is table 42
expecting something we can't deliver?
There was a miscommunication.
[French accent]
"Miscommunication."
I speak four languages,
and you're talking to me
about miscommunication?
[Sebastian] Calm down.
Your face will scare
the customers.
My kitchen, my face, my rules.
And what's my rule number one?
Do not fuck with your kitchen.
Voilà.
Service!
Welcome to Etoile Rouge.
Right this way.
[jazz music playing]
Bon appétit.
[kitchen staff chattering]
All right. How much longer
until I have my veggies done?
Come on, guys.
I need them faster. Come on.
[host] Chef Ana? Yes?
The patrons could
really use some face time.
I don't have the time.
They paid for a meal,
but they also paid
to be schmoozed.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Wait, wait, wait.
Show it to me.
No. No. No.
No, no, no, no, no. No, no, no.
Look, the beurre blanc
is separated.
Oui, Chef.
It might taste the same,
but I know,
and you really should know,
it's not right.
Oui, Chef.
Let me show you, okay?
And then quickly, but no rush.
Yes. Of course. Like this. Yeah?
Yes.Try.
Faster. As fast as you can.
Sorry.
Don't apologize. Just practice.
Good. Good.
Practice until
you can do it in your sleep.
Good evening, Chef. Good evening, husband.
I told him not to.
[Sebastian]
You must be lost, Ray.
The bar is in front.
Aren't you funny?
You must be the first
Frenchman in history
not to back down from a fight.
Okay, that's enough.
Back to work.
Et toi, ma chérie. You're fired.
You can't fire the owner.
Half owner, and this
half is mine, so out.
I come bearing gifts.
No.
Put it in the freezer. No, no...
That's your answer
for everything.
I think you better
take a look at this.
It's nice, isn't it?
How... How did you do this?
You have your talents,
I have mine.
You better be ready
to get real busy.
Well done, Ray.
Oh, thanks, Frenchman.
Coming from you,
that's a... a compliment.
Come on. You gotta go show
your face to the hungry people.
Oh, no, no, no, darling.
I'm busy.
Look, I'm preparing the...
Hey, I've been bragging
about you all night out there.
If you don't come with me
and show your face,
they're gonna think
I'm a loser. Come on.
You know I prefer
the kitchen, not...
I know, the spotlight.
But you gotta meet
the hungry people.
[Ray chuckles] So
this Parisian chef says,
"If you don't come back
with 50 pounds of salmon,
you're gonna have a hundred
pounds of pissed-off Russian."
[laughter]
[Ray] So I said, "Tell me more."
And that's how I met my wife.
There you have it.
Set up on a blind date
by a dead fish. Enjoy.
[patron chuckling]
[chef shouting in French]
[kitchen staff shouting]
[alarm beeping][chef]
Get the back door open.
[Sebastian] Open the back door!
Out of the way! Idiot!
What's going on?
What's happening here, guys?
What's happening?
Back to work, all of you!
The first night,
and we're messing it all up!
[host] Chef.Yes.
[phone ringing]Uh, phone for you.
Sebastian, come on.
Try not to burn
the kitchen down.
It's the first day.
Hello? Hello?
[person on phone
speaking Russian]
[speaking Russian]
[person speaking Russian]
Everything all right, Chef?
Huh? Yes. Yes.
Everything's fine.
As long as the restaurant
doesn't burn, we're good.
Let's get back to work. Come on.
Oui, Chef.
Imbeciles!
Back to work, all of you.
I'm gonna go out
on the sidewalk,
tell the waiters that it's
safe to come back in.
I am so sorry, ma'am.
We are all booked for tonight.
[chuckles] I'm telling
you, Paris was insane.
We'd walk out of the clubs,
we'd all be drunk
and stumbling around.
I mean, it was one party
right after another.
Richard, it's getting late.
Well, thanks for the drink, Ray.
Ah, pleasure. Nice to meet you.
Ah, look after yourself.
We have reached
our turnover early.
Can I start taking walk-ins?
No. No walk-ins.
I'd rather be in the red
than to take walk-ins.
Fully booked.
That's what we show
the world tonight.
Okay, I'll turn away
this two-top.
Ah, ah, ah, ah. Guests.
Not a two-top, not a four-top.
We're not an Applebee's.
You're in the big leagues now.
My fault.
Guests, right.
I'll take care of these two.
Why don't you get drinks for
that two-top you just seated?
Ray, you handsome devil.
[chuckles]
I mean, this place is...
Wow.
Thanks, Mickey.
What's up, fellas?
We're starving.
[Ray] Just have your
mama cook for you.
That's fucked up.[laughing]
[chuckles] You know, my
mother's dead, God rest her soul.
What do you want?
Dom wants to talk.
Tell him I'll call him
in the morning.
That's not gonna work.
Come on, bozo. Look around.
We're busy. It's a bad time.
He wants to talk now.
Just tell him I'll call him
in the morning.
Yeah, he's not gonna do that.
Come on. We're friends.
I'll talk to him,
and it'll all work out.
It's tonight, Ray.
Mickey. Come on, man.
It's opening night.
[Ray laughs]It's opening night.
I don't give a shit
if it's opening night.
Listen to me.
It's tonight.
Dom told me tonight.
I told you it's tonight.
And you always do what Daddy
tells you to do, don't you?
I'm next in line, Ray.
Show a little respect.
Respect is earned.
I'll talk to him in the morning.
We'll work it out. Don't worry.
Tonight, Ray.
Let's get outta here.
[sighs] Terminé.[applause]
[Sebastian] Speech, speech.
[staff] Speech, speech,
speech, speech.
Okay. [laughs] Thank you.
Uh, this place is what
I've always wanted,
Um, and it's thanks to you
that I stand here,
the proud owner of Etoile Rouge.
Half owner. [chuckles]
This is a special night.
And hopefully
just the beginning.
And, yeah, thank you, guys.
Thank you for not fucking it up.
[staff chuckles][speaking Russian]
So let's celebrate.
That is all,
ladies and gentlemen.
The kitchen is now closed.
Let's drink.
[staff whoop] Na zdorovie.
Hey, boss, are we gonna
do this or what?
I left my dad a message.
We're not doing nothing
till he gets back to me.
He did say it was tonight.
Yeah.
I know what he said.
He said it to me, genius.
I told you that.
I'm just saying.
[henchman 1] So...
we're just gonna wait here?
Did I fucking stutter? Huh?
He's getting a massage,
and when he's getting a massage,
he don't like to be bothered.
It ruins the mood.
[henchman 2] I never
got a massage before.
You gotta do those things naked?
Why the fuck would you go naked?
I heard you gotta do it naked.
Just shut up. Everybody shut up.
And get off the fucking car.
I just had it washed.
[henchman 2] That Ray.
Some balls on that guy, huh?
Yeah. Not for long.
[henchman 2 chuckles] Yeah.
I'd like to see that.
Oh, you're gonna see
something, lollipop.
[henchman 2]
Okay, we'll see. Yeah, lollipop.
Cheers.
[electronic dance music playing]
[exhales] It's disgusting.
How does it feel?
What do you mean?
To have your own place.
Yeah, it feels good. Um...
A little stressful.
Ay, caramba.
You did it, Ana.
I know you can't tell
right now, but you did it.
This is the start of something...
[stomach grumbles] CÇa va, Sebastian?
[speaking French]
[chuckles]
So... [chuckles] did you
always wanna be a chef?
No. Not always, no.
Well, you're really good at it.
Thank you.
You know, it's not just me.
Ray has done so much for me.
Mmm.
And I'm sure
he's somewhere here,
supporting me, right?
[sniffing] Whoa. That's
some pretty good stuff, Ricky.
All right. I got a second wind.
Let's go.
I think we gotta get home.
It's getting late.
Aw, come on.
We just got started, man.
Well, I'm out of money.
Here. Problem solved. [chuckles]
Sorry, Ray. We gotta get going.
[Ana] Party's over.
Give them their tips back
and go home.
[Ray] There you go, guys.
Leave me enough
for cab fare, will you?
And I mean you too, huh?
Wanna play a game,
just you and me?
Well, you know, I gotta work.
I need to prepare
demiglace for tomorrow.
You never stop.
All right.
I'll see you when I see you.
Mm-hmm. Beso.
Don't be all night.Mmm.
Good night.
I'll walk you out.
Eliza, how did we do?
Everything was great.
Cash till looks promising.
Great. Thank you.
[Eliza] You're staying?
Oh, she's gonna smoke
and pace and pace and smoke.
She gets all jacked up
on the adrenaline.
Mm-hmm. Well, at least
that's all I'm jacked up on.
[Ray laughs][Eliza] Oh.
[chuckles] Good night.
[singer vocalizing]
[Russian folk song playing]
[singer continues singing]
My feet are killing me.
What you ladies
put up with is crazy.
[Mickey] Look who it is. Oh, shit.
Aren't those the two guys
for the restaurant?
A legend. Who's the hooker?
Isn't it past
your bedtime, Mickey?
[chuckles] Now, why you
gotta be crazy like that?
I let you have
your big night out.
Now, come on. I've had
it up to here with you.
Come on. Go home.
This is between me and Dom.
I'll work something out.
Well, he sent me to handle it.
So I'm handling it.
Ray.
Freaks come out at night, baby.
All right.
Enough of this take-your-child-
to-work-day bullshit.
You know, I think
all of this Viagra
has caused you
some serious hearing loss.
It's tonight, lollipop.
Yeah. All right, Mickey.
Whatever you say.
What are they talking about? Nothing.
They're talking about nothing.
They just talk.
Oops.
Thanks.
[chuckles] She'll be fine.
Let's go, Ray.
I'm not fucking around, Ray.
Ray! Let's go.
[Russian folk song
continues playing]
[metal scraping]
[music stops]
[metal clanks]
[clanking continues]
[henchman 2] Be careful.
It's heavy.
[henchman 1] Yeah,
I know it's heavy.
I am using my back!
Look, the lights are still on.
[scoffs] Yeah, and?
[henchman 1]
It smells good in here.
[henchman 2] It's about to
smell a whole lot worse.
[line ringing][gasoline pouring]
Yeah, Ray. Leave a message.
Yo, Meatball.
This pot's hot.
So what?
[henchman 1] Place is
supposed to be empty.
Shut the fuck up.
We got a job to do.
Hand me your lighter.
What?
Give me your lighter.
I don't got one.
How the fuck do you smoke
and you don't have a lighter?
I quit.
Fuck, we're in a kitchen.
There's gotta be one around here.
You gotta be fucking kidding me.
[sighs]
[generator powering down]
What?
["Kalinka" playing]
[grunts]
[panting]
[Mickey] "Wifey." [phone buzzing]
She's calling you, Ray.
Let me talk to her.
You think I'm an idiot?
Yes.
Ray?
[Mickey] Lady, you got
bad taste in men.
Who's this?
"Who is this?" That don't
matter. "Who is this?"
Where's Ray?
Handsome Ray
is right here with me.
Put him on.
You don't like talking
to me, lollipop?
Put my husband on the phone.
Or what?
I'm not a person
you wanna fuck with.
[laughs]
Then you're not gonna like
what we did to your restaurant.
What did you do
to my restaurant?
[laughs] It's in flames.
Big, bright, orange,
gorgeous flames.
Oh, is it?
Listen to me.
You better get out of there right
now before we torch the place,
or your opening night
is gonna be your last night.
I doubt it.
[shouts] She hung up on me, Ray!
Shit.
[door latch opens]
Ana.
Oh, honey.
[sighs]Thank God you're okay.
Is that a gun?
Oh, just for emergencies.
Don't worry.
What... Where did you get a gun?
I had it. [chuckles]
Is that blood?
Yeah, but... What the fuck is going on?
Stay calm. Calm. Whose blood is that?
No, don't... don't
open the door, Ray. Don't...
Oh, fuck.
Dom is gonna kill me.
Who? Who's Dom?[sighs]
A bad man.
Why is he gonna kill you?
Ray!
Sorry, I-I-I didn't know.
You didn't know what?
I thought
there would be more time.
I didn't know
it was gonna be tonight.
Ray, what did you do?
[sighs]
I fucked up.
I owe a lot of money,
and I thought
I could pay it back,
you know, when the
restaurant got successful.
How much do you owe?
A lot.
How much, Ray?
1.2.
[scoffs] Million?
1.3 if you round.
Oh, God. All right.
Get a little deeper there.
Yeah. Oh, shit.
Not that deep.
Oh, goddamn, Gary.
[phone ringing][groans] Who the fuck?
Get that, will you, Gar? Yes, sir.
What?
Sorry to bother you, Pops.
I know it ruins the mood.
Get to the point.
Well, we got a little
situation going on.
And you can't handle it?
I can. I just wanted to, you
know, make you awares, check-in.
[Dom sighs]
This wasn't supposed
to be difficult, Mick.
That's why I sent you
to take care of it.
I am taking care of it.
Oh, not that, Gary.
Not that deep.
Son of a bitch.
If you were taking care of it,
we wouldn't be talking
right now.
[sniffles] Look, Dad...
Can you just send me
a couple more guys?
What happened to
the guys that you had?
Gio and the pip-squeak,
what's-his-name.
You know that jerk, Ray, he
really fucked us on this one, Dad.
What?
Oh, goddamn! Oh, sorry. Okay.
Put him on.
Can't do that.
Why not?
'Cause he's inside,
holed up with that Russian lady.
I gotta tell you,
I don't like her one bit.
[sighs] I'm on my way. No, no, no.
Just... Just... Just send...
Jesus, man.
Let this be
a lesson to you, Gary.
If you ever want
something done right,
don't ask your jerk-off son
to do it for you.
I'm still on the line, Dad.
Then hang the fuck up, idiot.
[line beeps]
[crying, sniffling]
[Ana] Ray, what did you do?
[sighs]
They wanna burn down
the restaurant
for the insurance money.
And you're okay with that?
No. Fuck no, I'm not
okay... I don't have a choice.
Please tell me
it wasn't your idea.
No, it wasn't.
Maybe... Maybe a little.
But, Ana,
I really believed that we
could make this place work.
It would've been great. "Would have been"?
[laughs]
You're giving up already?
That's it?
Sweetheart,
we don't have a choice.
No, you don't have a choice.
[scoffs] You're so
fucking irresponsible.
[sighs] I'm sorry.
Not sorry enough.
What if... Shut up!
No wonder
you've been divorced twice.
Now I get it.
That's a little below
the belt, don't you think?
I fucked up,
but I love you.
I truly love you.
And if I could go back
and change all of this,
I would do it in a nanosecond.
Well, you can't,
and you lied to me.
What about you?
What about... What about this?
What... What about them?
Did you kill 'em?
You really wanna know?
Ana, talk to me.[sighs, scoffs]
I, uh...
I used to work for the KGB.
Like Russian KGB?
Yes.
You're a spy.
I'm a chef.
Wait, wait.
I mean, that's not something
that you just walk away from.
How did you get out? I managed.
I disappeared,
until you fucking
put me on the map
with that stupid announcement.
How was I supposed to know
that you were fucking KGB?
No, ex-KGB.
All right, so what now?
Is the KGB gonna come after you?
No.
Maybe.
[chuckles]
So I guess we're both
full of shit.
No, except I lied
to protect you.
No, you lied to protect you.
What the fuck do you know?
Don't be mad. Don't be mad.
Don't be mad.
I can fix this.
Why am I here, then,
when I should be getting
a fucking massage?
I got a plan. You got a plan?
The only plan you got is
I got a plan.
A Russian problem calls for
a Russian solution, right?
You had your chance, Mickey.
Leo, Tommy, Billy, let's go.
I did what I had to.
I had no choice!
Welcome to the fucking club.
That's not the same thing.
It is exactly
the same fucking thing.
I tried so hard to get rid
of one thing in my life,
and here you are, fucking it up
like you fucked up
everything else.
I can fix this.
Let me talk to them.
Talk to him? [scoffs]
Talking will do nothing.
You don't know these guys.
They're not gonna
walk away from this.
There's a lot of money on the
line, and there's a lot of them.
I don't care.
Dom is not somebody
you wanna fuck with.
I'm not somebody
Let me talk to them.
He needs me alive.
He's not gonna kill me.
He needs me breathing
so he can collect on
the insurance money.
I can reason with him.
He's a reasonable guy.
He's a reason... Did he just
say he's a reasonable guy?
Oh, no, no. Did you just say
he's a reasonable guy?
No, we're not going
down that road.
No, wait, wait.
You like that word.
We're not going down...
No, we're not doing...
You call me unreasonable
all the time!
And what do I do?
I cook.
Sometimes I shout.
And that makes me unreasonable?
This guy wants to burn down a perfectly good
restaurant, and he's the reasonable one.
That's not what I'm saying.
No? No, we're on the same team.
No, we are not on the same team.
You want to talk to people
that want to
burn this place down.
And what do you wanna do?
You wanna kill 'em?
I won't let them
burn down my restaurant.
Our restaurant?
I'll talk to them.
It's the only way.
[Ray] If you're not gonna
be reasonable, I will.
[Ray] Dom!
I just wanna talk.
What's going on, Ray?
You can't burn it down. Not yet.
Why is that?
Give us a chance to
really make it work, please.
I got a good feeling
about this place.
And you had a good feeling about
the last four restaurants too.
Do you remember that?
Yeah, I know, I know,
but this one's different.
It's not working for me, Ray.
Is that all you got
is a good feeling?
Come on, don't bust my balls.
All right, look. I got a
really good feeling. All right?
Is that... Does that work?
Doesn't mean much
coming from you.
Dom, please.
Ray...
take solace in the fact
that you didn't run this one
into the ground.
You burned it.
[clattering]
[grunts]
[shouts]
[gunfire in distance]
You think they got her?
Enough bullshit.
Mickey, you're up.
Burn this place to the ground.
Dom, please. Come on.
[panting]
[line ringing]
[phone ringing]
[humming]
[Ana] Hello? Mimi?
Ana, is that you?
Yes.
How are you?
Um... [sighs]
I need your help.
Well, this is a blast
from the past, isn't it?
Same old shit,
like the old days.
You get in some shit, and
you call me to bail you out?
[chuckles] Yes.
Hmm. So you need my help.
There are some men trying
to burn down my restaurant.
Oh, no. On opening night?
Yeah.
Well, that's just rude.
How many are we talking?
[sighs] Not sure yet.
But can you help?
Well, what choice
do I have, Ana?
If you're calling me, I'm
guessing it's an emergency, right?
It is, yeah. Um...
Could you hurry?
I will, babe. Don't worry.
A road to a friend's house
is never long.
And we are friends, right?
Even after all these years?
Yeah, friends.
Good.
Protect yourself, Anya.
We'll see you soon.
Mimi, listen.
Uh...
I just want you to know I...
You know, when I left...
No, no, no, no, no. No.
We will chitchat all about it
when I get there, 'kay?
Can't wait.
[sighs]
♪ I like big guns
And I cannot lie ♪
This one's clean. Please stop
singing that.
[sighs]
[Mimi] Let's go.
We're leaving? Yes, pack your shit.
Let's go.Okay.
Girls, we're... Come on, girls.
Who was that?
It's simple. You just run in,
throw it on the ground. Boom.
I don't take orders from you.
This comes direct
from my pops.[sighs]
He told you to do it.
And I'm telling you.
It's called delegating.
It's what leadership is.
Now go.
[Mickey] Come on.
Are you scared?
I'll tell my dad
you did a good job.
Just do this thing.
It's gonna be huge.
[henchman] You do it.
You're not gonna convince me.
[Mickey]
You're being insubordinate.
Grow your balls and listen.
[henchman] No way.
It's not gonna happen. Fucking idiots.
[Mickey continues, indistinct]
Here, let's go.
Let's go.
You got it.
You can do it.
Come on.
Shit.
[popping lips]
Just saying, if we get pulled
over, it's gonna slow us down.
Okay. Thanks, Tom. Y-You're welcome.
Going fast.
Driving fast, too fast.
I think the speed limit's
actually...
Oh, my God, you're really...
Tom.Yeah.
You know what this
reminds me of?
Bucharest? Yeah, Bucharest.
Remember that was... that was
a... that was a good one. [chuckles]
You were good
in Bucharest. I was.
I mean, yeah, because we sma...
Remember we smashed into the
dog park and those really angry...
It was a mission, Tom.
And was it successful?
It was
a successful mission. It was.
Yeah.
This isn't a mission.
Nobody likes
a back-seat driver, Tom.
I'm sitting in the front.
[child 1]
Why did we have to come? Excuse me, lady.
You know exactly why.
I have homework, Mimi.
Do not fucking call me, Mimi.
The last time you had "homework,"
we came home to a party.
It was sociology.
And it was a get-together, so...
Yeah, okay,
so that's your truth.
Just listen to your Mimi...
Mommy... your mother.
Listen... Look, it was just a
suggestion. If you slow down...
Okay, well, I suggest that
you mind your own business.
Thank you for that suggestion.
I'm just trying to help.
Okay, you can help.
Just do it silently
inside your mind.
Dr. Gottlieb says that we should
have an open forum... You know what?
If Dr. fucking Gottlieb
knows so much,
why has she been married
three times, huh, Tom?
Oh, my God, just get
fucking divorced already.
[both] Language.
Do you realize how much
you guys are screwing us up?
Okay, your mother and I are just
working through a cloudy yesterday
to get to
a sunny tomorrow sometime.
Mm-hmm. Yeah, right.
Jesus Christ, Tom.
She's really gotten to you. You remembered
that thing hanging above her wall?
TROMP.
Oh, Lord. TROMP!
Trust, respect,
open-mindedness, positivity.
TROMP.Mm-hmm.
If you can't handle all four,
just pick one.
Okay, I will pick one.
I pick positivity. Puh!
I'm positive
Dr. fucking Gottlieb
hasn't gotten laid
since the Berlin Wall.
Makes three of us.
Well, then take
some fucking initiative.
[engine revving]
[sighs] Oh, God.
I'm just gonna make an observation.
You're driving like a maniac.
And I think this is a personal
vendetta against your best friend.
Ex-best friend, current enemy.
And will you have
my fucking back?
It's okay, girls.
Keep it locked up.
Keep the riffraff out.
Shouldn't be a long night.
Thanks for coming out.
No sweat. You got it, boss.
Six guys in, no guys out?
Shit, man. Man,
this is some bullshit.
Gary, focus, please. Man, I am focused.
That's how
I gather myself, okay?
I'm just a masseuse.
I shouldn't even be here.
Shit!
Don't be a bitch, man. Come on.
[whimpers]
Come on!
Shut up. God, please help me.
Gary, what are you
waiting for? Let's go.
[grunts] Ah!
Okay, come on. Go.
It's not locked.
You go first. You go first.
No, get your Black ass in there.
That's some racist shit.
You can't say that shit.
My bad. My bad. You're right.
[door slams]
I'ma go towards
the office, all right?
You go right there, boy.
You got that, right? [shouts]
[shouting]
[Gary] Bobby!
I'm scared! Open up, man!
Okay. A little bit of Ali.
A little bit of Jackie.
[shouts]
Okay.
Let's do this. I got you, okay?
You better get her, Bobby!
Yeah! Whup her ass, boy!
Kill that bitch!
Kill that bitch, Bobby!
[grunting]
Bobby, is she dead?
What the fuck...
[whimpering]
No. No! No!
No! No!
No!
[meat slicer powers down]
[body thuds]
[grunts]
[gasps]
I didn't see that.
I didn't, I didn't.
One more time.
Okay, that's just...
[gasps] Shit.
Bobby, Bobby.
Please, come on, Bobby.
[footsteps approaching]
[whispers] No, stay down.
Be quiet. Be quiet, be quiet.
[shouts] Okay, look! I'm blind.
I didn't see your face
or the dead bodies.
Aah! I didn't see nothing!
Oh, shit! Please!
[screaming]
[fryer powers up]
Please! [grunts]
You got 90 seconds
before the oil
turns your fingers
into pommes frites.
Come on. Oh, shit. Look, lady, I
only understand American threats.
It means french fries!
[grunts] Okay, look.
Okay, look, my name is Gary, and
I'm a Libra and I like Chinese food.
Who cares about
your fucking star sign?
And I don't have no problems
with you at all.
I have no problem
with you, Gary.
I just have questions
and I want answers.
Okay, look... [screams]
Tell me about Dom![grunts] Well, shit.
I think Dom, he's an Aquarius.
His birthday was two days ago.
No! That's not
what I wanna know.Okay.
Why does he wanna
burn down my restaurant?
I don't know why!
I really don't know!
Well, you better fucking know
because you've got
60 seconds left.
Okay, okay.
It's an insurance thing.
It's very confusing, okay?
It's confusing.
Why tonight?
Why tonight? I don't know!
Because they got... It's a
war between the families.
And he gotta have... He says
gotta have cash for the company.
How many men work for him?
[sobbing]
I don't know. I don't know.
This is getting hot.
It's getting hot, please.
That's the idea.
Please, lady, look,
I'm a masseuse!
All I do is massage! What?
Yes! [screams] I need my hands!
[shouting]
Please, let me go. Please.
Oh, stop fucking shouting!
[yelps, grunts]
Okay. Okay.
Please, please, please.
Look. Okay.
Okay, I just wanna say
thank you, first of all,
for respecting
an artist's hands.
You gonna kill me?
Huh?[sighs]
I don't enjoy this.
So you not gonna kill me?
[sighs]
Hell, you could let me go.
So you're a masseuse.
Yes, I'm...
I'm a certified masseuse.
I... I do massages all day,
and I can tell you need
a massage right now.
I can put my hands on you
and put 'em...
You're Gary, huh?
Yes, I am Gary. You a Libra?
Yes, I am a Libra.
If you don't like that, I can
change my sign if you want to.
[speaking Russian]
What that mean? What that mean?
That mean you about to...
Some people coming in?
It means get out of here, Gary,
before I change my mind.
I understand that.
But can I use
your restroom first, huh?
Okay, I'm out.
I don't like that look.
Get the fuck out! Okay.
Shit.
[footsteps running][Gary yelps]
[siren blares]
We had some calls about
some gunfire in the area.
You know anything about that?
Uh, we're digging up the
gas main at the restaurant.
Jackhammer is gonna be
going on and off all night.
Yeah.
It's a residential area.
Got a lot of busybodies.
I'll leave you to it.
Ready? Ready.
[child] Seriously,
why do we have to be here?
[both]
Because we don't trust you.
Hey, hey, hey. Ease up there.
Hello, ma'am?
Hello! Just passing through.
[laughs]
I'm sorry, ma'am,
this road is closed.
Closed? I...
No, I'm meeting a friend at
a restaurant down the street.
[worker] It's pretty late.
I'm pretty sure the restaurant's
not still open.
No, no, no, I'm sure
she's there waiting for me.
I'm sorry, ma'am, no can do.
It's just not safe.
You're gonna have
to call your friend.
Oh, dear. You can loop back aro...
Oh.
Fun. Warn me next time.
Oh, God.
[Dom] I understand.[Mickey] Pop!
[footsteps running]
I said I understand that.
I know it's short notice. Pop!
But this is a really big deal,
and it's
gotta go down tonight. Pops!
Alls I want is a quote.
Three guys...
No, make it four guys...
Pops... for three hours.
Can... Can you gimme
one second, please?
What?
The guys that just went in...
they're gone too.
She got Gary.
[gasps]
Scratch that.
I need 15 more.
I don't care about the cost.
Just make it happen.
[blows]
[chattering on cell phone]
[Mimi] Some time tonight
would be nice.
I may work slowly,
but I always finish quickly.
Oh, I know
you finish quickly, Tom.
I won't let your stress
disrupt my peace.
How long is this gonna take?
I acknowledge your impatience,
but I don't have
an answer for that.
[chattering continues
on cell phone]
[clears throat]
[tuts melodically]
So you're really gonna do
this. You're gonna kill her.
I don't know. I don't know.
You wanna talk about it?
I don't wanna talk about it.
You don't wanna talk about
it. Okay, no, I understand.
I'm really conflicted about
it. You seem conflicted.
I am. I'm conflicted.
You know what this
reminds me of?
Jakarta.
Jakarta? Jakarta was a shitfest.
Oh, it wasn't all bad.
Okay, but you
feel conflicted now.
Yes, she's... my friend.
She's your best friend. She was my friend.
And then she completely
ditched me and abandoned me
to become a fucking civilian.
I know. I was like... [scoffs]
Must've had a pretty good
reason for that, I guess, you know.
Whose side are you on,
Tom? You know the answer.
Do I? I hope that you do.
I hope you do.Okay.
I hope that you realize that this
feels like more of a conversation
than a conflict.Conflict.
Another fucking Gottlieb
gem. It's a good Gottlieb.
Thanks for that.
I'm gonna kill her.
I don't think you're
in the right mindset for this.
I don't think killing
should be personal.
It's like plumbing.
It's just a job.
Okay, well then, shut up and
do your job. All right, Tom?
Seriously, how long
is this gonna take?
It's gonna take
what it's gonna take!
Calm down. Calm down, Tom!
Okay.
Are you done?
Uh, hon?
Girls!
[both] God, I hate them.
[dog barking in distance]
Oh, shit. Hell no.
[yelping]
Oh, shit!
[both] Hello.
Are you okay?
Can we help you?
Where are you going?
What's up, dog?
[whimpering]
How's it going, Dom?
This is your last chance, Ray.
You need to go in there and talk
some sense into that wife of yours.
Think she's gonna listen to me?
You better pray that she does.
[sighs]
[door opens]
[door closes]
Not exactly the warm and
fuzzy greeting I was hoping for.
I could have shot you.
What do you want, Ray?
Dom sent me.
Maybe I should have shot you.
He wants me to get you
out of here.
Yeah, I'm sure he does.
What do you want?
Oh, now you wanna know?
We can take them.
We? [chuckles]We.
You just tell me what you
want me to do, and I'll do it.
Fine.
Get out of here.
Ah...
I'm not leaving.
Ray, please go.
Sixty-five percent. What?
Sixty-five percent of restaurant
staff quit during their shift.
I'm not gonna be one of 'em.
[sighs]
Did they hurt you out there?
Nothing a stiff drink won't fix.
How about you?
Well, you should see
the other guys.
KGB, huh?
Ex-KGB.
What the fuck?
How the fuck
did we even get here?
A Russki cooking French food.
It's crazy.
Doesn't make any sense.
I told you. After I left
Russia, I went to France.
That part is true.
What part isn't?
The rest of it.
I'm still the same person.
I had no idea they were
gonna try and torch this place
with you in it.
Doesn't matter now.
It matters to me.
So what's the plan, baby?
Well...
I've got a couple of ideas.
[chuckles]
I bet you do.
[Gary screaming]
No! Okay, just wait! Please!
Okay. Okay, look.
I asked God this morning,
I said,
"Send me two strong women."
I don't give a fuck what
you asked God about, Gary.
How did she seem, Gary? I don't know!
I don't know!
I think you do know, Gary.Okay.
Okay, she seemed sad.
I don't know. Sad.
[laughing]Honestly, sad.
Sad Anya. Wonderful.
And was she alone?
Well, sh... Yeah, she was alone.
She whupped all them
grown men ass by herself.
It was embarrassing. Oh,
so she's still sharp?
She's sharper
than a crackhead's toenail.
Honey, cut the guy some slack.
I wouldn't exactly be a
torturer if I cut him slack.
Listen to him.
You pussy.
Mimi really needs to get laid.
[Gary] Okay, okay!
How do you get in? The back door.
What other way
is there to get in? The front door.
Oh, wow, you must be
a fucking architect, Gary.
Not at all. I'm a masseuse.
I do nothing but massages.
You're a masseuse.
Do you fascial work?
Your neck is fine, Tom! Man up!
I got shrapnel between my C3
and C4. I'm in a lot of pain every day.
Why are there so many cars
parked down there?
I don't know!
I don't know, lady!
Well, tell me what you do know,
Gary! Bitch, I don't know shit!
Okay, I am so sorry
for calling you that.
I-I just don't wanna die. I don't think
he's lying.
[sobbing]
I'm not. I'm not at all.
Useless.
[panting, gasping]
You'll... She's...
Wait, useless?
H-Him or me? Him... Him or me?
White people, they so mean.
[whimpers]
[buzzing]
[phone beeps]
Yeah, Ray.
Time's up, Ray.
All right then.
Then come on out.
Mmm. That's not gonna happen.
Jesus Christ. [chuckles]
Do you got a death wish
or something?
Yeah, something like
that. Something like that.
I'm telling you right now,
this is your last chance.
If you come out right now,
well, you both go free.
But if you keep making me wait, I'm
gonna put a bullet in both your heads.
Fucking idiot.
If you kill us, you won't be able
to collect on the insurance money.
Be a shame if you did
all this for nothing.
It's not nothing, asshole.
Oh, it's something.
What the fuck's wrong with you?
You fucking idiot.
We're not coming out, Dom.
If we're going down,
we're going down swinging.
Then we're coming in.
Watch this shit.
They're gonna try to fuck me
without even buying me dinner first.
Let's move.[mercenaries chattering]
You Dom?
I am.
Good. We're here.
I can see that.
No shit.
You spoke to Terry?
I spoke to Terry. We spoke to Terry.
And he explained
the overtime rules?
[Dom exhales]
Yes. Several times. Yes.
My guys are coming straight
from another job.
And I appreciate that.
It means double time.
So I've heard.
And if we go over four
hours, we're gonna need lunch.
[sighs]
Catered.
[laughing]
Yeah, you got it.
I want you to kill
that Russian bitch.
[laughing]
[groaning]
Gary, Gary, Gary, Gary, Gary.
Gary, you're magic.
You're magic.
No, no, no, no, no.
You don't understand.
[groaning] Oh, Gary.
[neck cracks]Oh, Gary.
You're magic. Magic.
Magic hands.
Thank you, sir.
That means a lot, Tom.
[Tom] I needed this.
I needed this and I...
And I knew...
When I saw
those long phalanges, I knew.
[chuckles]I knew.
Well, you seem real stressed.
[grunts]
Yeah.
I used to be happy, Gary.
Me and Mimi were happy.
And we...
we had each other's backs.
She was like, "Thanks, hon.
I got you, babe.
I got you, babe."
And then we had kids.
[child] Hello?
We can hear you.
Yeah.
Me and my ex
had a cat named Blue.
[chuckles]
So I can relate with you.
I guess it doesn't help
that we work together.
What kind of work
do you do, Tom?
Well, Gary, I could tell you,
but I might have to kill you.
[both chuckle]
[both laughing]
I don't wanna kill you, Gary.
Yeah, we don't want that at all.
I'm not gonna kill you, Gary.
Thanks, Gary.
You're free to go.
You sure?
Don't wanna wait on Mimi?
No, I'm making the call.
Goodbye, Gary.
[footsteps running]
[door opens, closes][sighs]
I love you girls.
Tom must be off his meds again.
There's only two ways in.
For everyone who's gone in,
no one's come out.
Rocco didn't technically go in.
Yeah, he exploded in the
parking lot. Thanks, Mick.
How many are there? Just one.
Just one?
One giant pain in the ass.
Well, we'll hit him
from both sides.
Her.
It's a her? It's a her.
Huh.
Well, that's gonna cost extra.
You're kidding, right? I'm not.
I mean, I thought
you women wanted equality.
You're telling me we all
showed up for one woman?
I'm telling you
I got 10,000 bucks
for the person who kills
that goddamn Russian.
We're dealing with Russians?
Technically, Russian.
Just the one. Ana.
Is that gonna cost us more?
Everything costs.
We've dealt
with Russians before,
and it's not gonna be pretty.
I don't need it to be
pretty. I need it to be done.
I'm gonna need
one of those walkie-talkies...
for communication purposes.
Mick, go wait in the car.
Adults are talking over here.
Go wait in the fucking car.
It's my kid.
I'll do him for free.
Ready?
Ready.
Na zdorovie.
Exactly.
[exhales]
[water running]
[machinery whirring]
[electricity crackling][grunting]
We need backup!
Send in everyone!
[crackling stops]
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Get down!
[grunts]
[leader] Get her!
Table for five?
[mercenaries grunt]
No walk-ins.
[door opens]
[exhales]
Ray, get behind the bar.
[hip-hop music playing on radio]
[mercenary] Go, go, go!
[grunts]
Scatter, scatter!
[gunfire]
[Ana whispers] You okay?
[gunfire continues]
I'm good.
Hang in there.
[gunfire continues]
[mercenary] Go, go.
[grunts]
[gun clicking]
She's out of bullets! Push up!
[mercenary] She's out of ammo!
Watch your back!
Go, go, go!
[whispers] I love you.
[chuckles]
I love you, shithead.
[body thuds]
[rustling]
[mercenary] Watch out!
[mercenaries grunting]
[leader] There's another one!
[mercenary]
Where the hell is... [grunts]
[gunfire]
[Mimi]
What Chardonnays do you have?
I like something
a little fruity.
[mouthing words] Trust me.
[footsteps]
Whoo!
I mean, it can be pinot.
I really don't care what it is.
I'm not picky.
[sighs]
Mimi, you made it.[laughs]
Looks like I was just in time.
[gunshot]
Thanks, hon!
I got you, babe.
I missed you, Anya.
Oh, I missed you too.
It's been so long.
Oh, I know. Too long.
Thanks for coming.
Me, miss an opportunity
to catch up with an old friend?
I would never.
I've been looking for you
all these years.
Really?
I mean, that's what you do when
a friend just up and vanishes.
[laughs] You literally
disappeared without a trace.
I remember. Yeah, I know.
I think you owe me a bit of
an explanation. [chuckles]
Oh, come on, Mimi. It's
been such a long time ago. I...
I don't think you understand
quite how upset some of
our friends were when you left.
I'm sorry.
You're sorry?
Okay, well, then water
under the bridge, right?
Sure, I mean... [laughs] Wrong.
[chuckles] Mimi, come on.Anya.
All right.
Okay, so now what?
Well, now I kill you, sweetie.
[both grunting]
[Mimi]
They blamed me for leaving!
You're rusty.
[grunting]
You think I didn't think
about leaving, huh?
You could have told me!
Mimi, I tried to protect you.
[breathing heavily]
But I never would've left
without you.
[both grunting]
Oh, I've waited years for this.
I made a mistake, Mimi.
I'm sorry.
Aw. Not sorry enough, baby.
[grunting continues]
I never meant to hurt you.
[gasps]
Friends don't
abandon each other.
[breathing heavily]
You left me
without cover in Paris.
You had Tom.
Tom's a moron!
At least your husband didn't
gamble away your dreams.
What are you talking about?
Husbands are more trouble
than they're worth.
Yeah, tell me about it.
[both panting]
I made a mistake, Mimi.
Yeah, you really did.
You were my family.
And you're still
my fucking family.
[chuckles]
[hammer cocks]
I don't believe we've been
properly introduced.
Oh, he's tougher than he looks.
Thanks, hon.
Well, he looks geriatric.
I hope so. [chuckles]
Yeah, I'm an old man...
with a double-barrel shotgun
aimed at your head.
I'm Mimi.
An old friend of Ana's.
How about you put
that gun down, friendo?
Maybe he's not all bad.
He's got his moments.
I really miss you, Anya.
I miss you too, Mimi.
[sighs]
Well, that was fun.
[both chuckle]
We should go to dinner sometime.
Do a proper catch-up,
leave the boys at home.
[Ana] Sure thing.
Call me, okay?
Don't be such a stranger.
Thanks for the help.
[grunts]
[sighs]Hey.
I'm so glad.
Did you... Did you...
No. [sighs]
I'm getting soft.
Where's the hostage?
I let him go. You what?
I made the call.
You made the call.
Wow.
I'm gonna be making the call
a lot more often.
[chuckles]
Not in front of the girls.
Come here.
[both retch]
[chuckles]
Hmm.
Ten Gs down the toilet.
What are we gonna do now, Pops?
[groans]
Fuck, fuck, fuck.
Hello, lollipop.
[breathing heavily]
Mon chérie.
CÇa va?[sighs]
You hungry, baby?[chuckles]
I could eat.
I can always eat. I know, yeah.
[Ray] Chérie.
[speaking French]
You're so cute
when you speak French.
[speaks French]
Good.
Oh. Bon appétit.
[upbeat rock music playing]
♪ I dug you out today ♪
♪ I just wanna
Spend some time with you ♪
♪ Free, living life this way ♪
♪ Nothing else will shatter
My dismay ♪
♪ Not gonna see
Any city lights ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh-ooh ♪
♪ Just gonna blaze a trail
To true bliss ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh-ooh ♪
♪ Dodging all the rats
With all their frights ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh-ooh ♪
♪ We'll be ready to face
The death kiss ♪
♪ I dug you out today ♪
♪ I just wanna
Spend some time with you ♪
♪ Free, living life this way ♪
♪ Nothing else will shatter
My dismay ♪
♪ Not gonna see
Any city lights ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh-ooh ♪
♪ Just gonna blaze a trail
To true bliss ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh-ooh ♪
♪ Dodging all the rats
With all their frights ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh-ooh ♪
♪ We'll be ready to face
The death kiss ♪
[song fades]