[vocalizing]
[distant vocalizing]
[choir singing]
[bright music]
[cricket chirring]
We're movin'.
What?
We're gonna move.
When?
Two days.
In two days?
Yeah.
Not really.
Thanks for the news.
I haven't known for long.
I just decided,
I decided on Butte.
Butte, Montana.
What do I need that makes me
make these decisions?
You got me.
-Yeah.
What does Beth say?
Beth?
She says...
Beth says whatever makes me
happy, that's what she says.
[engine idling]
[car radio]
[horns beeping]
[beeps horn]
[rhythmic clicking]
How long a drive is it to Butte?
With me driving?
Twenty-two hours.
That's not bad.
In my car? It's a fuckin'
nightmare.
And there's no good radio in
Utah.
-It's all religious programs.
-Get saved.
No thank you.
[giggling]
Uh-uh.
Think about this.
Take a detour
and go through Vegas.
Kick off the trip.
You and Beth can have
a nice, romantic dinner,
see a show, play the slots,
get the free drinks.
No, that's too much money.
The show, the meal, the slots.
Then there's the hotel.
That's another hundred
down the toilet.
No!
You skip the hotel--it's night.
The highway's empty.
[laughs]
You, uh, you start speeding.
'Cause you've got
a little buzz on.
You get stopped in Utah
by the cops.
You flunk the breathalyzer.
They haul you in.
The judge is Mormon.
Ugh! You get 15 years.
You go to prison,
but at least your life
has taken a direction!
[shrieks]
[laughter]
Hi.
Hi!
Hi, honey.
-Bye.
-Bye!
Lunch tomorrow?
I'm all yours.
Wait--make it mine,
I've got the short shift.
Do you want me to come over
after?
Help pack?
Yeah, that'd be great.
I'm--I'm really--
I'm really sorry
we didn't tell you any sooner,
it's...
he just...
Yeah, oh, I understand.
Bye.
Fuckin' Nick.
I'm tired,
I'm going to bed.
What's your problem?
I haven't got a problem.
Okay.
You agreed to try Butte.
Yeah, I know--Butte, Montana,
city of the future.
Yeah, I read that a while ago,
so the future's probably
already there.
It's not like you're leaving
anything behind,
a good job or something.
No, just some friends.
You'll make new friends.
I know.
I'm not eight years old,
I know I'll make new friends.
So what is it?
Uh...
it embarrasses me.
I mean, the way that you and
Carol are together sometimes.
She's my best friend
and it embarrasses methat you used to live with her.
That was years ago.
It was three years.
Yeah.
We're moving, so...
she won't be your best friend
anymore.
Livin' with someone
isn't such a big deal.
Anyway, I live with you now.
[choir singing]
[coffee machine gurgles]
Beth?
Beth!
What?
It's rainin'.
It does that.
Since we got it?
No, lately.
Shit. What's wrong with it?
Water comes out.
Shit. I hate this shit.
Never kept the coffee hot,
and now this.
It still works.
No it doesn't.
Water comes out.
Okay.
Coulda got a new one on mydiscount but it's too late now.
-Want a doughnut?
-No.
I want an appliance that works.
This coffeemaker is junk.
[blender buzzing]
Blender is junk!
Our TV is junk.
I don't know why
we're even bothering to pack.
You got me.
Can't believe we don't have
a good TV.
Well, we don't watch much.
Yeah, but at our age...
Why don't you take one?
Ain't hungry.
Not a doughnut--a TV.
I might do it.
I say do it.
They can afford
to give you a bonus.
Maybe they are.
What do you mean?
Maybe when I get my check today,
there'll be a bonus in it.
Nick, they fired you.
Yeah.
There's no bonus.
And I sold a lot of TVs for 'em.
I should go.
Don't wanna be late
on my last day.
Gotta go.
[engine fires up]
[tires screeching]
[tires screech]
Hot enough for you?
Hey, Chip.
Supposed to hit 110.
Yeah, well, it's good practice
for hell.
I'll remember that one.
Hey, um, I heard that you're
leaving us.
Yep. I'm outta here.
They can you?
That's what they think.
Yeah?
Yeah, I was gonna quit anyway.
This way, I get unemployment.
I'm not stuck waiting around
for the layoffs to start.
Layoffs?
[elevator dings]
[door opens, closes]
-Who are you?
-The painter.
What are you doing?
Painting.
Well!
Good morning!
You.
Sid. Nice to see you again.
-Why are you here?
-To paint.
Realty office likes a fresh coatbetween tenants.
But we're still here.
Well, they said you'd be gone.
We're not.
I've done this house before.
Did a pretty good job.
Won't have to redo the trim.
Oh, fuck--could you come back
tomorrow?
Tomorrow's Sunday.
Yeah?
New tenants move in on Sunday.
Where you movin' to?
Um, Butte, Montana.
Why?
Can't be any worse than Enfield,Arizona.
I've lived in Enfield my whole
life.
You hold this?
It's masking tape.
I use it to mask.
Do you ever use masking tape tomask?
No, I haven't.
[tape snaps]
Sorry I'm late.
The new girl is a moron.
What's that?
A going-away present.
Thanks!
A map.
I thought you might need it.
I do.
I had a map, I lost it.
Let's highlight your route.
Okay.
Here's Enfield.
Here's Butte.
Where?
Right there.
Okay.
[humming]
-Look at that.
-What?
-Right there?
-Uh-huh.
Halfway?
That's the town I was born in.
Where I grew up,
where my parents live.
Isn't that a coincidence.
Visit 'em.
Nope.
You're gonna be driving by.
They're not near the interstate.
I haven't even called them in
years.
You might as well visit.
Nope.
Why not?
Wouldn't know 'em.
Wait, let me.
Pretty good.
I'm starving.
-Oops.
-Hello?
[mellow music]
I'm lucky I don't have to kill
'em.
What?
If these walls were any darker,
I'd have to put a layer of killdown first
so that the old paint
wouldn't bleed through.
Oh.
Yep.
Kill is an alcohol-based paint.
Covers the old paint
so that you'd never know
it was there, but--
but when it's drying,
it gives off these fumes.
The fumes are noxious.
Noxious fumes.
They, uh, they'd probably
find us on the floor,
unconscious.
"They"?
Yeah, the "they" that find
people unconscious.
-Nick.
Nick, the man I live with.
I guess he'd be the "they."
Yes.
He'd find us,
and he'd be surprised.
It was the drive
that killed us.
Ugh.
San Antonio to Seattleis just too many hours in a car.
-If we'da flown, we'da made it.
-No!
Things were all right in bed.
Yeah, but the rest of the time,they were awful.
-Really?
-Yeah! Nick,
we couldn't stand each other.
When we got to Enfield,
I dumped you, and, uh,
we just stayed.
Why didn't you go on to Seattle?It was your car.
Big trees scare me.
I'm thinkin' about stealin'
a TV.
What?
I'm thinkin' about stealin'
a TV!
Good!
I'm, uh, done in here,
except for the ceiling.
But I'm gonna hold off on that
until you've got
your furniture out.
Uh, I don't think we're gonna betaking too much
of the furniture, though.
No? How come?
It's ugly.
No it's not, it's...
That's fine, it's--it's
a pretty good-looking couch.
Oh. It's not a couch, it's a
sofa bed.
And it weighs 2,000 pounds.
Wow.
It's not--it's not ugly, though.
I-I tell you, we had a sofa bedwhen I was a kid,
it was the world's ugliest sofabed,
it was orange and red and purplestripes.
Phew.
You're not gonna take it,
you're just gonna abandon it?
Wow.
Can I have it?
It's yours.
Excellent!
Nick's gonna steal a TV!
Who are you?
The painter.
He's really gonna do it?
He says yes!
We have to talk.
About the crime?
There's no crime.
Nick's gonna steal a TV.
That's just an expression.
I've never heard that
expression.
It's makin' the rounds.
College students use it.
Where's he stealing it from?
-His mall.
-You want him to know?
He knows! He doesn't care.
Do you care?
I'm interested.
Crime's interesting.
It's not a crime.
-It's justice.
-It's poetic justice.
-How?
-They fired him.
He's got motive.
-Who is this guy?
-The painter.
-Sid.
He needs you at the store.
He needs me?
You lookin' or buyin'?
[car engine hums]
[tape peeling]
[soft music]
This is what you do?
I also mow lawns.
Which is your career?
Painting.
I'm an inside person.
Not a lot of lawns in the
desert.
That's true.
You've got a subtle tan.
Why, thank you.
Do you wanna get stoned?
Yeah.
This kinda painting--
Mm?
For people I won't know?
It's boring.
Really?
It's not very good.
It's homegrown.
-But it'll get you fucked up.
-Really?
Oh, it'll take you someplace.
We'll see.
-Thought about American?
-Nope.
I own an American set.
I'm very satisfied.
I want Japanese.
Now, you see, the thing is,
the thing is...
$150 gets you very little inthe way of Japanese technology.
Gets you that TV.
It's for my parents.
-Your parents?
-Yes.
Is that a problem?
No, it's just that,
you know, I never...
'scuse me.
Miss, I've got your receipt.
Oh, great.
It's all you need.
Thanks.
Just...take your receipt,
out back at the loading dock,
and they'll give you your
brand-new, beautiful TV set.
I get the TV?
Out back.
They'll help you load it in yourcar and everything.
Think about American.
Mostly Japanese parts, anyhow.
Excuse me, I just--
Miss, I'm dealing with this
customer here.
Perhaps you'd like to ask
someone else.
You mean you can't help me?
Not really. No.
It's very small.
Yes it is.
[ethereal music]
[car engine humming]
Excellent.
Maybe I should just leave it
packed.
What?
Oh, come on!
You stole this,
you gotta look at the loot.
Come on. Here, you hold the
bottom and I'll lift it up.
It'll be easy.
Wait.
Thought I heard the police.
Ha-ha-ha!
What?
-What?
-You're stoned.
Me?
You are stoned!
Busted.
Busted is right, Mr. Bunny Eyes.
I can't believe that you're
painting my house stoned.
Well, I'm just..I'm just a little stoned, but...
-Oh yeah.
-...I'm not that stoned.
-Oh no?
-No.
Carol is really stoned.
You got Carol stoned?
Very stoned.
I didn't think she liked you.
She doesn't.
But she likes getting stoned.
She does.
There's nothing like drugs
to create a quick and shallow
friendship.
Wow.
You didn't fool around.
This is the nicest thing
I've ever owned.
[car engine humming]
[rock music]
[tires squeal]
[dialing]
[dial tone]
[lively singing]
-Nice speakers!
-Yeah!
Fuckin' Nick.
Hi, kids.
-Hola!
-Hi! Come see.
I should've had him steal me onetoo.
Well, you can come over
and watch.
-You're moving.
-Oh yeah, right, right.
How's the painting going?
Too many distractions.
I'll be at it all night.
You have bad work habits.
Not when I'm actually working.
I better get set up in the
kitchen.
It makes TV seem
very futuristic.
Because you're stoned.
I'm hardly stoned.
Need some eye drops?
It was homegrown!
Gets the red out.
Thank you.
Need help?
Yeah.
Okay.
Tilt your head back.
Beth.
Stop moving.
-Got it?
-Got it.
Next eye.
Wait a minute.
He really wants to get
in your pants.
My pants are taken.
-Why don't you go for it?
-He likes you!
Got it.
Where the hell's Nick?
Probably getting drunk
with the stock boys
is probably what he's doing.
Beth.
Listen.
He's gone?
Yeah.
[soft chatter from TV]
Where'd he call from?
He said the highway.
He said he would've called you
but your phone is disconnected
'cause you're moving.
Do something, I've gotta do
something, do something.
I mean, I've gotta be out of
here tomorrow.
I gotta be out of here on
Sunday.
You can come to my place.
No, I mean, I...I just...
He's gone.
Fuckin' Nick.
[choir singing]
Fill 'er up.
You live there?
Nah. Closed at 7:00.
I got no one to shop for.
Shit! Fuckin' wind.
Yeah.
So what does it mean?
-What?
-The wind?
High pressure field coming in?
Not like that,
you know what I'm asking.
You're an Indian, right?
-I'm Navajo.
-Yeah.
So you're in tune with this
stuff, right?
Thirteen bucks for the gas.
All right, here's a--
here's a twenty.
So what does the wind mean?
You know, like an omen or
something?
Uh, change is coming
to the people,
spirit of freedom
is walking the land?
-That kind of meaning.
-14, 15...and 5 makes 20.
The wind?
It's just the wind.
Like I'm just Navajo.
-So that's it?
-Yeah.
Shit.
Be better if it meant something.
Yeah.
[engine revs]
[tires screeching]
[rock music]
He said he needs to be alone
again.
He needs to learn about himself.
To make a fresh start
in a new town.
He said he was sorry.
Aww, he's an asshole.
He's always been an asshole.
You'll be all right.
Yeah.
I'm here.
I know.
Ready for another?
-Oh no, no thanks.
-We're fine.
Nick comin' in?
...his father saw him
and had compassion and ran
and fell on his neck
and kissed him.
And the son said unto him,
"Father, I have sinned against Heaven ..."
[radio clicks off]
[map rustling]
[horn blaring]
[tires screeching]
[soft music]
[door creaks open]
You've lived here your whole
life.
Yeah.
You've never gone anywhere.
Traveling has no allure for me.
None?
Maybe through time.
That's not offered.
So I stay here.
Why?
It's my home.
I belong here.
I'm serious.
My father says that if you stayin one place long enough,
then your luck knows where to
find you.
Well, maybe that's my problem.
Maybe it is.
Sugar?
Think your father
knows the truth?
He's a bartender.
Oh.
He's lived here his whole life.
Are you all right?
Yeah.
Just must be the paint fumes.
[sighs]
It's a pretty moon.
Yeah, I guess.
Hey, Beth?
Mm?
Leave it behind.
Leave what behind?
Unhappiness.
-That was a bad answer.
-No, it's true.
It's not.
Come hold me.
What?
Come hold me
and you'll be happy.
Right.
And I'll find happiness
in your arms.
Yeah.
In you.
Yes.
That's bullshit.
I'm sorry, Sid,
but you have to find happiness
in yourself.
No, that's wrong.
People tell you that,
but that's wrong.
It's not.
It is. I know people
who have that--
that happiness from within,
and that--that happiness,
that's just them being pleased
with themselves.
-It's not enough.
-No, you're being naive.
I mean, you've just been
stuck in this town,
you don't know.
I know that two people
can meet each other and...
like that, it's...it's like
they've never been alone.
-But that's not life.
-Who says?
That's...We never met before
last night,
but we know each other.
I don't know you.
You know me.
No, I don't.
Yes you do.
No.
I know you wanna fuck me.
Is that what you know?
[intense drumming]
[mellow music]
[lights click on, door opens]
'Scuse me.
I'm looking for my parents.
My mother, my father, they
used--
Oh.
Hello.
This is my house.
I mean...this is the house
I grew up in.
Well, this is his house now.
-All right, nice to meet you.
-And he's deaf.
-Nice to meet you!
-He's stone deaf.
-And yelling doesn't help?
-No.
Right.
My name's Nick, Nick Brown.
What's your name?
Elizabeth.
No.
Yes.
I know an Elizabeth.
Call her Beth.
[crickets chirring]
I'd like to stay right here.
I have to be out tomorrow.
In this moment.
Enjoying this moment.
Moment's gone.
It can go on as long as we want.
Have you ever been
in a relationship?
No.
I was married,
but, uh, it wasn't really a
relationship.
You weren't married.
Yeah, two years right out of
high school.
Do I remind you of her?
Oh, no.
Oh, thank God.
What happened?
She disappeared.
Was she ever found?
Not by me.
No, I didn't go look.
She wanted to meet someone new
and I asked her why.
She said "Because he won't knowme from before, just now.
Just--just what I am now."
But you can't escape who you are
no matter what, all those yearsare there.
She didn't understand that if
you leave
they're still there in you.
But they stop being clear.
You stop knowing who you are andwhat you want.
You stayed here, you know who
you are?
I see the lawns I mow and the
houses I've painted,
friends I know, my parents.
I'm constantly reminded
who I am.
You know what you want?
I want you.
Oh.
I want to be inside you.
Oh, good.
Come here and put it inside me.
No, I want to be able to put
myself inside of you.
Doing this is as close as you
get.
Come here.
I love you.
Come inside me.
Beth?
Yeah?
What do you want?
Come inside me.
When did he move here?
Do you know where the people
before him went?
-No.
-You're sure?
Yes, he doesn't remember
anymore.
So he can't help me.
No.
I lost my parents.
Did you lose both of them at thesame time?
Is that a joke?
No.
Then, yes.
I lost them both at the same
time.
I lost mine one at a time.
Last year.
I'm sorry.
It's tragic.
They were six months apart.
Body failures, separate body
failures.
I'm--I'm really sorry.
Well.
Thanks for the sandwich,
it was delicious.
First--first, my father's heartkept stopping and starting.
Attacks?
Yeah.
My mother and I would go to
visit him in the hospital
and--and he'd grab at us.
He'd just grab our arms
and hold on.
That's really--that's very sad.
But I gotta be going.
Right before my mother died
she said to me,
"Elizabeth, you're adopted."
Did you find your real parents?
No.
Two are enough to lose.
I'm not alone, I have my
grandfather.
Listen...
...I have to go.
I'm sorry.
He's stone deaf.
[soft music]
I have to go.
[choir singing]
[giggles]
What's wrong?
I'm happy.
[thunder crashes, rumbles]
No.
No, no, you see, you have to beable to help me.
This is not a prank.
This--this is my home phone.
This is an emergency.
Yes it can, yes it can, it can
be done.
Someone there can hook the phoneback up.
It's not like a phone guy came
to our house
to disconnect the phone.
Nobody came to our house.
Someone just flipped a switch
somewhere.
Somewhere there, where you work.
Or plug--plugged something intoa computer
and the phone stopped working.
They turned it off, they can
turn it back on.
I know.
I know it's the weekend.
I know, call them at home.
They'll have a computer at theirhouse.
They'll--they'll have
a phone thing
to hook up into
the real computer.
That's how these people live!
They'll be glad to do it.
I can't have the police go to myhouse.
That won't work.
No, it's you, Janet,you have to be able to help me.
I gotta phone home, I can't
wait, it could be too late.
Janet, please.
You got--you gotta help me.
Please, you can reconnect me.
Janet, don't hang up!
Don't hang up!
You fucker!
You heartless fucker!
[choir singing]
[muffled alarm clock]
Good morning.
Hi.
I, um, didn't want to wake you.
Oh, I'm awake,
I'm a morning person.
Oh.
I'm not.
Why don't you come back to bed?
I can't.
Gotta pack.
Where do we start?
No, no, you paint.
Okay.
[wind chimes twinkling]
Oh, God.
[fly buzzing]
[motorcycle approaching]
The phone work?
No.
How was he?
Young.
A little weak on tenderness
but long on juice?
Long on conversation.
Mm.
Did you need talk?
I guess I did.
Good.
What are we doing?
Beth.
I don't know. Shit.
I mean, I was in Flagstaff
for two years
before you guys got here.
I mean, I've been here for fiveyears.
Yeah.
This state's driving me crazy.
What are you gonna do?
Well, I got no money.
I've got some.
I can't take it, I mean,
you're being great but I--I...
I'm gonna be gone,
we won't see each other again
and I won't send it.
I won't, I'll forget or I'll
just never get around to it
or just--I don't know.
Just...shit.
I--I'm just gonna sell
all this shit,
but I don't want any of it.
Just my car and my clothes.
Okay.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry,
just I shouldn't have fucked
this kid last night, you know.
I just--I should've slept.
Now I've got all this stuff to
do today and I'm tired
and I'm all churned up,
I'm in a fucking mood.
Let's do things,
let's get you busy.
Okay.
Uh.
You get all the stuff that you
want to sell
and, uh, I'll make some yard
sale signs.
No one's gonna buy my shit.
It's all junk.
That's what people buy at yard
sales.
[soft music]
Hi, is there something specificyou're looking for?
Yes.
Actually, everything,
I don't have anything.
Nothing?
I just moved to town.
My husband passed away and Ididn't want to have our things.
They were too familiar.
You can have everything.
For?
Three hundred dollars,
all of this stuff.
Everything, um,
stuff in the boxes
and there's a few more chairs
inside the house
and a table and a mattressand a couch but it's a sofa bed.
It folds out, it's very
comfortable.
Oh, my, I don't know.
Everything?
Yeah, everything.
Except the TV,
the TV's not for sale.
Maybe some nice turquoise
jewelry?
I don't think she really wears
jewelry.
How about a nice Diné rug?
What, as a present?
No.
What about that?
That will make her laugh.
That's authentic,
it's very expensive.
You got something like that
but fake?
I'm sorry, what's your name?
Oh, um, could you just leave
the name part blank?
I won't have an account
and I'll have to find a place
to cash it for me.
You're all loaded up and ready
to roll.
You did all the work.
Oh, we're a full service outfit.
I'd come and help you unload it
except I've got
to finish painting.
But, uh, my lovely assistant,
Carol,
here would be happy to help.
-Wouldn't you?
-Sure, sure,
I'll follow you in my car.
And I'll come by tomorrow with
my truck and the sofa bed.
Oh, don't forget these.
Oh, yeah, of course, thanks.
Thanks a lot.
Oh, thank you,
you've given me a home.
I'll be right along.
That had to be history's most
efficient yard sale.
I know.
It's true.
I'm sorry that Sid stuck you
with the unloading.
Oh, that.
[laughter]
No problem.
He kind of bites my butt.
But he's okay.
Yeah, he is.
Oh, well, listen,
I'm probably gonna be gone
before you get back.
You know, I was thinking that,
uh,
maybe we could be roomies,
you know?
Roomies.
Just until you figure out
what's next.
Hm, hm.
Uh-uh-uh, I can't, I can't.
Why not?
'Cause if I don't go now I'll
just wind up staying with him
and he just--he gets to me too
much, you know.
I can't.
You've done worse.
We both have.
Mhm.
[laughter]
Sid?
Hi.
I'm sorry about the sofa bed.
Oh, it's all right.
I didn't really need one.
When my friends get drunk
they just throw up
and sleep on the floor.
But I gave it to you.
Well, you--you gave me a lot
more.
It's all even in this
department.
Feel me.
Yeah.
You're hard again.
I want you.
All the time.
Oh, shit.
Mm.
I just fleeced a widow.
No, you didn't.
Yeah, I did, it was all junk.
I gotta go, take a couple of
aspirin.
Funny, I didn't think I had
enough to drink
that I would have a hangover.
You just feel bad for her
like I feel bad for her,
'cause her husband died.
Yeah?
Yeah.
That's about the saddest thing
there is.
Losing someone you love.
It's never happened to me.
If you died...
I couldn't stand life.
I have to go now.
New people are gonna be here.
-Go to my house.
-No.
Just while you're looking for aplace.
No, I gotta go.
Really, there's a friend
of mine,
I know she's got a place in
Agawam.
No. Agawam? No.
No, I don't know where I'm gonnago, just somewhere else.
Well, you--you can call me whenyou get there.
I'll give you my number.
Sid.
I'm going away, you're making meway too important.
You just met me yesterday.
And today I love you.
Oh, Jesus, one day.
That's not important, it doesn'tmatter if it's a day or a year.
It can happen in a second.
No, that's a fucking animal
thing, I've done that.
I meet men, I go home with them,and I just stay.
There's no decision involved,
it's just like--
it's just what I do.
That way I don't have
to lead my life,
I can just lead theirs.
I can't keep doing that.
-We're not that way.
-What way are we?
We're passionate, we're
comfortable, we're--
It's been passionate,
it's been comfortable.
But it hasn't been important
like you're making it.
It is important, you know that.
It was a night, it was fun,
it was some great fucking
but it's just something that
happened.
It's not just something that
happened, we're it.
I'm the one for you.
-The one?
-Yeah.
I'm twenty-fucking-eight years
old, I've had lots of ones.
-You're just the latest.
-No.
I'm the last, you found me
and it can go on forever.
Oh, oh, Sid.
Forever.
You've gotta understand
it's just talk.
It's not.
It is, it is!
I mean, come on, these things
you say?
Come on, what,
that if I died
you couldn't stand life,
that's--that's--that's--
-What? That's true.-No, you won't know when I die.
You won't be there.
You'd want me there.
If I wasn't there it wouldn'tmatter who was, you'd be alone.
No.
Beth?
-Beth, you love me.
-No.
How--how do you feel?
Think.
You love me.
I care about you.
You have to be with me.
No, I care about youbut I'm an adult, I can say no.
That's what makes you an adult?
Yes, I can say no.
No, I won't do that. No, I won'thave that. No, I can't.
You can say no to me?
Yes.
I'm going.
Beth.
Have some place to go.
I don't.
-Why don't you--
-Don't tell me what to do.
-What are you gonna do?
-I don't know.
[soft music]
Beth!
Beth?
[paint cart rattling]
She's not here.
Shit.
Excuse me.
Who are you?
Painter.
You're Nick.
Yeah.
The Indian Chief.
Shit.
You're too late.
She's gone.
I got that, where'd she go?
She didn't say.
Shit!
This really bothers me.
Do me a favor?
What?
Act normal.
This is my house.
You're in my house
and I'm tired of there
being strangers in my house.
This is not your house,
you're gone.
I'm painting for the new peoplewhose house this is going to be.
You're gone, they're not here
yet, I'm here.
Well, I guess that makes this
my house.
Mind if I look around?
Sure, make yourself at home.
Aw.
No.
She left the TV.
Yup, she didn't seem to want it.
You're back.
Yeah.
Is Beth here?
No, you know where she went?
No.
Shit.
-You're too late.
-She's gone.
Who is this guy?
Beth's new boyfriend.
What?
Is this true?
Not really.
Not really?
Not really!
What?
Did you fuck her?
I don't tell.
Jesus.
The next day.
Well, that's the world, huh?
Won't even wait a day anymore.
-You left her.
-Yeah, I didn't fuck anyone.
You didn't find anyone.
No, I didn't leave her for
another person,
I left her for another place.
Which I think is a little more
excusable!
I don't!
Well, this is none of your
fucking business.
-I think it is.
-Why?
'Cause you fucked her?
No, that gives you no business
in my life.
Leave him alone.
-Why?
-He was nice to Beth
when you treated her like shit.
No.
No, she was vulnerable
and he fucked her!
I loved her.
Yeah, right!
-He was there for her.
-And I wasn't?
You were halfway to Butte!
Yeah, but when I was here I wasthere for her.
Nick, you were never really
here.
Is that what you think?
I'm just telling you thatthey were good with each other.
And I brought them together.
It seems I'm blessed
in what I do.
I do wrong, it turns out right
that I've done right,
so it doesn't really matter
what I do.
No, no, because
if you hadn't left
I wouldn't have been with Beth.
I'd be done painting,
I'd be home.
Oh, be glad you have a home,
asshole.
Nick!
If you were such the happy
couple why isn't she here?
Because after three years with
you she wanted to be alone.
And why wouldn't you go be alonewith her?
It wasn't offered.
People aren't gonna offer you
anything.
You gotta take what you want.
Well, you can't take
another person.
They've got to give themselves
to you.
Oh, that's very wise.
But not very true.
I sell TVs, people don't know
what they want.
I have to show them.
Well, I--I couldn't.
That's too bad.
'Cause that's why she left.
To maybe be closer
to what she wants.
And what is that?
How the hell would I know?
What do I know?
What the fuck do I know!
I know that what I want isn't
out there!
It isn't in here, it isn't
inside, it isn't outside!
It doesn't exist
but he wants her!
And he isn't doing shit
about it!
I--I--I can go after her.
Yes, you can.
Fuck.
Oh, Sid, where are you gonna
look?
I don't know.
-Congratulations.
-Thank you.
You've just fucked up another
person's life.
-No.
-He's not gonna find her.
-He might.
-It's a big planet, asshole!
[engine revs]
Shit!
-She'll head for her parents.
-What?
She'll head for her parents,
they're in Florida.
Take Route 10, keep going east.
And around 11, start checking
every roadside motel.
The budget ones, if you do thatyou'll find her.
How do you know she's on the
highway?
When you don't know
where you're going,
you drive on the highway.
I didn't finish painting.
I'll finish.
[tires screech]
Nick?
Yeah?
What you've been doing you can'tdo anymore.
I understand.
It's not that you can't do it.
It's--it's that I don't want youto do it.
Anymore.
Okay.
Nick.
I've stopped.
I went to my parents' house.
Like you said to.
And?
There was this...
ancient man.
This giant man in the doorway...
...and I thought,
"That's my father.
My, how he's aged."
He was very tall.
He was too tall to be my father.
And he was wearing a long, longrobe and I thought...
it's a trick, he's sitting on
my mother's shoulders.
And then out from behind himcame this beautiful, young girl.
[soft music]
Beth.
Yeah, Beth.
And...
...they sang to me.
London bridge is falling down
Falling down, falling down
London bridge is falling down,
my fair lady
It was very touching.
I'm sure.
It was.
It was very touching.
Shit.
I hate talking to you.
[soft, bright music]
[choir singing]