--== McEphie ==--
For latest releases visit moviesnipipay website
That was a time of uncertainty.
That was a time before chaos
in an already chaotic world.
That was the time to escape.
Anyway...
I just want out.
Have some of these!
Hey! Get out of the way!
That was a time of yet another drought.
That was also a time for wishing.
Hey! My!
I have dreamt of living by the sea.
That was my simple wish.
Sheesh, she was moaning wildly!
And in the middle of the day!
Americans really are something else.
They don’t care.
She was faking it, I’m sure.
It's so easy to fool guys
when it comes to sex.
- We'll be having changes in our procedures.
- Is that what you do?
The hotel is getting
deep-cleaning disinfection materials.
…and we will all be trained
on how to use them.
The world has more important problems
than your tittle-tattle.
Why are you late?
- Sorry, sir.
- You drive me nuts.
You heard it on the news,
there's already local
transmission of Covid.
- He came from abroad,
- I'm not surprised.
- but he still got infected.
- The infection is spreading everywhere,
Imagine how many people
he got into contact with
- even before they found out he's positive?
- even in rich countries.
- I bet he's infected a lot of people.
- What more here where it's crowded?
It probably won't be that bad
since we're broken up
across different islands.
Manila's going to take
the brunt of it.
The virus won't reach here.
There's even talk of Martial Law
in our Facebook group.
I think it's better than have the virus
take us down one by one.
Probably not.
It's not Martial law.
That's not the same as a lockdown.
Well, the President did say
we're going to be fine.
"Nothing to be scared
of this corona virus thing."
That's what he said-
- in the news.
- Mylene, Ditas-
do you have something to share?
Ditas has something to share.
Maybe you'd like to get to work?
Hey, Toni, maybe
you could get me an advance.
You just had an advance, My.
It's called pool saving for a reason.
Everyone waits for their turn to collect.
You know that!
Good evening, sir. Welcome to Playa.
How may I help you?
One room. Two nights.
Do you have any reservations, sir?
None? Okay, I'll check it for you, sir.
It's such a small amount, sheesh.
Two thousand pesos is not small.
I'm just the treasurer, Mylene.
- It's not my money to give!
- Fine, fine. You're so fussy.
Like it's a big deal!
Would you like a room
near the beach?
Okay, I can give you Casa Agua.
Here's your card, sir.
Go straight then turn right.
Would you like me to accompany you, sir?
That was a time of unexpected encounters
or chances where hope could spring.
YOU AND ME AND THE END
Hello?
Hello, Abby, please…
It's Niko's birthday today, right?
Can I talk to him?
I just want to greet him.
Can I just-
Will you let me greet him at least?
Damn it, Abby!
He's my son, too!
We're fine without you!
Don’t bother thinking about us, Martin.
I hope this is the last time
we ever speak to each other.
Forget about us. Bye!
Shit! Shit!
I won't do it.
We're good, I won't call.
I just thought you were dead.
We're good.
Go on, miss. Get on
with your business.
It's okay. I can come back
when you're gone.
No, do it now.
Why, are you afraid of me?
Do I look like a psycho?
You look lonely.
But if you're going to kill yourself,
can you not do it on my shift?
Blood is messy.
You'll give me a hard time.
This is a no smoking hotel.
That day...
I thought of living a better life
just to get to know her.
- So many guests are checking out.
- That day...
I didn’t understand the tension
that I was feeling.
Either way...
It’s not fear.
More of concern
for him.
It's insane!
Everyone's losing
their heads over Covid.
I have a relative,
an OFW in Lombardy-
Do you know where that is?
That's in Italy.
She's worried because
she doesn't have enough saved up.
She won't last very long
without a job.
Not unlike many of us here.
So I suggest you don't slip up.
If the management starts
asking questions, well…
Hello, sir.
Here's the soap, shampoo, toothbrush,
and toothpaste that you requested!
Why did you bring these?
Sir?
The lady who did the cleaning earlier,
she's the one who forgot to replace those.
I told the reception I want her
to bring those over.
Ah, sorry, sir. We have
a shifting schedule per area.
But here's what you needed.
Is there anything else
I can help you with, sir?
Nothing.
- Ah, miss.
- Sir.
If I call for room service,
can I request that she be the one
to bring the order?
Ah, that's the Food
and Beverage department, sir.
We're assigned to different
departments here, so--
Wow, like it's a big hotel.
Do you remember the name of
the housekeeper, sir?
I can relay a message
when she gets off work.
Or did she cause you any trouble?
You can make a complaint--
Mylene. That's the name
on her nameplate.
Oh, it's My!
Okay, sir, I know her.
Can you tell her that
I want to see her?
In your room, sir?
Oh no,
it's starting to sound like
you're up to no good.
Maybe I should report you instead.
Well, then.
I'll let her know, sir.
Asshole.
I don't get why he's so
determined to see you.
I even told him to just
complain you to the manager
but he didn't want to.
What did you do?
Want to report him?
That's harassment.
Ah, no need.
You sure?
I'll just drop by,
see what he wants later.
- Want me to back you up?
- No.
- He looks like a thug.
- It's fine.
It's okay, Ditas.
I can do it.
- You're sure?
- Mm-hm.
I did some boxing you know.
I'll do it.
Hello?
Hello, sir. You need some assistance?
I knocked on his door.
And there... At that moment,
The end has begun.
Thanks for coming.
Come in.
No, thank you.
I just dropped by to say sorry
for whatever wrong I did
as an employee.
You told me not to kill myself, right?
See, I didn't do it.
But could you come inside for a bit?
Are you blackmailing me?
It's just that I don't have anyone
to have dinner with.
And you were right,
I am lonely.
You're lonely, too, aren't you?
I'm not some god who'll come
and save you, got that?
Sheesh, I'm just inviting you to dinner.
Why don't you eat at the dining area?
If I try anything stupid, point that at me
and pull the trigger.
Have a seat.
Nice to meet you, Mylene.
I'm Martin, by the way.
And there... At that moment,
The end has begun.
Is it good?
Sure.
I don't get to try
these dishes everyday, so
I'm savoring every bite.
Is that how it works?
Do things taste better
when you rarely get to eat them?
Duh.
Is that why I don't scare you?
With the number of men I've been with,
there are many who are far more wicked,
and far more attractive than you.
You're not the only gangster around here.
I'm not really a local.
I'm from Manila. Tondo.
But I got sick of that place.
Here,
the air is fresh, it's peaceful.
What about you?
It's obvious you're not a tourist.
- What's your read?
- Scammer.
You look like a scammer.
Scammer...
Want to order anything else?
Dishes you've never tried before.
Order all of them.
- Seriously?
- Yeah.
Hello, Jake!
Take my order. Yeah, room service.
For Casa Agua.
- Mylene? What are you doing there?
- I want one more Crispy Pata,
Bulalo, Steak,
and Assorted Fruits,
Iced Tea, that's all.
Oh, and Poqui-poqui.
Alright!
Yep.
You worked up an appetite.
You told me to order everything
I haven't tried on the menu.
Maldives has recorded
its first corona virus case
when two hotel employees
tested positive.
The authorities would not name the hotel...
Do you think the virus has reached here?
As in this hotel?
Some Chinese guests checked in here.
Are you scared to die?
I guess you aren't,
seeing as you already tried to.
I'm not scared of some virus.
I'll slap that bitch.
Sure you will.
Hey, mister.
You talk big for someone
who's holed up inside his hotel room.
Who are you hiding from?
What brings you here?
The truth?
Of course! No to fake news.
I'm Congressman Velez's bagman.
Ever heard of him?
Everyday I move bags of cash for him.
A lot of cash, different transactions,
all illegal.
Then one day it hits you,
you're so sick of your life and you wonder,
“When will I ever be this filthy rich”?
So I swindled the swindlers.
But they got tipped off before
I even got far so now
I'm wanted by Cong's men.
You asked me a question,
I gave you a straight answer.
Because you're full of shit.
- You're a scammer.
- What'd you say?
- Me?
Yep!
What the heck.
Want a slice of that?
Are you crazy?
Dragging me into your shit!
It's the end of the world, Mylene!
It's now or never!
I should not be smoking cigarettes.
But I treat myself with this one stick.
One per month. Only nine left.
But what use is waking up everyday?
Why do we go on living?
Sir?
You're concerned about me after all.
Your room's still clean, yes?
I'll get back to work.
And can you not think too much?
So you don't get any crazy ideas.
Don't you have a sibling
who's studying in Manila?
Yes, sir, I do. I should discuss
his trip with mother later.
What about your mom, Princess?
I'm chatting with her right now, sir.
Sir, I quit.
What did you say?
I'm resigning.
Why?
It's the end of the world, sir.
It's now or never.
Hey!
I swear, that woman
is not right in the head.
- My, have you gone crazy?
- Oh, no!
You're not even three months into the job,
now you're leaving?
What kind of reasoning is
"it's the end of the world"?
Pull it together!
Ditas, I'm just beating them to it.
Pretty soon they'll be cutting their losses
and have to let people go, I promise you.
And haven't you noticed?
The foreigners are scrambling
to get away from here.
This must have something
to do with that new guest!
Goddamnit, Mylene! What's wrong with you!
You can't be lusting over that?
He's no Prince Charming!
And god, he's so dark!
He looks like he's going to
beat you up every night!
Hey!
Hey, don't believe a word he says!
He's just tall, is all! My!
My! He's not really a blondie! It's fake!
I wanted to tell her,
“What the hell do you care”?
Not even my own mom
gave two shits about me.
She just dumped me in the streets.
And get this- you should
have seen her face!
She looked like an idiot!
She was so shocked about what I did.
Then what?
Then what happened?
Your mom dumped you in the streets?
I've already seen that on television.
It's true!
I grew up in an orphanage.
No kidding.
I got passed around a lot.
The streets taught me all I know
that's why men like you
don't scare me none.
Then
I became a prostitute.
I worked the streets for ten years.
But you know how it is.
Filthy. And it stinks.
So here I am. Turning a new leaf.
Look at you.
You don't believe me.
Hold on.
I'll show you
proof.
Come here.
Check this out.
See?
- Yeah?
- What's that?
- Dang! That's me!
- Whoa!
That's me! Gorgeous, right?
- Wow.
- Aren't I gorgeous?
I started out as a hostess,
then I got promoted to dancer.
- There.
- Who are those?
Look. They're girls
I work with at the club.
I was twenty, a full-time stripper.
- Your father?
- What, no.
He's one of my patrons.
I just didn't date him.
Too bad though,
he has a lot of money.
That's the downside of it.
I was selling love
but I had none left for myself.
I didn't have time for love and all that.
Yeah, right.
- Yeah.
- You never had a boyfriend?
Nope.
I'm not kidding.
How could I tell my boyfriend
that I’m a stripper?
True love.
Ouch!
True love my ass.
Did you quit your job
to find a real lover?
Who doesn't want true love?
What about you,
don't you have someone?
Huh?
Ah, nevermind. It figures.
That's why you…
Why do you ask?
Are you attracted to me?
I had someone. Abby.
Abby.
I got married to Abby.
Then she left me
when she found out about my job.
She took our son with her.
Wait, what?
You have a son?
Yes, one.
- Oh?
- A boy.
Yeah,
but they're not here anymore.
They're all the way in Mindanao.
Why Mindanao?
Abby wanted to get him away from me.
That's what I don't--
That's what I don't understand.
She took him away for no reason.
Or maybe there's a reason.
Plenty of reasons.
I just wasn't listening.
What's your plan when your pursuers
track you down?
Will you come with me?
To where?
To the end of the Philippines.
Man, can you talk straight?
Those morons won't catch up to me.
They'll get tired of it soon enough.
How long will you be staying here?
Are you sure you want to be
cooped up in here?
You're not even going out.
You're wasting the beach.
What about you?
Me?
Nothing.
Why did you quit your job
if you didn't plan on coming with me?
Were you serious about splitting the money?
Yeah, why?
Just like that?
You may not be a god, My,
but you're an angel.
The angel of my life.
In that case,
give me some of the cash.
Sorry,
I'm not an angel.
Once a hoe, always a hoe.
Wow.
- What?
- I thought we had something real.
Hey, don't fool yourself.
Besides, I just want to be happy
even for a little while.
I've never experienced that!
And...
It's easier to be happy
when you have money.
And isn't that what everybody wants?
To be happy?
Sure.
Even I just want to be happy.
I'll step out for a bit
to get some clothes.
You want something?
No.
Cigs.
Thank you.
I’m not sure if she’ll be coming back.
All I did was hope.
I need to cling to hope.
I don't really pray.
But I had to that night.
Maybe I’m just that desperate.
Hello, bro?
Hello bro. I'm in
McArthur Highway already.
You're close?
Okay, okay. Thanks, bro.
No problem.
- Thanks, bro.
- Anytime.
It's protocol. I got your back.
When will you be back in Manila?
My kids' classes are suspended
because of this darned Covid
but Digong won't announce a lockdown.
Well, I gotta get going, bro.
Sure. Stay alert.
Don't get caught here.
Like what you see?
Gorgeous, huh?
I have a new dress.
Jeez, calm down!
I wasn't gone for long.
Seriously!
I took a while because I bought
these button-down shirts,
shorts, and other things you need.
Look at this.
God, it's so cool.
Here, here!
It's a button-down.
I got it for you.
I bet it looks good on you,
check it!
You have to try it on later. But let me
see your phone. Give it here.
I'll save my number.
Give me that.
I forgot to give you my number.
There. So when you want me for anything,
Just give me a call.
I had you worried for a second, huh?
You thought I wasn't coming back?
In love with me already?
Madly.
Christ.
Get out of here.
Check this out.
Quickly! Try it on! Quickly! Come here.
Try it on.
I've been itching to see you in it.
Try it on, quick!
- Does it come in a different color?
- No! Try this on first. It looks so good.
There we go.
Looks so good.
Get in there.
Hoo!
Damn, man.
Hey!
Yum!
My?
Hello, sir!
Hi, Ditas!
Hello ma'am.
Towels?
Have a great time!
How does it feel every night,
you're in bed with a different--
In bed with different guys?
Nothing.
It's just work.
It's all psywar.
Some people use their heads for work.
Some people use their hands.
I use my whole body.
You're a scammer, too.
I sell wild fantasies, that's it!
Must be good to be out of the game.
It sure is.
Same with you.
Are you out for good?
I hope so, too.
If I can get away with it.
I wish the world would stop turning.
I hope so, too.
Fine, I'm coming with you.
To the end of the Philippines.
- Almost there.
- It's so far.
- It's so far. You blindfolded me ages ago.
- No, we're almost there.
- Come over here.
- Should I remove it?
No, don't! Don't remove it!
Okay.
Are you ready?
Yeah.
Okay.
Okay, one, two...
Three!
Happy Anniversary!
What's this?
It's our 25th anniversary,
did you forget?
- Ah, okay. Okay, 25 years.
- Yeah.
How old are we?
Doesn't matter.
We don't age. Come on.
Let's sit there.
Alright, sure.
Where's your spot?
- Here's money. Bring out the lobster.
- Oh, thank you!
Hurry, lay it on the table.
Where are you sitting?
- That's you. Right there.
- Alright.
And because it's our anniversary,
I'd like to reminisce...
The first time we met.
Alright, remind me.
- I was wearing a red dress.
- Oh, yeah.
Red dress, red lips,
red shoes, red everything.
You picked up my shoes
and chased after me.
But I didn't see you, I kept on running.
Running, running,
then you called out,
"Missy! Missy! Your shoes, Missy!"
Because that was in Italy.
Oh, I see.
- Wow.
- Lombardy!
Where?
- Somewhere in Italy.
- Ah.
It was in Italy.
Then I said, "I think we've met..."
- …"before."
- Yeah?
Those days, he was
the most important thing
and we were the only people
left in the world.
Those days, she was
the most important thing
and it felt like we're the last
people on Earth.
The appropriate procedures in containing
the citizens and the virus are in effect.
Citizens who disobey said procedures
may be imprisoned
for one to six months.
Citizens may also be fined for
20,000 to 50,000 pesos.
Meanwhile, in the United States,
cases continue to increase.
New York City is now the epicenter
with more than 50 cases reported.
My, are you ready yet?
Huh? Yes.
Yeah. I'll be right out.
Go reserve a spot for us.
My, we're the only guests here.
Let's go, I'll wait for you.
Huh?
I want steak.
Yeah, and… get our order in
so when I'm done, it'll be ready, okay?
Okay, then.
I'll see you there.
My, is everything alright?
Why were you in there for so long?
Are you okay?
Huh?
No, I'm okay.
I just made myself pretty.
Look. Is it pretty?
You don't even have to try.
- You're already pretty.
- You think so?
Should I have the steak brought out?
Ah, no, it's fine. You started drinking.
I'll start drinking, too.
- Whoop, hold on.
- Mark!
Let's get that for you.
Okay, okay.
- Thank you!
- Mark's still working.
- What's his name? Mark?
- Mark.
Cheers.
What should we toast to?
The end of the world!
- Okay, a toast to the end of the world!
- To the end of the world!
Cheers.
Let's dance.
Huh?
- I don't dance. There's no music.
- Come on! No, we're dancing.
Just bring out the steak.
♪ Even if  ♪
♪ you should ever  ♪
♪ leave me ♪
You know this song? Sharon?
- Of course.
- Hm?
♪ I will never ♪
♪ forget  ♪
♪ your kiss ♪
♪ - You're my first ♪
- Okay…
♪ love ♪
♪ In the beginning,
and in the end, only you ♪
♪ have brought  ♪
♪ - meaning  ♪
- I see you. Let's dance.
♪ to my life ♪
I'll dance for you.
♪ Even if ♪
♪ your memory  ♪
♪ should fail ♪
♪ My world ♪
♪ will not stop ♪
♪ turning ♪
♪ A star that you thought ♪
♪ has faded ♪
♪ but is only hiding behind the clouds ♪
♪ is like ♪
♪ your playful love ♪
♪ Didn't you say,  ♪
♪  'nothing is certain' ♪
♪ So if you find happiness,  ♪
♪  imagine no end in sight ♪
♪ I won't tell you  ♪
♪ not to  ♪
♪  change your mind ♪
♪ For as long as I'm with you ♪
♪ All my joys will last forever ♪
Damn, bro.
I thought we had a protocol, bro.
Bro, you didn’t tell me
that you upsetted the Cong.
I’ll be the one taking the hit
if I didn’t tell him where you are.
You’re already lucky to have me
because I’m giving you warnings.
Don't you call me bro
right now, bastard!
If I ever see you,
I'll shoot you myself.
Have a seat.
I’ll attend to your order.
Okay, yes, cuz. Thank you.
She's my cousin.
Working here at Playa.
Ah, yes. She seems familiar.
There aren't many guests left.
Ah, spiced pork liver.
That's delicious.
Try our local recipe.
That’s Playa’s special recipe.
It does look good.
How long will you be staying for?
Ah, we'll be on our way soon.
You should drop by the beautiful
attractions here in Ilocos Norte.
Pagudpud, windmill,
and what was that, bro?
- La Birhen Milagrosa of Badoc.
- Yes, La Birhen Milagrosa in Badoc.
We'll be sure to drop by.
Order some more.
Try the Halo-halo.
We have the best desserts in Ilocos Norte.
Let's eat, sir!
Ah, yes! Thank you!
Eat up.
Mylene, where's my gun?
Where did you put my gun?
Huh? I need it.
I'm asking you.
Where's my gun?!
You don't need it anymore!
You don't need it anymore, Martin!
You're carrying your past with you
as long as you have a gun on you!
I have a target on my back.
They're on my trail.
They're going to kill me
if I don't go back to them.
But damn those bastards,
they won't catch me alive.
I no longer say my prayers
but I tried to find God
during those times.
I need to know what is life for.
I need to know how He chooses to smite
those who sinned.
Who is to be saved?
Would a lover's plea be enough?
PRESIDENT: I am now
addressing the nation
together with the civilian,
military and police sectors.
The organizations that would count
in our enforcement of the laws
to protect the people
of the Republic of the Philippines.
Pardon my broken Tagalog.
For our fellow countrymen,
we stand together.
Do not panic.
Do not be stressed
of being unable to do what you want.
You may but with proper restrictions.
There are conditions due to the crisis.
The crisis is very, very clear.
Covid-19 is spreading
althroughout the country
including the Philippines.
This is too much, sir.
Please take it.
- Really? Okay.
- Thank you, sir.
The common restroom is at the back.
Sorry about this, Mylene.
We need to lie low for now.
We’re not going to stay here for long.
Congressman wasn't my first boss.
I've dispatched
and killed countless men.
I know I've earned a spot in hell.
All my life
I've been transacting with demons.
So when I met Abby,
I hid everything from her.
Especially my job.
I protected them from all of it
but it didn't last.
They had to get away from me.
It's probably for the best.
If you want to leave me, too, Mylene,
I would understand.
This is what I've always dreamed of.
To be a fisherman.
I'll row out far
into the sea at dawn
to get a hefty catch.
And when I come back in the afternoon,
you'll be there waiting for me,
you're with our child.
A small kid's holding your hand,
she looks like you.
Like me?
All of our children will look like you.
Then
I'll show you my catch,
it's ready for grilling.
Then you'll say, "Just
simmer it in vinegar!"
Because you're hungry.
That sounds nice.
Simple, but happy.
Is that alright with you?
Hello? Hello, Niko?
How are you? This is your daddy.
I miss you so much.
Daddy?
You're not my Daddy.
My Papa's right here.
Papa!
Hello? Niko, what are you doing
with my phone?
Hello, sorry. My son
answered the phone.
Who's calling?
Abby, I know you don't want
to talk to me.
Martin? Why are you so persistent?
You even used a different number.
Abby, please hear me out.
Don't hang up the phone.
I just wanted to tell you that
I won't bother you anymore.
I'll leave you and Niko in peace.
I just wanted to ask for forgiveness
for everything I did.
There's no need for that, Martin.
I've sworn you out of our lives
a long time ago.
That's good enough.
I'll change my number.
And if you'll keep harrassing us,
I'll put you in jail.
That is, if you're not already there.
Mylene?
Mylene, are you okay?
My?
Hey, you don't need to do that.
You're beautiful.
My…
Wha-
Mylene. Where are you going?
Hey, wait up. Don't--
What's the hurry? Mylene!
Did I say something wrong?
I’m sorry! Hey!
What did I say? Tell me.
My!
Go on, put on your lipstick!
If you want-
do whatever you want! Mylene!
My, wait up!
Wait. What is your problem?
What's the matter?
I have pancreatic cancer.
The doctor said I only have a year left.
It's the real reason why
I moved here from Manila.
The reason why I wanted to get away.
It's probably why
I came here with you, too.
Because I've got nothing to lose
if I took a chance on anybody.
What?
What kind of made-up story is that?
We're going back to Manila, alright?
We're going back to Manila.
We'll take you to the best hospital
and get a brilliant doctor.
We have a lot of money. You'll live!
Then you'll die?
You'll get killed when
they finally get to you!
Screw them, Mylene!
Screw them!
Shit, Mylene…
I'll bet my life on it,
I'll sell my soul to the devil.
I'll do anything, Mylene.
Anything. You will live!
Stop it. Martin, stop it. Stop this!
There's nothing anyone can do,
no medicine,
there's nothing more to be done!
Martin, you'll create
your own heaven on earth.
You'll create your own, hm?
Don't hold on to me.
Yet people always find a way.
Once they face death
and take responsibility
for their own actions.
You just had to give us
a hard time, Martin.
Now you're crawling back to us.
Be grateful that you're important to Cong.
You should know
you're not getting away with it
without a scratch.
I know that.
That's why I'll do everything
he wants me to.
As you should!
Not everyone gets a second chance, bro.
Martin?
Martin...
Keep driving.
Go straight.
Martin!
Go straight. Don't stop.
But you need help!
They won't catch me alive.
Son of a bitch!
I’m an action star.
Don't talk like that,
what's wrong with you!
What is life for?
Isn’t it for love?
Don't.
Don't move too much.
I just wrapped your wound.
You told me to keep driving.
Straight ahead.
To the end of the Philippines.
Somewhere by the sea.
We will live in your dream.