My people, the Chickasaw,
were a tribe of great and mighty warriors
who lived in the southeastern woodlands,
but in 1837 President Jackson removed
my people from their sacred homelands.
My English father and Chickasaw mother
traveled the treacherous
Trail of Tears into Indian Territory.
Once arrived, disease claimed my mother
and sent her spirit along
the white dog road to join our ancestors.
My father went east
to return to his prior life,
promising one day to return.
Raised by my mother's people,
my sister and I struggled
to survive in two worlds.
That of the Chickasaw who understood
the richness and beauty
of this new land...
- Papa!
Papa! Papa!
And that of the white man
whose greed brought nothing
but death and destruction.
OK, let's go!
Come on!
Yeah!
C'mon! C'mon!
Yeah! Whoo!
Yeah! Yeah!
- There we go!
- Come on, yeah, come on!
Come on, let's go!
Yeah, come on, let's go!
Come on, giddyup!
Here we go!
Come on!
Here they come!
Pick it up, Montford.
He's gainin'! Go, go, go!
Move it, Michael! Come on!
Yes! Yes!
Fourth place.
Whoa, whoa.
Yeah, Jack get you a Chickasaw horse
and you might have a chance.
Hey, hey, hey... you just be happy
it's your wedding day.
We both let you win.
Let's go again, then.
I'll beat y'all twice.
You're lucky you won, Montford Johnson,
or else I might not be marrying you.
- Even if I got second?
- Mm-mmm.
That's a strong-willed woman.
Hey! You ain't married yet.
Just 'cause I married your sister
don't mean you have to marry mine.
Figured it was only fair.
First place, whoo! Enjoy it.
It's your wedding gift.
Keep it, soldier. I want a redo.
No. Y'all better get cleaned up or else
none of you's coming to my wedding.
I warned you people.
Never bet against a Chickasaw pony.
Oh, I've got me some wedding gifts now.
Hey, I only saw six head of cattle.
Well, Union rustlers stole five,
I gave one to Granny.
Should feed her through winter.
Shameful, someone takes away
a man's livestock,
he takes away everything.
Most folks I know are turning their cattle
loose up in the hills,
so them blue bellies can't find 'em.
Rising Wolf, my Cheyenne friend.
So glad you could make it, brother.
You're a blessed man, my friend.
As the fires of war
rage across our lands,
let us celebrate the good things
that have brought us here today.
These gifts represent...
Who's that?
- Who is that?
- Jesse Chisholm.
Montford! I'm sorry,
I saw 'em coming this way.
I tried to talk 'em out of it
but they insisted.
Be careful with this commander.
They're looking for any good horses...
- Jack, hide the horses!
- and Confederate soldiers.
Adelaide, cover up Michael!
Whose place is this?
It's mine. How may we help you, Sergeant?
Well, I haven't killed no rebels
in almost a week now.
Well, you won't find any here.
This man a rebel, Chisholm?
Can't say I know him.
Well, looks like we got ourselves
a regular uprising going on here.
We got Cheyenne, Kiowa,
now why is it you Indians
sided with the rebs?
Could be 'cause the Union broke
every treaty it ever made with us.
Gets you to thinkin', don't it?
What's your name, Injun?
Montford Thomas Johnson.
Well, shoot, that ain't no
Injun name I ever heard before.
My mother was Chickasaw.
My father English.
That so? You must be waging
quite the internal conflict.
Your own personal civil war.
- Which side's winning?
- I'm Chickasaw.
Looks like you chose the wrong side.
Well, Mr. Montford Thomas Johnson,
I'm gonna search your place now,
and if I find one rebel on this property,
I'm gonna hang you for treason,
then I'm gonna shoot every other man here
and burn your place to the ground,
you understand?
Like I said, ain't no rebels here.
Better not be.
Spread out!
Hyah!
Go on, check that side. Come on!
Spread out!
You know when I was twelve,
my family moved out west
not too far from here.
Had big dreams
but wild Injuns didn't care
nothing about no big dreams.
They came in the night,
surrounded the caravan
and did what you wild Injuns do.
They kilt 'em all.
Except me...
'cause I hid under my father's dead body.
No horses or men, just these sorry cattle.
- We'll take what we can get.
- Montford! The cattle!
Sergeant! We depend on those!
Well, according to
Lieber Code, Article 39
marshal law extends persons and
property that are subject of the enemy.
That means we can take what we want.
Neither officers nor soldiers
are allowed to make use of their
position of power for private gain.
Article 42, Sergeant.
You an Injun lover?
Proud to say I am.
Well, howdy, mama.
C'mon on out here!
C'mon!
It's OK.
I think I could be an Injun lover too.
Sergeant! We need to move if you
wanna make the fort by sun down.
Move out! I'll see you soon.
Now get back over here,
we're gonna finish what we started.
They ain't ruining my day!
No, sir, everyone as you were, OK?
This is a blessed occasion
and I'm not gonna let
a little bit of rain spoil it.
Ah.
What you got there?
You know I'm always
gonna take care of you.
I know you will.
Let's go inside and you can
start taking care of your wife now.
Our Father God...
Like the spring, we are
grateful for the new blessings of life.
Meet your son, Edward Bryant.
We ask that you sanctify our children.
Halito, Edward Bryant.
Give them wisdom,
abundance, and love of family.
We give thanks for your Word
in this time of war
that sets brother against brother,
father against son.
You can't do this!
That's all we have! Please!
Give your angels charge over
the protection of our people
as they fall victim
to the ravages of war.
You're the fortress against those
who seek to harm us.
You are our refuge and our strength.
That's the last of 'em. Let's move out!
If it is Your will that
we should sit among our ancestors,
let it be as winters rest
and in the presence of Your fire.
It will be that way.
This drought is killing us.
Edward Bryant, come here, son.
One thing I learned from
the Manual Labor Academy is,
you gotta go deep in the ground.
You can't just scratch the surface.
Them gophers go to the academy with you?
Edward Bryant,
go on in the house. Now!
I got nothing left for 'em to take.
I got something for 'em.
What can I do for you?
This is the half-breed I told ya about.
Montford Johnson?
Yeah, that's me.
Lieutenant Richard Pratt.
I'm the new commander at Fort Sill.
You know General Lee surrendered at
Maddox Courthouse in Virginia? April 9th.
- War is over?
- It is indeed.
- Thank the good lord.
- Yes, ma'am.
We're all on the same side again.
I'd appreciate ya letting
your neighbors know.
Yeah, I'll let 'em know.
That we're on the same side.
Thank you.
Look, if you have a problem,
you come see me.
Ma'am.
Let's move out!
You need something?
Herd looks a bit thin.
Shame you can't provide
for your pretty wife.
Kind of takes away
everything it means to be a man.
Army's fat with cattle.
We'd be happy to sell it to someone
for half the wholesale price.
Someone meaning me?
Army's shifting focus.
Going after the wild Injuns.
Your kind.
We need eyes and ears.
An inside man to keep us informed.
You got the wrong someone.
- Such a nice family too.
- Pardon me?
You have a splendid day,
Montford Thomas Johnson.
That's Michael's whole life savings.
Confederate dollars! They're worthless.
We'll get through it.
I'm down to one cow.
We gotta pay Jack with something.
We can't lose him.
Papa, I'm hungry.
I know, son.
Let's find you something.
Someday soon this pasture
is gonna be filled with grazing cattle
from here to the horizon and back.
And one day,
you'll have a ranch of your own
filled with cattle with your brand.
A brand is permanent, it means
you're part of something much bigger.
You belong and belonging is forever.
Coyotes! There's coyotes out there!
I heard it too.
Shhh, look.
Jack, let's get them in the corral.
Open the gate.
- Shh...
- Where'd they come from?
- Montford!
- Look at all this. Shh...
♪ Lay down
What I can do ♪
Little doggy, lay down ♪
♪ Lay down
They must've
come down off them mountains.
That's Joe Carlton's brand.
This one here's Alec Cochran's.
That one right there, that's a maverick.
No brand so he's yours.
Mister, you just doubled
your stock overnight.
We gotta bring 'em back to
Joe and Alec in the morning.
Probably wrote 'em off as lost for good.
Yeah, but I bet there's more up there.
Four years is a long time
for cattle in the wild.
Yeah, I mean if they survived
the wolves and panthers and such,
there's gotta be more.
Do you see Joe or Alec, given their age
and health, lightin' up there after 'em?
No, hill country's too dangerous.
And full of cattle that have been
breading for years. Unbranded!
Well, what do you think Mr. Carlton?
You want me to agree to let you buy
any of my cattle you can round up.
Cattle I'd already given up on as lost?
- Yes, sir.
- And I don't do nothing?
You pay me my share when you
sell 'em to the next fella?
That's correct.
Go on! Go on up there and get 'em all!
- C'mon! C'mon!
- Hyah! Let's go!
♪ This sweat is dripping off my back
And onto me ♪
♪ They sayin' lesser man
Who lost his way ♪
♪ Well, if he's living hard
He's hardly living ♪
♪ Got me begging for mercy
Kill me then ♪
♪ I put my heart in there ♪
♪ Put my soul in there ♪
♪ You know I'll never stop
I ain't got nothing to show for it ♪
♪ My blood, sweat, and tears ♪
Whoo!
♪ 'Til I drop
So how come I ain't got ♪
♪ Nothing to show for it ♪
Couldn't even rope one.
I'm not fixin' to be brush poppin'
no beeves one after the other,
that's just plain crazy.
Gotta figure out how to get 'em to us.
Trap 'em.
Just like the devil traps
men with beautiful women.
Yup.
That's it right there. I got it.
Salt. We'll trap 'em with salt.
They'll do anything for a taste.
We got it!
I'll go fetch some water.
♪ You can talk about your farms ♪
♪ And your cattleman charms ♪
♪ But the cowboys... ♪
You, by the fire!
God-fearing Christians
just passing through.
Can we approach?
C'mon in.
Thank you, sir.
Evenin'.
We're just wandering,
me and my men, cold and hungry.
Find some solace at your fire?
Something smells good there.
Oh, you smell that boys? Ah?
I do my best.
So, uh...
what's, uh...
a boy like yourself...
doin' out here in the night?
Just looking for lost cows.
Mooooo.
Thank you.
What brings you gentleman
out to this part of the country?
We just rode up from Texas. We're hunters.
Thought we'd try and come scout some game.
What type of game you fancy?
Human kind.
You see, uh, these Mexican regulates,
they give us 150 pesos.
Comanche, Apache scalps.
We see, uh... any ol' red skin
scalp will do.
'Cause, uh,
a savage is a savage...
is a savage.
You all right, boy?
This scalp here,
that wouldn't make me a wooden penny.
Wrong texture, you see.
But I do have a few questions.
Have you seen any redskins around here?
No, sir. No Indians around
here that I know of.
You lying to me, boy?
I did see some soldiers, though.
No Indians.
Evenin'
Whoa! Easy there, Cochise!
We're all friends here!
You Texans have overstayed your welcome.
They always do.
Hey. Come on. You gonna leave us out here
with absolutely nothing?
- There's dangerous things out here.
- Keep the knife.
No knife, you get to keep your life.
Seems like a fair deal. Huh?
Don't get your britches
in a bunch there, chief.
You boys...
You boys are gonna regret this.
Threaten me again, I'll kill you.
Best believe when I say
I'm gonna do something, I do it.
I believe you would.
I'm gonna walk out of here, OK?
You better, cowboy.
Here, boy.
Let's move. No more fires.
We sleep in shifts.
Amen. I hear you, brother.
Looking good.
- You sure this is gonna work?
- Yes, sir. What comes in, can't come out.
Spread that salt around here.
Look! It's Papa!
Papa! Papa! Over here, over here!
Papa! He's home!
Edward Bryant, Mary Elizabeth.
Hey, welcome back!
Ah, y'all are a sight for sore eyes.
Oh, son!
Y'all find any cattle?
Oh, yeah! We found a bunch!
They're up there roaming,
more'n we can count!
- Oh, yes, ma'am!
- Well, where are they?
Oh, we just have to be a little
better prepared next time, that's all!
I was afraid that...
Oh, we're going back out there for sure.
- Oh!
- Yeah.
Gonna keep 'em in
that pasture right over there.
Gonna build a cattle tank,
fence off the draw.
Edward Bryant and I can handle that.
All right, yeah. Gonna bring back a bunch.
Yes, ma'am.
Seems like you both need
something to eat. Jack, please join us.
Oh, that'd be just fine. Thank you, ma'am.
Come on, come on, come on!
Aha! Look at that!
Told you, didn't I?
- Yes, you did!
- Now let's get these mavericks back home!
Sergeant, here they come!
There they are!
Go get 'em, trooper.
Go ahead and shoot 'em savage!
Hey, circle around!
Fire that gun and we'll
string you up on the spot!
- Those mavericks are mine!
- They branded?
'Cause if they ain't I got a real rancher
that says red devils rustled up 15 of his.
They look familiar?
- Yeah, they're mine.
- You lie!
You think anyone's gonna
care about a dead Injun?
Think about your wife and that little boy.
These belong to me!
Well, sir, I got a white man
who says they're his.
Who do you think the law's gonna believe?
This ain't right!
I consider all these wild cattle out here
property of U.S. Government.
I consider you wrong!
You wanna make some real money,
Montford Thomas Johnson?
Army's putting a premium on buffalo hides.
You realize you're taking everything
these people have? Huh?
Thinkin' is, no buffalo to hunt,
they gotta change their ways.
- Stay on the reservation.
- Yeah and what good is that?
Control and progress. Don't you get it?
It's why we always win
and Injuns always lose.
Always a pleasure, Monty.
Move out.
Next maverick we lay eyes on,
we brand it.
♪ I'm wearing out ♪
♪ These old leather boots ♪
♪ Working so hard ♪
♪ Paying these dues ♪
♪ I get my self up ♪
♪ But the rising sun can take all I got ♪
♪ Put it on the line ♪
♪ Long as I'm able ♪
♪ I'll push through ♪
♪ I'm gonna keep on ♪
♪ Keeping on ♪
♪ My aim is faithful ♪
♪ And true ♪
♪ What I do, I do for you ♪
I'll take 'em.
All right, thank you, Jesse.
Now we're square?
Montford Johnson, you're a good man.
♪ It's who I wanna be ♪
♪ Long as I'm able ♪
♪ I'll push through ♪
♪ I'm gonna keep on ♪
♪ Keeping on ♪
♪ My aim is faithful ♪
♪ And true ♪
♪ What I do, I do for you ♪
- Hey.
- Hey, sis.
Look at all this.
Mother would have been proud.
Father would be proud, too.
"Father."
Do you remember his face?
I do.
Thing is, I don't.
When the memories piece him together
for me, it just turns into a shadow.
- I've forgiven him.
- Not me.
Forgotten, not forgiven.
There's enough meat out there
to feed the tribes for months.
- You sure you're not hungry?
- No.
You can't imagine the stench.
Death.
Can't get it out of your mind.
Come up on some Kiowa looking hopeless...
What are they gonna eat?
Maybe God blessed us
so we could bless others.
Figure you'd pass
some of these on to the...
tribes hurt by the buffalo slaughter?
Sure. I'm sure they could use 'em.
Hey, isn't that Rising Wolf?
C'mon.
Whoa.
What happened?
We were...
We were camped near Lodge Pole River.
Soldiers appeared with the sun rise
and started shooting.
Which soldiers?
Long hair and his men.
They came from the north, Fort Supply.
Custer.
- Was there a battle?
- All of the men were out hunting.
We heard the gunshots and the screams.
It wasn't a battle, it was a massacre.
So sorry.
Black Kettle
had returned the night before.
He tried to make peace but the soldiers,
they kill him and his wife.
Shot all the horses before they
slaughtered the women and the children.
We got out who we could.
What can I do for you, brother?
We were on our way to
go to Jesse's, to trade.
I just left Jesse with a bunch of cattle.
Take whatever you need.
- You're welcome to stay at the homestead.
- Thank you.
We'll take the cattle...
but we have our own path to follow.
Ours will cross again.
Here! He's at the corral!
Let's go, c'mon. Over there!
Look out!
Come on, let's go. Let's go.
- Load it, come on.
- Come on.
Come on, hurry up.
Hyah, hyah, let's go!
Get out!
- Mommy!
- Go back to bed, E.B.!
Gotta push 'em back.
Move back, move back!
Let's go! Move!
Mary! Mary!
- Hyah! Hyah!
- Montford! The horses!
Don't worry about them! Give it to me!
Montford, you're shot.
Let's get that tended to inside.
- C'mon!
- Can we track 'em?
We'll track 'em in the morning.
Y'all go inside. I'll keep watch...
in case they come back.
In case they come back.
Ain't gonna get
nothin' for them horses.
There's that weasel right there!
Why the long faces boys?
- You believe this fella?
- He got some nerve.
Where's all the cattle?
Cattle? Oh. Must've slipped your mind
to tell us about the redskin
and the Black fella, who shot me.
Look at this fine head of hair
we have here boys.
This uniform says you'll hang!
What're you waitin' for?
That's right, Holden,
give him a shave.
You trying to scare me? Huh?
C'mon now...
Almost had me killed
and all my men killed.
For what?
This string of rancid horse meat?
We'll get the whole herd next time.
Hey, I do know
the whereabouts of plenty of Injuns.
A whole wagon load of scalps.
Sit.
Well, looks like they split up here.
Divided my horses.
One group went down yonder.
The other one went...
Well, well, well...
What is it?
Ammo pouch.
Indians use those?
No. No, they don't.
State ya business, Johnson.
Our business is with Lieutenant Pratt.
I said state your business or ride on!
As soon as I speak
with Lieutenant Pratt!
Mr. Johnson, how can I help you?
Lieutenant, you told me to come
see you if I ever had a problem.
My office.
Double time, thank you.
What is it?
We's found it at the rustlers' camp.
Sure it belongs to someone round here.
- Thievin' Indians always stealing from us.
- Thievin', huh?
Ya know, the past two years white men been
rustling stock all over the territory.
Talkin' about "Indians done it."
You create enough bad blood between
farmers, ranchers, and Indians,
- we end up forced on a reservation.
- If that is the case,
I certainly don't approve of the means,
but you must admit the ends do render
a safer United States.
Now the Indian must
fall in line with American society
or he will become extinct.
I've seen how the Army tries to civilize
by slaughtering innocent
men, women, and children
- and calling it progress.
- This is a war, Montford!
Our orders are total war
and the casualties will continue
to mount so long as the savages...
- You're the savage!
- Sergeant.
Mr. Johnson, I do believe if we
kill the savage, we save the man.
Sir, seventh cavalry has arrived.
Good luck tracking your rustlers.
I thought that was your job.
Let's get outta here, Jack.
Better be careful, Colonel!
Some day you might run into
some Indians that are ready for ya.
Easy, Montford. Easy.
Colonel Custer. Welcome to Fort Sill.
Those rustlers, they was
looking to take more than my cattle.
Home don't feel safe no more.
How many head we got?
Fifteen hundred beeves give or take.
Why you ask?
Drive 'em straight to market,
Abilene, Kansas.
Use the money to build
a new ranch out west.
Whoa... That's a big drive with 1500 head.
We'd have to go through Cheyenne,
Comanche, and Kiowa territory.
Yeah, just gotta ask
permission from the tribes.
Montford Johnson,
you are an honorable man.
Here assembled are
the great chiefs of many nations.
You can lead your cattle
through our lands.
In return, our people can have
some of your cattle
if they are in need.
There will be no hostility between us,
no blood to stain the grass.
We want it kept clean and pure.
Agreed.
Good.
Whoa, whoa. Whoa, whoa, whoa.
- Can I help you?
- Why, yes, sir, you can!
Hey, cousin Montford!
Do I know you?
We're cousins.
My grandfather was the brother
to your grandma, I'm Chub Moore.
I don't ever remember
my grandma telling me about
a cousin with the unusual name of Chub.
Well, sir, here I am.
I been living over near Blue Creek.
I heard things been
going real well for you.
That's your given name? Chub?
No, sir. Clarence.
Folks started calling me Chub
because I like to eat and,
well, sir, I tend to get big and 'round
around the middle. Ma'am!
What can I do for you, Clarence?
Well, times been tough, lately,
especially for some of the hard working
families around here.
A lot of the little ones
in these parts have lost their folks.
I think they'd be a great help
to you, Mr. Johnson.
Could you find it in your heart
and let 'em roost
at your place for a while?
They'd be welcome, Chub.
Thank you, ma'am!
Mr. and Mr. Johnson,
this is Frank Dwyer,
Josephine Harris, and Lon Gray.
I'm Mrs. Johnson, welcome to our home!
We've got Lucinda Gray,
Sally Thompson, Henry McLish
and we've got one more,
this is Alexander. But we call him Muggs.
Well, welcome, all of you.
Now, c'mon inside,
we'll get cleaned up for supper.
Come.
I think we're gonna need a bigger house.
Go on inside.
I'm gonna need something from you,
Clarence.
- Anything!
- How much you know about cattle?
About as much as that fence post.
Well, we're getting ready to have
a cattle drive, so what do you know?
Food! I now good eats, sir,
and I sure can cook like the dickens.
Nobody can fry a chicken like me.
Ha, I believe you. I guess we got
ourselves a cookie then.
Welcome home, cousin Clarence.
Call me Chub, Mr. Montford!
Every single child in the Johnson family
must have their own cow with a brand.
The brand never leaves.
It means that you are part
of something bigger.
You belong. And belonging is forever.
Ain't that right, Muggs?
What's the final head count?
Still at 1500. Got them all at the spring
at the north-west draw.
That's most of our cattle,
there's no guarantee.
Well, we've been down
to one skinny little cow before.
I'm not worried.
♪ I've got a fire burning in me ♪
♪ About to do some damage ♪
♪ 'Cause I've been pushed past the limit ♪
♪ The old maverick man ♪
♪ These days are for us ♪
♪ Wait for the prayer for us ♪
♪ These days are hard for us ♪
Tighten up, boys.
Round 'em up!
Come on.
That's what I was thinking.
♪ His hat was throwed back
And his spurs was a-jinglin' ♪
♪ And as he was riding
He's singing this song... ♪
- Howdy, cousin Montford!
- Hey! Shh!
Oh, sorry!
- Why is he always singing to the cows?
- Oh, it keeps 'em calm!
I've seen a heard spook and stampede
over nothing louder than a dropped spoon.
Ya don't say.
Oh, dang!
Careful now!
You don't ever wanna see a herd stampede!
Let's go! Push 'em to the north.
So where are these savages driving them?
Probably Abilene.
- And how many head?
- Around 1500, I count.
And you're looking for a cut?
Well, I can't join you
so I'll just take a tenth.
The rest is yours.
Aye, done.
One other request, that half-breed Indian,
I want him dead.
How much that gonna cost me?
The redskin?
That one's on me. That's a pleasure.
Storm's coming.
♪ But to keep you together ♪
♪ That's what I can do ♪
♪ Lay down little doggy ♪
♪ Lay down ♪
♪ My horse is leg weary ♪
♪ And I'm awful tired ♪
♪ Bunch up little doggies... ♪
I gotta scout for water!
♪ Bunch up ♪
Run boy! It's fine,
because today
ain't your day of reckoning
but it's coming.
And it's coming soon!
And I'm gonna take your scalp,
I'm gonna take your cattle,
that pretty little wife and your kids.
I'll be seeing ya!
Everyone, listen up!
There's some rustlers out there
who want to take our cattle.
They ain't gonna leave any of us alive.
- We can't let that happen!
- OK, uh-huh.
You know who we are!
- We're warriors!
- Right. Yeah.
We been fighting all our lives.
It ain't nothing new.
Uh-huh. That's right.
All right then. We'll take watch
in shifts tonight, guns loaded.
I'll take the first one.
Set the tongue to the north star, boys.
- We leave at day break.
- Yes, sir!
Beautiful morning!
Cross river here
and we'll push north-east
Mm-hmm. Yes, sir!
Oh, all right! What have we got, Clarence?
Biscuit and beans!
- Montford.
- Yes, sir?
There's something you should see.
How far are we from Abilene?
About 30 miles passing.
I'm sorry, Montford,
but they knew we'd have to pass
and they waiting for us
with more men and more guns.
Did you tell 'em?
They gonna be with ya
no matter what you decide.
Ya know, a lot of 'em got
a wives and kids at home.
Is there any way...
we can get around that bunch?
Montford, we'd have to double back,
head south.
Hit the river at its highest point.
It'd add another week.
Besides,
they just keep on after us.
Keep hitting us 'til we break,
but it's your call, boss.
What they singing?
War song.
We gonna go straight through 'em.
OK then.
Hyah! Hyah!
That's the place, don't let 'em stray!
- Get up!
- Yeah, yeah, get up.
- What's happening?
- Wake up! Stampede!
- Wake up!
Stampede!
Run! It's a stampede!
No! Run!
It's a stampede!
Get to the woods!
Yeah!
That's him right there!
Let's bury 'em. Him first.
He that seeketh mischief,
it shall come onto him.
Amen!
That's a fine lookin' herd.
Now you remember, don't take
nothing less than $30 a head.
So how'd we do?
Fifty-five a head!
Boy, we's in high cotton now!
Papa! Look, Papa's home!
Edward Bryant, this is for you.
And this is for you, Frank.
Here you go.
This is for you, Sally.
You're very welcome.
What'd you get?
I got something special for you.
Is that so?
You think we're made of money?
How much? $30 a head?
I told you, didn't I? I told you!
I think it's about time
we built that house.
I'd like that very much.
Edward Bryant.
- You pitch the hay in that lot?
- Yes, sir!
- Check on those heifers?
Who is that?
It's Rising Wolf's wife.
Asha, is everything alright?
- They took Rising Wolf and all the men.
- Who?
- The soldiers!
- Let's go!
Corporal, bring 'em in!
- S'cuse me?
- Yes?
- I need to speak with Lieutenant Pratt.
- Ah, Lieutenant Pratt's gone.
Where?
Him and Sergeant Richter
caught some Cheyenne criminals.
Taking 'em down to Fort Marion in Florida.
- Why?
- Too dangerous to keep here.
Too dangerous for who? The Cheyenne?
Good day, sir.
I gotta go get 'em.
Well, who's gonna take care
of the ranch while you're gone?
- Jack will stay here and help out.
- I don't like that you're taking E.B.
Not at all.
Florida is a long way from here
Well he's not a baby anymore.
I want him to know the world.
Learn to be a man.
He's gonna learn at my side,
not on his own.
Well, I guess I can't change your mind.
Can I help you?
Montford Johnson?
That's me.
Montford, uh,
I'm your father.
No.
Not you.
The swamps of Arkansas
swallowed up all of our wagons.
It was utterly impossible to get through.
- So what'd ya do?
- Well...
Charles,
so nice of you to join us.
Sorry, Boggy took your seat.
- Oh, forgive me, boy, I...
- Oh, hush, you're our guest tonight.
Sit down.
- Grandpa was just telling us about how...
- That's enough.
He's not your grandfather.
Montford, stop.
- Let the man talk.
- He ain't no man.
To be Chickasaw is to be family.
And he's neither.
Ain't no father.
A real father never leaves.
Can you pass me those potatoes?
So, Edward Bryant,
what was Mr. Johnson saying?
Uh, well, he uh...
Uh, Mr. Johnson was recollecting on how
he got his name during Removal times.
Mmm.
Sounds like a great story.
I'm sure he's full of 'em.
Well, Mr. Johnson,
tell us a story.
I implemented an old English trick
with Granny Vicey and Rebekah,
your mother, and I cut saplings
and laid them on the mud,
one on top another until...
until it was capable of holding
the combined weight
of our wagons and horses.
Uh-huh.
By that way we built a road
straight through the swamp,
uh, some prefer to call it a bog.
Charles became Boggy
because I led the people through the bog.
That's a real nice story.
Montford...
Maybe you could share with us a story
about where you been the last 30 years.
- Montford.
- I'm sure
everybody would love to hear that one.
You make me sick. I lost my appetite.
I know you're awake.
I don't like the children
seeing you like that.
N You need to speak to that man
and forgive him.
Why should I? He just comes back
and expects a big hug?
You know, I did everything right!
Provided, protected, fed, clothed,
put my life on the line.
Everything to make sure our family
was safe and could thrive.
Never once complained,
never shirked my duty.
Forgive him?
No, you're not like him, Montford.
That's true.
You did everything you could
to not become like your father.
But with all that you've done for us,
did you do it because you really loved us
or because you were scared
of becoming like him?
Hm?
Did you act out of love or out of fear
because that display at dinner
felt like a scared man to me.
I just don't know why he left.
I don't know why he left
and it bothers me.
And why does he pick now to come back?
Now that we're doing well?
Five'll get you ten, he wants money.
Well, just ask him, Montford.
I'm sure he's got an answer.
Took your time coming home.
Grass wasn't so green out there, huh?
Certainly was not.
Could you forgive me, Vicey?
I done did long ago.
It's him you have to plead your case to.
And because of you,
he is not a forgiving man.
You built quite the ranch here, Montford.
- It's very impressive. I'm proud of you.
- What do you want?
No, you know what, just tell me this.
What was so bad about us
that you needed to leave?
- Well, I, I...
- You know I waited every day for you.
Every night.
Counted on your word.
You said you'd come back.
And I believed you.
I walked the trail with your mother,
I know the Chickasaw way.
I knew family was everything, she knew it.
I just wished I could've lived it, I uh...
I well knew that every day
I lost was time irretrievable.
And I was afraid to return.
Well, all any boy wants
is a father to look up to.
Trust.
Know that he's gonna be there
when you fall.
- Well, you're the best example of that...
- And you're the worst example of that.
You know I needed you.
Adelaide needed you.
And where were you?
You promised you'd come back!
Yeah, I deserve that.
I know I can't bring back
the years and...
Son, I can't ask you to accept me
but I hope there's a place
in your heart for a weak man
who simply wishes your forgiveness.
That's all you came back for?
- Forgiveness?
- Montford.
- You sure it wasn't something else?
- Nothing else!
I'm not calling you father.
Mary said you were planning a trip.
A group of Cheyenne men
were taken from their families.
Held up in some old fort in St. Augustine.
I'm gonna go get 'em, bring 'em home.
I know that fort.
Spanish built, Fort Marion.
It's quite formidable.
The English Army
couldn't take it in 1702 or 1740.
What makes you think you can?
I don't know, Mr. Johnson.
I'll figure something out.
I gave my word
and unlike you I aim to keep it.
I have friends in Washington.
There's a Senator
who owes me quite a lot, actually.
A U.S. Senator?
That might be useful.
We leave tomorrow.
Haply I think on thee...
And then my state,
Like to the lark
at break of day arising.
From sullen earth sings hymns
at heaven's gate.
For thy sweet love
remembered such wealth brings,
That then I scorn to
change my state with kings.
It's gonna be a long ride.
My letter to the senator
should arrive today.
After all, he does owe me quite a lot,
of course.
You keep saying that
like you wish it was true. But is it?
Next stop, Blue Springs!
Whoa, now!
Could I interest this studious young man
in a sugar ice on a warm, humid night?
No, thank you, sir,
Whereabouts might Fort Marion be?
You referring to the local zoo?
That's what we call it, the zoo.
'Course instead of wild animals
we got wild Indians
and I mean to tell you
they are scarier than
the meanest zoo animal.
Human animal is the most dangerous kind.
Hey! We got friends in there
and they ain't no animals.
They didn't even do nothing wrong.
From one cultivated man to another,
I highly doubt that.
Ya know the ol' Fort, up yonder,
just past the school house.
It's the oldest building in this,
uh, very old town.
Now, please, enjoy your stay... gentlemen.
You're keeping these men here illegally.
They didn't do nothing wrong.
Not at all, Mr. Johnson, they will get
a trial, of that I assure you.
In the meantime, it is my endeavor to
assimilate them into American culture.
That way, if they are eventually released,
they can contribute to society.
If?
Lieutenant Pratt,
I appreciate your sentiment
but the rule of law
for any man in this country
dictates a fair and speedy trial.
I've noticed these men
haven't been given any trial at all,
not even a hearing.
You a lawyer, sir?
My name's Johnson.
I'm friends with Senator
Augustus Hill Garland of Arkansas
and President Rutherford B. Hayes.
I'm quite certain the Senator has been
in communication with you?
No, sir, he has not.
No correspondence of any kind?
Look, Mr. Johnson,
I can guarantee you and your friends
that the 70 men in custody here are being
treated with fairness and compassion.
Compassion?
Tell me, how compassionate
is it to keep them here
when their wives and children
are a thousand miles away?
We're teaching them. English,
skills, arithmetic, manners
so that they can get
the most of a cultivated life.
Mr. Johnson, I'm at a loss.
There are no Chickasaws here,
why do you make this your concern?
'Cause I know what it's like
to grow up without a father.
And what you're doing here,
it ain't right, no. sir.
They ought to be at home
providing for their families.
That's where they belong.
Not locked up in some filthy,
god-forsaken dungeon.
If you had any real compassion,
I think you'd understand that.
I do, understand that.
I'm sorry. You men have traveled in vain.
There is nothing any one of us can do
to change this situation. Goodnight.
Montford! Montford Johnson! Montford!
Montford!
You know all these men?
Longer'n I known you.
Keep it down!
I said keep it down!
Evenin', gentlemen.
I take it this old man here to be
from the better side of your lineage?
Three generations of fools!
We need more water!
Boggy! Papa! I smell smoke!
The hospital goes,
the whole town goes.
Is that the hospital?
More people in there?
Get those two barrels up here!
Cut it with a rag!
- I'm gonna go round back.
- More water! Come on!
- Where are they?
- Over here!
- Get a move on!
- Get there.
Come on! Help!
We need more men! Come around here!
Come on, come on, come on!
- We need more men.
- I need your help!
You got 70 good men right over there.
There's more people inside.
Help! There's fire everywhere!
Sergeant, release the prisoners.
Sir, all due respect,
they are not to be trusted.
Sergeant, that is an order!
C'mon, you heard him.
Come on!
Come around the side,
I need you! Montford, come with me!
- I'm going in.
- I'm coming too!
- Nope, no.
- Yes, c'mon!
Stay here! You stay here!
E.B., stay here. Help with the trough!
- Stay here.
- C'mon, let's go, let's go.
Come on.
There's people in the back
In the back. Let's go in.
I'll be back, son! Stay safe!
Stay low, follow me.
In here, in here! Here they are.
Careful, I gotcha.
Come on.
Get a bucket, get a bucket, get a bucket!
Go around back and fight it around back!
Here's another one!
Go around, go around.
Y'all get them buckets back here!
Bring those buckets back.
- Are there more inside?
- Yes!
Stay low.
Just up here!
Over here!
There's more of us up here.
Please help.
Over here!
- Help please! Please!
- Come on.
Let's go.
I gotcha, let's go.
- I'll keep looking!
- C'mon.
- I heard someone! Did you?
- Where?
This way!
Come on.
- I got her!
- Check that way!
All right.
Over here.
Over there!
Hey!
- Sir?
- Hey!
Nothing in here, mate.
She's gonna blow!
Hey!
This the last of 'em?
Montford?
Where's Montford?
- I don't know, I didn't see him.
- He was with you.
- I didn't see anybody else in there.
- Where's Papa?
- Where's Montford?
- Where is he?
Like I said I didn't see him!
C'mon, C'mon.
Stay here, E.B., go around back!
Clear Sergeant? We all clear?
As far as I know, sir. I'm gonna head back
to the fort to get some medical supplies.
Help!
Montford!
Anybody help!
- Help!
- I can't find you! Montford!
Help!
Montford!
Papa!
I'm coming for you, Montford!
I'm coming for you, son!
I got you, son! I got you!
Safe now.
Help! Come get him!
Help'll come by soon enough.
- Where's my father?
- He's over here, c'mon.
- Papa! Is he OK? Papa!
- Yeah, I got him. I got him.
Son!
I thought I lost you.
I'm OK. Your grandfather found me.
- What were you doing in that room?
- Richter trapped me.
Richter!
Something I can help you with,
Mr. Johnson?
- Shut up!
- Hey! Hey!
Arrest this man!
Whoa! OK, what's going on here?
- This monster was trying to kill my son!
- He's delusional!
- What is going on?
- He trapped him purposely!
Actually, sir,
I'd like to report something.
Whatever he says is a lie!
In the hospital,
I saw him, he jammed the door shut.
I'm a sergeant! You're gonna take
a private's word over mine?
Sergeant, at ease!
Both of you come with me right now!
That man tried to kill my son!
Lies! All Lies!
You gonna believe
an Injun's word over mine?
Quiet down! You're going away for life!
How you feeling, Papa?
Like I swallowed charcoal.
Thank you for coming, brother.
Even if we can't be free,
your presence has brings us
great strength.
We'd like to thank you all.
I'd like to thank you and
these other men for helping to...
save our town.
We're sorry.
We...
We coulda been better than we have been.
- Charles Johnson.
- Senator Garland.
- What an extreme pleasure to see you, sir.
- Thank you.
Thank you so much for coming!
I take it you received my letters?
I did indeed and
it deserved a personal visit
rather than written correspondence.
'Cause as you know, I, uh...
well I owe you quite a bit.
Uh, yeah, that's what I've been saying.
Oh, I'd like you to meet,
uh, well, this is...
I'm Montford Johnson. I'm his son.
Very pleased to meet you, Montford.
Very pleased. And this is?
Edward Bryant. I'm his grandson.
Really?
Lieutenant Pratt.
- Yes, sir. Friend of the Johnsons?
- I am!
Well, I'm not sure
there's much, as I've said,
that can be done under your authority.
I'm following Army orders.
It's not my own authority I come with,
but that of the United States government.
And, Lieutenant,
we give the orders to the Army.
Senator, if we could it'd be best
to discuss this in my office.
As you wish.
Senator, thank you so much.
Don't thank me now.
It's still an uphill battle.
- Yes, sir.
- Gentlemen.
Do you think they'll ever free 'em?
Eventually...
they'll have to send 'em home.
Why'd you leave?
Because my bad outweighs my good.
Why'd you come back?
E.B., I'm getting old
and running out of time, so...
with what I have left,
I need to make right many wrongs.
- What have ya there?
- It's a brand.
One I want to use on my own cattle.
Planning on following in
your father's footsteps?
Papa always told me a brand is one
of the most important things.
A brand is something that's permanently
a part of something bigger.
Painful though.
Sure, hurts at first but pain goes away.
Belonging is forever.
Very true.
Haha! Yes, sir!
Look what the cat
finally decided to drug on in.
They finally let you out.
- It's a good day.
- Is that really you?
Yes. Many of us have returned
to our lodges.
Welcome home, brother!
Today's the day for the real race.
It ain't gonna be
much different from last time.
Yeah. 'Cept it ain't your wedding day.
Let's go, c'mon! C'mon!
♪ I'm wearing out
These old leather boots ♪
♪ Working so hard ♪
♪ They needs due ♪
♪ I get myself up with the rising sun ♪
♪ And take all I've got ♪
♪ And put it on the line ♪
♪ Long as I'm able ♪
♪ I'll push through ♪
♪ I'm gonna keep on ♪
♪ Keeping on ♪
♪ My aim is faithful ♪
♪ And true what I do, I do for you ♪
♪ What I do, I do for you ♪
♪ I hear your whisper ♪
♪ Through these dark wood tree ♪
♪ And see your outline ♪
♪ In the tall grass fields ♪
♪ Everywhere I go
I see you there with me ♪
♪ The man that's in your eyes ♪
♪ That's who I wanna be
Long as I'm able ♪
♪ I'll push through ♪
♪ I'm gonna keep on ♪
♪ Keeping on ♪
♪ My aim is faithful and true ♪
♪ What I do, I do for you ♪
♪ No, it ain't for the money ♪
♪ It ain't for show ♪
♪ I would've given all that up ♪
♪ Long time ago ♪
♪ But I know what's driving me ♪
♪ I know what's driving me on ♪
♪ Whoa, long as I'm able ♪
♪ I'll push through ♪
♪ I'm gonna keep on ♪
♪ Keeping on ♪
♪ My aim is faithful and true ♪
♪ And true what I do, I do for you ♪
♪ What I do, I do for you ♪
♪ Whoa ♪
♪ Driving, driving, driving ♪
♪ What's driving, driving
Oooh, what's driving ♪
♪ What's driving, what's driving
What's driving ♪
♪ Whoa ♪
♪ What's driving me on ♪
♪ Driving me on ♪