[music playing]
DAN [ON TV]: A big
development today
in the computer wars
between Savatar Software
and Thornhill Industries.
With a business report
and the details,
here's Connie McKinnon.
CONNIE MCKINNON [ON TV]:Industry analysts report--
Hello.
Mr. Cannon.
No, not now.
Sorry.
CONNIE MCKINNON [ON TV]: --thatif the strike is not resolved
within the next two weeks,third-quarter profits
could hit an all-time low.
Savatar Software closed
up six points today.
Nobody's talking on the record.
But the rumor is their
new handheld direction
finder could be
rolled out about three
months earlier than predicted.
Now you'll have no excuse foryou to get lost on the way
home ever again, Dan.
DAN [ON TV]: [laughs]
There is no way they're
ready to roll out.
CONNIE MCKINNON [ON
TV]: Residential
construction stats--
[click]
Beecham!
I heard.
Savatar is leaking stories abouttheir new handheld navigator.
ROBERT: And we are
taking the hit.
Where's uh--
Mercer.
I've already talked to him.
And?
Production delays on the line,erratic output, unacceptable
error rates in the new chips.
They still can't find
the source of the dirt.
In other words,
nothing has changed.
Where's my brother?
BEECHAM: Haven't heard fromKevin since he left last week.
And he's not
answering his email.
ROBERT: Perfect,
absolutely perfect.
BEECHAM: Oh, come on,boss, you know how he gets.
ROBERT: Will you stop
making excuses for him.
It is time for him to
take responsibility
for the business.
It is not enough
to be brilliant.
[birds calling]
[creaking]
[beeping]
[dings]
[click]
[beep]
[beeping]
[thud]
BILL: Morning, Mr. Mercer.ORRIN MERCER: Hey.
Morning, Bill.
KEVIN: Hello, skipper.
Welcome aboard.
ORRIN MERCER: Kevin,
what are you doing here?
We need to talk.
Robert must be really upsetabout the Savatar announcement.
ORRIN MERCER: He's
not upset with you.
It's not your fault.
KEVIN: It is my fault.
I'm the one that talked
my brother into backing this.
It was a sure thing.
We were way ahead of Savatar.
We haven't seen what
Savatar's got yet.
Nobody has.
They're just trying to spook us.
Well, it's working.
Why can't we get theThornhill Explorer right?
Maybe I missed something.
I can't understand it.
Robert trusted me with
this, and I'm gonna
drive him into bankruptcy.
Don't worry about Robert.
He'll survive.
He always does.
[sighs]
Well, I have to
take the boat out.
I had some work done on thesteering linkage, and I wanna--
Mm.
--check it out
before it gets dark.
So why don't we meet
at the plant tomorrow,
and we'll talk about this?
We'll-- we'll find a solution.
Sure.
OK, buddy.
[keys jangling]
[engine starting]
[click]
[beep]
[beeping]
[click]
[birds calling]
WOMAN: Ready.MAN 1: Do we have everything.
MAN 2: Yeah, we're set.
MAN 1: OK then.
[inaudible]
WOMAN: OK.
Hey, Evie.
Oh, hey, Kevin.
You have to be the
most determined
fisherman I've ever known.
What do you mean?
Well, I see you
go out every day,
and I never see
you catch anything.
Oh, that's all right.
It's a zen thing.
Yeah, well, maybe you
should change your bait.
No way.
I haven't changed my
bait since I was a kid.
Really?
Yep.
My luck's about to change.I can feel it.
Well, just be careful, OK?
Because I think the
weather's gonna change.
KEVIN: This is Nova Scotia.
What else is new?
[engine starts]
Just a sec, OK?
Just in case.
Thanks.
Put it on my account, huh?
Ah, don't worry about it.
It's on the house.
Now I'm really gonna to
have to catch something.
[beeping]
[boat approaching]
[birds singing]
[waves lapping]
[door creaking]
[creaking]
[music playing]
ROBERT: Nova Scotia.
He was out fishing, sir,according to the police report.
Seems he'd been
doing that regularly.
[sighs]
[crying]
I'm so sorry.
ROBERT: The Thornhill
Explorer's late,
and he goes to Nova
Scotia to go fishing.
That day a storm came up.
His engine must've failed.
It looks like he panickedand tried to swim to shore.
His body was washed
up a day later.
Where is he?
FERGUSON: In Chester.
They'll release the--
Kevin's-- I can leave
right away, sir.
No.
No, I, uh-- I'll
go get him myself.
[CRYING] Yes, Arthur,
it is a terrible thing.
Thank you.
I'll-- I'll tell Robert.
That'll be all, Ferguson.
BEECHAM: Bye.
If you could tell
the authorities
that Mr. Cannon will be
coming to pick up Kevin.
Have Mercer meet him.
I'll take care of it.
Sorry, Mr. Cannon.
Yes, thank you.
[sighs]
[door closes]
[CRYING] The seaplane
is in Long Island.
It'll be here by 11:30.
I can't believe it.
ROBERT: I'm having
a rather difficult
time believing it myself.
Do you think the
Savatar announcement
had anything to do with this?
ROBERT: I'm not sure.
I guess I'll be
going to Chester.
[sighs]
[door opens]
[engine roaring]
[footsteps]
Robert.
Where do we go?
You don't have to goanywhere if you don't want to.
I've already identified thebody and made arrangements
for it to be released.
Robert--
[sighs]
--I don't know what to say.
I can't tell you how sorry I am.
Thank you.
I want to see him.
If the Explorer
hadn't fallen behind,
then Kevin never
would've come out here.
What do you mean?
ORRIN MERCER: Well,
I encouraged him.
I-- I feel responsible.
ROBERT: Well, don't.
It's not the first
project that--
that's fallen behind.
ORRIN MERCER: No.
But it was Kevin's project.
I told you when this
thing started to treat
it just like any other.
Let's go.
[plane engine humming]
ORRIN MERCER: I'm afraid
I've got some more bad
news, Robert, about Savatar.
What?
I didn't want you to
read it in the papers.
Well, tell me.
The rumors are true.
They've just released
their own version.
And it isn't a beta test.
It's the full deal.
This is gonna cost us, Robert.
What do we do to catch up?
[sighs]
I don't know.
ROBERT: Nothing ever
changes in this town.
ORRIN MERCER: It sure is pretty.
You must've lovedgrowing up here as a kid.
You know, Orrin, I
couldn't wait to leave.
How do we fix it?
Are the chips still dirty?
No, I think we've
got that licked.
ROBERT: Then, what?
We know the software works.
Well, in a cruise
missile maybe.
But we're trying to pack
a lot of information
into a device you
hold in your hand.
We're rechecking
all the schematics.
We're--
ROBERT: Orrin, how long?
Six months.
ORRIN MERCER: It's
just bad luck.
It'll kill the stock.
[door opens]
Sorry for your loss, Robert.
I appreciate your help, Ian.
I wish the help could've beenunder happier circumstances.
Where is he?
IAN MACRAE: He's up
at the funeral parlor.
I'm going to go see him.
Of course.
I'll meet you there.
[clears throat]
You don't have to
do this, Robert.
Yes I do.
[door slams]
Take all the time you need.
[footsteps]
[sobbing]
Orrin's already made thearrangements for you to take
your brother back to Boston.
No, I will bury him here.
Kevin grew up here.
Six generations of
Cannons are buried here.
Kevin would like that.
Yeah.
How long will you be staying?
I don't know, a few days.
I can't leave the
office for too long.
Where will you be staying?
The house
I closed up the house.
Well, then open it.
[beep]
IAN MACRAE: This is
such a great place.
I always liked it.
ROBERT: Well, I always
wanted to get rid of it.
Kevin loved it.
[door closes]
[footsteps]
Thank you, ladies.
Can I get you a drink, Ian?
Well, mineral
water, if you have it.
Mineral water?
What is it, duty or--
Old age.
[pouring drinks]
Well, here's to old friends.
It's good to see you again.
And you, Robert.
What happened, Ian?
It's all in the report.
Three nights ago,
Kevin went out fishing.
We found his tackle in the boat.
Yeah, and?
And when we
spoke to the owner,
she said he headed off inthe direction of Shad Bay.
The owner?
Yeah, he rented asmall outboard motorboat.
Which marina?
The one down in
Mahone Bay where we
used to play when we were kids.
I thought they turned
that into landfill.
IAN MACRAE: [laughs]
As a matter of
fact, it's running
the best it's been in years.
ROBERT: Who's the owner?
IAN MACRAE: Evangeline
Shaw, an American.
She and her husband
bought it two years ago.
Her husband was killed lastsummer in a boating accident.
You're suing a widow.
ROBERT: What are
you talking about?
Who's suing who?
IAN MACRAE: You'velaunched a wrongful death
suit against the marina.
ROBERT: It-- it's just
the legal department
doing its thing, standardoperating procedure these days.
IAN MACRAE: I
thought it might have
something to do
with what she's been
saying about Kevin's death.
What's she saying?
Well, that it
wasn't an accident.
[birds calling]
EVIE: Worms are
on sale this week.
BOY: Worms are cheaper,
but my uncle says squid.
Well, different people
use different bait.
BOY: Well, what do you think?
EVIE: Well, it depends
on what you like.
Now squid takes--
Excuse me.
Hi.
Um, I'll just be one second.
Squid tends to last
longer and take--
I-- I wonder if
I could possibly--
Well, I'm just
with a customer.
Um, if I were you, I woulduse bait that works fast.
So you see these guys here?
Now for the kind of fish
that you're catching,
I think these will work.
And you know what?
If it doesn't, you can alwaystry the squid tomorrow.
BOY: OK, thanks, Mrs. Shaw.
EVIE: You're welcome.
[ding]
[drawer rattling]
Now, can I help you?
Yes, my name is Robert Cannon.
I believe that you
knew my brother, Kevin.
Could you please leave?
I beg your pardon?
Let me make it simple for you.
Get out.
ROBERT: No, you--
you don't understand.
I need to talk to you.
I'm terribly sorry aboutyour brother's death,
but I have nothing
to say to you.
And why is that?
Because you're blaming mefor your brother's death.
You're suing me.
Oh.
Oh, the lawsuit.
Yes, well, um-- no,
you don't understand.
Uh, I-- I'm not suing you.
My company, Thornhill
Software, is suing
your company, Shaw's Marina.
This is nothing personal.
It's not personal?
This marina is all I have.
It's personal.
Right.
Of course it is.
I'll tell you what.
I will get my lawyers
to drop the lawsuit.
But I want you to tell me whyyou believe that my brother's
death was not an accident.
All right.
Let me show you something.
You see those boats on theother side of the dock?
That's my rental line.
Which one was Kevin's?
Kevin's was the
one at the end.
Now there's no way that hisboat quit like they said it did.
Of course not.
These look like the latestin high-tech design.
Yeah, well, high tech
isn't what you want.
Simple is better.
If you say so.
EVIE: Simple is reliable.
And I keep my boats
in tip-top shape.
I believe you do.
Five bucks says itstarts on the first pull.
That's three dollars
American, you know?
You're on.
You sure you can handle it?
I'll make sure the
plant cuts a check.
[laughs]
[engine starts]
How about double or nothing?
Sure.
[engine starts]
[pulls rope]
Well, what does that prove?
It proves that they'll startunder ideal circumstances.
Oh, you're tough.
You own your own company, right?ROBERT: Yes.
Why?
Well, it's just funny
because Kevin mentioned
that he had a boss, but he neversaid anything about a brother.
Excuse me.
[sighs]
[bells ringing]
It was a beautiful service.
I'm sure Kevin would
have appreciated it.
IAN MACRAE: Robert, we'reall gonna miss Kevin.
Mm.
EVIE: I'm really sorry.
Thank you.
I behaved horribly yesterday.
ROBERT: Well, I wasn't exactlya pillar of charm myself.
Mm.
Did you know Kevin well?
No.
But he was a wonderful guy.
I liked him.
This really is an
inappropriate time,
but did you look at
Kevin's fishing tackle?
He had very expensive gear.
And for gear that expensive,he never caught anything.
And he didn't run out of gas.
When they brought his boat back,his tank was still half full.
Thank you.
I'm sorry I interrupted you.
[waves lapping]
[birds calling]
[door closes]
[beeping]
Beecham.
[laughs]
Hey, boss.
We're all thinking of you.
Did the flowers arrive?
They did indeed.
Thank you.
And the sun shone, and
the minister was brief.
BEECHAM [ON PHONE]:
How are you doing?
When are you coming back?
I'm not sure yet.
I see.
What did you find out?
ROBERT [ON PHONE]: Nothingdefinite so far, but there
are a few unanswered questions.
BEECHAM [ON PHONE]:
Please be careful.
Oh, I will.
BEECHAM [ON PHONE]: Well,how long do you expect to be?
I'll arrange to send
you some more clothes.
About a week.
BEECHAM [ON PHONE]: Don't worry.
I'll reschedule everything.
Even under these circumstances,it must be nice to be home.
ROBERT [ON PHONE]: Well,it-- it would be good if I
could find something to eat.
Listen, you couldn't, uh,
order some sushi for me,
could you, from Takana's?
I hear they, uh, deliver.
[laughs]
Absolutely, but I think you'reout of their three-mile range.
You know, I'll have Mercer'sassistant go shopping for you.
No, no, no, no,
no, please don't.
The cupboard is full.
Look, there's something
I want you to do.
I want you to find out aboutand Evie Shaw, S-H-A-W,
first name, Evangeline.
Early 30s, American citizen.
She is the owner
of Shaw's Marina.
Could you do that?
[dial tone]
Bye.
ORRIN MERCER: Robert, youshouldn't be in today.
MAN: Did we get that shipment?
Unless we get the
Thornhill Explorer up
and running right
quick, our stock prices
are gonna melt down to China.
You just buried your
brother yesterday.
Nothing more I can do for him.
I want the latest anomalyreports, and I want them now.
[chattering]
[beeping]
ORRIN MERCER: The mappingsystem works fine.
But key in the intersectionof Brunswick and Duke.
[beeping]
Yeah, so what's the problem?
Sometimes theelevation function works.
Sometimes it doesn't.
[beeping]
Hm.
Right.
Now ask for a
view to the west.
[beeping]
[beep]
City Hall, past the Citadel.
So the memory's keyed in wrong.
That's all.
ORRIN MERCER: No, it
isn't that simple.
The actual building on thatcorner is the post office.
Not the Citadel, not CityHall, the post office.
Kevin figured that maybe
the access algorithm
wasn't syncing with the chip.
So he'd fix that, and thatwould offset something
else on something else.
And he ended up just
chasing his tail.
ROBERT: All right,
all right, all right.
Pull up the schematics.
Let's take a look at this.
[beeping]
ORRIN MERCER: Even thediscrepancies are inconsistent.
Everyone in the plant
has had a crack at this.
Well, do you mind if
I take a look at it?
You're the boss.
ROBERT: Orrin, how longhave we known each other?
ORRIN MERCER: 25 years.
And, uh, what was
my area of expertise?
Uh, computer software.
So don't humor me.
ORRIN MERCER: [laughs]
When was the last time
you wrote any code?
ROBERT: Yeah, well,
about six years ago.
And--
About six years.
--and darn tight code it was.- [laughs]
Six years is thedifference between the Pony
Express and email.
Ah, email, yeah.
All right.
All right, what do we do,keep it going or shut it down?
ORRIN MERCER: We
can't shut it down.
We put 30 million
in development.
Well, we can write it off.
Ugh.
All of Kevin's
work, for nothing?
I can't believe you said that.
Sentiment?
This is a business
decision, Orrin.
What are we gonna do?
Look, I'm sorry.
OK, here is what I'm gonna do.
I am gonna take this home,and I am gonna figure
out what is wrong with it.
I'll see you later, Orrin.
See you later.
[door opens]
[chattering]
[groans]
Hello.
EVIE: Oh, Good
morning, Mr. Cannon.
Good morning
[birds calling]
I, um-- I'd like to renta boat, uh, nothing fancy.
Um, maybe one of
these thingies here.
Oh, well, there's
nothing available.
Two of them are booked
out this afternoon,
and the other one
needs servicing.
Is that a big problem?
No, it's just regular
servicing, but--
So can you service it?
Well, I'm going to
later this afternoon.
How about now?
I'm busy now.
What's the big rush?
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I just wanted--
I wanted to get out there.
And I wanted to, uh, find thespot where they found him.
I'm almost finished.
Thank you.
I'll just wait.
[engine starts]
I'll see you later.
Thanks again.
[engine roars]
Whoa!
Whoa.
EVIE: You might
wanna cast off first.
[engine roars]
Whoa!
I don't know where I'm going.
I'll draw you a map.
Um, OK.
This is Shad's Passage
right here, right?
Now, right here,
as you go along,
there will be a dock
on the left, OK?
And just past that, there'sa white navigation marker.
That's where they
found Kevin's body.
[beeping]
[birds calling]
[music playing]
[sighs]
[engine sputtering]
[groaning]
Oh, perfect.
Oh.
Oh, ah, hey!
Ah!
Oh.
Shoot.
Hey!
Over here!
Robert!
[sighs]
[laughing]
I think the proper nauticalterm is "ahoy there."
Yeah, well.
[sighs]
Are you OK?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Well, what happened?
You were supposed to be back.
Well, what happened was
this perfectly reliable
engine of yours stalled.
- Mhm.
- That's what happened.
- Mm.
Well, I'm surprised
you didn't use
your mobile phone to call yourinternational headquarters.
Yeah, well, I--
I forgot it.
Mm.
Mhm.
Do you wanna throw me a line?
Where?
Over there?
Mhm.
Ah.
EVIE: You don't have a line?
I don't see any line.
EVIE: [scoffs]
[birds calling]
Come here.
I wanna show you something.
[groans]
See?
I, uh-- I guess that
explains what happened.
That's OK.
It happens.
- Mhm.
- Come on, I'll tow you.
[bird squawking]
You see that over there?
That there is Spyglass Hill.
No, it's not.
It's called Gibbons Bluff.
Nope.
That's called Spyglass Hill.
That's the name Kevin and Igave it when we were kids.
It's a haven for
smugglers and pirates.
He used to spend
hours up there looking
out for British men of war.
That's cute.
ROBERT: A lot of
people died around here
looking for buried treasure,out here and down by Oak Island.
During Prohibition,
they used to smuggle
booze from here down to Boston.
Piracy in these parts has hada long and venerable tradition.
Is there, uh--
[clears throat]
--any decent restaurant in town?
God knows there
wasn't when I grew up.
I'm starving.
- Why don't I make you dinner.- No.
No, no, no, I didn't mean that.
Uh, you've done more thanenough, uh, for today,
thank you.
I'm actually a good cook.
No, I believe you are.
But, uh, no, I'll just--
I'll just go home.
And make a box of cereal.
No, I was thinking
a can of beans.
I have to shop anyway.
OK, yes.
Great.
- Can I use your phone?
- Sure.
I'll be right back.
I just wanna call the office.
[door opens]
[dial tone]
[door closes]
[siren wailing]
BEECHAM [ON PHONE]:
This is Ellen Beecham.
ROBERT [ON PHONE]: Beecham.
BEECHAM [ON PHONE]: Hey, boss.
I faxed you the informationyou asked about on Ms. Shaw.
ROBERT [ON PHONE]: Uh-huh.
You turn up anything
interesting?
She looks pretty ordinary onpaper, except for her picture.
She's very attractive.
Uh-huh, uh-huh.
What else?
BEECHAM [ON PHONE]: Well, Ialso got a line on a housekeeper
for you-- uh, a
couple, actually.
She does the cooking, thecleaning, the shopping.
And he does the gardeningand the driving.
No.
No, that will not be necessary.
Well, you sure, boss?
I mean, I know you're onlygonna be there a few days,
but it will make you
more comfortable.
ROBERT [ON PHONE]: No, I, uh--
[door opens]
I'd rather be alone.
OK, well, if you need
them, give me a call.
I've got their number.
What would I do without you?
Uh, if you do, uh, go home,uh, be sure to let me know.
Boss, you know I always
sleep at the office.
Attagirl.
Thank you.
How much do you
pay that woman?
Beecham?
Not enough.
Let's go.
ROBERT: I can't believe this.
They got 15 different
types of olives here.
Things sure have changed
since I was a kid.
Yeah, well, they even havearugula and Reggiano-Parmesan.
Yes, and fresh
seafood on the coast.
Can you believe it?
Oh.
Oops.
[laughs]
You're a little excited.
I'm gonna go get the wine.
I'll do the shop.
[chattering]
Boy, oh boy, real food.
You really know
what you're doing.
[laughs]
You, I'm not so sure about.
No, I-- I don't know.
I was going for healthy.
But then, you know, I startedgetting all these cravings.
And I got-- I got
caught in a time warp.
But, uh, listen.
[ITALIAN ACCENT] Smell this.Mm, that aroma.
Mm, yeah.
With that diet, I don't knowhow you made it through puberty.
- I didn't.
- [laughs]
[ITALIAN ACCENT] Here,let me, uh-- let me, please.
- No, no.
- No, no, please.
No.
No, please, let-- oh.
Let me get this.
[beep]
[cash register whirring]
[waves lapping]
You are one great cook.
Oh, thank you.
I used to cater in California.
It was really nice to do this.
I haven't done this
in a long time.
That's a far cry from
catering in California
to running a marina out here.
True.
[laughs]
Must've been pretty toughafter your husband died, huh?
It was, but not in
the way that you think.
What do you mean?
It was a big surprise.
Why?
It was an accident.
Oh.
How many years were you married?
Three years.
We met in California.
We got married.
And then we came here
and bought the marina.
Now why would you wannago from California to here?
It was Grant's dream.
He wanted to get away
from the rat race.
Why'd you stay?
His life insurance
paid for the mortgage.
And I mean, I could've
sold it and left.
But then I realized
that I loved it here.
And it gave me a
sense of independence.
Sometimes I feel
guilty for that.
Because his death
bought you your freedom?
No.
We got married too fast.
Grant had this way about him.
He was hard to resist.
So what changed?
You ever wake
up in the morning
and you're not in
love with someone?
I felt relieved that I
didn't have to tell him.
So--
[sighs]
--have you ever been married?
Um, no.
So Kevin's your only family.
Well, our parents
died when I was 18.
Kevin was about six.
I guess I became more of
a father than a brother
to him at that point.
You did a great job.
No, this had
nothing to do with me.
This was entirely his doing.
He was a pretty, um,
engaging little kid.
[laughs]
Never complained
about anything.
I, on the other
hand, as a parent,
was completely hopeless.
Mm.
One time I took
him to the movies,
when I was in college,with some friends of mine.
After the, uh,
film was over, I--
I forgot all about him, andI left him in the theater.
That's awful.
About an hour
and a half later,
I realized what I had done.
So I went--
I bolted back there.
And there he was, sittingexactly where I left him.
He hadn't budged.
[laughs]
You must have felt terrible.
He-- he told me that, um,he knew that I was gonna
come back to get him and--
and that he appreciated
the fact that he could
watch the movie over again.
And then he told me
that he was sorry that--
that he made me worry about him.
What do you do with
a kid like that, huh?
[crying softly]
[CRYING] I can't believe I'mnever gonna see him again.
I'm sorry.
Um, thank you for
a wonderful dinner.
Wait.
Are you OK?
I'm fine.
[sighs]
I'm sorry to be such a
poor dinner companion.
Please stay.
If you'll excuse me.
[door closes]
[door opens]
[exhales]
[sighs]
[birds chirping]
I am opening it as we speak.
Where's the prototype?
What Prototype
ROBERT [ON PHONE]:
Kevin's prototype,
the thing that got
the whole thing
started in the first place.Where is it?
BEECHAM [ON PHONE]: So
someone is sabotaging
the Thornhill Explorer project.
I am absolutely sure of it.
Now here's what
I want you to do.
I want you to go and buyme the Savatar Navigator,
and you send it
to me right quick.
You think Savatar got ahold of Kevin's prototype?
ROBERT [ON PHONE]: You
remember the Concorde?
You remember how
the Russians ended
up designing a
supersonic airliner
that looked exactly like it?
Yeah, everyone said itwas coincident technology,
that the problems dictated
identical engineering
solutions.
Yeah, that's what
everybody said.
And that's what Mercer's tryingto tell me about the Explorer.
Meanwhile, 20 years later,we cut to the Russians,
and guess what?
Somebody sold the
Concorde design to them.
Surprise, surprise.
You get me that Navigator.
I'm gonna find out
exactly how they did it.
What's going on
with Shaw's Marina?
Oh, yeah.
[sighs]
Financials just came in.
It's pretty much how
Mercer described it.
Evangeline Shaw is
getting by, but she's
certainly not getting rich.
The balance sheet
doesn't show much more
than you can see from the dock.
Uh-huh.
BEECHAM [ON PHONE]:
Why the big interest?
Dropped the lawsuit.
ROBERT [ON PHONE]:
Yeah, you're right.
Forget about it.
She's got enough
trouble as it is.
I gotta go.
I'll call you later.
[hangs up phone]
[beeping]
[watch beeping]
Oh, shit.
[birds calling]
Hello.
- Oh, hi.
I just wanted to say that--
I was gonna--
- Oh.
- Sorry.
Sorry.
No, after you.
I was just really
worried about you
when you didn't show
up this morning.
Oh, yeah.
I was, uh-- I was
working on my computer.
I got lost.
[chuckles]
Oh.
ROBERT: Where's my boat?
What do you mean, "your boat"?
ROBERT: Well-- well, I was gonnarent a boat today, remember?
You said you were gonnarent a boat this morning.
ROBERT: Yes, well, I
was busy this morning.
I have a business to run.
EVIE: Well, I have a
business to run too,
and so I had to
rent your boat out.
Otherwise I would've lost money.
ROBERT: Well, uh, I wish
you would've phoned me.
I-- I would've paid
for the entire day.
Well, I did phone you,
but your line was busy.
I'm sorry.
Uh, tell you what,
I'll rent this boat.
No, you couldn't handle it.
Well, then I will
hire you to be my guide.
No, I don't think so.
ROBERT: Well, why not?
I don't see a heck of alot of action around here.
Well, something could come up.
Like what, a worm shortage?
I'll pay you.
I-- I'll pay you
to give me boat--
boat lessons for a day.
In fact, I'll pay you to giveme boating lessons for the week.
I'll pay in advance, OK?
I don't take out tourists.
Please?
On one condition.
What's that?
It's free.
Aye aye, skipper.
OK, you wanna hug
close to the shore
a little bit to
adjust to the wind.
Otherwise you're gonna
get blown out too far.
Now, you see that point
where that big tree is?
ROBERT: Yeah.
OK, you wanna head
straight for that.
See that old wharf?
There?
EVIE: There.
See it?
Yeah.
When it just passes
your left shoulder,
it's gonna be safe to turn in.
You have any idea
what Kevin was doing
out here the night he died?
No, he just said
he went fishing.
Do you know where exactly?
EVIE: He just said that heloved fishing when he was a kid,
so I figured he found somesecret spot that he remembered.
ROBERT: Kevin hatedfishing when he was a kid.
EVIE: Then why did he
go out every night?
You said he never
came back with anything.
He wasn't fishing.
That's strange.
Then where was he going?
Exactly.
EVIE: OK, you can turn now.
OK, you can stop.
[birds chirping]
He's been poking aroundfor two days in a row now.
What's he looking for?
GRANT SHAW: What does it matter?
He won't find anything.
ORRIN MERCER: I don't like it.
He's getting way too
friendly with Evie.
GRANT SHAW: So?
She's a beautiful woman.
You worry too much.
And you don't worry enough.
A man like Robert Cannon doesn'tindulge in idle flirtations.
Don't underestimate him.
GRANT SHAW: He's beenspending a lot of quality time
with my wife.
I'm hardly going to
underestimate him.
ORRIN: Get serious, Shaw.
You don't have to face
him day after day.
I tell you, he
suspects something.
[laughing]
He might suspect you,
but he won't suspect me.
I'm dead, remember?
And thanks to Robert
Cannon, very rich.
ROBERT: This is it, isn't it?
This is where they found him.
He was missing for 36 hours.
The currents usually
run this way,
so he was probably up onthe west part of the island.
I don't know.
It's hard to say.
If I had tide tables, it
would be a lot easier.
There's so many variables.
It doesn't tell me
a great deal, does it?
We should head back.
All the rentals
will be coming in.
ROBERT: You know, maybe,uh-- maybe you should drive.
I-- I'm terrible at this.
EVIE: No, you can drive.
I should just teach you
how to drive safely.
[motor humming]
ROBERT: OK, OK, this is good.EVIE: O-- OK, OK.
ROBERT: Have I got it?
EVIE: OK, yeah.
Just-- now--
ROBERT: All right.
EVIE: Just slow-- no, justsl-- slow-- slow-- no, slow.
- Where are the brakes?
- No, slow!
You just gotta-- no!
- All right.
No, just-- not-- jeez!
Oops.
You know, it's no use.
I'm no good at this.
No, you just need
a little practice.
No, no.I'm just no good at this.
No, you just need
a little practice.
Now you-- you, uh-- nowyou take over, because if I
have to keep doing this--
EVIE: Well, you can
give it another try.
No, no, no, no,
then we'll starve.
I-- I-- I was hoping to takeyou out for dinner to-- to-- you
know, to thank you.
But you know, where?
So you know what?
I'll cook.
I don't think so.
Look, if we were
in Boston, I could
take you to this great
Italian restaurant.
Yeah, well, if
we were in Boston,
I wouldn't have a thing towear because I've been working
at a marina for two years.
Well, then I'd take you downto the-- down to the pier.
And you could-- we
could go to Ed's Diner.
Good food, and plenty of it.
Maybe.
Can I take that as a yes?
Mm.
I don't think it's a good idea.
Are you gonna hold one momentof bad behavior against me
for the rest of my life?
It's complicated.
ROBERT: Yes, it is complicated.
Life is complicated, onedamn thing after another.
[laughs]
Can I bring dessert then?
ROBERT: Absolutely not.
In fact, you can bring anythingyou want, except dessert.
See ya.
[door opens]
[chattering]
[door closes]
[CASH REGISTER BEEPING AND WHIRRING]
[INSECTS CHIRPING AND WAVES LAPPING]
[footsteps]
Two dogs--
Ah.
--with the works.
I love sauerkraut.
- You know, I don't know--- Mm.
I don't know what
it is, but lately--
Mm.
--I've been having acraving for this kind of food.
I don't know.
- Mm.
It's comfort food.
It's cause you're home.- Oh, is that what it is?
I feel the same way.
Whenever I go home, I
always ask my mother
to make spaghetti and meatballs,tomato soup, meatloaf,
and grilled cheese sandwiches.
[speaking french]
Mm, you speak French.
Of course.
All these foods
are in my cupboard.
Mhm.
Except for meatloaf
and, uh-- mm-- this.
Now where did you get that?
Mrs. Beecham.
Does she have a first name?
Yes, she's my trusted
and loyal assistant.
She sends me care packages.
Try it.
[french], huh?
Mm.
That and, of course, mustard.
Now don't tell me shesent you this from Boston.
No, from Paris.
You're kidding.
That's why she's
indispensable.
I see.
I miss this.
And at the end of themeal, a further surprise--
dessert.
Now what would dessert entail?
Oh, I can't tell you.
It's a surprise.
Oh, come on.
Just give me a little hint.- No, it wouldn't be a surprise.
No, just a little hint.
Well, all right.
In boarding school,
this stuff was
so good that it wasforbidden to all and sundry
in the lower forms.
Really?
You're gonna have to wait.
Now what if I don't
have any patience?
- Eat up.
- OK.
[laughs]
ROBERT: Wow.
Well, I wanted to strikethe proper note of respect.
I feel like I'm being
admitted into some kind
of secret society.
That's absolutely
magnificent, my dear.
Now you have to,
um, come over here.
Now don't look.
Don't peek.
OK.
OK?
Now you're going to sit there.
And I'm gonna sit here, OK?
It's like a ritual.
- All right.
All right, together.
That's good.
Now--
- [laughs]
--close your eyes.
Close your eyes.
You can't look.
- Mhm.
- All right, ready?
OK.
No peeking.
I'm not peeking.
- OK, open them.
- Oh, my god.
Ha, ha-ha.
Mm.
Gosh.
[laughing]
[clears throat]
- Yeah.- That's your big surprise?
- Yeah.
- Mars bars?
No, no, no, this isn'tjust, you know, Mars Bars.
This is, like, frozen Mars bars.
- Mhm.
- What, what, what?
You know about it?
Yeah.
Oh.
Haven't you seen my
freezer at the marina?
No, why?
Well, I sell them to
the kids all the time,
and I actually have
my own secret stash.
You mean to tell meeverybody knows about this?
Mm, yeah.
This is terrible.
- Can I eat this now--
- Yes.
--before it melts?
OK.
Yes, there you are, my dear.
Oh, look, a chocolate.
Oh god, and vanilla.
Mm.
Mhm.
- I love this.
This is so good.
Mm.
You know what my sister
and I used to do?
No, what?
We used to take ice
cream and Mars bars
and peppermint crunchy things--
Mhm.
--and pistachios, and weput them all together, right?
And then we'd stuff thembetween these two graham
crackers.
And then we'd put
it by the fire.
And then it would all melt.- Mm.
And then we'd take a big bite.
And then we'd get it
all over our face.
- Oh, god.
- And it was so good.
It's a terrible addiction.
Mhm.
Mm.
What?
- Oh, nothing.
Hm.
What?
I think you might, um--
I think you have a little, um--
like a little, um--
- Are you trying to kiss me?- Yes.
OK.
[laughs]
Mm.
This one's hard to open.
Mm, oh, well, I like totake a bite out of each one
and then lick it--
EVIE: [laughs]
ROBERT: --and toss it away.
I haven't had
this much chocolate
since I was like eight.
- Mm.
- Oh, my god.
- This is so strange.
Mhm.
What's strange?
This is so strange.
I grew-- I grew up here.
This is my room.
Really?
Mhm.
Well, OK, where are allthe, like, airplanes and--
All those little dinosaurs?
--toy cars and
little dinosaurs.
Oh.
I, uh, had it re-- redecorated.
Yeah.
So what do you think?
Oh, yeah.
- Pretty-- pretty bland, right?- Mm.
Yeah.
Well, I-- you
know, I didn't even
meet the interior decorator.
I wanted to get
rid of this place,
but Kevin wanted
to hold onto it.
Why'd you redecorate?
It's a long story.
My dad bought this place formy mom cause she was sick.
Now he thought that maybe thecountry would-- would help,
do her some good.
But it didn't, and she died.
My father sank into a
very deep depression.
A year later he killed himself.
I'm so sorry.
Well.
Well, I still had Kevin.
And Kevin had you.
No, not really, not at first.
I pushed him away.
But everywhere I went,there he was, looking at me.
After school doing
my homework, I--
finally, I went up to him.
And I said, what do you want?
He looked at me, and heasked, are you gonna die too?
Are you gonna go away?
I-- I let him down.
EVIE: No, you didn't.
He loved you very much.
[birds calling]
[clock ticking]
- Boy--
- [gasps]
--you get up early
in the morning.
Oh.
[laughs]
You scared me.
I'm sorry.
Oh, well, you just--
you looked so peaceful
I didn't wanna wake you.
What ya doing?
I'm snooping.
Oh, you're snooping.
Mhm.
And what are you snooping at?
I just wanted to
see if I was right.
About what?
May I?
Yes.
Ah!
Yes!
You see, Kevin never
unwrapped his lures.
Hey, what is that?
This is Kevin's prototype.
I've been looking for this.
[clicking]
Aw, darn.
What?
It's not working.
Can I get you some coffee?
Coffee, yeah.
That would be great.
Thank you.
- OK.
[doorbell rings]
DELIVERY MAN: Here you go, sir.
ROBERT: Thanks.
[dishes clanking]
Would you like some breakfast?
I promise there are no
Mars bars on this tray.
[pouring]
What's wrong?
Come over here.
Take a look at this.
[sighs]
This is what Kevin was
working on when he died,
the Thornhill Explorer.
You tell it, uh,
where you wanna go,
and it'll show you
how to get there.
Well, it's a great idea.
Yeah, except it doesn't work.
And this here is the
Savatar Navigator.
It does what this
is supposed to do.
They didn't?
Yeah, as a matter of fact,they did, and I can prove it.
Take a look at this.
That's the Explorer's software.
Kevin designed that.
He liked to play around, putlittle messages, show off.
K-E-V.
ROBERT: "Kevin."
Now let's look at
the Savatar software.
Again.
See it?
There.
Oh, my god.
ROBERT: Identical software.
It's not a coincidence.
Kevin was murdered.
[beep]
I can't believe theykilled Kevin for software.
Yeah, well, it's
worth millions to them.
That's pretty good motive.
Ah.
I'm gonna have to buildone of these from scratch.
Why when you
already have proof?
Because whoever sabotagedproduction at the factory
is behind Kevin's murder,and he's still around.
Which means you can't getparts from your factory.
No.
And I can't trust anybody.
I can go to Halifax for you.
You know, you're
really something.
[birds calling]
[phone ringing]
[sighs]
[beep]
ROBERT [ON PHONE]: Hello.
I hope I'm not
interrupting anything.
ROBERT [ON PHONE]: Ah, Beecham.
It's OK.
I didn't need a shower anyway.
What's up?
I'm sorry.
But when you weren't
at the plant,
I figured I should give
you a call at home.
ROBERT [ON PHONE]:
Well, what is it?
BEECHAM [ON PHONE]:
Evangeline Shaw.
No, no, no, I--I thought we stopped all that.
Uh, what's going on?
More than meets
the eye, apparently.
ROBERT [ON PHONE]:
Well, what is it now?
Ferguson dig something up?
Uh, she has a history
of family lunacy?
She's got seven kids
somewhere, is that it?
BEECHAM [ON PHONE]:
It's financial, boss.
Ferguson got new informationon both her and the marina.
Well, then you better
tell me about it.
BEECHAM [ON PHONE]: No, Ican't, not over the phone.
It's too sensitive.
I sent you Ferguson'sreport by encrypted email.
Boss, I'm sorry to
say that Kevin's
name appears all through it.
Kevin?
[beeping]
Who else knows about this?
BEECHAM [ON PHONE]:
Just me and Ferguson.
ROBERT [ON PHONE]: I wantyou to keep this between us.
Absolutely.
[sighs]
What do you wanna do?
Play along.
Someone went to a lot of
trouble to set this up.
BEECHAM [ON PHONE]:
Oh, boss, come on.
This is getting really scary.
Kevin's dead because of this.
Don't do anything foolish.
Oh.
Well, I have no choice.
I'm gonna have to shake
this tree real hard
and see what falls out.
[door closes]
I gotta go.
I'll call you later.
[beep]
EVIE: Oh, my god, this
stuff is so expensive.
This guy thought that I wasthis real high-tech junkie.
Oh, I stopped by the marina,and I got these tide tables too.
And-- what?
I-- I thought you told
me that, uh, the marina
didn't make a profit last year.
EVIE: No, it didn't.
And-- and you--
you haven't bought a new
dress in over two years,
is that right?
Well, I haven't had
to until last night.
ROBERT: And-- and you knewmy brother, Kevin, only--
only to talk to him?
All right, what's going on?
- Tell me about "lantern."- "Lantern"?
Tell me about "beagles."
EVIE: "Beagles"?
When was the last time
you were in Switzerland?
Uh, Grant and I went
there two years ago.
And while you were there,did you happen to visit Davos,
visit a charming,
discreet little bank?
What?
Take a look at this.
A series of deposits in a Swissbank account, Shaw's Marina,
in your name.
What are you talking about?
What I'm talking about
is deposits of 600,000
in your name, deposits1,200,000 in your name, deposits
of 450,000 in your name.
[laughs]
I would know if I
had that much money.
You do.
This is your account,
your passwords.
Password, "lantern."
Password, "beagles."
Oh, and-- and one other
thing, coincidentally,
the date of the deposits
coincides with the dates
of Kevin's visits here.
That's a pretty good racketyou've got here, Shaw's Marina.
You must think we're
all chumps, don't you?
Is that what you thought
Kevin was, a chump?
Wait a second.
You're accusing me ofsleeping with your brother
in order to rip you off?
I am accusing you of
stealing his designs
and selling them
to the competition.
That's what I'm accusing you of.
Ugh.
What do I know about
computer software?
You don't have
to know anything.
All you have to do is slip a--a disk into somebody's pocket.
Now why would he do that?
Because he was jealous.
Of you?
You knew this whole houseof cards was gonna fall down.
That's why you started thisaffair with me, isn't it?
Oh, we had an affair.
ROBERT: It all went
according to plan.
"Keep your friends close andyour enemies even closer."
What do I know about computersoftware and money laundering?
ROBERT: Everything that
your husband taught you.
Or is this just coincidence?
You--
[scoffs]
You want to believe this.
You let me into your life.
You trust me.
And now you're pushing me away.
You'd rather believe that yourown brother sold you out than
admit that you care about me.
It's OK.
If you're that afraid, go ahead.
Call the cops.
[keys jangling]
Oh.
[door opens]
[door closes]
[beeping]
You really think shewas in on this with Kevin?
Security dug up the secretbank accounts in Switzerland.
I don't think it.
I got proof.
It's hard to believe.
It explains everything.
It explains the delays.
It explains the disasters, whyyou couldn't get to the root
of it, why it kept changing.
I guess I should'vekept a closer eye on him.
I don't know what I did wrong.
I just wanted what
was best for him.
ORRIN MERCER: You tried, Robert.
Kevin had to learn
to help himself.
I'm real sorry about this.
So am I.
[door closes]
But why are you arguing with me?
I wanna press charges.
In fact--
- There is not enough evidence--- --I want you to press charges.
--to lay a charge.
Oh, with all my
foreign accounts--
Oh, you sound like
you're proud of that.
--why am I stillselling worms to tourists?
It's quite obvious.
Because you're covering.
- Oh, please.
- You're covering up.
You're-- you're laying down.
Look, I've got evidence here.
I've got bank statements.
I've got deposit times.
I've got signatories.
I've even got passwords here.
I want her arrested.
- This is insane.
- Gimme that.
- All right, I'll take--
I want her in jail.
I'll take this evidence,and I'll look into any charges
that have to be laid.
Oh, you're gonna
arrest me, Ian?
No, I'm not.
But, Evie, I don't
want you to leave
the area unless you notify me.
Oh, well, where am I gonnago with all my accounts frozen?
[birds chirping]
Well, Cannon is convincedthat Evie and his brother
sold the plans to Savatar.
He found the money
you put their account.
Controlled by the Widow Shaw.
I left a little electronictrail for your eager boss,
a back door to themarina's accounting program
that nobody knows about but me.
Well, now what?
Now all we have to
do is get out of here.
[LAUGHING] I don't
have to go anywhere.
Cannon doesn't
suspect me at all.
Yeah, you're squeaky clean.
This is my lovely wife.
I'm going to take Evie
on our second honeymoon.
That's crazy.
GRANT SHAW: Really?
Well, I think she's earnedit, having to survive
the past year without me.
You can't come out of hiding.
GRANT SHAW: Why not?
I mean, who do you
think this is all for?
It costs a lot to keep
a young wife happy.
And I want to make
Evie very happy.
Even though I had your bossfind a couple of million,
there's more than enough leftover for us and Evie too.
But she thinks you're dead.
What if she doesn't
wanna go with you?
Well-- well, what if
she goes to Cannon?
Then I'll take care of Cannon.
No.
No more killing, Shaw.
You can't do--
- You're squeamish.
- --any more killing.
Kevin's death--
- All we had to do--
- --was unfortunate.- --was keep Kevin quiet--
Look, once you
travel down this road--
- --for a couple of weeks.- --you can't just turn it off--
That's all we had to do.We shouldn't have killed him.
- --whenever you feel like it.- I told you not to--
Grow up, Mercer.
It's not a road.
It's a roller coaster ride.
And the only way you're going toget off is if I throw you off.
[birds calling]
BEECHAM [ON PHONE]: Fergusonthinks we need help.
And I think maybe we should hirea team of forensic accountants.
No, no, no, not yet.
BEECHAM [ON PHONE]: Look,boss, we feel that--
[sighs]
I feel that you might beputting yourself in danger.
And I just can't standby and watch you do that.
ROBERT [ON PHONE]: Look,
Beecham, I appreciate
your maternal concern.
But I am gonna do
this my way, OK?
Well, just why?
What are you trying to prove?
ROBERT [ON PHONE]: What
I am going to prove is
that Kevin was not dishonest.
And I'm going to ensurethat he gets full credit--
[beeping]
--for the-- uh.
That's odd.
- What?
Kevin's prototype.
[beeping]
Uh, it looks like it's working.
It must've gotten wet
in the tackle box.
Listen, tell Ferguson thathe's right, but to hold off.
And, uh, I'll call you tomorrow.
Thank you.
[beep]
[beeping]
Cool.
Very cool.
Huh?
I'll be damned.
[door slams]
Sorry, we're closed.
GRANT SHAW: Hi, honey, I'm home.
[laughing]
Did you miss me?
Grant?
GRANT SHAW: In the flesh.
Not bad for a dead man.
Aren't you surprised?
[gasps]
I've come back for youlike Orpheus for Eurydice.
I couldn't leave the
love of my life behind.
[waves lapping]
[beeping]
Mercer.
GRANT SHAW: Orrin Mercer andI were friends in college.
We made beer moneypirating computer programs.
Oh, oh-- oh, no, nothing
like this, of course.
And when Mercer got the jobrunning the Thornhill plant,
I bought the marina,
and we waited.
Hm?
And I figured the longer wewaited, the better it would be.
With all that money
we'd get, he and I
could just take off forever.
Get a beautiful sailboat,travel the islands.
EVIE: So the marriage andthe marina was all a lie.
Not our marriage.
Never our marriage.
That was the hard part.
I never stopped loving you.
Staying away was the hardestthing I've ever done.
You love me so
much you set me up.
I didn't.
Well, not at first.
I just figured nobody
would suspect you.
Now I used a back door
to the marina's accounts
to get the money
out of the country
without attracting attention.
[beep]
This way no one would
be able to [inaudible]..
[phone ringing]
WOMAN [ON PHONE]: Hello?
I need to talk
to Sergeant Macrae.
WOMAN [ON PHONE]: Oh,
he's eating his supper.
No, no, this is
very important.
Tell him it's Robert Cannon.
And then Robert Cannongot too close to the truth.
I had to expose you against.
IAN MACRAE [ON PHONE]:
What is it, Robert?
Look, I'm down at the marina.
Orrin Mercer's
just been murdered.
What?
I think I'm looking
at the man who did it.
He's with Evie Shaw.
I need you to get
down here immediately.
I'm on my way.
[dishes clanking]
Sweetie, call the station.
Tell them to bring the boat.
And what about Kevin?
Kevin, hm.
Oh, yeah, well-- well, thatwas-- that was unfortunate.
EVIE: Grant, I don't wanna go.
GRANT SHAW: No, no,
of course you do.
EVIE: Grant, my
life is here now.
I have the marina and every--
I am talking about
Rio, Paris, Rome.
We can go wherever you want.
Come on.
It'll be like a
second honeymoon.
Grant, I don't wanna go.
GRANT SHAW: You have no choice.
EVIE: [gasping]
Your rich boyfriend
doesn't wanna
have anything to do with you.
He'll have you arrested.
Sorry.
We have to go now.
[waves lapping]
[gunshot]
Hey!
[all groaning]
Ah.
Oh!
GRANT SHAW: [breathing heavily]
[groaning]
Untie the boat now.
[groans]
Come on, come on, come on.
Get on board.
On top.
Move, move, move!
[engine starts]
[grunts]
Oh.
Ah
[breathing heavily]
Hey!
[motor sputtering]
Oh, shoot!
Reliable!
[boat approaching]
Hey!
Hey, Macrae, over here!
Macrae!
What happened to you?
Grant Shaw is alive.
IAN MACRAE: How
do you know that?
He's got Evie.
He killed Mercer.
He's in that boat out there.
We gotta go after him.
You'll never catch
him in the dark.
ROBERT: Oh, yeah?
IAN MACRAE: What's that?
Something my kid
brother invented.
[beep]
What's it do?
It sees in the dark.
[beeping]
IAN MACRAE: If we do
catch her, stay below.
I don't wanna see
your face up here.
[beeping]
He's changed direction.
Where's he going?
You remember Smuggler's Cove?
[LAUGHING] Smuggler's Cove?
Which Smuggler's Cove
you talking about?
Up the north end of Shad Bay.
Gin?
That was the night you made medrink a whole bottle of gin,
and I still can't
touch the stuff.
IAN MACRAE: Good thing I can.
[beeping]
ROBERT: He stopped.
[WAVES LAPPING AND BIRDS
CALLING]
Pull us ashore
over there a bit.
What are you doing?
We can't go charging up thecove with our lights blazing.
They'll see us miles away.
I'm gonna have to get offthe boat and go on foot.
That's the only way we'regonna surprise them.
And don't go being a hero.
Move.
Come on.
Please, Grant, let me go.
Ugh.
I'm fine.
It's for your own good, Evie.
If you stay here,
you'll take the fall.
Watch your step here.
I'm sure your
boyfriend will have
boats and helicopters combingthe area in the morning.
We'll have to make a run
for Maine in the dark.
Voila, plan B.
[laughs]
Evie, come back!
Evie, there's no place to go.
Evie!
[insects chirping]
[breathing heavily]
[groaning]
Where you going, Evie?
Get up.
[groans]
GRANT SHAW: Come on.
- Grant--
Just--
--let me go.
Just let me go.
IAN MACRAE: Freeze!
[cocks gun]
Don't touch that gun.
Oh, you're looking prettyhealthy for a dead man.
GRANT SHAW: [groans]
You're lucky, Evie.
Robert saved your life.
Are you all right?
Thanks.
ROBERT: Uh, actually, I, uh--
I didn't save your life.
Kevin's invention
saved your life.
It's the least I could do.
Especially since you thoughtI was involved in this mess.
ROBERT: No, no, no,
that's not true at all.
I-- I just-- you know, I hadto find out what happened.
EVIE: Oh, so you were using me.
Yes.
I mean, no.
No.
Yes, uh, to find out
who killed Kevin.
You are such a cold fish.
I am?
[birds calling]
Yeah, and-- and set upthat meeting with Savatar.
I-- I--
BEECHAM [ON PHONE]:
I've already done that.
I called the chairman
of the board at home.
And he was awfully apologetic.
Yeah, I'll bet he was.
BEECHAM [ON PHONE]:
He expressed his shock
and horror at the idea
of being in possession
of stolen software.
And he said that
they would launch
a full-scale investigation.
Plus, he's waiting
to see you the second
you get back to Boston.
I'll bet he is,
considering we're
about to launch
a better product.
[laughs]
I've already scheduled amarketing meeting as well.
ROBERT [ON PHONE]: What
would I do without you?
I'll see you tonight.
- Great.
Have a safe flight.
And tell Evie I'm lookingforward to meeting her.
Excuse me?
I-- I'm coming home alone.
BEECHAM [ON PHONE]: Alone?
Robert Cannon, that has got tobe the most ridiculous thing I
have ever heard you say.
What?
BEECHAM [ON PHONE]: Youhave just lost your brother.
You've just lost your closestand oldest business associate.
You love Evangeline Shaw.
And if you're thinking ofleaving that woman behind,
then-- then you're thebiggest idiot I've ever met
and you deserve to live alonefor the rest of your life.
Now-- now look, Beecham, I--
I appreciate your concern.
But this is really
none of your business.
BEECHAM [ON PHONE]:
Hold on a second.
ROBERT: Hello?
Hey.
Hello?
Beecham, are you there?
Uh, uh, where is
that plane going?
Where is that plane going?
Hello, Beecham?
Hello, boss.
I told them not
to land just yet.
What?
BEECHAM [ON PHONE]:
That you still
had some unfinished business.
Don't come home without her.
Goodbye, Beecham.
[splash]
In the cup.
[clanking]
I'm sorry.
10 millimeter.
I love this wrench.
I love you.
And I'm an idiot.
Well, not completely.
You're very good
at making money.
ROBERT: Yeah, but
what good is that if I
don't have you in my life?
Spark plug tool.
You know, it was really,really dumb what I did.
It was extraordinarily stupid onmy part putting you in danger.
I mean, I love you.
If I had any brains at all,I would not have done that.
I apologize.
Well, Grant would'veshown up sooner or later.
[wrench clicking]
ROBERT: Would you please stopdoing that with the wrench,
please?
Well, then I won't knowwhat to do with my hands.
Um, just-- just
stop that, please.
[laughs]
[clang]
[waves lapping]
[birds calling]
[theme music]