This is Captain, Apollo Jacobs
Engaging target!
I repeat this is Captain,
Apollo Jacobs...
Can anyone hear me??
This is Captain, Apollo Jacobs
engaging target, I repeat
This is an emergency broadcast
transmission beacon!
We repeat! This is an emergency
broadcast transmission beacon!
All survivors must report to
designated hibernation
facilities!
We repeat!
All survivors must report to designated hibernation facilities!
What's happened here?!
I hope to God that this is
just a nightmare!
...and I'll wake up soon!
♪
Where is everybody?
For all I know, this is
some kind of sick joke or
experiment...
gone horribly wrong!
My God!
What caused this!? Huh!
Please don't!!
You don't deserve this!
I'm sorry, I...
Welcome to hell!
Wait! Hey!
No!
What's happening here?!
Huh?!?!
No!
What the hell!?
Whatever did this to you guys
is going to pay!
♪
Strange!
Something is watching me!
♪
Neptune!
Athena!
♪
Huh!?
Looks like we have new tenants!
Hello!
Anyone here?
Hello...
Lost man here.
Who seems to have...
What the...
Who seems to have missed
all the action!
It finally happened!
I could defintely use
a cup of coffee!
Will you just stand
there, as if I do not exist?
*Calm Music*
Have a seat.
I was right
Commander, getting signal of
a possible rogue human,
a possible threat!
Human insects! All human
life must be cleansed
out, for our eggs to
hatch!
Begin phase two, the
resurrection protocol:
Alpha Terraformation!
The first migration-armada
will arrive soon. Earth is
now our new home!
♪
Knock-Knock!
Open sesame!
Whoever was here was
well protected!
Wow!
Baracted all the way
to the end!
♪ Classical Radio Music ♪
Wish you were around
to tell me what happened.
The names are on my holo-wrist!
My wife disappeared three days ago.
I am afraid they got to her!
Those things are still out
there, spread all over!
They are like, perpetual!
And I am the last man standing!
♪
Steady!
This is an emergency
broadcast transmission
beacon!
We repeat! This is an emergency
broadcast transmission beacon!
All survivors must report
to designated hibernation
facilities!
We repeat! All survivors must
report to designated
hibernation facilities,
immediately!
We repeat! All survivors must
report to designated
hibernation facilities,
immediately!
This is an emergency broadcast
transmission beacon!
We repeat! This is an emergency
broadcast transmission beacon!
Broadcast transmission
beacon!
All survivors must
report to designated
hibernation facilities!
We repeat!...
I had no clue what was going on.
My mind...
Flashbacks...
No memory, whatsoever!
What has happened here!?
This just gets weirder and
weirder!
Nothing but particles in
the sky!
Friend or foe?!
What the hell is this?!
Can't be real!
It is real, quite real,
I am afraid.
The particles you see all
around you...
are all that remain of the
destruction of humanity.
What? Can't be!!
What are you??
It's rather obvious sir,
I am a Robot!
Mass produced pre-apocalypse.
What the hell happened here?
My radar indicates something
big, soon to arrive from
that sky!
Take a deep breath!
Cause, what I am about
to say, is not going to
be easy, sir!
You have been in
hibernation for
hundreds of years,
and have just awaken!
You sir, are the last...
on this planet!
What??
At some point in the last
century...
A rogue asteroid, was discovered heading
towards Earth.
The final blow to mankind came
much later.
A small armada of Alien ships
arrived from another world.
A very hostile species the
humans
called 'Octaliens'!
They descended on the remaining
humans with advanced weapons,
unlike anything
witnessed by mankind!
Turning humans in to killing
machines, by using the dead
to kill the living.
Creating armies of undead
creatures which devoured
everything and anyone!
Harnessing the power of lightning
as a weapon with strange
death machines!
Not even the Atom bomb
effected them!
How am I alive??
You must have been involved and
have fallen through the cracks.
You were a guinea pig.
You had no family, am I right?
But I died, and woke again!
Perhaps the stress is
causing mental neurosis,
PTSD or hallucinations....
But then again, it maybe
another weapon from the
Octaliens, sir!
It may be worth noting...
There is a possibility,
that their maybe
several more like you.
That are still alive, trapped
and captured!
The probability, however,
cannot be accurately calculated.
What is your objective??
I am the last of the mass
produced Robot HX-3069,
built in the fight against the
undead creatures...
Since it was way too dangerous
for the living...
My last program update,
before I powered down,
was to locate a key to
activate an escape ship.
All clues point to this area,
in fact, the signal has gone
way up, now!
An escape ship!?!?
Yes, there is an emergency
escape ship that will take its
crew to a large Earth
habitat space station.
It is thought to sustain a
rather nice life,
away from here!
What was that??!!
My scanners indicate,
undead hostiles
approaching, sir!!
Robot! Come with me!!
My batteries are too weak
to move far!
I will hold them up, good luck, sir!
I am afraid my batteries are too weak to move far!
I am afraid my batteries are too weak to...
I am afraid my batteries
are too weak to move far ...
Who was this guy??
The antagonist has a
step on you.
What you seek is there...
But will you have the courage to
retrieve it?
♪
I woke up to this...
World's end.
Destruction is all I see...
I keep getting images of
horror, and death of the humans.
YOU ready to get this on?!
Right!!
This place is like a Comic Book!
Are you visiting someone?
I was visiting someone too!
Huh!!
They are coming!!
No!
Huh??!! No!!
Stay down! Did you just wake??!!
Nevermind!
♪
Huh?!
Stand back! Stand Back!
It's Nephele!
From the hibernation facility!
I watched you die!
They are playing mind games,
the Octalliens!
Space and time are not
perceived to humans
the same anymore!
It could have been three years ago when you think you saw me!
Get it??
I still can't comprehend
what has happened!
I haven't been able to move
fifty feet away from this place!
I have been paralyzed.
It seems impossible, but it's true!
You have been here all this
time??
My mind! It's scrambled!
All I see is images
of death and destruction!
These innocent people!
They have been transformed by something!
Horrible things!
Is this even happening?
I don't know!
I woke up here! In the QRZ...
At least that's what I think
happened!
I am looking for some
sort of key. I think
it leads to an escape
pod or ship.
That's right!
The Robot back there, said the same thing!
Robot?? What Robot?!
There is no Robots
that I've seen! Ever!
Maybe years ago!
What is this... Red Zone?
The Quarantine Red Zone!
This is where people were
quarantined before going
into hibernation facilities!
When the Octaliens
came, they blasted
everything to hell!
Trapped in the deadliest zone!
With no weapons! My luck!
Will you help me get
across the QRZ?
♪
There might be other
survivors... I hope!
♪
Hello! Come in!... Hello
Can anyone hear me?
- Come in!? Hello??
- Come in!!
♪
Why aren't you attacking?
I'll see you again!
Everything will be fine in the end!
I promise!
Let's see what's
waiting for me here!
What evil power did this!?
My God! He's here!
It's the Captain!
Are you the Captain!?
We have been waiting
here a long time! Thank God!
I'm sorry, I'm no Captain.
I know what's going here!
We are dead!...
This is purgatory!!
Don't you get it, people?!
Wake up!
Oh my God!
We have woken up, Steve!
Now we are not in
purgatory, ok!! Let's just
keep it together,
that was the plan, right!?
♪
I'm sorry, I'm not the Captain!
I'm sorry, I'm no Captain!
♪
He's here!
- It's the Captain!
- We've been waiting here a long time, thank God!
Yes, I'm the Captain!
I'm here to get you out of here!
Err, but we don't
have any weapons!
♪
Stoooooooop!
Everything is gone!
We have to go!
Where are we going??
I think I know where
the key is!!
♪
Report on the rogue human!
I want this thing taken car of.
He is making me look weak!
Commander, it has evaded
capture! Detecting dark
matter paricles. Indicating
a time loop state!
That is not possible!
How can this be? One human
insect can not be destroyed
with all this f*&%$ power??!
Apologies Commander!
There is an indication of, possibly more humans!
Apologies?! The migration will
not be clean with even one
living human!
I want the insects destroyed!
Must I do this myself?
Prepare my squad ship!
♪
Here it is!
Be careful in there!
Don't touch anything!
We just need to find the
key and split!
♪
This is an emergency
broadcast signal!
How long did you stay here??
This is Captain Apollo Jacobs!
-Looks like a long time!
-Captain of Sector 17
Bunker Shelter.
It has now been many years!
If anyone can hear this!
You look so sad here!
Eclips...
Trapped in sector 17, bunker
shelter!
It has now been many years!
If anyone can hear this...
We did't make it!
I buried as many as I
could in this sector!
It's the least I could do
since I couldn't
get them to the ship!
The names of the dead...
They are all in my log files
of the Holo-Wrist!
My wife disappeared
three days ago!
I miss her terribly!
I am afraid she has turned
into one of them...
I calculate that I may have
been here for a half of century!
Or more!
If anyone can read this...
Please stay away
planet Earth is gone!
This is Captain, Apollo,
signing out.
♪
The human aberration has
been located, commander!
Send everything at it!
We are running out of time!
Everything, Commander??
Affirmitive!
Do you wish to see this world ours or do you wish to fail??!!
♪
I need you to trust me right now!
I need you to shoot me!
What?!?!
When I die! The day resets!
I hope!
♪
Now!!!
Now damn it, now!
♪
Welcome, General! Everything
is under control!
These insects are just about
wiped out!
Good! Our armada of ships are
above the planet. We will begin
the final terraform process
soon!
♪
Who is this human?
Is he the rogue anomaly I was briefed on?
Affirmitive! He will soon be
destroyed, General!
We have detected a space time loop within him!
The matter will be finished now!
Affirmitive! Do not fail!
You have caused me enough
embarrasment!
You will no longer be resetting
the day, you filthy insect!
The loop within you will be
stopped in a few moments!
What do you want??
This world, is one of the
richest sources of natural
minerals so close to
Alpha Centauri Star System!
Your kind was ungrateful for
this planet's gifts!
We will now call it our home!
My kind is about to land!
♪
Apologies, sir!
On my back up system!
♪
My kind is superior to you!
Robot!
Thank you!
I will hold them off as
long as I can!
It has been a pleasure
serving with you, sir!
Goodluck!
♪
This is what I was built for!
You got to be kidding me!!
♪
I'm not letting those things
desecrate anyone else’s body!
♪
Look!
The ship!
I wonder if she has
any juice left!
♪
[Heavy Breathing}
I can't loop again!
♪
It's not working!
It's not working!!
We got to go back to
the bomb shelter!
Welcome Captain,
Apollo Jacobs.
Captain, please repeat
your command.
♪
Captain, please repeat
your command.
Ship!
Emergency launch sequence!
Please confirm, automatic
pilot control
for emergency launch.
Confirming!
Initiating launch sequence.
Launch in t-minus thirty
seconds.
Captain, non-human biological
presence detected on board.
Growwwl!
This is now our home!
Hahahaha
Set course!
For that large mothership
approaching!
♪
Full speed!
Negative, Captain. Detecting
PTSD or neurosis...
-Ship!
-in your speech pattern!
Can not comply with last
command!
Please repeat!
Ship!
Yes, Captain?
Set course for that large
Mothership approaching.
Full speed.
Captain, that will cause total terminal destruction of this craft.
Please repeat.
♪
Override.
Set course, full speed,
at that large Mothership,
approaching!
Confirmed.
Activating self-destruct.
♪
You fucks, want this
planet!?
♪
I'll see you guys in hell!
Boom ♪
♪
it's a simple five week program.
Four weeks you sleep in the
hibernation bed...
One more week, we keep you
for observation.
and then twenty four months
as an outpatient.
♪
What's going on?!
What's the year??
Where is the exit??
♪
This is Captain, Apollo Jacobs
Engaging target!
I repeat this is Captain,
Apollo Jacobs...
Can anyone hear me??
This is Captain, Apollo Jacobs
engaging target, I repeat
♪