[Christmas-themed
orchestral music playing]
[indistinct chatter]
[music swells, ends]
["Sweet and Spicy"
by Aimee Garcia playing]
[woman] Angelina!
[indistinct chatter]
[Angelina singing
in mixed English and Spanish]
♪ We can run, we can run ♪
["Sweet and Spicy" continues]
[Angelina singing Spanish]
[man singing in mixed English and Spanish]
[woman] Angelina!
[camera shutters clicking]
[Angelina singing Spanish]
["Sweet and Spicy" fades out]
Flawless as always.
Our spacing was completely off.
And that pose at the end
still isn't strong enough.
[sighs] Always the perfectionist.
So, what do we got?
Press junket's up next.
- Be nice.
- Always.
- [woman] Let me introduce you to...
- Angelina Costa.
Madison Sparks, Celeb Buzzpop News.
It is, like, a total honor to meet you.
I have been a fan since I was a baby.
A baby? Really?
The industry has changed a lot
since your first single.
Like how your labelmate Cheri Bibi
utilized Twitter
to put momentum behind her latest single.
Yeah. She certainly is very innovative.
Totes.
Well, do you find it difficult
to stay on top of current trends?
I'm just wondering
if it's difficult to stay relevant.
[tensely playful music playing]
For example, recently, you put out
a TikTok that felt a little...
[sucking in air]
...outdated. [chuckles]
Is there pressure to keep up
with these younger artists?
Esta idiota.
What was that?
Oh. I love your shoes.
[Madison] Oh.
["Deck the Halls" instrumental plays,
ends dramatically]
[Angelina] She asked about the TikTok, Mo.
The TikTok!
I mean, she... She pretty much told me
that I should retire to my face.
Who cares what she thinks?
You have a shoot to be on the cover
of Fashion Beat magazine tomorrow.
That's what you need to be focused on.
- Right. Yeah.
- All right. Okay.
- Yeah.
- [ringtone plays]
- Oh.
- Yes.
Right. [sighs]
It's Barry.
Mmm. Mmm, don't get it.
But he's the head of the label.
I have to take it.
Well, Mo, just tell him I'm not here.
- I don't know. Make something up.
- Okay. [shushing]
Barry! Hi.
Hey, Monique. I was hoping
I can catch a moment with Angie.
You know, you just missed her.
She's off to a fitting
for tomorrow's shoot.
[Barry] Great, great.
I had a thought.
Ange should make a Christmas song.
Christmas songs are good for business.
- [whispering] No, no, no.
- Christmas is a few weeks away, Barry.
And I'm not sure that a Christmas song
really fits Angelina's whole thing.
What? Look what it did for Mariah.
That one song alone
can buy her a private island.
Don't you worry.
We've been working on some new material,
and I think she has a hit.
[Barry] Okay.
So when can I hear something?
You can hear it on Sunday at the gala.
[Barry] Okay. All right, well,
just make sure she delivers. Yeah?
- Of course. Of course. Okay. Bye.
- [softly] No! No!
Why'd you tell him we have a song?
We don't have a song.
I've literally been rehearsing my hits.
Mo, I have not been feeling inspired,
and I don't... I mean, I don't really think
that a Christmas song is my style.
And... [chuckles] ...it's not like
the record label's gonna drop me
because I don't want a "Jingle Bell Rock."
[Angelina chewing on celery]
[tense music playing]
Are you serious?
Wait.
Are you telling me that
Barry gets a shiny new toy,
and he would kick this to the curb?
Well, that shiny new toy
has a top-ten single right now.
My advice?
Shoot.
Stop rehashing your old hits.
Get in touch with your inner Holly Jolly,
and write a new hit single
that he can release this Christmas.
["Luna Rumbera" by Juan Jose Covarrubias
& Janelly Del Carmen Russe playing]
[woman singing in Spanish]
- [dramatic music playing on TV]
- [man breathing heavily on TV]
[speaking Spanish]
[man on TV cheering, laughing]
- Mommy?
- [gasps in surprise, exclaims]
Could we turn the telenovela down, please?
No way!
Ricardo just got up from the dead!
[man on TV crying for joy]
- Yeah, that's more important.
- [Mommy sighs]
[pulsating beat from ceiling]
[mouths silently, sighs]
[upbeat Latin pop playing]
Cristina!
Sweetheart, can you please turn it off?
- [scoffs]
- [music stops]
Between your music
and your grandmother blaring the TV,
I can barely hear myself think.
Anyways, can you please play the guitar
on my video?
- No.
- Aw, please?
No.
Please?
I'll frame you out.
You won't even be in it. Okay?
[sighs heavily] You better.
Yes! [laughs]
[heartwarming music plays]
[playing "Jingle Bells" melody on piano]
[playing piano]
[mashes keys]
- [mashes keys]
- [sighs]
[siren blares in the distance]
[sighs]
[melancholic music playing]
I miss you, Ma. [kisses]
[sharply inhales]
[inhales, exhales deeply]
Tsk, oh...
[clicking on laptop]
♪ No matter where you go ♪
♪ I'll always keep you with me ♪
♪ And I know ♪
♪ Your love is here to stay ♪
♪ I'll always keep you with me ♪
♪ And I'll always ♪
♪ Have a place in my heart ♪
♪ Where you stay ♪
[touching music playing]
That song was by Angelina Costa.
- Who... Well, who doesn't know who she is.
- [laughs]
[sighs] My mom and I used to listen
to that song a lot together.
[sniffles] Um...
My mom passed away a few years ago.
Um, I'm gonna use it
in my quinceañera next week,
so it feels like she's there.
My Christmas birthday wish is
to one day meet Angelina.
Maybe take a selfie with her.
[sighs]
And tell her
how much her song means to me.
[gently inhales]
[piano playing]
[slams keys discordantly]
[playful Latin music playing]
Ah, there she is!
Smile for the camera, mi amor.
Ricardo! What a surprise.
Uh, well, hey there, everyone.
I plan on having some new music
for you very soon.
Oh. Well, what about
a little bit of, uh... inspiration?
Oh. Pues por supuesto.
- [both making kissing sound]
- [Ricardo chuckles]
[Angelina] Okay. Mmm.
- Merry Christmas to me.
- Oh. [chuckles] Okay.
- We have it?
- What're you doing here?
Baby, what? I can't resist this.
You know, the behind-the-scenes content
always lights people up.
No, no, no. Stop. Stop.
No, we agreed.
Baby, we got 15 million followers
that are hungry for content.
Plus, we need some extra footage
to promote the gala.
No, the gala?
That's not what the event is about.
It's about the charity, not us.
[Ricardo] I'm on your side, okay?
- Right?
- Yeah.
- Ricalina.
- Mm-hmm.
- Ha ha! It's good for both of us.
- Right.
- Yes?
- Yes.
- Yes! Yeah. Ricalina.
- That's a yes. That's a yes. That's a yes.
- Okay.
See you later, Mo.
- Catch up with you.
- [Angelina] Yep.
[Ricardo] Bye.
[Angelina sighs]
What?
I thought Ricalina
was going public with the breakup.
We can't.
We can't!
He's right. Not yet.
We got to get our numbers up.
We have 15 million. We need 200.
We got to get those Beyoncé numbers.
Whatever.
["Carol of the Bells"
instrumental playing]
[song abruptly ends]
[woman speaking Spanish on TV]
- [groaning] Dad, where's my phone?
- Where did you leave it?
Mijo, if she knew where she left it,
it wouldn't be lost.
[sighs] Ooh, what are you making?
[Dad] Pozole!
Mmm, it smells so good. [chuckles]
Here it is.
Yay!
[sighs] It's dead.
- Oh. It's a Christmas miracle.
- [chuckles]
Come on, we're gonna be late.
Love you, Mama.
- Adiós.
- Bye, Abuela!
- ["Born with It" playing]
- ♪ I got that energy, yuh ♪
♪ Ain't never stopping it, yuh ♪
♪ I got that energy, yuh ♪
♪ I know you wanna get, yuh, yuh ♪
♪ I got that energy... ♪
Girl! That outfit is fire.
I mean, I knew it was gonna look good,
but seeing it on you?
- You are working it.
- Thank you.
Yeah, I am feeling it.
You should.
I was actually going to order lunch.
You want anything?
Oh, absolutely not.
With the performance coming up,
I got to stay strict. [exhales]
You wanna talk about it?
Uh, yeah, sure. I plan on doing
a lettuce diet up until the gala.
Hold on. What is a lettuce diet?
It's when you only eat lettuce.
But you alternate by day
the kind of lettuce you eat.
It's much more exciting than it sounds.
- Mo?
- [Monique] Huh?
The transition from arugula to spring mix
makes your whole week.
Okay, no more distractions,
deflections, excuse me, or arugula.
Venga. Sit down.
Come on.
Talk to me.
[somber music playing]
My head is just not in it, Mo.
Okay, I'm not feeling it. I...
I mean, you know
I haven't felt Christmas since...
- Well, you know, Ma passed.
- [softly] I know.
And now they want me
to write a Christmas song. Seriously?
Ho ho ho, deck the halls.
No, it's not happening.
Okay, let's go.
[Angelina blowing raspberries
in music scale]
[Monique] You look beautiful.
- We have to make this tighter.
- No... We... I don't...
- [sighs] Wait, do I have muffin top?
- I'm not even answering that.
- I can pinch. I'm pinching.
- You're not pinching. Please.
- Angie.
- Barry.
- What are you doing here?
- Hey.
I figured I'd come by
and chat with you in person.
Is this about the song? 'Cause I've
actually been working on the song,
and it's coming along great.
I would absolutely love
to discuss the song. But first, Cheri!
You've met Cheri Bibi before, yes?
We haven't had the pleasure.
Oh my gosh. It is wild to meet you.
Likewise.
And look at your outfit.
I don't think I could ever pull off
anything so vintage.
[camera shutter clicking]
Mmm. [laughs awkwardly]
You... Why... Why don't you talk
to the photographers
and let Angie and I finish up?
Oh, of course.
So wonderful to meet you.
I cannot wait to hear the new single.
[squeals in delight]
[Barry] You a star, girl!
Mmm.
[whistles]
- Isn't she something?
- [Angelina] Yeah, yeah, yeah, she sure is.
What did you mean by
go talk to the photographer?
You and I need to talk about some shifts.
Shifts?
It feels like the focus is in your past,
and the label really wants to project
an image of the future.
I don't understand. What?
Fashion Beat agreed
to make Cheri the cover instead.
[tense music playing]
What? Wait.
- Are you serious?
- Yeah. She's just more relevant right now.
- Barry, you can't do this.
- It's already done.
You look great, by the way.
Hey, Monique.
[camera shutters clicking]
[melancholic music playing]
[struggling to contain sob]
Grab your stuff.
We're leaving.
[intriguing Latin music playing]
- We'll be at your place in 20.
- No. I don't want to go to my place.
I just wanna get out here,
out of the city.
- What do you mean, out of the city?
- Just anywhere but here, Mo.
Okay, I'm not sure
you're thinking clearly. So let me...
Let's just go.
Where do you want the driver to take us?
Just tell him to take the day off.
I'll drive.
Okay, okay.
- Thank you. Honey.
- You're welcome.
[chuckles] You haven't driven anywhere
by yourself in over a decade.
Okay, fine. You'll drive.
Okay.
So remind me again.
We're going where exactly?
I don't know, Mo. Okay, I don't know.
Okay. [scoffs]
Not that I don't love driving aimlessly
when we have a deadline
to finish a new song,
but the gala is in a few days.
This is not exactly the time
to be impulsive.
I just... I need to get away
from all this to come back stronger.
Okay, Mo?
Just... please, just give me this. Please.
That's it.
[Monique] What?
[playful music playing]
This is where we're gonna go, Mo.
What are talk... What?
What are you talking about?
- Okay, this girl.
- Okay.
Last night, I saw this video she posted
where she covered one of my songs.
Mo, her singing and her tribute
were so beautiful.
And in the video,
she said that she really wished
she could meet Angelina.
So, let's go grant her Christmas wish.
Why?
Since when do we do house calls for fans?
It's good business, Mo.
Meeting a fan and granting
her Christmas wish. I mean, come on.
I really need this.
I really need
to connect with my fans right now.
I mean, at least
they still think I'm relevant.
Say I go along with this.
- You will.
- I might not.
How do we even find this girl?
What do you mean? She geotagged her pic
and hashtagged her high school.
She's just a couple hours away.
Ugh. Social media creeps me out.
Whatever.
["The Twelve Days of Christmas" plays]
- [girl] Hey, Cristina.
- Hey.
Hi, Uncle. See you in music class.
And don't be late, and keep practicing.
Everything okay?
Yeah, it just needs
to charge a little more.
Not with the phone. I meant with you.
You know, there's still time
to make changes if you want.
Dad, it's my party.
I should be the one stressing.
Ah, you only turn 15 once.
I just want you to have an amazing day.
Dad, you're doing great.
[indistinct chatter]
[nervously] Hi.
You know, if you want a plus-one...
No.
Okay. I know. I'll make you a Bumble
'cause you're definitely way too old
for Tinder.
Absolutely not.
You don't have that app
on your phone, do you?
No.
- Oh!
- What? What is it?
Our video only got 20 views.
Good. Those videos should just be
for you and your friends.
What, you thought Angelina might see it?
Well, yeah. Sometimes she likes
and shares her fans' edits
and posts them on her story.
It's actually pretty nice
of her. [chuckles]
Angelina? Hey, is she on that Bumble?
Dad.
Uh-uh. No. Uh-uh.
[Latin pop music playing]
Where are the people?
[phone vibrating]
Seriously?
Stupid ex?
He's probably just planning
some Insta post.
However will he get through without them?
[Angelina laughs]
Oh, okay. So I think that's it.
[sighs] Well, at least this outfit
will get photographed.
- ["La Gata" by X-Ray Dog Music playing]
- ♪ Wow, wow, wow, wow, wow ♪
♪ All my kitties say ♪
♪ Meow, meow, meow, meow, meow ♪
♪ All my dogs say
Wow, wow, wow, wow, wow ♪
♪ All my kitties say ♪
♪ Meow, meow, meow, meow, meow ♪
♪ La gata ♪
[song ends]
[indistinct chatter]
[whispers] Ask him.
No.
[playful music playing]
[sighs]
Hey, Scott.
So, like, Cristina
has her quinceañera coming up.
There will be food and dancing,
and you should totally come.
So, like, a 15th birthday thing.
- Yeah.
- Mm-hmm.
Dope.
[mouths silently]
[woman on PA] Cristina and Miguel Torres
to the principal's office.
[tense music playing]
- What did you do?
- Nothing. What did you do?
Nothing.
Ah! Wonderful, you're here.
I didn't wanna keep them waiting too long.
- Keep who waiting? What's going on, Tom?
- Your daughter has a visitor.
- [screams with joy]
- Oh.
Oh.
[gasping] Oh my God!
I... I... I can't believe you're here!
- I can't believe it either.
- Wh... what is this all about?
Th... that's my dad.
Oh right, Ms. Costa, this is Miguel.
He's our music teacher.
Oh! Music teacher.
Well, Cristina's chops must run
in the family then.
Did you see the video?
I did. And I loved it.
- You did?!
[Angelina] Mm-hmm.
Especially the part about your mother.
I added some stuff.
You know, it reminded me of what
I felt like when I first wrote that song.
So, I wanted to do something for you.
You mentioned in the video
you wanted to take a selfie, right?
- Mm-hmm.
- Well, let's get you a selfie.
[playful music playing]
[camera shutter clicking]
- [Angelina] Are you happy with them?
- [Cristina] Mm-hmm.
Okay.
Well, we should get on the road.
We don't wanna get stuck,
especially since you're on a deadline.
Oh, you... you don't want to drive in this.
Or at least wait until the snowplows
clear the streets.
Well, since you're stuck here,
why don't we have dinner at my house?
[Miguel] Cristina!
- We'd love to.
- [Monique] We would?
[Angelina] Mm-hmm.
Are you crazy? We gotta get back.
We can't go anywhere
until the roads are clear, Mo.
Your ability to put off this song
is almost admirable.
[Cristina] My dad's an amazing cook.
He's really good.
Dad, please! Please!
[sighs]
I made plenty of pozole. [chuckles]
[intriguing Christmas theme playing]
[Monique] Mm-mm. Mm-mm-mm-mm-mm.
No. Not happening. Mm-mm.
No.
Uh,
can I use these?
[groaning]
[intriguing music playing]
[Angelina] Ooh, ooh.
[Monique] What are you doing?
Uh, what do you mean, what am I doing?
These are designer heels, Mo.
Okay, I got them
during Fashion Week in Milan.
[Monique] Mm-hmm.
They are not, and I repeat,
not meant to experience the elements.
I need a picture of this
so I can leak it to the press. [chuckles]
Don't you dare.
- [laughing]
- Don't you dare.
Too good.
[Angelina] Okay. Wait,
you're supposed to be my support.
Okay. He's right there.
[Monique chuckling awkwardly]
We're fine.
Yes.
[softly] Hi, sweetie.
- Thank you.
- All right.
- They're Yves Saint Laurent.
- [Monique] Mm-hmm.
Custom.
Yeah. So cute. Hi.
It's so cute.
[playful music continues]
- [Monique] Mmm.
- Oh.
[door closes]
Welcome to our home. Can I take your coat?
Oh no.
- Take the bags off.
- Oh.
- All right.
- [sighs]
Angelina! Can I show you
my quince dress ideas?
Uh, yeah, yeah, sure.
Oh. Okay.
[footsteps receding up stairway]
Wine?
- Dear God, yes. Thank you.
- [sighs]
These are my... [giggles]
...quince dress ideas.
[inhales, exhales loudly]
I was thinking about the rose gold,
but I don't know. What do you think?
This one?
Solid choice.
[inhales loudly]
Who is this young man?
Oh, just a guy from science class.
- Just a friend, huh?
- [Cristina] Tsk, I guess.
Gloria's always trying
to get me to talk to him,
but I'm like, what if he doesn't like me?
[whispering] But what if he does like you?
I know, scary, right?
But I'm the worst person to be giving
advice about this romantic stuff.
Just ask any of my exes.
Yeah, but aren't you dating
Ricardo Mondraga?
It seems you'd be the perfect person
to give advice on this kind of stuff.
Mm-hmm. [clears throat]
Is this your mom?
That was my mom.
[touching music playing]
- You wanna see a picture of my mom?
- Yes.
This is my mom.
[gasps softly]
She's so pretty.
Thank you.
She, um...
She passed a few years back.
During this time.
Uh, do you wanna sit down?
Oh.
You can sit down. It's okay.
- Go ahead, sit down.
- Oh.
Okay.
Oh! [sighs]
Things just have not been the same
since I lost her.
My mom.
She would have loved it here.
Oh, with all the lights and the snow...
She loved Christmas so much.
It's crazy, you know, I'll catch myself.
I'll get really excited
to tell her about my day,
and then I'll remember that she's gone.
I know that exact feeling.
There's so much I wanna share with her.
Like my quince, for example.
It's supposed to be this big moment
on my way to becoming a woman.
And it feels strange.
Just
not to have her there to see it.
Well, I'm sure
she would have been very proud of you.
And lucky for you, you've got your dad.
Yeah, he's...
[sighs] He's pretty great.
[grunts] I'm home.
That storm casi me mata.
[gasping]
I would've been back sooner,
but Conchi and Connie.
Ay, Dios mío,
those tías can talk.
¿Quiénes son estas?
Mama, these are my friends.
And the weather's too bad to drive home.
They're gonna sleep over. Okay?
Claro, mijo. [chuckling]
- Abuela, this is Angelina.
- Hola, señora.
And this is Monique.
This is my mom.
[all chuckling]
Welcome to our home!
Ay, bienvenida.
Gracias.
Yo soy Frida.
- Oh!
- Frida!
- Oh! Oh. Oh. Okay.
- ¡Bienvenida!
[Angelina laughs]
You hungry?
- Uh... [spluttering]
- Yes, we... Okay.
Let's eat!
[Spanish guitar music playing]
And we're live in the studio
with Angelina, que me fascina.
[laughing]
It's good. Es que...
- Where is she?
- [sound engineer mumbles]
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
[Frida exclaims]
[all laughing]
- Wow!
- Oh, this is...
So you don't get cold!
- Oh.
Gracias. Gracias, señora.
[Frida chuckling]
Wow. Wow. Wow.
This looks so delicious.
I have not had
a home-cooked meal in forever.
- Really?
- [Monique] Yeah, that's true.
I have all her favorite restaurants
on speed dial.
Mmm. Oh, uh, thank you.
I'm sure it's delicious,
but I'm just gonna,
uh, stick with some beans.
- Huh?
- I have to fit in my dress for this thing.
You're just gonna eat beans?
Yeah, I mean, it's protein.
Don't get me started.
It's a necessary evil of showbiz.
That's why you're so skinny.
You need some fat to be healthy.
[Monique chuckling]
- Go on, Miguel. Dale pozole.
- Oh no. Gracias, señora. Estoy bien.
Dale, okey, ¿cómo que no? Dale.
Okay, Just un poquitito. Just a little.
- Un poquitito nomás.
- Okay, that's good. Thank you.
Sí, ahora aprovecha.
Okay. Estoy comiendo.
[laughing]
[slurps softly]
[with full mouth] Oh my God! It's so good!
[all laughing]
Well, if you ever get tired
of eating just beans,
my kitchen's always open.
I'll make sure you have my number.
- [Cristina] Does Ricardo cook?
- Who?
Uh, her boyfriend, Ricardo Mondraga.
You're dating Ricardo Mondraga?
No way! You're too skinny for him.
He's on the show Grandma watches.
Usted... You watch Reina del Mar?
That's all I watch.
Yeah. She never misses her telenovela.
[chuckles] She may love
your boyfriend more than you do.
[Monique laughs]
The one that takes
his shirt off in every scene?
- Yeah.
- [Monique] That's the one.
I would like to make a toast to the chef.
- [Monique] To the chef.
- To the chef!
[all laughing]
[wind blowing]
And this is our music room.
Oh!
So are these real,
or are all these just for show?
Oh, these are all his instruments,
and he composes too.
He even had a band.
Cristina.
It was a garage band in high school,
and it never left the garage.
A band, huh?
Yeah, I had the hair and everything.
Oh, I gotta see that.
[laughing]
You know, I always admired
those hair metal guys.
The only boys I know
who used more hairspray than I do.
- What's this?
- Oh, that's nothing.
Well, it's not nothing. It's just not...
done.
They say home is where the heart is.
- [playing notes on piano]
- [softly] They... They say...
♪ They say home is where the heart is ♪
- That's actually pretty good.
- [chuckles softly]
But, I mean, this is just the verse.
Where's the... Where's the hook?
Well, you know,
I'm... I'm... I'm still working on it.
Working on getting the band back together?
No, it's just for fun.
I haven't written for fun
in a really long time.
I think I can hear it. They say home...
What do you... Wait, look, let's try it.
- They say home is...
- What, are you serious?
Yeah, I'm serious. Come on. Live a little.
- [playing melody on piano]
- ♪ They say home is where the heart is ♪
Then you repeat it...
[mimicking melody]
...and it lands here.
That's really good.
Yeah. So they say...
So, yeah, you know,
what if you just adjusted it a little bit?
[mimicking melody] Then you go...
[mimicking melody]
...and then you go down there.
- That's... That's a lot better.
- Yeah? Yeah.
[mimicking melody]
Yeah?
[pencil scratching on paper]
Oh, I am so sorry.
I'm writing on your stuff.
No, no, no, no. It's okay.
It's good. It's good. [chuckles]
- You sure?
- Yeah. Yeah.
[Angelina] Okay, so then
we would go down here, right?
[mimicking melody]
Yeah, you know, and it's not just
the notes and the chords.
It's... it's the message. It's really sweet.
Home is where the heart is.
It really could use some finesse
and some retooling.
[intriguing music playing]
But the message has a lot of heart and...
I could help you with this if...
I mean, if you're looking for a cowriter.
I...
Uh,
well...
What?
Why me? I'm just a music teacher.
So what?
A... A good song is a good song.
And the DNA for something
really special is on that page,
and... and I can really feel it.
O... okay, but yeah...
[spluttering] ...wouldn't you
rather work with a professional?
Good music comes from the inside,
and I really feel like together
we can write a great song.
- Yeah, I just don't...
- Okay, I'm gonna level with you right now.
I need this.
I need a brand-new song, Miguel.
I need a brand-new Christmas song.
Okay, there. It's... It's out there.
I owe my label a new track,
and I've been coming up completely blank.
And I really feel that this could be it.
I mean, you saw how seamlessly
we played it together inside.
- I think that we could do this.
- Okay? Say we do this.
How... how does it even work?
Easy.
We agree up front
that it's a mutual split,
strictly business deal,
and I get my single.
You, nice chunk of change that you can put
towards Cristina's college
as well as
royalties if the song is a hit.
It would be kind of nice.
Oh, also, you can finally get the band out
of the garage.
[playful music playing]
[hesitates] I don't even know what to say.
Just say yes.
[whispering] Yes.
- So easy.
- [scoffs]
So, deal?
[sighs] Deal.
[Frida] Miguel, Miguel.
Vente, vente. Vente, vente.
¡Okey, ya, vete!
Give me a chance
to get to know our guests.
Dile, Cristina!
We women need some space to chitchat.
[Miguel] All right, don't worry.
You're gonna be okay.
- Just... don't let her drink after midnight.
- [Angelina laughs]
- Dad! Seriously? Why would you say that?
- [Angelina] I made a deal.
Who wants a shot?
["We Wish You a Merry Christmas"
instrumental playing]
[music ends]
[sighs]
He's kind of cute, you know.
Mo, don't even start with that.
I am here for the song and only the song.
I just hope the song is good enough.
["The Twelve Days of Christmas"
instrumental playing]
Miguel? Oh. Oh jeez.
[Miguel sighs]
[Angelina groans]
[Miguel] Oh no.
- Oh yes.
- [Miguel scoffs]
What?
Grandma broke out the Christmas tequila.
Ay, Dios mío. [chuckles]
She is a hoot, that lady.
Here. Take this.
I haven't touched it yet,
and you're gonna need that
way more than I do.
Thank you.
[softly slurps, swallows]
Ah, that is so good.
I hope it helps. And I'm so sorry.
Oh, don't be sorry.
- It... It was actually kind of fun.
- [Miguel chuckles]
Where are you guys off to?
- Oh, we're headed to my quince rehearsal.
- Oh, cool.
Uh, hey, so I wanted to tell you.
I worked on the song some more last night.
- Really? Me too. What'd you do?
- What'd you do?
Oh, I can play it for you real quick
if you want...
- It's the...
- I... Well, no.
We... We will be back in a bit,
but you are more than welcome
to go inside, stay warm,
use the piano, and we'll be right back.
Or we could go back to the city.
[Miguel] Sure. Yeah. Yeah.
I mean, you probably have to go...
anywhere... celebrities go.
Miguel, I need the song ASAP.
I can't just stay here when we're both
clearly vibing on song.
I mean, we're... We're... What if we miss
a crucial moment of inspiration? I...
We're flowing. I can't...
Uh... [sighs]
Okay. Yeah, you know what?
I'll just come with you.
Yeah. I'll just come with you,
and we can work at the rehearsal.
What? You... you wanna come?
I mean, unless you don't want me to.
I... I don't want to overstep.
Well, no, no, no.
Of course, I'd...
Of course, we want you to.
I mean, you're more than welcome.
It's just,
you're probably used to
events of a certain
caliber and style,
and we're a little more...
Miguel, I'm a recording artist.
I'm not a space alien.
But, you know,
let me just clean up a little bit.
So, we're going to a quince rehearsal now?
[Angelina] Quince time.
Oh my gosh! I'm freaking out!
Speaking of freaking out,
I have no idea how your tías
are gonna react to this.
[both tías screaming]
[both speaking excitedly and indistinctly]
I said don't freak out.
Clearly it runs in the family.
It's her mother's side.
[both speaking excitedly, laughing]
This is Connie and Conchi.
Cristina's tías. And they're
helping Cristina with her quince.
- Hello.
- I love you.
Oh!
- Thank you.
- I love you more!
Oh.
Is this because of the video you did?
[kids laughing]
I know! You should do
a video for Beyoncé next.
I actually know Beyoncé.
[all] You do?!
[Cristina] Okay, guys,
let's stretch it out.
[Conchi speaking Spanish]
Okay, so can I show you some
of the lyrics I thought of last night?
Wow!
Okay. So... Ah, here we go.
What do you think about this?
I don't want Christmas
just to be another day.
Is that good? Is that too much?
No, no, no, no, no. I love it.
Wh... what... what about this? May I?
Oh yeah. Of course.
[Conchi] Come on.
[Conchi] Come on. Come on.
'Cause there can be
no Christmas without you.
Yes!
- Yes! That is it! That's perfect.
- [Conchi] Take it from the top.
- ["Luna Rumbera" playing]
- Five, six, seven, eight.
One, two, three,
four, five, six, seven, eight.
And one, two, three, four...
This... this is crazy.
I must have listened
to your Love It or Leave It album
a thousand times in the car,
the break room, at the gym. [chuckles]
Wait, Love It or Leave It?
That album was, like, forever ago.
What about Slingshot?
That one was a little... [hesitates]
[splutters] ...dancy for... for my taste.
Dancy?
- Huh.
- Oh, but that first album? [scoffs]
Oh yeah.
- [exhales deeply]
- That... That one was... That one was magic.
And now I'm sitting here
with the person who made it.
[Miguel chuckling]
I'm just like anybody else.
No.
I'm just like... [chuckling]
...anybody else.
[girl laughing]
Yeah, well...
I never had a quince.
Feels like I missed out.
What were you doing when you were 15?
Touring with J.Lo.
Oh... oh yeah, yeah. You were
really deprived. [laughing] Sorry.
And one, two, three, four,
and five and six and seven and eight.
Cristina, would you like
to show Angelina your baile sorpresa?
- What?
- Okay.
Yeah, I would love to see it.
[all giggling, talking indistinctly]
[softly] Okay.
[exhales]
- Okay.
- Hit it, Tía!
- [grunts]
- ["Sweet and Spicy" playing]
- Oh, that's my song.
Five, six, seven, eight.
- And one, two, three... No, stop, stop!
- [song stops]
- That's not it. That's not it.
- Oh. Ugh.
- We're struggling a little bit, but we...
- Okay. I...
I... I know... I know
what's tripping you guys up. I...
Everyone back to one.
- Oh my God!
- Okay.
- Oh my gosh, you guys.
- [Angelina] Okay.
What's tripping you up
is the signature change
after the intro. Okay?
But if you had a little choreography,
you can recover your timing.
So let's do something, like, we'll go...
One, two, three,
four, five, six, seven, eight. Okay?
- And...
- [girl] Okay...
Oh, um... Let's not do that.
Okay, let's just keep it simple.
Um, we'll go and one
and two and three and four
and five and six and seven and eight.
Okay, ready? Can we try it?
Five, six, seven, eight.
And one and two and three and four.
Now let's give it full commitment.
Okay, I want to see face.
I want to see performance.
Five, six, seven, eight.
- And one and two and three...
- ["Luna Rumbera" playing]
[inaudible]
[woman singing in Spanish]
[all cheering]
So, have you decided on
a chambelane for your quince yet?
You can always ask Scott,
but you def need a date.
I'm not putting myself through
that humiliation again.
Besides, I think I'm going to go
as an independent woman.
I mean, isn't that what this
is all about anyways?
- Bold!
- [giggles]
[both laugh]
- Then we can go into the verse here.
- [Cristina] Hey, Angelina!
Um, I was wondering...
You're probably really busy and all
'cause it's close to Christmas,
but would you wanna come to my...
[chuckles nervously]
...you know?
Your quince?
Next Saturday as my VIP.
- I would love to.
- [exclaiming indistinctly]
But only if you do me the honor
of coming as my guest first.
What do you mean?
There's this annual fundraiser
I do every year in the city at Christmas,
and I would actually love
for you both to come as my VIPs.
[squeals]
- Let's go! Let's go!
- I don't know what to say.
Just say yes.
I guess I have to.
Yes! [giggles]
Great.
Okay, well,
let's go finish this song.
Or otherwise no one's going to any gala.
Oh gosh, I mean,
you know, it was in the playbook possibly.
- So, but now I will reconsider. Oh...
- [phone ringing]
- [Miguel] Exactly.
- [Angelina chuckling]
- [ringing continues]
- Oh, um, I should take this.
Yeah.
[sighs deeply]
[whispering] Oh, what do I do?
[sighs]
Barry!
Where the hell are you?
I... I'm working on the Christmas song
just like you asked me to.
That's what you're
supposed to be doing here!
Well, I just needed
some time to figure it out.
It's the creative process, Barry. It's...
Okay, all right. So you do know the gala
is right around the corner, right?
[laughs] That... you know, that right there.
That is an excellent point.
So I guess I shouldn't be wasting my time
on the phone then. Bye.
Nobody hangs up on Billion Dollar Barry.
I hang up on people!
[sighs]
Miguel, ready to get started?
The tamalada waits for no one.
We could use your help with these.
[Miguel] Mom.
Maybe it'll inspire you.
- Sit.
- Food always inspires me.
Oh, uh... Muchísimas gracias, señora.
But we have so much work to do.
I mean, we have barely...
Huh?
But yeah, sometimes you find inspiration
when you're not looking for it.
Exactamente. Exactamente.
Ah!
[Miguel] Uh...
Hmm.
Uh... [exhales]
Can I give you a hand with that?
Oh, uh...
Yeah, I... I suppose.
- Let's just start from the beginning.
- Okay.
- [Miguel] All right. Turn it this way.
- [Angelina] Oh.
[Miguel] We're just gonna take
some of that out.
Do I push down on that too?
- No.
- Oh.
- [Miguel] Then you... Just like this.
- [Angelina] Okay.
You're gonna have to get 'em dirty.
There you go.
- So, do I put it all over the thing?
- No.
- No, just half of it.
- Just like about here to here.
- Oh.
- Okay.
That's good. You're doing it.
You're doing it.
[Latin pop Christmas song playing]
[chorus singing in Spanish]
♪ Can't wait to see what Santa brings ♪
♪ What Santa bring for me ♪
♪ And I can't wait to celebrate ♪
♪ Celebrate with everybody ♪
[chorus singing in Spanish]
Now, remember,
next time, less masa, less mess.
["Deck the Halls" instrumental playing]
[instrumental fades out]
[exhales forcefully]
You wouldn't know where
I can find a certain pop star, would you?
Ah... Have you seen this?
- [Barry] What the hell?
- Uh-huh.
Who is Conchi Cutie?
Yeah.
[Christmas music playing]
Everything okay?
- I really think this could be the one, Mo.
- The song or the music teacher?
I am not even gonna
entertain that with a response.
[Monique laughing]
I am going to shower.
We don't even have clean clothes.
Connie and Conchi are on it.
[clearing throat]
[laughing] All right.
Now, that is a good look.
- [chuckles]
- [Monique chuckles]
Why, thank you.
But, uh, just wait. This is the...
[mimicking techno beat]
...real show.
Who needs a club?
- The club right here.
- [Monique laughing]
Well, I'm gonna go see what Frida's up to.
[Angelina] Okay.
So, uh, where were we?
- Chorus.
- Ugh, yes, that line in the chorus.
What is that line in the chorus?
Uh, okay so...
[humming melody]
...after that.
[pencil scratching on paper]
I've never written
with anyone else before.
Get out of here.
All those albums? Not even once?
No.
I mean, I've done other people's songs,
but all of my stuff,
I've written completely alone.
Yeah, I've never written
with anyone else either.
It's too...
- Too intimate.
- Yeah.
[touching music playing]
I... I... I think there needs
to be a resolve here.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You're right. You're right.
- And the bridge still isn't working.
- Ugh.
I know. I know!
What do we do with that bridge?
[Angelina humming melody]
Wh... what do you do
in the studio when you can't crack it?
- I leave.
- [laughing]
What, you just run away?
No, although that's an excellent idea.
- [laughing]
- I mean, I... I just leave the studio.
I do my best work at home.
You can see the entire city from my place.
Ah, it's so great.
All those lights just really inspire me.
[tender music playing]
Come on. We're going.
Grab your coat. We're leaving.
Wha...? We're working.
[smacks paper pad]
[sighs, mumbles]
Well?
It's not Manhattan, but...
Oh!
[epic Christmas music playing]
I love it.
- [laughs]
- Miguel, oh, thank you so much.
[Miguel] I should be the one thanking you.
You were a real hit today.
You earned some die-hard fans.
[tender music playing]
Although, apparently,
I already had one die-hard fan
who has listened to my record
a thousand times.
[laughing]
You... you're just not gonna let me live
that one down.
Not in a thousand years.
Seriously though,
you make Cristina very happy.
Oh, I can't take credit for that.
Not when she's got an amazing dad.
- Well, I do my best.
- [Angelina chuckles]
Sometimes I wonder if it's enough.
Never doubt yourself,
especially when it comes to that.
You are a great dad. You really are.
[tender music continues]
You know, you...
You must be doing something right.
I mean, Cristina is such an amazing kid.
And the way she loves you,
aw, it's the sweetest.
[both chuckle]
I could say the same for you though.
You got the kind of career
most people could only dream of.
Yeah.
Hmm.
Although, I guess,
sometimes it could get lonely.
Sometimes.
[sighs] But this...
This really is so perfect.
I know what you mean.
[tender music continues]
I've tried to hide this love inside.
[music crescendos]
- What?
- I've tried to hide this love inside.
That is the line in the chorus
that we have been missing.
[chuckles nervously]
♪ I've tried to hide this love inside ♪
And then...
♪ 'Cause there can be
No Christmas without you ♪
- [laughing]
- Ah!
We did it! Oh!
See? Who needs Manhattan?
[exhales]
Let's go make some music.
Let's do it. Oh jeez! I can't...
[tender music playing]
[inaudible]
[knocking on door]
[knocking continues]
Ugh.
Hey, baby. Miss me?
Uh... Ricardo. What are you doing here?
How did you even find us?
Some lady posted a photo
of you on Instagram.
Her name is Conchi.
[groans softly]
Baby. Ah, you know,
we have a big night ahead of us.
I just thought I would come to make sure
that we make it back to the city in time.
- Huh.
- [Angelina] What?
Who's that?
Ricardo!
You're alive.
Hey! [laughing]
Hey, gracias.
Muy bien. Muy bien.
Okay, honey. I... I... I think, um,
we've had enough now
with our visit with the fans.
Come on, let's go. Let's go.
Ricardo, you know,
not that this is any of your business,
but we have actually
been collaborating on a song.
[Ricardo makes high-pitched scoffs]
Wait, you two
have been writing a song... together?
Yeah.
Well, I mean, it was really Miguel's song,
but yeah, we have been
writing a song together,
and... and it's actually...
It's actually been
a wonderful collaboration.
Oh, uh... [clears throat]
...well, I'd... I'd love to hear it.
- We just cracked it.
- It's not done.
You can hear it
when it's ready to be heard.
[spluttering] No pressure.
Yeah, no pressure. Yeah.
It... it's just Angelina, she's... she's...
She's such a dynamic stage presence
that I guess I just assumed
she'd be collaborating
with somebody who could match
that stardom.
Class.
Stop it.
Basta.
See you outside, mi amor.
[melancholic music playing]
- [Angelina sighs]
- [door opens]
I, um...
I'll go grab my stuff.
[sighs]
I'm so sorry about Ricardo.
Even on a good day, he can be a lot.
It's just another element to an already
really, really strange couple of days.
Well, it's not over yet.
I... I'll see you two at the gala.
I wouldn't miss it.
Bye.
["O Come, All Ye Faithful"
piano instrumental playing]
[engine starts]
[car door shuts]
[car door opens]
[Angelina sighs] Ricardo, por favor.
[Ricardo] Angelina. It hurts us.
That's all I'm saying.
It hurts us,
or it hurts the brand, Ricardo?
¿Y sabes qué? Por la quinta vez,
we were just working together.
- And that's not what it looked like!
- [sighs forcefully]
And that's the only thing that matters.
[Angelina sighs]
[somber music playing]
- Do you like this guy?
- No.
I was only there for the song.
And, sabes qué, you of all people
should know that I do not get involved.
Yeah.
Yeah. No. I, um... I remember.
Ricardo.
We tried.
Maybe we didn't try hard enough.
No.
[inhales sharply]
Seriously, Ange,
if you don't wanna do this anymore,
just tell me because... [exhales forcefully]
[inhales]
No, no, no. No, no, no. Mira.
This is... This is working for me.
Okay, Ricardo?
This is working. You're right.
The brand, it's important.
Okay.
See you at the gala.
[orchestral Christmas music playing]
[squeals with delight]
[Cristina] I'll get it!
[Monique] Hi, guys. Ready?
- Um...
H... hi.
I'm gonna get you to the theater. Come on.
- Oh, no, no, no. We're not ready yet.
- Come as you are. We got you.
Okay!
[sweeping orchestral music playing]
- [indistinct chatter]
- [cameras clicking]
- [man] There she is!
- [fan] Whoo!
[woman] Angelina!
[reporter] ...one of the most
anticipated performances tonight
will include pop superstar Angelina Costa.
[Cristina gasps]
What?! [chuckles]
[Monique] Pick an outfit.
[sweeping orchestral music continues]
- [softly] Wow.
- Right?
[indistinct chatter]
Where's your dad?
Ugh, still getting ready.
Mm-hmm. Men. Sheesh. [chuckles]
- Let's go.
- [Monique] Mm-hmm.
- Wait. Wait.
- Stunning.
[chuckles] What?
[touching orchestral music playing]
Angie.
[Angelina] Barry.
[Barry] You've been so secretive
these last few days.
I can't wait to hear this new song.
- Oh.
- [jazzy "Jingle Bells" playing]
You remember Cheri?
- Hi!
- Of course. Oh. Okay.
- It's so good to see you again.
- Mm-hmm.
I just quickly wanted to say,
you are such an inspiration to me.
- Really?
- Yes!
I watched
the Love It or Leave It tour three times.
It really gives me inspiration
for my shows.
You watched it three times?
Okay, five. Okay, ten.
Wow. That's... that's very sweet.
Cheri's playing Saturday Night Live's
Christmas special this week.
I don't have to tell you
how big of a deal that is for a career.
[Barry chuckling]
Cheri, that is wonderful.
And I wish you the absolute best.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I'm on in just a few minutes.
Can't wait.
[touching music playing]
- That didn't look fun.
- It wasn't actually that bad.
- You had that fake smile thing going.
- What do you mean?
- Stop.
- [both chuckling]
[Miguel] There you go. That's better.
When do you perform?
- In just a few minutes.
- Do you get nervous?
No.
- I still get excited though.
- [scoffs] I... I can't even imagine.
I haven't performed in so long.
I don't even play in front of my students.
Aw, that's a shame.
People should get a chance
to hear you play.
No.
I can't do what you do.
Hey.
Break a leg.
Thank you.
- [crowd applauding, cheering]
- [playing piano]
[Angelina] Thank you so much.
Thank you.
You all have been absolutely wonderful.
So we have one last song for you tonight.
It's a very special song.
It's a new song.
And in fact,
the person I wrote it with
is here tonight.
- [softly] That's you! That's you!
- [whispering] Stop, stop, stop.
Miguel Torres,
will you join me on stage, please?
[woman] Oh!
[softly] Yes!
[whispering] Go! Go! Go!
Aw, come on, audience. Let's help him out.
- Miguel! Miguel!
- [crowd] Miguel!
- Daddy! Daddy! Daddy! Daddy! Daddy!
- [Angelina and crowd] Miguel! Miguel!
Can we get a spot on Miguel, please?
Dad. Yeah!
You got... Dad, you got this! Go!
You've got this.
Yes, thank you so much, everyone.
You're in for a real treat.
You got this.
Miguel Torres, everyone!
[crowd applauding, cheering]
[chuckling nervously] What are you doing?
Getting the band out of the garage.
It's just you and me up here, okay?
Okay.
[crowd hushes]
[exhales]
[playing "Christmas Without You"]
♪ They say home is where the heart is ♪
♪ Although I could never find it ♪
♪ Now I finally see ♪
♪ I was lost in me ♪
♪ Now the fireplace is roaring ♪
♪ I can feel my heart warming ♪
♪ 'Cause there won't be ♪
♪ No Christmas without you ♪
♪ I never did believe in love ♪
♪ I was always thinking of ♪
♪ The things that could go wrong ♪
♪ And I'm always stuck inside my head ♪
♪ Leaving all my feels unsaid ♪
♪ Now you got me on the edge ♪
♪ 'Cause I've been hoping
That you're wantin' me to stay ♪
♪ 'Cause I don't want this Christmas
To be just another day ♪
♪ I've tried to hide this love inside ♪
♪ But there can be
No Christmas without you ♪
♪ Is it too late for me to say ♪
♪ That there can be
No Christmas without you? ♪
♪ Without you ♪
♪ 'Cause there can be
No Christmas without you ♪
♪ Without you ♪
♪ 'Cause there can be
No Christmas without you ♪
♪ Boy, I'm feeling so at home ♪
♪ Under the mistletoe ♪
♪ I just want you all alone ♪
♪ And you ♪
♪ You make me feel like no one else ♪
♪ You always see me for myself ♪
♪ But you got me so loco
It's like we're lovin' in slo-mo ♪
♪ 'Cause I've been hoping
That you're wantin' me to stay ♪
♪ 'Cause I don't want this Christmas
To be just another day ♪
[singing in Spanish]
♪ Without you ♪
♪ 'Cause there can be
No Christmas without you ♪
[crowd applauding, cheering]
[emotional music playing]
Miguel Torres, everyone.
[applause and cheering continue]
Oh!
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you.
- You got a standing ovation.
- [laughing]
And, I mean, you were... you were...
You were amazing.
- [chuckling] God, look at my hands.
- Oh my God.
I never felt anything like that
in my whole life.
- I can't believe you did that!
- I can't believe I did that either!
Angelina. Angelina. You did it.
You did it!
- We did it, baby.
- Oh!
- [Ricardo kissing]
- [Angelina] Oh!
Guys, wait until you hear this new song.
It's gonna blow your minds.
This has the potential
to be a massive hit.
Even this late in the season.
This could easily break the Holiday 100.
- People are going nuts over this new song.
- Come on. It's okay.
- [Barry] Come on. Let me talk to you.
- [gasps]
[Barry] Hey, listen, listen.
I want you
to do the SNL special this Saturday.
[somber music playing]
- Wait. What?
- [Barry] Yeah.
But wait, what about Cheri?
You can't do that to her.
It's already done.
Let's celebrate. Come on.
- [mouthing silently]
- [Angelina groans]
Come on. Ange. Ange, where are you going?
Ange.
[Angelina breathing heavily]
Hey!
Could I, um... Could I talk
to your dad for a minute?
Come on, kiddo.
Hey. So, um,
I wanted to tell you that, uh,
they want me
to play the song on SNL next weekend.
Our song. [giggles]
- [scoffs] Get out of here! No way!
- Yes way! [laughing]
And... And I want you to come with me.
What? To Saturday Night Live?
Yes! I could use a good pianist.
[chuckles]
A pianist?
Yes, of course, a pianist.
Are you kidding?
You were absolutely incredible
on that stage.
I wish I could, but I... I just can't.
Why not?
I already have plans this Saturday.
[somber music playing]
Oh. Right. Yes, of course.
Uh, Cristina's quince.
I was supposed to come.
She'll understand.
[sighs] Well, what about after the quince?
The song is gonna have a life, Miguel.
And... And we can work in the studio.
We can write more.
We can tour together.
- How fun would that be?
- Tour?
Angelina, I just can't up and leave.
Okay, I have a daughter.
I have a real life.
What is that supposed to mean?
[Miguel] These last few days,
with everything that's happened,
it was just about the song for you?
Nothing else?
I...
[sighs]
Yes.
Yes. Okay?
Th... this is... this is how I survive.
I throw myself into the music.
What good is surviving
if you're not really living?
Just having an image
isn't actually having a life.
You gotta take risks.
[exhales]
Miguel, uh, look.
[spluttering, sighs]
This whole thing was just business.
Okay, we agreed on that
from the beginning.
We agreed.
[somber music continues]
I spent years of my life missing out
on what you gave me in one night
because I was too scared to take a risk.
I never thought
I'd let anyone in again ever...
[sighs]
...and then here you come.
It was never about the song for me.
It was you.
It was always you.
And I think you feel the same way.
I can't.
You can't, or you won't?
Goodbye.
["Make It Feel like Christmas"
by Simon Tellier & Victoria Hills playing]
♪ ...I'm sitting all alone ♪
♪ The carolers are gone ♪
♪ The fire's burning low ♪
♪ I can't sleep
Though it's a silent night ♪
♪ 'Cause there's just one thing missing ♪
♪ To make this season bright ♪
♪ Baby, it's you ♪
♪ You make it feel like Christmas ♪
♪ Baby, can't you see? ♪
♪ You're the only gift I need ♪
♪ Baby, it's you ♪
♪ You make it feel like Christmas ♪
♪ I want you to know
I won't let you go ♪
♪ 'Cause you make it Christmas for me ♪
[reporter] Are the rumors true, Ricardo?
Look, I don't wanna make any commentaries.
I don't wanna say anything out of school.
Just... just... just to clarify, though,
I broke up with her.
Okay. She did not break up with me.
So we're all on the same page, okay?
I never liked him anyway.
Desgraciado.
I bet all those muscles
are probably fake too.
Oh no. They are very real.
[sighs] I feel like this is all my fault.
What are you talking about?
If I hadn't made that video,
none of this would have happened.
That video and your passion
made a superstar come into our house.
And she fixed your baile sorpresa.
- [Connie] Mmm.
- And I wrote a song with her.
And I got to perform it onstage
in front of a packed house
at a fancy theater.
It was horrible.
[giggles] That's not what I meant,
and you know it.
I saw the look on your face backstage.
- You have a crush on her.
- [Miguel] Oh yeah?
What do you know about crushes?
Dad, it's about to be my quinceañera.
You know, that whole thing
about becoming a woman.
I'm not a kid anymore.
I know about crushes.
[snickers softly]
And I... I just thought she liked you too.
- [scoffs] It's complicated.
- Complicated?
When Ricardo Santoval thought
that Ruby was dead for five years,
he married her sister,
only to discover that Ruby was alive
but paralyzed and loca,
living under an assumed identity
in Oaxaca.
That was complicated.
What's in your heart is simple.
You just need to follow it.
Now, cállense!
My show's starting.
["Silent Night" themed
instrumental playing]
[indistinct chatter]
So, I talked to Fashion Beat.
They want you for the spring cover.
That's great.
Oh no. Did Barry change his mind again?
No, I'm here as a fan
and to say that, uh,
there's no hard feelings.
I know how it goes.
You know, for the record,
it doesn't have to be that way.
There is enough room
for both of us, Cheri.
And...
Look, I don't really know you,
but you seem really sweet.
I don't wanna be pitted against you.
I wanna cheer you on.
- I wanna celebrate your wins.
- [Cheri squeals with delight]
- I wanna cheer you on too.
- [Angelina chuckles]
[Cheri sniffling]
Well, thank you so much for being here.
Where is that guy?
Your boyfriend?
- Oh, uh, Ricardo. That's... That's over.
- [Monique scoffs]
Oh, bummer.
He played a mean piano.
Oh, Miguel.
Yeah, he... he was never
my boyfriend. [chuckles]
- Oh, could have fooled me.
- Could have fooled all of us.
Well, that's sad because you two
are pretty magical together.
She ain't wrong.
My favorite musician
once wrote that home
is where the heart is, so...
[emotional music playing]
[sighs]
You know what?
I gotta go. [chuckles]
You go. I'll handle it.
[whispers] Okay.
[hesitates] Uh, wait, wait, wait!
[chuckles] Um, what's happening?
It looks like
you're performing tonight, after all.
Break a leg.
Two more minutes. Coming through, guys.
["Joy to the World"
instrumental theme playing]
Ah, thank you.
[indistinct chatter]
[touching music playing]
You ready?
[sighs]
I learn so much from you every day.
And you shine brighter
than I could have ever imagined.
I'm so proud of you, mija.
And I'm proud to be your dad.
[tearfully] And your mom
would be so proud of you too.
[sniffling]
[sighs]
[Conchi] Ladies and gentlemen,
family, and honored guests,
I present to you
Cristina Adriana Torres, La Quinceañera!
[guests applaud, cheer]
[gentle guitar music playing]
[guests] Aw!
[gasps]
[touching ballad music playing]
♪ No matter where you go ♪
♪ I'll always keep you with me ♪
♪ And I know ♪
♪ Your love is here to stay ♪
♪ Love is strong ♪
♪ If you keep it in your heart ♪
♪ I know, I know
You're here to stay ♪
♪ To stay ♪
♪ I'll always... ♪
Thanks for everything, Dad.
I just hope it's everything you dreamed.
Even more.
- But, Dad?
- Yes?
You should call her.
♪ I'll always know you're with me ♪
♪ Keep you with me ♪
[guests applaud, cheer]
Whoo!
["Sweet and Spicy"
by Aimee Garcia playing]
[guests cheering]
[gasps, screams]
[laughing]
- [Miguel] Hey!
- Hey.
[singing in mixed English and Spanish]
♪ It's true ♪
♪ We can run, we can run ♪
[singing in Spanish]
[man singing in mixed English and Spanish]
Yeah!
Yes! Yeah!
[singing in Spanish]
♪ Give it up, give it up ♪
- [song ends]
- [guests applauding, cheering]
- [Cristina] Yay!
- [Angelina exclaims]
Whoo!
- [salsa music playing]
- [laughing]
You look amazing! [laughs]
Best quince ever!
[both laughing]
Oh, good!
And...
now you can finally have yours. [giggles]
Thank you.
- Hey.
- Do you wanna dance?
- Yes! [giggles]
[Scott chuckles]
[guests] Whoo!
What about SNL?
Oh, you know,
I told them I already had plans.
You sure you're not just looking
for a pianist?
Nope.
You said something about making plans?
Yeah, I'm, um, still working on those.
[touching music playing]
Maybe you can help me.
Maybe. What are you doing for Christmas?
Christmas?
- With you?
- [chuckling]
Oh, you're gonna have to get
a sweater though.
A real ugly one.
Oh, I got a line on those.
[inhales]
And, um...
after?
We'll figure it out.
[romantic orchestral music playing]
["Christmas Without You"
by Aimee Garcia playing]
[Angelina] Mira, we're number one!
♪ I was always thinking of
The things that could go wrong ♪
♪ And I'm always stuck inside my head ♪
♪ Leaving all my feels unsaid ♪
♪ Now you got me on the edge ♪
♪ 'Cause I've been hoping
That you're wantin' me to stay ♪
♪ 'Cause I don't want this Christmas
To be just another day ♪
♪ I've tried to hide this love inside ♪
♪ But there can be
No Christmas without you ♪
♪ Is it too late for me to say ♪
♪ That there can be
No Christmas without you? ♪
["Feliz Navidad Mi Amor"
by Jasmine Lopez playing]
[woman singing in Spanish]
[Christmas-themed
orchestral music playing]