Does everybody
know what time it is?
AUDIENCE: Tool Time!
That's right! And now here
he is, the star of our show,
Tim "The Tool Man" Taylor!
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
(EARL HINDMAN READING)
Before you hurt
yourselves, sit down.
Thank you.
Thank you, Heidi.
I am Tim "The Tool Man" Taylor,
and, of course, you all
know my trusted assistant,
Al "Who Put the Bore
in Boring" Borland.
All right, then.
Today, on Tool Time,
we're doing our
salute... Salute...
(MACHINE ROARING)
to steamrollers.
No, no.
No, you promised
if I did this show,
there would be no
heavy equipment.
I'm kidding. What's
blowing your skirt up today?
What's going on, huh?
I'm just kidding around.
We're gonna do a
simple circuit breaker.
Heidi, my simple
circuit breaker, please.
Simple? You call this simple?
This is a 10,000-amp
industrial circuit breaker.
Au contraire, my
lumpy lumberjack.
I added some power, and
this is now a 50,000-amp
simple circuit breaker.
Oh, Al, how would you like to
connect these last two wires?
I don't think so, Tim.
How many out there would like to
see Al connect these last two wires?
(APPLAUDING)
How many out there would like to
see Tim connect these two wires?
AL: Thank you very much.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah! Yeah!
You mean-spirited people.
I'm not going to do that.
'Cause even if I did,
nothing would happen.
(EXCLAIMING)
It's not a real circuit breaker.
It's not even a real Tool Time.
And that isn't Heidi,
that isn't Al Borland.
That's Debbe Dunning, the actor.
(CHEERING)
And this...
This is not Al Borland. I'm
sorry if you thought it was.
This is Richard Karn.
The new host of Family Feud.
Survey says... Says...
We even have a disc jockey,
Casey Sander from the K&B boys,
giving us music tonight.
Always great to be here, Timmy.
It's been over three years
since we did our final
episode of Home Improvement,
and I wanted to
do a retrospective,
but didn't wanna
wait 20 years to do it.
I wanted to do it now, while you
guys still remembered who I am.
I wanted to do it now, while
I still remembered who I am.
We had such fun doing this.
So tonight, what we're gonna do
is put together some clips,
show you some inside stuff,
maybe give you a few tips.
Enjoy these clips that
we think are the best.
And we created a User's
Guide to Home Improvement.
So, Debbe, my
User's Guide, please.
Here you go, Tim.
The stunning Debbe Dunning.
Anyhow, this book is
chock-full of helpful hints.
Well, like this one.
HINDMAN: On Home Improvement,
the best conductors of electricity
are copper and Tim Taylor.
Tim, this'll work.
You twist and pull the broken
bulb right out of the socket.
But first, you must...
Jam it in the light.
Unplug the lamp.
Ground. Looking for ground.
Now, red is all...
Yellow, see? The sun is
yellow, it heats the ground,
that's how they name stuff.
Is that car running?
(TIM SCREAMING)
Shake it off.
We got our belt
attached with a rough grip.
And we wanna plug
the thing in now?
'Course you wanna be
sure the trigger switch
is not locked in
the "On" position.
Any idiot knows that, Al.
What a bonehead.
I'm just like him.
(CHUCKLES) Admit it,
guys. You are, too, you know?
We will eat anything
that's cooked over a fire
or shoved into an animal casing.
That's a sausage, to you women.
We like the smell of sweat,
motor oil and diesel fuel combined.
Yeah, if it spins, smokes, or
better yet, catches fire and explodes,
that excites guys.
This next clip is from what
we call the pilot episode.
You may remember it. It
went something like this.
(GASPS) What the hell is that?
That is the power source
to your new dishwasher.
Take it out. No, no, no.
No, take it out now.
You don't like the fact
that I improved the
dishwasher? No.
Remember that yolk that wouldn't
come off the plate this morning?
Watch this.
(DISHWASHER HUMMING)
Hear that hum?
That's a Finley two-stage,
five-horse Blastmaster compressor.
Air delivery system is 18
cubic feet per square minute.
That should say
testosterone right on there.
'Cause that...
That is a man's dishwasher.
(CHUCKLES) Yeah.
Critics didn't really like
this show that much.
As a matter of fact, I mean,
there was a bunch of critics
who said it just won't last.
There was one newspaper,
I'm not gonna mention The
New York Times by name,
but they...
Wow. That was really weird.
I mean, that just
slipped out. I'm sorry.
They said the show
couldn't go three episodes.
I mean, how many things
can this meathead blow up?
Don't strike that match.
That's something else.
(PHONE RINGS)
(EXCLAIMING)
Well,
as it turns out...
As it turns out, he could
blow up 4,100 items.
Home Improvement wasn't
just about blowing stuff up, folks.
The heart of it was a relationship
between a man and a woman.
Right? If you've got
your User's Guides handy,
turn to page 78, under
"Building a Relationship."
It says, "Romance doesn't
come out of the box factory-made.
"Some assembly is required."
(I GOT YOU BABE PLAYING)
♪ They say we're
young And we don't know
♪ Won't find out till we grow
TIM: ♪ Well, I don't
know If all that's true
♪ 'Cause you got
me And baby I got you
Good.
BOTH: ♪ Babe
♪ I got you babe
♪ I got you babe ♪
I love you very, very much.
These are the best
15 years I've ever had.
(EXCLAIMING IN DISGUST)
Put a lid on it.
You know, sometimes I just forget
what an amazing hunk of man you are.
Whoa.
Well, I'd love to stick around
and give you a little reminder,
but the boys need me.
I need you.
(HORN HONKING)
(GRUNTS)
Demolition derby... Sexy wife.
Demolition derby...
Ooh. Sexy wife.
Could you hold that thought
till about 10:00 tonight?
Wait a minute.
This thought here?
Mmm-mmm.
(CHUCKLING)
That would be the one.
Hurry back, mister.
Every time I see two heaps
slamming into one another tonight,
I'll be thinking about us.
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
What is this?
(JILL LAUGHING)
Are you gonna still
find me desirable?
I didn't marry you because
of your uterus or your ovaries,
I married you because
of what's inside.
If you think you can
keep up, please join in.
All right.
(GIGGLING)
Hmm.
(GRUNTS)
Hmm...
Looks like somebody's
ready to come over to Daddy.
It's just you and me.
Got any ideas about
what we could be doing?
I'm getting one.
MARK: Mommy and
Daddy sitting in the tree,
K-I-S-S-I-N-G.
RANDY: We're
in the tree, stupid.
(WHISTLES)
Are you looking good. Let me
get out of these cruddy clothes.
Don't take too long.
I won't.
What a great night
with the boys, though.
Lot of good food. Oh.
(SIGHING)
I got some double-cheese
nachos sitting right here.
(BURPING) Oh.
Tim.
Little gas bubble.
Moving, moving...
(BURPS)
This is real attractive.
So where were we?
It's kind of hard to remember.
This will refresh your memory.
(BURPS)
Sorry.
Sorry. I'm sorry.
Mark was right. Ugh.
You shouldn't have double
onions on those chili dogs.
Hello.
♪ Then put your
little hand in mine
♪ There ain't no
mountain Or hill we can't...
♪ Babe
♪ I got you babe
♪ I got you babe ♪
(MUSIC STOPS)
The Minimag 100 is perfect
for picking up screws and nails.
It can also pick up small tools
that have carelessly been dropped
behind the workbench,
perhaps the fault of a co-worker.
And the Minimag 2000.
Small, but powerful. 10
pounds will pick up 400 pounds.
This would suck The Tin
Man right through a keyhole.
Well, it was designed
to pick up sheet metal,
so you wanna keep
it pointed to... Tim.
No, no, just slide
it straight down!
Tim.
Pretty powerful
little thing, isn't it?
Marv, hold it back. Marv!
I just love this set. Yeah.
There's so many
memories on this set.
Mario Andretti stood right here
and gave us a bunch of grief.
And then, one of the astronauts,
Ken Bowersocks, and all his team
were standing right
there. Remember that?
Yeah.
And then you insulted
my mother, right there.
my mother over there.
'Course, you insulted
my mother back there, too.
Just about everywhere,
you insulted my mother.
Richard, Richard,
Richard. Hold on a second.
Focus on me right now.
It was a television show.
Wasn't your real mother.
I loved my pretend mother.
Let's all pretend
that he didn't say that.
Let's pretend to move on.
Okay, I understand,
I understand.
Let's just watch a clip of
the Tool girls, shall we?
MAN: Yeah. WOMAN: Yeah.
Does everybody
know what time it is?
Tool Time! Tool Time!
That's right! Binford
Tools is proud to present
Tim "The Tool Man" Taylor!
Tim "The Tool Man"...
Nice dress, Deb.
Thank you.
Do you remember the
first time I wore this?
(STUTTERING) Yeah, at
that hardware convention.
No. No, that was Al.
Here's a little bit of trivia. The first
time I appeared on Home Improvement,
I was not the Tool Time girl.
And it went something
like this. Something like this.
Whoa, baby, bad news.
This is not the night for you
to give up looking at women.
Uh-huh. Oh, why is that, Jill?
Because an unbelievable
young goddess just came in
and sat right behind
you. Yeah, right.
Yes. I'm gonna
fall into that one.
What, a 74-year-old steelworker?
(GRUFFLY) "Hey, Marge,
they got no beer here."
Not exactly, Tim. Oh, yeah,
she's the va-va-voom type?
Well, as a matter of fact,
she has great va-vas
and a darned good voom.
All right with me, because
you're looking pretty good
since you took a couple
of pounds off your voom.
(CHUCKLES) Well, thank you
so much. Now, if you'll excuse me,
I'm going to take my
voom to the ladies' room.
I'll be looking at my
menu and nothing else.
Oh, man. Off to the right,
three o'clock. Unbelievable!
Hey, it is you.
Tim "The Tool Man" Taylor?
I never miss your show.
Oh, you have me confused with
that handsome guy on Tool Time.
Don't be modest. Could
I get your autograph?
Yeah, quick. Why don't you
just slide it right under here,
under my head here? Okay.
Could you make it out to Kiki?
Kiki.
K-I...
Oh...
Okay, Kikster, here you go.
Hmm. Could you put
my last name, too?
Ah, you know, my
wife is due back.
She's coming out... Kiki
Van Fursterwallenscheinlaw.
What? F-U-R
S-T-E-R-W-A-L-L. Uh-huh.
I'm getting a hand
cramp. Hold on.
E-N-S-C-H-E-I-N-L-A-W.
Uh-huh. Uh-huh.
L-A-W. Good thing
it didn't run out of ink.
(GIGGLES)
Now can you grunt for me?
Well, you know, my wife
is coming back and I just...
Hello, honey.
(CHOKING) JILL: Excuse me.
(GRUNTING)
(ALL GRUNTING)
What are you doing?
Are you choking?
The reason men check out women
isn't because we lust after them.
We look because it reminds us of
how much better we have it at home.
Right, men?
(MEN CHEERING)
Are they lying, women?
Yes! Yes!
We have a disagreement.
That's because men and
women are different, duh,
much like a dry-cell battery.
The positive side
is free-flowing,
full of energy, giving
life everywhere,
but the negative side just sucks
all the energy out of every situation.
Negative, negative, negative.
You never do any
work around here.
You're always
leaving the seat up.
Well, you decide
which end is which.
Why don't we watch another clip?
Tim, I don't wanna
be a nagging wife.
Then how will I recognize you?
Got to be something in
here you can get rid of.
Yeah, but I stayed married
to it because of the kids.
Why do you always bug
me during the football game?
Did I bug you during childbirth?
No, but you bugged
me during conception.
You never told me
about a job interview.
Tim, do you ever listen to me?
It was the last thing that I
said in bed to you last night.
No, I believe, if you recall,
the last thing you said to me
in bed last night was,
"No!"
You're thinking of tonight.
If your husband was
something you find in the kitchen,
what would he be? Oh,
that's deep. Yeah, that's deep.
I think you'll find this
very insightful, Tim.
"A," an oven, warm and
self-cleaning. Not me.
"B," garbage disposal,
grating and eats anything.
"C," a refrigerator. Very
cold and the light's never on.
These are stupid.
Well, come on.
You haven't read the
one that I picked for you.
Read "D."
"D," a tea kettle.
Hot and steamy,
done in two minutes.
Do I ever wish that I
married somebody else?
Why would I wanna
marry anybody else?
You're funny. You're sexy.
Creative, you take chances and
you're definitely not afraid to be wrong.
I'm perfectly happy being
married to a man who thinks
that PBS is something that
women get once a month.
Quit that.
No, really, stick your nose right there
and tell me I don't smell like a man.
(CHUCKLES) Yeah, Cro-Magnon man.
(GRUNTING)
I believe he was
never fully erect, either.
(GRUNTING)
We never actually said that we
weren't gonna have another baby.
I've said it. I've talked about
it. I know I've talked about it.
I mentioned it on Tool Time.
Oh, great. So 11
people know about it?
Remember babies
at all? Dirty diapers.
Colic, 2:00 am feedings,
3:00 am feedings!
I don't have the
energy for that anymore.
You don't have
the energy to say,
"Wake up, Jill, the
baby wants you"?
I just read this survey,
and it said that some couples,
no matter how busy they are,
still make love
five times a week.
With each other?
Yeah.
Hi.
Come down here, I want
to show you something.
What?
Come here.
I made a scale model
of the office I'll build you when
you become a psychologist.
Here's your desk, here's
your chair and here's your nut.
Where am I?
Seated at the desk.
And why did you do this?
I thought it would cheer you up,
because I think you
might have the blues
and maybe we
should talk about it.
So you're saying you wanna talk.
Why do you think
I'm laying down?
You know, the other day, when
you asked me what I was feeling,
I told you, and you
jumped down my throat.
You're right. It wasn't fair.
If I'm going to ask
for your feelings,
then I should be able to accept
them, no matter what they are.
And not hit me on the
head with a croquet ball.
Sorry about that.
(KISSES)
Not sure you should kiss your
patients on that part of the peanut.
Absolutely free!
Oh, did you say free?
"No, it's me, I'm
Spartacus." "I am Spartacus."
(LISPING) "No, it's me. I'm Spartacus.
Really, I'm Spartacus. Ask anybody."
Clap.
Uh...
(HUMMING)
Yes!
And now, you just...
I am a sick, sick man.
In the eight years
I did the show,
there was only two times,
seriously, that I was ever scared.
And the first time...
Well, I'm going to tell
you, I have a Telestrator,
one of those things that
Madden used. So you gotta watch,
because this could be kind of
fun to use. I've never done this.
The first time that I was
scared on Home Improvement
in these eight years
went something like this.
Watch carefully.
I never knew how to drive this.
Watch the front wheels.
Right here. Not good!
No, no.
Stop it. Stop, stop.
All right.
They didn't even ask me if I had
ever driven one of these things before.
Let me point out a few
John Madden-type things.
These are the distances
you should be very aware of.
Here and here.
Right there. See that?
See that little distance here?
That's how far the
wheel is off the ground.
That's a no-no.
See this, here?
That's the bucket.
Up here, above my
head. Another no-no.
But the real telling part of this
scared, a butt-clenching scared...
Right there are the two
joysticks that control the vehicle.
(LAUGHING)
And here...
Yup, those are my hands.
And that is a man
driving a car like this.
(SCREAMING)
All right.
Too funny. Now,
the second-scariest
moment is this next clip,
where it's more of an emotional
scary. It really was scary for me.
We had had a romantic
evening in the script planned,
and she didn't tell
me, right, Case?
Yeah, I remember that. That was
the night you came down to the bar
with me and the fellows after
work and had a couple drinks.
Right. But when I got home...
Well, it went something
like this. Something like this.
I spent two days
planning this evening.
Do you have any
idea how long it's been
since we had a quiet,
romantic evening together?
I was on the phone. Why
didn't you say, "Come home"?
I wanted to surprise you.
Well, I'm surprised.
Come on, Jill, lighten up.
I didn't understand what
you meant on the phone.
Well, what did you think I meant
when I said all that stuff about
how I was looking forward to
seeing you and, "I'll be waiting"?
Oh, like you said it
like that, "I'll be waiting."
Well, I wanted to be more subtle.
What did you want me to say?
"The kids are gone, I'm home
alone, come and take me, Big Daddy"?
Well, that, I understand.
Good night. Come on, Jill.
I don't go out with these guys every
night. What's making you so angry?
I am angry because you said you
were going to be home in 15 minutes
and then you weren't.
Because I'm flirting with you like crazy
on the phone, you didn't even notice.
And most of all, because I
went to all this trouble for nothing.
I spent the whole
evening by myself,
and now you're stuck
with a plate of cold food.
Oh, don't worry about
me, I ate at the bar.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
I didn't have dessert.
All right, stop
it here. All right.
Roll it back here. Stop, stop,
stop. All right, now, right here,
she had just said that
and I actually jolted out of...
I was in, like, a trance.
And see this face here?
That just says, "Fear."
It wasn't supposed to be that
way. It was supposed to be just...
The dialog... I knew she was going
to get angry. She got so angry with me,
I came out of character
and stopped the show to go,
"Jeez, Pat, are you all right?"
She walks up to me, gets about
an inch in front of my face, she goes,
"Yes, Tim. That's
called 'Acting.'"
Oh.
I sat there, going, "I'm
going to have to try that."
If you parked a brand-new car
under a tree filled with hungry pigeons,
you know, I'll call Triple-A...
(LAUGHING)
Even if you park
a new car under...
Even if you do something as
crazy as park a new car under a tree,
filled with just-fed...
Even if you do
something as crazy
as parking your car under a
tree filled with birds, I am not...
This is jammed or something, Al.
I'll just climb up there and
show you how sturdy this is.
The Binford telescopic
ladder. Just as supportive as...
Tim, you might
wanna watch the...
Could I finish here, Al?
I just want you to be
careful, so you don't...
(SCREAMING)
Thank you all. Look.
This is it.
This is the garage. This is
the home of the automobile.
It's the piston palace.
And the carburetor castle.
It's that muffler mansion.
The transmission Taj Mahal.
Casey, give me
some road-rage rock!
You got it, Timmy.
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
(MIMICKING ENGINE)
I'm addicted to cars.
Well, duh.
I've been thinking of checking
into the Henry Ford Clinic.
This is the greatest gift
you've ever given me.
I gave you three children.
Yeah, but none of them
came out this clean.
On Home Improvement, I
was a father to three boys.
Of course, I wasn't
their real father.
No, no, no, no, of course
I wasn't their real father.
I was really more like a mentor,
you know, an older
brother, maybe.
Well, a twisted,
demented older brother,
who taught them
about family values.
No, no. Dad, it
smells under here!
(SCREAMING)
There's a snake behind you.
Oh, I bet there is!
Dad, we're not joking.
It's moving towards you.
Why don't I just open my shirt
and let him crawl right in, huh?
Tim, the snake
wasn't in the bag.
Because the
snake is in my shirt!
I have a woman. Mommy.
Your mommy can't be
your woman, doofus.
A lot of men pay a psychiatrist a
lot of money to figure that one out.
Mom! What?
Dad's cussing. I'm not cussing.
He said a bad
word. It wasn't bad.
Yeah, he said "hell" and "damn."
I did not say "damn."
Now you did.
It's not that big a deal. I
mean, I've had detention before.
It's the first day of school!
No one ever gets detention
on the first day of school.
I wouldn't say "No one."
Oh, it's gonna take
a minute to boot up,
I still have that
old 286 chip on it.
You know, not much power.
Are you saying this
thing needs more power?
Let me open it up. I can
make this thing go faster.
Well, why don't we
just save you the trouble
and throw it up
against the wall?
Let me talk about sex for a
minute. BRAD: Dad, I don't wanna...
I want you to listen to me. Listen
up. Can you, please? Listen up.
Sex is...
It's like a car.
The best idea is to keep the car in
the garage for a long, long, long time.
And then, somewhere in
the future, the distant future,
when that garage door opens,
you gotta think, "Car cover."
You know, you just keep
feeding them and they grow up.
Don't they? You know?
Well, you know, sometimes
you read your script,
and you can't wait
to do the episode.
This script scared me.
Called The Vasectomy One. Yeah.
(CHUCKLING)
Tim agreed to have a vasectomy,
and then we told
him what that meant.
But when he got down
to the doctor's office,
there was one thing
that Jill forgot to tell him.
And it went something
like this. Something like this.
Hi, Mr. and Mrs. Taylor, I'm
Dr. Kaplan. I'll be with you in a minute.
Harold!
A woman? You brought
me here to see a woman?
I didn't know that she was a
woman. My gynecologist just said
that Dr. Kaplan was
the best urologist in town.
How am I supposed to talk to a woman
about what's going on in man land?
Man land?
Now you got a theme
park between your legs?
My husband, I think,
is just concerned
about how this is gonna
affect his performance.
(CHUCKLING NERVOUSLY)
Honey, let me handle this.
You see, I put on a good show.
And I just wanna make sure
the curtain doesn't come down
in the middle of the first act.
This will not, in any way,
affect your sexual function.
We simply cut off
the flow of sperm...
Oh, boy.
To prevent it from
entering the seminal stream.
Mmm-hmm. So I'm
fishing without bait, now.
No bait.
Why don't you tell us what's
involved in the procedure?
Yeah, I'm dying to hear this.
Well, the morning
of your appointment,
you'd have to shave in the area
where I'll be making the incisions.
Shave? Here?
It's just a routine procedure.
Not in my house, it's not.
What do you think? I
wake up in the morning,
brush my teeth, comb my
hair and shave ping and pong?
The first thing I do is give
you a shot that's a local.
Local, like here in Detroit?
No, local, like here
in your scrotum.
Oh, boy.
That does sting
for a few seconds.
You think?
Forget about it, Wilson. I'm the kind
of guy that likes to stand his ground.
Whoa. Whoa. Whoa...
(GROANING)
You okay there, Tim? Oh, yeah.
Yeah, I just was tired
of using that ladder.
Wilson...
Oh, I love that part. Wilson
was played by Earl Hindman,
who couldn't be here because
he's doing a play in New York City.
He was one of my favorite
characters on the show,
really one of my
favorite actors,
and certainly one
of my favorite friends.
You know, he lived next door to
us for eight years, but, you know,
I got to say, I just never
saw enough of the guy.
Tim, you growing a beard?
What do you think?
Well, I'm not sure,
I could never understand why a
man would want to hide his face.
There was a time when I
thought my extensive research
into ancient tribal cultures,
obscure scientific data,
the thoughts of great philosophers
would never come in handy.
Then you moved in.
Well, Tim, I'm reminded of
what Aristotle said about Plato.
"Keep the lid on tight, otherwise it'll
all dry out." That's what I tell Mark.
I like to create, Wilson. Everything I
do, I wanna make bigger and better.
Well, Tim, this obsessive
desire to create partly happens
because men feel
inferior to women.
(GRUNTS)
It's because we
can't bear children.
I don't mind the boys that much.
Wilson, you're not
making me feel any better.
Well, excuse me, why do I always
have to be Santa's little helper?
Well... I mean, I have wants,
I have needs, I have issues, but
does anyone ever come to the fence
and say, "Wilson, do
you have a problem?"
I mean, no! It's just
"Me, me, me, me!"
Tim?
Wilson, you up?
I am now.
Have you ever had a
real annoying neighbor?
Tim, is this a trick question?
I sure miss you,
Earl. I really do.
Wilson often quoted
philosopher Joseph Campbell,
who said, "Before you can
create, you must destroy."
I've tried to live by that.
(SCREAMING)
If that's good advice, I'll
give you more good advice.
Always think safety when
working with a spinning lathe.
You notice I didn't
wear a necktie.
We get a lot of
letters about this.
You want nothing hanging down,
and no loose
clothing. Possibility...
Let me finish.
Sometimes...
(MIMICKING ENGINE)
The mouse goes in
the little door here... Ah!
(EXCLAIMING)
Presto, you walk
through and door shuts.
(MIMICKING ENGINE)
Missed a shift.
Ow!
Al, I was gonna get to that.
You wanna set your laminate securely
on your chimney's front and back.
(EXCLAIMS)
(JILL LAUGHING)
What is this thing on your head?
It's a little piece of table.
Do you think you should
go to the emergency room?
I was just there. They
said I wasn't a priority.
Why? Was there a guy with a
whole table stuck to his head?
Ow!
Tim. Oh, ow!
(MIMICKING ENGINE)
TIM: It's a little weak here.
You wanna avoid this area, too.
(SCREAMING)
AL: Tim!
Al, you all right?
Look out!
Tim, your foot. Don't
hit the brake release!
What?
Good night, everybody.
Good night! Bye!
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
Hey, just a little bow.
TIM: A bow. AL: A bow!
HINDMAN: You know, we always close
our show with bloopers. Guess what?
Yes, you don't wanna be the only
one with an incredibly desirable woman.
Kiss me before
I get rigor mortis.
Mmm.
That just caused rigor
mortis in a fashion.
(LAUGHING)