Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
♪ Bless us, O Lord
And these your gifts we pray ♪
♪ To bring us strength
To do your will today ♪
♪ Alleluia, alleluia ♪
♪ May not the constant
Grace for God be still ♪
♪ They all who hunger
Have their needs fulfilled ♪
♪ Alleluia, alleluia ♪
(cheerful music playing)
Peace be with you, sisters.
Although, at first
I hesitated to deviate
from the usual solemnity
of our meal times,
I had to acknowledge
that tonight, indeed,
should be a joyous occasion.
Sister Gertrude has been
with us for many years.
And celebrating the birthday
of a sister in Christ
- summons us to-
- Nun: Whores!
You are whores!
You are all whores of Christ!
And you will fucking burn
in hell!
You are vain
and you are lustful!
And I see you! He sees you!
(yells)
Cocksuckers! (yells)
(demonic yelling)
...your fucking God!
Fuck you!
(operatic singing)
- (animals calling)
- (water trickling)
(cars rushing by)
Man: Maybe ever fretting shirt
of punishment
give myrrh-threaded
the golden folds of ease.
Your scarce sheathed bones
are weary of being bent.
Lo, and God shall strengthen
all the feeble knees.
Benjamin, you remember
your Hopkins. (chuckles)
- You're looking well.
- Thank you.
Uh, what were you
doing just now?
Admiring the handiwork.
Not even Solomon in his glory
was arrayed as one of these.
And I understand
congratulations are in order.
I heard you passed your exams,
if only just barely.
Just as you taught me.
If you can't be good,
be good enough.
(laughs) Right.
Good advice for all of us.
And I'm kidding, of course.
Reports are you did brilliantly.
How long have you been out,
a semi-free man?
Three weeks, Father Donaghue.
I'm gonna take my vows
in the spring.
And then they're talking about
taking me on at St. Joseph's.
Perfect, Saint Joe's.
God knows we could use
one like you.
Days like this,
I think the church got
it wrong with Augustine.
Too much original sin.
It seems more likely
that we were conceived
in a state of original blessing.
Well, don't tell
the bishop that.
Oh, of course I wouldn't.
Wait, the bishop?
Why are you here Benjamin?
Well, they called on me
to fetch you,
the bishops
in Father Cappa's office.
He's here? Jesus Christ. Fuck.
And there's another
priest with them, too.
Tall, glasses?
It's vicar general,
isn't it, Father Exley?
I thought this was good news.
No, Benjamin,
it is not good news.
- It's the worst possible news.
- How do you know that?
Ah, Christ, and they
sent you to fetch me,
to humiliate me, no doubt.
What are you even
talking about?
Just forget it.
Thy will be done.
(ominous music playing)
Take a seat, gentlemen.
Father Exley: Relax, Frank,
it's not what you think.
I assume you're familiar
with a convent
in the far corner
of our diocese,
the Carmelite Santa Theresa?
- Yes.
- Understand that this matter
requires the utmost discretion.
Of course.
You have special training,
I'm told.
All kinds. Not so much
with religious sisters.
- Do you think this is funny?
- Let's just cut to the chase.
Two weeks ago,
there was an incident
with one of the sisters
at Santa Teresa.
An incident? You're serious?
His eminence and I rarely
leave the seat of the diocese.
I assure you,
we are absolutely serious.
Does he need to be here?
I don't think he's ready.
Frank, just stop.
They have their reasons.
We'll get to that later.
I have to admit,
I don't understand.
Father Donaghue:
Be glad you don't.
They're talking about
the Holy Rite of Exorcism.
- So, what happened?
- The signs are all there,
spontaneous violent outbursts,
eruptions of vile blasphemy,
surprising feats of strength.
Their diagnoses
was inconclusive.
Dissociative disorder?
Father Exley: Yes.
So vague it might as well
be demonic possession.
(suspenseful music playing)
Father Donaghue: What
do we know about this girl?
She's lived there for years.
Their record's almost a blank,
no family to call.
No history of psychological
problems, sexual abuse?
None that we know about.
I almost find it amusing
you would ask that.
This is hardly useful right now.
My apologies.
But what will happen is this.
The two of you will drive to
Santa Teresa early tomorrow,
talk to the sisters, investigate
this poor girl's symptoms.
Stay as long as you need to.
Use your...
judgment.
At the very least,
we need to rule out
the worst case scenario.
Possession?
Actual demonic possession?
Right, you understand
I don't really believe
in this medieval woo-woo?
You understand that you're
in no position to refuse?
The sisters
will be expecting you.
Father Cappa will help you
with anything else you need.
You're dismissed,
Father Donaghue.
Father Cappa: Benjamin,
would you stay a moment?
What did...
Oh. Gene, don't do this.
I'm sorry, Frank.
I'll talk to you
tomorrow morning.
(suspenseful music playing)
This is gonna be
difficult to hear.
It's hard to say.
He's been a good friend
of mine for years,
and he's done so much
good for this parish.
Until now.
We're sending him away,
far away from here,
perhaps overseas.
What's going on?
What is the shame
of the church right now?
No, I don't believe it.
Father Cappa: I don't either.
But accusations have been made,
and he doesn't deny them.
Pray for him,
but keep an eye on him.
We're afraid the added
pressure is making him...
- erratic.
- Desperate.
Am I gonna have
to worry about...
- my own welfare?
- What do you mean?
Am I gonna be safe with him?
(laughter)
You're a grown man, Benjamin.
You're gonna be just fine.
(laughter)
(dramatic music playing)
Nun: What?
Well?
Mother Superior: Sisters,
get some clean laundry.
- (thunder crashes)
- (screaming)
Mother Superior:
Hold her down, sisters!
- Oh, my God!
- (evil laughing)
- (sisters screaming)
- (Agnes gnarling)
(birds chirping)
What draws so many
young men to the priesthood,
not so much nowadays,
is this beautiful vision
of service.
- Yeah.
- I mean, don't get me wrong,
it is a beautiful vision,
but it needs to be more
- than that.
- I know, you told me about this
in class, remember?
I know all this already.
I just wanna be sure this
comes from your heart of hearts,
not from some idea
of how to live a good life
because you don't know
what you want.
Or... or you're compensating
for something.
Or you're scared of life.
There are plenty of ways
to live a good, meaningful life.
I'm not scared of life.
I've searched my heart,
and it says become a priest.
That seems courageous to me.
- I pray about it a lot.
- Okay, then.
- Benjamin: Do you regret it?
- No.
I don't, but... but it's tough.
And this is really personal,
but what about chastity?
- Benjamin: What about it?
- Don't you want to get a job,
make some money,
meet the nice girl
(growls) or guy?
That'd be okay, too. I don't
know what you're into.
I'm not into anything.
I'm taking a vow of chastity.
Pancakes and sausage
with a side of syrup.
At the very least, know thyself
before you jump into this.
You got this
or you want me to do it?
Father Donaghue: Go for it.
Bless us, O Lord
and these thy gifts,
which we are about
to receive from thy bounty.
Through Christ, our Lord. Amen.
So...
what do you know about exorcism?
Benjamin: Not much.
I know that
it's still a holy rite,
even though the church doesn't
really practice it anymore.
Wrong.
They do.
They just don't claim it.
It's all very hush, hush.
(ominous music playing)
- Thanks for telling me.
- Even if,
in our current age,
less people believe in God,
it seems that belief
in the devil is rising.
Maybe that means
he's winning, I don't know.
It seems to me that people
are just in more pain.
Good. Yes.
They are.
And they don't know why.
So they clutch at whatever
reason they can find.
Look, I've performed exorcisms,
five or six full ones,
with Father Rigazzi,
who really knew the rite.
But I never saw anything
that convinced me
a demon was actually
inside someone.
But I do know
the exorcisms worked.
The power of faith.
Maybe, people needed to get sick
to some other worldly
or unimaginable degree
and could only get well
when a priest forgave them,
someone ordained by God.
Hmm, maybe...
some people just need
to walk through darkness
before they even
get to the light, as...
as cliché as that sounds.
You don't believe in demons?
I'm afraid the answer is no.
Mother Superior:
Our a way of life
is no doubt hard.
It demands rigor, discipline
and strength of spirit.
But, most of all,
the purity of heart.
But sometimes we falter.
Now, understand that I have
sought the Lord's guidance
and deliberated hard
over this decision.
Two days ago, I requested
help from the diocese.
A priest with experience
in such matters,
a true man of God
with the highest of reputations
is now on his way to us.
We will host him
until he decides what
must be done with Sister Agnes.
I'm told
he will arrive this evening.
Now, it goes without saying
that I expect conduct
of the highest standard
during this time.
Remember who you are, sisters.
We are not accustomed
to admitting men
within our walls, even holy men.
So let every action
reflect the dignity
of your solemn vow
before Almighty God.
- May I ask a question, Mother?
- Mother Superior: You may not.
If you have concerns,
you may seek my counsel
after our duties are finished.
We will spend the rest
of the day cleaning
before Father Donaghue arrives.
Sister Mary,
youngest in Christ
and lowliest among us,
I'm told you were friends
with Sister Agnes?
Sister Mary: Yes.
Mother Superior:
Then your hands
must be idle least of all.
You will clean the chapel
from floor to ceiling,
removing every mote of dust.
It's likely Father Donaghue
will serve mass while he's here.
Yes, Mother.
Father Donaghue:
Here, put this on.
- Oh, I can't wear this.
- Father Donaghue: Why not?
I'm not a priest.
You said at lunch
your vows are all but taken.
Yeah,
but I haven't taken them yet.
This is gonna cause
problems in there.
Look, sorry, Father Donaghue,
there's just no way.
Suit yourself.
Don't say I didn't tell you.
(car doors close)
I saw Father Donaghue
give mass once
before the sisterhood.
It was inspiring.
Nun: Who's that
supposed to be, his driver?
Whoever he is, he's handsome.
Sister, you need
\ to contain yourself.
I'm sorry, but he looks
like a movie star.
And Father Donaghue
isn't bad, either.
- Nun: Sister Honey!
- What?
We can't even talk about it?
I don't see the problem.
It's not like I'm going
to go up to him and say,
- "Oh, Father, I..."
- Nun: Sister!
The younger one
is wearing all black,
but no priest color.
Nun: He's probably a deacon.
(dramatic music playing)
(brush scrubbing)
(suspenseful music playing)
I must say, I wish I was told
your young companion
would be accompanying you.
I find it inappropriate.
Almost insulting.
I'm sorry,
Mother Superior, I assumed
- the vicar general...
- Of course, Father Benoit
visits us for mass
three times a week,
but he's 77 years old.
It's unusual enough to have
a priest stay overnight,
let alone this young man.
Again, my apologies Mother.
But he is a very pious
young man.
And I assure you,
he is absolutely essential
for my work here.
Then I assume
we should look at this
as a test of faith
for all of us.
Benjamin, Mother Superior
is concerned... (smacks lips)
How should I put this,
about having a young
unordained rooster
loose in the hen house.
Father, there's no need
to be crude.
Mother Superior, I'm taking
my vows later this year.
I absolutely assure you, with
Christ himself as my witness,
I will remain a model
of propriety
as long as you are kind
enough to host me.
Well, I'll expect so,
and we'll insist upon it.
(cart rattling)
This is Sister Ruth.
This is Sister Honey.
- Thank you, Mother.
- Father Donaghue: Honey?
I... I believe it's Proverbs.
"My son, eat the honey,
for it is good.
And the drippings
of the honeycomb
are sweet to the taste."
(chuckling)
Oh, my God, stop.
Sister, that's enough.
Leave them be.
Have Sister Mary
take their dirty things
- when they're through.
- Yes, Mother.
And afterward, we should do
what we came here to do.
The sooner, the better.
Mother, forgive me,
one last thing.
Do you happen to have any wine?
"And they said of him,
'He casts out devils
by the power of the devil.'"
Careful, Mother.
In that passage, the Pharisees
are talking about our Lord.
Humph.
I thought you said
you were interested
in this going smoothly.
We'll be in and out
of here anyway.
The inflicted sister probably
just needs some priest
to come and say the magic words.
Don't worry. I've seen this
more than a few times.
(suspenseful music playing)
(rattling)
(water splashing)
(dishes shattering)
- (knocking on door)
- Mother Superior: What?
It's Father Donaghue.
It's not appropriate
for you to be here.
But I imagine you knew that.
Forgive me, Mother.
I wanted to apologize
for my behavior.
It was a long trip today.
And I'm not accustomed
to your way of life out here.
I wasn't thinking,
and I should've known better.
You should have.
I'm afraid I'm more used
to dealing with lay people.
Sometimes I joke with them.
It puts them at ease.
But here I should conduct
myself with more respect,
especially toward you.
Well, then I must forgive you.
My temper is...
It's been quite
a stressful time.
May the Holy Spirit
guide us both.
Now, shall we go see
about your poor lost lamb?
(suspenseful music playing)
(crackling music playing)
Has she spoken at all
in any ancient languages?
- No, Father.
- Has she said anything
about any of you
she couldn't possibly know?
Secrets or private details,
particularly those things
from before you took your vows?
Of course not.
Likely all will be well.
Follow my lead as we discussed.
If you become afraid,
you can't let it show.
You have to be strong,
but fill your hearts with love.
If you see anything strange,
stick to the script.
You tied her up?
You treat someone
like an animal,
they'll act like an animal.
Mother Superior: The poor girl
injured herself.
Oh. What's her name?
Mother Superior: Agnes.
Sister Agnes.
Sister Agnes, can you hear me?
Can you feel me near you?
(dramatic music playing)
This looks bad,
but maybe not that bad.
Benjamin, the holy water.
(growls)
Well, let's begin.
- Lord, have mercy.
- All: Lord, have mercy.
Christ, have mercy.
- All: Christ, have mercy.
- Fuck you.
Lord, have mercy.
All: Lord, have mercy.
Christ, have mercy.
All: Christ, have mercy.
Father Donaghue: Begone, you.
Begone, seducer.
Your place is in solitude.
Your abode
is the nest of serpents.
Get down and crawl with them.
You might delude man,
but God cannot be mocked.
Go to hell, cocksucker.
It is He who cast you out,
from whose sight
nothing is hidden.
It is He who repels you,
to whose might
all things are subject.
Many things. Many things.
Father Donaghue:
Is He who expels you.
He who has everlasting fire.
(interposing voices
and music playing)
In the name of the Father
and the Son and the Holy Spirit.
All: Amen.
Mother Superior: Oh,
dear sweet sister.
That was dramatic.
It has to be.
It's an exorcism,
one of the most elaborate
song and dance acts
the world has ever seen.
So, that was all in her head?
More or less.
Look, the Carmelites
here in Santa Teresa
belong to an entirely
enclosed order.
In some ways,
they're more a relic
of the old church
than even exorcism itself.
- Yeah, but if they...
- That's enough heaven
and hell for one night,
Benjamin, let's get some sleep.
I'm knackered.
(birds chirping)
God sees the truth...
but waits.
Over 100 years ago,
Leo Tolstoy
wrote a story with that title.
And it has always stuck with me.
I find that so many of us
who devote our lives to God
through our vows,
spend a great deal
of time waiting.
Waiting on God.
It can be so easy
to fall into despair
in this fallen world.
How could we know this gift,
the glory of salvation,
of finding our way to Christ,
if at first we did not wander?
How could we ever
truly appreciate
the miracle of redemption
and grace
if we'd not suffered tribulation
and come to darkness?
I haven't met all of you,
but the Mother Superior
tells me that you are a pious
and devoted bunch.
And I am truly grateful
for the hospitality
that you've shown us
during this time of trial,
to me and my strapping
young buck of a companion.
Isn't he handsome, ladies?
But there is one among you
who I am most pleased
to have become acquainted with,
one who has suffered much,
walking through a darkness
that most of us
cannot even imagine,
one who has endured
a true test of faith.
God sees the truth, but waits.
And he can always see a heart
that is fundamentally pure,
as I know hers is.
Okay, Sister Honey.
(dramatic music playing)
What say you, dear sister,
are you ready to join us
in the Lord's sacrament?
We must be patient.
Understandably, our dear sister
will take some time
to return to her former self.
Well, aren't you just
the sweetest old liar?
What?
(laughs)
(Sister Agnes sighs)
(dramatic music playing)
(in child tone) Father Frank,
he touched my wee-wee.
Father Frank,
he touched my wee-wee!
(growls)
(all scream)
So, should we call the diocese?
Absolutely not.
- Well, the rite didn't work.
- You've made this worse
- by your pride.
- Obviously,
that was not my doing, Mother.
It ambushed us.
So, it's an it now?
What she said about the child,
how could she know that?
I thought everybody
knew about that.
I have never seen anything
like this before in my life.
I thought you were
supposed to be the expert.
They were setting me up to fail.
- Sister!
- I'm sorry, Mother.
We have to call the diocese.
You don't want that kind
of attention here right now.
And it's not needed. I know
someone who can help us.
- We served in Rome.
- You mean a priest?
Kind of.
(dramatic music playing)
Cross Talk with Guy Chesterton.
No matter
your religious beliefs,
you're probably familiar
with the old adage
giving the devil his due.
Well, our guest this evening
can be said to have done
all that and more,
tracing an unlikely career path
through decades
of macabre service,
casting out alleged demons,
possibly saving souls,
and becoming a household
name in the process.
We're pleased to welcome
Father Henry Black
in the studio with us
this evening.
- Welcome, Father Black.
- Well, thank you, Guy,
that was quite an introduction.
It's good to be with you.
Now, your methods are said
to be quite different
from the Catholic church,
not to mention from the way
we've seen exorcism
represented in the media
and on films.
It's true
you were ex-communicated
from the Church
over 17 years ago.
Never looked back. Hmm.
Now, I'm sure they miss me just
about as much as I miss them.
Let's go back
to the beginning.
When did you learn you had
a talent for this kind of thing?
When I was a child,
my little sister was possessed
by a demon named Bune.
You were involved in exorcisms
from a very early age.
No, Bune,
he was a stubborn demon.
He wouldn't get out.
So, you're saying
a demon named Bune
infiltrated your sister's body
years ago,
and to this day
resides in your family's home?
- Father Black: Correct.
- And all this can be verified?
It took some getting used to.
But growing up,
I was forced to adapt
to the ways of the demon Bune.
I grew accustomed to interacting
with him on a daily basis.
So, by the time I got my collar,
I already had all
the know-how I needed
to exorcise anything
you put in front of me.
And yet,
with all your experience,
you were never able
to exercise the demon Bune
- from your sister.
- It's complicated, Guy.
I mean, the family,
at this point,
had become so familiar
with Bune.
He still lives with my family,
still eats at the table,
still sleeps in what used
to be my sister's room,
family vacations and whatnot.
His favorite color is green.
His favorite dessert
is lemon chiffon cake.
What do you say
to those who claim
you're simply exploiting
the families you visit
and capitalizing
on the mental illness
of the so-called possessed?
(sighs) Let me put it
to you this way, Guy.
I didn't choose
this line of work.
It chose me.
God chose me.
He put me on a path of darkness.
He put a demon
by my side and said,
"Be not afraid, my son."
We'll be right back.
(dramatic music playing)
- (dog barking)
- (crickets chirping)
She's given herself
over to the devil.
She needs medical attention.
Sisters, you forget yourselves.
As if we don't have
enough to do.
Sister Honey,
find out if Father Donaghue
has stopped bleeding. If so,
clean and dress his wound.
Yes, Mother Superior.
You two,
finish cleaning the filth
that Agnes has trailed
from the chapel. Go.
You, prepare a light meal
to be served to the rest
of the sisters
in half an hour.
We will gather our strength,
after which
we will retire to our rooms
and we will pray
for the rest of the evening.
- Do I make myself clear?
- Yes, Mother.
Sister Mary, Sister Ruth,
she's quiet, yes?
She hasn't stirred since
the straps or the holy water.
Then go.
Sister Mary,
since you two
were thick as thieves,
you will attend Agnes,
or whatever holy
remains in her.
We might still call her
by that name.
I can't see her.
You're frightened, child?
You don't have the luxury
to be frightened.
- Yes, Mother.
- And mind,
if she speaks evil,
don't listen.
Hail Mary, full of grace.
The Lord is with thee.
- Blessed art thou among women.
- (doors slamming)
And blessed is the fruit
of thy womb, Jesus.
Holy Mary, Mother of
God, pray for us sinners
now and at the hour
of our death, amen.
Hail Mary, full of grace.
The Lord is with thee.
Blessed art thou among women.
And blessed is the fruit
of thy womb, Jesus.
Holy Mary, Mother of God,
pray for us sinners
now and at the hour
f our death, amen.
Hail Mary, full of grace.
The Lord is with thee.
Blessed art thou among women.
And blessed is the fruit
- of thy womb, Jesus.
- Sister Agnes: Mary!
- Holy Mary, Mother of God...
- Sister Agnes: Go home!
...pray for us sinners, now and
at the hour of our death, amen.
- Hail Mary full of grace...
- Praise Jesus!
- Blessed is the fruit of thy...
- (Agnes speaks indistinctly)
Holy Mary, Mother of God,
pray for us
now and at the hour
of our death, amen.
Holy Mary, Mother of God,
please pray for me.
(demonic voices
drown out praying)
Hey, Mary.
Hey, Agnes.
Are you afraid of me?
You bit off
Father Donaghue's nose.
Well, he had a nice nose.
(giggles)
I wish I'd said goodbye
to everyone before I left,
told them how much I loved them.
But I guess
that doesn't matter now.
Aren't you uncomfortable?
What do you mean?
Come on, take that shit off.
(gentle music playing)
There, isn't that better?
You and I have never
really been honest
with each other, have we?
You lost someone.
- Yeah.
- I lost someone, too.
The love of my life.
He was my teacher.
He could make me laugh
like no one else could.
But I was stupid and I lost him.
Paul Satchimo.
You loved him?
And he loved me.
You lost your son.
The only person I ever loved.
You have to bury the dead, Mary.
(ominous music playing)
(coughs and chokes)
I'll always be with you.
Mother Superior: I beseech you
now for guidance, Lord,
you whose righteousness
has always breathed
through this convent
like the sweetest song.
How is this wretchedness
come to pass upon us?
Is my service
not pleasing to you?
- (knocking on door)
- What?
- What's it?
- I'm sorry, Mother.
For a great many things,
I'm sure.
I think you should go see Agnes.
What are you talking about?
The devil is in her.
Has it gotten into you as well?
I don't think it's the devil.
She was kind to me.
The devil leads with kindness.
And why are you not presentable?
There are men
in this house, you slut. Leave!
(door slams shut)
(gentle piano music playing)
Do you want me to pray with you?
No, Benjamin, just
leave me to the wolves.
Maybe a priest without a nose
won't seem so strange in...
Vietnam or Croatia
or wherever the hell it is
- they're gonna be sending me.
- That's it, think positive.
I am thinking positive.
I'm positively fucked.
(chokes) Yeah.
Father Black
will be here in the morning.
Well,
that should be interesting.
(sobbing) I am fucked.
I am fucked,
I'm fucked, I'm fucked.
(birds chirping)
(gently dramatic music playing)
(doorbell rings)
Frank.
Good to see you again.
So what happened there, Frank,
somebody spite your face
a little bit?
Yeah, something like that.
Father Black,
I would like to introduce you
to Benjamin,
one of my best students.
Father Henry Black
and his lovely assistant.
I'm sorry,
I didn't catch your name.
- I didn't disclose.
- Right.
Pleased to make
your acquaintance.
You should be
ashamed of yourself.
- Who's this guy?
- I'm sorry.
We've been under
considerable stress
in our current predicament.
- Benjamin, if you...
- Mother Superior: Boy's right.
This is not the sort of company
I'd ever allow in this convent,
no matter what the circumstance.
You absolutely
cannot smoke here.
You know, I can sense
when I'm not welcome, Frank.
I appreciate the call
- after so long, but...
- No, no, no, no.
- Come on, let's...
- Please, Henry, please.
The fact is that we are
in dire need of your expertise.
That's probably true.
Mother, you and the sisters
in your cherished convent
have been the most
gracious hosts.
But now I have a request.
Respectfully,
would you give it a rest?
- Excuse me?
- Forgive us, Mother.
- This is highly inappropriate.
- (chuckles) At this juncture,
I don't see that you
have any other choice.
Please escort us to Agnes
so that we can end
this dance once and for all.
I most certainly will not.
Very well, then.
If you will follow me,
I would love to introduce you
to the poor girl,
and you can commence your work.
Oh, what the hell?
I drove this far.
Mother Superior:
I'll be notifying the bishop.
I am curious.
(dramatic music playing)
Hello there, Agnes.
(hisses)
Wow, shows some good instinct
because I'm not your friend.
I'm not your friend at all.
No, ma'am.
Let me ask you something.
Do you feel like
you're welcome here?
Is that what's going on?
You feel like you're welcome?
Because I've looked around.
You're in a convent.
So... so, you're not
welcome here.
Which means that you and I,
well, we're gonna have to...
have this little talk,
aren't we?
You're a disgrace.
Well, you can sweet
talk me all you want,
but I'm not scared.
Fuck you, cocksucker.
Oh! Yeah, you can't bruise name
with your words, either.
I've been to all nine
levels of hell and back.
Hell wouldn't have you.
Well, you see, that's...
that's where you're wrong
because I have escorted
several there myself.
(demonic laugh)
I think
I'm starting to like you.
Well that's, that's sweet.
Let me tell you something.
Come here,
let me tell you something.
I love you.
You love me?
I do. I love you.
And you know who else loves you?
Sister Agnes: No.
- Jesus Christ! Get out, demon!
- Stop, no! No!
- Time to go! You hear me?
- No, stop, please!
- The power of Jesus Christ...
- I'm sorry!
- ...our true Lord and Savior...
- No, no!
- ...compels you!
- No! No!
- And I say begone!
- I'm so sorry!
- (yells indistinctly) Begone!
- I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
- This has to stop now!
- Just wait!
Child of God, for it
is He who commands you!
(whimpering) I'm sorry,
I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
What just happened?
It's all right, my child.
You're safe now.
I don't understand, I...
I could... I could see, like,
I could feel.
It was like, it was like
I was another person.
Yeah, well, you were,
you were in the grips
of a creature most foul.
But it's okay, you're safe now.
You see, folks,
that's the way
the cookie crumbles.
You see, if you'd have let me
have my camera crew in here,
we could've documented
some history.
- Nice work, Henry.
- Thank you, Frank.
Father Black, thank you.
No, there's no need
to thank me.
No, I want to thank you.
But I have to tell you,
I'm afraid.
Well, there's nothing
to be afraid of.
Sister Agnes:
Maybe not for me.
- Well, what do you mean?
- It's not me I'm afraid for.
I don't understand.
It's you.
(Agnes yells)
Oh, goddammit, son of a bitch!
- (gasps in horror)
- Please, praise me! God!
- Please, please! God!
Somebody help me!
Aren't you going
to do something?
- Father Black: Help!
- (vomits)
(screaming)
- (Agnes laughs demonically)
- Father Black: God damn you!
(buzzing)
(light, upbeat music playing)
♪ Even though
I am a part of you ♪
♪ You would like to lose ♪
♪ You are forgetting
That love is a profession ♪
♪ You can never choose ♪
♪ So kiss me once for some ♪
♪ Kiss me once for running far
From base arms ♪
♪ Cradle me in your embrace ♪
♪ Hold me like the baby
That I am ♪
♪ For even just a memory... ♪
Wanda: Yeah, we're good.
Hey, Wanda, do you know
if our paychecks are ready?
Oh, I don't know. Go ask Curly.
He's in the back.
- How are you doing?
- Man: All right.
- Good.
- (knocking on door)
Curly: Come.
Hey, I was wondering if
my paycheck was ready yet?
Yeah, sure, sure, sure.
You're...
You're that new girl, huh?
What was your...
what was your name again?
- I'm terrible with that stuff.
- It's okay. Uh, Mary.
Mary, Mary, Mary, Mary, Mary.
Mary Jane, Mary Jane.
There we go, I got you.
All right, here, there you go.
- Thank you, sir.
- Curly: Yeah.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
You just call me...
call me Curly, all right?
Today your day off?
Yeah, I'm working
a double tomorrow.
Oh, nice.
Well, you enjoy your day.
Yeah, you too.
Curly: Used to be a nun, huh?
- Yeah, I was.
- Golly.
I've always wanted
to meet a nun.
Well, I'm sure I've met
enough for the both of us.
(Curly laughs)
I bet you have.
I bet you have. That's good.
That's good.
Hey, listen,
I'll be the first tell you
that I don't for fraternizing
with the employees here,
but since you're new in town,
if you ever wanted to, you know.
I'm out and about a lot.
I don't know if you like
to drink or if you like wine.
I like wine. (chuckles)
I like...
I like other stuff, too.
So... When was the last time
you went out with somebody?
I don't know.
I guess you got
all kinds of stuff
just stirring up inside you.
(forcefully exhales)
Yeah, well,
you just think about it.
You know where to find me.
Hey, enjoy your day off.
Thank you.
(door closes)
(ominous music playing)
Later, girl.
(teller muttering)
Now, take care.
Thank you so much.
Hi, how can I help you?
I just need to cash this check.
Teller: Sure. You have
a checking account with us?
I don't. Do I need one?
Yes. In order to cash
your check, you do. Yeah.
Mary: Okay.
Does it cost anything?
It's $25,
but we have great benefits.
- Twenty-five?
- Cashier: Twenty-five, yes.
You have a good day.
Woman: (On TV) It seems
I remember doing this before,
only then
I didn't have so far to fall.
(dramatic music plays on TV)
Woman: (on TV)
Where are you now, Martin?
(gentle orchestral
music playing)
(sobs)
(child giggling)
He brought by his dog
thinking I would babysit.
I mean,
now what kind of lazy SOB
would think that I would
take care of his dog?
Just crazy son of a...
There you go.
You have a good day.
I sure like that tie and
that pink shirt. Looks good.
Oh. Hey, Mary,
- could you do me a favor?
- What?
Curly's yapping about
some spill on aisle four.
Would you clean it up for me?
Please? I mean,
my back is just killing me.
I've been standing here
- for four hours.
- Okay, fine. Fine.
I'll watch your register.
Curly: What the fuck
are you talking about?
This is not the plan, all right?
He was drunk
off the booze you made.
- Okay?
- Oh, so it's my fault?
- Woman: Yes.
- Curly: Listen,
I have bills to pay.
You have a bill to pay.
(muttering)
He fucking gets drunk and
takes advantage of you?
Woman: Go to hell, Curly.
(muttering)
How are you doing today,
- Sister Mary?
- I'm good.
I just got off work and I'm
gonna go meet some friends.
Please, if you want anything,
just help yourself.
Well, I ain't gonna trouble
you none. I just...
I just need a moment
of your time,
if that's okay with you.
You got a little bit of time?
Yeah. Is everything okay?
Nah, nothing like that.
You being a nun and all, when
you came looking for a place,
well, you know,
I gave you a special deal.
And I appreciate it a lot.
I really do.
Ah, it was nothing.
It feels good to help, it does.
But well, my wife, Ona,
she gets bent
out of shape a lot.
But you gotta understand,
she's a juice head.
Been that was for as
long as I can remember.
And when she caught wind
of me helping out
another young woman and...
Well, she got ideas.
- Is there something that...
- Earl: Hold on now.
I done told her wasn't
nothing going on between us,
but that don't mean
she listened.
See, we have a history
that stretches far and wide
across this city.
And I done quit drinking,
understand,
I don't touch this stuff.
This ain't my doing, but anyhow,
I'm afraid I'm going to have
to break our promise.
I know I told you
I needed 450 for this place.
But in order to be fair
to the other tenants,
be fair to Ona, I'm going
to have to ask for 600.
Six hundred dollars?
Earl: I'm real sorry.
It ain't like me to promise one
thing and then take it back.
Right. It's just $600
is a lot of money.
My job doesn't pay very much.
Earl: It's tough all over,
Sister Mary.
♪ For even just a memory... ♪
Earl: I'm gonna give you
the number
of another young woman
named Evonne.
She works up at the laundromat.
She's always looking for help.
It ain't much,
but maybe it'll help you
get over the hump,
won't put you out much.
The work's easy.
♪ Even though I am a mountain ♪
♪ You wish to crumble ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Your heartbeat run away
Like a tray ♪
♪ Skippin' on the ground ♪
♪ You will start to smile
And the air is ♪
♪ Come flooding back ♪
- Hello, sisters.
- Sister Mary. Aww!
Sister Ruth: You look wonderful.
Sister Honey: We just wanted
to see how you were doing.
Mary: I'm fine.
But how are you?
Mary: Good.
So, you are living in this town?
Yeah, I got an apartment
near here not long ago.
What a coincidence.
We're only a few stops up
the bus line at Villa Lucia.
It must be part of God's plan.
- Do you like it?
- Sister Ruth: Oh, yes.
But it's very different
than Santa Teresa.
- It's a convent in the city.
- Can you imagine?
After Sister Agnes was put away
and Mother Superior
laid to rest...
(murmuring prayer)
...the diocese thought it
best to relocate all of us.
And the new order
is very different.
So, what have you been up to?
Well, I got a job.
You're so brave.
I always said that
you were the brave one.
Didn't I always say that about
Sister Mary, Sister Ruth?
Yes, she always
did say that about you.
And also that
you were pure of heart.
I did. I did. (chuckles) I did.
We understand better than anyone
how difficult it must've been
for you to leave the convent
the way that you did.
And we want you to know
we have your best interest
at heart, but we feel that...
Listen, we understand,
we really do.
What happened was
traumatizing, to say the least.
Sister Ruth: We want you to know
we have your best interest
- at heart.
- Sister Honey: Traumatizing
for everybody. Traumatizing.
The Church not only
lost Santa Theresa,
I heard it was sold last month,
but Father Donaghue as well.
That brave and gentle man.
- What happened to him?
- Sister Ruth: He disappeared.
No one has seen him since.
We know that
it's been a lot to deal with,
and we respect your choice.
But we would also like
to extend our welcome
if you wanted to join us
at Villa Lucia.
Sister Honey, Sister Ruth,
I appreciate you reaching out,
but after all
we've been through,
it just felt right
to put everything behind me.
We understand that.
But may I ask you
a question, Mary?
- Is it about Agnes?
- Sister Ruth: No.
Do you still carry the faith?
I don't know.
I keep a crucifix
on the wall in my apartment
and I pray sometimes,
but I don't know what
it all means anymore.
I mean, now that I'm
back in the real world,
my time at the convent
feels like a dream.
I keep asking for God
to guide me and...
I hear nothing back.
Did you know
among our other duties
in the new order,
we service the poor.
Yes, our soup lines
are very popular. (chuckles)
Hey, I got this.
Thanks. I'm gonna go clock out.
- You all right?
- Yeah. Yeah.
Curly: Hey, whoa.
Who's taking over your shift?
It's Wanda. She's out there now.
Can't be Wanda.
I done fired Wanda.
- No, I didn't know.
- Yeah, well,
there's a lot
you don't know about.
Especially what
goes on back here.
I don't know.
I noticed you've been picking up
a lot of double shifts.
You're a worker.
Not like these other girls that,
they don't care
about getting ahead.
- My rent just went up.
- Yeah, I know
your rent just went up.
And I get it. I get it.
We all got stuff like that
in our lives.
Let me ask you something.
This job,
all the double shifts,
the back-to-backs,
is it gonna be enough?
We'll see.
Yeah, we'll see.
How about this?
How about I give you
a little extra cash.
Then when I need a favor,
- I can call on you.
- Mary: No, thank you.
"No, thank you"?
I appreciate it.
But I can't take that.
My money's not good
enough for you?
I'd just like to make it
my own way.
(clears throat)
Yeah, I can respect that.
I'm going to get you
one of these days.
I better go back up front.
Curly: Yeah, go on.
Evonne:
So, you're Earl's friend?
Yeah.
I'm his tenant.
Mm-hmm.
He's really nice.
Evonne: Oh, I'll bet he is.
(light acoustic music playing)
Host: Lady, if you don't know
the difference between
a meatball and a matzo ball,
I cannot help you.
(audience laughs)
Anyway, please give it
up for my good friend,
the great Paul Satchimo,
ladies and gentlemen.
- Paul Satchimo.
- (audience applaud)
Hey, everybody.
You know what I've noticed?
Not everybody's trying.
You ever notice that?
Okay, I saw a guy
on the sidewalk yesterday,
he was pushing a shopping cart
full of newspapers,
wearing pink stretch pants.
- He was trying.
- (laughter)
He went to the bank
to get a loan.
They weren't trying at all.
I went to this bar back here
to cash in my two drink limit,
and, man.. (scoffs)
...they weren't trying either.
So, now here I am,
up here trying, dead sober.
- (laughter)
- Okay. Check this out.
Some people are trying,
some people aren't trying.
Some people
aren't even trying to try.
But some people
are trying to not try.
And some people are trying
to try not trying.
Hey, if I thought that
could work, I might try it.
(laughter)
Anyway, what do you
guys want to talk about?
Money?
Jobs?
I had a regular type
job once, I did.
I was a cold caller
selling restaurant quality
meats at wholesale prices.
I was not very good at it.
(laughter)
One night...
Yes, one night...
victory.
I sold 25 pounds
of New York strips
all across the greater
metropolitan area.
My name topped the sales board.
I rose from my cubicle
like a champion
as my colleagues watched
with... with, um...
with envy,
and disdain
because they knew...
- (laughter)
- ...that I had been chosen
by the team leader, Mark,
to enter the inner sanctum,
the deep freeze,
the deep freeze
which held a cornucopia
of frozen meat products.
And as I stood there,
gazing into the...
the glistening vista
of frozen meats,
Mark said to me and I quote,
"Pick anything you want."
Anyway, that's it.
That's the story.
It's not really a joke, I guess.
It's really more
just a 38-year-old man
sitting alone in his apartment,
eating three pounds of sausage.
(audience burst into laughter)
You know what, that sausage
didn't make me happy.
Things, things do not
make people happy.
Do you know what does make
people happy? Do you know?
Connection.
Us, connecting in this room,
right now.
- Forget about the sausage.
- (laughter)
It's an electricity.
Do you feel it?
- Right now, it's happening.
- Father Donaghue: It's us.
We're communicating
with one another.
That's where real happiness
comes from. I don't know.
Anyway, what else you
guys want to talk about?
(pulsating music playing)
(laughs)
Frozen meats.
Hey, hey, hey.
What is so funny?
People are complaining.
(giggles)
- That's what I thought.
- (laughs)
Would you calm the fuck down?
Mary: I'm sorry.
Jesus Christ.
(lively music playing)
Evonne: It can't compare
to the nonsense,
She started saying things.
(music drowns out
Evonne's words)
And concentrate
on the things you can handle.
Sometimes,
I gotta pray for strength.
Like the good book says,
"Like a dog
returneth to its vomit,
so a fool repeats
his foolishness."
Mary, are you even
listening to me?
Hi. Do you need any help?
Um, no, I don't think so.
I just came in here to...
Wait, what do people
come in here to do?
(laughs) Um, I can show
you how the machines work.
(washing machines rattling)
I think I got it, but thank you.
No problem.
Okay, well.
Yeah, just let me know
if you need anything.
Paul: Sure.
- Who's that?
- He's a comedian.
He don't look funny.
Is he funny?
Yes. He's a comedian.
(door creaking)
- Oh, hey.
- Hi.
Am I not allowed
to smoke out here?
It's fine.
Cool. You never know these days.
I saw your show.
Oh, okay. Well, no wonder.
Well, thanks for coming.
So, what did you think?
Of the show?
Yeah. Did you laugh?
- No.
- Huh!
Everyone's a critic.
It wasn't my best night.
But I laughed later.
Well, I guess that's something,
the slow burn kind of a thing.
Of course, the point is
to laugh during the show.
That's kind of the idea,
I guess.
Hell, I dunno.
You know what?
Laugh when you wanna laugh.
It's a free country.
I knew Agnes.
Excuse me?
I was in the convent
with Agnes before she left.
Oh.
Wow.
She was in love with you.
(gentle guitar music playing)
(pulsating roaring)
You look nice.
Paul: I have to say I haven't
even heard her name in...
I don't know, it's been awhile.
You must've known her
pretty well.
Mary: We had talks.
Not a lot, but the ones we had
were important.
She was incredible.
And do you know
where she is now?
You mentioned
she left the convent.
She's in a different place now.
What do you mean?
I don't want to talk about it.
I understand.
I always wondered about her,
to be honest.
The minute that things
got hard between us
was the minute she gave up.
And I never bought into any
of her religious horseshit,
by the way.
I'm sorry if I offend, but I...
I couldn't understand why she
went to such great lengths
for her salvation.
Anyway, we were young.
I... I didn't usually make
a habit of dating my students,
but I, you know, in that case
I made an exception.
How long have you
been a funny man?
A what? (laughs)
I guess, I don't know,
I've always been funny.
I, uh, I was funny
when I was a kid,
started putting an act
together when I was like 19,
and I should probably be
farther along in my career
than I am, but...
But you're comfortable?
You like who you are?
Yeah, I think so.
I... I make just
the right amount of money
and I... I'm happy
living life the way that I do.
I don't,
I don't need fame or fortune.
I do what I love.
How about you?
What's your story?
Why did you leave the convent?
That was Agnes, really.
She convinced me there
was maybe more to life
outside the Church.
So, what do you think?
I don't think either of us
ever belonged there.
Is there anything
you're passionate about?
Anything at all?
I don't know.
The only thing I ever worked
hard for was becoming a sister.
Well, geez, Mary, that's about
the saddest thing I ever heard.
Can I ask you
a personal question?
Have you ever felt love
outside of God?
(gentle piano music playing)
Pedro: Hey, Paul, don't mind us.
We just been here a few hours.
Are you gonna introduce
us to your friend?
Oh, sorry. Peter, Evelyn, Pedro.
This is Mary.
Evelyn: Nice to meet you.
He's the best.
I always say he's the best.
(gentle music playing)
Anyway, here we are.
You can feel free
to make yourself at home.
I don't know, have a seat
or whatever you do.
I'll be right back.
I like your place.
Paul: Thank you.
You were the funniest man?
- Like in the world?
- Paul: What's that?
Oh, that? Yeah.
That was many years ago.
Who's the funniest man now?
Um...
I actually don't know.
Do you like music?
I used to.
Okay.
You read a lot. Books.
Oh, yeah. Well, as I said,
I used to teach.
There was a time...
I can't say that I really
have the focus to just...
to just sit and read a book.
I haven't for a while.
I don't know
what happened there.
What do you do now?
You mean to take
the place of reading?
Um...
I don't know. I guess I drink.
I have to say, I don't know why
I'm being so honest with you.
I know that we just met,
and I...
I don't know.
Well, you're not...
you're not the usual sort
of woman that I associate with.
You asked me a question
in the bar
before your friends came.
Yeah.
I asked you if you'd ever
been in love before.
The answer is yes.
When I was really young,
I got pregnant.
Back then, I was
a different kind of person.
I don't even
remember the conception
or who the guy was.
Anyway, I decided
to keep the baby.
And it was like...
a whole new window
opened up on my life.
I loved my son
with everything I had.
I loved the way he laughed.
I loved to hear him cry
when I left the room.
I loved the color of his cheeks
and his stupid little teeth.
I was even...
starting to love God.
(melancholy music playing)
Then, one day,
God took my son away
and left me with nothing.
I prayed.
I begged God to tell me why.
- And he said...
- Paul: What'd he say?
He said nothing.
I don't know what lives there
in that nothingness now.
But he just...
he put a spell on me.
(ominous music playing)
(indistinct hollering)
(indistinct yelling continues)
- (yelling stops)
- (moans)
(Paul groans)
- (Mary laughs)
- What is the matter with you?
(laughs)
Oh, I'm sorry.
- (laughs)
- Stop fucking laughing, then.
I'm sorry.
No, I'm really sorry.
- Why did you do that?
- I'm really sorry.
(demonic laughs)
My face!
I have a show tomorrow night!
- Are you sick or something?
- Mary: No, please. No.
Paul: Just... just leave, okay?
Come on. Just...
(ominous music playing)
- (Mary panting)
- (Paul groaning)
Hail Mary, full of grace.
The Lord is with thee.
Blessed art thou amongst women
and blessed is the fruit
of thy womb, Jesus.
Holy Mary, Mother of God,
pray for us sinners
now and at the hour
of our death, amen.
Dear God, please listen to me,
please listen to me.
(continues praying silently)
Please, I beg you. I beg you.
I'll do anything you want me to.
Please just talk to me.
Please just show me,
show me, please.
(muttering)
(ticketing gun clicking)
(clicking echoing)
(loud rattle)
(dryer rumbling)
(bench squeaking)
Excuse me.
Yes, I know it's a big diocese,
but someone in your office
has to know
who I'm talking about.
He was around the tragedy
at the Santa Teresa convent.
I was a sister there.
(grunts) Okay. Yes. Okay.
I can hold on, but I am at work.
- What the fuck are you doing?
- It's an emergency.
Crazy bitch.
(snarls)
Hello? Okay, hold on.
What the fuck is wrong with you?
You're sure that's
the right number? Thank you.
Curly: You're fired.
You're fired!
You think you
might be possessed?
That's serious.
No, not really, I guess.
(sniffs)
You shouldn't joke about that.
I think I just remember Agnes.
Were you two close?
Yes. Yes, we were.
We had a good conversation
right before she, uh...
you know. Anyway,
she helped me rethink my life.
That's great. I never
would've guessed that about her.
So, how's it going?
Oh, I don't know.
I just walked out on my job,
so.... (snickers)
You know, after what
happened at Santa Teresa,
the Church would probably
put you up for a few months
if you can't make rent.
Thanks, but I'll figure it out.
I'll call you again if I can't.
Now, I'm told
your former sisters
invited you to join them
at Villa Lucia.
Do you think
the life of a religious
could appeal to you again?
I don't think so.
It's different
than Santa Teresa.
It's less confined.
But if you no longer
hear the call.
Maybe not then.
Well, maybe not.
A wise man once taught me
it's not something
you should try to fake.
So, can you think of any other
work you'd be passionate about?
No.
You, uh...
Oh, never mind.
What?
It can't be that bad.
I had a son.
He died.
Just now, I was thinking how
much I would've liked him
to grow up and be like you.
And that's way too much.
- (Mary chuckles)
- No, it's not.
It's just, um...
my mother died.
I was 11.
So, that means a lot.
Can I ask you
a spiritual question?
Benjamin: Yeah,
of course, it's my job.
I hope I can answer it.
How do we know God?
Well, there's scripture.
And there's a few thousand
years of church teaching.
I'm not talking
about any of that.
I'm talking about contact,
connection.
How do we know God?
How do you know God?
- In this world?
- Mary: Yeah.
Okay. Yeah, I'll try.
Just remember, I haven't
been a priest very long, so.
All right.
Let's take this sandwich.
We're hungry
and it's all we've got,
but let's look at it.
First, there's this
terrible crappy bread
you've got to get through.
And that's most of it, really.
It's so much bread,
this starchy, substandard
awfulness, this filler.
Most of this sandwich,
most of this world,
just a bunch of junk
to chew through,
hoping that it ends soon.
Then you got
flavorless tomatoes,
this wilted lettuce.
Cheese looks like death.
Sauce, if you had a jar of it,
you'd probably die.
But hidden within all
this sound and fury
is a thin sliver of meat.
And that's the stuff
we really came here for. Right?
You can imagine a better
sandwich, a better world...
I know I can.
More fulfilling, with more meat.
Just like you can imagine
more good people
when you've met one
really good one, you know?
Okay.
So for Christians, at least,
that one really good person
who brings out the best in you,
makes you want to bring out
the best in other people,
that's Christ.
And if you look hard enough,
he's in this world.
He's the meat in the sandwich,
this stuff we'd realize
we were really hungry for
if we knew ourselves
like God knows us.
Because Christ is God incarnate,
and carne means meat, flesh.
You know, he comes to us
in a form that we can recognize,
God in a meat suit like us.
God con carne.
But to know him in this world,
to really know him,
you have to deal
with the whole sandwich.
And if you chew through it,
and you keep a pure heart,
you can know God,
taste God.
You just ate God.
Well, he invites us to.
That's the sacrament.
Take this, my body,
and eat of it.
He invites us to the feast.
And it's a gift freely given.
And as long as we're willing
to open our hearts.
When I open my heart,
it just hurts.
That's right.
I think you know.
Something has to go out of you.
To make room
for the spirit to come in.
We get there by loss.
That's what spiritual hunger is.
And joy can follow, too,
if we let it.
Like we have to say goodbye
to the people we love,
the people we care about.
(gentle piano music playing)
I'm afraid so.
Hopefully not too soon.
But no one can ever
actually say goodbye, right?
(suspenseful music playing)
Benjamin: No.
(orchestral music playing)
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
(ominous music playing)
(operatic singing)
(gentle music playing)
(ominous music playing)