[upbeat music plays]
♪ Let's get it
Let's go ♪
♪ It's about that time
For me to shine ♪
♪ I got dreams
♪ I got goals
♪ And real soon
They're all gonna be mine ♪
♪ Fresh and dressed
Early in the mornin' ♪
♪ Glance in the mirror
And I'm feelin' the view ♪
♪ I got a big day
Big plans, big chance ♪
♪ It's time to take
Them big-boy steps ♪
♪ And advance
We got people to see ♪
♪ Things to do
Places to go ♪
♪ And somethin' to say
I hope you're listenin' ♪
♪ Let's get it
Let's go ♪
♪ It's about that time
For me to shine ♪
♪ I got dreams
I got goals ♪
♪ And real soon
They're all gonna be mine ♪
♪ See, I'm sweet on my feet
And I'm nice with my rhymes ♪
♪ I'm always on point
But I'm rarely on time ♪
♪ And today me and my crew
Got a date with fate ♪
♪ I stay fly
So I'm fashionably late ♪
♪ What's up?
♪ Let's get it
♪ Let's go
♪ It's about that time
For me to shine ♪
♪ I got dreams
♪ I got goals
♪ Real soon
♪ They're all gonna be mine
- Hawthorne Community
Church Choir,
led by Mrs. Angela Howell.
[applause]
- I want to let you know
I'm so proud of you all.
Just remember, be bold.
[mouths] Smile.
["This Little
Light of Mine" plays]
ALL: ♪ This little
light of mine ♪
♪ I'm gonna
♪ Let it shine
♪ This little light of mine
♪ I'm gonna
♪ Let it shine
♪ This little light of mine
ZACH: ♪ Ooh
ALL:
♪ I'm gonna let it shine
♪ Yeah
♪ Let it shine
♪ This little light
Of mine ♪
♪ Ooh
♪ I'm gonna let it shine
♪ I'm gonna
Let it shine ♪
♪ This little
Light of mine ♪
♪ This little light
Of mine ♪
♪ I'm gonna
Let it shine ♪
♪ This little light
Of mine ♪
- ♪ This little light
ALL: ♪ I'm gonna
Let it shine ♪
- ♪ I'm gonna let it shine
ALL: ♪ Let it shine
♪ Let it shine
- ♪ Let it shine
ALL: ♪ Let it shine
- ♪ Shine
♪ Yeah
- ♪ Let it shine
ALL: ♪ Let it shine
♪ Let it shine
- ♪ Shine
ALL: ♪ Let it shine
- ♪ Ooh, yeah
- ♪ Gonna let it shine
ALL: ♪ Let it shine
♪ Let it shine
- ♪ Gonna let it shine
ALL: ♪ Shine
♪ Shine,
Let it shine ♪
ZACH: ♪ Gonna let it
ALL: ♪ Shine, shine,
Let it ♪
♪ Shine
[applause]
- Truly lovely work.
And, uh, of course,
Crossroads Christian Choir
is here.
Thank you for coming.
[applause]
Now, we are just waiting
on the Bellevue Boys Choir.
They are supposed
to go on second.
So let's all just hang tight
for a few minutes.
[woman clears throat]
- [mouths] Bingo.
- Oh, um...
Well, uh, it seems we are
a bit pressed for time.
So let's get this show
on the road.
Now, I don't think I need
to remind you of the stakes.
The top two teams will earn
a spot in the upcoming
states competition
and the chance
to win the grand prize
of $10,000.
[applause]
All right, then.
Crossroads Christian Choir,
come on up.
[weakly] ♪ Come thou,
Fount of every blessing ♪
♪ Come thou, fount
Of every blessing ♪
♪ Come thou,
Fount of every blessing ♪
- ♪ Come thou, fount of
ALL: ♪ Come thou, fount
- ♪ Of every blessing
ALL: ♪ Every blessing
- ♪ Tune my heart to sing
ALL: ♪ Heart to sing
- ♪ Sing thy grace
ALL: ♪ My praise to sing
♪ Praise to sing
- ♪ Streams of mercy
♪ Streams of mercy
Streams of mercy ♪
- ♪ Never ceasing
ALL: ♪ Streams of mercy
- ♪ Call for songs of
ALL: ♪ Songs of loudest
- ♪ Loudest praise
♪ Of loudest praise
ALL: [flat] ♪ Teach me some
Melodious sonnet ♪
♪ Sung by flaming
Tongues above ♪
♪ Praise his name
I'm fixed upon it ♪
- ♪ Praise his name I'm
ALL: ♪ Praise his name
- ♪ Fixed upon it
ALL: ♪ I'm fixed upon it
[ cell phone rings]
♪ Praise the name
♪ Of God's redeeming love
♪ Praise his name
I'm fixed upon it ♪
- ♪ God's
ALL: ♪ Praise his name
- ♪ Redeeming
ALL: ♪ I'm fixed upon it
♪ Praise his name
I'm fixed upon it ♪
- ♪ Love
ALL: ♪ Praise his name
♪ Praise his name
- ♪ ...Name
[claps]
[inaudible conversation]
- All right.
I apologize
for the disruption,
but, uh, there's been
a bit of a mishap,
and, uh, I'm afraid
I have some unfortunate news.
The Bellevue Boys Choir
will be unable to make it today,
due to a food poisoning incident
involving egg salad.
- Ew.
- Nothing like this
has ever happened before,
and, uh, we're kind of
improvising here.
After conferring
with the judges,
we have a made a decision.
Both Hawthorne Choir
and Crossroads Choir
will move on to compete
in the states competition.
Congratulations.
- Oh, my gosh.
I can't believe this.
[chattering]
- Thank you all
for coming today.
Bye-bye.
- We made it, guys.
We finally made it.
- Good work, guys.
- Thank goodness for
egg salad, right?
[all chuckle]
- Yeah.
- This is whack.
- Yeah, all our hard work,
and those clowns
slide through to states.
- Don't get distracted.
States is in one month.
You still have work to do.
- It's gonna work out fine.
♪
- Hey, sweet win.
[chuckling]
- Oh?
- Bye.
- Can't believe
we just won.
- Won.
- We'll win.
- Hey, drop that beat.
Drop that beat.
- All right, all right.
Okay, here we go.
[beatboxing] Wha,
I rock-rock the beat.
[beatboxing]
- All right, go ahead.
- All right.
Manhole.
[laughs]
- Okay, okay, okay.
- Come on.
Come on.
- ♪ See me in the middle
Of the street ♪
♪ You would think
I was a manhole ♪
♪ I got the rhymes
People can't handle ♪
♪ Throwin' up words
Like a spray can vandal ♪
♪ I gets money
But I don't panhandle ♪
[laughs]
♪ Work hard, train hard
♪ Like commando
Soldier ♪
♪ I'm gonna be just like my pops
When I get older ♪
♪ But when is it over?
♪ Even though
I miss him a lot ♪
♪ I know it's
A mission he's got ♪
♪ So I'm gonna be brave
Just like him ♪
♪ Play it just right
And everybody listen and watch ♪
- Oh.
- Oh. That was good.
- That was tight.
- That was good. That was good.
- That was--
That was a good one.
- Okay. That was good.
- Yeah.
How is your pops?
- Uh, he's good. I just
got an e-mail from him.
Um, his tour's almost over.
You know, a couple weeks.
- Oh, cool.
- That's nice, man.
Yeah. Hey, Aundrea.
You wanna go?
- Tsk. Yeah...
- Let's see what you got.
Let's see what you got.
- Okay, okay.
Bring that beat back. Go.
- Okay.
[beatboxing]
- Hit me.
- All right, um...
Crossroads Choir.
- Good one.
- Yeah.
- Okay. All right.
All right. All right.
- Come on.
- ♪ Crossroads is lame
They gots no game ♪
♪ And they--
♪ Da-da-da-da-da
Da-da-da-da-da ♪
♪ Walk of shame
- Oh.
- Dis.
- Man.
[all laugh]
- That was...
That was whack.
- I worked all night
on that one. Come on.
ZACH: That was so good.
♪
ALL: Which we are
about to receive,
through Christ our Lord.
- And please bring Dad
back home soon and safely.
- Yes. Amen.
- Amen.
- Only two more weeks
until Dad's back, right?
- Yeah, sweetie.
That's it.
So--
- So guess--
- Go ahead. Go ahead.
What were you gonna say?
- Well, remember that choir
competition that I--?
- Oh, Zach, how was it?
How'd it go?
- Uh, it was fine.
We made it to states.
- Oh, Zach, that's amazing.
That's fantastic.
Oh, I forgot.
Oh, Zach,
I wish I could've
been there.
- Um, it's okay. You can--
You can go to states.
We'll have something
bigger then.
- Oh, okay.
Tell me more.
- Mm.
But what were
you gonna say?
- Well...
I have something
to tell you guys,
but I don't want you
to be nervous.
Everything's
gonna be all right.
Today, I found out
I lost my job.
♪
The hospital
made some cutbacks,
and a lot of people
lost their jobs,
and I just happened
to be one of those people.
- Uh, I'm sorry, Mom.
- Can you get a new job?
- Mm.
Yes,
of course I can.
But that takes time,
and there
just aren't
a lot of jobs
in this area.
- Uh, it's okay.
It's okay. Um, is there
anything we can do?
- Well...
actually there
is another thing.
We're gonna
have to move in
with your aunt
for the time being.
Just until we get
back on our feet.
- So...
we're moving?
- Yeah.
- So we have
to switch schools?
- Yes. And I've talked
to your Aunt Janet, and--
- Aunt Janet lives,
like, 45 minutes away.
- Okay, just listen.
I've talked to Aunt Janet,
and we've got you
set up in schools--
- Set up?
Wait. So you knew
this was gonna happen?
- Well, I had an idea
that my job was in jeopardy,
but I wasn't sure
that we'd have to move.
You know, it's really not
gonna be that bad.
- For you, maybe.
I mean, what about--?
What about my friends
and my choir?
- This isn't easy
for any of us, okay?
We will make it
through this.
- If Dad was here,
we wouldn't have to move.
- Now, that's not fair.
- [scoffs] Whatever.
- Zach.
♪
[car horn honks]
[beat plays]
[music gets faster]
[wind blows]
- Hey.
- You seem stressed.
Is it
more school stuff?
- Nah.
Just family stuff.
- Tell me.
Is everything all right?
- I'm moving.
- What are you
talking about?
- My mom lost her job,
and we have to move.
- When?
- Next week.
She already has me set up
in another school.
- [sighs]
I can't believe this.
I can't believe you're leaving.
Tsk.
But what about the group?
- I know.
- We were
just getting started.
I wanna feel for you,
but you can't
just leave like this.
- What do you
want me to do?
- I don't know.
We need you.
We're going to states.
- Well, I guess you're gonna
have to go without me.
["In My Shoes" playing]
- Oh, that's it.
- ♪ Hold up one minute
♪ Do you think
That I want it this way? ♪
♪ Gotta leave my friends
Ditch my plans ♪
♪ Pack and move away
♪ I thought that you
Would hold me down ♪
♪ I see now
It's all about you ♪
♪ Oh
- ♪ Wait
Wait a second, boy ♪
♪ You're not gonna
Turn this around on me ♪
♪ When you're the one
Skippin' town ♪
♪ Right before we finally
♪ Get the chance
To go to states ♪
♪ Guess that ain't
Important to you ♪
♪ Oh, boy
- ♪ If you really cared
♪ Then you wouldn't
Talk that way ♪
- ♪ And if you didn't
Wanna leave ♪
♪ Then you would
Try to stay ♪
- ♪ You can't understand
♪ What
I'm goin' through ♪
♪ Till you step
In my shoes ♪
- Well, congrats.
You're out the hood now.
And you're moving on up
to the East Side, right?
- What? It ain't
like that, believe me.
I gotta relocate, Dre.
You got it easy.
- I gotta pull it together
without you.
- Yeah, well, I gotta
take on somethin' brand new.
BOTH: ♪ You must be blind
If you can't see ♪
♪ The pressure this puts on me
- ♪ If you cared
You wouldn't walk away ♪
- ♪ And if you didn't
Want to leave ♪
♪ Then you would
Try to stay ♪
BOTH: ♪ You can't understand
♪ What I'm goin' through
♪ Till you step in my shoes
[birds chirping]
- [sighs]
[chattering]
GIRL: And we need to work.
- I think that we should have
some sort of, like, theme.
- Hello. And you are?
- I-I'm Zachary.
- Ah, yes.
The new student.
This is perfect.
We're assigning new pairs today.
Zachary, hang tight
for just a minute, okay?
Uh, boys and girls,
I need everyone's
undivided attention, please.
Eyes on me.
Today, we are starting
our desserts unit.
New partners time.
Now, uh--
Uh, Jason and Ryan,
I'd like you
at Station 1.
Robin and George,
Station 2.
Savannah and...
our new student,
Zachary, Station 3.
Sadie and Doug...
- Yeah, but I'm gonna be
a little late because
of the yearbook meeting.
- That's fine.
- Hi.
- Hey.
- I'm Savannah.
- Zachary.
- Now, open your recipe book
to page 51.
- Okay, so page 51--
- 51.
- Okay, it says half a cup
of vegetable shortening.
Half a cup.
Just--
Just drop it.
- Sorry.
- It's okay.
There you go.
- Thanks.
- Okay, next is two eggs.
Right there.
[gasps]
Wait, wait, wait.
N-no, no, no.
No.
- What?
- Well, when you crack it
like that,
you get the shell
in the batter.
So you just tap it...
- Oh.
and then it opens.
- Thanks, boss.
- What's that
supposed to mean?
- Um, nothing. I mean, you're
just really on top of things.
You know, like, uh...
student council,
yearbook, choir.
Eggs.
- Okay, well, if you think
you can do it better,
then you take over, boss.
- All right, um...
"a half cup
of sugar."
- I could do it.
- Uh, half cup.
- I know what a half cup is.
- Okay.
- Thanks.
What's next?
[school bell rings]
TEACHER: Zachary? Welcome.
Why don't you go ahead
and just take a seat
right over there, okay?
[students chattering]
- Hey.
I know you.
- Yeah, I know you too.
- What on GGE are you doing
in my Bible Study class?
- GG what?
- It's "God's green Earth."
TEACHER: Okay.
Settle down, now.
Good morning, everyone.
We have a new student
today: Zachary.
So everyone please
introduce yourselves to him
and make sure that you help him
whenever possible.
We're a little short
on textbooks still, Zachary,
so would anyone mind
sharing with him?
- Yeah. I will.
It's no problem.
- Thanks.
- Your homework was to read
"The Tower of Babel."
Now, what I'd
like you to do
is read the response questions
in your workbooks
so we can discuss them.
And those questions
begin on page...
- Uh, page 42.
- Thank you, Miles.
- Page 42 to 45.
♪
TEACHER: Yes.
[closes book]
- What?
- [whispers] I'm onto you.
- What are you
talking about?
- You think you can come in here
and spy on our choir?
Well...you're wrong.
- I just moved here.
And your choir isn't good.
- Right.
That's exactly
what a spy would say.
- Hey, come on, man.
TEACHER: Gentlemen?
I gather from your talking
that you're ready to discuss?
♪
- Aunt Janet.
Hey, Zach.
- Hey.
- How's it going?
How you liking it here?
- [exhales]
Um...
It's nice of you
to let us stay here,
but, um, school's just
kind of rough, you know?
- Yeah? Well...
is there
something you like?
I mean, is there
a choir you can join?
- Ugh. I would never
join their choir.
- Heh. Why not?
- Because they can't sing.
- Oh, come on.
They can't be that bad.
- Oh, they're--
They're that bad.
- Okay, well...
tell me something else.
How's your classes?
- Uh, most of them
are kind of boring.
Except Home Ec.
Home Ec's okay.
- Okay.
Well, that's something.
JANET: What's wrong?
- The military extended
your father's tour
for another six months.
♪
JANET: Come here.
It's gonna be all right.
[car horn honking]
["Cross that Bridge" playing]
♪ I've never been so scared
♪ I feel so unprepared
♪ This is so unexpected
♪ Who would have guessed it?
♪ I'm trying to understand
♪ This wasn't in the plans
♪ My life feels
So out of my hands ♪
♪ My feet are so heavy
♪ My heart isn't ready
♪ For what's on the other side
♪ But I'll cross that bridge
When I get there ♪
♪ I'll take
One step at a time for now ♪
♪ I hope this road
Leads me somewhere ♪
♪ That I can call home
Again ♪
♪ Just when everything
Started going my way ♪
♪ I get dealt a hand
That's too hard to play ♪
♪ Maybe things
Aren't as bad as they seem ♪
♪ I guess all I can do
Is just wait and see ♪
♪ But I'll cross that bridge
When I get there ♪
♪ I'll take
One step at a time for now ♪
♪ I hope this road
Leads me somewhere ♪
♪ That I can call home again
HOWELL: If you just
give me a couple of weeks.
Of course. Look,
I appreciate your point,
but $10,000
is a lot of money.
And this church--
Look, this church
means everything to me.
It is my mission
to make sure that
the funds are secure
to keep the doors open.
Look, I'm not prepared
to do that just yet.
I'm sure if you just
give me a couple of weeks.
Look, I'll come up
with something. Okay.
Thank you.
Bye-bye.
- Is everything
all right?
- Everything is fine.
- Is the church in trouble?
- No.
No, not as of yet.
But that's nothing
for you to worry about.
Okay? That's for me
to worry about.
Your job
is to put together
an amazing performance
for states.
- All right.
If you have a few minutes,
I wanted to go over
some ideas with you.
With Zachary gone, we have a
lot of figuring out to do, so--
- So you're gonna take the lead?
- Yep.
I guess I'll just have
to figure it out on my own.
- I think you'll
do a great job.
So let's hear
what you came up with.
♪
[knock on door,
door opens]
- Hey, Savannah Banana.
- Hey, Dad.
- What you working on?
- Just studying for
a biology test.
What you working on?
- I'm all done for the day.
I've got an early
Church Affairs meeting
in the morning,
so I gotta get up early.
You need
some help studying?
- Sure. If you wanna quiz me.
- I've love to.
- I just have to finish
this last one.
- Okay.
You are so busy, sweetie.
And now you're
choir leader too.
Do you have any problems
juggling all that?
- Not yet.
- You sure?
If you ever get overwhelmed,
you can do what
your mother used to do.
- What's that?
- She would simply put a
piece of bubblegum in her mouth,
and--and she would
blow a big bubble.
And she would say a little--
Little prayer
right before she did it.
She'd say, "Dear God...
make this bubble
take away my trouble."
And she would picture all--
All those worries
and all that stress
in that bubble.
And when it popped...
they were gone.
- I didn't know she did that.
- Yeah.
She did that.
Let's do these.
Are you ready, Savannah?
[clears throat]
Order of mitosis.
- Interphase, prophase,
metaphase...
telophase, anaphase?
- Mm-mm. Close.
Anaphase, telophase.
- [sighs]
I always mix those two up.
- That's all right.
You could try something
to help you remember.
For instance,
interphase starts with "I."
So I'd say "I."
Prophase, "P." "I played."
Metaphase, "marbles."
- Oh.
- "I played marbles."
- Okay.
- And you just keep
adding the words.
Interphase.
"I played--" Metaphase.
"My...accordion today."
Interphase, prophase,
metaphase,
anaphase, telophase.
"I played
my accordion today."
- See? It worked.
Great job, sweetie. Next.
Whoa. "Chromatid."
- Interphase. "I played
my accordion today.
I played my accordion today.
I played--"
- Whoa. Uh--
- S-sorry.
- You play the accordion?
- No, I just--You know,
I have--I have this--I--
- Heh!
- Forget it.
[chuckles]
[school bell rings]
♪
- Okay, so it says
to write the fortunes first.
- Oh.
I don't know
what to write.
TEACHER: Now, remember,
the first few you fold
might not look
like a fortune cookie.
They might resemble
something more like...
a geode.
- [mouths]
What's a geode?
Okay, so let's get started
with the cooking.
- Okay. Um...
two egg whites.
That's all you.
- On it.
- Remember,
no shell, please.
- Funny.
- Uh--
- Uh, no. Why?
- It's okay.
It's okay. Here.
- Zachary?
- Yes?
[giggles]
- I was, uh--You know,
I saw you at regionals, and...
I know you were doing choir
at your old school, and I--
I-I was just wondering,
if you're interested,
you might wanna join
our choir.
- I don't think so.
- Why not?
- If I'm gonna sing,
I'm gonna do it at Hawthorne.
- All right, well, let me know
if you change your mind.
- Okay. I will.
♪
- Settle right down, please.
Gentlemen. Hats.
Thank you.
All right. Who would like to be
the first to present today?
Miles. Of course.
- Yes.
The Last Supper was painted by
the brilliant Leonardo da Vinci.
It was created
for Duke Ludovico Sforza
and his duchess,
Beatrice d'Este.
It depicts
each apostle's reaction
when Jesus said one of them
would betray him.
They can be identified
by their reactions.
If you look at the picture
closely, you can see
this one on the far left
is clearly...
Unfortunately,
despite all efforts
to preserve this painting,
in 1517,
the painting tragically--
- Miles? That's all
we have time for today.
- Oh. But, Mrs. Stewart,
I was just getting started.
- I know. And you have gone
above and beyond as always.
Thank you.
Zachary, why don't
you present next?
- I don't have mine.
- You didn't
do the assignment?
- No.
- Zachary, I've had
to speak to you before
about not completing
assignments.
Detention with me
after class.
- Wait, Mrs. Stewart.
Isn't the first of the month
your department meeting
in the faculty lounge?
- Ah.
We could use help
cleaning the choir room.
Zachary could
do that instead.
- No, no, no. Um, I'll just
do detention tomorrow.
- No, Zachary,
that's perfect.
You'll report
to the choir after school.
♪
- Okay. You sing
the high part, then we get...
- [sighs]
- ...to the coda and go...
Oh. Hello, Zachary.
- All right, so what
needs to be cleaned?
- You can wash the board.
There's a, uh,
cleaning agent and a sponge
over there for you.
- Uh...
H-hello?
- Oh, that, heh--
That's Margaret there.
- What? Oh, gosh.
Sorry.
- Yes.
- Hi.
- It's good to go.
Let's give it a try.
Might... Wait.
I might wanna start,
um, here...
- Hm. Look who
decided to come.
- No, I--
MILES: No, no, no, no. Heh.
I've arranged,
uh, as a punishment--
- Mrs. Stewart sent me
here for detention.
- Um...okay, everyone.
Go ahead and grab a folder,
and stand over here.
Grab your folder.
- [exhaling]
- Miles?
States song?
- Right.
[piano plays
"Be Thou My Vision"]
ALL: ♪ Be thou my vision
♪ O Lord of my heart
♪ Naught be all else to me
♪ Save that thou art
♪ Thou art best, Lord
♪ By day or by night
♪ Waking or sleeping
♪ Thy presence, thy light
[all singing off-key]
- He-hey. Um...where do you
think you're going?
Board's clean, so...
- You don't wanna just stay,
you know?
Maybe help us out? Plea--?
- I don't think so.
You guys
need a miracle.
♪
[beeping]
AUNDREA: Hey, Zachary.
- Hey, Dre.
- Hey, I can't really
talk right now.
We're working on
our performance for states.
- No, that's cool.
GIRL: Aundrea, come on.
AUNDREA: Okay, okay.
I gotta go, Zach. Bye.
- Bye--
♪
TEACHER:  Lee las palabras.
Por último,
escribe la respuesta.
Sigue el modelo.
[upbeat Latin music plays]
♪ Father
♪ Whoa-oh-oh
♪ Thou shall believe
♪ Father
♪ Whoa-oh-oh
♪ Thou shall believe
- Stop, stop, stop.
I don't think
that's gonna work.
- Don't you think Zachary
could make that flow?
I mean, he'd be
able to tie it in.
- Zachary's not here.
It doesn't work
like that.
- Well, fine,
let's just move on.
- Yeah,
We have a lot of
ground to cover. From the top.
One, two, three,
and...
♪ Father
♪ Oh, I believe
♪ Whoa-oh-oh
♪ Father
♪ Yes, I believe
♪ Thou shall believe
♪ Father
ALL: [off-key]
♪ By day or by night
♪ Waking or sleeping
♪ Thy presence, thy light
[singing off-key]
- Okay, everyone.
Let's just take five minutes.
Just work on the last line.
- Okay.
[playing harmonica]
[plays "Amazing Grace"
- Hey.
- Are you coming in?
- Oh, no, no.
I was just chilling.
Um, I didn't know
you played.
- Oh, this? No, it's--
- No, no, no.
It's cool. You should use it.
- Really?
SAVANNAH: Hey.
- Hey.
- Zachary was
just saying
we could use
my harmonica.
- Oh, no--
No, I was just saying--
- You think
that could work?
- Well, I mean, if you guys
wanna try
something different.
- Uh, I think we know what
we're doing around here.
MARGARET: Um...
I don't think that's true.
- Yeah. Zachary,
what do you think
we should do?
- Nah. I mean, you guys
can do your own thing.
- No, no, no.
We want your help.
I mean, if you're
willing to help us.
- Well...with my old choir,
we used to
put our own spin on things.
- Like what?
- Um, like anything.
We just did
whatever we felt,
and then...
songs became ours.
Music isn't
something you learn.
It's something you feel.
- This seems very radical.
[All Over Me" playing]
- Listen to me, y'all.
You gotta do your own thing.
[chuckles]
'Cause that's the only way
people are gonna hear you.
You know what I'm saying?
Listen.
♪ I got a song way down
In my spirit ♪
♪ I gotta let it out
♪ It sounds so good, I want
The whole world to hear it ♪
♪ It makes me wanna shout
♪ Hip-hop, rock 'n' roll
Rhythm and blues ♪
♪ It's all the same
When the band plays ♪
♪ And whether black, white
Brown, green, purple or blue ♪
♪ We all are in it
For the same thing, uh ♪
♪ See, I can feel it all
In my hands ♪
♪ And I can feel it all
In my feet ♪
♪ See, I can't help myself
♪ 'Cause it's all over me
♪ Let me talk to you
For a minute ♪
♪ It's okay to have some fun
When you're singing ♪
♪ It's only natural
♪ Don't ever forget
That God is the reason ♪
♪ And sing it from your soul
Yeah ♪
♪ Just as long as the message
Doesn't change ♪
♪ We can still
Have a good time ♪
♪ The gift is special
Don't you be afraid ♪
♪ To go ahead
And let your light shine ♪
♪ See, I can feel it all
In my hands ♪
♪ And I can feel it all
In my feet, uh ♪
♪ I just can't help myself
♪ 'Cause it's all over me
♪ Charlie, play that thing
For me one time ♪
[playing harmonica]
♪ Miles, please play
Them keys ♪
[piano plays]
♪ Come on, Margaret
♪ Don't be afraid
To step out of your shell ♪
♪ And, Savannah
Let me hear you sing ♪
- ♪ Hey, ho-oh
- ♪ I think I need
A break ♪
[clapping]
♪ Everybody say
"I feel it" ♪
♪ I feel it
In my hands, y'all ♪
♪ I feel it in my feet
♪ Oh-whoa-whoa-whoa
♪ It's all over me
♪ Yeah, yeah-yeah-yeah-yeah
Yeah-yeah-yeah ♪
♪ It's all over me
[applause]
See? We had a little
something there, right?
- I know.
We actually sounded okay.
- Yeah.
- So...does this mean that
you're gonna join our choir?
- Um, I'm not sure.
- Well, why not?
- Uh, it's just...
I gotta think
about it, you know?
- Uh, excuse me. Heh.
We can't just invite people
to join willy-nilly.
Shouldn't we have some sort
of democratic process
to decide on these...changes?
- If Zachary decides he
wants to join our choir...
then I'd love to have him.
All in favor?
♪
- Okay, guys. Um,
we're done for the day.
So we'll just
pick it up tomorrow.
Cool? Cool.
Bye.
Sorry about before, Trev.
- Eh, that's cool.
We're all a bit stressed
about getting this together.
- You know, I think
we can pull it off.
We just--It's gonna take
a little bit of time--
ZACHARY: Hey, guys.
TREVOR: Nice seeing you, man.
- Hey, bro.
AUNDREA: What are
you doing here?
- I just came by
to see you guys.
- Oh.
TREVOR: Wait.
Coming at the end
of rehearsal?
We could've used you
in here, man.
- Actually, just came
from rehearsal too.
- What rehearsal?
- I'm--I'm kind of helping
the Crossroad kids
get their act together
for states.
- Wait. You're helping
those jokers?
- They're actually
not that bad.
I wanted to talk
to you guys about it.
- What are you talking about?
Are you really a part
of that choir now?
- I just tried
working with them once.
I just miss being
part of a group.
But, believe me,
I have my work cut out for me.
- You realize you joined
up with the competition?
- So you think
they're competition now?
- Well,
maybe now they are.
- [scoffs]
Well, you make me sound
like some kind
of traitor.
- You said it.
I didn't.
- It's not like that, Dre.
- I don't know, bro.
- Peace.
- Later, dude.
- Dre, wait up.
[sighs]
♪
[cell phone beeps]
- What's going on?
- It's Zachary.
He's gonna join the choir.
- [sighs]
This could really
be the downfall
of the Crossroads Choir.
- What are you
talking about?
- I-i--I-it's very risky
making such drastic changes
to our routine
at this point.
And I haven't even
ruled out the possibility
that he's a spy.
You're doing this all wrong.
Try it like this.
- Miles. We need
to work together.
- [groans]
This isn't choir, Savs.
You're not the boss.
I take that back.
You're not the boss
of choir either.
Huh. You--
You think you are,
but you're not.
So there.
- Miles, you need to stop
being so stubborn
all the time.
You know, some of
these changes could
actually be good for us.
- Oh. You think you got it
all figured out, huh?
"I'm Savannah. I'm perfect
and wonderful and amazing."
["You're Not the Boss"
playing]
- "I'm Miles.
I whine and complain
all day long."
- ♪ I'm the preacher's
Little girl ♪
♪ And my choir's
gonna sing ♪
- ♪ If I pound
The piano louder ♪
♪ Then they'll never hear
A thing ♪
- ♪ My conservative
Styling ♪
♪ Graces every key
BOTH: ♪ You might
Fool the others ♪
♪ But you can't fool me
♪ You're not the boss
- ♪ Who do you
Think you are? ♪
♪ You're not
The boss ♪
♪ A high school
Superstar ♪
BOTH: ♪ You're not the boss
♪ Not in your wildest dreams
♪ Oh, I'm no fool
♪ You're not the boss of me
- ♪ My classical grace
Makes us sound so sweet ♪
- ♪ We need more talent
If we want to compete ♪
- ♪ 'Cause I can crack an egg
And make a swell pie ♪
- ♪ He's got what
It takes ♪
♪ To be a decent guy
- ♪ He's not the boss
- ♪ I never said he was
- ♪ You're jealous
Just because ♪
♪ You're not the boss
- ♪ How can I make
You see? ♪
BOTH: ♪ Oh, it's our school
♪ You're not the boss of me
- ♪ Oh, if you wanna be inspired
Better kick out Zach ♪
- ♪ He's good for the choir
You better take it back ♪
- ♪ We're at
The crossroads ♪
♪ My way's good
And he's bad ♪
- ♪ Have I ever told you
♪ That you're cute
When you are mad? ♪
BOTH: ♪ You're not the boss
SAVANNAH: ♪ Who do you think
You are? ♪
BOTH: ♪ You're not the boss
MILES:
♪ A high school superstar
BOTH: ♪ You're not the boss
♪ You call that reality?
♪ Oh, in your dreams
♪ You're not the boss of me
- Zachary? See me
before you leave.
- Zachary. Oh.
Thank you so much
for all the time
you've put into the choir.
Your dedication
is truly a blessing.
- Uh...you're welcome?
- It, um--
It must be hard, though.
I mean,
lately you've been
so busy
with choir rehearsals,
you must not have
much time for, well,
anything else.
- Hm?
- See you at choir. Ciao.
- I wanna talk to you about
your work in this class.
I'm rooting for you.
But I really need to see you
take this seriously.
- I know, I know. I--
I need to work harder.
- You know, don't be
so nonchalant.
This is your education
we're talking about.
- Okay, Mrs. S. I will.
I'll try harder.
- I'm not through.
You've got
to take this seriously.
So unless you get a B
or better on the next test,
you will not be allowed
to participate in the choir.
- Are you serious?
- I'm sorry. It's the only way
I can think of
to get through to you.
You may go.
♪
- Zachary. Hi.
- Hey.
- How's it going?
- [sighs]
It's going.
- Is everything okay?
- [clears throat]
Yeah,
everything's good.
- Oh, okay.
Good.
♪
Dad!
- Coming!
What, sweetheart?
- Look.
- What?
- You shrunk
my favorite shirt.
- I'm sorry.
- I can't believe this.
- Well, I'm not
a laundry expert.
- Just forget it.
- I'm sorry, Savannah.
- Things like this
never happened before.
- Before your mom...?
- Never mind. Just leave.
- This has been very tough
on both of us.
And I'm sorry
I shrunk your shirt,
but I am doing the best
that I can--
- Dad. Get out of my room!
- You miss your mother.
I miss your mother.
I understand exactly
what you're going through
right now. The feelings--
- No, you don't understand.
She's my mom.
- Maybe I don't understand.
Why don't you talk
to me, Savannah?
Help me understand.
- Every time I wanna
tell her something, I can't.
It's not fair.
- Sometimes
we don't understand
why God gives us
the challenges that he does.
Don't turn away from me.
Savannah, look at me.
He has a plan for you...
and he has a plan for me.
- I don't believe that.
- Well, you are angry.
You are angry right now--
- Dad, I'm your daughter.
Stop preaching to me.
- Savannah, stop it.
- Dad, get out
of my room!
- Savannah--
- Dad, get out of my room!
[beat plays]
- Hey, what's going on?
- Oh, it's Peer
Tutoring Tuesday.
- Oh. Well, I better
get going then.
- No, come on.
Just come hang out.
- Yeah, right. Like I'm
gonna tutor somebody.
- Why not?
Or, you know,
you could just study
or something.
You know,
I could help you.
- No, I'm good.
- Zach...sit down.
- [sighs] Okay, okay.
So, what's next?
- Okay, this is gonna
have to be the last one,
'cause I gotta
get going.
Okay, so it's
Proverbs 27, verse 19.
Okay?
"As in water,
face answereth to face,
so the heart
of man to man."
- I don't know
the "answereth."
- Okay, let me
break it down for you.
Okay. So the first part:
"As in water,
face answereth to face."
See, when you look
into the water,
you'll see a reflection
of your face.
Right? And so,
take the second part
and explain to me
what it means.
- Wait, so...
they're both
about reflections?
When you know your heart,
then you can understand
someone else's.
- Right.
Uh, what does
that mean to you?
- Well, um...
that we're all the same,
deep down.
Um, even though
we may seem different.
- Exactly.
See? There's no way Mrs.
Stewart can keep you off choir--
Sorry.
You know, I just--
I overheard her talking to you.
- It's just
a little embarrassing. Uh--
I don't know if I'm gonna
pull it off, you know?
- Yeah, you will.
- Thanks for your help,
though.
- I wasn't helping you.
I was just, you know,
looking out for choir.
- Okay, okay. My bad.
[chuckles]
SAVANNAH:
Yeah, trust me. I know.
Miles can be
pretty ridiculous.
But...other than that,
are you starting to feel
more at home?
- I'm getting there.
It's just my Hawthorne crew's
being kind of tough
on me, you know,
and I just
didn't expect that.
But...I know
that God will only
put as much on my plate
as I can handle.
Just gotta keep praying
and stay positive.
- Yeah. I don't know.
Sometimes I think I have
a little too much on my plate.
- What do you mean?
[chuckles]
A tragedy in Savannahland
is, like, if choir,
student council
and yearbook
all fell
on the same day.
- That's not true at all.
What? You think you're
the only one that has it rough?
- Come on.
- You don't know
anything about me.
- Uh, I'm pretty sure
I have a good idea.
I know that you're
the pastor's daughter,
that you're top of the class,
you're in every club.
I mean, what's the worst
that could've happened?
- Actually, my mom died
a few months ago.
♪
- I'm sorry. I didn't--
- That's okay.
You didn't know.
- Uh--
I'm not sure if this
is saying much, but...
I know how it is
to miss a parent.
My dad's overseas
in the military,
and I don't know
when he's coming back.
But you gotta
stay positive, you know?
- You're right. You know,
I don't wanna think about my
mom and be sad. I want--
I want thinking about her
to make me happy.
- It's okay to be upset.
You'll feel better
when you're ready.
- Thanks for
being there for me.
- Got your back, girl.
[singing]
♪ Father
♪ Yes, I believe
♪ Whoa-oh-oh
♪ Father
♪ Oh, I believe
♪ Yes, I believe
[ claps]
BOY: That was it.
That was it.
HOWELL: Hello, everyone.
- That was it.
- Aundrea, you're doing such
a lovely job with the group.
And you all have come so far.
- Yeah.
- Sit down, y'all.
I need to talk to you.
- So, what's up,
Mrs. Howell?
- This is hard.
Okay. You all know
that it's been
a very rough year
for the church
and the community.
Despite all of
our fundraising efforts...
we've still fallen short.
We're out of ideas,
and we're out of money.
Hawthorne will be
closing its doors
at the end of the month.
- What?
- Hawthorne
can't shut down.
- We all grew up here.
HOWELL: I'm sorry.
- W-- Where else
will we go?
- There must be something
we could do.
- What if we win
the prize money at states?
ALL: Yeah.
- Yes, that would help
pull us through,
but we don't have money
to send you to states.
And that is too much pressure
to put on you.
- I know we can win
this competition.
Can't you figure
something out?
- Believe me, I've tried.
This is the last thing
that I wanted to do.
I'm sorry.
- Mrs. Howell...
this was our opportunity
to prove that we
could do something.
To prove that Hawthorne
Don't you see that?
- Look, I know it's hard.
Believe me. I understand.
But this is not about you.
This is about the church.
And there is
no other option.
Look, I know it's hard,
and things don't always
work out the way that--
Aundrea,
where are you going?
- I'm outta here.
♪
ZACH: ♪ Let's get it
Let's go ♪
♪ It's about that time
For me to shine ♪
♪ I got dreams
I got goals ♪
♪ And real soon
They're all gonna be mine ♪
♪ Fresh and dressed
Early in the morning ♪
♪ Glance in the mirror
And I'm feeling the view ♪
♪ I got a big day, big plans
Big chance ♪
♪ It's time to take them
Big boy steps and advance ♪
- Hey.
- Hey. How did
the test go?
[sighs]
- [sighs]
- Zachary, it's fine.
Don't even worry about it.
- Psych.
A-minus.
- [gasps]
Oh, my gosh.
[chuckles]
- I have to get to class.
- Me too.
- All right.
Remember, after school?
- Yep.
- Okay.
- See you later.
- Bye.
♪
- So this is where
you used to come?
- Yeah. It's, uh,
nice to have a place to go
where you can get away,
you know?
- [chuckles]
Choir's good.
- Um, yeah, it's great.
I mean,
everyone's really nice.
Or almost everyone.
But a few more rehearsals,
and we should be
in good shape.
- Crossroads
Choir rehearsal?
Sounds like fun.
- Dre, hey.
- Hawthorne Choir
rehearsal's going great.
Thanks for asking.
Oh, wait. We don't
have them anymore.
- What are you talking about?
- While you've been busy
with your new choir,
Hawthorne Church
is shutting down.
- Are you serious?
- Yeah.
No church,
no choir.
And we can't go
to states.
Guess you left
just in time.
- Drea, I don't
wanna fight with you.
- Oh, of course you don't.
Everything's perfect
for you now.
- What are you
talking about?
- New choir,
new friends.
A church
with money.
♪
Do your thing.
- Dre, don't be like that.
- Love and unity.
Let's all just take a moment
and reflect on those two words.
What do they mean?
We are all given
obstacles in our--
In our life, that test us.
And they make us question
ourselves, and...
sometimes the people
that we love.
But we are also
given an opportunity
to live the most fulfilling
and the most
righteous life possible.
♪
Well, Colossians 3
instructs us
to put on a heart
of compassion.
And beyond all things,
to put on love.
This is the perfect bond
of unity.
Today, I wanna talk to you
about this passage:
Colossians 3.
And how you can use
its words...
to make you better people
and help you live a better life.
Colossians 3 gives us some
very good guidelines for this.
Compassion and kindness...
humility and patience.
We should care for others,
despite our differences.
It cites unity...
as the ultimate goal.
Unity.
Love and unity among people.
This is the key to living up
to one's true potential.
Love and unity.
In this upcoming week...
I challenge each
and every one of you
here in this congregation
to strengthen the love
and the unity...
in your lives.
In closing
of this Sunday's service...
we have a very special
performance by our youth choir.
[Piano playing
"Be Thou My Vision"]
ALL: ♪ Be thou my vision
♪ O Lord of my heart
♪ Naught be all else to me
♪ Save that thou art
♪ Thou art best, Lord
♪ By day or by night
♪ Waking or sleeping
♪ Thy presence
Thy light ♪
♪ Riches, I heed not
♪ Nor man's empty praise
♪ Thou mine inheritance
♪ Now and always
♪ Thou and thou only
♪ First in my heart
♪ High king of heaven
♪ My treasure thou art
[indistinct chatter]
- God bless.
How are you?
[chatter]
And there she is.
- Thanks, Dad.
- For what?
- For your sermon.
- You're welcome.
I love you, sweetie.
- I love you too.
- And I'm very, very,
very proud of you.
- Dad. I gotta go
talk to the choir.
I'll be right back.
- Okay. Go ahead,
busy girl.
[chattering]
[Trevor beatboxing]
AUNDREA:
♪ Apple in my tree
♪ Go straight to me
♪ And then when I eat it
I get a-- ♪
[laughs]
I get a--
- All right, all right.
- I don't know!
[laughing]
- Just do beatbox.
- That was good.
- What is this?
- We wanted to talk to you
guys about an idea that we had.
- What is it?
And what are they doing here?
- We think it's awful that
you guys can't go to states.
Uh, you guys are
really talented.
We wanna help.
- We want you guys
to join our choir.
- Isn't that against
the rules or something?
- No. Margaret read
the entire rulebook.
It doesn't say anywhere
in there that we can't.
- Why would I ever
join your choir?
- Because you love to sing,
and nobody can sing like you.
And I know this church
means everything to you.
- Yeah.
This could be our only
chance to go to states.
- We don't need
your charity.
We know we're good.
We don't have anything to prove.
- But we need your help.
And you guys are good.
And we have a better chance
of winning the prize money.
We all want that
to go to Hawthorne.
- We've been working
really hard.
We're getting better.
- Okay. I'm in.
Let's do it.
Guys, what you think?
- Yep.
- Yeah, we'll do it.
- Aundrea?
- Fine. I--
I will admit that
your voice
would be an asset.
- I guess this is
the only option.
Hawthorne needs us.
I just wanna sing.
- So you'll do it?
- Yeah.
- I just wanna win.
- Well, me too.
[chattering]
- Try you
up there.
Hey, where's Zach?
SAVANNAH: Oh.
He's always a little late.
- I know.
- Oh, Aundrea.
You're gonna stand right here.
Okay, everyone.
We're gonna get started.
Let's begin
our choir rehearsal.
We're gonna begin
with some warm-ups.
Miles.
[playing scales]
ALL: ♪ La, la, la, la
La, la, la, la, la ♪
♪ La, la, la, la
[Miles hits higher note]
La, la, la, la, la ♪
[higher note]
♪ La, la, la, la
La, la, la, la, la ♪
- Aundrea, please?
- What?
- Ugh. Never mind.
[groans]
SAVANNAH: All right, guys,
let's just continue
with the "mi's."
Miles?
[playing scales]
♪ Mi, mi, mi, mi
Mi, mi, mi, mi, mi ♪
[Aundrea singing loudly]
[higher notes]
♪ Mi, mi, mi, mi
Mi, mi, mi, mi, mi ♪
[higher note]
♪ Mi, mi, mi, mi
Mi, mi, mi, mi, mi ♪
[higher note]
♪ Mi, mi, mi, mi
Mi, mi, mi, mi, mi ♪
- Aundrea,
you're too loud.
- Well, I can't hear
myself sing over his piano.
- And we have
to make up for her.
Girl, you're not
even singing.
- I'm shy?
- Yeah, but she
can sing, okay?
- Please.
- What's your problem?
We invited you here.
- And?
- And we can easily
un-invite you.
- Oh, I don't think so.
- This is not
what I expected.
- Hey, guys.
- Nice new friends
you have here.
- It's not gonna work
if you can't listen.
- Wh-what's wrong?
Okay, chill out.
Come on,
let's figure this out.
♪
- We are clearly
not welcome here.
I know this is hard,
but we have to make this work.
- [sighs]
- Okay, remember
when we first started out?
And you thought
you were all that
and I thought
I was all that,
and you told me
you didn't need me anymore?
- Yeah.
["Better With You" plays]
- And remember the first time
we sang together?
Like, really sang together?
- Yeah.
- ♪ I've got a mission
♪ That I can't complete
Without you ♪
♪ I've got a dream that
♪ I'll never reach
Without your help ♪
♪ I want this thing to work
♪ But I can't do it by myself
♪ Let's get focused
And look at the bigger picture ♪
♪ Let's be open
To the differences ♪
♪ That we may have
♪ It's difficult
At first ♪
♪ But I promise
It won't be that bad ♪
♪ I may be okay
On my own ♪
♪ But I know I'm so much
Better with you ♪
♪ I don't want to
Do this alone ♪
♪ 'Cause it just feels
So much better with you ♪
♪ I may be okay
On my own ♪
♪ But I know I'm so much
Better with you ♪
♪ I don't want to
Do this alone ♪
♪ 'Cause it just feels
So much better with you ♪
- ♪ Just like the waves
♪ Need the winds
To get to the shore ♪
- ♪ Together
- ♪ We can do the impossible
♪ And so
- ♪ So
ALL: ♪ Much more
♪ I may be okay on my own
♪ But I know
I'm so much better ♪
♪ With you
♪ I don't want
To do this alone ♪
♪ 'Cause it just feels
So much better ♪
♪ With you
♪ I may be okay on my own
♪ But I know
I'm so much better ♪
♪ With you
♪ I don't want
To do this alone ♪
♪ 'Cause it just feels
So much better ♪
♪ With you
[clapping]
BOY: Boom, boom, boom,
boom, boom, boom.
Boom, boom, boom, boom.
- Okay, okay,
okay, okay.
Try it like this.
Stomp, hit,
hit, hit, hit.
No boom-booms.
[laughs]
Just stomp, hit, hit,
hit, hit. Ready?
- Dinner will be ready
in 10, guys.
- Okay, watch this.
Stomp, boom, boom, ah, ah.
- Wow.
You're getting good, Jakey.
Hey, why don't
you go inside
and help Aunt Janet
set the table, okay?
- Yeah, sure.
- Okay.
[chuckling]
- So are you nervous
for tomorrow?
- Yeah, I mean, we haven't
had a lot of time to practice.
- You know, it's really
nice to see you working
so hard for something.
I'm really proud of you.
Mwah.
Dinner in 10, okay?
♪
- That really
bothers me.
[people chattering]
GIRL: Doesn't
help anything.
- All right, guys.
There's two more choirs,
and then we go on.
-Okay.
- Oh, no.
- What?
- C.O.T.G.Y.C.
ZACH: What?
- Church of the Gospel
Youth Choir.
They've won
the past three years.
- And they will never
let anybody forget it.
- I'm not worried.
Don't worry about it.
[applause]
- That's right,
big applause.
Let's hear it
for the 14th Street Choir.
And now presenting the Church
of the Gospel Youth Choir.
[applause]
["Praise" playing]
♪ In the morning I praise
♪ Praise
♪ In the evening I praise
♪ When I'm dreaming I praise
♪ When I'm walking I praise
♪ Praise
♪ When I'm talking I praise
♪ When I'm singing I praise
♪ When I'm feeling down
He will come around ♪
♪ I won't make a sound
♪ Praise
♪ Whoo!
♪ If you're feeling blue
Shadows over you ♪
♪ You know what to do
♪ Praise
♪ When I'm walking I praise
♪ When I'm talking I praise
♪ Praise
♪ When I'm singing I praise
[applause]
MAN: That's right,
big applause
for the Church
of the Gospel Youth Choir.
Next, Kingston Choir and
Hawthorne-Crossroads.
MAN: Hawthorne-Crossroads,
you're up in 10 minutes.
SAVANNAH: Guys, we gotta get
going in a few minutes.
[chattering]
♪
[inaudible dialogue]
[chatter gets louder]
- I'm gonna go check something
out, I'll be right back.
- Okay.
[sighs]
[door closes]
FATHER: "Make this bubble
take away my trouble."
♪
[people chattering]
[speaks indistinctly]
- Oh. There you are.
- Okay, we are
minutes away, people.
Let's get dressed.
Let's get ready.
Let's get started.
- Hey, I've been meaning
to give you this.
- What are you doing?
- It might be
kind of stale, so...
[chuckles]
"You will get a fortune
and then win
the states competition."
[laughs]
Oh, Zach.
- Well, are you
gonna try it?
- [laughing]
It's not that good.
MAN: Excuse me.
Excuse me.
I'm looking for whoever's
in charge of this choir.
- What seems
to be the problem?
- Miles, I got this.
- It's been brought
to my attention
this is a combination
of choirs.
- Yeah, the Crossroads
and Hawthorne,
we formed one choir.
- Well, I'm sorry.
I cannot allow
two choirs
to perform together.
It wouldn't be fair
to the other choirs.
- Wait, we worked so hard,
and it means so much
to all of us.
- I'm sorry.
- Uh, please don't do this.
- I-I really
do apologize.
- Guys--
- What just happened?
- I don't know. I--
[chattering]
- There's nothing I can do.
- Guys, it's okay.
- It's not okay. No, it's--
- Margaret, weren't you
the one that said
this wasn't
against the rules?
- There's no reason
to blame anyone.
- Hawthorne Church
needed that money.
- I'm so sorry, guys.
I mean, it's terrible,
but there's nothing
that we can do about it.
- Are you serious?
I can't believe you guys.
Why would we even
come this far
if you were just
gonna give up that easy?
- Yeah. Yeah,
she's absolutely right.
- Okay, okay, let's just
think for a second.
- Um...I might
have an idea.
- What is it?
- Now she talks.
- What we did here was
something really great.
We united two very
different groups of people,
and we made it work.
I think we
may have an argument.
- Okay. Okay.
Okay, yeah.
I'll get the others.
GIRL: I'll get
the others.
Okay, so here's what
we're gonna do.
♪
- Hey, thanks a lot, man.
- Excuse me, Mr. Jerome.
May we have a word with you?
- All right,
but just briefly.
We understand your concern
about fairness.
To quote
Zacharias 7:9.:
Administer
true justice.
Show mercy
and compassion.
That is what we have done
in working together.
And that in turn
is what we ask of you.
We don't want to disadvantage
or hurt any other group.
We just want the chance
to do something
that means
so much to all of us.
We want to perform.
[speaking indistinctly]
- Well, I just don't feel right
about letting you compete
against the other teams.
However, I also
don't like the idea
of you not having
the opportunity to perform.
Therefore...
you will not be eligible
for the prize
or the state title,
but you may go
out there and sing.
- We'll take it.
Right, guys?
MILES: Yeah. Definitely.
- Of course.
- This is our last choir
of the night.
Now, we have a little bit
of an unusual circumstance.
Because they've
joined together,
the Crossroads-Hawthorne
Choir performance
will not be eligible
for the competition.
But let's make them
feel welcome, shall we?
Here they are:
the Crossroads-Hawthorne Choir.
[applause]
- Okay, play C sharp.
[organ playing
"His Eye Is On The Sparrow"]
- ♪ Why should I feel
♪ Discouraged?
- ♪ Why should
the shadows come? ♪
- ♪ Why should my heart
Feel lonely ♪
♪ And long for heaven
And home? ♪
BOTH: ♪ When Jesus is
♪ My portion
♪ A constant friend is he
♪ His eye
♪ Is on
♪ The sparrow
- ♪ And I know
- ♪ Yes, I know
- ♪ I know
BOTH: ♪ He watches
♪ Over
BOTH: ♪ Me
- ♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah
[switches to up-tempo beat]
ALL: ♪ I sing
♪ Because
♪ I'm happy
♪ I sing
♪ Because
♪ I'm free
♪ For his eye
♪ Is on
♪ The sparrow
♪ And I know
♪ He watches
♪ Watches me
[applause]
♪ I sing
♪ Because
♪ I'm happy
♪ I sing
♪ Because
♪ I'm free
♪ For his eye
♪ Is on
♪ The sparrow
♪ And I know
♪ He watches
♪ I know
♪ Watches
- ♪ Me
ALL: ♪ Me
[applause, cheering]
[indistinct chatter]
- Excuse me.
Excuse me.
Hey.
- Ah, it's so good
to see you.
So, what are you doing here?
You okay?
- It's nothing.
I'm just glad to be here.
- Yeah.
- You were great.
- Thanks, Mom.
- So, what did you think?
- Incredible, man.
The whole group was.
- Uh. Unbelievable.
♪
- Well, the time has come
to announce the winner,
who will be taking home
a prize of $10,000.
[applause,
cheering]
For the fourth year
in a row,
Church of the Gospel
Youth Choir.
- One moment?
- Uh, certainly.
Uh, someone would like
to say a few words.
- We're very grateful
and honored
to be receiving
this award.
However, we feel that we
should give over the award
and the title
to the true winners today:
the Hawthorne-Crossroads
Choir.
[applause]
- Thank you, man.
- Good job.
[chatter]
- I'm sorry about before,
all right?
- There they are.
The Crossroads-Hawthorne Choir.
Thank you, everybody,
for coming.
We'll see you next year.
[chattering]
- Whoo!
- Good job.
MAN: Girl, we won!
- So...the church?
- This will do it.
This will do it.
[ chuckling]
[applause]
Thank you.
♪
["Better With You"
playing]
ZACH: ♪ I've got a mission that
I can't complete without you ♪
♪ I've got a dream
That I'll never reach ♪
♪ Without your help
♪ I want this thing to work
♪ But I can't do it
♪ By myself
♪ Let's get focused
And look at the bigger picture ♪
♪ Let's be open
To the differences ♪
♪ That we may have
♪ It's difficult at first
♪ But I promise
It won't be that bad ♪
♪ I may be okay on my own
♪ But I know I'm so much
Better with you ♪
♪ I don't want to
Do this alone ♪
♪ 'Cause it just feels
So much better with you ♪
♪ I may be okay on my own
♪ But I know I'm so much
Better with you ♪
♪ I don't want to
Do this alone ♪
♪ 'Cause it just feels
So much better with you ♪
AUNDREA: ♪ Just
Like the waves ♪
♪ Need the winds
To get to the shore ♪
♪ Together
♪ We can do
the impossible ♪
♪ And so
- ♪ So
ALL: ♪ Much more
♪ I may be okay on my own
♪ But I know
I'm so much better ♪
♪ With you
♪ I don't want
To do this alone ♪
♪ 'Cause it just feels
So much better ♪
♪ With you
♪ I may be okay on my own
♪ But I know
I'm so much better ♪
♪ With you
♪ I don't want
To do this alone ♪
♪ 'Cause it just feels
So much better ♪
♪ With you
[clapping]
["All Over Me"
playing]
ZACH: Listen to me, y'all.
You gotta do your own thing.
[chuckles]
'Cause that's the only way
people are gonna hear you.
You know what I'm saying?
Listen.
♪ I got a song way down
In my spirit ♪
♪ I gotta let it out
♪ It sounds so good, I want
The whole world to hear it ♪
♪ It makes me wanna shout
♪ Hip-hop, rock 'n' roll
Rhythm and blues ♪
♪ It's all the same
When the band plays ♪
♪ And whether black, white
Brown, green, purple or blue ♪
♪ We all are in it
For the same thing, uh ♪
♪ See, I can feel it all
In my hands ♪
♪ And I can feel it all
In my feet ♪
♪ See, I can't help myself
♪ 'Cause it's all over me
♪ Let me talk to you
For a minute ♪
♪ It's okay to have some fun
When you're singing ♪
♪ It's only natural
♪ Don't ever forget
That God is the reason ♪
♪ And sing it from your soul
Yeah ♪
♪ Just as long as the message
Doesn't change ♪
♪ We can still
Have a good time ♪
♪ The gift is special
Don't you be afraid ♪
♪ To go ahead
And let your light shine ♪
♪ See, I can feel it all
In my hands ♪
♪ And I can feel it all
In my feet, uh ♪
♪ I just can't help myself
♪ 'Cause it's all over me
♪ Charlie, play that thing
For me one time ♪
[playing harmonica]
♪ Miles, please play
Them keys ♪
[piano playing]
♪ Come on, Margaret
♪ Don't be afraid
To step out of your shell ♪
♪ And, Savannah
Let me hear you sing ♪
SAVANNAH:
♪ Hey, ho-oh
- ♪ I think I need a break
[clapping]
♪ Everybody say
"I feel it" ♪
♪ I feel it
In my hands, y'all ♪
♪ I feel it in my feet
♪ Oh-whoa-whoa-whoa
♪ It's all over me
♪ Yeah, yeah-yeah-yeah-yeah
Yeah-yeah-yeah ♪
♪ It's all over me
[applause]
BOY: Whoo! Oww!
["This Little Light of Mine"
playing]
CHOIR:
♪ This little light of mine
♪ I'm gonna let it shine
♪ This little light
of mine ♪
ZACH: ♪ Ooh
ALL:
♪ I'm gonna let it shine
ZACH: ♪ Yeah
ALL: ♪ Let it shine
♪ Let it shine
♪ This little light
Of mine ♪
ZACH: ♪ Ooh
ALL: ♪ I'm gonna let it shine
- ♪ I'm gonna
Let it shine ♪
- ♪ This little
Light of mine ♪
- ♪ This little light
Of mine ♪
- ♪ I'm gonna
Let it shine ♪
♪ This little light
Of mine ♪
- ♪ This little light
- ♪ I'm gonna
Let it shine ♪
- ♪ I'm gonna let it shine
- ♪ Let it shine
♪ Let it shine
AUNDREA: ♪ Shine
♪ Yeah
ZACH: ♪ Let it shine
ALL: ♪ Let it shine
♪ Let it shine...