[music]
[speaking russian]
[music playing]
Running red.
[gunshot]
You know your directives?
Yes.
Time to rock and roll.
Major Cheung, I trust
you had a pleasant trip.
Major.
MAJOR CHEUNG: The
nerve gas has been
enhanced to our specifications?
COLONEL DIAZ: That is correct.
The kill cycle
has been increased
three times its original state.
Mr. Mercier, you
realize that the ship
must leave by 0700 hours if
we are to avoid alerting NATO?
Yes, I do.
And there won't be
any problem, Major.
The ship will leave
right on time.
Colonel Diaz.
Yes, the vials
are being injected
and sealed as we speak.
[music playing]
Look out.
[gunshot]
Try me.
PATROL THREE (ON
RADIO): Patrol three.
Report, south
perimeter is secure.
COMMANDER (ON RADIO):
Copy that, patrol three.
[non-english speech]
[crashing]
[groaning]
One man with a radio
brings a hundred with guns.
Come on.
Let's go.
Hey, Maria you
look great today.
Mama?
Oh, sweetie, I told you
to go play in the back.
[groaning]
What's she doing here?
[speaking spanish],, my
husband got drunk again.
He was arrested last night.
I had to bring her here.
[gunshots]
Let's move.
Get down.
[gunshots]
Lock down the plant now.
And ready the helicopter.
[speaking spanish]
I believe you have a
security problem, Mr. Mercier.
I've got the best
guards money can buy.
Forgive me if I
appear skeptical.
The helicopter's
warming up right now.
[gunshots]
A Soviet, no?
You should suffer.
Yes.
[gunshots]
Mr. Mercier, I believe we
have more pressing issues.
[gunshots]
Come on, Major, the
helicopter's one floor down.
[gunshots]
Go, go, go, go, go!
Shit!
[gunshots]
Call the helicopter.
Tell them to land here, now.
But there's
nowhere for it to--
Just do it.
[gunshots]
You sons of bitch.
Come on!
You all right?
Yeah, they've got
us pinned down here.
[gunshots]
[non-english speech]
[explosion]
[shouting]
[gunshots]
Where's the
goddamn helicopter?
It's on its way.
[gunshots]
The glass is bulletproof.
Extreme deflection.
Cover me.
[gunshots]
Let's go.
ALEXI: You have the angle.
I got it.
[gunshots]
[music playing]
Hey!
Hey, come back!
Come back!
You fucking bastards!
[gunshots]
Where's Sergei?
We've got to leave
before the MIG arrives.
He probably didn't make it.
I'm not leaving
without my brother!
[groaning]
No.
Sergei.
It was Messier.
I was stupid.
I was looking at--
No, it wasn't your
fault, little brother.
Come, I'll take you home now.
I don't think so.
[music playing]
He's gone.
Come on.
Finish her.
She's just a child.
I don't care if she's
your own daughter.
No witnesses.
I gave you an order.
I said no.
All right.
The explosion will
probably get her anyway.
Go on.
Go.
No.
[gunshots]
It's done.
You killed a child.
I gave you an order.
Never disobey my order.
We must get moving.
COMMANDER (ON RADIO):
Rover one, all
homing devices are activated.
Weapons are free.
Repeat, weapons are free.
[explosion]
Too bad Mercier got away.
We did our job.
We stopped them.
It's over.
Yes, it's over.
[music playing]
Tired?
Relaxed, thanks to you.
You're welcome.
Found Amanda's slinky.
Ah, chilled the way I like it.
Hey, Dad.
I've been looking for this.
- Give me a kiss.
- OK.
Morning.
You kids have all
the fun, don't you?
Well, I wouldn't say that.
Hey, how about if we
have a barbecue tonight?
I'll go get some chicken.
Hamburgers, too.
There are too many hamburgers
in your life, young lady.
I have a budget
meeting tonight.
You guys know what
pot luck means, right?
I guess it's just you
and me tonight, kid.
Unless pot luck means
hamburgers, only you, Dad.
- Will you do me a favor?
- Yeah.
Will you go to the
cleaners and pick
up my cheerleading uniform?
Honey, I know
you're my biggest fan,
but let's not overdo it, OK?
It's for my reunion.
I have $100 riding on it.
Whoever can still fit in their
cheerleading uniform wins.
Good morning, everyone.
We do have a front
door, you know.
Well, yeah, but this is
where you keep the food.
You ready Amanda?
Thanks for dropping her off.
Hey, what are neighbors for?
Besides, it's my day off.
Yeah, how's your
new job going?
Very sexy new boss.
That's a little bit too much
information if you don't mind.
Where'd you get that jersey?
Oh, I went out with that
hockey player again last night.
How'd it go?
Can you say double overtime?
I know you're talking
about boys when you do that.
Oh, you're a smarty.
Come on, time for school.
Hi five, babe.
AMANDA: Love you.
- Love you, too.
Love you, honey.
That was my banana.
Dad, Mom never
picks me up this late.
GREG: Yeah, but--
AMANDA: No buts, Dad.
GREG: --Mom doesn't
have Monster Mashers.
No way.
Hey, Dad, thanks.
You're welcome.
Can we stop for a Coke?
Oh, honey, you know what
your mom says about that.
Fathers and daughters
need to have some secrets.
Deal.
[music playing]
I'll be right back.
They're here.
Can you get rid of them?
Oh, I can get rid of them.
Question is for how long.
They're resilient
little bastards.
You know, in your lean times,
a cockroach will eat one
of his own limbs to survive.
Now, would you do that?
I don't think so.
Great.
Oh, for God's sake sir,
please keep your voice down.
You're scaring
away my customers.
Now just get rid of them.
God I love the sound of
that crunch when you pulverize
one of those little fuckers.
Please, sir,
just do it quietly.
CLERK: Will that be all, sir?
Yes.
No, actually.
Do you carry Forbes
Magazine here?
Yes, you'll find
that right in the back.
[clatter]
Oh no.
The whole thing, yeah.
Whoa.
I'm all right.
You all right?
Leave me alone.
I'm on level four.
Full tank, dude.
This is a little bigger
job than I thought.
Please, quietly, sir.
I'm gonna have
to go out the van.
Get the big guns.
Let's go.
I am gonna make a
fortune on this job.
[tires squealing]
Amanda.
Call the police!
Whoa.
What the hell?
What the hell you think
you're doing, buddy?
Don't you know it's
a federal offense
messing with a bug buster?
You better pull this
van over right now.
They got my daughter.
Yeah!
Chop shop will give
us plenty for this baby.
THIEF: Yeah, it will.
[shouting]
There's a kid back here.
Shit!
THIEF: Pick it up, man.
It's the bug guy.
Now I got you.
You give up now, I'll tell
them to go easy on you.
That smarts.
All right, sir, you have
the right to remain silent.
Anything you say
can and will be used
against you in a court of law.
Now, do you understand
these rights
as I've explained them to you?
Shut up!
I got it.
[laughing]
[crashing]
Oh God.
Oh boy.
Won't let us by
your truck, huh?
Why don't you step out
of the car, tough guy?
Come on.
[screaming]
Amanda.
Are you okay?
Whoa, Dad, how did you?
Whoa, Dad.
Listen, honey, I don't want
mommy to get upset, so let's
just keep this between us, OK?
- OK.
- All right, come on let's go.
Come on.
Wait, Dad?
Yeah?
Did you get the Cokes?
[laughter]
GREG: OK, get in the car.
REPORTER (ON TV):
Unfortunately, the home
video footage was
unable to catch
the license number of the car.
Police are asking
anyone with information
about the unknown crime
fighter to call the crime
tipsters at 800-555-3698.
However, I do have with
me Mr. Wally Gorch,
a partial witness to
today's activities
here in this neighborhood.
Mr. Gorch, what can you tell us
about what happened here today?
WALLY: Well, Suzy.
I can call you Suzy?
Yeah, there must have
been nine or 10 of them.
Now, I fought them off as best
I could with the karate moves.
That's about when this
other fella shows up.
Now, he helps me mop
up the last couple.
And then I believe that's
when your video guy showed up.
You know, after I'd
already done my thing.
Hey, handsome.
Hi.
How was your day?
The usual.
Is Amanda in bed?
Yeah, she's out like a light.
Hey, why don't you take
a nice, hot shower.
And maybe I'll give
you a massage later.
Well, that sounds great,
but I've got to get some food.
Can I talk you out
of these clothes first?
Tell you what.
I'll compromise.
A turkey sandwich first and
the massage right after.
Turkey sandwich first.
Can I talk you out of it.
Lettuce and tomato
on white, please.
GREG: OK.
REPORTER (ON TV): Not everyone--
GREG: Come on, honey,
don't turn on the TV.
It's just the news.
REPORTER (ON TV):
City Councilman
Earl Chambers is
at the forefront
to stop the new sports arena.
We don't need a stadium
built on public lands.
What we need is more
housing, more police,
better schools, and more park.
You know, I agree
with Chambers.
If they're gonna
get rid of the park,
they should at least sell
it for a lot of money.
REPORTER (ON TV):
Police are still
unable to identify the
mysterious stranger
who beat up the two hoodlums.
Now, I know it's blurry,
Fred, but can you run
that videotape again, please?
Your sandwich is done.
Oh, that's service.
Hey, check it out.
This guy's pulling the
kung fu on these guys.
[screaming]
Hey, Greg, that
guy looks like you.
Lucky guy.
That's our car.
Sandwich?
Why didn't you call the police?
Why didn't you call me?
Maybe I should have
called you, but Amanda's OK.
We don't need a bunch of police
reporters descending on us.
What do you think I was gonna
do, run down to channel nine?
Look, honey, these guys
might have been in a gang.
I mean, you read the newspapers.
The less said, the better.
Amanda's all right, that's
really all that matters.
You had no right
keeping this to yourself.
I deserve to know.
I am her mother, in case
you haven't noticed.
I'm sorry.
I was just trying to spare you.
I was wrong.
Where'd you learn
all that stuff anyway?
In the army.
I thought you said
you were a cook.
I was.
But with my cooking, you had to
learn how to defend yourself.
That's not funny.
Well, it was a little funny.
I'm serious, Greg.
I was really scared.
I'm never gonna let anything
happen to you or Amanda.
Come here.
REPORTER (ON RADIO): If
you're thinking of getting
on the 405 south, don't.
And if you're already
sitting in it--
How does one person go through
18 pairs of socks in one week?
I'm sorry, did
you say something?
REPORTER (ON RADIO):
Thanks, Bill.
Police are still looking
for the vigilante who
made short work yesterday
of a couple of car thieves
in the Valley.
Witnesses gave
differing descriptions.
Enough of that.
Thank you.
[phone ringing]
Hello?
STRELKIN (ON PHONE):
Your tickets are ready.
I'm sorry.
I think you have
the wrong number.
Moscow Circus is in town.
Perhaps you've
forgotten, Mr. Wallace.
[phone ringing]
Mr. Wallace, you have to
pay for your reservations.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Remember what I
told you, Gregori.
Never disobey an order.
Hilton lobby.
One hour.
Be there.
I left the service
11 years ago.
ALEXI: You never
leave the service.
So you are determined
to use Gregori?
I can't do it.
You certainly can't do it.
Want to keep this operation
as subtle as possible.
The less people who know
about our history, the better.
Besides, he's the best.
Mercier and Diaz,
they meet this week.
Relax, comrade.
I'll make him an
offer he can't refuse.
You just keep an
eye on Chambers.
People are starting
to listen to him.
Don't worry, I'll
take care of it.
[knocking]
VALET: Sir?
Thanks.
[chattering]
Gregori, it's good to see you.
Sit, please.
[speaking russian]
I'm an American now,
and I speak only English.
I've missed you, Gregori.
I'm sorry.
Greg.
How did you find me?
Was it that-- that
little piece on the TV?
Yes, I saw you, but we
always knew where you were.
Excuse me, sir, can
I offer you a drink?
GREG: No, thank you.
Thank you.
I'm in real estate now.
It's tough for some,
but Americans, they're
soft like Tootsie Rolls.
We Soviets, we
thrive on hardship.
The Soviet Union is gone.
Yes, but the
loyalties still remain.
You forget, I brought you here.
If not for me, you
would be rotting
in some Ukrainian prison, along
with all those other fools
who stayed behind.
You knew that the payback
would have to come on day.
Well, that day is here.
What is it you want?
I have a problem.
I am being threatened
with exposure.
As you say, you
have a problem.
If I have a problem, Gregori
Ilyanov, you have a problem.
We did some terrible things, no?
Does your wife know
about your previous life?
No, of course not.
What do you think she
would say if she knew
that you were a trained killer?
If we are revealed
everything changes.
You know, in some ways, you
have more to lose than I do.
You made a beautiful
family here.
I envy you.
Why ruin it?
If you cooperate,
I promise you I
will call my friends in Moscow.
They will erase
your combat file.
The Gregory Ilyanov I
know will cease to exist.
What exactly do
you want me to do?
Cheer up.
There is something
in it for you too.
I think you remember this man.
You should.
He killed your brother.
[music playing]
[laughter]
Excuse me, sir,
you forgot your key.
What?
Your key.
Gregori.
I thought I
recognized your voice.
Follow me.
Come here.
Strelkin has already done
the prep work for you.
He's still my aide.
I'm here only for Mercier.
Sit down, please.
Give him the file.
This is the current
information on Mercier.
And this one is for Diaz.
Mercier's stooge?
He moved up in this world.
He now handles all
Mercier's arms deals.
What about Mercier?
Moved into drugs.
Mercier has a criminal
indictment pending.
He's looking to make a deal.
He's trying to peddle
information on me.
What exactly do you
want me to do about it?
What you do so well, kill him.
That's not me anymore.
I've got a family now.
I haven't held a
gun in 11 years.
ALEXI: But you have the skill.
Remember, we saw
you a few days ago.
I only did that because
my daughter was in danger.
Get him to do it.
Look at his hand.
I can still kill,
if I'm close enough.
We're handing Mercier to
you on a silver platter.
When?
The two of you will
travel to Detroit tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
I have plans with
my wife tomorrow.
She can go to the
reunion by herself.
We do our homework.
And since we are
all capitalists here,
there's $50,000 in it for you.
No strings attached.
You can keep your money.
All I want is your word of honor
that this will be the only hit.
You have my word.
Hey, you look great.
Why do you have
a suitcase packed?
Because I have to go
to Detroit this weekend.
You've got to be joking.
What about my reunion?
I know.
I'm sorry.
They didn't give me any notice.
There's some kind of a problem
with the McKendry account.
I thought you were off
the McKendry account?
I was.
But some problems with the
stock options not going through.
If I don't go this weekend,
we're gonna lose the account.
So when were you planning
on telling me all of this?
After Amanda went
to bed tonight.
Greg, I'm not mad.
I know it's not your fault.
I'm just disappointed.
You know how long I've been
looking forward to this.
I wanted to show you off
to all my old friends.
I'm really sorry, honey.
Look, you just give
me this weekend,
and I promise I'll
make it up to you.
Wow, look at that
pretty picture.
It's gonna be a
mommy killer whale.
Really?
Should've known.
Hey, I just saw Greg
leaving with a suitcase.
Where is he going?
Detroit.
Honey, what
about your reunion?
Let me guess, business trip?
Mhm.
Yeah.
Remember Bill, my
first ex-husband?
He used to go on a
lot of business trips.
One day he came home, I
checked his briefcase.
Guess what?
Completely empty.
Not Greg.
No, not Greg.
He's one of the best.
I'm just once bitten, twice shy.
Shy?
Not exactly.
Hey, you got any coffee?
[music playing]
Diaz has the guns now.
Mercier has raised
his usual price,
but they think the
deal with Cubans
will go down tonight anyway.
Where's Mercier?
No sign of him yet,
but he'll be there.
He doesn't trust Diaz that much.
It's just a few guards.
Diaz has gotten lazy.
Living in America
does that to you, huh?
But don't you worry, there will
be plenty of security tonight.
Precision hit.
Limited access.
It's not gonna be easy.
You'll have to get close.
Hi, honey, it's me.
I didn't want to bother
you at the office.
I just wanted to tell
you that I'm sorry.
And if there was any way I could
have been there for you today,
I would've.
My appointments here.
I'll call you from the airport.
Love you.
You got it?
STRELKIN: Six shot .38, custom
silencer, and three clips.
Black Talons.
GREG: I asked for a Beretta.
That's Alexi's choice.
Then let Alexi do it.
Next time I ask for something,
you deliver exactly that,
or I take the next plane home.
Are you forgetting something?
You work for us.
You do as we say.
[phone ringing]
Yes?
I'll be there.
Diaz has arrived.
And Merc may be in town already.
I'll be back in an hour.
This is not over.
[music playing]
Cold out here tonight.
Here they come.
Cubans are here.
Okay, gentlemen, time
to make some money.
Keep your eyes open.
I don't trust these guys.
[music playing]
[speaking spanish]
I trust that you
brought the money.
In bearer bonds,
as you requested.
Where's your boss, Mercier?
He got stuck in L.A.
[speaking spanish] Business.
But when you deal with
me, you deal with him.
I don't deal with
flunkies, all right?
You get your goddamn
boss down here
right now before I get angry.
I'm just kidding.
Hey, just relax guys.
Relax.
I always wanted to
say that, you know?
Just like on the television.
Messier isn't here.
Only Diaz.
Where are the guns?
Send them.
CUSTOMER: What the
hell is this, huh?
Going on a field trip?
To the zoo, maybe?
Cops check trucks.
Not buses.
STRELKIN: Gregori, do Diaz now.
I'm here only for Mercier.
So he couldn't make it.
Kill Diaz.
You're a smart guy, Diaz.
Gonna send you guys
some Cuban cigars.
They're illegal here, you know.
Makes them taste
better don't you think?
State of the art.
This is bullshit.
Mercier's supposed to be here.
Well, he isn't Do it.
DIAZ: 30 cases,
ready for shipment.
Our deal was for 40 cases.
Yes, but customs is
cracking down on us right now.
When we say 40 cases,
we mean 40 cases.
STRELKIN: Gregori, you have
to [inaudible] him, damn it.
This time, I am not joking.
Set up!
[gunshots]
Save him!
[camera clicking]
[honking]
Sorry.
Slower cars move to the right!
Wanna play with the big boys?
Come on.
[shouting]
[bell chiming]
Shit.
[music playing]
[laughter]
[steam whistle blowing]
[screaming]
[crashing]
[glass shattering]
Nice driving.
You cut it close.
Too close.
Come on, go, go!
You're home early.
My lunch meeting canceled.
Maybe we can get
Stephanie to babysit Amanda.
We could go to
dinner tonight, huh?
So you were gone when
I got up this morning.
I had an early conference
with John and Tracy.
AMANDA: Daddy.
Daddy, come see.
I'll be right back.
OK, let's see.
All right, that was good.
She's fine.
She really loves her new toys.
So how did the reunion go?
I didn't go.
Why not?
Because I didn't
want to go without you.
[phone ringing]
I'm sorry, honey.
I know how much it meant to you.
Hello?
It's for you.
Hello.
ALEXI (ON PHONE):
Congratulations, Diaz is dead.
A little messier than
I would have liked,
but you can't make an omelet
without breaking some eggs.
Look, you got what you wanted.
I'm done.
ALEXI (ON PHONE):
Not yet, Gregori.
Mercier still breathes.
I don't care.
I want out.
ALEXI (ON PHONE): That
is not our arrangement.
Be at the hotel in one
hour, and don't be late.
I did the job in Detroit.
Diaz is dead.
The fact that Mercier wasn't
there is not my fault.
May not be your fault,
but it is your problem.
What do you think the
media would do if they
found those photographs?
Why should Mercier
have all the fun?
Drugs, women, you name it.
While your life
is falling apart,
and your brother, Sergei, is
rotting in a Spanish grave
unavenged.
You gave me your word.
Doesn't that mean
anything to you anymore?
Not since I moved
to L.A. Now, it
so happens that
Mercier has developed
an unhealthy heroin habit.
He's having a party this
afternoon to which you, posing
as a drug dealer, will attend.
One of his party girls
will be waiting for you.
She will get you into the party,
This afternoon?
Yeah.
All right.
[music playing]
Katherine?
Honey?
Amanda?
Katherine?
Honey?
Damn it.
Katherine!
What?
Didn't you hear me?
What the hell have
you been doing?
Gardening.
What's it look like?
The front door is open,
and the window is broken.
What is going on?
I locked myself out.
I had to break the window
to get in the house.
Then I left the
door open, sorry.
Where's Amanda?
Greg, it's Tuesday.
She's at dance class.
Right.
OK, that's it.
What's it?
I'm under a lot of
pressure at work right now.
I want you to take Amanda and
go stay at Stephanie's dad's
cabin in Arrowhead for a while.
Will you do that?
What are you talking about?
We're not going anywhere.
Do me a favor, will you?
Listen to me, just this once.
No, would you do me a favor?
If you want to clear us out
to turn our home into a love
nest with another
woman, don't give me
some lame ass excuse
about work and pressure
and all that garbage.
Another woman.
What are you talking about?
I know why you
went to Detroit.
Oh you do, do you?
But if you're gonna
ruin what we have,
I wish you'd at least have guts
enough to do it to my face.
OK, I will.
I have kept some
things from you.
I was in the army.
What does that
have to do with it?
It wasn't the American army.
It was the Russian army.
What?
There are some
men from my past.
They want me to do
something for them.
If they don't get what they
want, they might hurt you.
They might even hurt Amanda.
The police can't stop them.
There's really only
one thing that can.
If there was ever a time
I needed you to believe
in me, honey, it's now.
I trust you, Greg.
But if anything happens
to our daughter--
I'm not gonna let anything
happen to either one of you.
Now, please, go pack your bags.
I'll call Stephanie.
I'll have her pick
you up after work.
OK, but you have
a lot of explaining
to do when you get back.
[music playing]
STRELKIN: Leave the
money to [inaudible] when
she introduces you to Mercier.
What about the weapon?
I'm sure there will be
plenty of metal detectors.
You are the weapon.
Meet Fawn, old friend of mine.
Hi, I'm Nick.
Nice to meet you, Nick.
Fawn is a regular
at Mercier's parties.
You will go in as
a her new supplier.
So I get you in, and
then I get the money.
That's all I have to do, right?
That's all.
You like partying, Nick?
I'm married, thanks.
Who isn't?
Hey, Frankie.
Adam.
Did you miss me?
GREG: So are these
all Mercier's friends?
Guys like Mercier
don't have friends.
They have associates.
You either have something
that he wants to buy,
or you want to buy
something he's got to sell.
And where do you
fit in on that plan?
Don't judge me, Nick.
I've got something
all men want to buy.
I get you into this party,
you give me the money.
We're associates.
Fair enough.
Showtime, Nick.
Hey, Johnny, how's it hanging?
Well, I got you in,
so where's my money?
Where's Mercier?
Look, he's around someplace.
He's always around.
Yeah, well I need
an introduction.
You see, there you go
changing our relationship, Nick.
We had a deal.
No, your deal
was with Strelkin.
No Mercier, no money.
Well, then maybe we
should look upstairs.
Good choice.
Well, he should
be here somewhere.
Hey, how you doing, Fawn?
Hey.
Who's your friend?
Oh, this is Nick.
You better be nice to him.
He's one of Colonel
Diaz's friends.
This is Dominic,
Mercier's associate.
I want a drink.
Make yourself useful, huh?
Sure.
So you're a friend
of Colonel Diaz, huh?
That's right.
How come I've never
seen you with him?
Well, I like to
keep a low profile.
Diaz does too.
About six feet low.
Well, Mercier
won't mind if I take
care of deliveries from now on.
We'll see Come with me.
So where's the boss?
He'll want a sample.
Show me the money.
You know who the hell
you're dealing with?
You better be a hell of
a lot faster than you look.
[shouting]
Dominic.
That's enough, Dominic.
Take a hike.
Later.
I hear you got
some private stock.
It's expensive.
I think I can afford it
Pure heroin.
None better.
MERCIER: Pure heroin.
Pure horse shit.
What are you trying to pull?
I don't understand.
My brother, he said
it was the real stuff.
You brother?
Well, screw your brother.
You already
screwed my brother.
You don't remember him?
Spain?
The nerve gas shipment?
Remember, everything went
bad at the last minute?
What are you crazy?
I-- I don't know your brother.
GREG: Now you remember him?
You blew his knees out
just before he died.
[moaning]
[screaming]
Let's get him.
Kill that son of a bitch.
Now I'll never get my money.
[gunshots]
Come on, we need to find him.
Let's go!
[music playing]
There he is.
He got away, you idiot.
Down to the water.
Heading into the park.
Let's split up.
- Anything?
- Nothing yet.
Well, keep looking.
[music playing]
HENCHMAN: Hold him up.
Freeze, asshole.
I don't now who the
hell you think you are.
You think you can come
in to our party, huh?
Screw with me, kill
my boss, then what?
Run over here and
play in the park?
Well, screw you, asshole.
Hurry, police are on the way.
[music playing]
Where are they?
Your family is fine.
I could kill you now
and then find Strelkin.
You know me better than that.
If you hurt me, they will die.
That's better.
[speaking russian]
If you hurt them in any way--
Gregori, to hurt them now
would be not only stupid,
but it would be un-American.
I have one more task for you.
One measly little task for you.
We don't need a stadium
built on public lands.
What we need is more housing,
better schools, and more parks.
Chambers will be in
Clarion Park tomorrow at noon
before the rally to prepare
for his media circus.
It's 200 yards.
It's difficult. But
for you, piece of cake.
You know, I love that
American vernacular.
Chambers is not a drug dealer.
You don't have
any past with him.
Did I say I did?
This is not about
exposure, is it?
This is about the state.
Welcome to reality, Gregori.
I now own the lion's share of
a professional football team.
We need a stadium
for them to play in.
It's as simple as that.
Mercier never, ever threatened
you with exposure then, did he?
No.
You were a gunrunner with him.
That's how you made the money to
pay for the stadium, isn't it?
That's why you wanted him
killed, just in case somebody
like Chambers might
look into your past.
That's good, Greg.
Good.
You do not succeed in
this country in business
unless you step on some toes.
Oh, don't look so shocked.
That's what I'm doing.
I'm living the American dream.
I don't think too many CEOs
have murder on their resume.
I have sunk $10 million
dollars into that stadium.
Into that team.
I think that's very
American, don't you?
Now you think I'm
going to see that all
lost because of some
loudmouth politician who's
looking for votes?
No, I don't think so.
And you are going to ensure
that that does not happen.
KATHERINE (ON PHONE):
Honey, we're OK so far,
but please do what he says.
AMANDA (ON PHONE):
Daddy, help us.
I'm so scared.
One condition.
I'm listening.
I see my family
before I do the hit.
You'll see them.
And the moment I do
it, you release them.
Agreed?
Why not?
Strelkin will be
waiting for you at four
this afternoon in the park.
Don't keep him waiting.
Go get some rest.
What's our position?
Brownfield Plaza Hotel.
Our cover, elevator repairmen.
Security is a joke there.
Virtually doesn't exist.
What am I using?
Remington with Leupold scope.
Subsonic ammunition.
Personally, the radio bomb
would have done it for me.
And kill maybe 100 innocent
people instead of one?
What's the difference?
GREG: This thing is too rushed.
I don't like it.
There's going to be mistakes.
STRELKIN: It's going to be fine.
GREG: Is that what
you told my family?
STRELKIN: It's only 200 yards.
I saw you do a mile.
GREG: Not like this.
I had more time.
STRELKIN: His car will arrive
two hours before the rally
at approximately 1100 hours.
He'll go to the stage to
check the preparations.
The best shot will be before
he reaches the podium.
That's my department.
What happens afterwards?
A car will be waiting for us.
Then what?
That's my department.
All right.
It's gonna be okay honey.
Mom, where's Stephanie?
She's in heaven.
I'm so scared.
It's gonna be OK.
Daddy's gonna help us.
[music playing]
Little wind.
Low humidity.
Conditions are good, Gregori.
Where's my family?
Nearby.
Base?
ALEXI (ON RADIO): Copy.
Condition red.
ALEXI (ON RADIO):
Understood, vanguard.
Running red.
So in 10 minutes your problems
will be over, unless you miss.
For our good and the
betterment of all our families.
Isn't that laying it
on a little thick?
So far you've been
getting great press
on the nightly news.
People are looking
for anything to take
the blame for their
problems, television,
guns, movies, sports stadiums.
It'll get you votes.
OK, I'll say it.
ALEXI (ON RADIO): Three
minutes, vanguard.
I want to see my family.
Base.
ALEXI (ON RADIO): Copy.
Daddy wants to say hi.
ALEXI (ON RADIO): Put him on.
Where are they?
ALEXI (ON RADIO): Safe.
All right, no
more messing around.
I see my family now
or I walk, Alexi.
ALEXI (ON RADIO): Fair enough.
The side of the building.
Look down.
You'll see a blue van.
What about Amanda?
Dad.
Amanda are you all right?
AMANDA (ON RADIO): I guess so.
Mom says we'll be all right.
And they will be, too, as
long as you follow instructions.
I want to see her now.
No, no, no, I do not show
you both at the same time.
I need to protect myself.
AMANDA: Mommy.
Here, come here.
Are you OK?
I'm fine.
Daddy's up there.
Hello, good to see you.
Thank you for being here.
Thank you so much.
It's a pleasure.
Good to see you.
Hello, how are you?
This is never gonna happen.
Here he is.
Not a worry in the world.
CHAMBERS: Oh, thank you.
Thank you for coming.
- Go get them.
Thank you for
being here, buddy.
Can't do it without
you, you know that.
Good morning, everybody.
Hello, it's great
to see you all.
What are you waiting for?
CHAMBERS: Good
morning, everybody.
Joey, oh, so glad you're here.
Hi.
Great job, everybody.
You're waiting too long.
Shut up.
Wonderful job, everybody.
Thank you for all being here.
We're gonna have a great
rally this morning.
Shoot, damn you, shoot!
[speaking russian]
[gunshot]
Stop the land grab.
More parks.
[gunshots]
What's going on?
Think I heard shots.
[gunshots]
[screaming]
[gunshot]
Yeah, watch his head.
Let's go.
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
ALEXI: Come on, move it.
AMANDA: No.
ALEXI: Now.
AMANDA: Mommy.
KATHERINE: Amanda.
ALEXI: Let's go.
Amanda!
ALEXI: Help!
Help us!
Get out of the car.
[horn honking]
Katherine!
KATHERINE: Greg!
GREG: Are you all right?
They took Amanda.
Go, get her.
ALEXI: Get in now.
GREG: Amanda!
Hey!
Back up, now.
Get down.
Whoa!
I said down.
[horn honking]
[screaming]
Come on.
Come on, hurry, hurry.
AMANDA: No, let me go.
Stop it.
Come on, get in here.
[screaming]
Is there another
way out of here?
Yes, through the kitchen.
Get out of the way.
[gunshot]
What the hell is going on?
[music playing]
[gunshot]
AMANDA: Daddy!
Amanda, are you all right?
There's no way out, Alexi.
Let my daughter go.
I have nothing to lose now.
Now, you back off.
You leave.
You get away.
Then I let her go.
You're not leaving
here with my daughter.
AMANDA: Daddy!
Daddy!
Son of a bitch!
But that was just a warning.
I'll kill her if I have to.
You know I will.
I see what you're
doing, Gregori.
It won't work.
You don't have the
right angle from there.
You need a rifle, not a pistol.
Now, put the weapon down.
Suppose while you
think about it,
I put my hand over
her nose and mouth.
Would that help to
speed up the process?
[gunshot]
Daddy.
Are you OK?
Yeah.
All right, stay
here Stay here.
OK.
I love you.
GREG: Come on,
let's go find Mommy.
Tuck you in.
Good night.
Love you
Love you too, sweetie.
I think she's gonna be OK.
Yeah.
Well, whatever
it is, it's over.
It is over, isn't it?
It is over, yes.
You think you can forgive me?
I don't know, can I?
Well, I know I have a
lot of explaining to do.
Maybe a whole day's worth.
Think you could
start in the morning.
[MUSIC - ASTRAL PLANE, "PAINTED
RAIN"]
ASTRAL PLANE: [singing] I've
been running from the heat
of night for most of my life.
Touch of love and
your innocence.
You're my reason why.
I found my future in
your arms tonight.
Feel the morning light.
It haunts me from
the truth I hide.
You're always by my side.
Painted rain.
You and I together.
Free from pain.
No more running forever.
Painted rain pours
down my window.
We are the writers of the show.
Running red.
Waves of shadows
cross the open sky.
There's nothing to
feel when you die.
What I have lives
deep in dreams.
You're my reason why.
Painted rain.
You and I together.
Free from pain.
No more running forever.
Painted rain pours
down my window.
We are the writers of the show.
Running red.
Painted rain.
You and I together.
Free from pain.
No more running forever.
Painted rain pours
down my window.
We are the writers of the show.