(gentle music)
♪ I just kept hoping ♪
♪ The way would become clear ♪
♪ I spent all this time ♪
(car engine revving)
♪ Tryna play nice ♪
♪ And fight my way here ♪
♪ See, I've been having
me a real hard time ♪
♪ But it feels so nice ♪
♪ To know I'm gonna
be all right ♪
♪ So, I just kept dreaming ♪
♪ Yeah, I just kept dreamin' ♪
♪ It wasn't very hard ♪
Just headed up to the lake.
♪ I spent all this time ♪
♪ Tryna figure out why ♪
Anything else?
Yeah, this too.
(car engine revving)
♪ See, I've been having
me a real good time ♪
♪ And it feels so nice ♪
♪ To know I'm gonna
be all right ♪
You like that one, right?
Thanks.
♪ Don't take my feelings ♪
So we get service.
That's good.
♪ I have found at last ♪
Yeah, I saw you on
your phone over there
and didn't expect
we get service.
That's good.
♪ Don't take my feelings ♪
♪ I have found at last ♪
♪ Yeah, if I wanted to ♪
This is beautiful, huh?
Literally, everything is dead.
Fine.
I'm sorry.
My God.
Why, what for?
I don't know, 'cause you're mad.
What does that even mean?
You're mad, I
just wanna make you
feel better.
- Okay, you're gonna
answer that, wow.
Do you really not know really?
And don't lie.
No, I don't know.
But if I did something
wrong, I'm so sorry.
[Albee] My God.
How could you be sorry
when you don't know
what you're sorry for?
Bullshit, Albee.
(gentle music)
♪ Well, that's good and fine ♪
♪ I spent all this time ♪
(car engine revving)
All right, all right,
You just wanna tell
me why you're upset?
Oh my God, Walker,
I don't care anymore.
I don't care.
- Yeah, well I do.
Okay, all I said was baby,
hey, I don't think we
can afford it, that's it.
No, that is not how you said it.
You weren't all sweet
and like, "Oh baby."
No, you fucking said
it like I was retarded.
Hey Albee, come on.
Don't use that word.
What about Ricky?
Okay, like I was special.
Is that better?
Well, you're special to me.
I'm just saying that if we're
gonna do this shitty thing,
we might as well
do it at the beach.
Yes, but it doesn't
have to be shitty.
Okay, yeah.
Fixing your marriage
is so much fun.
I heard it's a real party.
(car engine revving)
♪ Please, don't
take my feeling ♪
Okay Albee, just get it out.
There's nothing
left to say, Walker.
♪ Yeah, if I wanted to ♪
(car engine revving)
Just 'cause we're going
up the mountain, we're fine.
♪ I'd be all right ♪
(gentle music)
(car engine revving)
I think we're close.
Hey.
Want some fries?
I could do fries.
(gentle music)
So what happens if
I get an audition?
[Walker] It's the weekend.
I audition on weekends
all the time.
One time.
And I'm not sure you're
willing to be the face
of a Mexican tampon.
Point is that I better
not miss anything important.
Yeah, well hopefully
this is more important.
How does it work?
We do the book, I guess.
They put cheese on this.
[Walker] That's cool.
Can I get a pill?
Well, yeah, but I mean
like walk me through it.
What is the plan?
Well, there are seven questions.
So I figured we.
Hey, what are you doing?
[Walker] I thought
you wanted to start.
No.
We are not having
a marriage crisis
in the middle of
a fucking diner.
Guess what?
No one knows what we're doing.
They will.
Okay, in 10 minutes we'll be
screaming each other's heads off
and you'll be sad and
I'll be the bitch.
So can we please just fall
apart somewhere private.
- Al, it's just seven questions.
- Like a normal couple.
We don't have to
kill each other.
Do you think you would kill me?
Maybe you just don't
know your husband
like you think you do.
See.
You're just being a brat.
Plus these are pretty delicious,
so it's just a win in my book.
[Albee] Walk me through it.
[Walker] We do the book.
Okay, but like gimme
a road map or something.
There's two days, right.
So I'm thinking that we do
four tomorrow, three Sunday,
or we could do it
the other way around.
But hopefully we just,
we go back to L.A. happy,
you know, together.
But we have to be honest.
Okay, that's like
literally the only thing,
it's total honesty,
good or bad we're.
- Okay, I get it.
- Yeah?
Yes.
Okay cool, deal.
Walker.
Shake my hand.
Come on this is us
making an agreement
that we're gonna do our
best, that we will try, okay.
Have you?
Just shake my goddamn
hand, Albee, okay.
This is us doing it properly.
We're gonna be honest and
hopefully we fix it, okay.
(car engine revving)
You're gonna have a stroke.
(gentle music)
Okay.
That's okay.
(gentle music)
Hey.
God, you're so corny.
(car engine revving)
(gentle music)
Is this where you
come to murder me?
Oh, you know, I thought murder
might be better than divorce.
(Albee laughing)
[Albee] There's, oh,
there's a creature.
[Walker] Oh.
It's Daphne from, "Scooby Doo."
Hey guys.
Hi, sorry we're late.
No, no, no, grab
your bags, come on in.
Is this your idea of romance?
Yeah, yeah.
There's hikes and the
lake, you'll see.
If we make it that far.
(seat belt alarm ringing)
Here we are.
Oh, there's the champagne
and cheese you asked for.
Wow, yeah, this is perfect.
Right, Albee?
It's a dream.
[Carly] When did
you guys get married?
Eight long years ago.
No, you're so young.
Yeah, we were 16, it was Texas.
Oh.
Well you have such
a beautiful face.
Is that what you do in L.A?
Have a face?
No, I meant model or act or.
Yeah, she does.
She's an actress or starting
out anyway, right baby?
Yep.
I guess that's it.
Oh, oh, did you see the
Ferris wheel on your way in?
The Brians set it
up every summer.
Wine, picnics.
Yeah, no, I was hoping we
could hit that on Sunday,
on our way back home.
If we're not divorced.
That's why we're here.
Jesus.
Yeah, we're just
sorting some things out.
Okay.
If you need anything,
you have our numbers.
[Walker] Thanks.
[Carly] Good night.
Night.
God, I need a bath.
(insects chirping)
Hey, how are they?
Oh, he's a sweetheart.
She's ahh, she's beautiful.
[Ben] Yeah.
Yeah.
This sounds bad, but you can
tell she's the kind of girl
that just thinks she's too
good for him, you know?
Yeah, yeah, I know the kind.
[Carly] Really?
Yeah, for sure, like beautiful,
thinks they're too
good for their fiances.
Yeah, why do I
get the sense that
in your case it's actually true.
I have no idea.
No?
Okay then.
Hey.
(gentle music)
[Albee] I'm in the bath.
Well, I know that.
You want some champagne?
No.
(gentle music)
[Walker] What's going on?
Walker, what happens
if it doesn't work?
(gentle music)
Why do you keep asking me that?
[Albee] Just walk me through it.
Well, we break up, I guess.
I don't know, we finish it.
It's like you said, right.
But I think if we got
through this last month,
I think we can get
through anything.
(gentle music)
We would be okay, right?
I mean,
you would be okay.
(gentle music)
(insects chirping)
(both laughing)
Shut up.
Really though.
I am.
I'm really happy.
[Carly] Me too.
Let's not change that, yeah.
Let's just always have fun.
Yeah, I'd like that.
Hey, I was thinking
maybe we should have them
over for lunch, the guests.
You said that she was a dick.
No, they're just young.
I think they're having
relationship problems.
What about our rule?
No hang with the guests.
[Carly] Yeah, you hate rules.
Yeah I do, I'm a rebel.
(both laughing)
[Carly] Yeah.
Oh but seriously though,
bad relationships are
contagious, we don't want that.
That's silly, it's one meal.
I love that you care about them,
but maybe they're not
supposed be together.
Maybe they are.
Well then they will be.
(gentle music)
[Walker] Hey.
Is there no WiFi here?
Seriously, there's no
service and no WiFi.
Did I not mention that?
You sure?
It must have slipped my mind.
But there are bears here,
what if something happens?
Babe, if you get
attacked by a bear,
who the hell are you calling?
The bear police.
(both laughing)
I don't know why you
didn't just get twin beds,
that couch looks shitty.
Well because I am an optimist.
I'm not there.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
No, that's, that's okay.
It's okay.
Sleep tight.
(birds chirping)
(gentle music)
Al?
(gentle upbeat music)
(birds chirping)
Shit.
(cellphone vibrating)
(gentle upbeat music)
Hey.
Is that alter coming?
You think you might
finish it this week?
Yeah.
Maybe.
Hey, any of that for me?
Nope.
Oh wait, wait, wait,
let me run that down.
I don't trust you.
Love you, Babe.
(gentle music)
(birds chirping)
Got it.
Okay.
Shall we do this?
All right, let's see.
It says, "Creating a
sense of space and peace
"between you and your spouse.
"Ask each other the
following question.
"Remember, there are no
right or wrong answers.
"There are just contra."
Look it's basically just saying
that we need to be super honest
and we already agreed that we're
gonna do that, right?
- Let's just go.
Yeah.
I'm gonna.
So, Albee, what was the first
thing that drew you to me?
So like, what did
you like about me?
Oh is that what that means?
Why are you being
so pissy this morning?
I don't know, why are
you being so stupid?
First thing that comes to mind,
just whatever
attracted you to me.
Oh my God.
Al.
Hold on, I'm thinking.
That you liked me, I guess.
[Walker] That I liked you.
Sure.
That I liked you,
are you being serious?
So, I could have
been a serial killer,
but as long as I liked you.
God, that's so dramatic.
Also, you said there
are no wrong answers.
No.
No, you actually used to say
really nice things about me.
Okay, fine, I liked your laugh.
Is that better?
God, it was so long ago.
Well, shit, I remember.
You remember meeting me?
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm gonna sound
like an idiot now,
but of course I remember
the first time I
saw you so clearly.
Fine.
Fine, yeah, you were in the
TV room of the big house
and you had this blue, like,
right past the knees, dress.
Right, and you got it dirty,
which you got in trouble for.
And obviously that
made you so mad
and you were just
pretty, you know,
but it was more than that,
there was something
special about you.
Special?
I'm being serious Al,
there was something
important about you.
- Oh my God, Walker.
I could see it even then.
We were 12.
So.
So the only way that I
could have been special to you
is if I was made of candy.
I mean, when you're young
like that, you get crushes,
then they're just stupid
little, nothing crushes.
It's just that usually
people grow out of them.
The thing is that we were
idiots and we got married.
No, no, no, we were so happy.
No, you just saw
some girl in a dress
and came all over yourself,
like every other stupid
idiot boy in that place.
So by that thinking then
a bunch of boys liked you?
Yeah, sure, lucky me.
Yeah, well you chose me.
So whether you want
to admit it or not,
there was something that
you did like about me.
Or you were just the
first one that asked.
(gentle music)
Why do you act like
this just never worked?
Is this done?
I answered your
question, this is done.
Really?
(gentle music)
Hey, can we?
Al.
Albee.
(car engine revving)
(gentle music)
(birds chirping)
Well what happened?
They weren't home.
Yeah, I thought I'd go
grab yourself from Joan.
Do you need anything from town?
Oh, just my dress.
And you are not seeing that.
[Ben] Okay, I'll be right back.
Don't go make any
new friends, okay.
(gentle music)
Hey, just me.
Oh, hey, sorry, I was
just checking this out
and you know, you might wanna.
You know, I noticed that you're
using framing
lumber for the deck
and you're gonna want
some thicker posts,
if you want to keep
this thing level.
And you're gonna need some
more materials as well.
When did you want
this thing done?
Oh, two weeks.
Oh, well, I can
help you if you want.
Just that this is
a bit of a mess.
It is?
Yeah.
No, of course you
don't need to do that.
It's not a problem,
it's a pretty easy job,
if you know what you're doing.
You don't say.
(birds chirping)
You're married, is
this just what it's like?
Oh, no, not yet.
I mean, that's what all
this is for, but no.
Oh.
She's not always like that.
We were good.
You know, we were really
good at the start,
and then we weren't, she wasn't.
[Carly] Do you know why?
I figured it's 'cause
she got to know me better.
She just had a tough
time growing up.
My parents were a
bit of a nightmare.
So I get that.
No, it was a foster home.
That's where we met.
Oh, so you lived together?
No, no, it was a group home.
She got adopted and yeah.
The guy that adopted her,
he's got a nice seat in
hell waiting for him.
Yeah.
What about you?
Are you happy?
I'm not dumb.
I told her I look after her,
I promised her I would, so,
I will.
(birds chirping)
(gentle music)
Morning Joan.
Hey.
Just grabbing some
lumber for the wedding.
Oh cool, how's the build coming?
Oh, you know, I think
it's getting pretty close.
Awesome.
Then I guess you
have time for a beer.
Beer for breakfast.
You're having one.
It's Saturday.
Let's think of more reasons.
Okay.
Big weekend or something?
Something.
I'm Ben, by the way.
Ben, did I look
like I wanted to chat?
'Cause if so, I'll
change what I'm doing.
Hey, I'm happy to go.
It's just kind of early
for you to be hitting on me.
[Ben] No, you're not my type.
This is just me being friendly.
That is usually my experience
with older men and bars.
So friendly.
Okay, fine, maybe you
looked a little lonely.
Think you can fix it?
[Ben] So you're
flirting with me now.
This is just me being friendly.
(cellphone vibrating)
Hey Ben, will you
tell your fiance that
I'm done with the alterations.
I'll come by tomorrow.
[Ben] Thank you, Joan.
Get you anything else?
No, this is good.
You can put it on his tab.
Relax, she's
staying at the cabin.
(gentle upbeat music)
(birds chirping)
Walker.
Hey.
What is this?
What's it look like?
You said we never have fun.
This is us having fun.
And I brought your favorite.
This is so you.
Yeah it is.
All right, we're gonna
lift this thing on three.
You ready?
One, two, three.
Look at you muscles.
Yeah, actually I
could use some help.
Oh yeah.
You know, I think I'm
carrying this by myself.
Where should we
launch this, here?
Maybe over here?
I don't know, maybe
by the lake somewhere.
Yeah, it's starting
to get a little heavy.
Oh, you sure you don't
want me to push this out?
Hey, I'm from
Texas too, you know.
Walker, what is that?
Oh yeah, I thought we
could do a couple questions
while we were having fun.
Oh you did, you sly, sly boy.
Can't run away on a boat.
Oh no.
No, Albee.
Albee, Albee, Albee.
Yeah, well, have a nice trip.
Okay baby, you know this
isn't gonna stop me.
I'm sorry, what?
What'd you say?
- All right, all right,
let's do it.
Here we are, question two.
"Start by thanking your
partner for their time."
I'll start.
Thank you Albee for
taking this time.
Yeah, you wanna say it back?
No, I'm good.
All right, well, you know,
I heard that canoeing makes
the heart grow fonder.
Actually it's rowing.
Rowing makes the
heart grow fonder.
You look a little hungry.
Oh.
- What even is that?
- Oh, that's on me.
[Albee] I'm sorry, which
one of us played baseball.
All right, they're
bringing in the reliever.
Is your arm okay?
- Ready?
- What's going on?
(laughing)
What are you trying to kill me?
You gotta catch that.
She's calling for a fastball.
Oh, that was high and outside.
You can do better.
What are you gonna
throw walks all day?
(gentle upbeat music)
(birds chirping)
You sure you don't
want to come out here?
You're on your own buddy.
(gentle upbeat music)
Yeah, that's right, bring it in.
Walker, where are you going?
[Walker] I got the
whole lake ahead of me.
Walker.
(birds chirping)
(cellphone vibrating)
Hey, the cabin lady
came by the lake
and invited us to
lunch, and I said, yes.
Why?
Because what else
was I supposed to say?
Nothing.
[Ben] Why would you do that?
We talked about this.
Because it's the
right thing to do.
Also, it just kind
of slipped out.
Look, I had this really
awkward thing with her today.
What thing?
Oh, at the bar, just
kind of feeling her out.
What?
[Ben] Just see how much of
an asshole she was, you know?
Not really.
And don't call her that,
we don't even know her.
It wasn't weird.
I was just curious to see what
she was gonna do to this guy
to see if he could trust her.
That's all.
And here you're telling
me not to interfere.
It's one lunch.
Besides I figured you
want me to make up
for being such a bitch
last night.
Sure, sounds good.
Look, we'll just eat quick
and we'll just get
'em outta here, yeah.
(gentle music)
(birds chirping)
Oh God, maybe
this was a mistake.
It was your idea.
Why are you being so weird?
Hi.
This is Ben.
Walker, Albee.
Nice to meet you.
Again.
He told me he
met you, how funny?
Yeah, it's so funny,
he didn't mention you.
[Ben] Well, you
weren't exactly chatty.
Funny, you didn't
mention it either.
Because it wasn't
very memorable.
It's simple.
Oh, that's not gluten free,
if that's still a thing.
It looks good, Babe.
Wine?
I'll have some.
That's very friendly of you.
Walker, some wine?
You got anything stronger?
[Ben] Yeah, I do, be right back.
Stronger?
Like you said, it's a party.
Here you go man.
Cheers.
(glasses clinking)
[Albee] So, you guys
are getting married?
[Ben] That's the plan.
Oh, we're gonna do it
right here, actually,
if we can get the
altar finished in time.
[Ben] Well that's easy,
'cause I used to do
carpentry in L.A. so.
[Carly] He was in a
band, weren't you, Babe.
They were amazing.
[Albee] They were?
So what is here, anyway, camp?
[Carly] That's the plan,
yeah, a little summer camp.
You know, once we
get it fixed up.
Oh, it was Ben's idea to use
it as an Airbnb first though.
[Albee] If you need to fix it,
Walker could help you.
He loves broken shit.
(birds chirping)
What's going on?
What?
Fuck you, what are you doing?
[Walker] Just eating lunch.
By the way this pasta salad
is so good, thank you.
Okay, you're mad.
We were supposed to be
doing something else
and I changed the
plan, so he's upset.
I'm so sorry, I
didn't mean to intrude.
Oh no, don't apologize
please, it's completely fine.
You don't look fine,
Walker, you look mad, own it.
Maybe just leave him alone.
Baby, I thought honesty
was the point of
this weekend, right?
So just say
something, get angry.
It was a book, it's
some $5 piece of shit,
that's supposed
to make us happy.
It's called, "Seven
Questions to Grow a Spine."
Yep.
I'm sorry, he's just determined
to make me look like an asshole.
Okay, fine, we'll do the book.
I'm really sorry
about lunch, you guys.
Let's go at Walker.
I'm good.
Walker, I said we
could do the book.
Your point is made, let's go.
Maybe you're right, you know,
maybe they are just
seven dumb questions.
You know, I think
those books are great.
We did marriage classes
in the spring, right Ben?
Babe, no.
I know it can be uncomfortable,
but we found it to
be very helpful.
I'm sure you did.
Walker, let's go.
Well, we could always do
a few questions together
if that helps?
[Ben] Carly, no.
Look, it's clear that you
all are in a very hard place,
but maybe that's why you came
here so we could help you.
Maybe she's right.
Walker, you really wanna
do this in front of them?
Think about that.
You know me so well, do I?
Great, I'll grab the book.
Walker, hey, what the actual
fuck, why would you do that?
What?
You wanna hang, I wanna do
the book, perfect solution.
No, I did not come here,
so the Anne of
fucking Green Gables
would be our marriage counselor.
Why?
Well, I don't wanna embarrass
you in front of anyone.
Well, that's a first.
See, this is great, we're
already making progress.
Look, I get it, and
I love your concern,
but this isn't our place.
Well, I grew up learning to
help people when they need it.
She doesn't need your
help, she needs an exorcist.
Then he does.
And I disagree.
Do you know that they
were foster kids?
How could I know that?
Look, that's awful, I'm sorry.
It is awful.
He said she had a
terrible childhood,
which just makes so much sense.
You know, people like
her, they're just scared.
No, Carly, no, she's not
scared, she's a fucking monster.
Believe me when I say this,
I dated girls like
her for 20 years.
I think it's the
right thing to do.
Well, I don't.
Then I'm asking you to
do this one thing for me.
It is that important.
Can you do that for me please?
Yeah.
(gentle music)
[Albee] Vape, neat.
You know, all the
kids are doing it.
Yeah, you gotta let that kid go.
Just fucking end it.
[Albee] Good chat.
Listen, I'm gonna be nice to you
because Carly wants me to be,
but I just want you to know
you're a fucking asshole.
Seriously, this whole, "Mean
Girl" bullshit is tacky.
Yeah, well coming from the guy
who looks like a backup
singer for Lenny Kravitz,
I think I'll live.
Fuck you.
By the way, I also
think you're an asshole.
(birds chirping)
Do I just start?
[Ben] What are we doing?
Just one question please, Ben.
Okay, so, it says, "The
goal of this question
"is to clear old wounds that.
(cellphone vibrating)
"To clear old wounds
that might have become."
(cellphone vibrating)
Do you wanna get that?
No, that would be rude.
But I will do the
reading for you, Babe,
that was never really
your strong suit.
So, skip that,
"Looking at your partner,
tell them the first time
"you felt wounded by them."
Wounded, oh, another winner.
Wounded anyone?
Well, why don't we go first?
Why are we doing this?
Okay, fine, fine.
[Carly] I can go
first if you want.
No, you don't have to go first.
Can somebody go?
Okay, I got it, okay.
All right.
Remember that table
I made for you,
like a couple months in?
[Carly] The side table?
Yeah, it was like the
first thing I made you.
And it's kind of dumb,
but when I gave it
to you, you laughed.
I don't remember that.
I love that table.
[Ben] Yeah to put that
fucking doily thing on it.
Maybe, I wouldn't
pick it out myself,
but hey, I love it now.
I don't know why
this bothering me.
It's because you cared.
Yeah, I had no idea.
Well, this is a
good fucking book.
Okay wait, she laughed
at your woodwork,
are you fucking kidding me?
It was important to him.
It's woodwork.
What are you six?
[Ben] Well, I'm sorry we're
not as miserable as you.
Seems like you're halfway there.
God, like what is hers gonna
be, that you don't recycle?
I thought we were fucked up.
Look, I appreciate the honesty.
I told you, Babe.
That was not honesty,
that was bullshit.
Okay, people hurt each other.
Yeah, well not
everybody clearly.
Okay, fine, people who love
each other hurt each other.
How about that?
How does he hurt you?
[Ben] And you want us to believe
that you are in
love with him, yeah?
Hey, do you think
she'd be wounded,
if I told her how you
hit on me this morning?
Nice try, I already
told her I spoke to you.
And you know what?
I wasn't hitting on you,
I was feeling you had to see
if you were cheating on him.
You bought that?
Good for you.
Yeah, she did
because we have trust,
something you wouldn't
fucking understand.
Calm down.
Yeah, Ben, what's
got you riled up.
Actually, I wanna talk to
the fiance for a second.
You trust him?
Yes, 100%, that's
why I'm marrying him.
Really?
I mean, he's a good looking guy,
that must have been a real
catch for a girl like you.
Don't you talk to her like that.
The kind of guy that you
overlooked some issues for,
you know what I mean?
You're just being mean.
It makes you wonder
though, doesn't it?
What about me, Albee?
[Albee] What about you?
What's the worst
thing ever did to you?
It's easy, you're a liar.
It's what I hate about you.
You're lying right now.
What?
You can't do that
I don't lie.
How can you even say that?
It's my question,
I don't need to explain it.
[Ben] You know
what your problem is?
Oh, please enlighten us.
Everything is a compromise.
You don't realize that no
one gets what they want.
Maybe you don't.
Don't change the
subject, just answer me.
Okay, fine.
I'll answer you by doing
yours for you, how about that?
So when could I possibly
have hurt Walker?
Oh, I've got one.
It was our honeymoon.
You remember that, right Walker?
You took me to that shitty
motel in beautiful Jersey.
This was the one time in my life
that I was maybe interested
in the idea of sex.
And Walker here had a problem
rising to the challenge.
So what did I do?
Did I kiss him and
make it better?
Did I work him up?
No.
I made him cry.
Isn't that right, Walk?
He probably had
too much to drink.
It happens all the time.
Sure does.
That's not the point.
I'm cruel and I know it.
So how does that
make him a liar, huh?
You're crazy.
Because he's sitting
here married to me,
acting like I'm not.
Why?
Because I love you Albee.
There it is.
You can't Walker.
You might think you
do, but you don't.
[Carly] Pretty sure he does.
Oh, thanks cabin lady.
We've known you for what?
Three hours.
- What are you
talking about Albee?
Everything I do is
for you, everything.
I moved to L.A. for you.
Okay, that's for us
because I love you.
How can you even say that?
Look at you, you're so mad,
you look like you wanna put
your hand through a wall.
But what are you gonna do?
Nothing.
You're just gonna tell
me that you love me
when you should hate me.
God fucking dammit,
would you just turn this
stupid piece of shit off?
Or what?
You'll cry.
What is wrong with you?
I warned you.
Fuck it, last question.
[Albee] Shoot.
Did you ever love me or is this
just so you could get away from?
Don't, Walker.
Then fucking answer me.
Fine, did I come here thinking
that fucking a plate of cheese
and a book is gonna fix this?
No, idiot, I didn't.
(gentle music)
Walker.
Fuck.
Walker, no.
Walker, don't you dare.
I swear to God.
Oh my God.
What did you do?
What I should've done
eight goddamn years ago.
I didn't have a phone
eight years ago, asshole.
Are you crying?
No, you owe me a new phone.
What the fuck, you're
crying over a phone?
Fuck you.
Were you ever gonna
try to fix this?
Huh, did you have any
intention of trying
to make this better?
- No, never.
I don't know if
that makes you happy
or I don't know what you
thought was gonna happen.
Do you love me, Albee?
(gentle music)
Did you ever even like me?
Actually, I asked you answered.
- Walker.
- Go.
(gentle music)
I need you to stop
saying that, okay.
Because I know that.
[Ben] Could you please
stop cleaning for one second?
I can put things away
and talk at the same time.
I did not mean for
things to go this way.
[Ben] Yeah, I know
but I told you.
I warned you.
Okay, I get it, you
know that kind of girl.
Well, I know that kind of
boy and I felt bad for him.
Honey, I love you, I do, okay.
But this whole saving
people bullshit, it's just.
Okay, I'm sorry, forget it.
I'm just gonna go
get some work done.
What a nice idea.
(gentle music)
♪ You shouldn't say that about
yourself when I'm with you ♪
♪ You ♪
♪ You make it look so easy when
you get water in your shoes ♪
♪ It's ♪
♪ Not lying if
it's storytelling ♪
♪ I do it often ♪
♪ She, said how much
are you selling ♪
♪ I said, I do it with caution ♪
♪ You're not mine ♪
♪ But I act like you are ♪
♪ Are ♪
♪ And at my bed,
I see your shadow ♪
♪ Hanging over my head ♪
♪ You're not mine ♪
♪ Mine ♪
♪ Take me to your
sister's place ♪
♪ Down by the lake ♪
♪ Sing your lullaby 'cause
you know I'll appreciate it ♪
♪ Fly with your blue bug ♪
♪ You know that I'll
meet you any location ♪
♪ Smile and breathe
in and breathe out ♪
♪ When you feel
your body shaking ♪
♪ Bring you out to the desert
and maybe we can bake ♪
♪ Worry about messing up
'cause it's stuck in our DNA ♪
♪ Head on over to your house ♪
♪ And we'll see
what we can create ♪
Babe.
Babe, are you up?
♪ Like we do best 'cause
the rest is so overrated ♪
(gentle music)
(birds chirping)
(sighs)
Hey, you beat me to it.
I got the croissants
that you like.
Thanks.
This is for the guests.
[Ben] That's optimistic.
Hey, are we okay?
Yeah, I'm tired.
Look, I know you were
trying to do a good thing.
And I was being a dick.
I was saying things
that I didn't even mean.
Okay, I'm gonna be better.
I love you.
I love you too.
Joan is coming over
later to fit the dress.
So you need to be
out of the house.
Okay.
I'll just hop in the shower
and I'll go work on the deck.
Okay.
(door knocking)
[Carly] Hey guys, breakfast.
Have you seen Walker?
He didn't come home?
I hoped that...
We'd break up.
'Cause that's what happened.
God, Albee, I'm so sorry.
Don't be.
It doesn't mean
anything, anyway.
What time is checkout?
- Three, but.
- Okay, great.
(gentle music)
Shit.
I'm working tonight,
if you wanna come down.
Joan, is it ugly?
What?
No, it's Mom's dress.
You wanted to wear
this for 30 years.
I know.
Okay, I promise you
get the fit, right.
No, it's not that I just.
Can I ask you something?
Is this a good idea?
I'm really asking.
I want you to be honest.
I realize I never
asked you before.
And then I just started thinking
like maybe I never asked myself.
All right, well
you're not a fucking idiot.
Two like caveats,
A, I know shit all
about dating men, so.
I knew there was a
reason I never asked you.
Exactly.
Does he make you happy?
That's all that really matters.
I think so.
But if I'm being honest,
really honest,
I don't know.
It's not like this clean thing.
The boy, the one
who's staying here,
I think he would literally
die for his wife.
Okay, well that's just sad.
Is it?
Ben won't even finish the altar.
It's been weeks
and it is literally
the place we're
supposed to stand
and say our vows to each other
and he just won't finish it.
He won't.
Well, what did you expect?
I'm not being mean, but
he's kind of a fuck boy.
How is that not mean?
Okay, Cinderella.
I'm just saying that he's
an ex musician from L.A.
who ran away to the woods.
Are you really surprised
he's not a grownup yet?
I'm not saying he won't be, but.
Right.
You did say be honest.
(birds chirping)
(Ben laughing)
Hey man.
[Walker] Hey,
sorry, I just kind of.
Finished the
whole fucking thing.
[Walker] Yeah.
Shit, hey, did Carly see this?
I haven't really seen anyone.
What, did you run away
from home or something?
It's over between Albee and me.
I finished it or she did.
Maybe we both did,
I don't really know.
Holy shit, like it's done, done?
Yep.
Hey, you know what that is?
That is great fucking news.
You know what great
fucking news needs.
Ah.
Hey, come on.
You're a younger looking kid,
you're not gonna be lonely.
All right, trust me.
Shit, I almost envy you.
(birds chirping)
Hey, you know,
I saw that you guys
have some work that needs
to get done around here,
you know, some stuff for
the wedding and whatnot,
I thought maybe I could.
[Ben] What are you
looking for a job?
More a place to stay.
Dude, if you tell Carly
that I built this thing.
You can stay here for
the rest of your fucking life.
I mean, you're
out of the Airbnb,
but you can stay at the
shit cabin that we have.
I don't care.
Look, trust me,
I know it sucks right now,
but this is the best day
of your fucking life.
(birds chirping)
Hey, that was a real dick
move of you to not come home.
Well, I didn't wanna see you.
People don't run not
to be chased, Walker.
I should know.
We can't end like that.
[Walker] Why not?
Because we didn't even
do your stupid book.
We still can, if you want to.
Hey, I read your notes.
I get it now.
Okay, so what, that's it,
one stupid fight and it's done?
Al.
Walker, you threw
my phone in a lake.
I got mad, you can't
hate me for that.
I don't hate you
Albee, you know that.
I'm embarrassed, you know.
I've been telling you this
whole time to be honest
and you were.
You know, it was me
who wasn't listening,
but I get it now, and it's okay.
It fucking, it's okay.
You should go.
I want you to.
What about you?
I'm gonna stay here at the camp.
Yeah.
Okay, maybe Hansel and
Gretel will adopt you.
I'm serious, Al.
[Albee] Walker, no,
what about the car?
Take it.
All your stuff is in L.A.
It's yours, you could
sell it if you want,
I don't really care.
I'll help you pay rent as
long as you need me to.
Can we just please not turn
this into another fight?
Look, you're gonna be good.
You're gonna be better than
good, you're gonna be great.
You're you.
God, of course,
you're fucking nice.
(gentle music)
(car engine revving)
♪ I've got to love life ♪
♪ For once in my
life I feel fine ♪
♪ And the girl and
the boy are okay ♪
♪ And now it's time
to play again ♪
♪ Flowers in the prayer room ♪
♪ Flowers in the bathroom ♪
♪ Tie it in the skyline ♪
♪ Everyone is leaving
at the same time ♪
♪ On the way home ♪
(gentle music)
(door knocking)
Hey.
Hi.
I was on my way out of town
and I found these in my car.
Walker needs them.
He forgets to take
them all the time,
but he gets really
sick if he doesn't so.
Okay.
Hey, are you all right?
I heard that.
Oh, I'm sure you guys
think this is great.
No, I truly just wanted to help.
Look, you hated me from
the moment you saw me
and I don't think
you were wrong too.
Can I be honest?
Let's don't do this right now.
Go ahead.
I know you had a rough
time growing up, okay.
And that kinda shit
can leave a mark.
What?
[Ben] The foster thing, it
sounded awful and I'm sorry.
He told you?
All right, what
we're trying to say is,
we know that the foster
system isn't great.
Oh, what the fuck?
Walker just told
me a little bit.
Oh, fuck you, he did.
He was just trying to
explain to me what happened
between you guys.
Look I hope that.
- No, no, no.
Like you're just some like
hermit lady in the woods
with a fucking bullshit
fiance, all right.
I don't know what he told you,
but you don't fucking
know shit about me.
I'll be right back.
(birds chirping)
(gentle music)
(car engine revving)
(door knocking)
Oh, hey, sorry.
I'm just getting my
final stuff outta here.
[Carly] Walker,
listen, I'm so sorry.
I think I really messed up.
I told Albee what you said
about the foster thing.
I was just trying to help.
- Did you?
Yeah.
Shit.
Do you know where she is?
I don't know,
she just drove off.
I'm so sorry.
No, it's not your fault.
Fuck.
Are there any buses in town?
I gotta get back to L.A.
Yeah, let me drop you.
(cellphone vibrating)
Walker.
(gentle upbeat music)
♪ There's a paperclip
resting on my countertop ♪
♪ Sunday morning I forgot ♪
♪ What it's like
to lose a friend ♪
♪ Yesterday ♪
♪ How it seems so far away ♪
♪ And I've said all I can say ♪
Thank you.
Cheers.
♪ But now it's time ♪
Do you want one?
♪ I get to goin' ♪
♪ But now it's time I
get to find my own way ♪
(car engine revving)
[Walker] Awesome.
Thank you for everything.
[Carly] Yeah, I really
hope it works out.
You too, I hope the
wedding goes well.
Did you see the altar?
Yeah.
He did a really beautiful job.
♪ I don't really care ♪
♪ For the golden sun ♪
♪ Has washed me away
and I've become ♪
♪ Just another vagabond
holding my head, oh ♪
♪ But now it's time
I get to goin' ♪
♪ But now it's time I
get to find my own way ♪
♪ And I'll leave you lonely ♪
♪ I'll leave you lonely ♪
♪ All in all it's
a beautiful day ♪
♪ When I wake up all alone ♪
♪ I cannot help but run away ♪
♪ Now I'm afraid ♪
♪ That it's all in my head ♪
♪ Don't you know ♪
♪ That it's all in your head ♪
♪ So you roll the dice ♪
♪ Melt a fire, burn the ice ♪
♪ Find the girl
with yellow eyes ♪
♪ And go and break her heart ♪
♪ See that nothing changes ♪
♪ And I know not
what I've become ♪
♪ A prisoner to everyone I've
loved from the start, oh ♪
♪ But now it's time
I get to goin' ♪
♪ But now it's time I
get to find my own way ♪
♪ And I'll leave you lonely ♪
Hey.
So what do you think?
Ben.
Do you want this?
What?
Of course I fucking do.
Carly, what?
Be honest.
I want you to.
Do you wanna get married?
(insects chirping)
I don't know.
Yeah.
I know.
It's a shame.
Walker did a beautiful job.
(insects chirping)
(gentle upbeat music)
This is too easy.
Shut up.
(gentle upbeat music)
Stop.
Can't have it
starting like that.
- [Man] Was it too much?
- No.
I need you to get out.
[Man] Hey, I'm sorry.
No, it's okay,
it's not you. I just.
Get out.
- Yeah.
Yeah I can go, yeah.
(gentle upbeat music)
(Albee crying)
(gentle music)
♪ I don't wanna be a bother ♪
♪ Coming back your way ♪
♪ Heading further and further ♪
♪ And I'll be gone by Tuesday ♪
[Carly] I'm not really
sure about anything.
It's okay.
Come here.
♪ Misery will wait ♪
♪ Baby you're so kind ♪
♪ The last I saw you ♪
Is he okay?
[Carly] I mean, are
either of you really okay?
♪ I've paid enough ♪
(gentle music)
I'm so sorry about
whatever happened to you.
Don't be.
A lot of people
will feel much worse
and don't act like I had.
You were a kid.
But I'm not anymore.
That's the only reason that he
proposed, was to get me out.
He would never admit
that, but it's true.
Or maybe he loves you?
♪ And I'll wait, and I'll wait ♪
No, because how
can you love this?
Fuck.
[Carly] What's scarier,
that he doesn't love you
or that he does?
(gentle music)
♪ And I'll wait, and I'll
wait, and I'll wait ♪
♪ I'll be there, I'll be
there, I'll be there ♪
(car engine revving)
What are you doing?
Just, don't stab me or anything.
♪ You look so good ♪
You're gonna be okay.
You really, really are.
(Albee crying)
(gentle music)
[Albee] Walker.
Albee, what are you doing here?
I wanted to talk.
Yeah well, I don't care anymore.
Yes you do.
Just look gimme five
minutes, all right.
Come on, I fucking ran here,
you know how much I hate that.
[Man] Keep your
arms and legs inside.
Don't throw anything.
Rides away.
Classic Walker.
Picked the happiest place to be
sad.
(insects chirping)
I don't know what's
wrong with me,
but I know that
it's not your fault.
Look, I wanna make you deal.
No.
No, Walker, trust me,
you're gonna like it okay.
When this ride stops,
I'm gonna stay on
because that's what I want.
And If you wanna go,
if you're really done,
then you can.
- Albee.
I'm not gonna be mad at you.
You're not a liar.
Okay, you're fucking so good.
God, you're so good
it's like you can't
even see the bad in me.
And there's so much of it.
Why is that all you see?
I don't know.
'Cause there's something
wrong with me, broken.
There's nothing wrong with you.
You're not broken, Al,
you're stronger than me.
You must be stupid
if you think that then.
Walker, could we just call
it another bad weekend?
I mean another stupid fight.
I mean, we're not good at
this, but how could we be?
Okay, nobody ever wanted us.
We're all that we ever had.
Because I wanna be happy too.
I deserve that.
But with you I'm not.
Okay, so we'll be better.
- No.
- I'll be better.
No, you're right,
we're ruining each other.
No, I wasn't right.
When was the last
time you kissed me?
Just because you wanted to,
'cause you liked me.
I'm not saying it to
rub your face in it.
Can you remember?
See, what is it that
we even holding on to?
You know, I'm with you
and I'm so fucking lonely.
Look, I know it's not fair,
but what if what happened,
took that part of me?
I don't know Al, we
can't even talk about it.
I know, it's just
that when I try,
I literally feel like
I'm falling apart.
So fall apart then.
Fall apart, do it.
You're a fucking mess.
I'm a mess.
We're both a mess.
No you're not.
I chose you, didn't I?
Yeah, you did.
God, I know that I can't
ask you to anymore.
And that's what sucks because
that is all I've ever wanted.
Okay, that's all I want.
And I know that even
right now, as they say it,
you can't believe me.
Because how could you?
You'll be okay Al.
Please don't say that.
Well you're just scared
because we're all
each other's ever had.
No, don't say that.
I'm not doing this again.
You need to know that
it's not your fault.
Nothing's your fault,
including us,
we're not to blame.
We're not.
(insects chirping)
You had a cap on
'cause you needed a haircut.
What?
The day that we met,
you were wearing a hat.
And it was just
like neon yellow,
like they was scared
you were gonna
run into traffic or something.
And I had just gotten in trouble
for not wanting to
play with anyone.
Very surprising.
And I dunno, you came in and
you just sat down with me
and then you took your hat off
and it looked like you fucking
cut your hair with a
lawn mower or something.
And all the other kids
started making fun of you
and you didn't care.
You didn't care at all,
you just talked with me
like we were old
friends or something.
That was the first thing
that I liked about you.
You didn't run
away from anything.
So if you're gonna go, please
take that story with you,
and not the one that I
said, because I lied.
Okay, Walker, you're not
too weak or too nice.
I mean, you're not perfect, but,
I don't know, it's
like all this time,
I've just needed you to
see the ugliness in me.
Because what if you don't
and then I believe you
and I let go, and
then you see me.
I'm not saying that
it makes sense,
but I swear, it's like
the minute that you left,
I understood, like I fucking
woke up or something.
And could you please
say something?
Walker you wanted me
to be honest and talk,
and now I am, and I
don't know what to say
because you're the only person
that I've ever been close to.
And I know that I'm shitty
at it, but God, I love you.
I love you so much.
(insects chirping)
Walker, come here.
(both crying)
Albee.
(gentle music)
It's okay.
(both crying)
♪ And I will stroll
the merry way ♪
♪ And jump the hedges first ♪
♪ And I will drink the
clear, clean water ♪
♪ For to quench my thirst ♪
♪ And I shall watch
the ferry-boats ♪
♪ And then I'll get high ♪
[Man] Ride stops.
♪ On a bluer ocean ♪
♪ Against tomorrow's sky ♪
[Man] Are we staying or going?
I'll stay.
[Man] Bud?
♪ And I will never
grow so old again ♪
[Man] Bud, are we
staying or we going?
(gentle upbeat music)
♪ And I will walk and talk in
gardens all wet with rain ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Sweet thing, sweet thing ♪
♪ My sweet thing ♪
♪ Oh, my, my, my,
my, my sweet thing ♪
♪ And I shall drive my chariot
down your streets and cry ♪
♪ Hey, it's me, I'm dynamite
and I don't know why ♪
♪ And you shall take me
strongly in your arms again ♪
♪ And I will not remember
that I ever felt the pain ♪
♪ We shall walk and talk
in gardens all misty wet ♪
♪ Misty wet with rain down ♪
♪ And I will never, never,
never grow so old again ♪
♪ Oh sweet thing, sweet thing ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, you sweet
thing, sweet thing ♪
♪ My, my, my, my, my ♪
♪ And I will raise my hand
up into the night time sky ♪
♪ And count the stars
that's shining in your eyes ♪
♪ Just to dig it all an' not
to wonder that's just fine ♪
♪ And I'll be satisfied not
to read in between the lines ♪
♪ And I will walk and talk in
gardens all wet with rain ♪
♪ And I will never, ever,
ever, ever grow so old again ♪
♪ Oh, oh ♪
♪ Sweet thing ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Sugar baby ♪
♪ Oh, oh ♪
♪ Sweet thing ♪
♪ Sugar baby ♪
♪ Sugar baby, sugar baby ♪
♪ With your champagne eyes ♪
♪ And your saint-like smile ♪