(light chiming)
(light playful music)
(gentle music)
(water splashing)
- [Bridget] I'm stuck.
Can someone help me with this line please?
(Sam laughing)
Can someone help me with my line?
Mom, I snagged my line.
- I can't help you,
Bridge, I'm tying this fly.
(water splashing)
Sam!
- Come on, Mom, take the plunge.
Come on, you're not gonna melt.
- Now, you heard the boy.
Get in this water right now.
(fishing pole clacking)
Whoa, hey, there we go.
- Nice one, Dad.
- That's a big one.
- [Jesse] Yeah, it's a good size.
(water splashing)
- Sam!
- Gotcha!
Oh, take that, take that.
- Sam!
- Oh, you are so dead.
- Well, I think I just caught us dinner.
- Not the way Sam eats.
- Want me to catch a bear?
- I actually think he prefers moose.
- Ah, well, Sam is a moose.
(Bridget laughing)
- [Bridget] You really do
look like a moose, Sam.
- [Sam] At least I don't
look like an elephant.
Got ya.
(water splashing)
- Okay, guys, let's get packed up.
- I would I could get my line out.
Will someone help me with this please?
- [Jesse] Bridge, you take
care of that mess downstairs?
- Yeah, well, I will if you buy a new suit
for my sweet 16 party.
- Wait a minute, I never heard about this.
What's wrong with my old suit?
- According to style, like last century.
Mom, please make him buy a new suit.
- I've never been able to
make your father do anything.
- I never heard about this.
When did this, wait...
Wanna cook?
- Dad.
- Come on, Bridge.
- Seriously.
- Fine, you want me to buy a
new suit, I'll buy a new suit.
- Thank you.
- Yes.
- Hello!
- Hey, there they are.
- Oh, Burt, Ellen, hi.
- Susannah!
So you were the surprise.
Wonderful.
- We haven't seen you
in front of that grill for years.
- We haven't seen that grill for years.
- Yeah, well Jess seems
to think a seasoned grill
means never cleaning it.
(Ellen laughing)
- Good to see you.
- Good to see you too.
- Do you guys know what a buffalo says
to his son on the way to school?
- Not this one again.
- No.
- What does a buffalo-
- Bye, son.
(family laughing)
- Who taught you that one?
- It took me a second.
- [Jesse] It did, it took me a second too.
- It's better than you.
- That was a good one.
- Well, I for one have had
a wonderful time today,
but it's time we headed back home.
- Mom, we don't have
to go back yet, do we?
- Yeah, honey, we do.
- Mom, come on, it's summer vacation.
- I can't miss the after
theater dinner crowd
and I don't want your
father to make two trips.
- No, no, I don't mind.
I can take 'em back Monday night.
- Please, Mom.
- Oh, come on.
- Okay.
- Actually, Derek is due in Monday night
and I have to go to town
anyway, so I can haul 'em.
- [Bridget] Is that one
of your 10,000 grandkids?
- Yeah, from Los Angeles.
Jane's going through
a pretty nasty divorce
and they thought he'd have a
better summer up here with us.
- So, just what kinda
after theater dinner crowd
is there in Anchorage anyway?
- Well, not that you ever noticed,
but there is some culture
to be gleaned in the city.
- Yes, a lot more than there is
to be gleaned out here
in the sticks I guess.
I mean, not that I ever
got tired of this, but-
- Guys, come on.
It was such a good day.
- Sorry, hun.
- Come on, Suze, I'll take you back.
- [Susannah] See you guys
again sometime, okay?
- Soon.
- Bye, sweetie.
- Bye.
- Bye, bye, bye, bye.
- Bye, Mom.
- Bye.
(somber music)
Well, if any of us thought
that they might be getting
back together, I think
today pretty much killed it.
(somber music continues)
(plane engine rumbling)
(water splashing)
- [Jesse] Well, thanks for
roughing it for the day.
- [Dock Crew] It's
secure, you're all good.
- [Jesse] I guess we won't be
doing that again anytime soon.
- I don't know what makes you think I ever
had anything against the wilderness.
I used to love it up there.
- Couldn't seem to get away fast enough.
- Yeah, 15 years is a real clean getaway.
- Well, I guess that wasn't
even the thing you trying-
- Jesse, can we not do this right now?
- Okay, fine.
- We already know this
argument by heart.
- Yeah, sure do.
(door slamming)
(plane engine rumbling)
- Oh, thank God you're here.
- What?
- Okay, the salmon's
not fresh, Andrew
dropped a case of Merlot,
and the mayor just popped
by with a party of 12.
He had to wait half an hour.
- Oh, well, find a bottle
of Merlot that didn't break,
and send it over to his
table with my compliments.
And why on earth do we
bother living in Alaska
if we can't get fresh salmon?
- I don't know.
- Hey.
- Oh, hey.
How was family day in the sticks?
- It was great, until Jesse
started pushing my buttons.
- How is Gary Cooper anyway?
- Jesse is fine and his cowboy charm
wore off a long time ago.
- Yeah, but not his
good looks though, huh?
- Yeah, he's attractive,
I'll give you that,
but you try staying home through
one too many week long fishing trips and-
- And then you come up and you
go to bed with Gary Cooper.
Look, I don't see the problem.
- That's good.
- I know.
- Try putting up with it for 15 years.
I mean, he'd be working so
hard to pay off the house,
and then I'd be home with three kids,
alone in the middle of nowhere.
- Yeah, well, at least you
had the kids to talk to.
I mean, Rich used to
go off on an oil tanker
for six months at a time, you know?
Well, it's been great.
I mean, if I hadn't
have broken up with him,
I never would have gone to cooking school,
I never would have met
you and got this job,
and well, a real life, you know?
- Yeah, yeah, I'll take
shaky financial independence
over good companionship
and regular sex anyway.
- It wasn't that regular.
(Susannah laughing)
(light music)
- It's Dad.
(plane engine rumbling)
(water splashing)
(car engine rumbling)
He brought nerds.
- Great.
- Hannah, go tell Burt and
Ellen that Derek came in early.
All right?
So, this is my house.
It's nothing fancy, but you
guys didn't come to sit inside.
Hey, you.
(birds chirping)
- Derek.
Derek, come on and sit down, son.
Teach you how to tie a fly.
You haven't said a word
since you've been here.
How's your mom doing?
- You talk to her on the
phone every week don't you?
- Yes, but you see her everyday.
And it's hard for me to
know if she's been crying
when I'm talking to her on the phone.
- Well, then, to answer your questions,
no, she isn't doing very well,
and yes, she cries all the time.
(Bridget scoffs)
- He was just asking.
You don't have to be such a jerk.
- Since I'm here against my will,
I think I can be a jerk
for at least a few days.
- Well, at least there's an end in sight.
(door slamming)
(Jesse sighs)
- Well, the guys'll be ready in a minute.
They're on a video conference.
Hey, let's get packed up.
Come on, it's time to go.
- I found it.
- Ah, thanks.
See ya.
- See ya.
- Have fun, guys.
- Ellen, how come no women ever wanna stay
at the Wilderness Ranch?
- Women are smart enough
to go to the Bahamas.
- You know, 'cause I've been thinking
if mom and dad are really
over, I think it's time we have
to start thinking about the future.
I mean, dad needs a woman.
He never goes into the city
and they certainly never come out here.
- [Ellen] And what makes you
think your dad needs a woman?
- 'Cause he's lonely.
- [Susannah] Hannah's right.
Dad's a good looking guy,
he's probably got needs.
- Oh, Lord.
- How about a set up.
Don't you have a cousin in Juno?
- Well, yeah, but she's 58 years old.
- Oh.
- You know, by the off chance
that you're serious about this,
what about something like this?
- "Alaska Love," what is that?
(Ellen giggling)
- [Burt] Oh, you are bad.
- [Ellen] Well, I only
buy it for the crosswords.
- Oh, sure, millions of men buy Playboy
just to read the articles.
That was a hunting and fishing journal,
and a couple of years ago
somebody started a personal column
and it took over the whole magazine.
- What kinda personals?
- Oh, yeah, love connections.
There's a lotta lonely men in Alaska,
and a lotta women looking to meet 'em.
- Really?
- Sure.
How do you think I met Ellen?
Mail order bride right there.
- Oh, stop that.
- I still go the box she came in.
Marked "fragile, handle with care."
- He's kidding.
So, what do you think?
Divine inspiration?
(water splashing)
- I got one.
I got one.
I got one!
- Yeah, yeah, good, good, good.
All right, good, good.
No, easy now, easy, easy, easy, easy.
That's it, pull her in.
All right, up.
(light music)
Too small.
Hey, hey.
(both laughing)
All right, you.
Lights out.
- Do you ever get lonely, Dad?
- Oh, sweetie, I don't
have time to get lonely.
- Don't you miss mom?
- Uh...
(soft music)
It's a little tough seeing
her like that yesterday.
Brought back some good memories.
- Like when you first brought her up here?
- Yeah, that's right.
(Jesse chuckling)
Yeah, I'd come up here to work
one summer during college,
and I just fell in love with Alaska.
- You wanted to build a ranch,
but grandpa wanted you to work for him.
- He sure did.
Yeah, at that point, real
estate sounded as good
as anything else I guess.
- But Momma knew you'd hate it,
so she didn't let you do it.
- That's exactly right.
She knew I'd go crazy wearing a suit
and talking on the phone all day.
- [Hannah] So, you did it.
- Ah, we did it.
You know your mom stood right next to me
when we told your grandpa?
He got so angry.
Ah, but he got over it.
And your mom and I got married,
and we had us three beautiful
little kiddie, kiddie,
kiddies like you.
(Hannah giggling)
- And then?
- Uh and then...
Well, here we are.
(somber music)
Hey, listen, you.
You sleep, okay?
I love you.
- Love you too.
(birds chirping)
(door creaking)
(cereal crunching)
- Morning.
I said good morning, grouchy.
- Sorry.
I didn't sleep at all last night.
Did you guys even realize
that the sun never went down?
(children laughing)
- Welcome to the top of the world.
- Yeah, for a couple
of weeks in the summer
we have almost 24 hours of daylight.
- Huh, cool.
- I couldn't sleep either.
I don't think Daddy wants
to be alone anymore.
- How do you know what Dad wants?
- Because he talks to me.
He does.
- Yeah, right.
- You know what, I couldn't
stop thinking about
that "Alaska Love" magazine.
- Maybe we could send Dad's picture in?
- Are you crazy?
You'd have better luck auctioning
him off on the internet.
Only desperate guys do personal ads.
- Oh, morning, Dad.
- [Jesse] Hm.
- Hello, desperate guy.
(Jesse groaning)
- Okay, what do we have to fill out?
(light music)
- [Hannah] Make sure she likes kids.
- Yeah, if you find a woman with two boys,
a girl and a dog named
Tiger, you're all set.
- Now, how do we even know that Dad's
gonna have enough choices
to be picky about?
- Because we're really gonna sell him.
He's handsome, funny, caring, giving,
and he always makes you laugh
if you're feeling upset.
- Oh, hey, put down that he's
good in case of an emergency.
Remember when that guy
from Ohio almost drowned,
then Dad gave him CPR and saved him?
- That, that's good.
- Hey, you guys didn't fill
out the cultural interest form.
Does he like music or art?
Does he read any books?
- He read me "Curious George Goes
To The Hospital" last week.
- I'll make up something good.
- So, what does he have
to say about all this?
You're not telling him?
- Well, it's not like he'd
actually go along with it.
- Uh, I think his reaction
might be a tad bit stronger
than "I'm not going along with this."
- Yeah, but it doesn't matter.
By the time the letters start coming,
it'll be too late to stop it.
- You guys oughta sell real estate.
Maybe even used cars.
You got a real knack
for making a fixer-upper
sound like the find of the century.
- But he is the find of the century.
- Yeah, we're just
worried no one will find
the find up here.
- What about your mom?
Anybody worried about
her being on her own?
- Mom's different, she dates.
Knows how to do all this kinda stuff.
- Yeah.
- So, you had fun out at the ranch?
- I did, it was really nice to
get out there with the kids.
Stretch my legs and breathe the fresh air.
- Mm hm.
- That's not to say
I'm not having a lovely time
ducking out of work today
to go to the museum with you.
- Oh, well, I'm very glad to hear that.
It's not how I meant it.
I'm not trying to compete with your family
or your husband or anything-
- Ex-husband and of course
you're trying to compete
with him, you're a man.
- Oh, well, don't hold
anything in, Susannah.
Just tell me what you really think.
- Was that blunt?
- Wasn't subtle.
- I'm sorry, I have been
told I can be blunt.
- Well, I'll be blunt too.
It's been two months.
How am I doing?
- You want the long version
or the short version?
- Uh, any chance a guy
can bum a cup of coffee?
- Uh, can I give you a rain check?
The kids are gonna be back soon and...
- Sure.
- Okay.
- Um, actually, Susannah,
I don't wanna sound...
Well, I'm just being a
really good boy scout here,
but I'm also a boy.
- I know, I'm sorry.
I just, you know I'm just trying
to get used to this dating,
relationship thing again.
- And I don't wanna rush something
that's worth waiting for.
- Thank you.
(car engine rumbling)
(car door slamming)
- Mom.
- I better go.
- Okay.
- Call you later.
- Thanks.
- Hey, guys.
- Hi.
- [Sam] Hey.
- Hm.
- Hi.
- Hey, Mom.
- Hey, how you doin'?
- Good seeing you.
(dogs barking)
- [Jesse] Well, I guess
I don't need to ask
how the rest of your weekend was.
- No, you don't.
- It looked like he was on his way in.
- I asked.
- Oh, yeah?
- But he has to get up early for court.
- Let me guess, he's a
big defense attorney,
working hard to get those
criminals back on the street asap.
- Well, not that it's
any of your business,
but he's actually trying
a big class action suit
against one of the oil refineries up here.
- Wow, a real job and principles to boot.
Well, maybe you found what
you were always looking for.
- Maybe I have.
Don't you have a plane to catch?
- It's okay, I know the pilot.
- Good night.
- Yeah.
(light music)
- I've got a secret.
- Oh, you do?
- It's about dad.
- Wow, so, spill it.
Good night.
You know what she's talking about?
- Hm (spits), hardly ever do.
(Susannah chuckling)
- Good night.
(light music)
You know what Hannah's secret is?
- No idea.
I don't know.
- You guys are up to something.
(Bridget giggling)
Lights out.
Now.
(gentle music)
- Hi.
- Hey.
- So, I ran into Burt at the store
and he said you were here.
- Yeah, yeah, I had to get some new CDs.
I think it's gonna be fine.
So, what were you doing at the store?
- I was checking out the magazines.
- Did you find out if they're gonna print
the article or not?
- No, not a word.
I got you something.
- Thanks.
- It's so you can sleep.
- I'm just gonna take a wild guess and say
that I look like a complete
moron with this on.
(Bridget laughing)
- It wasn't my intention.
- Yeah.
Thanks.
(light music)
- All right, guys, here we go.
Oh my...
- Oh, my God.
- No way.
(children giggling)
- That is such a good picture.
- Look at that one.
- That's good.
- So, what's so great about the magazine?
- That's our dad.
- Your dad?
- We're surprising him.
- Man, you guys are in a world of trouble.
- Why?
Bring it over here.
I'll show you why.
A subscribership of over 200,000.
- 200,000?
(Sam gasps)
- [Cashier] And that doesn't
include over the counter sales.
- Are you serious?
(cashier chuckling)
- 200,000?
- Bridge, what's wrong?
It turned out great.
- Mm hm.
- Way to go, kids.
- "I'm looking for someone
who likes adventure,
barbecued ribs and children."
- Well, I'd write him
a letter, I'll yell ya.
- Oh.
(both laughing)
- What?
- Oh, nothing, nothing.
- You two need to get out more.
- You going to town today?
- Yeah, I gotta buy a
suit for Bridget's party.
Why, you need anything?
- No, just asking.
- All right.
- Oh, don't forget to
stop at the post office.
They called and said they
had some packages for you.
- Yeah, that's weird.
Don't remember ordering anything.
(light music)
- [Susannah] Josie, you're late.
- I was detained at the news stand.
- What?
Oh, my God.
- Gary Cooper rides again.
- Oh, my God.
(light music)
(mail bags thudding)
- I have 41 pounds of letters and packages
from all over the country.
Any idea what's going on here?
What?
Did you do this?
- I have a sneaking suspicion
it was your children.
- I'm gonna kill 'em.
All three of 'em.
No jury would convict me.
Oh, man!
Oh!
Where did they even hear
about a rag like this?
- Don't look at me.
That's not where I go to shop for men,
or even trade 'em in.
(Susannah chuckling)
- What am I gonna do with this stuff?
- I don't know.
(Jesse sighs)
(Susannah laughing)
- Why did we decide to have kids again?
- We were young and in love.
Come on, let's go find you a suit.
- [Jesse] You sure about this, gray?
- Trust me, I shopped for you for years.
- What?
What's the matter, is it okay?
- Yeah.
Yeah, sure.
Let's just find you a tie.
- What, no clip-ons?
- [Susannah] Mm hm.
Maybe you should think about
getting some new shirts
and some underwear.
- I don't need a mother, Suze.
- Well, maybe you do need somebody.
Maybe that's what he kids
are trying to tell you.
- Well, why don't they just tell me?
Instead of sneaking around behind my back.
(Jesse grumbling)
- Wait.
Why don't you just read
some of the letters.
I mean, what harm could it do?
Misguided or not, the kids
went to a lotta trouble
in a very sweet effort to help you.
- Well, why can't they
help you find somebody?
Oh, that's right, you already have.
How is Sebastian?
- Stephen is his name as you well know,
and he's wonderful.
- Well, maybe I will read some letters.
Look at some video tapes.
Ah, granted my future
dating plans didn't involve
putting out an all-points bulletin.
- He's gonna need those pants.
- But there could be someone wonderful
just waiting in that bag.
You know?
Seriously doubt it.
- Well, now, see, that's the picture
that should've run on the cover.
Pants.
Give them to me.
(light music)
(car doors slamming)
- Hi.
- Oh, hi.
Look who it is.
Here, grab this for me, will ya?
Ut oh, take this one too.
While you're at it, pick that stuff up.
Hi, there.
- Hi, Dad.
- You know,
it was Bridget's idea.
- Bridget's idea.
(Jesse chuckling)
You're all grounded for
the rest of your lives.
So, your mom wants to read
some of these letters.
Why don't you grab those.
(gentle music)
- "I can already tell
you're my type, Jesse.
My late husband was kind of a cowboy.
He smoked unfiltered cigarettes
and drove an El Camino."
- Wow.
- What's an El Camino?
- It's kind of a car, truck,
hybrid kind of a thing.
No one really understands it.
I think we can pass on that one.
- Oh, here's one, Dad.
"I like to go dancing at the techno clubs
and walking in the park."
That's good.
"I know New York seems like a world away-"
(paper crinkling)
- Pass!
- "Dear, Jesse, my name is Chloe Walton,
I'm 32, blonde, five foot, eight,
and love the outdoors.
I'm a marine biologist and spent some time
in Alaska helping clean up
after the Valdez spill."
- All right, go on.
- "I'm enclosing a video
tape so we can have
a face-to-face encounter."
Oh, hm.
- Hm, well.
Let's throw it in.
- Mm.
- Hi, Jesse.
I really liked your
bio, but you know what?
I started thinking, well, I bet
a lot of women will as well,
so how do I make a lasting impression?
Well, maybe I'm not
really a marine biologist
and maybe I've never been to Alaska,
but I do have this going for me.
I hope you like it.
(Susannah gasps)
- Oh!
(Bridget laughing)
(children laughing)
- I can't believe that
woman just did that.
- Oh, my God.
- Wow.
- Well, kiddies, have we
learned our lesson today?
Hm?
Like maybe this isn't the best way
to set your dad up on a date!
- Dad, they're not all gonna be like this.
- They're not all gonna be anything,
'cause they're printing a retraction.
- You can't do that.
I mean, they're already out there.
- Well, then, then you three
are gonna use your allowances
to send every letter and package back.
- What, Dad, wait a minute-
- That is not fair-
- This is the last I wanna
hear about "Alaska Love."
- No, Dad.
- Can you-
- Ah, ah, ah, am I clear about that?
Now, go to bed.
Go on, go, go, go!
- Hm.
(Jesse sighs)
You were a little hard
'em don't you think?
- Oh and how exactly would you be
if they tried to play cupid with you?
- Well, I would've been a little upset.
Okay, I would've gone ballistic.
- Thank you.
(Susannah laughing)
- Good night, Jesse.
- Good night, Suze.
Thanks for all the help today.
- You're welcome.
(plane engine rumbling)
(mail bags thudding)
- Look, I-
- No, no, no, don't say it.
- Look, I tried-
- Ah, ah!
Not a word.
- I tried to talk 'em out of it.
- Oh, really?
- No.
(both laughing)
- [Burt] I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
(Burt snorting)
(plane engine rumbling)
- We expecting anyone?
- Oh, you got about a dozen lady callers.
I got all their names and numbers.
Three of 'em just flew into
Anchorage and wanna know
how to get out here right
away, but I just played dumb.
(both laughing)
- Please tell me that's a joke.
- No.
- Well, how did they find me?
- The magazine must've
leaked your telephone number
to the internet.
- Oh, give me that.
- It's only gonna get worse from here.
(fist knocking)
- Here they come.
(light music)
(Burt chuckling)
- Oh, my God, it's really you.
I can't believe I'm really standing here,
and you're standing there.
And I brought you these cigars
because I thought, flowers?
No, he's a man.
- I thought chocolate?
No, he might be a diabetic.
You're not are you?
Diabetic I mean.
- Excuse me, who are you?
- Maisie Lee from Chester, Pennsylvania.
- You didn't get my message?
- For five years I've
been reading "Alaska Love"
looking for Mr. Right.
- I've been divorced for six years now,
and you know how tough
the single scene is.
- All these blind dates and
trying to figure out what's in-
- And what's out.
- You know, trying to
always watch what you eat.
Well, you understand.
- Excuse me, had did you get out here?
- Oh, Mr. Langley was sweet enough
to fly me in on short notice.
- You know he has his own plane?
- Isn't that amazing?
- Every third person in Alaska
has his own plane, Maisie.
And listen, about the article,
I'm afraid there's been some mistake.
(door creaking)
(door slamming)
(truck engine rumbling)
(light swanky music)
Hey, Ruthie.
- Hey, Jesse, how you doing?
- Ah, you know.
- I'll get you right away.
(light swanky music)
Here you go.
- Thanks.
- Oh, Jesse, got some mail for you.
(light music)
(light swanky music)
- Jesse, I'm Margaret.
I just flew in from Tampa to meet you.
I hope that's all right.
- Well, Margaret, that's
very ambitious of you,
but I don't know what universe
that would be all right in.
- That's awfully rude after I
flew 3,000 miles to meet you.
- First of all, Margaret,
I didn't ask you to.
Okay and second of all,
I was polite to the first
dozen women who did it.
Now, I'm just fed up!
Now, if you'll excuse me.
(door creaking)
Please.
(Jesse groaning)
- Jesse.
- What?
- Don't bark at me.
- I'm sorry.
- You forgot your receipt.
- I'm sorry, thank you.
I'm sorry, if I see
another woman stalking me,
I'm gonna shoot first
and ask questions later.
- You're living the dream
of every damn man in Alaska.
And still you're not happy.
(light dramatic music)
(light swanky music)
- Last weekend, this woman
came all the way from Spain
and pretended to be on a fishing trip.
This was wearing this long
dress and these high heels.
- And of course Dad
knew why she was there,
but still took her fishing anyways.
- She lost her fancy shoes in the mud.
- Oh, God, I can't believe you guys
are doing this to your father.
- You know what?
I am glad he's meeting new women.
I think he's kind of enjoy it.
- Yeah, okay.
Dad puts on a really good
show of being all ticked off.
- Yeah.
- But he likes the attention.
- Hold that thought.
I wanna talk about this some more.
Is there anything else I can get you?
- Oh, another cop of coffee.
- Okay, sure.
Are you a photographer?
- A photojournalist actually.
These guys are climbing a glacier.
I'm gonna go along and document it.
- Oh, it's...
You work for that magazine?
(Gina chuckling)
- Hardly.
No, my sister gave me this as a joke.
I have to admit, this
bachelor looks pretty good.
Hm, he's probably airbrushed.
- No, actually, he, that's
pretty much what he looks like.
- You know him?
- Mm hm.
- You think you could introduce me?
(light dramatic music)
(Gina giggling)
(light music)
(somber music)
- Hey, again.
Jesse, this is Gina.
Gina, Jesse.
Gina is town for a few days and
she wants to see the sights,
so I thought why not the expert.
- Ah.
- You can show her
the lay of the land.
- Great, absolutely.
Here, why don't you join me?
I should get rid of
some of this stuff here.
Can you?
Thanks.
Here, let me get this for ya.
- Thank you.
Very sweet of you, thank you.
- [Jesse] Oh, so, how are you?
(muffled talking)
(Josie scoffs)
- So, tell me something.
I'm kinda curious.
Why on earth have you decided
to back one of the horses
vying for your ex-husband's affections?
- I don't know, I...
Maybe the kids had it right?
- Hm.
- Maybe Jesse is lonely.
- Mm.
- I mean, she seems nice.
- And people thought that-
- Are you serious?
- Yes, I'm very serious.
- Oh, yeah.
Very nice.
(Josie sighs)
(dishes clanking)
(birds chirping)
(water trickling)
- [Bridget] So, is your
eye mask helping you sleep?
- Yeah, I'm getting used to
this 24 hours of daylight.
I kinda like it now.
- Oh, you scared of the dark?
- My parents always fight at night.
That's when they fight most I mean.
What was it like when
your parents split up?
- I couldn't believe it.
I mean, I knew my mom felt
cutoff from the world out here,
and dad was always working so hard trying
to keep the business going.
I don't know, I guess (sighs),
I guess there's a lotta things that go on
that we don't always know about.
- And then they stop
caring if you know or not.
My parents started
screaming all the bad things
at each other and that's all I could hear.
- It wasn't really like
that with my parents.
Just kept getting quieter and quieter.
- End result's the same I guess.
(light music)
January fell away sorta
like feather to the ground
And the smiles that
used to haunt this place
Packed their bags
and headed outta town
- [Bridget] Hey.
Where will you go?
- [Photographer] All right,
everybody say cheese.
- [All] Cheese.
- Yeah?
- Hey, how are you?
Now your new found friend
Is this beginning of
a long, long journey
Or are we getting closer
to the end of January
January
Faith has come inside your eyes
Shining like a diamond in the rough
And laughter makes a good disguise
But tell me, baby, how is there enough
- Hey, having fun?
- Yeah, happy birthday.
You look good.
And who will you
(party guests laughing)
- Oh, there's a lotta food
when you're ready there.
- Burt.
Well, I say bravo to Josie.
Thank you very much, honey.
- My old lady.
- What did the mobster-
- Sam!
- Oh, here we go, Sam!
- Sam, I don't wanna hear it.
- [Jesse] It's her
birthday and she said no.
- [Josie] Oh it's, yeah, no.
Oh, come on.
- Hi.
- Hey.
- [Gina] I could make it after all.
- Oh, wow.
Here, let me.
Wow, hi.
- I hope it's okay.
- No, it's fine.
It is, it's great.
Good to see you, yeah.
Come on, let's make room here.
Yeah, we'll just slide everybody down.
No, here, why don't you.
Everybody, this is Gina.
- Hi.
- Hello.
- Nice to meet you.
- Everybody.
This is Bridget, it's her birthday.
Little vision in pink.
She's 16.
- Happy birthday.
- Thanks.
- And you know Susannah.
- Yep.
- That's our little girl, Hannah.
Uh, Suze and I got divorced two years ago.
- [Hannah] Mom, I have two sugar packets.
Isn't that when I stop?
(Susannah laughing)
- So, she's helping you
meet other women now?
- It was am amicable divorce.
- Oh, I'd say.
- I'd say.
It's good to see you.
Can I get you anything?
Glass of wine?
- I'll have some wine.
- Sure.
- Cake coming through.
- Oh!
- Oh, wow!
(party guests gasping)
- Look at this.
- Okay, time to sing
happy birthday to the birthday girl.
Bridget?
Bridge?
Where's Bridget?
- Where's Derek?
(lips smacking)
Whoa, whoa, hey.
- Bridget, honey.
- Hey, break it up.
- Bridget, Bridget.
- Hey!
- Oh.
- Honey, you have guests inside.
We'll talk about this later.
- Oh!
- Oh, my God.
(Susannah laughing)
(Jesse laughing)
- Oh, my God, my little girl.
- Break it up?
(Jesse laughing)
- [Jesse] That the first
thing that came out.
- Well, nothing happened.
They're just trying to figure it all out.
- Yeah, well, I don't want 'em
to figure it out too quickly.
Oh, man.
- So, I see you invited Gina?
- Yeah, that introduction you made
was under false pretenses.
I thought she was a friend of yours?
- And now, she's a friend of yours.
It seems to be going okay.
- Just curious why you'd
care how it's going?
Why you practically
arranged the whole thing?
- I just want you to be happy.
- Well, can't argue with that.
(dogs barking)
- Hi.
- Hey.
- So, you wanna talk about what happened
at your birthday party?
- No.
- You have anything you wanna ask me?
(Bridget chuckling)
- Um.
(Susannah sighs)
- Why don't you tell me about Derek?
- Okay.
I mean, I really like him a lot.
And he's great to talk to.
When he's actually talking.
- How do you feel when you're with him?
- I feel good.
You know, kinda safe.
Which is weird because
he's really insecure
and his family's a mess.
I mean, he doesn't even live here.
- But none of that matters.
- No.
- Mm mm.
- It just, I don't know
if sex is like love
or if it's just something
you do to get outta the way.
You know, with both of our
parents split up and everything,
we kind of wonder, you know,
can people actually make it work anymore?
Not that I wanna marry Derek or anything.
- Oh, no, no, we're just
talking about the sex part.
- Mm.
- Uh huh, okay.
Well, obviously I think you should wait.
Take your time.
It's a really big step, honey.
And I'm just old fashioned enough to think
that love comes first and then the sex.
- Yeah, that's what I was thinking.
- Good.
(Susannah giggling)
(gentle music)
(birds chirping)
(somber music)
- Hi, I'm Gina.
I'm a photojournalist, I'm a size one,
and your ex-wife just handed
me to you on a silver platter.
(Susannah sighs)
Oh, God, I'm such an idiot.
(light music)
(birds chirping)
- So, is living out here as
bad as you thought it would be?
- At least gramps has a satellite dish.
- Yeah, right.
Everybody comes to Alaska
so they can can five HBOs.
- [Derek] Wow, this is amazing.
- [Bridget] Yeah, I guess living in Alaska
does have some good parts.
- [Derek] This is pretty cool.
It's better than Hollywood
Boulevard, even Venice Beach.
I guess I could see how
you could stand it up here.
(water splashing)
(fishing reel clicking)
- So, you want it to
move really naturally,
so the fish just thinks that
it's a fly lazying in the water.
All right?
- Okay.
- [Sam] You're doing good.
You're doing really good.
(family laughing)
- Everything all right?
- [Burt] Who caught this?
- Yeah?
Not bad.
- Thank you.
- [Bridget] So, Dad, how
come Gina had to go back?
- Well, she does have a job, you know,
outside of entertaining you guys.
- But she's coming back, right?
- I take it that means you like her?
- Of course we do, Dad.
So what's the scoop?
- The scoop is Gina's fantastic.
You bloodhounds can call off the search.
- And then, Dad said we
could call off the search.
Gina's the one.
- Really?
- Mm hm.
- [Susannah] Wow.
Good night, honey.
- Good night, Mom.
- You okay, Mom?
- Yeah.
Yeah, I'm fine.
Hi.
- Hi.
- So, what happened with Gina?
- [Bridget] Oh, we had a great weekend
and then she had to leave for her job.
- Great, so your dad likes her, hm?
- Yeah.
- Mom, are you jealous?
(Susannah gasps)
- No.
No, I'm not jealous.
I just, you know, I hear she's the one.
So, obviously I'm gonna be curious.
- Well, he has fun with her,
but beyond that, I don't know.
- Okay.
Good night, honey.
- Night.
(soft music)
- [Jesse] Are you sure there's
no way I can stop this?
I mean, this is harassment.
- We have to give it to you.
What you do with it
from there is up to you.
(light music)
(mail thudding)
- [Susannah] "Dear Bachelor of the Month,
I'll start out by
admitting that I'm already
embarrassed about writing this letter.
But you'll never guess exactly why.
Something in your bio really
touched a chord in me.
I'm also divorced with three kids.
I love what the article said
about you never giving up
on your dream of building
a ranch in paradise.
My husband and I shared some
pretty amazing dreams at the start.
You seem to be proof
that people can move on.
You've made your dream a reality.
That gives me hope.
Take care, Sarah Jennings."
(light music)
- [Jesse] "Dear Sarah,
I'll start by saying
that you're the first
woman I've replied to since
the 'Alaska Love' article was published.
And it's not just because
you're the first sane one.
I don't really know how these things work.
Your words struck a chord in me too.
You really seem to understand the pure joy
I get from what I do.
That the picture on the
cover isn't a gimmick.
I may not be making a fortune,
but I'm living my dream everyday.
Sincerely, Jesse Stanton.
P.S., I have some regrets
about my past as well,
it's good to know I'm not alone."
(light music)
- Oh, hey, Mom.
- Hi, honey.
- What are you reading?
- Nothing.
- Okay.
(light music)
- [Bridget] "Dear Jesse,
thank you for the reply.
If I'm truly the only one, I'm flattered.
And it's not such a miracle
that I can tell what you really like.
I can see the integrity in you.
The love you feel for
your family and friends.
When you said, 'I may
not be making a fortune,
but I'm living my dream every day,'
it made me wonder if maybe
I gave up on my dream too quickly.
Okay, I'm gonna stop before
I really embarrass myself.
Take care, Sarah."
- [Burt] What's wrong?
(Jesse sighs)
- I've been exchanging letters
with this woman, Sarah.
- Cool, you wrote one back?
Must be something special.
Why don't you see this one?
- I don't know.
- Well, I think I do.
And it's got nothing to do
with this Sarah or even Gina,
as nice as she is.
You got another woman
on your mind, Susannah.
You still love her.
Why don't you just admit it?
I've been watching the two
of you and I don't get it.
Of course, I didn't get why you
broke up in the first place,
but all the signs are there.
At Bridget's party, I
thought the two of you
were gonna sneak away and make out.
- Well, Susannah was my
life for a long time.
You see, that's the point though.
She's my past.
I think Gina's my future.
(Burt sighs)
- Well, if you were happy
with that arrangement,
why are we having this conversation?
- We're not.
This never happened.
(dog barking)
(Sam sighs)
(bag rustling)
(computer beeping)
- [Bridget] "Dear Jesse,
I've been trying to
get you out of my head, but
it isn't working very well.
If you're having the same
problem, meet me for lunch at
Jenny's Cafe in Anchorage on
Tuesday the 10th at 1:00 p.m."
(light music)
If this ever gets to you
Will you know it's from me
Would you think it was a joke
Throw it back to the sea
Or do you, do you know
Everything I'm feeling
Do you know no one could love you more
Let me
Love you more
Love me
I'm so lost
Never felt so lonely
- Well, I won the case.
They said it was unwinnable.
I won it!
- Congratulations.
- Oh, of course you know what that means.
I've gotta head back
to Boston pretty soon.
But hey, Boston's a great town.
We got museums, we got restaurants,
you name it, we've got it.
I want you to come with me.
Think about it.
You can hop on a train and be in New York
or D.C. in a couple hours.
We got schools, your kids would love it.
Some of the best schools
in the world there.
- Stephen, my whole life is here.
- Well, you can make your
life anywhere you want.
You can.
I'm crazy about you.
You know that.
- Stephen, I, I can't.
I'm sorry.
- Well, I can't say it
comes as a total shock.
I mean...
Maybe I should've advertised
in that magazine too.
- Ugh, this has nothing
to do with my husband.
- Ex-husband, isn't it?
Well, this sure isn't how
I saw this day ending.
- I'm sorry.
- We need to talk.
- Do you mind knocking please?
- Mom has been writing letters
to dad pretending to be someone else.
- Yeah right.
- No, no, no, I saw the letters
and I followed her yesterday.
She arranged a lunch I guess to tell him,
and then just bailed on him.
- Well, why would she
do something like that?
- Because we screwed up.
- Mom still loves Dad.
- So, you mean we set Dad
up with some new girlfriend
when we could've been
setting him up with Mom?
- Do you guys even watch your
parents when they're together?
Of course they're still in love.
My parents, not in love.
The only problem is your
parents happen to be divorced.
- Oh, okay, well, maybe it's not too late.
I mean, and Dad, he likes Gina,
but there might still be time.
- Time for what?
(light music)
So, Gina, you really like our dad, huh?
- [Gina] Yeah, I do.
- Has he told you about
his little problem?
- [Gina] What's his little problem?
- He has six toes on each foot.
- Oh, really?
- No, seriously.
It's some genetic thing.
I mean, none of us got it,
but if he has any more kids
he could pass it on to them.
- [Gina] Oh.
- So, Gina was saying her
whole family lives in Chicago.
Brothers and sisters, everyone.
They sound pretty close.
You know, I bet she'd
have a hard time leaving.
- Well, your mom left her
family behind in Seattle.
You know, sometimes a woman
wants some independence.
You know, so she can
start a family of her own.
- [Bridget] Yeah, but that was mom.
She's a really independent person.
- Yeah, Gina doesn't really
seem like the independent type.
- No.
- Yeah, being a freelance
photographer and traveling
all over the world alone
is a sign a real dependent personality.
- Sometimes he'll just go into
the woods for like a year.
He says it helps him think.
- Yeah, Dad doesn't take
clean clothes or anything.
He says the experience needs to be pure,
and he'll only eat what he
can kill with his bare hands.
You know, when he comes
back he smells really bad,
and he's got a beard so thick
he almost looks like Bigfoot.
- Hm.
- Yeah, for a while,
we thought he was one of those guys
who keeps a stock of guns.
- [Sam] Or the Unabomber.
- [Bridget] Well, would
you ever wanna marry
someone like that?
- Oh, sweetie.
Look, if I ever wanted
to get married again,
you'll be the first to know, okay?
Well, maybe the second.
- I was just thinking because I think
she's gonna marry Stephen.
You see the way she
looks at him don't you?
- Yeah, it's pretty obvious.
(wood thudding)
- Well, your mom's a big girl.
She deserves to be happy.
- Yeah, she does.
- You told him what?
- But mom broke up with Stephen.
- Yeah, but she also
told us not to tell dad.
Which means she did it
because she still loves him.
- Wait a minute, how does that
give us permission to lie?
- Oh, come on, Sam, what Dad
doesn't know won't hurt him.
Anyways, all is fair in love and war.
- So, I'm hiking along with these guys
a group out of San Diego.
I had done a hike with them I don't know,
about four years before
that and it was July, right?
And they're hiking along
in tank tops and t-shirts.
I mean, they have absolutely no idea
that it goes below freezing after dark.
Why, why, why are you staring at my feet?
- I'm not.
(door slamming)
- Okay, who's idea was it to
tell Gina that I had 12 toes?
- Sam, I told you not to use that one.
- Yeah, but Kyle's dad has
six toes on his left foot.
I mean, it's not like it's not possible.
- Okay, that is the stupidest-
- You told me I could do
whatever I wanted to.
- Okay, hey, hey, hey,
hey, hey, hey, hey!
I know what you're trying
to do here, so stop it.
Okay?
I thought you guys liked Gina?
All right, it doesn't matter.
Since I am being
undermined in my own home,
I'm gonna make it up to
her and I'm gonna take her
to the Lancaster for the weekend.
I didn't need your interference before,
and I certainly don't need it now.
(door slamming)
- Good one, Sam.
- But-
- 12 toes.
(muffled talking)
- Your waiter'll be right with you.
Hi, guys, you hungry?
- Oh, wow, you're busy.
- We're a little busy today, yeah.
So, why don't you just,
I think there's a table.
Yeah, just opened up over there.
- Okay.
- I can't join you today
though, sorry.
- That's okay.
- Suze, Suze?
- Yeah?
- I'm sorry,
I know you're crazy right now.
I gotta know this.
Is it you?
- Is what me?
- Susannah, two glasses
of Chardonnay, table seven.
- Is it?
Okay, it's, it's busy.
Honestly, forget it.
- No, no, what?
What's the matter?
- The kids are just messing around.
It's all right.
While I have you though, could
you take 'em this weekend?
Gina and I, we're gonna spend some time,
you know, alone together.
- Oh.
- Yeah, she read about the Lancaster Hotel
in some tour book.
Now, so got her heart set on going there.
- Yeah, I can take the kids.
- Susannah, we're outta
mushrooms for the special.
What should we do?
What did I do?
(birds chirping)
- Okay, cough it up.
What's bugging ya?
- Jesse's taking Gina to the Lancaster.
- So?
They have been dating
for a while you know?
- No, you don't understand.
The Lancaster is where we were supposed
to go two years ago on our anniversary.
I had this beautiful romantic
trip to the city planned
and then he just canceled
at the last minute.
He had to lead some big corporate retreat.
You know, when this whole thing
started with the magazine,
I thought it was kinda funny.
Then I got curious, so
I wrote him a letter.
- Well, (sighs).
You're jealous, honey.
(Susannah sighs)
You're the only woman
Jesse's been interested in
for a very long time.
This was, this was inevitable.
Now, you gotta just figure out
if it's because you don't
wanna see him with anyone else
or you really want him back for yourself.
I better get back in there.
(birds chirping)
(smooth jazz music)
- This is amazing.
You know, apparently this
guy, Jacob Lancaster,
made his fortune in gold
at the turn of the century.
And he built this to lure his
fiancee away from New York City.
- Wow.
- Yeah.
- Did it work?
- Indeed it did.
They were together for
43 years blissfully.
Do you realize that tonight
is our one month anniversary?
I don't know if you intended that or not,
but it's awfully sweet.
(smooth jazz music)
What?
(Jesse scoffs)
- I kinda did a bad thing.
Not intentionally or anything,
but I just don't think
I'm really gonna be able
to enjoy being here.
- Am I the part that you're not enjoying?
- No, no, no, no, it's not that.
- Um, Jesse, I know that you like me.
Maybe you're just not ready for this.
- Well, it takes time.
- I think you know I'm
willing to put that time in.
Or we could just be friends.
I kinda wanna know now.
Maybe we should cut this weekend short.
- [Bridget] So, Mom,
you thinking about Dad?
- I wasn't until now.
- You sure?
- Yeah, I'm sure.
Why?
- Mom, we know it was you.
- You know what was me?
- The letters.
- What letters?
- To Dad.
- From Sarah.
Mom, I read the letters in your computer.
And I followed you the
other day to the cafe.
(Susannah sighs)
(Susannah chuckling)
- Okay, I wrote your dad some letters.
- You still love him.
Don't you?
- Yes, of course I still love him.
He's your father.
- You know what we mean, Mom.
(Susannah sighs)
- Yeah, I know what you mean.
(somber music)
But you know what?
Your dad and I could not make
our lives compatible before,
so what makes you think it's gonna be
any different this time?
(birds chirping)
- [Jesse] She doesn't
wanna give up her job
or at least adjust it for me, you know?
- That river down there supplies
some of the drinking water for Anchorage.
- Something Suze could never do.
- Could never do?
Jess, she did it for 15
years while you were off
blazing trails and rafting and fishing.
- She's the one who
left our marriage, Burt.
- Yeah, well, you're the one
that didn't give her much of a choice.
When you get down there,
throw away that fancy bottled
water and fill up with it.
That's the best you'll ever taste.
- We tried to, we tried to talk,
but we just always messed it up.
- Maybe you should've written it down.
(light music)
- I think these letters are from Suze.
Now, you read that part
about following your dreams.
Susannah is the only who has
ever understood me like that.
- I don't know, maybe you're right.
- Why would lie about it?
She hates lying.
And why did she stand
me up at the restaurant?
- Could be she chickened out.
That'd be perfectly understandable.
- I don't know, I think she's
doing it to mess with my head.
What if, what if she's the one that tried
to get the kids to break up me and Gina?
- Oh, give me a break.
Your kids don't need any help
to think up stupid ideas.
- That's true.
(Jesse groaning)
I don't know, Burt.
I think maybe I just need
to sit down face-to-face
with her and have a
chat with her you know?
- Face-to-face, the two of you?
Well, it's worth a shot.
(Susannah laughing)
- Also, listen to this.
Bridget wants to become a vegetarian now.
- I know, I heard.
- Yeah, I think that's Derek's influence.
- Oh, she's gonna be so
crushed when he goes back home.
- Ah, well, maybe not.
- What?
- I invited him back next summer
to work for me if he wants.
- Are you crazy?
- I know, I don't know.
He's a good kid, we just have to watch him
a little more closely.
- So, is everything good
or what?
- Oh, it's fabulous, Joey.
- Lovely, thank you.
- It's great, Joey.
- Now, that's what I like to hear.
Look at this.
Got a face on her like an angel.
I tell you, I must've
done something wrong.
You know the last time
I seen you two in here?
When your youngster was still a toddler.
- Are you kidding?
- I'm not kidding you.
You two enjoy yourself, huh?
I'll talk to you later.
- Thank you.
So, you wanted to talk
to me about something?
- Yeah, actually.
(Susannah sighs)
Remember we used to have
those long talks in school?
About the chances of meeting
your true love in college,
and the chances of there being only one?
- Mm hm, yes.
And we oh so logically
came to the conclusion
that there couldn't possibly be
just one right person for you.
- You still believe that?
- Well, we better believe it.
Otherwise we'll end up pretty lonely.
(gentle music)
- Okay.
So, listen, I wanna read you something.
I've been getting these letters.
Yeah, it's gonna sound like
one of those stupid things
in those romance novels
my mom used to read.
Here.
These letters are from this woman that...
She just seems to get me somehow.
Okay, where's that part?
Is this the one?
Yeah.
"When you said, 'I may
not be making a fortune,
but I'm living my dream everyday,'
it made me wonder if maybe
I gave up on my dream too quickly."
I don't really know how
to read into this further.
I worry still.
(gentle music)
Second chances.
(glasses clinking)
- Yeah, it was nice.
- [Jesse] It was.
It was nice.
(Susannah sighs)
(Jesse sighs)
- You have a plane to catch.
- Yeah, it's okay.
I know the pilot.
(Susannah laughing)
Good night.
- Good night.
(gentle music)
- I need, I need my jacket.
- Ah.
(Jesse laughing)
(gentle music)
(soft chiming)
(water splashing)
- [Bridget] Isn't the sky gorgeous?
- Yeah, in L.A., you can't see the sky.
The city just has this pink
haze over it every night.
- Why pink?
- I don't know.
- How about every night at 9:30,
we'll both go outside and
we'll look at the moon,
and then we'll be
thinking about each other.
- Bridge, for a girl who
struggles everyday to look cool,
that was pretty dorky.
(both giggling)
Why don't we just use the internet?
- Okay.
(birds chirping)
(light music)
Mom, we're home.
- Mom?
- Wake up!
- Ow, jeez.
(Susannah hushes)
- What do you mean (hushes)?
What?
- The kids are home.
- Mom?
It's 10 o'clock.
Mom is so busted if she's not up yet.
- What should we do?
- I don't know.
- What do you mean you don't know?
What am I supposed to do?
- You never let us sleep past-
- Mom, it's 10:00-
- Here we go.
(Susannah laughing)
- Dad?
- Hey.
- We're gonna go get some donuts.
- No, no, no.
- No, honey.
You don't need to go.
- It's okay.
- I told you guys.
- Mom, Dad, are you really back together?
(light music)
(Susannah laughing)
Dad's home.
- Oh, silly.
- Let's go, Mom.
- Okay, all right.
- I can't believe this.
- This is so cool.
- Well, I knew this was gonna happen.
Ever since Jesse told me he couldn't sleep
'cause he was staying up-
- Hey, Burt, Burt.
- All night reading your letters.
- Burt.
- My letters?
What...
You knew last night those
letters were from me?
- No, no, no, Suze.
- Jesse, what are you doing?
- No, no, no, no, no, it's not like that.
- What did you just wanna make me squirm?
Is that what's going on?
- Okay, hang on a sec.
- What for your personal entertainment?
- No, listen, wait a minute!
You're the one writing letters and putting
somebody else's name on the bottom.
You're the only one getting to play games?
Suze, come on, give me a break here.
- I think you should leave.
- Suze.
- Now, now!
- Mom, please, Mom.
- No, Mom, this isn't fair.
- No, everybody needs
to get out of this room,
and you need to get dressed.
I want everybody out!
(somber music)
- Jess.
- No, I'm not talkin' to you.
- How was I supposed to know
you hadn't told her yet?
- No, no, no, no, you don't just offer up
random information in
a situation like that.
I had things under control.
- This is ridiculous.
You're both adults, you wanna be-
(luggage thudding)
- I am just so angry!
- [Josie] I don't see what the problem is?
- The problem is he lied.
- Yeah, well, so did you, Sarah.
(Josie laughing)
- Whose side are you on?
- Oh, you two.
You're both acting like second graders.
Neither one of you wants to blink first
in this stupid little game
you're playing, do ya?
- What do you suggest I do?
- What do you want to do?
- [Announcer] Flight 232-
- Okay, come on, Derek.
We gotta go.
- Is now boarding.
- I'll meet you inside, son.
- Thanks, Gramp.
- Jesse.
This isn't exactly the way
I planned to tell you this.
But I'm thinking of retiring
and moving Ellen and me into town.
Maybe you should sell-
- What?
- The ranch and do the same thing.
It would be easier to run
your business from Anchorage.
- Sell the ranch?
Give up the dream I've
worked for my entire life?
- You want your wife back?
(somber music)
- [Josie] Okay, honey,
I'll see you tomorrow.
- Yeah.
- Just go outside a minute.
- Bye.
- I'm driving you home.
- Yeah?
(somber music)
(keys jingling)
(fishing line whooshing)
(birds chirping)
- If any of you are interested,
I've got an idea to get
mom and dad back together.
- Yeah, like putting an article of dad
in a personals magazine?
- Give it up, Bridge, we tried.
- No, they want this and you know it.
(Sam sighs)
- All right, what were you thinking?
- Okay, we can make a world
where they can both be happy.
You know that service road
they've been building forever?
Well, it's done.
- I didn't think they'd ever finish that.
- Well, now, you don't have
to fly all the way out there.
And it's only like a 70
minute drive from Anchorage.
It's still remote enough for dad,
but not so far outta the city
that mom's gonna go crazy.
So, what do you think?
(light music)
- Hm.
- [Bridget] I think this
could really work this time.
- Yeah, I think I've heard
that from you before.
I mean, whenever we do what you tell us,
we get grounded.
- Yeah, and mom and dad
still end up mad at each other.
- Well, fine then, we'll get grounded.
'Cause I can tell all mom and dad
need is a push, a solution.
I think this plan could be it.
- Don't you kids think
you've done enough already?
- Yeah, your parents have been
pretty patient up until now,
but I think they're
reaching a breaking point.
- [Bridget] Come on, we
can't stop when we're ahead.
- No, she's right.
They're back together,
they just don't know
that they're back together.
- Even if your idea could work,
how could you get two people
that stubborn to sit down and talk?
- Good point.
- I gotta go, the kids called.
There's some emergency at the ranch.
I don't know how I'm gonna
get a flight in this late.
Oh, boy.
- Take the new road.
It's finally open.
- You got the candles, Bridge?
- Yeah, they're over there.
- All right.
Hurry up with that letter, Hannah.
- Hannah, could you
grab an end for me here?
How's that floor coming, Burt?
- [Burt] Oh, it's a thing of beauty.
(soft music)
- Oh, you missed a spot.
(light music)
(plane engine rumbling)
(soft music)
- Don't say a word.
(light joyous music)
- Welcome to the Stanton Ranch B and B,
where you can leave all your
worldly cares at the door.
- All my worldly cares, huh?
- She read it in a book.
We thought it was kinda catchy.
- You know, I think what you guys
are doing is really special-
- Please step into our parlor room,
where guests can mingle and
relax or simply read a book.
Oh and don't forget to
sign our guest book.
- And come into our dining room,
where guests can enjoy
a delectable, delicious,
and elegant meal.
- Prepared of course by
our master chef, Hannah.
- Dinner will be served in 10 minutes.
Would you like freshly
prepared appetizers?
Try one.
(Susannah laughing)
- And if you'll join us
upstairs to the guest rooms.
(light joyous music)
Um, this is the Kodiak Suite.
- This is our Alpine Suite.
- And this is the New Dawns
Suite, our finest culmination.
(gentle music)
So, can you picture it?
And now that you can use the road,
people can come from all over.
And I mean, a bed and
breakfast would be great
for Dad's business.
And Mom, think about the
restaurant you can make
with the romantic setting.
(door creaking)
- What?
What's going on?
- Hi, Dad.
- Hi.
Uh, the, the kids seem to think
that we could turn this place into a,
a full service B and B.
- Together.
- Why don't we go and swing on the swings.
- Oh, no, no, that's okay.
I'm just-
- Sam, let's go
swing on the swings.
- Hey, ow, jeez.
- [Bridget] Hi, Dad.
- A B and B, huh?
Well, it would take more than this.
I mean, we'd need some renovation money.
(gentle music)
- Well, the restaurant...
Well, it's worth quite a bit.
- Yeah, I mean, it's been a good year.
I've been able to just squirrel some away.
What do you think?
- How's Gina?
- Well, she got back from
her trip and she dumped me.
She was too perky anyway.
How's Sebastian?
- We actually, we broke
up a couple weeks ago.
'Cause he was too (sighs).
He wasn't you.
- I love you.
- Well, that's a relief
'cause I love you too.
(gentle music)
- We're gathered today,
in the presence of family
and friends to join in holy
matrimony Susannah and Jesse.
Marriage is a sacred union.
(Jesse sighs)
It is truly a journey.
Jesse, do you take Susannah to love,
honor and cherish forever?
- I do.
- Susannah, do you take Jesse to love,
honor and cherish forever?
- Yeah, I do.
- By the power vested in
me by the state of Alaska,
I now pronounce you
husband and wife, again.
(both laughing)
(family applauding)
(gentle music)
(light music)
(light chiming)