- Sorry about being a, you know.
- It's okay, I deserve it.
I am a loser.
Boo!
- You're just--
- A square?
- You're with this square?
- Yeah, but I went out with you!
Johnny Keen.
- They're coming!
- Who, where, what...
The Martians! - Just calm down!
Martians everywhere man!
- Whoa man, what are they smoking?
- No way!
Smells like shit, this tastes legit!
They turned my friends into zombies!
- Have you been smoking the marijuana?
- See!
Marijuana makes people crazy!
They whack people with hatchets!
- Government propaganda man!
- I think that's a house!
- Ya! - What do you
hooligans doing here?
- There's an army of zombie beatniks...
- Did you say zombies?
Head for the tool shed
in back!
Go, dammit!
Stop those Martians from coming in!
- Let's rock!
♪ Well, the news of the saucer been a-flyin' around
♪ I'm the only one that seen it on the ground
♪ First thing I seen when I saw it land
♪ A cat jumped out and he started a band
♪ Flyin' saucer rock and roll, flyin' saucer rock and roll
♪ But the crazy beat just a dropped me dead
♪ I couldn't understand the things they said
D-Day children!
Hold it right--
you beatnik zombies!
Don't move!
You're beatnik zombies, aren't ya?
I'm no beatnik zombie!
Put that contraption down!
What, the camera?
Put it down! - You're not gonna
shoot us are ya?
Why shouldn't I?
We're lost!
Lost?
Yeah yeah, we just want to go home!
I was lost once.
Now for a long time.
I guess we could find you a way home.
Uh, come on in then!
Come on!
Okay.
Go inside!
Wow, check this place out.
Well make yourself to home.
Cool.
Sit!
Just, just.
Uh, here.
What's that?
- Peace offering.
You know, like, like a candy bar.
You do know what a candy bar is, right?
Should have brought steak flavor.
- Oh!
Eww.
What else you got?
Uh, I got some, uh, water.
- What kind'a glass is that?
Um, it's plastic.
Kind of like glass, except unbreakable.
- Like bakelite.
- Plastic.
- What year is this?
Uh, 2005.
- Jumpin' jalopies!
What year did you think it was?
- I don't know, hell I thought it was, 1900 and 67?
- So sir, um, why are you out here?
Uh, why, why did you stay out here in the wild?
- Martian zombies.
Shut up bitch,
and just give me the camera.
Please sir, about the zombies?
- I don't even know if it really even happened now.
Maybe because it didn't?
- Guess it was, like a dream, and also
it faded away, and... - If you
don't shut up I'll kill you,
this is the greatest thing that...
- All I wanted to do is stay alive.
Excuse me, Indie.
Trevor go outside.
- I did stay alive I don't know why I stayed alive.
About the Martian zombies?
- I got to stay alive I guess it's so I--
Please sir, about the zombies?
- Yeah I remember!
I remember!
Frankie and I, we, ran all around
in his Skyline convertible.
Every girl wanted to ride in that convertible.
That Skyline was red and white, and...
Except Susie, she didn't like Frankie.
But, he didn't care, he knew he was gonna date her.
One day, Frankie and I go into Pop's Soda Shop,
and there's Susie in there, Peggy Sue sitting at a booth.
We saunter up.
They're looking pretty as can be.
Quit daydreaming Rocky,
let's go!
Is this Johnny boy's car?
Yeah, Johnny boy.
- Let's go say hi to him.
- I can't believe you're doing this!
- He's kind of cute.
Do you?
A total square.
- A bet is a bet.
Even.
- Hey Susie!
- Hey Frankie, Rocky.
Who you waiting for?
- Oh, wouldn't you like to know?
- A pretty thing like you shouldn't be kept waiting.
- Don't you start!
- How about coming to the Grange with me tonight?
There's a rockabilly show.
- Look, even if I could leave,
I wouldn't leave with you.
What, you too good for me?
- Go away!
I hear Betty's looking for you.
- Come on, you know you want some sugar daddy!
- Go away!
- What?
I didn't order two shakes.
You guys order two shakes?
You're with this square?
Hey you guys. - Oooo,
Johnny and Susie.
Nothing's happening, we're just...
- I think those are for me!
- No, these aren't,
the, these are for Susie and me.
- Don't you like me?
I thought you liked me, Johnny?
Well gee, I--
You don't?
- I like you.
Yeah, I do.
Really, its...
It's just that--
- I'll give it to her.
Ooop!
Johnny Keen, now look what you did.
- No!
It's, it's just that my--
- Yeah?
You're mommy gonna kill you?
Poor Johnny baby.
- No!
Fine.
- You kill my Johnny, but that's why I like you.
Just not enough to kick your butt.
- Go away!
I mean, leave please?
- Why don't you go ahead and make me?
Come on tough guy, I'll give you one shot for free.
Go ahead, come on, weeny!
What are you waiting for?
Boo!
- Stop it, just stop it!
- Little Susie doesn't want us making fun
of her Johnny baby!
Johnny baby!
We better get out of here
before we get hurt!
Bye bye Johnny baby!
And Susie, give me a call when you want a real man.
Johnny baby, ha ha ha...
- I'll let you know when I see one!
Can we get out of here?
Even your car is a loser!
Ug!
Someone please wake me up from this nightmare!
- Sorry!
Dad warned me about the voltage regulator.
- Like I care!
Push this heap of junk out of here now!
- Rufus and the guys better get here soon.
Yeah, so...
- Do you have to do that?
- Sorry, so I'm nervous, I would sing it but,
I thought it might bother you.
It's just a silly song my grandpa sang.
I don't know why I sing it.
It's really stupid, it's stuck in my brain.
It's weird, I feel better after I sing it.
♪ BS makes the grass grow green
♪ The cow, he eats the grass
♪ The farmer, he milks the cow
♪ And we drink the BS from the glaaaaass.
- Sorry about being a, you know...
- It's okay.
I deserve it.
I am a loser.
- You're just...
Different?
- Yeah.
- A square?
- Well Einstein is different.
And he's not a square.
- Yeah, Einstein's not cool.
- Yeah he is!
- Right, you'd go out with him?
- No!
But I went out with you, Johnny Keen.
So um,
you want to go up to Lover's Peak?
Uh, I mean it's what all the cool kids
are doing on a Saturday night, right?
- Sure!
We're cool!
- The coolest. - Yeah!
You, me, verse...
Coal, black, asphaltic,
steamy enslavement of the void,
empty, E equals MC squared.
Square root, root canal, pain,
of the impossible journey to see
translucent Martian brothers, pie in the sky,
rhubarb Mars, crimson with ire,
I tire of the time, space, conundrum, ho-hum.
Infeasible tract, restore primitive man,
ape, neanderthal, ignorant, low-brow, biped,
oblique, ori-eyed vibrations, discord,
dispeace, disharmony, disunity, dissension,
dissidence, dis-service to serve to me,
to serve tea, to me?
Misunderstood we, cerebral fiber, chaotic,
door to enlightenment, key stoned, of my soul.
Yeah dig it!
Jive it my brother.
- Dig it.
- My man Maynard, are you next?
- Well, I-- - Why you standin'?
You were gonna walk the weasel!
- Lumber the louse, ramble the rascal!
- Sweat the snake?
- Amber reptile, slither earth-bound.
- Bits of pepperoni strangle the Stradivarius.
- Squeeze spicy sausage classical--
- And hit him, with a Maynard.
- Main miniscule Maynard man.
- You need help finding little Maynard man?
Isn't that why Edna left you,
she couldn't find little Maynard?
- Ooooo...
- Ooo!
- Burn on Maynard.
- Don't get lost!
- Oom-pah-pah! - And don't piss yourself!
- Well, arithmetic makes me feel so stupid.
I guess I am.
I don't know, I just don't get it.
- You're not.
I know you're probably real smart.
- I barely get C's.
- Grades don't mean anything.
You don't necessarily have to be smart to get A's,
just good at taking tests.
- Really?
- Sure.
Like math.
- Uh hmm.
- It's one of those subjects
that you have to see from just the right angle.
You take the Grand Canyon.
If you were driving by, you wouldn't even know it was there.
Or in a plane at 30,000 feet.
But, if you were to stand at the edge,
it hits you.
It's so clear it's, simple, magnificent.
- Really?
You make it sound so...
Exciting. - I do?
- Uh hmm.
I never thought math could be so...
- Logical?
- Engaging.
- Yeah.
Uh, I know if, if you saw it from just the right angle,
you'd be a whiz.
- Can you now...
Demonstrate, these angles?
- Whoa...
- Whoa!
- Whoa man, what are they smoking?
- No man, what have we been smoking?
We come in peace, brother man.
You need to slow down.
- Martians!
Cool man.
Do my eyes deceive?
What's this?
- Atomic tea man?
Chemical cranium
expander man.
It's the good shit.
- Cool man, been smoking the wicked tea?
Damn!
- Ugh...
- Your dog roll this man?
- No man, he birthed it man.
Ooo!
- Tea.
- Tea, yeah I can dig it man.
- Tea, you smoke it.
- No way man, that's some foul shit!
- It's good, makes you feel good!
- You smoke it man!
I don't think these guys are playing around.
- Okay.
I don't know where he's gonna put that thing.
Sure ain't gonna smoke it.
I think we better smoke it man.
Spread the tea, man!
Yeah how is it man?
Oh man!
Smells like shit, this tastes legit!
You said it man!
- Hmm.
And then, the Martian said,
take me to your wiener!
Here, you got to try it Chet.
- Women!
Women.
- Chicks, I can dig it man.
- Party with chicks man...
- Good tea man!
- We could probably scare up a few chicks.
- Might be scary looking though man!
- Find us 10 Earth women.
Bring them back to here.
Build a cage for you.
Bring them here.
We need women!
Women, women...
Our planet is without women,
we need their ovaries.
Now get 10 women, bring them back.
And when you have them, press this green button.
This is very simple.
Do you understand.
Wow, I didn't know Lover's Peak
was so far away.
Just have a little patience.
Okay, I am, but I got to go,
I have a curfew, and I have to--
Shhh!
It's worth the wait.
♪ My heart's broken, and you're to blame
♪ You left me alone
♪ Thought is was love, but it was your game
♪ You left me, all alone
- You should leave it on.
♪ I don't need a light
♪ All I need is you to come
♪ And wipe these tears from my eyes
♪ Early in the fall
- You have, uh, something in your glasses.
- I'm so blind without these.
- Here, I'll do it.
♪ The Vegas lights took my only one
♪ And left me with desire
- Are you, are you finished?
- Almost there.
- Do I have something on my face?
- I think there is.
- They're coming man!
I'm sorry, I didn't mean--
- They're coming!
- Well, where, what?
- Martians!
- A weirdo! - Give me my glasses!
- We have to split the scene man!
- Who are you? - We have to tear away!
- What are you doing in my dad's car?
- The Martians!
Let's calm down! - The Martians everywhere man!
Calm down-- - Go!
- Let's calm down and figure out
what this is all about!
Who's late, what, what's happening where?
- I was in the woods, with my friends, these beatniks...
Martians came down, in this flying saucer...
- Hey Rufus I thought you said Jax was gonna be here?
- He said he'd be here.
- Hey what's that over there?
- It's just a rat.
- Hey look I think he's smoking a joint!
- And then I saw your car!
So let's split man!
- Look at him!
He's crazy!
And even if he isn't, he's a beat!
And you can't trust beats!
- You can too!
- Can not!
Would you trust someone dressed like that?
And besides, beats do the marijuana!
- So?
- Haven't you ever seen Refer Madness?
Marijuana makes people crazy!
They whack people with hatchets!
- Government propaganda man!
J. Edgar Hoover does tea, and he wears lady's underwear,
and I don't see him putting hatchets in peoples' heads!
- You know, when was the last time you saw J. Edgar Hoover?
Was he wearing your underwear, man?
- Have you been smoking the marijuana?
- See?
Listen to me, you can't trust him.
He'll put a hatchet in your head!
- Beat to L-seven!
Get the penolopie, on the go!
- Maybe we should just go back to town?
- Now you're speaking the language of sense, man!
Back to town!
Back to where we need to be, free from here!
Feminine fanati-- - We'll take you back
as far as town.
- The sweet sound of town man!
Let's put some pavement between
this place daddy-o!
- Dang!
- Dammit Johnny!
You are so stupid!
Why am I so stupid?
Why am I even here?
How could I even think it was possible!
- Let's get this sled, sliding man!
What's up with the breaks in our existence?
Always have to suck out our brain!
Please make this baby run--
- Shut up you hairy ferret!
- They'll get you man!
An army of zombies man!
- Leave him!
- Aren't you coming?
- They're coming man!
- How safe will you be in the car?
- They're waiting for you man,
the legion of the lifeless!
Listen!
I hear 'em!
Listen to the sound of your doom man!
They'll ambush you!
- I'll take my chances outrunning them.
You wanna wait for them to open up your head
and eat your brain like it was Jello?
- Leave the beat freak!
You can walk with us, if you shut up!
- You shut up!
- Don't tell me to shut up, you shut up!
- Shut up!
- Will both of you shut up!
Ow!
Shush! - Ow, ow!
Susie you hear anything?
- Don't tell me you believe the creep?
- Listen.
Let's get off the road.
My dad's gonna kill me!
- I wouldn't worry about your dad.
They're gonna kill us.
- You don't understand, it took me six months
to get my dad to let me drive his car.
Now I got zombies making a mess out of it!
- Who cares about your stupid dad,
or your stupid car!
- Yeah.
I do!
You wouldn't know, you don't have parents Maynard,
beats are hatched!
Baby...
- Let's go!
Leave him!
What are you doing?
Let's go!
Help!
Ignore it, it's a trick!
Help me!
Don't Johnny!
- Help me man!
- You could have done this yourself!
- It proves you care man.
- Watch out Johnny!
- That's for taking Edna, man!
- I think that's a house!
- Well then what are we waiting for!
- A goose from a zombie, man!
I'm a cool cat, I'm no back-burner man.
Ya! - Do you have to do that?
Move over there!
What are you hooligans doing here?
Speak up!
No secrets among friends.
You are friends?
'Cause I bury my enemies.
There's an army of zombie beatniks, man!
They're gonna suck out our brains!
The end is near, daddy-o...
- Did you say zombies?
Recognize this?
Why?
- The Martians gave one to Jack!
- Who's Jack?
- He's my friend.
No, he's a jerk.
And now he's a zombie. - Know what it's for?
Well I'll tell ya!
When they're done with your friend...
- He's not my friend.
- Shut up!
Your friend's gonna push this here button
signaling the Martians, and it's all over.
It's all too late.
Don't let him push this here button!
They've come back.
- Back? - About 30 years ago,
Martians came for our women.
Took 10.
Something about repopulating their planet,
or some cockamamie story like that.
I imagine they've come for 10 more.
Took my Millie.
I still have nightmares
of them Martian freaks on top of my Millie.
- If it's any consolation sir,
they probably use this new scientific technique
I've been reading about.
- What the hell are you talking about?
- It's not the birds and the bees thing,
they use science.
Johnny!
- Or something-- - They turned my boys
into zombie freaks!
Those lazy space bums made my boys do their dirty work!
- That was just a story!
- Well I lived it!
I had to kill my boys.
I'll never forget that day.
How do we know he's not one of them?
- We don't!
- Well, I guess there's only one way to know for sure.
Wait!
He saved us!
- Get to the kitchen!
Horse feathers!
Looks like I'll be joining ya' soon, Millie!
Get to the tool shed in back!
I'll hold them off long enough!
Go you dumb kid!
I'm an old man, you got your whole life ahead of you!
Go dammit, stop those Martians from coming in!
And god dammit, destroy that box!
- Johnny, let's go!
- Bar up the door!
- What are you doing?
- With an army of zombies seconds from killing us,
and you're worried about--
- Getting your clothes dirty?
- You gonna golf all day?
Hand me a nail, chicky!
Flapping your tongue
isn't gonna get us anywhere!
- Ogling Oscar Mayer is?
Man!
- We should have let you
to be moronized by your zombie friends!
Man! - At least they had more
brains than you, chicky!
- If you call that brains I wouldn't want any of it!
Back!
- Enough lollygagging, chicky!
Man!
♪ Out of the shadows, came our hero, one dark night
♪ Wearing thick black glasses, gonna set things right
♪ However unlikely, a hero he would be
♪ And they called him
♪ John-ny Keeeeen
♪ Johnny was not a likely hero
♪ No one ever thought he'd be the one
♪ But he rolled up his sleeves
♪ And he wrangled all his friends
♪ In the hopes of saving everyone
♪ Everyone
♪ Many evils can be found here on Earth
♪ And many can be found far away
♪ Martians came from a far off cloud
♪ To take our women away
♪ So Johnny built a ray gun and Johnny built it right
♪ For the day of reckon is tonight
♪ Johnny hope you're on the ball
♪ And make sure you give your all
♪ 'Cause Martians and zombies
♪ Are revved up and ready to fight
♪ Heeya
- Let's rock!
- What's that man?
- It is a replica of a ray gun
found at the Roswell crash site.
With one minor difference,
ours is lacking the Martian power source, so...
- That's about your size.
- Suffering from envy, chicky?
- Enough lollygagging!
Shut up!
- D-Day, children!
Maynard!
Susie, grab the saw!
My arms are getting tired!
Not mine!
- Where are they all coming from?
There's too many of 'em, I'm gonna blow a fuse!
We're gonna have to make a run for it!
Dang it!
Let's go!
What are you doing?
Come on!
- She'll be okay!
They need her man, they won't hurt her, remember?
We need to split!
We need to split like now!
Try it now!
- We can't leave her!
I've got to go back! - Be wise my man,
we need help!
We can't do it alone!
She's okay!
Use your cranium, gymnasium!
How long do you think we'll last?
They'll turn us into zombies man!
You know that!
You can't save Susie that way!
- They won't get away with this!
- I know, daddy-o, but in the meantime
let's speed, get some help man!
Where you going?
Do you know where you're going?
Let me go!
- We're lost man.
Admit it, we're lost.
- You lousy stinking beatnik!
This all your fault!
My first real date, with a cute girl,
now she's a zombie!
- She's not!
They don't make chicks zombies man, right?
Besides, if you were generous enough to call that a date,
you wouldn't know what to do with it man.
- I would to!
- Name your last date before this one.
This is your first date with someone other than your sister.
- I don't have a sister!
- Fine, your mother.
- Like you would know what to do with a girl like Susie?
- Sure, beats are cool cats.
Cool cats get the chicks man.
Chicks can't resist cool cats.
It's a fact!
It's a fact man.
- So where is Edna? - Shut up!
- The big bad Casanova beat couldn't keep Edna!
- Shut up man! - You gonna make me?
- Maybe!
- Maybe?
Baby!
♪ So I grabbed my and I put 'em in a sack
♪ Went on down to that railroad track
We interrupt this program
to bring you an up-to-the-minute
news bulletin!
Reports of strange lights and flying saucers,
I repeat, flying saucers have been pouring in
from all over the county, and now there's
zombie attacks on females!
Citizens are all advised to stay at home,
hide your women, and above all, lock your doors!
I repeat, lock your doors!
That is all.
- I didn't know a square could put down.
- I guess we're both hits with the chicks.
- You'd make a cool beat.
- Thanks.
You'd make a good square.
I don't know if
I should be thankful, man.
- Listen!
Listen man!
Listen you stupid muscle head!
- Think so?
- No.
Maybe a little.
Listen, really listen...
I propound that if we follow that sound,
we can find Susie,
or if we go in the opposite direction,
we can get help.
Now that that understanding washes over
your suburban brain, I recommend
that we go in the opposite direction and get help,
and go back and save your fair maiden.
- What are we waiting for?
- A goose from-- - Don't bring Goose
into this conversation.
- What are you doing?
Don't, stop, put me down!
Stop, help!
Help, help!
- Ain't no way out.
- If there was a way out we wouldn't be in here.
- Do you think we're stupid?
- You're too good?
- Let's go daddy-o!
- Wait!
- Look, I know we're from different sides of the tracks,
but, given the situation, I think we should call a truce,
until, or if we ever get out of here.
- Hey man could you pass me the five-eighths?
This one's a little bit too small.
Yeah yeah yeah.
Thanks. - Whatever.
Hey what are you?
Let go of that, let go of that!
- Hurry up we're gonna be late for the Chop Top show!
What's the problem man, come on hurry up!
Let's go!
Come on man what are you doing?
Let go, give me the wrench!
No!
There it is!
The Grange Hall, let's go!
- I thought I was so smart.
Now look at me.
I suppose, in a way, I deserve this.
It was cruel.
I mean, he really likes me, and there's just no way...
- You suburban types can't get past looks.
Maybe we can because we don't have the luxury.
We just don't pay that much attention to the obvious.
If you do, I think you'll miss out on the guy
that you're meant to be with.
- What Einstein is saying,
maybe you should give this guy a second look.
- I'm Susie.
- Betty.
- I'm Candy.
I warn you, call me Candice, and I'll bust your chops.
Oh you like my jacket?
It's a letterman jacket, don't you know?
Isn't that great?
Oh, did you see the game, yeah, the defense?
We pulled the lunch,
we were in the pressure cooker for a minute.
- Jumpin' jalopies!
- Where are you pukes going?
- We have to save the world!
- You do that!
But remember, when I'm done here,
I'm gonna kick both your butts!
- Frank, if you're smarter than you look,
you'd stay in the back seat.
- What's that supposed to mean?
- Forget it, we don't have time to waste on you!
Hey come back here!
- Come on Cathy I want to get out of here.
- Jeez Louise Veronica
could we just wait a few more minutes?
They promised they'd be here.
- Oh they always promise they'll be here!
- Oh look, there they are right now!
I don't remember Jimmy having a limp.
- No, me neither.
- Hey guys, this is a private party.
Yeah, invitations only!
♪ It's getting late
♪ Backstage queenie
♪ And I could hardly wait
♪ You'll have to close him down
♪ Backstage queenie
♪ She's a long way around
♪ Backstage queenie,
♪ Backstage, backstage queenie
♪ Oh backstage queenie, you're too good for me.
♪ Backstage, she's a backstage queenie
Thank you!
What the hell?
- Can I have your attention please?
- Hey man come on get off the stage!
Let's see what this clown has to say.
- Hello!
The world's gonna end tonight.
We're all gonna die!
They're are zombies outside!
Listen, you bunch of hillbilly hicks!
The Martians have landed, they want our women!
- What the hell you been drinking?
- Yeah or smoking!
Listen, I'm serious!
Please listen!
- No you listen!
We're not gonna let you wreck our party
or scare our chicks!
Yeah!
- I don't have to!
The zombies will be here in a minute!
This is what they look like!
You gotta be kidding!
- Hey man this is not cool!
All right man...
- Real nice.
Uh, we're gonna play a little number for you guys,
sorry about that...
Stay away from our chicks!
- What the hell? - We're fighting!
- Not gonna let these guys wreck our party!
- Come on guys, get 'em!
I got the funny looking one!
- Come on, let's go!
- Let's go, you know what I mean?
- No, these freaks...
Go, let's get 'em!
Let's go!
They're moving pretty slow.
Let's kill these guys!
Come on bitches!
Going down!
I'm taking you down, freaks!
Get down!
♪ Well, the news of the saucer been a-flyin' around
♪ I'm the only one that seen it on the ground
♪ First thing I seen when I saw it land
♪ A cat jumped out and he started a band
♪ Flyin' saucer rock and roll, flyin' saucer rock and roll
♪ I couldn't understand a thing they said
♪ But the crazy beat just knocked me dead
- Hey baby...
♪ Well the little green men, they were real hep-cats
♪ Rockin' and a-rollin' to the crazy flats
♪ They brought out a sax - I got this guy!
♪ and they started to blow
♪ They brought out the drums and they started to roll
- Get him rooky!
- Yeah!
Oof!
Take this!
♪ I couldn't understand a thing they said
♪ But the crazy beat just knocked me dead
What now?
♪ Well, I come out a-hidin' and I started to rock
♪ Little green men taught me how to do the bop
♪ They were three foot high, hit a few bars
♪ Started rock and roll
♪ All the way from mars
♪ Flyin' saucer rock and roll, flyin' saucer rock and roll
They're getting away with the girls!
Come back with our chicks!
♪ Crazy beat just knocked a me dead
- I'm gonna kill you!
God dammit!
He didn't know what hit him!
Come on you freaks!
He said that feels good, doesn't it?
Man, is everyone okay out there?
I guess the kid with the ray gun was right.
- We've got some unfinished business!
- Frankie, have you seen these zombies take girls?
- Yeah, a couple ran off
just a little while ago, down that--
Ooo!
Ooo ooo ooo ooo!
- Shhh!
Shh!
- Go!
- Stop!
- Johnny!
- Susie!
Let her go!
Let 'em all go!
- Yeah, let us go you lunkheads!
- Johnny!
Toss the cord!
- Overdrive!
- Creep, take that!
Jerk!
That was easy.
Yeah we did it!
- Saved the world!
A beat and a square saved the world!
- Dude, shouldn't you find Susie!
- Thanks for saving my life!
- You're welcome!
- Candy.
- Maynard.
- Is there still something on my face?
- There sure is.
- Aww...
- What do you guys think about my gun?
Isn't it the coolest?
- Like you, Johnny!
- You're pretty cool Johnny, even for a square.
- You're a square?
- Was, now I'm just me.
- So, how are we supposed to get home?
- It's a nice night out for a walk.
- What are we waiting for?
- A goose from a zombie?
Don't!
- I just wanted to get your goose.
- Well if it's not my favorite pukes!
- Get lost Frank!
- You'll have to ask nicer than that,
and maybe I'll go out with you.
- Come on Frank, it's late, can we finish this tomorrow?
- What are you doing?
- Trying to be nice.
Get along.
- You won't embarrass me again.
- Can we have a ride?
- How much money you got?
- Is that offer still good?
You know the one where I can take my best shot?
- Oh, uh, yeah.
Can't do it.
It's just that we're friends, Frank, and,
gosh, it just doesn't seem right.
- Yeah really?
Johnny, baby...
- Are we finished now Frankie baby?
Are you sure, Frankie baby?
I mean, we really didn't even get started.
I'm not having fun yet, are you?
Maybe next time.
Oh yeah, Frank, can I borrow your car?
- Jumpin' jalopies!
I gotta get out of here!
Beatniks, zombies, Martians, aaaaa!
- And I've been waiting for 'em to come back ever since.
That's why I'm up here.
You seen any?
You sure? - Yes!
We're positive!
No Martians, no zombies!
You can come out of the cave!
- I'm not feeling so good.
I don't feel good at all.
You got any marijuana?
Burnout.
Anna! - Ran out about
a week ago. - Come on you got your story!
Now let's go home!
- I've been feeling edgy
ever since. - You can go home if you
want to, just, just go.
- You know, I found these strange cigarettes
in this metal box,
Sir? - and I figured the beatniks
brought it and left them behind...
No, sir?
Uh, you swear this is true?
- I swear on my dead mother's grave,
god rest her soul, it's true!
I've, it's as real as Roswell!
Please, this is not real.
Uh, is too! - Is not!
Is too! - Is not!
- Will you shut up!
Your giving me a headache!
What's it like out there?
I don't think you'd like
the 21st century very much.
- Any zombies?
No, no beatniks either, they're all gone,
extinct, you know, kind of like the dinosaurs.
- Are you sure?
- Enough already!
You can believe whatever you want to believe,
Wait! - but let's go home!
- I got proof!
I can show ya!
Yeah, yeah it's here, ain't it, oh!
It's Johnny's ray gun!
Oh my god!
- Yeah, yeah hold it chief.
Of course, it hasn't worked in a long time, but,
that's it, it's real, that's your proof!
Yeah, that's your proof!
Do you believe me now?
Of course...
You got a name?
I'm Rocky!
Right here, yeah...