♪
[ Announcer: ]
This ball has a chance.
It's outta here.
Home run. Eddie Mills.
The Clippers, with the
help of Mills' late-leading
21st homer, hold on to
beat the Mudheads 5 to 3.
There's a hard-hit ground ball
down the third-base side,
diving Grant by Mills,
from his knees he
throws across the dive.
It hits Harris by a stitch.
What a play by Eddie Mills.
Some sad news tonight
out of Cooper Stadium.
After last week's tragedy,
Clippers star third-baseman
Eddie Mills has left the team,
and there is no word on
whether he will re-join the
Clippers anytime this season.
♪
Three times two.
Six.
Three times four.
You already asked
me that one.
Well, then,
what's the answer?
Ouch.
Sorry.
Three times four.
Four three times.
I just told you.
10, 9, 8, 7...
Eat your orange.
I hate it when
you count down.
6, 5, 4...
12. Three times
four is 12.
That is correct. Very good.
Here you go.
Three three times.
I'm gonna miss the bus.
OK, all right.
Bye. I love you.
Bye.
Oh, um, can you tell
me what tonight is?
My night.
You're gonna hit
it out of the park.
[Coach:]
All right, what
are we gonna do?
[Team:]
Win!
[Coach:]
What's that?
[Team:]
Win!
I can't hear you.
[Team:]
Win!
All right, yeah!
Partner up.
Right here, Abbs.
All right.
Abby.
Hey guys.
Steve.
Hey, Ed.
OK, Abbs, here's the deal.
He's working both
sides of the plate.
Shoulders down,
nice and relaxed.
Power's gonna come from
your back foot, OK?
Short, compact swing.
And remember...
Don't take my
eye off the ball.
You're up, Abby.
Go get 'em.
[ cheering ]
Come on, you can do it.
You can do it.
We really need
your hit, Abbey.
Come on. Keep
your eye on the ball.
[ Bat hits the plate ]
[ clapping ]
[ Umpire: ]
Strike!
[ Dad: ]
Let's go, Abby!
[ Spectator: ]
Come on, Abby!
[ Umpire: ]
Strike two!
[ clapping ]
[ Teammates: ]
You can do it, Abby!
[ Umpire: ]
Strike three!
You're out!
You were great out
there today, honey.
I struck out twice, Dad.
Yeah, well Babe
Ruth struck out...
I'm not Babe Ruth!
I strike out all the time.
Don't you remember?
Babe said you've gotta
start from the bottom.
No! He wasn't
talking about me.
I can't hit at all.
They lose because of me.
You...tagged Matt Reid
out at second, hum?
Maybe I shouldn't
play baseball.
Are you kidding? You've
already got the Mills swing.
I wanna try ballet, Dad.
Krista does ballet.
What?
Ballet. I wanna try
it. It looks fun.
Fun?
Baseball's fun.
[ sigh ]
Is, uh, is that your
truck out there?
Yup.
She needs some work. Looks
like the base is caving.
I'm Matt...Nelson. I,
uh, I came from Sammy's
Garage off Route 33.
You know it?
Nope.
Yeah, I was like second
guy up at Sammy's.
I needed a change, though.
Uh...man. It really is you.
The guys at Sammy's said
you were working here.
I did not believe them.
Excuse me.
I thought maybe a
different Eddie Mills.
Wait 'til I tell my old
man. He's gonna want
to bring me to work.
Every night at dinner, we
got an Eddie Mills update.
Oh man! I was only
in junior high.
Who'd have thought we'd be
working at a garage together?
Ouch, that hurts Dad!
I'm sorry.
Look, look at her hair. Mine
doesn't look like this.
Yes, it does. It does.
[ sighs ]
Actually, if you want
my opinion, I think
it looks better.
Dad, I look dumb.
Make it right.
All right. Hold
on a second here.
Everyone is gonna have
their hair braided.
So are you. So are you.
Just a second.
Oh...
Why can't you just put
on a baseball cap? Why?
Because I'm going to
ballet, not baseball.
Do you get it? Ballet!
Abby!
Hey, Steve.
Hey.
Let me give you a hand
here. Help you load up.
What's going on?
Well, you know this whole
ballet thing with Abby?
She's never gonna like it.
No, I think probably all
little girls like ballet.
No they don't. Not really.
Besides, baseball's
in Abby's blood.
No, Abby quit baseball.
She doesn't have the
mechanics yet, to hit
the ball consistently.
But if we can encourage
her to keep her head down,
right on top of the ball...
I think we've got a
player on our hands.
What do you think?
I think that Abby is the
only girl on a team of
7- and 8-year-old boys,
who want to win
the championship.
Abby's never gotten
a hit, Ed, ever.
She bunted...against
Smart Mark.
[ sigh ]
All right, look Ed, I'm
gonna be honest, OK?
Those boys wanna
win, and so do I.
Abby doesn't have
what you had.
And I think it's
great that she's trying
something else. I'm sorry.
Your boy looked
pretty good out there.
I like what you've
done with his arm.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Did you see that curve
startin'? It was like
right down the middle.
Yeah. We know baseball.
Yeah.
All right. I can take
it from here, Ed.
Thank you for your help.
[ piano music ]
Let's go home.
Wasn't what you thought, huh?
Yeah, it's hard.
We learned to spot,
which is like, staring
at the same place,
and then when you turn
around you have to find
the same exact place again.
Krista was really good
at it. I got a
little dizzy, though.
Well, you wouldn't
have known unless
you tried, right?
Yeah. I have to learn to
spot before the recital.
There's a recital and
everything with costumes.
Well, I hope you
remembered to bring
your Yankee hat home.
It's in my bag. They
said I wasn't allowed
to wear it during class.
Really?
[ knocking ]
Ed, you're eating late.
Lucky for you, I just
went to the store.
Eggs or milk?
I borrowed one egg, one time.
OK, two maybe.
A cup of milk last week.
I'm glad to help.
You working late?
Yes, I'm filling
all my clients' orders
for those baskets.
Summer's just around the
corner. Work, work, work.
Huh...
Ed, did you want
those organizer
shelves for your porch?
They're so easy.
You just hook them on.
I told you, Nancy, I
don't need your shelves.
You can see your
porch from the street.
Um, Abby is starting
ballet lessons.
Just a couple,
and I thought...
[ laughing]
Ballet?
Oh my gosh, that's
a fantastic idea.
Now Ed, do you have all
the clothes she needs?
Because she'll need the
leotards and the
tights and the slippers.
I have all the clothes,
and...the slippers.
Uh, um, I was wondering
if you could take her
for a lesson or two.
I can pick her up.
What happened to
the baseball thing?
She's taking a little
break...a little breather.
The place is on...
A breather?
Yes, Nancy. Even the
pros sometimes take short
breaks from baseball.
Um, the dance place is
on Pearson and Fifth,
Tuesday and Thursday.
She'll have her clothes with
her at school. If you could
pick her up at 3 o'clock...
No problem. Tuesdays and
Thursdays are perfect for me.
Thank you.
Mmm-hmm.
Oh, um, could you make sure
she has her seatbelt on?
She knows, but make sure.
Everybody wears a
seatbelt in my car.
Are you sure you don't want
those organizer shelves?
Uh...
[ dog barking ]
[ Abby talking to Ed ]
Good morning, guys.
Hey.
Do you still play?
No.
You know I, uh, I hear
Ryan McGillan was closing
in on your homerun record.
He already beat
your RBI record.
Did you know that?
No.
Yeah, he, uh, he has
quite a following.
They're comparing him
to you, which is absurd.
He's great...but you...
You ever heard of him?
Yeah, he'll be called
up any time now.
The Yankees are, uh, looking
at several of the guys.
The Clippers are doing real
well this year. They're the
best farm team in the northeast.
What about an
after-work league, Ed?
You've still got some good
years in you. You ever think
about joining one of those?
Hey!
What are you doing?
Waiting for you to get home.
Two for one - plus popcorn.
Let me see.
I pick "The Parent Trap" again.
You can pick the other one.
Cool by me.
How was school?
Good.
Krista asked me to
spend the night tonight.
That was nice of her.
You hungry?
Her mom said OK already.
You wanna sleep there?
All night?
Dad, it's a
sleep-over. Get it?
When do you come home?
In the morning...I think.
Oh... OK.
I'll be careful, Dad.
OK.
I'll be careful.
Do you have your toothbrush?
Yes.
And your clothes
for tomorrow, right?
Yes, Dad.
And your pajamas for tonight?
[ Annoyed: ]
Yes, Dad.
OK.
Listen, you can
call me anytime.
You can call me anytime, it
doesn't matter, all right.
I'll come pick you up.
And we can watch
movies late night.
Kristy has bunk beds.
She does?
Yeah. She said I could
sleep on the top one.
I mean, there's like a
ladder and stuff, too.
Be careful, OK?
I love you, Dad. Bye.
[ Giggling. ]
Hey, Ed.
Sarah.
Oh, right. Right.
Hey, listen, thank
you for this.
Oh, it's no problem. We're
glad she could come over.
Abby's a really good friend.
Well, better go before the
girls burn the house down.
I'm kidding.
You used to have a
great sense of humor.
I mean, a bit off-color,
but you were still funny.
High school?
Mr. Nelson's class,
fourth period.
It was right before
baseball. I think you
came twice the whole year.
You were in Nelson's class?
Yeah.
I mean, it's been
a while. I didn't really
run in that crowd.
I was in the back, over
to the side, actually.
Behind Robin!
Oh, she was always so nice.
She was always so nice to me.
I'm sorry.
You know, Abby
really has her smile.
Mr. Nelson is still
teaching. Can you imagine?
Still drawing those
sentence diagrams in
the shape of spaceships.
Well, um, here's our number.
So call if you need anything,
and I'll see you tomorrow.
The bunk beds...
Surely the top one
has a safety bar.
Oh, yeah, yeah it does.
All the way across, both sides.
Yeah.
They're not really that
high off the ground anyway.
Yeah, well, you know,
they're off the ground, so...
Right, right.
You know, if you don't want
her to sleep in them, I can
always put them downstairs.
No, no, it's fine. If you
say it's safe and she really
wants to, it's not a problem.
OK.
Listen, you don't
have a pool, do you?
They won't be out
of my sight, OK?
[ truck starts ]
[ TV channels changing ]
[ door opens ]
Hi, Dad!
Abby!
Hi!
I'm gonna show
Krista my room.
Hi, Krista.
[ giggling ]
How were the bunk beds?
Teardribble, The Klutzy Cupid.
Now do you remember me?
You, um, you wore the pink hat
with the silver bead thingies.
That matched my braces.
Yeah, I got braces late.
Yeah, I remember your story.
Uh, you remember the hat.
Well, who could
forget the hat?
Well, Klutzy Cupid
paid off, so I guess the
mortification was worth it.
[ girls giggling ]
You know, children's
books and stuff.
Surprised?
No. No.
You were...you were one
of the smart girls.
Yeah, one of the nerdy girls.
I don't know anything
about baseball.
What?
Really?
You're kidding, right?
OK, watch this.
See this is my
all-time favorite card.
That is Tino Martinez. He
plays for the
New York Yankees, OK?
The owner of the
red Mustang came in.
I was running late.
You were supposed to
be here an hour ago.
The Mustang's finished.
Bobby knows that.
Bobby has his own jobs.
The Mustang was yours.
And I finished it!
What, you have a
girlfriend, huh?
Is that it?
You've been sidetracked
these last few weeks.
I just wonder what
you've got going, because
it's affecting your work.
Affecting my work?
You're sidetracked.
This is ridiculous.
Abby left her ballet
clothes at home. I dropped
them by school.
That's it. OK? That's it.
Your, uh, your girl
is, is taking ballet?
Eddie Mills' girl
is a ballerina?
What, you practice
with her, huh?
Those leaps and spins?
[ laughs ]
There's a new ding in my
truck. What are you
thinking? That's a classic...
That is not your
truck, all right? Now
stay off my back.
I just... I...
I'm outta here.
Where we going?
Ha! Ha!
You know, my dad was in a
major funk when you quit.
Baseball season was over for
him. For a lot of people here.
People think you'll come back.
Try to get it close to
the plate, all right?
[ bat cracks ]
Yellow cheese or white cheese?
Yellow.
I was thinking we could
spend the day throwing the
ball around at Pebble Park.
It would be fun.
Get some ice cream after.
[ knocking ]
Dad, come look.
These are so good.
I brought you the recipe, Ed.
And I included my easy
version of my lasagna recipe.
These muffins aren't
too difficult.
Have you ever had lasagna,
Dad? It's so good.
Look at that pretty
hair of yours. It is
a rat's nest, though.
It would look
so nice braided.
Now, for ballet. You have
ballet slippers, right?
And you have
leotards and tights.
Now, do you have...
I have one pink leotard.
Only one? Oh,
that's not gonna do.
We'll take you
shopping today and we'll
get you some more, OK?
And I was thinking,
what about one of those
skirts like that
little blonde girl has?
It's so dainty and nice.
Any color you like.
A purple one?
Oh, purple would
be very nice. Yes.
Oh, Ed, this is a good idea.
Why don't you peel this
orange for her? You know,
fruit is so important.
Can I go, Dad?
Yeah, I guess, if
you want to. Sure.
[ giggling ]
You want something? A leotard?
Tights? Ballet slippers?
[ lawnmower ]
OK, these are all of them.
Um...
Here we go. A family timeline.
Choose three pictures that
describe you and your family.
First picture: you as a baby.
Second picture: a current
photo of yourself.
And the third picture: create
a drawing of yourself and your
family five years from now.
This is a silly project.
We should've started earlier.
OK, you start drawing. I'll
go through the pictures.
Five years, that'll make
you 12. You'll be in
the seventh grade.
[ whistles ]
[ both laughing]
I loved that ride.
Me, too. So much
fun. Wow. OK...
I'm drawing you and me.
Did Mom write that?
Yeah.
It's pretty.
I never do this.
I never write on the
back of pictures.
We'll remember.
[ straining ]
Matt, help me pull.
Come on.
That battery is too big
for this car, Eddie.
I know. Help me pull.
Why would you put a battery
that size in this car?
I didn't.
Man, this must
be embarrassing.
It isn't a common mistake.
It's a battery.
A battery like that doesn't
fit in a space like that.
See, Eddie, you're not
a mechanic. I've been
trying to tell you...
Listen. Listen, the owner
of this car put this in.
I've gotta get it out.
Help me pull.
OK, you aren't pulling.
You aren't pulling.
Hi.
What? What's wrong?
Oh, nothing. Absolutely nothing.
Uh, I'm sorry to interrupt
your working, but I was
just over at the bakery...
I'm homeroom mom this week.
Abby told me which
garage you worked at.
We're ordering costumes for the
girls tonight, and she wanted
me to check with you about...
Can we...
Let's move outside.
Order anything.
Oh, OK. Great. Um...
Why are we over here?
It's quiet.
Order whatever
she wants. Really.
Just as long as it's not one
of those hats with the silver
bead thingies, I'm fine.
Wow, you always succeed in
making me feel like I still
have braces on my teeth.
Sarah... I was...
Sarah, I was kidding.
I don't even remember
you with braces. We never
talked in high school.
No, we didn't.
You know, I just want Krista
to have a good friend.
I'm sure they both need it.
That's why I'm here,
OK? For the girls.
I'll, um, order the
ballet costumes.
Sorry for interrupting.
[ phone rings ]
Ronny's.
Yeah, uh, Eddie...telefono.
This is Ed.
Ed, it's Sarah.
Sarah, listen...
Is that Abby?
Yeah, I just got to
school to pick Krista up
and take her to dance,
and Abby wants to go, too.
But I wanted to
check with you first.
Well, the Yankee game's
on tonight, so she'll
just take the bus home.
Right...well...she wondered if
you could tape it for her.
The Yankee game?
The Yankees are
playing the Red Sox.
She mentioned that.
Roger Clemens is pitching.
Ed? Ed?
I'm here.
Oh, sorry, this phone
just cuts out sometimes.
I'll tape it.
What?
Did you say you'll tape it?
Yes.
Great.
Well, um, listen
I'll bring her home.
The girls get their costumes
tonight, so it'll be,
you know, a late practice.
Invite your friends over,
you know. Watch the game.
[ TV: ]
We've got a packed house
again tonight in Yankee Stadium.
Roger Clemens enjoying his
first game back. Of
course, he missed
his last start due to
stiffness in his lower back.
Hey, Tom.
Eddie Mills.
It's been a long time, huh?
I'm ready to play
ball again, Tom.
You're ready?
The deal was you'd be back
on the field in six months.
It's been five years,
Eddie. Five years.
I've got a team of boys. Good
athletes, fast and young.
I hold the record.
Look, this better not
be about no lost youth.
Don't waste my time trying to
get those years back, Eddie.
You asked me for a favor.
What?
I went to school
yesterday, and I waited.
Miss Kerry told me she'd
already gone home with
Sarah Parker and Krista.
She did leave with
them. I forgot.
You forgot! I waited.
I was worried.
She got her
costume last night.
Sarah just thought
it would be easier...
It's just up the street. It's
no big deal for me to do it.
And switching around like that
is confusing for a child.
It is sort of out of Sarah's
way to drop Abby off.
Yes it is, so I can do that.
It would help Sarah out.
She has her hands full already
with her own daughter,
and zero help from that
no-good ex-husband of hers.
Not that she needs
any help from a man.
[ bat cracks ]
All right.
The team's traveling to
Louisville, then to Charlotte.
You warm up with them, just
to get your juices flowing,
and then we might try
you out next home game.
You're hittin', Eddie, but
don't get too comfortable.
Derrick's just two weeks
out of high school. Hasn't
even made the rotation.
But, great potential
there, huh?
[ Tom: ]
Oh, boy. I love this game.
Don't move.
You look pretty.
What?
You look really pretty.
I like your lipstick.
Turn around.
[ knock at the door ]
[ giggling ]
We're back here.
There he comes.
What happened to your face?
How do we look?
Nancy did my makeup,
and I did hers.
I think...I think you look
beautiful without makeup.
But don't we look fantastic?
She's seven, Nancy.
She doesn't need to learn
about makeup, and she's
not allowed to wear it.
Wash your face, Abby.
But Dad...
On second thought, let's wash
your face at home. Come on.
My daughter doesn't
wear makeup.
And we are not rearranging
our porch...ever.
[ knock at the door ]
Go away! My room is private!
Private?
Don't you have math homework?
I already did it...
On Nancy's computer.
It's easier that way.
What's that?
I strained my shoulder.
All the moms let their
daughters wear
makeup on stage.
I'll be the only one.
For the recital...only.
Look at you.
New cleats?
That's your costume,
huh? Hum...
What's in the box?
Ballet slippers. Nancy
has to do them, though.
Do what?
Like, sew on the piece.
I can do it for you.
Nancy can later.
I can sew.
You can't sew these.
It can't be that hard.
Let's see...
Very nice.
You're gonna mess it
up, and then I'm
gonna need new ones.
Are those your cleats?
Yeah, I just got 'em.
Why?
That looks good, huh?
If it's OK with you,
and you care, I'm ready
to play ball again.
For the Clippers?
Yeah, if it's OK with you.
You'll be on the team?
Yeah.
Third base?
I hope so.
No. 4 in the lineup?
I don't know.
You get to ride the bus
and go to different cities?
Mmm-hmm.
You're going to
play baseball!
I don't have a Clippers hat.
That's OK.
Where do you go first?
How many days again?
One week plus one day.
Eight days.
Right.
So the next time you
go, I get to go on the
bus with you, right?
That's right.
Where are we now?
Right here.
Where?
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8.
Yoo hoo.
Hi. Hey.
How'd you like to come
see your new room?
Yeah, let's go.
Will any of these do?
Wow.
You have a lot
of nice luggage.
Well, everyone needs
good luggage, in case.
Now this one has a lot
of different compartments.
This big compartment would
be perfect for shoes.
And it has smaller
compartments, which you could
use for makeup or whatever.
That'll work great.
Sure you won't be
needing any of this?
Well, I may need to whisk
off to somewhere exotic.
I promise I'll bring it back.
I'm not worried. I
have your daughter.
If there's anything
else that you need...
Thank you, Nancy. Thank you.
Show and tell. Last
Friday of every month,
which isn't this Friday,
but it's the Friday
after, so you might want to
start thinking about
something for that
as soon as you can.
What else am I forgetting?
Did I give you her vitamins?
Yes, her vitamins, great.
You know about ballet.
Of course.
Oh, for emergencies, you
can call Tom's cell phone.
Yes, his cell phone number.
I have it right here.
OK. OK.
Abbs...
You ready?
I'm ready.
[ whispering: ]
Watch the ball.
Hey, hold that
for me, man.
Come on, man,
get out of here.
Tommy, get on the bus.
Jones...
Mills...
OK.
Yeah.
Buffalo, they have Reggie.
Have you seen that guy's arm?
Yeah, he's got an arm.
But, uh, we can stay
in there with a couple of
dingers. Right, McGillen?
Yeah, that's right.
Isn't that right, Eddie Mills?
[ ball hitting the glove ]
Mills! Get in there,
loosen that arm up.
[ crowd cheering ]
[ Eddie: ]
Nice game, guys.
Way to go.
Nice game.
Can I get a beer please?
Thanks.
Don't tell me
you missed this.
I missed all this.
You can't ignore
your calling, Eddie.
You tried. It didn't work.
You had a blind
spot in your life.
You dating anybody, Eddie?
Nah.
Whew! Look at all these women.
Some beautiful women.
Some nice women, too.
What about you?
You seeing anybody?
Me? Naw.
I've been real
busy these days.
Excuse me.
Is she there?
Are you sure?
OK, could you just tell her
that I'll call her tomorrow?
OK. Bye.
My mom was a good cook.
Oh, really?
Yeah, my dad says.
Well, I'm sure she was
perfect, judging from
her perfect daughter.
Was your mother ill?
No, she died in a car
accident. I was a baby.
Oh, I'm sorry.
You know she's always
with you, right?
My dad gets sad. He
stays in his room.
Oh...
And you know that
she's always with
your dad, too, right?
Did your husband die?
Oh, no, I've
never been married.
You haven't? Why not?
Well, a woman
doesn't always have
to get married.
Sometimes we're better without.
Do you have any kids?
No.
You don't want kids?
[ sighs ]
You know, I didn't even
ask you if you
like blueberry pancakes.
Getting used to a bat again?
You take a healthy cut.
[ bat cracks ]
Now, Tom. Let me hit.
I can bring 'em in.
We'll see how you do
next home game, Eddie.
Matthews, bring 'em in.
Let's go, boy.
[ crowd cheers ]
[ truck engine ]
[ dog barks ]
[ knocking ]
Hey, Nancy. Good
to see you.
Ed!
Is she here?
We weren't expecting you
'til this evening. I was
on my way to pick her up.
Oh, great, I'll
get her. Thanks.
It's not a ballet
night, is it?
No.
Hi. How was your day, huh?
It was good.
Dad!
Ah, I missed you.
You're taller.
Tell me everything.
Where'd you get this?
The fair.
There was a booth at the fair.
We went on the roller
coaster. Front seat. I put
my hands up the whole time.
I held onto her.
Sounds fun.
Dad, you're not
supposed to be home.
Nancy and I are making a
homecoming meal for you.
See you later.
I guess we're going now.
There's a home game
tomorrow. I'm playing.
Good luck.
There's no roller coasters,
but the games
are pretty exciting.
It's free hat night.
Dad, let's go.
OK, so the Clippers are
15 and 6. The only team
close is Toledo, right?
Right, they're 14 and 8.
Right. I can't wait
to go to Toledo.
I figured you'd be in here.
You know, there was
a time I thought
I'd have to kick you out
so the other players
would get a chance
to use the facilities.
Unfortunately, the cage
has stood pretty
idle without you.
The new boys, they don't
have the discipline.
They won't go above and
beyond what I require.
Anyway, look I'm
gonna lock up.
Close the door behind you.
I've got dinner
at Matthews' house.
I've gotta address
his swing, or lack thereof.
But his wife, she
makes a mean meatloaf.
Although nobody's cookin'
holds a candle to Robin's.
She must've thought
I had a tapeworm.
Bring that bat all
the way around, Eddie.
That was pretty good, huh?
Is Ryan McGillen nice?
Yeah, he's nice.
How many RBIs does he have?
Did you know that Abby made
this whole meal herself?
I told her what to do,
but she did everything.
It's delicious.
I don't know.
Pete Stewart's got
a good arm, huh?
He's got an unbelievable
arm, and he's only 20.
He's got his whole
career in front of him.
Any girls on the team?
Not yet.
You know what, this was
wonderful, but I'm beat.
Oh, we have dessert.
I think I'm gonna
have to pass.
Abby made it. You can't pass.
OK, so after tomorrow's home
game, we go to Indianapolis,
and then To-ledo.
Mmm-hmm.
Pie?
Mmm.
[ giggling ]
And then we come
back for three days to play
Buffalo, and then we go to...
Abby, would you run
and get some plates for me
and some forks?
And pour some milk.
Big glasses?
Sure.
Abby knows
a lot about baseball.
She knows that Boston,
Massachusetts is the
home of the Red Sox,
and of the famous
Roger Clements.
Clemens, Roger Clemens,
and he is now a Yankee.
Oh, and she knows that the
Yankees originated in Boston,
and that Babe Ruth played
for the Red Sox before
he went to New York.
And the Orioles before the
Red Sox, but Abby knows that.
But you know what
she doesn't know?
Is that Boston Massachusetts
is the home of the
famous Boston Tea Party...
and Paul Revere and
the Boston Massacre.
Baseball is history.
She'll learn
the rest in school.
Besides, Abby knows more
than most 7-year-olds.
Yeah, she does, and she will
learn the rest in school.
Dad, do you want milk, too?
No thanks, honey.
She tells me that she's going
around with you to a bunch of
different cities on a bus,
and that she's gonna be part
of a team, one of the boys.
Ed, she needs school.
She needs girlfriends
who are 7 years old.
She needs a home.
She needs stability.
Surely you know
that...don't you?
I couldn't carry
the plates, too.
I'll help you.
[ birds chirping ]
So you got your costume, huh?
Mmm-hmm.
But you're gonna
miss the recital.
You sure you want
to miss the recital?
There's two of 'em. I'll
be in the winter one.
You're gonna miss Krista
probably, and school too, huh?
Isn't there a spelling
bee coming up soon?
I don't care about
the spelling bee.
Well, you should.
Besides, we're not
gonna be gone forever.
No, we're not gonna
be gone long at all.
Nancy will probably rearrange
the porch while I'm gone,
and I won't be able to find
anything when I come back,
but what are you gonna do?
You said I could go
on the bus...with you.
I know I did.
You lied.
You said you never
lie, but you do.
You said I could go with you.
Abby...
You lied! You're a big liar!
I wanna live
with Nancy forever!
Wait a minute!
Abby!
Honey, I want you
with me every minute.
Abby...please understand
I want you with me every
minute of every day.
But school is important.
And...and...stability, and...
I am your father, and you
need to stay in school for
the next two months, Abby.
It's important.
[ knocking ]
[ truck starts ]
[ dog barking ]
She needs to come
home now. It's late.
She's been asleep for 20
minutes, Ed. I'll bring
her home in the morning.
No, she sleeps at home.
Let her sleep, Ed. She
wants to stay here.
No, Nancy, you want
her to stay here.
She belongs at home with me.
[ knock at the door ]
I don't think Abby's up
for going to the game.
Not up for the game?
I'm playing tonight.
I know.
It's free hat night.
She doesn't want to go.
It's just a game, Ed.
So what's it like
out there, Eddie?
It's like "The
Natural," isn't it?
I love that movie. When
he hits the lights.
I bet you could hit
the lights, make it
spray everywhere.
My dad played
in high school.
His arm wasn't bad,
but he was pretty
slow and couldn't hit.
It wasn't for not
trying, though.
He worked so hard.
Worked me so hard.
Nothing else exists
within this fence
for nine innings,
nothing.
You can smell the
popcorn and the hot dogs...
Hear the crowd...
It's on the outside, you
know. It's got nothing
to do with you. Nothing.
You can be whoever you
want on that diamond.
It doesn't matter.
Just play a good game.
Well, good game.
♪
♪ Sunshine shining in
the summertime breeze ♪
♪ The whole world smiln'
if you know what I mean ♪
♪ Cool, cool time hangin'
out with the boys ♪
♪ AM radio makin' some noise ♪
♪ Tunin' in to a
moment in time ♪
♪ When everything seemed
like a perfect rhyme ♪
♪ Here it is, here I go,
my show, can't wait ♪
♪ Gotta do it now
before it gets too late ♪
♪ Hey man, look at me now ♪
♪ Nothin' in the world's
gonna get me down ♪
♪ Sparks flying, I'm on fire ♪
♪ Way up high, and
I'm getting' higher ♪
♪ Turnin' it loose,
turnin' it on ♪
♪ On a day like this,
what could go wrong? ♪
♪ Tip my hat, blow a
kiss to the crowd ♪
♪ Hey man, look at me now ♪
♪
♪ Green grass growin'
on the edge of my feet ♪
♪ Feels good knowin' I'm
not out of my league ♪
♪ Singin' a song that
I never have sung ♪
♪ Outta my reach, on
the tip of my tongue ♪
♪ Who knows if
tomorrow will come ♪
♪ It really don't matter
'til this day's done ♪
♪ Gotta move, gotta
go, my fate, my turn ♪
♪ Still a little
daylight left to burn ♪
♪ Hey man, look at me now. ♪
♪ Nothin' in the world's
gonna get me down ♪
♪ Sparks flying, I'm on fire ♪
♪ Way up high, and
I'm getting' higher ♪
♪ Turnin' it loose,
turnin' it on ♪
♪ On a day like this,
what could go wrong? ♪
♪ Tip my hat, blow a
kiss to the crowd ♪
♪ Hey man, look at me now ♪
[ crowd cheering ]
♪ Sunshine shining in
the summertime breeze ♪
♪ The whole world's mine,
if you know what I mean ♪
♪ Here it is, here I go,
my show, can't wait ♪
♪ Gotta do it now before
it gets too late ♪
♪ Hey man, look at me now ♪
♪ Nothin' in the world's
gonna get me down ♪
♪
Whew!
All right, boys. Bus
leaves tomorrow 8 a.m.
If you're not there,
you know you can walk.
Hey, good game.
Thanks, man.
Well, I'm out 20 bucks.
To Ronnie, no less.
I was sure you'd give
me a homer, Eddie.
I never knew baseball was
this exciting. I was dying
when you got that guy out.
She was excited.
Hey, uh, well good game,
Eddie. Good luck on the
road. I'll be listening.
Thanks, man. Don't you
touch my truck, all right?
You're just as good as
you were in high school.
Somehow it doesn't
feel as easy, though.
Well, you make
it look easy.
Listen, I gotta go...
Just like you make
raising Abby look easy.
She won't talk to me.
You must just trust your
instincts with baseball.
So you must be doin'
somethin' right.
You know, baseball's fun.
I thought you
might want this.
It was free
hat night tonight.
All those people
wearing Clipper hats.
They played "Clipper
Fans, Ring Your Bell."
Everyone singing, dancing.
It was kinda neat.
Pete was pitching a
no-hitter into the eighth
inning. You believe that?
Can I show you something cool?
You don't have to feel sorry.
I don't wanna go with
you anymore anyway.
[ clearing throat ]
[ piano music ]
How do I look?
Beautiful. Fantastic.
Good luck, sweetheart.
[ bat cracks ]
[ crowd cheers ]
[ Announcer: ]
Ladies and gentlemen,
the final score this evening is
Columbus, 7; Louisville, 2.
The Clippers and Riverbacks
thank you for your attendance.
McGillen, let's take a walk.
Yeah, hold up.
Now.
Hey, he got the call.
[ voice on the phone: ]
She was the best one.
Once, there was a klutzy
cupid named Teardribble.
I can read.
OK, read to me then.
[ Abby reading: ]
Once there was a klutzy
cupid named "Teardribble."
What are you
doin' down here?
Can't find 103.1 FM.
Well...
[ radio tuning ]
[ Commentator: ]
... competition
so far this season,
but the club will now
have to deal with the
loss of Ryan McGillen,
who was called up to the
Yankees earlier this week.
And who knows who the
Clippers are going to have
to pick up the production.
One candidate would certainly
be Eddie Mills, who's making
a comeback for the Clippers.
You might remember him
from the '93 campaign,
and we'll see if he'll be
able to keep up the pace,
and if he does, who knows
where Mills might end up
at the end of the season.
McGillen, at the
time of the callup...
What does that mean?
I'm not sure.
Where would my dad be?
I don't know, but
I think he means
he'd be surprised if your
dad hadn't been called
up to the majors by then.
Hey, but who knows, right?
Just a bunch of
commentators talking shop.
What do they know?
Hey, you like popcorn?
Well you can't listen to
baseball without popcorn.
OK, now you're
the pitcher, see.
OK, um, you stand over
there, and you have to get
it between here and here.
Throw it over the plate.
You can throw it underhand
if you need to, or overhand.
Oh, hold on...
OK, you want to take the
ball, follow through,
bring your leg up, OK?
Little lower.
[ Sarah ]
Keep trying, Abby.
All right, Abby!
Good job, Krista. All right!
Could you do that again, Krista?
[ phone ringing ]
Hello?
Oh, hi, Ed.
She's fantastic. Guess what?
100% on her math test.
Tell him I hit the ball.
What?
Tell him I hit it.
Yes, and, um, she
was playing baseball with
Krista and she hit the ball.
Four times.
Yes, yes, she
hit it four times.
[ Ed: ]
All right Abbey!
Be really careful,
because this roof
breaks easily, OK?
You remember all
the steps we took?
You're gonna have a
fantastic show and tell.
Everyone's gonna want
to know how you made
this beautiful house.
So here's some directions
in case anyone needs them.
The other moms, or
Miss Kerry, even.
Whew. You have
everything you need?
I'm ready to
talk to my dad now.
Oh, I think that's nice,
honey, but we don't
have any way of getting
a hold of him right now.
Tom's cell phone.
Oh, that's just
for emergencies.
And your dad's probably
in a practice anyway.
He'll call you tonight.
What do you need?
I wanna talk to him now.
I'm sorry, honey,
but let's go to school,
and tonight will be
here before you know it.
Show and tell's
gonna be so much fun.
If my dad calls,
ask him to come home
tomorrow morning before
his game in Toledo.
Toledo isn't that
close, sweetie.
So, me and my brother
Zach go to the pond. We're
usually there all day.
And mom calls us forever.
She gets mad because we say
that we'll get home earlier.
She says she won't
let us go again, but she
always lets us.
I caught four
fish last weekend.
My brother only caught two.
Well, a big one and a little
one, so like one and a half.
I caught four.
My dad is a
baseball player.
He plays ball for
the Clippers, but...
He's gonna be a Yankee.
[ kids talking ]
Well, I knew our
gingerbread house
would be a hit.
Oh, I brought you
a recipe card.
It's not too difficult.
Oh, OK.
[ Anchor: ]
Roger Clemens pitched
the New York Yankees
to another victory today.
Clemens pitched seven innings
of two...hit baseball,
and Derrick Jeter...
Yo, Ed, what
are you drinking?
I'm OK, thanks.
Oh, come on man,
we're celebrating.
No, I'm, I'm OK.
[ woman at table: ]
Bobby tells her she's
a good girl when
she cleans her plate.
I've told him over and
over again, she's going
to be an overeater
if she thinks she's only
a good girl when
she cleans her plate.
Yeah, that makes sense.
No, I think
it's OK in some
circumstances. Like we do.
We emphasize that she's a
good girl if she finishes
all her vegetables.
She hates vegetables.
Except, if you ever
force a kid to eat,
they'll start thinking
they have to eat
on a schedule...
Instead of just
when they're hungry.
But she won't
eat all day if I
don't force her to.
Oh, she'll eat.
When she's hungry,
she'll eat.
It's like sleep. When
she's tired, she'll sleep.
And not until then.
Ain't that the truth.
It sounds like
a full-time job.
Oh, it is.
It's a great full-time job.
OK, here you go.
I don't feel good.
You don't feel well.
You don't feel hot.
I don't feel good.
Heartache is worse
than the flu.
[ sighs ]
Let's buckle you up again.
There you go.
You didn't pull on
it. You have to check.
Oh, it clicked.
I know it clicked, but you
still have to pull and check.
OK.
My mom's seatbelt didn't work.
My dad checks. He
makes everyone check.
I'll check it from now on.
I won't tell him.
Thank you.
What time is it?
It's almost 9 o'clock.
My dad's practice is
at, um, 10 o'clock.
What time's the game?
Five-thirty.
Well, I certainly hope it's
free hat night, or free
shirt night or something.
Eddie...
Eddie, a Yankee suit wants to
meet with you after the game.
Brocious strained his
arm last night. The Yankees
need a backup, just in case.
A third baseman who can hit.
[ both laugh ]
Yeah.
[ Announcer: ]
Hi everybody.
This is Terry Smith from
Skeldon Stadium in Toledo,
where tonight the Clippers
get ready to take
on the Toledo Mudhands
for the first
time in the 2000 season.
These two teams
battled each other down
the stretch a year ago.
The Clippers had
a win the final three
games of the '99 season.
You feeling good?
Eddie...
Yeah?
How you feeling?
You feeling good?
It still smells like
it did five years ago.
You'd think they would've
done something about that.
Play a great game tonight,
and you hit like you hit
the last time you were here.
You remember that game?
Yeah, I remember.
All right, go get 'em
Eddie. Go get 'em! Eddie!
[ Announcer: ] Coming to
the plate for Columbus,
the third-baseman,
number 3, Eddie Mills.
Come on, Eddie.
[ crowd cheering ]
[ exhales ]
Any time you're ready.
Right, right.
[ clapping ]
Go, Ed!
Go, Dad! Go get
'em! Crack! Whoo!
Eddie, this is Bryan Hall.
Bryan's with the Yankees.
Good to meet you.
And you.
[ Bryan: ]
Eddie, we lost a player
due to injury.
We're gonna need you on
the field tomorrow night.
You're bookin' the
red-eye to New York.
Game time is 7 p.m.
There'll be a Yankee
uniform waiting for
you in the locker room.
Be on the field
at 5 o'clock, ready
to play ball.
Well, I hope you
didn't miss too
much at school today.
We have a long drive
ahead of us, Abby.
We definitely should go now.
Dad!
Abbey!
Oh, I missed you so much.
You were amazing dad. Crack!
He was pitching inside.
Let's just you and me ride
home in the back seat, OK?
Let me see, um, you must
be the famous Abby Mills.
I'm coach Tom Donner.
Hi.
You know, I believe you've
got the look of a ballplayer,
just like your dad...
who got the opportunity
of a lifetime tonight.
Your dad is gonna
be playing ball at the
Yankee Stadium tomorrow.
Wow.
Could you still
ride home with us?
Oh, we don't put
it in bowls.
What do you
put them in?
Oh, we just
eat off the floor.
Abby...
[ TV announcer in
the background ]
We don't eat off the floor.
Abby, are you hot?
No.
Are you?
You're letting in the bugs.
It's baseball. We have
to let the night air in.
[ phone rings ]
[ sighs ]
Hello?
Yes, just a minute.
It's for you.
Hi, Abbster.
Dad! Where are you?
I'm in the dugout. I'm
on Jeter's cell phone.
No way!
Way!
Nancy forgot to get peanuts.
She doesn't know how to
keep score or anything. She
doesn't know anything. She...
Abbey, baby I gotta go. I'm
goin' in. I'm goin' in.
I'm playing for you.
Dad? Dad?
[ phone beeps ]
[ Announcer: ]
Eddie Mills coming in
now for Scott Brocious.
Looks like Brocious is in need
of a break after the strain on
his arm from last night's game.
[ door opens]
Oh, Ed. You're here.
I, um, uh...
Ed, I've...I've never
raised a child, and um...
I don't know what to do
for her when she's upset.
If you should need anything,
I'll just be nextdoor.
[ clears throat ]
Dad!
Hey! Hi, baby!
You played ball
for the Yankees.
I warmed up
Paul O'Neil's arm.
And you talked on
Jeter's cell phone.
And I threw the ball to
Tino for the first out.
I cried.
You played three
innings for the Yankees.
Yep.
Scott Brocious' arm isn't
as bad as we thought.
So you'll play in Durham
tonight with the Clippers.
Nancy didn't do anything
right. She doesn't get it.
I'm not gonna stay
with Nancy anymore.
I wanna stay in
my own house, in my own
room, from now on.
Hey! Weight room locked?
I don't know.
Look, don't be
discouraged, Eddie.
You knew Brocious was
going back into the game.
I want you in there,
cage six days a week,
five days on weights.
We've got 55 games left
in the next two months.
I want you to eat,
sleep, breathe baseball.
This time, you'll stay up,
a full-time Yankee. Huh?
Oh, man, geez.
You know, Eddie, some guys,
they spend their one game
with the Yankees on the bench.
But you...
You played in the bigs.
Come on, Eddie. You coming?
You make Yankees
out of Clippers.
You're the coach that makes
the difference...for all of us.
I love baseball.
But sometimes, it's
from the bench that
you get the best view.
Besides, my daughter and I
can't both be in the spotlight.
♪
[ knocking ]
Ed.
I thought I'd return these.
And, um, let you know that
Abby wants one of those hats.
She does?
Yup. With the silver thingies.
I told her only the cool
people wear them, so
naturally, she has to have one.
[ sighs ]
I feel like all I
do is start over.
Would you like
to start over?
Yeah.
[ sighs ]
Baseball game's a
good place to start.
It's a beautiful
day for baseball.
♪
♪ Come down from the place
where you've been hidin', ♪
♪ And come out in the
sun where you belong ♪
♪ Sorrow's gonna pass ♪
♪ Sadnesss doesn't
last too long ♪
♪ Come what may,
come what may, ♪
♪ It feels good,
to hear you say ♪
Here you go.
No, thanks.
It'll help you bat.
♪ Come what may,
come what may ♪
[ Nancy: ]
Oranges! Oranges, boys!
♪ There's something in
the rush of the water ♪
[ clapping ]
♪
Orange?
I hear you, um,
make a mean lasagna.
♪
♪ Come what may,
come what may ♪
[ cheering ]
♪
All right, Chad,
here we go, buddy.
Watch the ball, now.
Hips before hands.
Come on, Chad! Go,
Chad! Hips before hands.
♪ Come what may,
come what may ♪
♪ It feels so good,
to hear you say ♪
♪ Hello sunshine,
it's a good ole day ♪
♪ Come what may ♪
♪ Oh, come what may ♪
♪ It feels good, just
to hear you say ♪
♪ Hello sunshine,
it's a good ole day ♪
♪ Come what may,
come what may ♪
♪
♪ I wanna learn
from my mistakes ♪
♪ I wanna give
back what I take ♪
♪ I wanna be there
for my friends ♪
♪ I wanna always
make amends ♪
♪ I wanna live
like that ♪
♪
♪ I wanna laugh
right out loud ♪
♪ I wanna make
my mama proud ♪
♪ I wanna have the
strength to cry ♪
♪ I wanna always
wonder why ♪
♪ I wanna live
like that ♪
that way ♪
♪ I don't wanna
be afraid ♪
♪ I wanna love
like that ♪
♪ Cherish every day ♪
♪ I wanna live like that ♪
♪ I wanna be heard
when I pray ♪
♪ I wanna slow
dance in the rain ♪
♪ I wanna love and
be loved back ♪
♪ Lose my way
without a map ♪
♪ I wanna live
like that ♪
♪
♪ I wanna walk where
things grow wild ♪
♪ I wanna see
my baby smile ♪
♪ I wanna grow
old gracefully ♪
♪ Gather shells
beside the sea ♪
♪ I wanna live like that ♪
♪ I wanna live that way ♪
♪ I don't wanna be afraid ♪
♪ I wanna love like that ♪
♪ Treasure every day ♪
♪ I wanna live like that ♪
♪ I wanna live that way ♪
♪ I don't wanna be afraid ♪
♪ I wanna love like that ♪
♪ Cherish every day ♪
♪ I wanna live like that ♪
♪