[music playing]
KIM JAMESON: The
Renaissance was a time
of rebirth and rediscovery...
a time when artists took a fresh look at the world
in which they lived.
And these artists helped to rekindle a sense of adventure
and romance as they struck out to discover things
about themselves and the world that they had never
taken a close look at before.
Now during this period, each
city had a school of art
with its own style and approach.
But all were
dedicated to a feeling
for the individual, their personal emotions, and beauty.
Now this can best
be seen in the work
of [inaudible] contemporary of,um, Veronese and Tintoretto.
[bell tolling]
[music playing]
All of these painters explored light and dark with their use
of color and composition.
They were trying to illustrate the diversity of human nature
and human individuality,the way in which all of us
have a light side and a
dark side to our nature.
That sounds a
little pretentious.
OK, it's the right idea.
Just try and not be
so serious about it.
OK, "Lady in
Reflection" Illustrates
that essential quality.
It also reminds us that the face we show the world
is often different
from our true self.
Now, despite the
impression of vanity,
[inaudible] interest was in showing that true beauty
comes from within.
Ms. Jameson, the
rest of the campus
is under the impression
it's summer break.
The rest of the campus don’t have a doctoral thesis
to deliver this fall.
And besides my
lectures, I have about
three dozen research papers to read, not to mention your text.
What kind of a summer is that?
My dear, you are without a doubt our brightest graduate student.
Your scholarly instincts
are remarkable.
But a work of art
depends as much
on what we bring to it as what the artist gives us to look at.
Art is only a reflection
of life, Ms. Jameson.
It is necessary for
us to have a life
before we can truly
appreciate it.
You need to show your
true face to the world.
Maybe after I have my PhD.
Well, right know, I need you to join the class outside.
Oh, not another group picture.
Just say...
Cheese!
Sorry, I forgot
to advance the film.
I hate having
my picture taken.
Now, now, Miss, Jameson,leave us not be testy.
This is my end of term portrait,and you more than anyone
should appreciate the
photographic process.
Smiles everyone.
[click]
There.
All right, now.
Ready?
Cheese!
I thought it might be you.
Kate!
Oh, it is so good to see you.
I just got in from Paris.
Duty free.
I knew I couldn't count on you for anything stronger than tea.
Welcome home!
How did you get in?
What do you think?
I told the doorman
I forgot my key.
He said that he
liked your new look.
Oh, that old game.
As fun as it ever was.
Yeah, it was fun
when we were kids.
That's right, uh, you
haven't like playing
it since, what was his name?
It's Peter Robinson.
Oh God, I have missed you, Kate.
Mmm, the name is
Dominique now, remember?
What?
You all right?
You look tired.
Yeah, you just haven't
seen me in a while.
Four years isn't a while.
Has it been that long?
Mm-hm.
Even longer since
you've seen mom and dad.
Well, they must be happy with all your degrees.
I think that they’re proud of both of us, Kate.
Well, so we should celebrate!
Put on your party dress because
I am taking you dancing.
Nah, I don't think that...
Mmm, thinking is not required.
What is required is something black and sexy.
I've got one you can wear.
I came in town to do
a favor for a friend
and I may as well do you a favor and get you out too.
Come on.[excited chatter and cheers]
[inaudible] beautiful.
Thank you.
Wow, I can't wait to tell Mr.Arneau how fabulous this is.
Anything for Jacques.
Would you take care
of my sister please?
Oh, sure.
[inaudible] Come on, please.
Let the lady through.
What were you doing?
This really isn't
my style, Kate.
Come on.
You're going to go
have a good time
whether you want to or not.
[dance music]
I can't believe you
get paid for this.
We just put this
dump on the map.
Hey, Dominique.
Care to dance?
[dance music]
[groaning] Start up.
OK.
Thanks, Tony.
I'll let Jacques know
what a hit you were.
Anything for Jacques.
Come on, what are
we waiting for?
Sorry, it's been a long day.
The jet lag finally hit.
Take it easy.
Ooh.
[laughs] Oh.
KIM: Maybe you
should just lay off.
Oh if I need it, I'd take it.
If I don't, I don't.
You've been
drinking all night.
Why don't you get a life,Kim, so you don't envy mine?
I don't envy alcoholics, Kate.
I work hard.
It steadies me.
Right now, you got to be steady enough to climb Mt.
Everest.
Cut the sarcasm, Kim.
It doesn't suit your image.
The way falling down
drunk suits yours?
God, Kate, I'm so sorry.
Look, I'm in trouble, OK?
Are you satisfied?
I arrive late at photo sessions.
I can't walk straight sometimes.
I need one of these or
I can't even remember
where I'm supposed to be.
I want to stop and
I'm not strong enough.
Well, you don't
have to do this alone.
There's a good
rehab center here.
I can't.
My career would
be over in a week.
Come on, recovery
is a status symbol.
Everybody who's anybody is coming back from something.
Look.
This is Jacqueline, Kim...
little miss young and ruthless.
She wants to be the next
Chamber 10 cover girl.
If they found out I was drying out, she'd take my place.
And once you're off the cover, you never get back.
We're talking about
your life, Kate.
This is my life.
Without it, I don't
have anything.
I wish I could
take your place.
What did you say?
I said, it's...
it's too bad I can't
fill in for you.
No.
Yes.
Take my place.
Kate, don't be crazy.
I told you that I never...
It would work, Kim.
You'd save my
career and my life.
No.
Please?
It's the only way.
You'd check into rehab?
Yes.
I can't do the things
that you do I don't
have your grace or your style.
I'll teach you.
Kim, it would work people always got us confused.
We're from
different worlds now.
I could never be
as free as you are.
I don't have your strength.- You call this strength?
- It would never work.
- You wanna bet?
Get rid of that ponytail.
So?
What do you think?
This is too crazy for words,but I'll try if you'll try.
That's better.
Good.
Come on back.
One, two, three four.
One, two, three, four.
Kate, this will never work.
I can't do this on a runway.
So you won't have to.
We only do the big
runway shows when
we're debuting the new lines.
The Chamber 10 line doesn’t debut for six weeks.
You said you only had tobe in the clinic for four.
Yeah, but I still have
to act like a model.
You only have a
few private showings
scheduled at the salon.
Henri will be so happy I'm not bumping into the customers,
he won't notice your technique.
Henri?
Henri Chambertin of
the house of Chambertin.
Actually, I should
draw you a floor plan.
Paul is his doorman.
You have a nodding acquaintance with the salesgirls,
and Marie is the chief fitter.
I helped her out of a
jam a little while ago,
so if you need her,
you can count on her.
Now who's he?
Philip Clairmont.
He's an American.
He's Henri's new partner,bought a controlling interest
in the company last year.
He's not bad looking.
KATE: Yeah?
Well, he doesn't
have much use for me.
He would love to fire
me, but he can't.
Why not?
Because I'm a star.
The question is, am I?
This will tell
you about everyone
and everything you'll need to know for the next month.
What about the man they opened the club for, Jacques Arneau?
He's gone to Hong
Kong for a month,
so you don't have
to worry about him.
Is he someone special?
No, he owns some nightclubs.
He sort of designs the scene.
Just forget about him.
It's almost 3:00.
Well, let's get ready
and get out of here
before I change my mind.
KIM: Kate, relax.
Fair Oaks has a
great reputation.
They're among the
best in the world,
and they're very discrete.
I know this is hard, Kate, but you’re doing the right thing.
Maybe you should just
phone and tell them
you don't know where I am.
I'll figure out something later.
No, it'll work out.
Just leave it to me and concentrate on getting better.
Ms. Jameson?
I'll take you up and
register you now.
The doctor will be along later.
And don't worry.
We're here to help
you through this, not
judge what brought you to us.
I'll call you
as soon as I can.
I'm sorry, there are no
calls or visits allowed
for the first three weeks.
It's best for all concerned.
I love you, Kate.
And don't worry about a thing.
Mademoiselle Dominique?
Monsieur Arneau requested we meet your plane.
We?
He felt the world
should know Dominique
had returned to Paris.
[photographers chatter]
Stop.
Um, stop.
Stop... [speaking french]
[music playing]
Welcome home.
I'm sorry I had to
send the limo instead
of meeting you in person.
You like the flowers?
Yes, thank you.
I thought that you had,uh, business in Hong Kong.
Yes, I made my
business arrangements
more quickly than I expected.
The new club owner said
you were wonderful.
I'm glad.
Perhaps it's time to discuss another type of performance.
Excuse me?
I told you when I came
back from Hong Kong,
I wanted to discuss
an important matter.
Don't tell me you’ve forgotten, [speaking french]
Actually, uh,
I'm a little tired.
Would you mind if
we discuss it later?
Fair enough.
But we can't leave
it too long, can we?
Let's have dinner at
[inaudible] this week.
That would be fine.
Don't forget to dream of me.
[music playing]
[phone ringing]
Hello?
Who?
Henri.
No, of course I
haven't forgotten.
My plane was late.
I'll be right there.
[music playing]
[SINGING] I'll do it.
I'll do it.
I'll do anything.
I'll do anything for you.
And I will like.
Mademoiselle Dominique.
Good morning, Paul.
Good morning, Dominiques.
Good morning.
Paul's the door man.
You have a nodding acquaintance with the sales girls.
Marie is the fitter.
[WHISPERS] Just confidence.
Relax.
Oh!
Oh, I'm so sorry,
Sorry.
I see you decided
to come back to us.
Yeah, I just went
away for a few days.
Without letting anyone here know where you were going.
Won't happen again.
You may still think you’re a star, but some of us
are having our doubts.
I didn't realize
that visiting my sister
was any of your business.
Anything that takes you out of Paris is my business.
Including my private affairs.
When you go out of town to open a new club for Arneau,
I can't help thinking you
have something to hide.
And I can't help
thinking that you're...
Dominique?
This can't be you.
Look at her, Phillip.
She has put on at
least five pounds.
I think she looks
almost normal.
My customers don't
like normal women.
We will have to give the
finale to Jacqueline.
She will never
get into the gown.
Yeah, she may have had
too much home cooking,
but she is not deaf.
You can talk to me.
And the gown will look better with more of me in it.
What do you think, Phillip?
I think if the gown, fits,we should let her wear it.
Well, thank you.
If you'll excuse
me, Marie's waiting.
Carmen, you're in the solids.
Jacqueline, you're
in the polka dots.
Polka dots make me
look like a child!
You want me to
tell Henri you think
his collection is childish?
Good morning.
Your [inaudible]
is there, Dominique.
Sorry, I'm late.
How was your
mysterious weekend?
Ah, uneventful.
Jacqueline was hoping
you'd fall in love
and never come back.
Oh, I'm sure Dominique would never let her heart
interfere with your career.
In fact, I heard she had it removed so it couldn't.
Your sister must
be an excellent cook.
My sister?
The one you went to visit.
Why don't you put this on?
It's wider in the hips.
All right, everybody.
Everybody else is free
to leave for the day.
Who are you?
I know Dominique's body,
and this is not it.
Are you a twin?
Yes.
Why the hell did she send you?
Where is she?
She's in a rehab center.
Oh, well, she finally admitted she has a problem.
You are a model.
I'm an art history student.
You are as crazy as she is.
You know you'll never
get away with this.
She needs to get well.
I'm only going to cover
for her for a month.
A month?
Oh no!
The new line debuts
next Saturday!
Saturday?
MARIE: Yes.
She told me that it...
No, no, no, no.
Phillip brought the date forward to break the competition.
This is our most important runway show in years.
I can't fake a
big fashion show.
No, of course you can't!
We're just going to
have to go to Phillip
and tell him the truth.
- No, no, no.
No, no.Saturday is almost a week away.
We could... I could take lessons.
You could teach me.
No, I couldn't.
Philip would find
out immediately,
and if you were found out on the runway, we'd all be finished.
This is insane.
Dominique told me that she helped you out of trouble once.
So?
So maybe it's your
turn to help her out.
Dah!
Please, Marie.
She loses her career,
she'll never get sober.
That's true.
Oh, all right.
All right.
I guess I owe her that much.
Thank you.
You just save your thanks until we know that this works.
OK.
MARIE: And lose
those few pounds.
[music playing] [SINGING]I'll do anything.
I'll do anything for you.
I'll do anything.
Everything.
[inaudible]
I'll do anything for you.
I'll do anything.
I'll do anything
happily, happily.
I trust you know
where these go.
La-la.
[inaudible] Mademoiselle.
[whistles]
[music playing]
[SINGING] I'll do
anything for you.
I'll do anything.
I'll do anything for you.
I'll do anything
happily, happily.
You know, you and your sister have more in common
than you think.
KIM: Yeah?
Mm-hm.
Come and sit down for a while.
KIM: No, I've got
to go for a run.
Ah, there's no need to
push yourself so hard.
Besides, Phillipe said he likes you with your new curves.
I don't know how
Kate does this.
Who's Kate?
That was my
sister's real name.
You know, I always thought that she lived this soft life.
A lot of parties, a
lot of boyfriends.
Oh, she has a few.
Jacques Arneau?
Never struck me as her type.
Well, she came home
to do him a favor.
He seems to expect
something more.
You be careful.
He may be a charmer.
Hm, he has all the
charm of a cobra.
I can't thank you enough for all you've done for us.
Oh.
Your sister has a lot of faults, but she helped me when
I desperately needed money.
It was very selfless of her.
That seems to run
in your family.
Yeah, Kate sure can mess things up, but she has spirit.
Now that is the
attitude you need
for the runaway, that spirit.
A body is just a body.
The very best models,
they do it all up here.
Up here.
Mm-hm.
It's the ultimate
strut your stuff, yes?
Yes
You have to believe
that you are the most
beautiful woman in the world.
If you believe it, they will.
[music playing]
Thank you.
It's nerves.
[music playing]
Good.
You will be perfect.
Believe it.
[music playing]
Don't stumble
tonight, Dominique.
[music playing]
Oh, God.
What's the matter with her?
[music playing]
[applause]
AUDIENCE: Bravo!
[cheering]
You top that, if you can.
[music playing]
She's a genius!
You'll sell out the line.
I hope so, Henri,
for both our sakes.
[music playing]
You were inspired!
Mmm!
Actually, I was scared stiff.
Ha ha!
And how are you now?
Exhausted.
Oh.
My dear, you were superb!
Everybody wants to meet you!
Everybody!
Oh, well done, my child.
Nice work.
Come, [inaudible].
[music playing]
Excuse me.
Let me take you home.
- Ah, no.
Henri said...
I don't care what Henri said.
I'm taking you home before you fall down, OK?
Excuse us.
You don't know how
much I appreciate this.
It's very gallant of you.
Well, good...
Are you capable of
undressing on your own?
Yes, I'm quite capable
of undressing on my own.
You're wearing
Henri's merchandise.
Sorry.
I should... I'll be
back in a second.
Oh, and thank you, for getting me out of there because I was...
oh...
fading fast.
[inaudible] I thought the show went quite well.
I was concerned what
effect a drunken model
would make on the customers.
Hey!
I am not drunk, I'm exhausted.
I work my behind
off for this show.
Then get some sleep.
You have a photo shoot
first thing tomorrow.
[music playing]
Yes!
Perfection!
Enough.
Thank you, my dear.
That's all for today.
Dominique, we do the covers now.
But first, we change the lighting, so take a break.
Do you like it?
Yeah, it shows less linear emphasis than his early work,
and his use of light and color is much more confident.
You certainly know what
you're talking about.
Forgive me for
assuming you'd had
too much to drink last night.
It's not like I haven’t given people that impression.
You like this collection?
Yes, I'm write...
I'm reading a book on it.
I get my thoughts
down and I compare
them with the books at home.
Is Venetian Renaissance
art your specialty,
or do you have broader tastes?
Such as?
Favorite work?
Actually Actually, something that I've never seen.
What is it?
It's a bronze in
the private collection
of the Marquis de Belliveau.
Really?
Oh, Nick!
How nice to see you!
Jacques?
Congratulations.
on last evening.
Your string of
triumphs continues.
Thank you.
Monsieur Claremont,
it seems our friend
has assured that Chambertin will survive one more season.
House of Chambertin is as solid as ever, Monsieur Henri.
Taste is a fickle commodity.
No one knows that better than I.
Or I. I believe the,
uh, museum is closed
to the public for the day.
Yes, so I understand.
I, however, came
to see Dominique.
Excuse me.
I made a reservation
for this evening.
8 o'clock, all right?
Dominique?
8:00... ah, sure.
Um, if you'll excuse
me, Jacques, I
have to get back to work.
JACQUES: Don't be late.
Your career may depend on it.
Has she changed since she came back, or is it just me?
No, she's not the same woman.
Not at all.
[music playing]
[knocking]
Hi.
In the 16th century,
the Marquis de
Belleville came to
my family to borrow
money to buy works of art.
Came to your family...
I... I thought that
you were American.
Well, yeah.
I mean, for the last couple of hundred years, sure.
But, uh, before the revolution,we Claremonts were counts,
dukes, whatever you want.
I had no idea that I
was talking to royalty.
Well, hardly.
But you did say they had a sculpture you wanted to see.
KIM: I've never seen so many beautiful sculptures.
Look at this place!
And no one here to enjoy it.
Makes it a privilege to show it to somebody who will.
Thank you.
I come here a lot by myself.
Yeah, right.
It's true, I do!
For 1,000 years
before the revolution,
we Claremonts were
patrons of the arts.
It's something I'd always wanted to get back to.
Oh, is that why you invested in the fashion business?
Well, yeah, I always wanted to return to Paris,
and fashion in its
way is an art form.
Yeah.
So I'd been led to believe the house of Chambertin
could be profitable.
What, it's not?
Well, Henri is a great artist,but, uh, his business sense
is nonexistent.
We needed a very good season.
Needed.
We're about to launch
the new season now.
This morning, somebody broke into Henri's office
while we were doing
your cover shots.
Some sketches and the Muslims patterns were stolen.
Why would anyone
steal his work?
Well, it happens from time to time in this business...
mass marketers in the Far East using his patterns.
Before we could even
break this line,
Henri's creations could be in hundreds of stories.
Did you call the police?
Publicity like
this could ruin us.
Do you have any suspects?
Has to be somebody
inside the firm.
So I think they're working for Jacques Arneau.
Arneau?
Because of his clubs, he has access to all the right people
and all the wrong ones.
You don't think that I had anything to do with it.
Not unless you can be
in two places at once.
Nope.
Oh, that is more beautiful than I expected.
You know, I feel like I'm just getting to know who you are.
Yeah, I know what you mean.
Wanna go out for dinner?
I can't.
I already have plans.
Can't cancel them, huh?
No.
I want to.
Maybe I can persuade you.
Um, could you
just take me home?
Why?
Because there's
someone I have to see.
Sure.
[music playing]
Oh no, mineral water, please.
Thank you.
Watching my weight.
You look enchanting
already, and no life is
worth living without champagne.
No, no, no.
I should have known the
paparazzi would be here.
Dominique is on top once again.
It would be a shame if
this fame were fleeting.
Did you get the sketches?
The sketches?
I'm disappointed.
I heard there was a problem at Chambertin today.
I was hoping that you’d finally come through for me.
This is what you
wanted to discuss.
Don't play innocent.
You weren't that drunk when I first told you about this.
And we both agreed that friends should do each other favors,
didn't we?
Yeah, but it's too risky.
Philip already suspects me because of our friendship.
He does, does he?
Maybe we should tell
him the whole story.
My dearest Dominique...
what would he
think if he knew that your wild evenings at my club
could destroy the reputation of the house of Chambertin
all by themselves?
I doubt that he would listen to what you have to say.
True, but he will
believe his own eyes.
Some may call that pornography.
I prefer to think of it as art.
Quite a night, wasn't it?
Imagine how these would look in one of those magazines
or on Philip's desk.
They're fakes.
My dear, we both
know that you've
lost entire days to the bottle.
And I was always
there, sweetheart,
scraping you up off the floor when you couldn't move.
I don't remember.
Perhaps you were too drunk to remember what you were doing,
perhaps not.
Get me the sketches
and muslin, Cherie.
When I get them, you get these.
And I am prepared to
bring you down along
with the house of Chambertin.
SECRETARY [ON PHONE]:
Fair Oaks Clinic.
Yes, uh, Kate Jameson, please.
It's an emergency.
SECRETARY [ON PHONE]: I'm sorry,there's no contact allowed
for the first three weeks.
But if you'd like
to leave a message...
No, no, no, no.
That's too complicated.
Please just get her to call her sister as soon as she can.
Thank you.
Where's Marie?
Being questioned
by [inaudible]..
His designs have been stolen.
Speaking of which, have you seen Jacques Arneau lately?
Don't bate me, Jacqueline,I'm not in the mood.
From the screaming, it sounds like Marie is about to confess,
whether she did it or not.
Good.
Maybe we'll get a cheap fitter who won't put me in polka dots.
How can you treat
her like this?
All right, Marie,we'll speak to you later.
That woman has given her life to the house of Chambertin.
Yes, she also just bought
herself a new apartment.
So?
Her husband died a year ago.
He was a civil
servant who never made
enough money in his
lifetime to buy a car,
let alone an apartment.
And that's enough to assume she’d destroy the only company
she's ever worked for?
But she just
found an apartment
and somebody else paid for it.
I paid for it.
You?
Yes!
But what didn't she say?
Why should she?
Why should I?
How was your dinner?
I heard you and Arneau
were together all night.
I have done nothing to hurt the house of Chambertin.
That woman.
One day, you want to fire her.
The next, she's every passion you want to associate
with your your designs.
Henri, I think we should risk the publicity
and go to the police.
We'll explain these become the patterns to your creations,
kind of a... a blueprint.
This is not a blueprint!
This is a vision...
a one of a kind
stroke of genius!
Irreplaceable!
We have to replace them.
We have no choice.
We can stay in business unless we market a full line
of designs this season.
Oh yes, have another vision.
It's easy for you to say.
Henri...
No, no, no, no, no.
No, it's the fate of the artist.
I will go seek my muse.
You just pray that I find her.
Marie, why didn't you
tell them that Dominique
gave you the money?
I thought it would
make them suspect her.
You probably would
have been right.
They know that I didn't
steal the designs,
but I don't know how deeply Dominique was involved.
Meaning?
Arneau has photos of her, the kind of photos that make you
a little more than notorious.
No!
She would have
agreed to do anything
to keep them from being seen.
And the way he saw
it, it was obvious
he thought she'd
done it for him.
I've always thought
that man was dangerous.
He's a street thug with money.
You know, there's a
rumor there is bad blood
between him and Phillip.
Well, whatever's
going on, I just lied
to Phillip to cover for Kate.
Oh!
You're very attracted
to him, aren't you?
Me?
No, of course not.
Oh, good.
That's one less
thing to worry about.
OK, there is a
little attraction.
But it's not me that he sees.
It's... it's Dominique.
Oh?
I knew we shouldn't have played that game again.
Game?
When I was 17, I met this boy, Peter Robinson.
He was the first boy
I ever had a crush on.
He asked me out, but I had a term paper to deliver,
so Kate took my place.
And what happened?
She was her usual
boisterous self,
and he fell in love with her.
Oh, that girl.
KIM: After that, we never played the game again.
This is an exclusive original.
I can't go on a
catwalk like this.
There is no catwalk.
You walk among the guests.
Oh, Jacqueline.
Want to wear this?
Trying to impress Phillip with your restraint?
Oh look, Phillip
brought a lady with him.
Lovely, isn't she?
Turn around, please.
What do you think, Mimi?
It's not really
my style, Phillip.
Thank you, Dominique.
Dominique, I want
you to meet Mimi.
Um, actually,
I'm on my way out.
I'm pleased to
meet you, Dominique.
I can never wear clothes the way you do, not even when it's just
[inaudible].
Dominique, my
sister, Mimi Dupre.
Your Your sister.
Hi there.
It's nice to meet you.
Hi.
You look like
a Rafael Madonna.
When are you due?
Well, two weeks but might just as well be two months.
Phillip tells me you're
quite the art expert.
Oh, hardly.
Hardly.
Well, I'm sure
he's also told you
that our family's had a long,uh, relationship with the arts.
Yes, yes.
Mimi spends much of
her time raising money
to restore damaged paintings.
Ah, ah!
I thought if I can get you to host one of our fundraisers,
it might draw some attention.
Oh, uh... mmm...
Oh, you know, where Dominique goes, the press follows.
It really would help.
Do you want to sit
down tomorrow night?
My husband Stefan
and I are staying
with Phillip in the city
until the baby is born.
Please, say yes.
Yes, yes.
OK, I would be glad to help.
Tomorrow evening.
[music playing]
What do you want now, Jacques?
What I've always
wanted, Cheri.
I have customers who
are getting anxious.
Now where are those sketches?
I told you, I don't have them.
Don't lie to me!
Now, I will give
you one more day,
or your career might not be the only thing I bring to an end.
OK.
Thank you.
Wow, this is a
stunning building.
It's one of the last
private houses in Paris.
So how long have
you lived here?
Well, I lived here as a child, but, uh, my father, uh,
was unhappy here,
so we had to leave.
It's hard to imagine
not being happy here.
[music playing]
MIMI: Hi!
Hi.
Dominique, you remember my sister, Mimi.
Thank you for coming.
I hope you'll feel at home.
Thank you for having me.
Of course.
She'll be dazzled by
the meal I prepared.
This is my husband Stefan.
He, uh, likes to
help in the kitchen.
I had to pay my cook
extra for the privilege.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
Your home is magnificent.
The last count de Claremont had it built in 1770.
Our father bought
it and had restored.
Ah, Philip told me that it was only a drafty old house.
In France, understatement is.
Everything
Come on, let me
show you around.
If I'd said, come to our home with everything our terribly
important family
has ever bought,
he'd have turned
me down for sure.
Mimi, your
humility is showing.
It comes from inbreeding and living too far from Versailles.
Who's she?
Our grandmother.
I can see the resemblance.
Do you have a painting
of your mother?
I do in my home, but, uh...
Stefan, let's say we go get a nice bottle of wine, huh?
I'll ask the butler to.
I'd rather do it myself.
[music playing]
MIMI: Oh!
Oh, oh, oh.
You all right?
Yes, sorry.
The baby's just restless.
Don't let Stefan know.
He fusses.
OK.
And Philip is even worse.
You two seem to be very close.
Yeah.
We had to learn
to stick together.
Our father brought the family to France when we were kids.
He wanted to move
back permanently.
Then mother left
him for another man.
Sorry.
Dad immediately took
us back to the states.
It was an awful time.
Philip has never really
trusted a woman since.
Surely there must
have been someone.
Yeah, he's had
girlfriends, but no one
he's ever given his heart to.
All right, you two.
The cook says my first course is ready to serve.
Great!
Now we use the pregnant lady as a guinea pig, hm?
Claremont used to be one of the most famous and respected
titles in all of France.
We still didn't
keep our ancestors
from losing their heads
during the revolution.
STEFAN: When Mimi
wanted to marry me,
her family was astounded.
I'm just a mutt.
But a very rich one.
STEFAN: Would you like
some coffee, Dominique?
Oh, no thank you.
Everything is delicious.
I'll compliment the chef.
Would you like
to take a stroll?
I guess what I'm asking you Todo is show me my own etchings.
Well, I doubt
that I can teach you
anything about your own art.
Well, you might be surprised.
These brush strokes
evolved into a figure.
So you're saying
the artist was just
feeling the composition
as he went along?
Yes.
The best don't really
paint a picture.
They make you feel it.
When you sense that
rush of emotion,
you know that you're in the presence of great art.
Yes you do.
What a great
place to grow up in.
Oh, I think the beauty
was lost on me then.
My childhood is not something I remember fondly.
Mostly, I remember being alone.
You're very beautiful.
Stefan says it's time to put the pregnant lady to bed.
Thank you so much for oh!
Mimi!
My God!
- Get her onto a chair.
No, no, no, no.
Leave her here.
Get her a pillow.
Get her a pillow
for under her head.
Are you all right?
Mm-hm.
Oh, God.
OK, call the doctor, Stefan.
I'll get the car.
No, call the doctor now.
He's coming!
What...
The baby's coming.
What?
Just relax.
Stefan!
[music playing]
They are both going to be OK.
Can we see her?
We three are all going to the hospital for the night.
We'll be here if
you need anything.
The baby would never have made it without you.
Thank you.
Thank you!
Mmm!
It was quite the night.
You were amazing!
I've never met anybody
quite like you.
[romantic music]
[SINGING IN FRENCH]
Fresh croissants
from the local bakery.
Mmm.
And the coffee?
I always make the coffee.
Mmm, smells like heaven.
You smell like heaven.
Yeah?
Have you always
been this beautiful?
Phillip, I want you to care about me for who I am.
I want that too.
I want to know all about you.
I want to know all
about your life.
I want to know all about your family, why you chose modeling
when art is obviously the thing closest to you,
and why'd it take
me so long to find
out how incredible you are.
I know why.
Mimi.
She told you about our...
our mother.
She was... she was
very beautiful too.
But it was her sole
reason for [inaudible]..
The day she left, she
put her arms around me
and said I love you more than anything in the world.
And then she walked out
and never came back.
You're the first person
I've ever told that to.
Phillip, there's something I have to tell you.
Not now.
OK.
You give up easily?
Sure.
[inaudible] people talking if we show up together?
I [inaudible] speechless.
I don't care.
Mademoiselle Dominique?
Monsieur Arneau asked me to get this to you right away.
- [inaudible]
- What is it?
What is it?
Come on.
Just come on!
What is it?
Give it to me!
Aren't you going to open it?
No.
What is it?
Let's just go upstairs, OK?
There something
I shouldn't see?
Phillip... where's Jacques?
Up here, Cheri.
Can I get you a drink,or are you still dieting?
What did you
hope to accomplish
by sending me those photos?
Just a reminder.
I gave you fair warning.
The next one will
go to the press.
Well, your little reminder was almost seen by Philip.
I would have given anything to seen that little aristocrat's
face if that had happened.
Why is that?
I hate all his
kind, making people
fawn over them and
do their bidding
just because they have money.
Well, I hope that there’s more to this than that.
My family worked their fingers to the bone for the Claremonts
and they tore us apart.
And?
I don't need you
to believe anything.
I'll give you until
tomorrow night
to deliver those sketches.
After that, I can't
be held responsible
for the consequences.
Your time has run out, my sweet.
Well, you can do whatever you want with the photographs
because I'm going to the police.
JACQUES: Don't forget to tell them you took the sketches,
and I have a witness if you want to tell them about her.
What witness?
The newspapers will
have a field day...
those lurid photographs,
top model brought
down by her biggest rival.
Jacqueline.
This will give her everything she's always wanted.
You're trapped.
It's the flip side of
the party, Dominique.
Now go and get me
what I asked for.
If what you say is
true, this is the end
of the house of Chambertin.
It's unbelievable...
all this history ruined
by some sordid little story.
Could Jacqueline
have stolen it for her?
She's a hungry one.
I've never seen anyone want a magazine cover like she does.
But no one would stoop that low.
Was she friend of Arneau's?
No, no.
She never goes to the clubs.
Her career is everything.
So what's going on
with her and Dominique?
You would have
to ask your sister.
I can't.
The clinic called.
She checked herself out and they don't know where she went.
That girl.
Well, maybe she didn't
know that these things
were going to happen.
And maybe I don't
know my sister at all.
And maybe you should go back to your old life.
These are not your problems.
I can't.
And finding out the truth is the only thing that's
going to save her from Arneau.
And maybe save
you and Phillip?
There's not much
chance of that.
Henri, what are you thinking?
The new collection.
No, no, I mean, are...
are you going somewhere?
Why are the drawings out?
Well, because I've been working on the new collection.
They are beautiful, yes?
Yes, they are.
I just hope we're the ones that get to sell them.
You know, you’re practically inviting someone
to come in and steal these.
Oh, don't be
ridiculous, Phillip.
A true artist cannot function in an atmosphere of paranoia.
Besides, I'm in a rush.
I have tickets for the
opera, and you know
I hate to miss the overture.
So I go!
Henri.
[music playing]
Ah, wait here, please.
Thank you.
[music playing]
Hello there.
I'm looking for
Jacqueline le Claire.
Mama!
What are you doing here?
We need to talk.
Wait for me in the front room.
Mommy needs to
talk to this lady.
Come on, let's go
to your room, OK?
Your son's a
beautiful little boy.
What do you want?
You have something
which belongs to Henri.
What makes you think that?
Jacques told me.
Why would you do
something like this?
Don't pretend you don't know.
I don't know.
You You had told
him about my past.
He's blackmailed me ever since.
I never told him anything.
Does he have something
like that on you?
He's playing us
off of each other.
Yes.
He finds your weakness
and exploits it.
With you, it was your drinking.
With me, it was what I
came to care for my son.
There were so many men offering money, and my son needed food.
I was all alone.
I was desperate.
I... I thought if I
took the drawings
and told Jacques you had them...
That it would
finish my career.
I thought maybe that
would be the end of it.
He'd have beaten Phillip.
That's what he really wants.
Why?
His parents worked
for the Claremonts
until Philip's mother ran off with Jacques' father.
Without his father, Jacques' family sank into poverty.
He's always blamed the Claremonts for what happened.
You'll have to return these.
I can't!
It was hard enough
getting them out.
No, it's impossible!
Yes you can.
You just walk in there,
you put them back,
and you walk back out again.
I can't fight him.
Wait.
This won't stop him.
I'll handle Jacques.
[music playing]
Hi, Paul.
I'm just locking
up, Miss Dominique.
Um, I forgot my earrings.
Just a second?
All right.
[music playing]
I'm returning the sketches.
Having taken the opportunity to copy them, no doubt.
No.
I'm returning the
sketches for someone
who took them and regretted taking them afterward.
Who?
I can't say.
Oh, of course not.
Tell me.
How much is your friend Jacques paying you to do this?
Philip, I didn't steal them.
Stop lying to me.
I'm not lying to you.
When did you decide to use me me in your little game?
Was it while we were waiting to see if Mimi and the baby
would live?
I didn't mean to hurt you.
[music playing]
Dominique?
This cafe has inspired artists for centuries, all the greats.
It's fitting you should choose for my latest triumph.
I've never really thought of you as an artist, Jacques.
You are the clay in
my hands, Dominique.
Where are those designs?
Show me my talents
have not been wasted.
Blackmail isn't an
art, it's a crime.
Such ugly words from
such a beautiful woman.
You disappoint me.
Why?
Because I'm not afraid of your photographs or your threats?
Because I'm not afraid
of a low life pimp?
Don't tempt me, Dominique.
Give me those sketches or I will ruin your career.
You see, I don't
think it's the sketches
that you really
want because that's
not interesting enough for you.
Jacques, you want to use me, at least give me the satisfaction
of knowing why.
I want to see Phillip's face when all he has left
are his title and his arrogance.
I want to see him drowning in your betrayal.
You're unbelievable.
Thank you.
Now give me those sketches.
My buyer is waiting.
My photographs, Jacqueline’s photographs with negatives.
No.
I ask myself, why
would you help her?
She hates everything about you.
Well, that's the deal.
You don't have them.
Now, it's not very nice
being threatened, is it?
You want to get Phillip?
Then you play by my rules.
Stay out of my life.
Dominique!
Hurry, the house of...
You're finished!
Do you hear me?
You are finished!
Don't tempt me, Dominique.
Give me those sketches or I will ruin your career.
HENRI: Dominique!
Come in.
Jacqueline has just
told me everything.
I couldn't let
you take the blame.
Thanks.
You were both of
you very foolish
not to tell me
what was going on.
I always look after my girls!
And if Arneau had
made any trouble,
well, I think my
contacts with the press
are more powerful than his.
I am owed a great
number of favors.
Well, I think
that this will help.
Jacques admitted everything.
Dominique!
Where are you going?
You have to give
Philip the news.
I think he'd rather
hear that from you.
Who's there?
Hey, Kim.
Oh, looking good!
It suites you.
What are you doing here?
And why did you
leave the clinic?
I read about the
new line in the paper
and I didn't want you
to deal with Arneau,
so I came back to take over.
Well, it's too late.
He was here all along.
It's OK.
We'll talk about it later.
Now how are you doing
with the program?
Let's just say that I had sometime to look at who I'd become.
I'm sorry.
Promise me you'll
continue treatment.
I've already looked
into a clinic here,
and I start next week.
Anyone find us out?
Only Marie, but
she covered for us.
Well, if there's
one thing I've learned
these past few weeks,
it's that I have
to be honest about who I am.
So tomorrow, we'll go in and I’ll tell them the truth.
No, I, uh...
I'm going to call
and thank Marie,
but I'm taking the first
flight out of here.
She what?
She's going home to America.
I could not talk her out of it.
What time is she leaving?
I don't know, but
she said she had
time to say goodbye to Paris.
[knocking]
Dominique!
You can't leave!
- Phillip...
Look, you've got to give me a chance to apologize.
- I need you!
Phillip!
Look, I know that
night in my apartment.
meant something to both of us...
Oh, Phillip, you
better stop right there.
I am not the woman
that you think I am.
Hey, buddy!
Watch where you're going!
Damn Frenchmen!
Dominique told
me what you did.
I was crazy enough to trust you.
Yeah, you were.
It's just like I told, hun.
French... they ain't like us.
I know.
You know what?
You're going to have
to marry me so we
can work on this every day.
Don't you think you need to know the name of the girl
before you marry her?
[music playing]