[doorbell ringing]
[security alarm ringing]
[door closes]
[ringing continues]
[beeps]
[ringing stops]
[rattling]
[straining]
[door opens]
What the...
-[phone ringing]
-Here we go.
[alarm keypad beeping]
[keys jingling]
[exhales]
[humming]
[doorbell rings]
[man] Come on in.
[door closes]
Hello?
Hi. Go on up.
I'll be right there.
[man humming]
[woman] Hi, there. Nice place.
-[man] Filipino, right?
-Actually, half Filipino
half Samoan,
[man] Mmm-hmm.
You know, I've had dates
with over 50 nationalities.
[woman] The UN needs
more like you.
[man]
Equal opportunity fucking.
That'll be my platform.
[woman] Oh! Oh, hold on, hon.
Your friend there
needs a raincoat.
Okay, I'll be back in a minute.
[man humming]
[man urinating and humming]
-[sighs]
-[water flushes]
[man humming]
[man] Hey, I'm gonna
take a quick shower.
You wanna join me?
[woman] No, thanks.
I don't like to get wet.
[man humming]
[telephone ringing]
Oh, fuck.
Hello.
Hello?
Nice.
[security alarm beeping]
[man] Who's there?
Call 911.
What, are you crazy?
Me call the cops?
[alarm continues beeping]
[dog barking in distance]
[man] All right,
you son of a bitch!
Come and get it.
[alarm continues beeping]
[officer] Xenia Kelly?
[horn blaring]
[indistinct announcement]
Brought him in an hour ago.
He was asking for you
before he went under.
Where'd you find him?
In an alley. Drunk.
Pretty nearly asphyxiated
on his vomit.
I'm very sorry.
The nurse was asking
if you'd be,
you know, making
the arrangements
with the hospital.
Me?
[chuckles softly] Arrangements?
You know what, you just say
three Hail Marys
and then pull the plug.
[Xenia] You're wasting
a good candle.
-[door closes]
-He is your father.
Piece of shit.
You're more like him
than you know.
Thanks. That's really what
I needed to hear, mommy.
Look, I... I can't stay.
I just... This is crazy.
I just came here
to give you this.
-It's too much.
-Just take it. I got a new job.
-It's a big
landscape consultation.
-No. No. No, no, no, no.
[Xenia] What are you doing?
Mommy, what are you doing?
I am going to the hospital.
He falls out of the sky
after 20 years and
you want to go see him?
I should be there.
Come with me.
There's not enough money
in the world.
I'm sorry.
Where you going?
Out. To a bar. To have a drink.
What dear old dad
would do, isn't it?
[upbeat music playing]
♪ Only one man, baby
-Hey, white boy.
-Hey.
Come on.
Hey, Mamma Mia.
What's up?
I just quit smoking.
Oh, I'm proud of you, Xenia.
My father turned up.
He left when I was five.
Then one day I'm eight,
he shows up,
takes me to the zoo.
And all day, all day,
I'm working up the courage,
you know, to ask him
if he's gonna come
visit me again. You know
what he says to me?
He says, "Don't expect me to be
some kind of Disneyland dad."
That's cold.
Oh, shit. I need to dance.
Come dance with me.
In my dreams I'd dance
with you, Xenia, here,
I'm the bartender.
[men chattering]
♪ Attraction
[laughter]
♪ Oh, I just wanna
be mean to you
Give me the night ♪
♪ To show you sweet love
♪ Make love to...
-I don't like to dance alone.
-Huh.
I don't like to dance at all.
Well, you can never trust a man
who doesn't like to dance.
Nobody said you were
supposed to trust me.
♪ Oh, girl
♪ Take me
♪ Mmm, Give me the night
[chatter]
♪ Give me, give me, give me
♪ Give me the night
♪ To show you sweet love
♪ Let me love you up
All through the night ♪
[crowd cheering and clapping]
-[woman] All right!
-[man whooping]
See you around.
[Latin American music playing]
Hey, I don't know
what happened to my wallet.
Uh, I can leave my watch
while I go get some money.
What do I need
with a goddamn watch?
Well, what do you want me
to do? Wash the dishes?
Please put it on my tab,
it's okay.
I can take care of this myself.
[bartender] You can't take care
of it yourself.
So say thank you to the lady.
If you want, you can
leave me your watch.
Thanks, I appreciate it.
I got to say I've been having
a bad night.
Would you like another drink?
[chattering]
Maybe some other time.
[car starting]
[Xenia] Hey!
Cowboy!
Your bad night just got better.
Well, how about that.
[car engine stops]
So where'd you find it?
I didn't find it.
There's a couple of wise guys
in there, if you know
what to look for.
-Oh. yeah?
-Mmm-hmm.
What I owe you
for those drinks?
You're insulting me.
I'm Xenia Kelly.
Garden consultant.
I do a quarterly,
Pacific Native Garden.
I'm sure you've seen it.
Uh...
-Pacific Native Garden?
-Mmm-hmm.
Very nice.
[laughs] Oh, wait,
no, no. no, no, no.
Now, this is where
you're supposed to tell me
something about yourself.
Bram Hatcher.
I'm a rancher.
Horses?
Snakes.
Snakes?
Yeah. I, uh, breed and sell
them to pet shops mostly.
I got a couple of acres
up at Fraser Cove.
Well, I should've guessed
you'd be into something weird.
[chuckles softly]
I always liked reptiles.
So you like snakes
better than people?
On a bad day.
You know...
You never did tell me
why it was such a bad night.
[chuckles softly]
It's not anymore.
[car starting]
[Ray] Yeah, I'll come see you
next Sunday, I promise you.
[dogs barking]
Okay, I gotta go.
Yeah, I gotta go. mom.
Okay? I gotta go.
Yeah, I'll call you later. Bye.
-[knocking at door]
-[dogs barking]
Come on. Come on,
Come on, come on,
come on. Inside.
Jesus Christ,
get the dogs fixed.
[man] Great. Now you want me
to emasculate my dogs?
Go and get them laid.
They're too excitable.
[sighs] Right.
They're guard dogs.
Will you ever consider
an alarm system?
Like the kind
you so confidently disarm?
Listen, my dogs are not just
ordinary dogs, you know.
They're Egyptian
Pharaoh Hounds.
Otherwise known as
the Ibicenco.
They have been pure-bred
since 3000 BC.
Ray, those dogs aren't even
the same breed.
Yeah, well, Molly.
Molly is a bit of a stray,
but, you know, she has
the heart of an Ibicenco.
[laughs] Man,
you're so full of shit.
Five for the pearls.
Five?
Do you know what those
go for at Bulgari's?
They're rare.
Makes them hard to move.
Check out the diamonds. Derco.
Shame to break up the settings.
Some of these are scratched.
Fuck you, Ray.
Probably when you
took them out.
Look, I know
how to handle stones.
If they're scratched,
then that's the way I got them.
[smacks lips] Seven.
-Twelve.
-Eight.
Don't treat me
like a junkie, Ray.
Eight five.
And that is the best I can do.
That is more than 20%.
[chuckles softly] 20%.
Twenty-percent.
That's the story of my life.
And what do I got to do
to get a 100? [chuckles softly]
You know, you should...
You should get out
of this crap.
You know, you should go back
to lumberjack state
or wherever it was,
and just read books
about kings.
"True hope is swift, and flies
as swallow's wings..."
I don't remember. [chuckles]
"Kings it makes gods,
and meaner creatures..."
"...Kings." Right.
See what I mean?
That just comes out of you.
It's incredible,
you could do so much better.
So could you, Xi.
[birds chirping]
[door creaking]
[crow cawing]
[Xenia] Hello, snake rancher.
I'm looking for
a Suriname Red Tail Boa.
Very exotic.
Hard to find.
Yeah, well, I hear they run
like crazy from people.
Well, some breeds
handle Homo Sapiens
better than others.
How did you find me?
I asked around
the snake grapevine.
There's not that many of you.
Well, I'm not going to ask
how you got in.
Front door.
Ooh.
-Left it open, huh?
-Hm.
Ha! How silly of me.
So, do you do this often?
What?
Just walk into men's houses.
No, I just wanted
to see a snake ranch.
[glasses clink]
[Xenia] They look happy.
Yeah. You, uh, give them food,
shelter, warmth...
Maybe even some love?
[laughs] Snakes
don't need a lot.
Too bad you can't say
the same thing about people.
[Bram] This is
a Burmese python.
[chuckles nervously]
[chuckles softly]
You didn't strike me
as a squeamish type.
No? How do I strike you?
Barbed wire with perfume.
Sometimes I'm scared shitless.
Well, fear's just
nature's way
of making you smart.
Come on, buddy.
So why did you come?
I just wanted to know
the truth I guess.
And?
I haven't decided.
Ah, so it doesn't matter
what I say.
Well, it never matters
what people say.
It's what they do.
So...
If I wanted you to leave...
[ice tray cracking]
...how do I get you out?
You could call the police.
[Bram laughs]
Or you could just tell me
that you want me
to leave and I'll leave.
[glasses clinking]
I didn't say that...
I want you to leave.
You didn't say anything.
[Bram] Do I have to say?
Tell me that you don't want me.
I didn't say.
I didn't want you here.
[Xenia] Tell me that
you don't want me.
[Bram] I didn't say
I didn't want you.
[Xenia] Tell me that...
Tell me...
[breathing heavily]
[gasps]
[suspenseful music playing]
[clicks]
[dramatic music playing]
[metal clinks]
So these rated
for half-inch steel cable?
Oh, you bet.
It's got a ten-year guarantee.
You're looking at the best.
[cell phone ringing]
Hello.
[Bram on phone]
What do you wear?
Nothing.
When can I see you?
When do you want to see me?
Now.
-Uh...
-[honking]
Running some errands?
Can you hang on a second?
And where are you?
Oh, I'm out about.
I miss you bad.
How bad?
Real bad.
I lie down, I smell you
on the pillow.
Then change the sheets.
I feel your hands on me
when I wake up at night.
Take a shower.
Oh, I need to wash off.
Look, I'm busy tonight.
Do you think you can defer
some gratification?
Oh, well, no, no,
I'm bad at that.
Tomorrow.
How about a picnic?
Sounds perfect.
I'll make it worth your wait.
[instrumental music playing]
[Xenia] First the Indians,
then the settlers.
and then the rich people.
[Bram] That's the deal.
People hang on to things
until somebody rips them off.
I thought this was
supposed to be a picnic.
It is.
A very special little picnic.
[security alarm beeping]
[keypad beeping]
What is it, Xenia?
This is Cassie Michael's house.
-She asked me to cat sit.
-Oh.
Like to meet Cassie sometime.
Well, she's in Portland
for a few days.
She just called me
and asked me to feed the cat
and water the plants.
It's Mayan Snake God, Chac.
It's worth fifty thou,
give or take.
Here, kitty, kitty,
kitty, kitty.
Here, kitty, kitty, kitty.
-[cat meowing]
-Hello, you.
You hungry? Hm?
You hungry?
So this was a good idea, huh?
So how did you meet Cassie?
We're getting our legs waxed.
[chuckles]
They're pouring this
hot gunk all over us, you know,
and Cassie turns to me
and she says,
"Maybe you can save
my evening primrose."
Well, then the wax
starts to harden
and she wants to hold my hand
because she's scared.
I don't know,
there's something,
something about pain,
you know, even...
stupid girly pain like that.
Anyway, afterwards she had me
do her entire garden.
She has the most beautiful
evening primrose.
Did you know
that evening primrose
only blooms at night?
Nothing but the best
for girl Cassie, huh?
[Xenia] Hm.
[glasses clink]
Hey, Colin.
Hey, Brammy.
Hey, buddy, wait up.
Hey, check this out.
Last night, some guy
steals a pink Merc.
-Now, who the fuck
would steal a pink car, huh?
-[laughs]
Oh, man, drugs, cops.
We all getting done.
Yeah, it's the lead, man.
in the air.
Things were a whole lot simpler
ten years ago.
Ah, you're missing the uniform.
I don't miss the uniform.
But I liked it when we were
partners, you know?
[Bram] Yeah, me too.
[chatter]
[telephone ringing]
[dramatic music playing]
[indistinct announcement]
[chatter]
[honking]
-[Colin] Hey, Bram.
-Colin.
Mind if, uh, I look around?
Might be related to something
I've been working on.
Sure.
We got a guy and a gal
gardening across
the street saw them.
Walks in, polish off
a $300 bottle of champagne
and the caviar.
Lifts some priceless
pre-Colombian gizmo
and three hundred fifty grand
worth of stones.
-Jesus Christ.
-Can you believe it?
The woman kept her jewelry
in the fucking deep freeze.
Read an article somewhere
that said it would
survive a fire.
-Forcible injury?
-Uh-uh.
Maid was fired last week.
Took off to Guadalajara.
The perp had a key, alarm goes.
knew the occupants
were out of town.
Help yourself.
[officers chattering]
[camera shutter clicking]
-[officer] Yeah, I guess
it's temporary.
-[camera shutter clicking]
[officer chattering]
[Colin] Bram, what the fuck?
What the fuck
are you doing, man?
I never had $300 champagne.
Man, I got enough problems
without you mixing
your prints in.
I'd have you arrested.
Yeah, you know,
I've been doing
dumb shit like that all day.
You know, it's the lead, right?
Okay, I'm sorry, man.
I'm sorry.
Look, I'll
get out of your hair.
It's not my guy's style
anyway, right?
Forget about it.
[sighs]
[siren wailing in distance]
[man] You don't worry.
I'll go check.
Good evening.
[instrumental music playing]
[siren blaring]
You gonna bust me, Bram,
you better wait till you can
find more in my car
than a spare tire
and a bottle of Obsession.
Get your dirty
cop hands off of me!
You have a very interesting
investigative style, don't you?
Ever occur to you that I didn't
want to make this arrest?
Yeah, right. You just happened
to meet a woman in a bar,
and what a coincidence,
she's a crook and you're a cop,
and you just happen to have
a fucking book on her?
I mean, come on.
Opposites attract, but that
strikes me as a slight
compatibility problem.
Xenia, I was at that bar
because your car was spotted
near a robbery
a couple of months ago, okay?
I was backgrounding you,
all right?
How the hell did I know
you were gonna come in?
When you did, well...
I was attracted to you,
all right? Hey.
Hey! I tried to bail.
You hunted me up, remember?
-After that...
-Yeah, and after that,
you developed a little
conflict of interest.
Is that fair?
Yeah, well, you could safely
say I forfeited my case. Yeah.
And what does that mean?
It means you just
committed grand larceny
and I don't give a damn.
I don't want us to end.
And what makes you think
this isn't already over?
Look, I'm still a cop, okay?
All I ask is that
you don't rub my face in it.
When we're together,
if we're together, that...
Just leave out the part about
how we earn our daily bread.
So I just keep my mouth shut
and go on being
acrobatic in bed,
and I don't have to worry?
That's not what I said!
Look, you know,
I am not exactly
what you would call
an upstanding citizen.
All right? I routinely
break six out of the ten
commandments,
-but I've got...
-You told me you were
a garden consultant!
That's all I want to know!
Here's your goddamn file.
I never turned it in.
Nobody downtown
knows you exist.
You play kinda fast and loose,
don't you?
Ever since I met you, yeah.
Then I guess
I haven't been very good
for you, then, have I?
Maybe been too good.
Hey, the world's full of rules.
In the end, you got
to answer to yourself.
[breathing heavily] What if
they found out?
I'll be suspended,
probably fired.
[both breathing heavily]
[chattering]
Here you go.
Lettuce and something.
[sighs]
How come every day
these things look worse?
I don't know, man,
because they are.
That Verdugo job.
Anything come in?
Yeah. They find your prints
all over the goddamn place.
Besides me.
Well, a lovely couple
had loved practice
along with their champagne.
[laughs] Made themselves
right at home.
Yeah, sounds like fun.
Oh, yeah. You're telling me.
Anything else?
What do you mean
"anything else"?
Yeah. A whole group
of extraterrestrials
came in this morning
and confessed.
"Anything else."
That the hell are you talking
about? What do you care?
Yeah, yeah.
Hey! My new tie.
[Xenia breathing heavily]
[exhales loudly]
Mm.
What is the matter with you?
I think I am bored
with the country life.
You can't... You can't
spend a whole day
potting, watering damn plants.
Yeah, well... [grunts]
[straining]
Read a book or something.
I don't like sitting around.
I want to... I want to move.
I want to go somewhere.
I mean, dance. I mean,
you didn't have
a radio in there.
Do you have a radio?
No, I don't think so.
-So you want to dance?
-Yeah, I wanna dance.
Huh? Well, come here.
-How about this?
-[Xenia laughs]
What the hell is that?
Oh, some kind of
strange two-step.
-Do you mind?
-No, I mean like...
You know, escape velocity?
-You ever heard of that?
-No.
It's the speed that, um,
that a rocket needs
to get beyond gravity.
Well, I want to go
that fast sometimes.
Oh, is that why you steal?
So you could go fast? Escape?
-No, I steal because
I'm good at it.
-Well...
I mean, why are you a cop?
Good question.
Well, I thought it was because
you liked being a good guy.
Well, every cop likes
being in a good guy.
You know...
Good and bad, they're just
concepts of the system
that fell apart
a long time ago.
[Bram] I'll tell you a story.
A couple years ago,
I'm up for a promotion.
And I catch this guy
with a hot stereo.
Now he's living in this...
crap hole of a van
with the wife, couple kids.
The guy, he's so scared
he can't even talk.
But the wife, she is
begging me to let him go.
So I tell them... [straining]
just keep the damn stereo
and get out of town.
The next day,
he is busted for crack.
-Mm. [laughs]
-And he's wailing for me.
Mr. Mercy.
Next thing I know,
I'm on probation
in this asshole I trained
is my boss.
Mm. And look at you now.
And now you're having
an illicit love affair
with a crook.
Now you're spending
all your time
slinking around in secret.
All right, all right.
I know you're restless.
Are you hungry?
Yes.
[Xenia] I was 17 and his name
was Constantine Alexakos.
But everybody
called him "Connie".
And he did, he did a lot
of second-story work.
And I used to always ask him
if I could go with him,
and he would always,
always tell me no.
Until finally,
one day I got to him.
I'll not tell you
how I got to him.
-All right.
-I really got to him.
And after that first house,
I thought...
this is it.
But his specialty was safes.
One day we were doing
this big old Schneider.
You know, which...
The tumbler's the size
of a dinner plate,
and this piece of C-4
went off in his hand.
I mean, I'm standing there
and I'm watching him,
and it's like... Boom!
And all this blood is spurting
and his index finger
is just gone.
-And then, we spent...
-[both laugh]
We spent the next
five minutes looking for it.
-[laughs]
-Not to save it.
You know, but because
it had his print on it.
-[Bram chuckles]
-I...
I don't do safes anymore.
My favorite public servant!
My favorite public ass.
Ricky Madden.
Xenia Kelly.
-You're not really
going out with this guy...
-Yes, I am.
Now, Madden, be civil,
just shut up and
get out of here.
What do you do, Mr. Madden?
Well, he's a lawyer.
-A criminal... lawyer.
-[both laughing]
Well, you know, you don't
look like a lawyer.
Well, thank you.
I don't really think
of myself as one.
Now, isn't that right,
Mr. Hatcher?
See, um, along the way,
some of his beach body
has got caught up
in the dope he is.
Now, you're the one
that keeps him
riding the waves, aren't you?
You know, Xenia,
it's tough being a cop.
You watch people break the law
and get away with it.
Watch him get rich...
Get your goddamn hands off her.
...bust your ass
and come up empty.
-But then...
-I said, get your hands off.
Detective Hatcher'd like
to think of himself
as arctic white.
But could it be,
he's a couple of notches
down on the grays...
-[man 1] Hey, whoa.
Hey, hey, hey.
-[man 2] What's going on?
[both grunting]
[gun cocks]
[Ricky] Be careful, Brammy boy.
Be very, very careful.
All right, folks, I hate
to break this up,
but who'll be taking care
of this check?
I think this one's on you,
Mr. Madden.
[Ricky chuckles softly]
[thunder rumbling]
[Bram] Come back.
I can't sleep without you
anymore. I wake up.
[Xenia] I gotta go.
Is this a job?
We don't discuss
business, remember?
You want to come
with me, don't you? Hm?
What, are you bored up there?
All right, hot stuff.
Teach me.
I work alone.
Well...
-You said that I'd be good.
-Yeah, I said you would
be good at it.
I didn't say that
I wanted a partner.
[Bram] Why?
[Xenia] Well, because sooner
or later, they let you down.
I don't want
to be your partner.
I wanna be your student.
You had Connie.
Let me have you.
So you wanna learn
how to be a thief?
Hm?
You wanna learn how the...
case prospects and...
the security systems,
tell real from fakes?
Risk getting shot?
-[breathing heavily]
-Hm?
You wanna do that again?
[Bram moans]
What if we get caught?
[straining] You willing
to do time?
-Huh?
-[grunts softly]
Are you willing,
in your heart of hearts,
to cross over?
Huh?
[instrumental music playing]
[ominous music playing]
[bottle rattling]
[objects clattering]
[car approaching]
Let's go.
[indistinct murmurs]
[grunts]
[gun cocking]
Don't move, asshole,
or I'll fucking kill you!
Drop it, now!
On your knees.
I said, on your knees,
Get down on the fucking floor!
You alone?
Who else is here?
Answer me, damn it!
Talk to me, motherfucker!
Or you're dead.
You want to fuck
with me, asshole? I'll blow
your fucking head off!
[gunshot]
Hey.
If you're out there,
we need an ambulance on Elmont.
[police 1] Two peeps.
Through the back door!
[police 2] All right,
I got it, I got it!
[police 1]
Through here, up here!
[both grunting]
[sirens approaching]
[Xenia] Oh, God.
He'll be okay.
You got him in the shoulder.
Your partner?
Your fucking partner?
He used to be
before I made detective.
Shit, I never shot a man.
Jesus God, a fucking cop.
But nobody knew you were there.
He didn't fucking see ya.
He saw me.
He's got brown eyes, right?
Well, his brown eyes
looked into mine
and he saw me.
Listen to me.
There's no way he could ID you.
The sun was blasting in
behind you.
You saw him,
he didn't see you.
We're gonna lay low
on ride this thing out.
Bram, there are gonna be
cops crawling
all over the fucking place.
You know, they all get
a fucking heart attack
when somebody shoots
a cop, like cops matter
more than anybody else.
-We do.
-Oh, "we".
That's a hot one.
Look, I'll monitor
the police bands.
I'll see how bad
things really are.
As soon as word's had
a chance to get out,
I'll look in on Colin
at the hospital.
I'm coming too.
Are you out
of your fucking mind?
Look, I shot a man.
The least I can do is
have the balls to go see him.
Xenia, you do
something crazy like that,
you're gonna fuck us up.
Now, just relax,
have a few beers,
take a warm bath.
Oh, you think
a fucking bubble bath
is gonna fix this?
Just sit tight, all right?
[ship horn blaring]
[groaning]
I tell you, buddy.
it was worth to get shot at.
That night, nurse babe
catheterized me.
I get a hard on
just thinking about her
putting on them rubber gloves.
[Colin laughs]
-[Bram clears throat]
-Huh?
-And this is...
-Xenia.
-And you're Colin.
-I am.
I'm sorry we have to meet
under these circumstances.
Don't. I'll be happy
to meet you under
any circumstances.
You know, I had a feeling
there was something
he wasn't telling me.
Work with a guy for ten years,
you know when
he's holding out on you.
I brought you some medicine.
Hey-hey!
Where'd you find this girl?
She found me. I was minding
my own goddamn business.
So did they catch who did it?
Well, we, uh, we know
we're looking for a lady.
Really?
-Yeah.
-What kind of lady?
I don't know. I didn't
get a good look at her,
But she was young, and a fox,
almost as pretty as you.
Oh, maybe I should
rob some houses.
I could use the money.
[Colin laughs]
It was weird, you know,
this guy was,
It's like, he knew
what I was gonna do
before I did.
When you ever heard
of a guy look away
when you're pointing
a gun at him, huh?
Must not have been
his first bust, huh?
Yeah.
[groans softly]
You better call
Florence Nightingale,
I need some more drugs.
[indistinct chatter over PA]
What the fuck is
the matter with you? Fuck!
It was a test
that he flunked, okay?
How do you know that?
I don't know that.
I think that, all right?
It doesn't matter.
Are you fucking suicidal?
I mean, I'm doing
everything I can
to keep our asses
out of the slammer,
and you go making
a cameo appearance before
the only goddamn witness.
You just can't stay away
from fucking flame, can you?
Come on. I thought you were
some kind of tough bitch, huh.
What's that,
some kind of compliment?
Look, it is just his shoulder.
It is not gonna
fuck up his life.
And who're you to say
what's gonna fuck up
somebody's life?
Look, just go home, dammit.
Huh?
You nervous or something?
Lay low, all right?
[phone ringing]
Hello.
[Bram] What are you wearing?
Nothing.
I miss you. What are you doing?
I'm getting the tools
out of the house.
I rented a storage locker.
Don't think it hurts
to be too careful
[man knocking at door] Hello!
C-Can I call you back?
-Hello?
-[door opens and closes]
[Colin] Hi.
Hi.
It was unlocked.
-It was?
-Yeah.
You should be more careful.
Oh, my God.
What are you doing out of bed?
I just got a couple extra
holes in me, that's all.
I thought I'd stop by
and, uh, thank you
for the flowers
You're welcome.
-I just need these for driving.
-Oh.
Well, this is nice.
Thank you.
Yeah. Bram tells me
you're in the flower business.
-Uh, well, garden consulting.
-Uh-huh.
Did you catch that, lady thief?
No, not yet, but we will.
Listen, Xenia,
there's something
I got to ask you.
The day I got shot,
according to the police report,
there's a car like yours
spotted near the scene.
Really?
Where?
Body Bay Road,
around 4 o'clock
Thursday afternoon.
Hmm. Well, I go
up there sometimes,
but not last Thursday.
Oh, oh.
We didn't have
any license plates.
Just, uh, you know,
one of them dealer things
you get when they're
new, you know
Listen, Xenia,
You were once convicted
of passing bad checks,
weren't you?
I was eighteen.
I got a suspended sentence.
You make a lot of money
telling people what to plan.
Are you serious?
Hey, look, because you've got
a record, I gotta ask, right?
Right, you're serious.
aren't you?
You're serious.
I was young,
and I made a mistake.
And as you can see,
I got myself straightened out.
Okay?
Okay.
Might I have have
a look around?
Yes, I...
Yes, I do.
I do mind.
Well, uh, here's my number.
In case anything comes up
you want to tell me.
-All right.
-All right?
-How dare you!
-What?
You know what!
Hey!
Bram!
A car like hers was spotted
near the scene,
and she has a criminal record.
You know that?
Of course I know that.
What are you,
fucking sixteen or something?
Hey, what the hell's
the matter with you, man?
It's routine, Bram.
You know that.
You'd have done
the same thing yourself.
Let me tell you something
as a friend.
Before stepping out,
I checked for
quicksand, mister.
Colin, I love this girl.
You say a fucking word
against her without
having something solid,
you do anything that hurts her,
So help me God, man...
So help me God.
He died this morning
Mummy, why are you
doing this?
-Mummy, what are you doing?
-I belong here.
He left you.
He left us.
He was a very proud man.
He didn't want us to know
how bad off he was.
He always sent us money
when he could.
[scoffs]
I was a good wife.
Mummy...
You're not still
married to him.
I told everybody
we were divorced.
It was easier.
It was easier on you.
[groans softly]
Xenia, he's still your father
And you better learn
to love him the best way
that you can.
[sobbing]
[inhales]
[car approaching]
Hi.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
My father died
I'm sorry
It's gonna be a funeral?
No, thank God.
I spent the day
talking my mother out of it.
Instead, she'll get
a little urn of his ashes
to obsess over
for the rest of her life
Bram, I thought you said
you were gonna get rid of this.
I told you to dump
the fucking gun.
I am going to.
-You're getting sloppy.
-Xenia.
Colin is looking
for his shooter.
I know him. He is
not going to let up.
I'm going to help him find her.
As soon as I can,
I'm gonna slip the gun
into the evidence lockup
hanging on some cute
little gang girl corpse.
Colin gets his lady,
case closed.
Gonna stick a shooting I did
on some dead person?
-Gets calling off our backs.
-No.
This is not a good time
to discuss this.
You're still thinking
like a cop.
You think you can do
whatever the fuck you want.
"Some dumb shit crackhead.
What the fuck does she matter."
-Is that how you think
-You know why
you don't like it?
Because it's not down
to the letter, exactly
what you've been doing
for your ten glorious
years of crime?
"It's not the book,"
according to convict.
That's right.
I had a way of doing things,
and it worked
Xenia.
Come on, hey, hey.
We're fucking up.
We're starting to fuck up.
No, we're not.
We're getting out, we're
gonna go someplace else
to start over.
We don't have enough.
It doesn't matter.
Yes, it does.
I don't want
to live like my mother,
and I don't want to die
like my father
[Bram] We need somebody
filthy rich.
It's got to be new money.
[Xenia] Yeah, somebody
who hasn't learned
how to take care of it yet.
Yeah, like, uh, dealer,
bag man or something.
What about, uh,
Nah.
Come on, who?
Nah, forget it.
No, come on.
We have to think
of every possibility.
Just think about
maybe Ricky Madden.
That obnoxious guy
at the restaurant?
Yeah.
He scrubs money, right?
He's perfect.
Forget it. We tried to get
a bug into his house
a couple of years ago,
it's like Fort Knox
Except...
I think maybe he moved.
Come on, he's such an ass.
I'd love to hit him
just on general principle.
Come on, Xenia.
He's got a new place.
It'll be tougher
than his old one.
Unless he's still
getting moved in
[Bram] So what's
the entry point?
Skylight?
[Xenia] It's probably late.
But maybe the system's
not all hooked up yet.
Yeah, because maybe
there's nothing in there
to steal yet.
Yeah, but suppose there is,
you don't put up
an electric wire
unless you got
something to protect.
[Bram] Slow down
a little bit, will you?
This place is built
with drug money.
That just means that Madden
can't report the theft.
It also means
that man's friends
are serious people.
The cops get you,
you do time.
Madden's friends get you,
you're dead.
I got you.
I could live without
whatever's in there.
I can't.
I want it as bad
as I want you.
[Bram] We're gonna
need information.
All right, my gut tells me
it's a Sapphire
security system.
The usual lace job
plus passive infrared.
If that's up and running,
we're fucked.
I can do it.
Oh, come on.
You can't go near
one of those things.
I said I can do it.
Yeah, well, all right,
let's say you can.
He keeps his money
in a wall safe.
Guy said it's one of those
big custom Moslers,
that moves the money
every day or two.
On the other hand,
his pattern's consistent.
Makes his calls
from a pay phone.
Goes to that restaurant
every afternoon about 4:00.
Drinks, has dinner and stays
until about 9:00.
-Ready?
-Go.
[Xenia] One, two, three.
[alarm beeping]
[beeping continues]
[beeping stops]
[alarm beeping]
[grunts]
[sizzling]
No keys.
That would have been too easy.
who
Don't worry,
it won't explode... yet.
-Ready?
-Mmm-hmm.
[drilling]
[drilling noise continues]
[lock disengages]
[drilling noise stops]
Xenia, you have
done this before, right?
Yeah, with Connie.
Like Connie was there
while you did it.
when I was watching him.
Jesus Christ.
Bram, you're disturbing
my concentration
[ticking]
-Get going.
-You're gonna be okay?
Yeah.
You meet pretty women
in the most unexpected places.
You'll forgive me.
I've forgotten your name.
Xenia.
Last time we met, Xenia,
you were with a guy.
Bram Hatcher,
officer of the law.
I'm glad this time
you're by yourself.
Don't disappoint me
and tell me he's here too.
I work alone.
This isn't a social call.
If you get that gun
out of my face,
then maybe we could chat.
I feel naked without it.
Of course, it's not
a bad thing with a girl
that looks like you.
-I'm not armed.
-That is stupid.
I call you a woman in jeopardy.
Is that a prelude
to a rape that I can't report?
No.
That'd ruin my story.
That I killed an intruder
in self defense
[gunshot]
[screams]
[hyperventilating]
This is one time you can
thank me for bringing a gun.
[bell ringing]
[alarm ringing]
That's it, come on,
let's go.
[tires squealing]
-Oh, my God.
-Xenia?
-Bram, I think
I'm gonna be sick.
-Xenia!
-Oh, God!
He's dead, he's dead.
I got to go back
to the station.
tie up loose ends, huh?
No, I can't be alone.
Please, I don't
wanna be alone.
Please, please.
I need to feel you
next to me, please.
Fuck me.
-Yeah?
-Yeah.
[Xenia] I shouldn't have
dragged you into this.
You were a cop, you know.
You were, you were a good cop,
and I just, I made you dirty.
Hey.
We're in this together.
All the way.
Let's go home,
get your passport,
leave you
at the airport at dawn.
We'll take the first flight
out of the country.
-God.
-Xenia...
I'm sorry.
-Hey.
-I love you.
[footsteps approaching]
[Colin] Hello, Xenia.
You know, some of this
is very interesting.
Harvesting purple prairie
cornflower seeds
with dust buster.
You come by
for some gardening tips?
You know, Xenia, I have
a special interest
in this case.
Not only because I got shot,
because I keep hoping
I'm gonna find out
that Bram's only involved
in this from the waist down.
Oh, by the way, your place
is whistle clean.
Found nothing.
Well, almost nothing.
Complete specs
for Sapphire security
alarms systems.
What's this, a little
late night reading
before bedtime?
It this illegal
to own a technical manual?
Hmm?
You know, this would
even qualify
as circumstantial.
And while we're at it,
you haven't shown me
your search warrant.
I don't have one.
File a complaint.
You know where I found that?
In your closet.
In a jacket. A man's jacket.
Bram's jacket.
Well, then why don't you
go to his house then
and sit in the dark?
Well, maybe I should.
Trouble is, I hate
those goddamn snakes.
Be seeing you soon, Xenia.
[knocking at door]
Yeah!
[dog barking]
What's going on?
Things are getting hot.
So many tools and stuff.
Just get rid of them,
all right?
There's more in
my storage locker.
Here's the key.
Just get rid of that, too.
Okay?
Just keep... Whatever,
whatever sell it for,
just, just keep it.
You okay?
Gonna get you a drink.
Ray, where'd you get this?
What?
The pre-Columbian, the snake.
Where did you get it?
That's Chac.
That's a Mayan snake god.
God damn it, Ray,
Where did you get it?
-Client.
-Who?
Hey, I don't ask you
any question.
Which client?
Was it Bram Hatcher?
Like you, Xe, I owe
all my clients discretion.
Cut the shit, Ray.
You goddamn
know Bram, don't you?
How do you know Bram?
Ray, I said
how do you know Bram!
Come on, cut that shit out!
Tell me the truth now.
Yeah, I know him, all right?
He's a cop.
He busted me once.
Said I could continue
in this business
if I paid him off.
Pay him off how?
-Cash.
-What else?
Was it information? Huh?
You're a snitch, aren't you.
You're a fucking snitch.
Sometimes.
Look here, I wasn't
snitching on you, Xe.
A guy comes to me
with a big job
he's not talking about.
Asked me who's
the best I knew at B&E.
Someone to do
a third floor break in.
Top of the line alarm system.
-Sapphire.
-Sapphire?
Yeah.
He said that?
He said Sapphire
specifically?
Asked me if I knew
anybody who did safes.
I told him you did.
I wasn't sure
if you still did.
What else?
Something to do in
and unoccupied building.
He said that was
very important.
When was this?
It was way before Christmas.
Why didn't you tell me?
I didn't want to go to jail.
I wouldn't make it
in there, Xe.
You look like an all round
win-win-win situation.
[phone ringing]
Ray. Look, Ray, I'm not here.
I'm not here.
And we never talked.
-Okay?
-Okay.
[phone ringing]
[phone continues ringing]
[phone beeps on]
Hello?
[glass shattering]
[thumping]
[dog barking]
Oh, God.
Ray.
Oh, shit.
Xe. Xe...
Hang on, Ray.
The hospital's close.
I'm fucked, Xe.
Come on, Ray, come on.
Get up. Come on.
Come on, Ray.
The hospital's close.
Shit! Come on, Ray!
The worst that can
befall thee...
Fuck you.
-Measur'd right.
-Get up! Get up.
Finish it.
-Finish it.
-Fuck you, Ray.
Get up! Get up!
[sobbing]
Is a sound slumber
and a long good night.
Please, get up, Ray.
Please. Please!
Please, Ray. Please.
Please.
[sobbing]
Please, Ray.
[door opens]
[keys jingling]
Xenia?
I'm here
You okay? Huh?
We go a change of plan.
Where's the money?
-I hid it.
-You hid it?
I got, I got nervous.
I didn't want it around.
I put it in a sewer pipe.
It's under
the Tannhauser bridge.
I got some bad news.
There's a fence, you know him.
Ray Costello.
He got, uh, picked up tonight.
He's downtown now,
copping a plea.
Spilling his guts
about you and your career.
So we've gotta get you
out here of.
This place is gonna be
swarming with cops
and about five minutes.
Don't worry.
I've worked this out.
Just listen to this.
Listen, all right?
-Okay.
-They know that I'm here.
I asked to make
the collar myself.
Like, uh, like
I'm gonna bust you. Right?
Now, this is the way
we're going to do it.
You're gonna, you're gonna
to shoot me here in the thigh.
Don't worry.
It'll go through clean.
It'll heal up quick.
It'll take away any suspicions
that I let you go.
I'll scream, "Freeze, police!"
all that shit real loud
so the neighbors can hear,
then fire a couple of shots
in the air.
But you just keep on going.
You follow?
Xenia.
We got no choice.
Things got fucked,
they got fucked, but
we're gonna make it. Okay?
We'll just get you
out of town, I'll lay low
a couple of months,
we'll figure it out.
Don't cry, don't cry.
You got to do this.
Don't worry about hurting me.
I'll be okay, all right?
God damn it, Xenia!
Listen to me,
you've got to do this.
[groaning]
Freeze! Police!
[grunting]
Drop the gun.
Drop the damn gun!
Go!
[gasping]
Bye, Mummy.
Shit.
[dialing]
[cell phone ringing]
[phone continues ringing]
Yeah?
Is it Colin?
Just listen to me, all right?
There's a fence.
His name is Ray Costello.
Ray Costello.
He was murdered tonight.
And I know this is
hard for you to believe,
but Bram killed him.
Okay? You've got to help me.
Please help me.
Well, Xenia.
How nice of you to call.
Why?
You were always telling me
to break the rules.
What made you think
I wouldn't break yours?
I'll explain it better
when I see you.
You won't find me.
I'm a cop, remember?
I could put out warrants in
all 50 states if I have to.
Real pretty photos.
Whatever it takes,
I'll find you.
I'll talk.
I'll go down, but I'll talk.
And tell them what?
We dated a couple of times
I dropped you, that's it.
The rest you made up.
I caught you planting evidence.
It's old stuff, but it works.
I'll make sure of that.
And now, there's...
There's nobody left
to back up your story.
Nobody.
[car door opening]
I don't think
that's biodegradable.
What's in the bag, Xenia?
Money.
Why?
You gonna frame me?
Call the cops,
come back, get it later
when I'm in jail?
I think maybe...
you better go get it
Open it.
Just money? Money,
that's all you wanted?
All I wanted?
You know, my whole
goddamn life changed
when you came into the picture.
I mean, I was even
trying to improvise
so this whole thing
could work out for us.
I told you I didn't need
that goddamn money.
All I needed was you.
But you? You wanted
the money as much as me.
You know?
We could've been partners.
Madden didn't have to die.
We could have done
10 Madden jobs
without anyone getting hurt.
Well, partners.
Fuck you, how you said that.
Xe, Madden knew
too much about me.
I was his partner,
his silent partner.
So much for partners.
I mean, you were better off
before I came
into the picture, right?
You know...
The only thing
that I didn't count on
was falling in love with you.
Love?
Is that what you call this?
The toughest part of all.
So this is how it ends?
You just gonna
shoot fish in a bucket?
I wish we both could've been.
I do love you.
Well, you can't kill memories.
And I'll never
forget you, Bram.
Never.
[grunting]
I can wait for you forever.
[ticking]
[bell ringing]
I'll get you
everything you need.
Food.
Shelter.
Warmth.
Maybe even a little love.
Hmm?
[car starting]