Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Oh, God. [LAUGHS]
Hello.
Official YIFY movies site:
YTS.MX
LILY: Who's Adam talking to?
SEAN: I don't know.
He's being all Hollywood
right now.
LILY: He's so Hollywood.
Look, that's Hollywood.
LILY: Hollywood?
He's probably on...
He's probably on the phone
with his agent.
LILY: That's it.
That's what it looks like?
"I didn't sign up for this."
DURRIE: It's a type of candy.
It's like, um...
It has the consistency
of a Jolly Rancher
but the flavor of, like...
Kind of liquorish almost.
SEAN: And you eat these things?
Yeah, my grandmother
would have them.
They're little like lozenges.
LARISSA: I bet
she had horehounds.
Yeah, my grandmother had
a bucket of horehounds.
You happy now?
Yes.
Yes, I am.
LILY: Let's just, uh,
repeat the scene.
[CLEARS THROAT]
Look at this place.
Looks like a gold plated
trash can.
They do?
Do you think
we deserve this?
Hey, what's up, everybody?
This is Lily,
your director,
talking to you
from the van.
We are on the way
to Vegas,
shooting my feature film,
Napoleon.
I've got my lovely cast
in the van with me.
Let's meet everybody.
These are my actors.
This is Durrie.
Durrie is an actor.
Living the dream.
LILY: Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
LILY: This is
bonus feature material.
Durrie is multitasking.
He's driving.
Yes, yes, I'm multitalented.
LILY: Larissa.
Hi.
LILY: Hey, lady.
There's Joy.
She's sleeping as you can see.
We've been driving for a while.
Alycen.
Hey.
LILY: Hey.
Casey, what's up?
Hey.
There's Sean.
Hey, buddy.
And Adam.
The lovely Adam.
What's up?
You guys jazzed?
We're going to Vegas, baby.
Vegas!
Yeah.
Vegas.
LILY: Whoo!
Coffee then Vegas.
Hey, Lily, um...
What if we went
to that little Vegas,
the fake one?
The Baby... Baby Vegas?
LILY: Broomtown?
With the roller coaster.
I hate you, Vegas.
LILY: You wanna stop
at Broomtown?
Yeah!
LILY: Why?
Why not?
LILY: 'Cause we're going
to real Vegas. Why would
we go to fake Vegas?
So we can get ready.
SEAN: Real Vegas.
DURRIE: So we can all
smell like failure.
For, like, an hour.
[LILLY LAUGHS]
LILY: Nah.
LARISSA: Yeah,
it's on the way, though.
LILY: If you want to stop,
we should, um...
There's this cool spot
on the way.
This mining town, Garlock.
We stop there
and check it out.
Yes.
Yes, let's do that.
[LAUGHING] What?
Let's do that,
let's do that.
Garlock, let's go there.
LARISSA:
That's the real name?
Is that the real name?
Who knows?
She's not... She's serious.
There's this place.
I was reading
before we came out.
There's a couple of them
out here. And it was one,
and it's called Garlock.
And it is by far
the coolest looking one.
By far.
And it is like some weird...
LARISSA: Are there
like hotels and stuff?
Is there a pool?
[CHUCKLES] No, no.
ADAM: It's like a creepy, old,
weird mining town.
And there was this guy,
like, I don't know, like,
a billion years ago.
LILY: I can't believe
you know this.
I know, right?
And he's like...
This guy's name is...
Burro Schmidt.
Burro, totally.
El Burro. And he,
he wanted to get, like,
ore from, like, one side
to the other side
of the mountains,
which blew a freaking hole
through it or something
like that.
And then he took...
I don't know, like,
his life or something
in the cave
and then next thing you know
he's haunting the place,
and now the town is weird,
decrepit and old and freaky.
We should totally go there.
Sounds great.
Instead of...
LARISSA: A touristy
type of place?
I wouldn't say touristy.
I would say...
I would say
sketchy as hell.
I would say fun,
I would say cool,
I would say weird.
CASEY: You guys, we should
just get to Vegas, I think.
We have a movie to shoot,
remember?
We have to prep,
rehearse, settle in...
ADAM: Casey,
you're really boring.
Wow.
LILY: Yeah, but like...
LILY: We don't even
have to shoot
till tomorrow afternoon.
I know, but still,
we should get there,
settle in, prepare, right?
So, this is like
by Vegas, or in Vegas?
LILY: We could just
check it out
like real fast.
Oh, so we should
definitely go.
It sounds like fun.
LILY: Yeah, it's on the way.
ADAM: A room in the mountain
that has chandeliers in it.
What? Oh, my God.
Super weird, right?
DURRIE: It's like a weird,
creepy little...
Is it really haunted?
If they want to stop
at little Vegas, then
we stop where they stop.
LILY: Don't fight.
It's not far. It's not
far off the road.
It's worth going and seeing.
It's still day time.
LILY: Yeah, it's on the way.
It'll be fun,
it'll be creepy,
it'll be great.
LILY: Yeah, Durrie,
should we stop?
We're stopping.
We can go anywhere
where I can stop driving.
[ALL LAUGHING]
Okay, it's decided
we're going.
We're gonna go
see Garlock, we're gonna
see what it's all about.
Get some excellent b-roll.
LILY: Onward, my friend.
We are Garlock bound.
Awesome!
I have no idea
where that's at.
[SIGHS]
What?
What... What do we deserve?
What...
Are you high?
[ALL LAUGHING]
What are you talking about?
ADAM: He was fat,
and he was a dork.
DURRIE: And works for the NSA.
LILY: You're such a virgin.
LARISSA: Haunted things,
and I don't like that.
[ALL LAUGHING]
ADAM: That's the problem.
I mean, that DUI...
LILY: He's passive-aggressive.
DURRIE: Keep your secrets.
Don't tell 'em to me.
I don't like fish.
I don't like...
Is it Jaws or is it
like just fish?
No, it's like fish.
Like, a shark
would freak me out.
But I think a shark
would scare everybody.
Like, I'm not...
If anybody was swimming
and a shark swam by them,
everybody would be like,
"Fuck, move!" Uh...
But, like, if a...
You're not scared
of getting mugged?
A salmon swam by me
and I was swimming,
I'd be like, "Ugh! Fuck."
You're not scared
of getting mugged?
Sure. But again,
I think that's something
that scares everybody.
That scares everybody,
is scared of getting mugged.
Uh, and everyone's
getting mugged.
ADAM: Hey,
I have some good news.
I think we're almost there.
LARISSA: We are? That's good.
JOY: How can you tell?
There's no road signs.
CASEY: I can tell
it looks all the same.
ADAM: I feel...
I can feel the spookiness.
I remember that...
You remember that bush,
right?
ADAM: Yes, I remember that.
I peed behind a bush.
ADAM:
It was in this pamphlet.
LILY: Here it is.
Slow down, slow down.
Turn right here.
DURRIE: Yeah.
ADAM: We're here.
LILY: How do you know
this is it?
This is nothing.
DURRIE: 'Cause it's
the only other road.
ADAM: This is totally it.
LILY: Dude, don't drive
all the way up there
with the van.
It'll fuck up the van.
LILY: Here we are,
majestic Garlock.
[GRUNTS]
Come on.
LILY: Casey?
I'll just wait for you guys.
Come on, Casey.
I don't know,
I'll just hang back here.
SEAN: We could be
here for hours.
You'll love it.
You will like it.
LILY: It'll be fun.
Everyone is looking now.
LILY: Let's do it.
ADAM: What's going on?
LILY: Casey doesn't wanna...
CASEY: I'm coming.
SEAN: She's coming.
ADAM: Don't worry.
Your trailer's up here.
Perfect.
[LAUGHS]
LILY: Yeah!
SEAN: You want that, Casey?
LILY: There's hillbillies?
SEAN: You should
take it if you want it.
LARISSA: Not even close enough
to tell if they're mutated.
LILY: Guys.
You guys are so sexy.
I love my sexy cast.
ADAM: Sean,
I found your bed, Sean.
SEAN: Oh, yeah?
LILY: You see
the swimming pool?
Is this in my contract?
You think it's covered
if I fall down and break
my ankle? [LAUGHS]
LILY: Don't break your ankle.
I have
a first aid kit, though.
These aren't hiking shoes.
I thought we were
gonna be in a hotel.
LILY: Yeah, I know,
Vegas, right?
Yeah.
Fuck.
ADAM: Who said
there's a house over here?
JOY: You think
anybody lives out here?
LILY: I don't know.
There's a house over here.
The rape house.
What do you mean "House"?
There's a house.
Shack.
ADAM: Great choice.
JOY: This is not a good
place for anything.
Very good.
LILY: Oh, shit!
ADAM: Go ahead, Lily!
SEAN: Watch out!
JOY: Lead the way.
We're going inside.
ALYCEN: Oh,
this is disgusting.
So what's the deal
with this place, you guys?
Cases of shellings
on the floor.
Empty cans of beer.
LILY: Holy shit.
It's shells, dude.
You guys...
You guys,
is this gonna...
JOY: Let's go out
onto the veranda.
Yeah.
LILY: Kind of shady,
dude, look.
Adam.
JOY: Yeah,
they're everywhere.
LILY: Bullet shells.
ADAM: Shady business.
Someone lost a foot.
What're you saying?
Why would you ever
leave without your boot?
You come here with two boots.
This is fuckin'
redneck country.
Why leave without one?
ADAM: Well,
there's the other one.
There's the other one.
JOY: This is not
a good place.
CASEY: This place is great.
What are you talking about?
This is better than
our hotel room in Vegas.
LILY: I think we're deep
in the heart of redneck country
is what I think.
Your masseuse
is in the other house.
Be careful going down.
LILY: Yeah, good luck to you.
The fuckin'...
Obviously, people
have been here.
Yeah.
There's another
house over there.
ADAM: That's great.
LILY: All right,
who's going in first?
ADAM: The Asian.
LILY: Casey.
DURRIE: The Asian
always dies first.
It looks kinda cool
from the outside.
Who knows what's
on the inside?
I told you.
I told you the Asian
would go first.
LILY: Did he?
Yeah.
LILY: What's in that?
CASEY: It's not good vibes.
There's a rug!
LILY: What is it?
DURRIE: I don't know.
Like a shady office.
SEAN: Oh, look at this.
CASEY: What?
Let me see.
This is like nice.
LILY: What's in there?
SEAN: Skinhead.
Really?
Really cool.
"Skinhead" written there?
Are you serious?
How do you know what
skinhead writing looks like?
'Cause it says "Skins".
LILY: Wait, wait,
what does it say?
You're a skinhead-
writer-transologist?
[ALL LAUGHING]
What does it say?
LILY: That's fucked up.
That's really cool.
[CHITTERING]
[ALL SCREAM]
LILY: Fucking A, you guys.
Oh, my God.
What was that?
It was like a white bat.
Where are all these mines
you were talking about?
I have actually
never been here, Casey.
Right.
But you looked it up?
Yeah, I looked it up
on the Internet.
You saw pictures?
I saw pictures of it.
But I've actually
never been here.
LILY: Who needs
to take a dump?
Hey, check it out.
There's a new outhouse.
JOY: Oh, man.
LILY: Oh, my God, dude.
ALYCEN: 18th Century turds.
LILY: Oh, Jesus.
Yeah, no.
LILY: Let me see.
Hold that up
for the camera.
Look at that.
LILY: Oh, dude,
someone's been shooting.
Yeah, I think it's best
to get the fuck out of here.
I'm sure there's
nobody here now.
CASEY: Where is this
ghost town you
were talking about?
I'm sure this is more
of a summer vacationing place.
ADAM: I didn't know
exactly where this was,
okay? Sorry.
Shit.
[WOMAN LAUGHING]
LILY: That's okay, dude.
God, he's so
sensitive, isn't he?
In real terms,
I know that I want to be,
you know, just be happy
and be feeling
satisfied in what I'm doing,
whether it is acting,
which is what I like,
to be in writing or if
it doesn't end up being that,
you know,
it might be teaching
or something.
And whatever it ends up
being, so be it,
you know, I just...
I wanna feel fulfilled,
I wanna feel happy,
and that, to me...
LILY: Where's the noose?
That's not a noose.
ALYCEN: I know.
It just looks like a noose.
LILY: You're so imaginative.
I like it.
I could tell when you guys
argued in the van
like an old married couple.
ALYCEN: Freaky shit.
Not being happy.
Not... [STUTTERING]
Not finding
that happiness in my life.
Like, coming to the end
of my life and being...
Looking back
and being miserable.
Like, I would not want
to have that, I would not want
to have regrets like that.
DURRIE: So that was...
That was great.
LILY: Was it awesome?
That was great, Lily.
Was that Garlock?
That was Garlock,
and I'm sorry that
that was so uneventful.
It was amazing.
Really?
LILY: I'm gonna grab
one last shot of the sunset.
SEAN: I'll get over there.
LILY: You're gonna ride shot?
DURRIE:
This is not starting.
Yeah, but it's not
turning over at all.
LILY: What do you mean
it's not fucking turning over?
Well, who knows something
about cars? Call Triple A.
Yeah, pop the hood.
I'll see it.
LILY: Do you know
anything about cars, dude?
Know anything about cars?
No.
LILY: Joy.
ADAM: Here, I got it.
LILY: Yeah, I got it.
You're filming?
Really, Lily?
What?
DURRIE: You really
gotta film this?
LILY: Well, I mean I'm sorry,
I'm just filming.
ADAM: Does anybody else
have a phone?
LILY: Here I am,
fucking filming.
DURRIE:
Is anything happening?
No.
Not even now?
There's crackers.
CASEY: Great.
Thanks, Joy.
LILY: Obviously, it's not
the battery because the lights
are on in the car.
Well, I know
it's not the battery.
No, it might have enough
juice to power the lights but
not to turn the engine over.
Still, good point.
JOY: There' enough for
the radio and lights.
CASEY: Why hasn't
anyone phoned yet?
LILY: Dude, because I have
no fucking signal.
Like, my piece of shit
phone has no signal.
Do you?
LILY: Here,
I have the number.
I'll give it to you.
Try it on your cell.
Nobody gets service.
'Cause we're out in
the middle of nowhere.
This'll look great.
ALYCEN: Well,
who's idea was this?
How far away are we
from the last...
No one has service.
LILY: Sixty miles.
Sixty miles?
LILY: Yeah, that's
the fucking last town.
ALYCEN: How many?
LILY: Sixty miles. 6-0.
LILY: All we need to do
is just chill out.
Why don't we just like
fucking grab the bottle of
vodka and grab our shit,
and kick it...
Are you joking?
Like, we're gonna
have a crack house.
LILY: Well, we can't
fucking stay down here.
Like, all of us.
We can't even fit with
all the equipment in there.
Like...
We're gonna stay
in the crack house.
Yeah, no.
LILY: We all
have to stay together.
Why not?
Did you go down there?
Yeah, but I mean...
LILY: Dude, we all
have to stay together.
And shells all over the floor.
Yeah, that sounds great.
What the fuck else
are we gonna do?
We need to figure out
where we're staying tonight.
Phones don't work.
We're not fucking
walking anywhere.
So, that's what we're doing.
We're fucking sticking around
for a little bit.
Let this thing cool down.
LILY: Yeah, exactly.
ADAM: Yeah, we can
definitely go back
to the house.
SEAN: Crack house.
If it gets too cold
out here.
LILY: Or we could light...
Does anybody have
a lighter?
I need...
I need my jacket.
Put your coat on.
It's getting cold.
LILY: Do we have flash lights?
Dude, we have flash lights
in the car in the...
We got flash lights,
we're good.
LILY: We have flash lights.
Just grab some warm shit,
grab your warm shit.
Really? We're doing this?
Casey, what are the options?
We can't walk 60 miles.
It's a little crazy.
And then, we should
not have stopped.
We should have just
went to Vegas.
LILY: I know.
I'm sorry that we did,
but we did.
I mean,
we can't just...
Well, we're fucking
stuck here for the night.
Our van's still not working,
and looks like we're gonna
hole up in this here
shanty shack.
Crack shack.
It's really fucking cold.
[GASPS] Fucking...
God, Adam!
You scared the fucking
shit out of me, dude.
[GRUNTS] Let's go
check out our new home.
LILY: Careful.
[DOOR CREAKS]
I do not want
to go in there.
LILY: Yeah, but there's
no one in there.
They're moving furniture.
ADAM: Ladies, come on in.
JOY: No, that's
not what she's saying.
She's saying that
when we left here
the door was open.
And when we got here again
it was closed.
LILY: It's cold and...
The wind might have...
...and we gotta stay warm.
It stinks in here.
Yeah, it smells really bad.
SEAN: Just the girls.
We're not sleeping in here.
We're not sleeping at all.
Are you kidding me?
Well, okay, fine.
LILY: You guys okay?
No, I'm not okay!
LILY: I know, but...
We should be in a hotel room
right now, this is...
LILY: I know.
All right, all right.
This is the kind of place
that fucked up people...
That isn't happening.
Anyone could
come here right now.
There's nothing we can
do about that.
Everybody,
just calm down!
Everybody...
LILY: Yeah, I agree.
Just have a seat.
Take a deep breath.
The car got overheated,
so I'm gonna go check on that.
Everybody else stay here, okay?
Don't go by yourself.
I'm the only one that
knows what they're doing.
But don't go by yourself.
Go with somebody.
Adam, cut the light.
Lily, you come.
Will somebody...
One of the boys stay.
Sean will stay.
I got it.
Give me the lantern.
ADAM: Lily, you come with me.
LILY: All right.
Find something that
you can hit someone with.
LILY: Okay,
we'll be right back.
Quick, come back quick.
We'll be here.
JOY: If you get service...
Yeah, no, I'll definitely...
Keep checking.
ADAM: I'm sorry.
LILY: Fucking pretty sweet
idea to come to Garlock.
I'm so sorry
about that. [LAUGHS]
LILY: We should be
in Vegas right now.
[GROANS] I really hope that
he's having more luck
'cause they're gonna
be so insane.
LILY: Dude,
please tell me it's...
Please.
We're out of here.
LILY: So that thing
is the same?
No, I...
I don't know what it is.
I mean, the lights work
and the battery's fine.
I checked the fluid.
I checked the oil,
I checked the timing belt.
I don't know
what's wrong with it.
LILY: All right, so,
okay, so hang on a second.
Come here.
Okay, so we're
staying here.
Yeah.
'Cause the girls
are freaking out.
I'm gonna go back there
and have to tell them that.
They're gonna be so bummed.
I'll... I'll do it then.
So, we just have to fucking...
What are we gonna do?
We're gonna stay the night,
we have no choice.
And then,
tomorrow morning...
Camping trip.
We'll figure it out.
Be in Vegas by fucking noon.
A camping trip.
Camping trip.
LILY: You know, let's just...
Let's just grab the vodka.
Yeah?
Let's fucking grab it.
Let's get fucked up.
There was this episode
of Rescue 911 once
where they performed
a tracheotomy on this guy
on an airplane,
and it was totally
like a re-enactment.
But like, the took
a ball point pen and they
stuck it in his throat
because he was choking,
and there was blood everywhere.
I was like... [SHUDDERS]
Like, I literally couldn't
pick anything up
with my hands.
I couldn't pick up
the remote control
to change the channel
because I was literally
like, "Oh, my God."
So, yeah, maybe I think
I'm a hard ass,
and that's in my head.
[LAUGHS]
I'm probably a big wimp.
It's cold.
Turn the camera off.
LILY: No. I mean,
I'm in a room...
I'm in a room full of actors
with a camera.
Oh, yeah, I could
turn it off and then
we'd have no light.
Don't turn that off.
Just leave it on.
You don't have to put it
in my face, oh, God.
Maybe not burn my retinas.
[LILY CHUCKLES]
I, uh, am going to
get in that pool
that goes by itself
and you just lay in the thing.
The lazy river.
Yes.
With a pink drink,
I don't care.
With a pink drink
with an umbrella,
cheery, and a pineapple.
JOY: Yeah,
that sounds good.
I'm just gonna
stay in my bed.
[EXHALES] I'm there.
I'm not gonna leave the room.
I'm there.
Even when the maid comes in.
LILY: I wanna have steak.
Okay.
Hey, Casey.
What?
What are you gonna do?
Uh...
She's gonna pass the bottle.
Sleep in a warm bed.
Have that vodka.
I'm cold.
I think we should
try to get out of here.
Yeah, right now.
LILY:
We can't, it's night.
It's freezing.
Just here. Just drink.
Have some...
We're fine.
Have this and just chill.
Everybody, relax.
Sit down, relax.
LILY: It'll be morning
in a couple of hours.
We're gonna get...
We'll be fine.
I can't consume it.
LILY: Do I want something?
For your camera.
Do you got
something for me?
Yeah.
LILY: What do you got?
So, these...
Is it good? [CHUCKLES]
It just seems dramatic
with the lights,
but whatever.
JOY: Adam.
What?
You groaner.
No.
I didn't finish.
I didn't get
to finish the story
of the burrow man.
JOY: No, Adam.
No, no, no.
You should know this.
DURRIE: A history lesson.
The man that built
the mines in this town,
apparently, was
obsessed with his job.
So obsessed that
he never saw his family.
[SIGHS] I don't know
why I'm telling you
this right now,
but whatever.
He was so obsessed
that he never saw his family.
And his son, one day
went up to the mines
to go find his dad
so he could spend
some time with him.
And then, apparently,
the wife followed
and then nobody
ever saw them.
[LOUD THUD]
[GIRL SCREAMS]
What was that?
LILY: Wait, shh, shh.
SEAN: What the fuck was that?
LILY: Sean.
[LILY SHUSHING]
Dude, don't open the door.
[ALL SHUSHING]
Oh, geez.
[DOOR CREAKING]
[SQUEALING]
Oh, come on!
LILY: Shut the door.
ADAM: It's nothing.
JOY: Get that flash light
out of my face.
LILY:
Did you bolt it, Adam?
Is it just me or is it
getting colder?
Yeah, it is.
A lot colder.
Like literally...
It literally just
dropped ten degrees.
Shut up. Don't say that.
I swear to God.
I do, too. I know.
ADAM: Look at this.
LARISSA: It's bats.
LILY: No, it's not.
She's right.
LARISSA: It's bats.
LILY: Bats?
Bats.
We saw bats earlier,
here, remember?
LILY: Yes, it's bats.
That's what it is.
[LISA SHUSHING]
[GENTLE THUD]
[LISA GASPS]
Okay, that is
another thing I heard.
I'm sorry, I can't...
JOY: This is like...
CASEY: I don't even think
we should sit here.
I don't think we should
just sit here and wait
for somebody to come.
LILY: Nothing's gonna
come in here.
It's better than going
and being all out
in the middle of nowhere.
Have you been here?
The mines are
right over there?
LILY: The ones
where the guy disappeared?
Adam, have you
been here before?
No.
Then how do you know?
JOY: You're full of it.
No. I...
You know a lot
about this, Adam.
When we pulled up...
He's just trying to...
SEAN: We're not going
to these mines anyway.
LILY: Nobody wants to go
to the mines. I just want
to know where they are.
I want to know if
they are close by
or like far away.
No, I'm not, I'm not.
Why did you want
to come out here?
ADAM: Because I thought
it would be fun.
[SCOFFS]
And I was wrong.
DURRIE: Before the car
broke down, it was
pretty cool.
ADAM: Thank you.
It was daylight.
LILY:
What are you talking about?
This is awesome.
We're having a blast.
It's a blasty blast.
It's not his fault.
It kind of is, actually.
[LAUGHING]
Kind of is.
ALYCEN: We should've
listened to Casey.
I'm just saying.
We've been here a long time.
That means it's a short time
till the sun comes up.
Let's hold it out,
keep it together.
What are you doing?
LILY: Adam.
JOY: No, Adam, look,
come back, Adam.
What are you doing?
What is he doing?
He's out of his mind.
He had more than half
a bottle of vodka.
LILY: Please stay in here
with us, Adam.
I'm serious.
Listen to me.
I want you to come
and stay in here with us.
Don't go out there right now.
ADAM: I understand.
LILY: Listen to me, Adam.
Come here.
Come here for a second.
I'm just waiting out.
I'm not...
Listen to me.
Just come here for a second.
[WHISPERS] We've got the girls
scared shitless in there
right now.
JOY: Weren't you saying
earlier that you thought...
CASEY: What's happening?
What's happening?
LILY: We have to stay in here
and just chill out.
Nothing's out there.
LILY: We're totally gonna
laugh about this tomorrow.
I promise.
Okay?
What are you looking at?
CASEY: I'm just looking.
JOY: No more vodka for Adam.
[ALL LAUGHING]
SEAN: You're cut off.
[WHISPERS] Hey.
[LISA WHISPERS] Hey.
Can't sleep?
No.
The vodka worked?
I think so.
You okay?
Yeah.
You sure?
Yeah. I'm just...
...mad at myself,
that's all.
[LILY SIGHS]
But we're
gonna get out of here.
Tomorrow morning.
Be in Vegas tomorrow.
Vegas tomorrow.
I think I'm gonna
move to Eritrea.
To where?
It's the third poorest
country in the world.
According to what?
I googled it this morning.
Okay.
So what continent
is it on?
I don't know.
I didn't click that far.
Africa, I think.
So you're gonna move
to a country you know
nothing about.
I know.
Because of a Google search.
I know it's
the third... [MUTTERING]
I know it's the third
worst country in the world.
Anything else?
Anything.
I think I can help them.
Help them what,
adopt kids?
Look, I'm just
tired of it, okay?
I spent my whole life,
you know, always doing
the safe thing, you know.
Always doing what
I was supposed to do.
I just...
I've never taken a risk,
not one. Ever.
Okay.
Maybe dating you.
Oh. Well, there you go.
Living dangerously.
Wanna go with me?
Oh, fuck.
Are you filming me?
Jesus.
[SIGHS]
I'm gonna check on the van.
LILY: I'm coming with.
Whatever.
[LILY SIGHS]
Wait, was...
Huh.
Pretty...
Sean, are you sure
this is where we parked?
SEAN: Uh...
I mean, I was just
kind of walking,
but this is...
...where we came.
I mean, did we park here
or is it just
not here?
I don't know.
LILY: Is it a...
Is it a different road?
No, no. No.
I mean, this is like
a one way in, one way out
kind of deal.
Oh.
Oh, no, this is
not happening.
This is the road,
this is where we pulled off.
Where else would it be?
It's a van. It's a big van.
Look at this.
There's nothing here.
Fuck.
LILY: Um...
Maybe it got stolen.
I mean, what did
we expect, you know?
Fuck!
Wait, dude.
What are we
gonna tell them?
LILY: Well...
Lily, what the hell?
LILY: I don't know.
DURRIE: It was right here!
ADAM: No way.
We parked it here.
That's the sign
we parked in front of.
LILY: But their might be
another sign that
looks just like that.
Everything looks
the same out here.
Fuck.
LILY: I think it must
not be here. This must not
be where we parked it.
We parked it
right by that sign.
LILY: No, but there might
be another sign like that.
It's like a state park.
Lily, this is where
we parked our car.
I'm sure of it!
That sign is here,
this is where we
parked our fucking car.
[SCOFFS] How many people
do you see around here?
Exactly! How many people
do you fucking see
out here? No one!
Our car broke down
and now it's fucking gone!
Maybe a cop came.
A cop didn't come.
Some fucking redneck
is going to shoot us!
That's what's going
to fucking happen.
Don't even say that.
Have you seen who put it out?
LILY: Calm her down.
Calm down, Larissa.
I'm sorry. I'm fucking sorry.
This is where we parked our car,
and again...
This is ridiculous.
And I'm sorry that we're here
but the car's not fucking here.
And it's fucking
weirding me out that...
[STUTTERING]
Everything that's
going on right now.
LARISSA: Dude,
I'm not fucking crazy.
We need to go.
JOY: Nobody thinks
you're crazy.
LILY: I just don't think
it could be gone.
I think...
We don't know
where it's fucking gone.
I think we have to look
for it, I think maybe
we parked somewhere else.
Listen,
we'll look for it.
We'll look for it, okay?
We didn't park anywhere else.
LILY: What do you wanna do?
What do you wanna do, Joy?
You want to just stand here
and scream at each other?
We have to fucking
look for it.
I'm gonna walk down the road
and see if I run
into anybody.
And if I don't run into
anybody, at least hopefully
my cell phone will work.
Anybody who wants to
come with me,
I'm going down the road.
We have to leave.
I'm not staying here.
Maybe she's right.
There's no fucking way...
Wait, shut up.
You're probably right.
It might be on another road.
They all look the same.
So let's just check around.
LILY: It could be another road.
We walked, it was night time.
I mean, we walked
15 minutes, and look,
it all looks the same
out here in every direction.
It has to be out here
somewhere else.
It all looks the same.
We've been back to this spot,
to the van!
And now we just
forgot where it was?
It was right
fucking here, Lily.
LILY: It's a dirt road.
We're coming back.
Okay.
If we find help.
An hour?
Okay, an hour.
We'll probably
be here, waiting.
If we find someone,
we'll get a ride.
Exactly.
LILY: Okay.
So they're gonna go...
But then hold on,
don't just leave.
SEAN: What do you want?
Can we figure this out?
LILY: I just want us
to all be, you know...
I'm going.
We're going, let's go.
We'll be back.
LILY: Okay.
LILY: So we should do
like a loop and look for
the van and come back.
Fuck the van!
Lily!
We need to get our
cell phones to work so we
can call the fucking police.
They're gonna go there,
we're gonna go this way.
The first person
to get cell service
call 911.
LILY: Dude, Casey.
Just calm down.
We're gonna find it.
We are probably
parked on the wrong road.
She's totally right.
Everyone's freaking out,
we didn't sleep last night.
We're all crazy, a little
tense, a lot tense.
Let's follow them.
Somebody's phone's
gonna pick up.
Okay.
Okay?
It's gonna be all right.
LILY: I'm soaking wet.
Where the fuck
is the van?
Gone!
God, the van is gone.
The van is so gone,
Lily, it's ridiculous.
LILY: That doesn't
make sense.
All my equipment
is in there.
CASEY:
It does make sense.
They stole it.
Like, who wouldn't
want to steal that?
They're probably
stole it all
and the van is gone.
ADAM: You know what
the funny thing is, Lily?
LILY: What?
I always wanted to
shoot a movie in the rain.
LILY: Sweet.
Here we are, right?
LILY: Well, we have rain.
In spades. And it's cold!
LILY: Yeah, I'm gonna be
at the slot machine
right now.
[ADAM CHUCKLING]
[WOMAN SCREAMING]
LILY: What is that?
What happened?
Oh, my God.
LILY: I think it's Joy.
Shit.
What is wrong?
LARISSA: Snake went in
a hole or something.
SEAN: Snake? Okay.
Is it still here?
Where is it?
A snake bit her
and there's a hole in there.
SEAN: Uh, okay.
All right, Adam,
help me drag her away.
Oh, my God!
LILY: Fuck.
She's bleeding.
LILY: What happened?
It came out of the bushes
and struck at me.
This snake's a fucking...
Oh, shit!
Jesus.
Okay, hang in.
We're gonna take a look.
We have to take a look.
[GROANS]
Be careful, be careful.
Shit.
LILY: Oh, my God.
Oh, fuck!
Okay, okay, all right.
Ah, shit, Joy!
Don't look at it.
Here, hold on.
Let me put my belt on it.
You guys, what do I do?
Gonna pull my belt out
and we're gonna try
and stop the bleeding,
and try to
slow down the venom.
Was it a rattlesnake?
I have no idea.
I didn't hear anything.
If it's a rattlesnake,
what am I supposed to do?
Just relax, just relax.
Just take deep breaths, okay?
Control your breathing, okay.
Oh, my God, you guys.
You guys, I'm scared.
Okay, it's okay.
Let's go back to the shelter.
Let's go back.
We're going back
to the shelter.
Yes. We're gonna carry her.
Guys, we're gonna carry her.
No, I really don't want
her to walk, you guys.
Are you sure?
Yes, I promise.
Here, just cross your...
'Cause that's gonna
make it a lot worse.
Okay.
All right, just trust me.
Okay, can you carry her leg
very, very carefully?
On the count of three,
we're gonna go up. Ready?
One, two, three. Up.
Okay, okay.
Larissa, lead us back
to the shelter,
please, will you?
I'm gonna
follow you, okay?
LILY: We're gonna carry her?
It's really fucking far.
We have to, Lily.
LILY: It's a good thing
I got this on tape.
ADAM: Lily, the fuck
with the camera. Shit!
Oh, my God.
Sorry.
JOY: Sean?
Yeah.
I don't feel good.
I know.
Now we're gonna
get you help.
We'll just figure out
what we're gonna do now.
I feel like
my tongue's going numb.
Sean.
Yeah?
I think somebody
took our van.
It's looking like it.
Hey, Adam.
I'm gonna get it back.
CASEY: We gotta get you
to a hospital.
I know, I know.
I know you do.
Look, listen to me.
I'm supposed to...
I know, I know.
I know, we're gonna
get you out of here.
Look, he's gonna stay
with you, okay?
He's gonna stay with you
because he's good at this.
This is not my thing.
I'm gonna go
and I'm gonna find
our van.
I'm gonna find our van,
or I'm gonna find
whoever took our van
and I'm gonna kick
somebody's ass, right?
Lily?
What?
Does that thing work?
Got batteries and shit?
Yeah, yeah.
Come on.
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
[PANTING]
[LILY CLEARS THROATS]
Adam.
Fuck.
Adam, what are you doing?
Uh-huh.
LILY: Adam what are you doing?
Hey.
Lily.
What are you doing?
Lily, listen to me.
Listen to me, okay?
I'm listening.
I'm gonna do something
right now.
I'm gonna go up
into these hills,
and I'm gonna go find
whatever the fuck
is chasing us, okay?
And whatever took our van.
I'm gonna go get it back.
Whatever fucked with us,
I'm gonna go fix it.
Because this is my fault.
It's not your fault.
It's not anybody's fault.
It's something bad
that happened.
It's something really bad
that happened,
and it's not your fault.
We're gonna get out of this
because we have to.
Lily, I'm going to go
kick somebody's ass.
What do you mean
you're gonna kick
somebody's ass?
Wait, I'm coming with you.
Adam!
[GRUNTS]
Oh, shit. [SHUSHING]
[WHISPERING] Zoom in.
I got it.
Zoom in, zoom in,
zoom in. I wanna see this.
What the fuck? Look.
LILY: It's on. Look.
That's people.
Someone's there.
LILY: What if
someone's in there?
Adam.
I'm gonna go around the back.
Come on, come on.
Hold on a second.
[WHISPERING] Adam!
LILY: Shit!
Oh, shit!
Shit!
ADAM: Okay.
Okay, sorry.
I'm just kind of
working up a little bit of...
LILY: No, I can see.
See if you see anybody.
Is there someone in there?
You see anything?
I don't think we should...
ADAM: Okay.
Maybe there's...
Let's do this.
[LILY BREATHING HEAVILY]
[MOUTHING]
[CANS RATTLING]
[SHUSHING]
[WHISPERING]
I'm gonna go up, and then
we're gonna go slow.
Through these bushes, okay?
There's a back door.
Fuck. Fuck. Okay.
Careful.
[DOOR CREAKING]
[WIND HOWLING]
ADAM: Holy shit.
LILY: What the fuck is that?
ADAM: It's a tent.
LILY: Hello.
ADAM: Hello?
Hello?
LILY: Is someone there?
ADAM: No.
Or he'd fucking open it.
What are those?
[INDISTINCT SHOUTING]
LILY: Shit.
Look. Look.
Look at that.
Fucking shotgun shells.
They're everywhere.
ADAM: Someone was just here.
LILY: Fucking footprints.
Holy shit.
Oh, my God.
Someone was just here.
They stopped.
Adam...
Someone...
Somebody got in a car
or something,
'cause they don't...
Tracks of the cars
they go around this.
Van?
Holy shit.
You think people
took the van here?
Let's go find out.
Fuck. Oh,
what the fuck is that?
LILY: Whoa.
Is that a mine?
LILY: That's a mine.
That's totally a mine.
Wait, you're gonna
go in there?
Uh...
I don't know.
You all right?
LILY: Careful.
What?
What the fuck is that?
Come here. Come here.
LILY: Holy shit!
Shit.
[COUGHING]
Dude.
[RETCHING]
Holy shit!
LILY: Ugh.
Adam...
[RETCHING VIOLENTLY]
LILY: Jesus, Adam. Oh...
Adam, hey.
[GROANING]
Shit. Are you all right?
Fuck.
What's going on here?
I'm so fucking scared
right now, Lily,
I can't even fucking...
I can barely breathe.
I know, dude.
I can barely breather,
I'm so fuckin' scared now.
Holy shit.
Fucking turn
the fucking camera off.
Oh, sorry.
I'm so fucking scared
right now.
LILY: What? What is going on?
What was that?
I need to get out of here.
I need to get the fuck
out of here so bad.
I'm freaking out.
I want to get out of here.
I think...
I think we should just go.
I want to fucking
get out of here.
And I don't want
to stay here anymore.
I'm sick and fucking...
What about everybody else?
Whoever can leave
should leave.
What does that mean?
I don't know. It means
I don't want to fucking
stay here and find out
what the fuck is going on.
Because is this...
I don't know.
What about...
What about Joy? I don't think
she can even walk right now.
I know.
That's what I'm saying.
What the fuck
are we supposed to do?
It's 60 miles.
She can't even fucking walk
five feet.
It's 60 miles.
I hear you.
And I don't wanna...
I hear you, I hear you.
I don't want to
stay here another...
I don't want to stay here.
I don't either.
After the sun sets,
I do not want
to stay here.
I don't want
to stay here tonight.
We are so fucked
because she can't
fucking walk.
If we go back there right now
and tell them what we saw
what the fuck do you
think she's gonna say?
I'll handle it.
Huh?
Jesus Christ!
LILY: Cool. Um, well,
thank you for coming in.
Thank you for having me.
I'm curious about
your green bracelet.
Oh, man, it's funny.
This is...
You know, it's one of
those squiggly bands,
and everyone thinks that
if you flirt with somebody
in middle school,
they give it to you.
But mine's, um...
Can you see?
A dollar sign.
Yeah.
Uh, at the restaurant
that I work at,
this was actually my tip.
That's...
No, that's it.
Like, instead of money,
they left me this.
That was a tip?
Oh, wow.
Dollar sign squiggly
bracelet thing.
I kind of like it, though.
Do you like it?
Yeah, no, no...
It's kind of like
a double-edged...
Yeah, I mean, you know.
[JOY SCREAMING]
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
[CASEY SIGHING]
LARISSA: Is she breathing?
Joy?
Oh, God.
[JOY GROANING]
CASEY:
Is she gonna be okay?
Joy, you all right?
We're still here, okay?
Hey.
[MOANING] Stop it.
I'm sorry. We're gonna
get you help, okay?
[MOANS] No, don't, don't.
SEAN: Okay, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
[GROANS IN PAIN]
I know, I know.
I'm sorry.
[JOY GROANS]
I know, I know, I know.
Okay. It's done.
I'm done, I'm done.
I fixed it.
Okay?
Joy?
LARISSA: Is she...
Can I talk to you?
Hey, Casey, we're gonna
be out on the, uh...
Right here.
Let me know if
something changes, okay?
[WHISPERING]
All right, this is serious.
I gotta go. We gotta go.
I gotta go get help.
ADAM:
Where are you gonna go?
Dude, at least
It doesn't hurt her anymore.
LILY: Guys,
what is going on?
Come back inside.
SEAN: I gotta go.
I'm gonna get the van.
ADAM: Sean, don't go.
That's ridiculous.
LARISSA: What's going on?
ADAM: It's ridiculous.
I'm not gonna
let that happen.
You cannot go.
No, don't leave.
Sean, don't leave!
[LILY SHUSHING]
I'm going after him.
I'm going with her.
Lily, please, please
don't leave.
Please don't leave.
He can't go alone.
LILY: Casey,
I'm coming with you.
Wait up.
ADAM: What are you doing?
I'm gonna go with her.
CASEY: Sean!
Wait. I'm coming.
What are you doing?
Casey, get back
in the house.
CASEY: No, you can't go!
Get back in the house.
Sean.
Now.
You're not going.
Yes.
No.
Casey, we have to
find the van.
What are you doing?
Okay, but we looked
for it all day,
we didn't find it.
So you're not gonna find it
in the middle of the night.
We're gonna find the van,
we're gonna find the people
that took it, we gotta
find somebody.
You can't go.
We're helpless
sitting here right now.
Sean, you can't go.
If she's...
She's gonna die
if we just stay here.
Lily, come on.
LILY: Sorry.
Sean, if she is dying...
Giving you guys some light.
Sean, if she is dying,
you're the only one
that can help her.
So stay.
Sean.
Are you coming?
Sean, please.
Baby, don't go.
Sean.
Come on.
Lily, come on.
LILY: You staying?
Yeah, Lily, go on in.
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
Adam.
What?
Durrie and Alycen
still aren't back.
Oh, I know.
LILY: I need to get some air.
ADAM: You awake?
LARISSA: Yeah.
ADAM: I'm really sorry.
LARISSA: It's not your fault.
ADAM: I know I apologized
a bunch of times, but like,
if we're being realistic here,
this totally is my fault.
LARISSA: But you didn't know
this was gonna happen.
Um...
We need to, uh...
We need to get out of here.
I know.
Um...
Joy's situation is...
...obviously getting worse.
And we're not doing
ourselves any favors
by staying here.
We...
We can't leave her.
I don't want you to
think of it like that.
I think that's
the wrong way to look at it.
I think that you should
see it like, if we go,
we can actually do something.
For all of our sake.
We'll come back.
Guaranteed we'll come back.
I'm telling you,
if we stay here,
something's gonna happen.
What if she wakes up
and no one's here?
She's here in the dark
by herself.
She's our friend.
I know.
LILY: Question.
Just curious if you could
just give me a sense of
kind of what are you afraid of?
What am I afraid of?
Yeah.
Um...
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
[RAIN PATTERING]
Um...
Would have to call
my mom into my room.
[LAUGHS]
To sleep in my room
because I was very scared
of my imagination in the dark.
Um,
and I know most kids
do that till the age
of like seven.
I think the last time
I did that, I was probably
14 or 15.
Because I just...
My imagination...
It's kind of funny
that we're...
...hanging out
under these circumstances.
Yeah, I guess
it's funny now.
Wasn't funny before.
[SIGHS]
I guess I'm glad
we are, though, I guess.
You guess?
I guess.
Well, when you're sure
let me know.
[CHUCKLES]
Maybe when we get back
we can...
What, have coffee?
[LAUGHS] Yeah.
Yeah, all right.
If we get back.
No, we'll definitely
get back.
And I feel pretty good
about it. And this is...
I think we've been through
rougher stuff than this
in general.
[WIND BLOWING]
Right?
Snakes bites, stolen vans.
I don't know. [CHUCKLES]
Yeah, well, that's all
on the outside.
[BOTH CHUCKLING]
Talking about the inside.
You're delirious.
Yeah. Maybe.
Hungry, cold, wet.
Sean.
[CHUCKLES]
I'm glad you're here,
thought, honestly.
I don't know.
I mean, I was pissed
that you got cast,
but now, like...
I'm glad you're here.
Thanks.
[LAUGHS]
I think.
I'm glad
you stuck here with me.
I'm happy you're here, too.
I just didn't know
what to think
when you got cast.
It was like, "Awesome!"
You know, I mean,
I was... I was...
I missed you.
I missed you, too.
Really?
Yeah. Yeah.
[JOY HUMMING FAINTLY]
ADAM: Sean!
Adam.
Larissa.
[FOOTSTEPS POUNDING]
[ADAM PANTING]
We need to talk.
Let's go.
Lily.
Yeah, I'm right here.
Can I have...
I'm right here.
I'm gonna be right back.
I can't see.
I'm gonna be right back,
okay?
I can't see.
[MUMBLING]
Be right back.
You know
what the fuck that is!
Who put this fucking here?
This is my jacket!
My jacket from
my fucking clothes in there.
Someone came in there...
You were in there
the whole time.
Nobody was in there!
Who put this here?
SEAN: I don't know.
I don't know.
One of you fucking people
put this here?
Are you joking right now?
We need to figure out
what to do!
We need to leave.
SEAN: Where are you gonna go?
I'm getting the fuck...
CASEY:
We're not leaving her here!
No!
SEAN: We're not doing that.
We're not leaving Joy here.
You have another
fucking idea?
LILY: Is it blood?
What the fuck is it?
Yeah, it's blood, but...
Shut the fuck up, Lily.
It's blood.
Who the...
We can't take her with us!
We're not leaving her here!
Listen to me.
I am not staying here.
Nobody wants to stay here!
We're not leaving her here.
We don't. We leave water,
we leave food.
We go, we take her.
How the fuck
are we gonna do that?
LARISSA: I wanna
get the fuck out of here!
We all do!
We all wanna go, Larissa!
But we're not leaving Joy.
That insane!
ADAM: Listen to me.
We just... We get her,
we go down to the road,
there's gonna be a car
that comes by
at some point.
It's better we're all
together and just wait there.
We can...
No, you know, we can, uh...
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
CASEY: We can what?
Adam, we can what?
We can fucking help her.
I don't wanna fucking
be here anymore.
Adam, what are you
talking about?
You don't...
You don't wanna,
she doesn't wanna
fucking be here
any fucking more.
Adam, what are you
talking about?
SEAN: What the fuck
are you saying?
We can...
We can end it right now.
CASEY: What are you...
What are you saying, Adam?
We kill her?
We...
We don't have to kill her.
No. No fucking way.
You get your fucking
shit together!
Are you fucking kidding me?
Larissa.
Don't wanna die.
CASEY: Are you listening
to what he's saying, Larissa?
Are you fucking kidding me?
Are you both out of
your fucking minds?
I can't...
I can't fucking believe you.
Oh, my God.
[YELLS] Damn it!
What are you doing, Adam?
What are you doing
out there?
CASEY: What is he doing?
She's walking around.
Why did she go with him?
LILY: He just needs
to calm down.
We can't let him
do anything to Joy.
SEAN:
She's just standing there.
He keeps going in and out.
LILY: All right,
I'm going over there.
I'm gonna talk to him.
SEAN: No, don't.
LILY: He'll listen to me.
No, don't go there.
CASEY: I'll go with her.
LILY: I'm going.
This is ridiculous.
I'll go. He's not gonna
do anything bad
with the camera.
[DOOR CREAKING]
What do you want?
Where's Adam?
Adam.
Look, I know everyone's
freaking out right now,
but we have to
stick together.
Larissa.
Adam.
Adam!
Are you hearing
what I'm saying, Adam?
I need to think
by myself right now.
Both of you
should get out of here.
I don't want to
go with them now.
Larissa, go.
No. No.
You have to get out of here.
Get out of here!
Get the fuck out of here!
[WHIMPERING]
Adam, what are you doing?
[YELLING]
CASEY: Adam!
Larissa!
[SOBBING]
Larissa, stop!
LILY: Casey,
I'll get her.
Larissa!
Larissa, wait!
Lily, where...
Has she come back?
Larissa.
Where'd she go?
CASEY: Where is she?
Hello! Did you see her?
Lily? You lost her?
You ran after her?
LILY: I don't know.
I don't know
where she went.
What happened at Adam's place?
LILY: She went out there
and she just...
No, no, no.
What happened at Adam's place?
LILY: I don't know
what fucking happened!
All right, you need to get
Larissa and bring her back here.
What is he doing?
We need to get Larissa
and bring her back here.
No, there's something
you're not telling me,
and you're not telling me.
We need to get her, Sean,
and bring her back.
What happened over there?
LILY: Calm down,
don't yell at me!
Is he coming over here?
LILY: I don't know.
Larissa is...
I don't know
where she went.
All right, fine.
I'm gonna go find Larissa.
Is he coming over here?
All right? Hang out.
No, Sean, you can't
go by yourself. Sean, wait!
Sean!
Stay here.
Hey.
[GROANS FAINTLY]
Come on.
I'm gonna help you up.
[PANTING] Okay.
Okay, okay. Okay.
Hey. Hey.
All right.
[EXCLAIMS]
It's okay.
It's okay, it's okay.
[YELLS]
[SOBBING]
SEAN: Oh, Adam?
CASEY: Adam.
CASEY: Adam?
Joy?
CASEY: Adam! Adam!
Joy! Joy!
Joy!
Joy.
God.
CASEY: Fucking idiot!
How could you do that?
[CASEY SCREAMING]
ADAM: Stop taunting me!
CASEY: You killed her!
You fucking killed her!
You fucking gagged
her to death!
No, Adam!
Don't hurt me!
Adam!
Get the fuck away
from me, Casey!
[THUD]
SEAN: You motherfucker!
Where's Casey?
She in there?
You motherfucker!
I'm sorry.
[GRUNTS]
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
[LILY PANTING]
Lily.
Hi.
Where are you going?
Who's bag is this?
What is this?
Really? Why were you
hiding these?
[LILY PANTING]
SEAN: Lily!
Lily, stop!
Lily!
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
[LILY GASPS]
SEAN: God,
is that the fucking van?
Fucking van!
You knew where the van was
this whole fucking time!
Open the fucking door!
Lily, stop!
[LILY PANTING]
Lily!
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
[LILY SOBBING]
[STONES CLATTERING]
[LILY PANTING]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
[LILY SOBS]
LILY: Sean.
Sean, please.
Sean, listen.
[WEEPING]
Just listen to me.
It was a mistake.
Please don't do anything.
I only wanted
to scare you guys.
It wasn't supposed
to be like this.
Sean, listen to me!
[THUD]
[SEAN GRUNTS]