(Multicom jingle)
(somber piano music)
[Priest] We are here today to say goodbye
to the dear soul of Helen Walsh.
May perpetual light shine upon her,
and may she rest in peace.
Amen.
(somber music)
Let us take a moment to reflect
on how she touched each one of our lives.
Helen was always there with a kind word
and a helping hand.
She lived in this community
all of her adult life,
and worked tirelessly to keep it a place
where we could all be proud
to raise our families.
The Walsh home was a warm and loving home.
And all of us who were fortunate enough
to spend time there,
certainly were aware that Helen's radiance
was at its core.
Let us pray that she
has found eternal peace,
and let us also pray that
her beloved husband, Frank,
and their beloved sons,
Robert, James, and Steven,
find solace in the knowledge
that she is amongst the angels.
Amen.
(somber music)
I can't believe Uncle Bill didn't show.
Yeah, that's your
mother's side of the family,
a bunch of kooks.
You gonna tip?
Did you tip?
- Yeah, yeah, I tipped.
Nice little place you picked out here.
Waiter!
[Waiter] Yes, sir.
Never seen people eat so
much in my whole entire life.
Free meal.
Thank you very much.
- Thank you.
So, who's that woman you were speaking to
at the service?
Which one? I was talking
to a couple of them.
Yeah, I know.
Everybody thought you worked there.
At a funeral parlor?
Well, you spoke to every
woman that walked in.
They were mom's friends, from work.
She never told me she worked
with so many younger women.
Probably trying to keep her job.
A ha!
You're a funny guy, Pop.
Thank you.
Now, Dad, our place is your place.
Come by tomorrow, I'm making
franks and beans for supper.
Don't worry about it.
Kids, get in the car!
Get in the car!
Okay, Bob, goodnight!
Goodnight, Dad.
Goodnight.
I'll call ya.
If you need us, just give a ring.
Don't worry, don't worry about it.
I'll call you in the morning, Pop.
Okay.
Goodnight.
You gonna open the door for me?
All right!
I forgot.
You know, your brothers aggravate me.
Where do they find those girls they marry?
Your mother was nothing like that.
And what's her name?
- Joy.
You see the face on her all day?
Did she ever smile once?
It was a funeral.
They can't have kids.
You know why, don't you?
It's her fault.
I don't understand you boys at all.
What's her name?
[Robert] Who?
[Frank] You know, the wife.
Darlene.
Darlene, yeah.
Well, she's gotta be at least
10 years older than him.
Did you see her today?
Your mother looked younger.
She has 2 kids and he marries her.
What is he thinkin' about?
He's a kid himself.
How old is he?
I can't remember any of that stuff,
your mother knew everything.
You didn't get a chance to talk much today.
Are you gonna be okay, Dad?
Yeah, yeah, I'll take a walk later.
Okay.
So, everybody was asking me
whether you're gonna settle down.
Pop, I'll settle down
when I find the right girl, all right?
- What do you mean by that?
I never know what you mean.
I mean the right girl.
Like your chair, right?
You know how it feels right?
That's what I'm looking for,
something that feels right.
- I know what you are,
you're what they call a confirmed bachelor.
Make it sound like I have a disease.
Hey, whatever happened to
that girl Kathy something?
I'm just curious.
See, that's exactly what I'm talking about.
She wasn't right for me.
And you know what?
I probably wasn't right for her, so...
How long did you go out with her?
I don't know.
A year, year and a half?
- I remember how it was,
it was the same thing every night.
I mean, she was a nice
girl, I liked her a lot,
but it was like...
"What do you want to do tonight?"
She's like, "I don't know,
what do you wanna do?
I don't know."
That stuff drove me crazy after a while.
That's what you go
through, that's what it is.
You should've married that girl.
What are you gonna do now,
go through life alone?
Well, I'm alone now.
Eh, you gotta share,
you gotta share your life with somebody.
Share what?
Share my day, my troubles?
(Robert chuckles)
It would've been nice
having someone there today,
you know, mom dying and everything, but...
I did okay, you know?
I got you, and James, and Steven.
It wouldn't of been her mother
who died anyway, it was mine.
My mother I'm gonna miss.
So, in the end, I'd be
just as alone, wouldn't I?
(somber music)
You know, your mother
was a beautiful woman.
Yeah, she was, Pop.
To Mom.
(glass clangs)
(dog barks)
(whimsical music)
May I help you?
Yeah, I need a microwave.
[Man] What size?
For one person.
Right this way.
Here we go.
That's for one person?
Yes.
Looks kinda big.
How does it work?
There's directions inside the box.
"As a general rule, when doubling a recipe,
increase the cooking time by about 50%.
When cooking...
When cutting a recipe in half,
reduce the time by about 40%."
(siren blares)
(cars honking)
Tony.
Robert.
Hello.
Okay, everyone, I would like
you to meet Susan Prescot.
Hi.
Susan is a whiz with the new tax laws.
We're lucky that the office
in Milwaukee could spare her.
Robert, could you familiarize Susan
with the Burton account?
Absolutely.
How do you like your new office?
Yeah, it's great, I just can't stop
staring out of the window, it's-
- Yeah.
Happens to everybody, and you
never quite get used to it.
Um...
I've gone over the Klein account,
and I saw what you accomplished
here, very impressive.
Thank you very much, I appreciate that.
Well, as far as the Burton
account is concerned,
I've only had a few hours to look at it,
but my first reaction is
we've got a lot of work to do,
but yes, we can definitely,
definitely save them money.
Good, good, good, good, that's good.
We have a shot at the account then.
Let me show you what
I've come up with here.
Go to 14A.
No, yeah, 14A.
(cars honking)
(calming jazz music)
Falco was right, this girl is sharp.
We're gonna have that Burton
account locked up in no time.
I heard she's married.
Separated.
[Man] She's not your type.
[Robert] What do you mean not my type?
She's slick and east-side,
you're funky and downtown.
This girl's got something,
she's a straight shooter.
You like him, don't you?
Well, I don't know,
I've been working with him
for a couple of days.
He seems nice.
Oh, yeah, he is.
But just be careful.
(somber piano music)
(laughing)
Did you get that one?
Yes, thank you for dinner.
Chivalry is not dead.
You're welcome.
(Susan chuckles) You eat a lot for a girl.
I can't believe you would say that-
- I don't know if you've ever heard that.
I could understand seconds, but thirds,
I think it's a little much.
I did not have thirds!
What were you saying now before?
You asked me a question.
I was asking...
Oh, do you have any brothers and sisters?
Oh, no, I am an only child.
Oh.
And spoiled.
- Spoiled, spoiled.
Of course, I knew you would
say that. Spoiled brat, yeah.
Was it lonely growing up?
Eh, a little bit maybe,
but I had a lot of friends.
High school and college
I joined some clubs.
The debating club, the science club,
the business club-
- Those are all the kids I
used to beat up in school.
You beat up kids in school?
I didn't really beat 'em up!
That's for all the kids
you beat up, that's terrible!
Ow, ow, she's beating me up!
- I am not!
- Help!
- No, I'm not!
(Susan chuckles)
Did you wave for a taxi?
No!
Is there a taxi here?
They're right behind you.
When you need a taxi, can't find a taxi.
When you don't want a taxi,
like in a moment like this,
sure enough a cab shows up.
Well, I kind of want a
taxi, it's a little late.
- Right.
- I had a great time.
Yeah, I had a good
time too. Here, allow me.
Thank you.
Buckle up.
I will.
Take care of her!
[Driver] Yeah, yeah, right.
She's a lousy tipper, so...
[Narrator] The ring-tailed
lemur is often found
on the island of Madagascar.
(somber music)
(Robert yawns)
You've gotta be kidding!
Is that old?
(Susan laughs)
- It's very old-
- I'm sorry.
- But it works.
- It's the only one I know.
(Susan laughs)
All right, so there are five boroughs.
Is that what I was talking about?
Five boroughs, we're in one of them.
- Really?
- You don't care, do you?
I do, I do, it's just
you wear the best ties.
Well, thank you, I made this one actually
in a weaving competition.
- No way.
- Yes, I did.
I won first prize for this.
It's very elegant and sexy.
Oh, why thank you.
Especially this one.
You're welcome.
(ship honks)
What are we having for dinner tonight?
Oh, dinner?
What?
What, one kiss and I gotta buy you dinner?
- Well, I'm hungry!
- Again?
First base, boom, buy me dinner.
(Susan laughs)
You're always hungry!
That's not true.
All right, I'll make you dinner.
I'm gonna make you a very nice dinner.
A little shrimp thing I do.
All right.
Home cooking, that sounds good.
Well, do you have health insurance?
Yeah, why?
I may make you sign a
waiver of responsibility-
- I'm sure you're an excellent cook.
I've never killed anyone...
Yet.
(lighthearted jazzy music)
(Susan chuckles)
[Susan] What was your grandmother like?
[Robert] Oh, my grandmother.
Now, she was one of the first women
to become a shop steward
for the electrician's union.
[Susan] Wow.
[Robert] She worked down
at the Brooklyn Navy Yard.
[Susan] Huh.
What was she like?
[Robert] She was beautiful,
smart, and senile actually.
(Susan laughs)
But she was nice.
[Susan] I love how you're so proud
of your family, that's nice.
[Robert] Yeah.
[Susan] What was your mom like?
My mom was special.
Yeah?
And of course I'm gonna say
that 'cause she's my mom, but-
- Well-
- I remember, she used to
take us down to the beach
at Rockaway every Sunday,
no, every Saturday.
Every Saturday, she'd take us
down to the beach at Rockaway.
And I remember this one time,
I'm looking out at the ocean,
she comes up to me and she
whispers in my ear, and she says,
"Make a wish on the third wave."
The third wave?
- Yeah.
- Oh.
And I did.
And I got my wish.
- No!
- Yeah.
Really?
What was it?
- I wanted to see a whale.
Oh, you're kidding!
I wanted to see a whale, and sure enough,
the third wave, right out of the horizon,
boom, a whale pops in.
Your mom believed in magic, huh?
- I guess so.
- Yeah.
Wow, I don't think I've ever
told anyone that story before.
Want to go on a picnic tomorrow?
- Picnic?
- Mhm.
I'd love it.
Picnic?
That's so funny.
What's funny, a picnic?
No, no, no, I came here to work,
I came here to work,
and I've just had the best two weeks
I've had in a long time.
Really? I wanted you
to have a terrible time
while you were here.
- Oh, why thank you.
- Oh.
You've been a prince up to this point.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
That's the kind of guy I am.
In fact, you can call
me "Prince" if you want,
'cause he's not using the name,
so you can call me prince.
(Susan laughs)
No, no, it's...
It's strange.
That I can meet someone from so far away
from where you're from,
and you feel like you...
Like you know them.
Yeah.
You know?
And I know you.
Yeah.
(romantic jazzy music)
(lighthearted music)
(pump sprays)
(garbage can rattles)
(dog barks)
I'll just drop this off,
I'll be back in one second.
I cracked the windows for ya.
Don't bark at the neighbors.
(Susan chuckles)
You said noon!
Hey, Pop, how you doin'?
Did you see it?
What?
Come on, I'll show it to ya.
What do ya got?
Here, take a look at this.
Eh?
Looks like one of them fancy imported jobs.
Oh, yeah, very imported looking.
Nice car, Dad, nice car.
Listen, you know, you
gotta put oil in your car.
Did you change the oil?
Yeah, yeah, I changed it.
Good, because that's very important-
- Dad, I have a friend with me,
I'm going to a picnic.
Is it okay if I invite her in?
Sure, sure, bring her in, bring her in.
Okay.
Another one of those...
Susan!
Pop, this is Susan.
Susan, this is my father, Frank.
Hi.
I was looking forward to meeting you.
I just bought a new car.
I saw.
That's yours, huh?
It's very, very nice.
Yeah, you can't keep
anything nice around here,
they steal it.
Hm.
Were you ever over here before?
My son has so many girlfriends, sometimes-
- No, no, she was never here, Dad.
I was sorry to hear about your loss.
Thank you.
I wish it was me instead of my wife.
My wife was much, much better with people.
A nicer person, anyway.
Let me show you something in the basement.
Okay.
Here.
Robert built all this
stuff, isn't it great?
No, I didn't!
Built this bar.
The bar I built.
The bar, that's very nice.
Yeah, I want you to see the backyard here.
Actually, I paid a couple of
kids and told him I built it.
Oh.
My, what a cute backyard!
Pops, Susan is from Wisconsin.
I bet you have a backyard
bigger than this whole block.
Yeah, but we didn't have the ocean.
Why not?
Wisconsin, Pop.
Oh.
I sent this guy through college
so he could tell me these things.
You two eat yet?
No, we're going to a picnic but-
- I want to show people that I got company,
I don't want them to feel sorry for me
because my wife died.
I'll go get some cold cuts.
Where are my keys?
Um...
See my keys around, Robert?
Let me see.
Here.
Oh, thanks.
Watch my spot, will ya?
All right.
What's a spot?
Well, out here in Queens,
it's more than just a
place you park your car,
it's kind of an extension of your house.
Symbolic.
It represents family pride, you know?
See that garbage can?
That garbage can is a marker.
We have a spot.
When my father passes away,
not only will my brothers
and I inherit the house,
but we'll also inherit the spot.
Yup.
Now he's got a spot and not much else.
I felt sorry for him.
I know, every time I come over here,
I find it harder and harder to leave.
But I think he liked you, though.
Really?
How can you tell?
'Cause he showed you the basement.
Oh. I'll bet you he shows every girl
you bring over the basement.
Yeah, but he showed you the
basement and the backyard,
he never does that.
Oh, wow.
Ah, don't get me started!
We're at your father's house.
Oh...
Listen, if it's okay with you,
I'm gonna ask Falco to make us partners
on the Burton deal all the way through.
Is that all right with you?
Um, well, actually, I
was gonna talk to Falco
on Monday morning and tell
him that I'm going back home.
Why?
Well, Ted called.
What did old Ted want?
Well, he misses me and I want to see him.
Well, what about us?
What about us?
What, are you saying that this
was an exclusive relationship?
Yeah!
For me, it has been.
Oh, come on, Robert, be honest.
I am!
Last week you asked Joanne
from payroll out for a drink.
I did?
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Well, it's just a friendly
thing, totally platonic.
(Susan chuckles)
I have been here two weeks,
and even I know that no one asks
Joanne from payroll out for a drink
expecting it to be platonic.
Well, she didn't show.
I know, I had lunch with her.
She didn't know you and
I were seeing each other,
very few women know that
we're seeing each other.
The word on you up there is
not to expect anything else.
The word on me?
What's wrong with a guy who dates?
Nothing.
You just shouldn't expect loyalty
if he doesn't have any himself.
Susan, I'm totally loyal.
I'm totally loyal to
whoever I'm going out with.
Okay.
All I'm saying is that
I'm going back to see Ted
to see if he and I could work things out.
Yeah, that's cool.
Doesn't she eat?
I have to be able to fit into
my bathing suit this summer.
If a man likes a woman he likes her
if she's got a belly or not.
You know, if I were a younger man,
I'd fight you for her.
Seems I got competition everywhere I turn.
[Frank] Yeah.
So where's Steven and
James? They coming over?
No, no, James is in Boston tonight,
and Steven and his wife,
you know, what's her name...
[Robert] Joy.
She's sick again, always sick, you know.
So they're not coming over.
They should be here tonight.
Ah, they got their own lives to live.
So do you!
Well, we'll have to do it without them.
What do you got?
What are you doin'?
Come on, will ya?
I'm not a kid!
Move that, move that.
You bought yourself a
car that looks imported,
I got you a fat-free birthday cake.
Fat-free birthday...
You ain't gonna sing
Happy Birthday, are ya?
All right, we won't sing happy birthday.
Oh, good, thank you.
Here, now make a wish.
What?
Make a wish and blow out the candles.
Make a wish?
I already got everything I ever wished for.
Your mother loved you, you know.
Come on, blow 'em out.
(Frank blows)
(clapping)
You like my son, huh?
How can I not?
Yeah, well, I feel sorry for ya.
Funny.
Listen, if you're ever in
the neighborhood, drop by.
You don't need to bring him, you know.
(Robert chuckles)
(Susan laughs)
I might take you up on that offer.
Okay.
Well, it was a pleasure to meet you.
Pleasure.
Watch your step going down.
Thanks, all right.
You know what?
I'll meet you at the car,
I'm just gonna walk him back up, okay?
Okay.
- Watch out there.
- Thanks.
All right, Pop, I'll call ya.
Nice girl.
The way you ever found
a nice girl like that,
I'll never know.
Well, she's married.
She's what?
She's separated, but she's just
going through something right now.
Come on.
Come on in, come on in.
Don't waste your time.
If the girl has somebody,
it's normal to go through
life with somebody.
What are you trying to
tell me, Dad? It's fate?
Something like fate? Like
you put two people together
and you sprinkle fairy dust on them
and they're happily ever after?
I don't know what you're saying.
I always had to ask your
mother what you were saying.
Your brothers I don't understand either,
but at least they settled down.
Yeah, but they married
people you don't like.
Don't you see the irony in that, Pop?
What are you looking for?
My keys.
I had my car key and my
house key on the same ring.
Well, they have to be
around here somewhere.
Where'd you put 'em?
I don't know.
Whenever I lost something,
your mother would always find it,
I never had to worry.
Check your pockets?
I checked them, I checked them.
All right, you go, I'll find them later.
Go ahead, don't keep the girl waiting.
[Robert] You sure?
Yeah, yeah.
I'll find them later.
All right.
I'll talk to you later, Pop.
Oh, thanks.
Where were they?
In the door.
(Frank chuckles)
(whimsical music)
I'll see ya.
Okay.
(somber music)
Lydia and Warren invited me to a dance.
They say it's been 6
months, I should get out.
Some kind of luau thing,
they bought me this shirt.
Ooh!
Yeah, very nice shirt, very nice.
Now, I've been thinking about it, Dad.
You should go out, meet somebody new.
You've been thinking about it?
Yeah. I mean, I don't know
what the dating scene is
for a youngster like yourself, but,
I'm not saying get serious,
I'm just saying meet a
new friend or something.
Who's gonna put up with
me the way your mother did?
Good point.
I mean, you know, just
someone to share things with,
someone to go on your walks with,
watch TV with you.
Good point.
That's it, right?
[Falco] Oh, Robert.
Yeah?
Yeah, I'm thinking of
sending Wilson off to Milwaukee
for that conference.
What do you think?
Why don't you send me?
Well, are you sure?
I mean, it's gonna be a couple of weeks.
I'd want you to stop into
Detroit on the way back,
look at the Firestone account.
I can do that, I can do that.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Great.
Good idea.
All right.
Yeah, I can...
(people chattering)
I can't take this.
It's a long time since I've
been to a dance without her.
I probably forgot how to
do it, it's embarrassing!
Just mingle.
You'll have fun!
You look great, Frank!
Doesn't he, Warren?
You look great.
Okay, I'll give it a shot.
(calming tropical music)
Uh, I'll have some of that punch.
Hey.
What's your sign?
42 long.
(Florence chuckles)
No, sign!
You know, like Sagittarius,
or Capricorn, Leo.
Oh, astronomy.
Astrology.
Uh, Libra.
Ooh!
Is your mother with ya?
No, she dropped me off.
You're not a senior citizen, are ya?
You want to dance?
Sure.
Come on.
I'm not exactly a great dancer.
Fake it.
(Frank chuckles)
(calming tropical music)
My name's Florence, like in Italy.
My name is Frank, like in hot dog.
(Florence chuckles)
I don't know.
You don't look like a Frank to me,
you look more like a Francis.
It's classy.
My wife passed away last spring.
Four years for me.
No kidding?
Mhm.
How old are you, Florence?
Old enough to know better,
but young enough to
learn a new trick or two.
I just thought I was old
enough to be your father.
Good!
Then you can help me with my homework.
(Florence chuckles)
Woohoo!
(Florence laughs)
Whoa.
Suave of you.
You got a nice smile, you know that?
Yeah?
It's my legs you've been looking at.
No, your legs?
When?
The whole night!
(Florence laughs)
(calming tropical music)
I'm thirsty, how about you, huh?
Thirsty?
I'll get you some punch.
No, no, I'd like a real drink, huh?
I don't think they serve liquor here.
What's the matter, don't you drink?
Oh, no, I don't.
Well, look, I know this cute little diner
over on Belle Boulevard.
You could buy me a real drink,
and we'll get you a cup of coffee, huh?
You know, my wife was so neat
she used to put newspaper
under the cuckoo clock.
(Florence laughs)
Oh...
Tell me about your kids.
Well, three boys.
One is an electrical engineer,
he's doing very well,
the other one, he sells
something, he's a salesman.
I think computer products,
something like that.
He's doing pretty good.
And Robert, Robert's an accountant.
Except for the fact that he's
got too many girlfriends,
he's doing very well and he's a nice kid.
(Florence chuckles)
That's terrific.
Yeah, you know, I'm proud
of my sons, all of them.
Do you tell them that?
No.
You know, my husband,
Sam, God rest his soul,
absolutely adored our daughter.
But then he died.
And the first thing she said to me was,
"Mom, what did Daddy think of me?"
Life's short.
Get my drift?
I don't kiss on the first date.
Whatever's right.
I had a good time though, thanks.
But I'm free Wednesday.
Wednesday?
Mhm.
Francis, when I first laid eyes on you
back there at the luau,
I saw that sad, hangdog look of yours,
and I just thought maybe I'd
like to get to know you better.
I was hoping maybe you would
like to get to know me better.
(calming jazz music)
Call me tomorrow?
I just broke my rule.
(whimsical music)
(engine revs)
Don't you have anything better to do?
Snoopy!
(whimsical music)
[Robert] So, how was
the dance the other night?
[Frank] Okay.
Just okay?
[Frank] Yeah.
Hey, listen, I'm going to Milwaukee
for a conference for work.
For how long?
[Robert] I don't know, a couple weeks.
And from there I'm gonna go visit a friend.
A friend?
[Robert] Yes.
Girlfriend?
Yes, it's a girl.
Well, you be careful.
All right, you be careful too.
Bye, Pop.
(lighthearted music)
I bought the business from my boss 15...
Thank you.
15 years ago.
We do department store receipts.
And, well, I used to have
25 girls working for me,
and now I got 6!
Everything is computerized these days.
Hey.
You okay?
Hm?
Yeah, yeah, I'm fine.
Oh, come on.
Tell me, talk.
I feel strange.
About what?
Florence, for over 40 years
I've been faithful to my wife,
and now...
Now she's gone.
It's important to respect
her memory, Francis,
but you gotta move on.
It took me a long, long
time to accept that fact,
but you just have to.
Yeah, I know, but it's
easier said than done.
You don't want to see me anymore, do you?
I'm not sure.
Well, that's too bad,
because you made my week.
You know, you just might surprise yourself
and be on this planet
a long, long time yet.
You really want to waste those years?
Florence.
There's gonna be a little get together
in my house this Saturday
afternoon with my sons.
Will you please come over?
I'd love to.
Good.
Sit down and have some dessert.
(wistful piano music)
This is good.
(doorbell rings)
(lighthearted piano music)
Robert!
Hi.
I guess you don't have to
fight for spots around here, huh?
Yeah, no.
Wow, what are you doing here?
Oh, I was just in the neighborhood,
so I thought I'd, you know, swing by and...
- Yeah, right.
(Susan chuckles)
No, I came to see you.
I'm not interrupting anything, am I?
No, no, not at all.
These are for you.
Thanks.
Come in, I'm sorry.
Come on in, come on in.
All right.
(dramatic saxophone music)
Well, I saw Ted.
Oh, Ted.
Yes.
How did it go?
Well, he wants to move to Seattle,
which I thought was kinda funny,
so I told him that a change of location
would not necessarily fix
what's wrong with our marriage.
And I just realized that being with Ted
actually stopped me from
doing a lot of things.
For instance, I've always
wanted to go to New York,
and you know like when the
business trips would come up,
he would talk me out of them all the time.
Well, maybe it's best that you two
aren't together anymore.
Yeah.
You know, Falco wanted to
send someone else to Milwaukee,
but I insisted that I come.
Well, this isn't New York, Robert.
My problems aren't a hundred miles away,
the fantasy month is very much over.
So, you're saying we're
not in Kansas anymore?
(Susan chuckles)
Exactly.
Well, why don't we just take a shot?
Hang out together, you and I.
No pressure, just hang out.
I have a friend who has a little cabin
right on the lake in
Vermont, it's beautiful.
You're very persistent, aren't you?
Well, can you blame me?
(Susan laughs)
I don't know what you did, coming here-
- Stalking you.
Showing up at my doorstep
was very brave, you know.
I could've shut the
door right in your face.
You would've never shut the door-
- I could have, I could have.
Not this sad, little
face coming to see you.
You would've slammed the door on me?
No.
I guess not.
See?
(lighthearted music)
I hate to leave so soon,
but I promised Falco
I'd go check this account out in Detroit.
Oh, it's better this way,
it'll give us some time to think.
[Robert] Bye.
Bye.
Hey, tell your dad I say hi.
Oh, yeah.
You know, I talked to my brother,
and he said that my dad met somebody.
You're kidding!
I'm so happy for him.
Yeah.
It's nice to meet somebody.
(lighthearted music)
You turn an unexpected
corner, and then wham!
Your life changes on you just like that.
(kids playing)
And my motto...
My motto is that you always
take it while you can
and run like hell with-
- Stop with the balls!
[Kid] Come on!
Go!
[Kid] I got it, I got it!
Don't you get tired?
Oh, no, no.
Life's a blast!
Right, Francis?
Yeah, usually.
(Frank chuckles)
Nice outfit.
Oh, thanks.
My friend's daughter has it in blue.
I think...
I'll be right back, I
got some ice, I think.
I think I'll go see if
Francis could use some help.
Francis.
What'd I do wrong?
You didn't do anything.
Well, your boys, they just sat there
and looked at each other.
Well, that's the way they are,
they usually keep to themself,
don't worry about it.
And the wives!
I can just imagine what
they're saying about me now.
I don't care what they say.
Come over here, I want to talk to you.
Robert will understand, he's been around.
It'll go better with him, I know it will.
Oh.
Aw!
(lighthearted music)
[Commentator] The
quarterback is not getting
the protection from his offensive line,
and he's having to let go of the football-
- Oh, the door's open, he must be here.
[Florence] Oh!
Hey, Pop.
Hey, kid.
How are ya?
Hi, Robert!
I'm Florence.
- Nice to meet you.
Hi, Florence.
- Hello!
Hey, give us a hand with this, will ya?
All right, let me get this for ya.
Thank you, thank you.
Oh, so you're Robert?
Yeah.
Oh!
Your father's told me so much about you.
Most of it's good.
- Oh.
(Florence laughs)
Can you just put those down there?
Yeah.
So, how you doin' Pops?
Just put that down.
Your father's gonna live a hundred years.
Oh, so, listen.
Can I get you something, huh?
Name your poison.
Uh, I'll have a mineral water.
Honey?
Same thing.
Okay, coming right up!
I'll check on dinner too.
Interesting pattern there, Pop.
Oh, thanks.
Florence picked that out.
I was never any good at that stuff.
I did buy some paintings though.
Clowns, they're all clowns.
There's something about clowns that I like.
You know, your mother and
me were always interested
in purchasing some works of art,
but we never could get around to it.
You like them?
- They're clowns.
- Eh?
Yeah.
Well, don't they make you feel good?
They sort of pep you up a little bit.
Okey dokey, here we are!
- Oh, wait a minute.
- Here you are.
Here's your water.
- Thank you, thank you.
Come on, sit down, honey.
Come on, come on.
- I'll take a seat.
Here's your water.
- Ah, thanks!
- Very well.
Robert.
You know, your father told me
that you've been away, huh?
Yes, yes, I was on a business trip,
and I went to visit a friend in Wisconsin.
Oh.
Wisconsin?
Where the hell's Wisconsin?
Is that near Vegas?
(Frank chuckles)
Close.
So, you're the one who's not married, huh?
Yeah, he's got too many girlfriends.
Oh, he's the wild man of the family, huh?
I'm a people person.
He's a what?
[Robert] A people person.
It's an expression.
He's a people person.
He likes people, yeah.
(Frank chuckles)
Yeah.
So, where are you from?
- Well-
- Me?
He's talking to me!
Originally, I'm from Texas,
but I've been living
here a long, long time.
I've got a cute little
place over in Rosedale.
Hm.
Should we have something to eat?
Good, yes!
Yes, I'll get it in a jiffy!
We got a microwave.
What's the matter?
Full.
So, Pop, do you guys have
fun, you and Florence?
Yeah!
She loves to do things.
We're gonna paint the
house over the weekend.
She's had it very rough, you know.
Her husband died of liver cancer.
She's like a rock.
Well, I can see that.
You should see her daughter.
Beauty.
Oh, but stay away from
her, she's getting married.
Listen, Pop, you should...
Why don't you think about
this a little bit, you know?
Maybe play the field a little bit.
Maybe date some other women.
You're a handsome man, you're funny.
You know, word gets out,
those women are gonna
be running towards you,
I guarantee it.
- Yeah!
- Yeah.
- Yeah, sure.
- Yeah, no.
That way you and I can
double date or something,
it would be nice.
- Double date?
- Yes.
Florence would like that.
You boys want seconds?
No, no thank you.
I'm still...
You got anything for dessert?
It's a surprise!
Okay.
What are you doing?
Just doctoring it a little.
That was some dinner.
- Thank you!
- Yeah, some dinner.
Hey, you tired, huh?
[Frank] Nah.
A little bit.
Say, Florence, you need a lift?
A lift?
Oh, you drove?
Her car's in Rosedale.
Oh. Oh, all right, it's
a little out of my way,
but I don't mind. You know,
it's late, that way my father
doesn't have to drive you home.
No, you don't understand.
Florence is staying here tonight.
Hm?
We have an early morning.
Oh.
Well, I guess I better go upstairs.
[Frank] All right.
Goodnight, boys.
Night.
So?
Everything okay?
Yeah.
Good.
Yeah, I gotta get outta here, Pop.
[Frank] What?
No, I'm fine, I'm gonna take off.
You what?
I'm driving over to Steve's tomorrow.
You want to take a ride?
[Frank] No, we're
painting upstairs tomorrow,
and tomorrow night we're
seeing some friends.
Oh.
Does she have money, Pop?
She's got her own business
with six people on the payroll.
You know, they make you feel
happy when you look at them.
What?
The clowns!
The clowns.
They make you feel happy
when you look at them.
Yeah.
I'll see ya.
Okay.
(dog faintly barks)
(lighthearted jazzy music)
He gonna be okay?
Him?
Yeah, he'll be all right.
I love him, you know.
Well, it's an awful lot
for him to take all at once.
You and I are getting married.
(Florence laughs)
I bet you say that to all the girls.
Nah, just two.
Come on upstairs, I'll
show you my etchings.
(Florence chuckles)
[Announcer] Flight 232,
nonstop service to Chicago
is now boarding in gate-
- [Robert] Susan!
Hi.
[Robert] Hi.
How are ya?
- Good, how are you?
- Good.
Good.
How was the flight, good?
- Oh, it was all right.
Sorry I'm late, thank you.
That's okay.
My dad's having a little party,
wanted to stop by for a bit.
Yeah.
What's the party for?
I don't know, he didn't say.
You look good.
Great, I mean.
Thanks.
[Robert] You okay?
Yeah, yeah.
Just wasn't planning on
coming back to New York,
but here I am.
Well, I'm glad you came.
Good.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
You're a true gentleman.
Oh, I don't know who I am anymore.
Since I met you, I don't know,
my world has-
- What?
I don't know, I hear
your voice and I'm excited,
I see you, I'm unnerved by it, you know?
It's okay!
I mean, I like it.
It's a good thing, you know?
And women, I don't even care.
(knocking)
Hey, hi, come on in!
Hi!
Hi, this is Susan.
- Oh, hello, I'm Florence.
- It's nice to meet you.
Oh, it's so nice to meet you.
Pop, you remember Susan.
Yeah, pretty girl.
Hi, it's good to see you again.
I'm sorry I'm late, my plane was delayed,
left a little bit of bad
weather back in Wisconsin.
Is that near Vegas?
- Uh-
- Close.
- I know it's not.
(Susan chuckles)
May I use the little girl's room?
- Oh, sure, it's right
upstairs, it's on the...
First one on the left.
Okay, thanks.
She's so pretty.
Yeah.
Does she still got somebody?
No, Pops, she filed.
Oh!
Oh, look at this.
You guys have done some stuff.
What color would this be?
Well, it's kind of a burnt orange
with a little bit of terracotta.
You know, your brothers were here
the other day with their wives.
They were speechless.
Really?
So, what's the occasion today, Pop?
What are we doing?
No occasion, we're just
having a little get together.
Yeah, yeah.
We got everything fixed
up down in the basement.
Come on!
We don't need an occasion, come on down!
Get your friend when she comes down
and go to the basement.
Oh.
No, my mom must be doing
flip flops in heaven right now.
Well, shall we join them?
Yeah.
Can I...
Sit down one second, I just want to...
I've been thinking.
I need to settle down in my life.
I need to be more responsible.
Okay.
So, I think that we
shouldn't see other people.
[Florence] Yoohoo!
Hey, come on down, we're waiting for you!
Don't, just think about it.
I'm just- Okay, well
Don't, just...
Come on.
(lighthearted piano music)
Not...
You want to dance with me, hey, Papa?
(lighthearted music)
So, Robert tells me that your marriage
didn't work out so good.
Pop, I heard that.
Are you drinking?
You know I don't drink.
So, did you come to marry my son?
Pop!
I've never seen you like this,
what's the matter with you?
What's the matter with you?
You're never here, you're
never around, you never fax.
(Susan laughs)
I'm here, and you don't have a fax.
And if you had a fax, you
wouldn't know how to use it.
(phone rings)
Oh, excuse me.
I'll be right back.
Absolutely.
(phone rings)
Yeah?
Yeah.
(Susan chuckles)
Okay, I'll talk to you tomorrow.
Steven, he's not coming over,
his wife is sick and he doesn't
want to leave her alone.
What about James?
James' car broke down,
the wife needs the car in the morning,
so he's working on it.
They live two blocks away.
Yeah, they're not very big
in the walking department.
I'm glad you're here anyway,
because I think you should hear this first.
I'm selling the house.
Good, good, that's a good idea.
You gonna move in with Steven?
No, no, I'm moving to
Rosedale with Florence.
You're gonna move in with Florence?
Yeah, we're gonna live
together until next spring,
then we're getting married.
Married?
Why?
Because they want to get married, Robert.
Yeah, I'd like to get married
so I could have some happiness.
Is there anything wrong with that?
I don't want to talk about this, not here.
Oh, no, wait, wait, wait!
Robert, no, come on back.
Talk to us, tell us.
Pop, a lot happens to a person
when they lose their
spouse, they go into shock.
It's not a good time to be
jumping into something like marriage.
Besides, it's been like not
even a year since mother died.
You were married to mom for 41 years.
You're talking about
us like we're children.
I just think that maybe you
guys don't know what you want.
We want marriage.
What's the matter with you?
Are you always this negative?
Florence, please, I'm not being negative.
It's just, there's a lot
to take into consideration.
I'm being realistic, that's
all I'm being, realistic.
You don't like me.
That's what this is all about.
No, I like you, it has nothing to do
with the fact if I like
you or I don't like you.
It sure as hell does.
Listen, why can't you be honest?
What's the matter with you.
Just say it, talk, tell us.
At least that would be a beginning.
You don't like me!
Yeah, too bad you don't
like her, 'cause I do.
That's good, good, I'm glad you like her,
and I like her too, believe me.
It's just, there's a lot
to take into consideration here.
What's he talking about?
I never know what he's talking about.
What do you have against marriage?
[Robert] Nothing!
It's a very good question, Robert.
I have nothing against
marriage, I know my father.
Pop, mom took care of you for four decades.
Now, the fact that you
can't take care of yourself
and you don't want to be alone
is no reason to run off and get married.
That's enough out of you.
[Robert] Where you goin'?
Gettin' out of here.
Pop.
I thought you had some common sense.
Why do you have to jump into this?
I thought you'd understand.
Why?
How long do you think I'm gonna be around?
I'm trying to protect you, that's all.
Protect me from what?
- From yourself!
- Do me a favor, will ya?
Don't protect me.
I'm just trying to be happy, that's all.
That's what's wrong with you.
You don't care about being happy,
you're a damn coward!
(dog barks)
Can I ask you something?
Do you understand him?
Oh, dear.
Well, to tell you the truth,
I kinda thought it was time
the man tried understanding me, you know?
Understand you, him?
Honey, you've got your
hands full with that one.
Yeah, I know.
Right now he's out
there sitting in his car,
and his father's out there
sweeping up God knows what.
And you know what?
That's how they communicate.
They've known each other all their lives,
and this is the way they
tell each other they care.
Boy, that's kinda scary, isn't it?
Mm, good point.
And you want them to understand us.
(Florence chuckles)
Honey, even if they had the inclination,
they don't have the equipment.
Yeah.
(Susan laughs)
(lighthearted music)
He's sitting in his car.
Yeah, I know.
He used to sit in his room.
Once, he didn't talk to me for two months.
It isn't healthy.
Yeah, some people are like that, I guess.
He's too old to be strange.
You know, it's probably
really none of my business,
maybe he thinks because he's your son
it's his responsibility to speak up.
He sounds stupid with his ideas.
(lighthearted music)
Boy.
They think too much, these kids.
They don't know what they want.
Well, they got too much to pick from.
Well, all I know is I don't
want to be sitting alone
in front of a damn TV set all my life.
Can't he see that?
Well, maybe he likes you there,
he knows where you are.
All he ever knew his whole life
was you with his mother.
It's a price you pay for
being something for so long
and then changing it on him.
You know, what he said might be true.
We hardly know each other,
I wonder if we're doing the right thing.
Ooh.
(somber piano music)
Look, Francis, if you
got any doubts about us,
I'm outta here.
I couldn't take it.
Listen, Florence, I've learned something
in all these years of marriage,
and that is you can't please everybody
at the same time,
even if it's only two of you.
What the hell is that
supposed to mean, huh?
I can take the aggravation,
I just can't stand the quiet!
Well, you'd never have a
moment of quiet with me around.
You don't have to go anywhere,
I know what I want.
April 23rd.
[Florence] What about it?
Well, April 23rd, that's the day
I want us to be married,
if it's okay with you.
It's okay with me, Francis.
Frank.
Please don't call me Francis,
I don't like Francis.
The name is Frank.
Why didn't you ever tell me that before?
I've been calling you
Francis this whole time!
Well, I wanted to try it out.
You said you liked it,
you said it had some,
what did you use, the word class?
Fine.
I don't like it though, I like Frank.
Well, okay!
Why April 23rd?
I looked at the calendar that day,
and there's nothing going on,
so I figured I'd make it special.
You know, it was just an ordinary day
with nothing in it.
Okay, Frank.
Human beings make no
sense at all, me included.
I mean, everybody puts so much importance
on finding somebody and falling in love
and getting married-
- But that's normal.
She doesn't even know him!
She's a total stranger.
I mean, I'm a total stranger to my father,
and he's a stranger to me,
but she's a double stranger.
It's hot.
Robert.
Robert, your father is in love,
he wants this woman in his life.
That's all that's
important to him right now.
Don't you understand, Susan?
Don't you understand what's at stake here?
Marriage puts strangers
together for a lifetime,
I'm just trying to make
some sense out of it all.
You can't make sense out of everything!
You know, I meet you,
and suddenly my life has
totally turned around.
I mean, you're so wonderful, Susan,
and you're so smart,
and when I'm around you, I feel better,
I feel like a better
person, I feel funnier.
Part of me says, you know what?
You should chuck it all, Robert,
you should chuck it all,
go to Wisconsin and marry this girl.
I don't want to get married, Robert.
Another part of me
says whoa, wait a minute.
No, wait a minute, not so fast.
Because think about it, everywhere
you go, she'll be there.
She'll be complaining,
she'll be doing things,
she'll be making those funny
little noises, you know?
You'll slowly drag her into your life,
and she slowly drags you into her life.
It doesn't have to be like that.
In the end, in the
end, if it all works out,
and it does take work,
because everybody says,
"Marriage takes work,
relationships take work."
It's not about caring, it's about enduring.
Seeing who will outlive who,
because at the time, someone
will be standing at the grave,
they'll be looking over that person saying,
"You know what?
I really loved that person,
I cared about that person."
But they didn't realize it
when the person was alive!
Who needs all that?
You have a wonderful
and gentle side, Robert,
and I know you want the best for everybody,
but you're just not ready for all this.
I shouldn't have dragged
you all the way out here, huh?
Robert, you should never get married.
(dramatic music)
Susan.
I hope I see you again.
(dramatic music)
At least you'll never have
to worry about a spot again.
(Frank chuckles)
And the best deli in town
is just a couple of blocks from here,
and it's right next door
to the most fantastic bakery.
Oh!
Yeah.
I go there a lot.
(lighthearted music)
Well, this is it, this is my favorite spot.
What do you think?
Oh, it's okay.
It's a little quiet here.
It's supposed to be, it's a park.
Yeah, but I know a lot of parks
where it's pretty noisy.
(bell tolls)
That's pretty noisy.
There, you got some noise.
Belmont Park, Central Park.
(Florence chuckles)
Oh!
What am I gonna do with you, huh?
Well, Your Honor, it was all like this.
All right, Charlie, listen to this one.
"I'm a Gemini, SWF, I've never been a DF.
I was once an SSWF, but now I'm a non-SSWF.
I love the rain."
(Charlie chuckles)
Kill me, shoot me.
(car honks)
No, no, I'm here, go ahead.
Just say it again.
Right.
That's fine.
No, tell him I said that's fine.
Yeah.
Hi!
Hi, Robert.
Linda!
Robert, hi!
Hi, how are you?
Good, how are you?
I'm good, I'm good, I'm glad you're here.
- Yeah!
- This is good.
Can I buy you a drink?
Oh, no, I'm sorry, I can't.
I'm waiting for my fiance.
It just happened this
weekend, isn't that great?
Yeah!
Well, thank you!
I'm so happy for you!
Hi!
Listen, we have dinner reservations.
Excuse me.
[Bartender] Hey, man.
What will it be?
Can I get a beer, please?
The name's John.
Robert.
How are you?
Ah.
Just came from a singles weekend.
That must've been a horror story.
My friends have been
dying to get me to one.
There's 500 hungry women up there
looking for a good time, they told me.
Yeah?
"A woman away is a woman at play."
Terrific.
I just think the whole thing's depressing.
But I went anyway, and I'm lucky I managed
one conversation with one girl.
Maybe you're trying too hard.
I was engaged just a year ago,
but she met somebody else.
Could you believe that?
Canceled the wedding and everything.
She just married the guy a few weeks ago.
Wow.
Yeah.
I go to a bar, any bar, and I
think I see her in the crowd.
Sometimes a song will come on, and I...
It's okay, bud.
You had a year, why
didn't you go after her,
tell her how you felt?
Yeah.
Thanks for listening.
(jazzy music)
Can I get a vodka martini
instead of this beer, please?
[Bartender] You got it.
Thanks.
[Voicemail] The number you
have reached has been changed.
The new number is...
212-555-0189.
(phone rings)
[Susan] Hello?
[Robert] Susan?
Hi, it's Robert.
Robert!
Hi, how are you?
Hi, I'm good, I'm good.
How are you?
[Susan] Very well, thanks.
I can't believe you're living in New York.
I mean, you are living in New York?
[Susan] Yeah.
Yeah, I can't believe it, that's so wild.
How'd it happen?
Well, I took an offer
from Lamont and Company.
I've only been here few days.
[Robert] Well, it's great.
I mean, it's so great
that you're living here.
I had to get away, you know what I mean.
Yeah, yeah.
Well, maybe we can hang out sometime,
maybe go to dinner or something.
I don't know about that, Robert.
Oh, oh, okay.
Um, then how about lunch?
You know, it would be just really cool,
we just hang out, say hi.
Yeah, yeah.
Sure, sure, that's fine.
How about the day after tomorrow?
That's gonna be bad for me.
No, I'm kidding.
Yeah, okay, yeah, the day
after tomorrow would be good.
How about the Corner Bar?
That's fine.
[Robert] Okay, noon?
Noon is good.
Good.
All right, bye Susan.
How was your meal?
It was all right.
Not as good as your famous shrimp dish.
(Susan chuckles)
You know, I'd love to
cook for you again sometime.
Yeah, we did have fun, didn't we?
I was thinking about that the
other night after you called.
I think about it all the time.
You know what?
That was a fantasy time for me, Robert,
I've said that already.
And I'm really happy that
I experienced it, I am,
but after Ted, and you and me,
I think I really believe that
it has to happen for the right people
at the right time, you know?
That could be us, Susan.
No, when I get involved again,
it's gonna be with someone
who feels the exact same way that I do.
I do.
I feel exactly the way you do.
Robert, forgive me,
but I don't think you know what you want.
We're just not right for
each other, that's all.
Understand?
Okay.
I'd like you all to meet Wendy Ferris.
Wendy joins us from our office in Miami.
Welcome aboard, Wendy.
Thank you.
[Falco] Okay, let's get right to it,
and let's put you under the gun.
You have a report for us this morning?
[Wendy] Yes, you take a look at this?
[Falco] Thanks.
[Frank] They keep it up nice.
Yeah, they do.
You know, I wouldn't change
what I had with your mother for anything.
But if I went first, I would want her
to get on with her life too.
I don't know how you do it, Pop.
Ah, there's nothing brave about it.
Boy, am I nervous.
But I guess at my age
it's good to be nervous about anything.
What about you?
Why do you like being alone?
I don't like being alone.
All right.
Happy birthday, sweetheart.
(lighthearted music)
Who are you taking to the wedding?
I don't know yet.
What about that friend of yours?
That girl from Wisconsin.
Susan?
Yeah, she moved to New York, you know,
she works right down the block.
Then why don't you ask her?
She doesn't want to see me anymore.
Too bad.
She's a nice girl.
(lighthearted music)
How's it going, kids?
Eh?
Having a good time?
What are you doing, Jimmy?
Ah, cooking.
Hey, how's the new car?
It's great, I love it.
I want to sell it and get a Jeep.
We need a Jeep.
Don't you ever think on your own?
You know, I remember when you were a kid.
You had an opinion about
everything, you never shut up.
I'm married now, Pop.
Hurry with the hot dogs!
Right.
Well...
Hey, Pop, you having a good time?
Yeah, I'm having a terrific time.
Pop, we're curious.
What are you gonna do with the house?
We're having a party here, Steven,
what are you asking that for?
The house is all paid for!
Pop won't need it if he's
gonna live in Rosedale.
It's just a question.
Well, I figure I'll sell the house,
put the money in the bank,
or take it to the track.
Good.
What about the furniture?
Steven!
TV, stuff like that.
[Robert] I can't believe you!
[Darlene] It's just a question.
No, no, no, no.
Robert, this is a legitimate question.
It's okay.
Let me tell you something.
When you mother and I got married,
we had a big party just like this one
outside in the backyard, at
her Uncle Charlie's place,
well your grandfather said to me,
"Son, what are your plans?"
I said, "Plans?
I plan to buy a house and raise a family."
Now, those were big plans in those days,
because, you know,
I didn't have two nickels to rub together.
But your mother and I saved
and scrimped for five years.
And we put the down
payment down on a house,
and I'm proud of that!
You should be, Pop.
But what are you gonna do?
You guys want any part of the house?
Fine.
You're gonna fight about it?
Forget it, I'll give it
to the Salvation Army.
Nice party talk.
Uh, Darlene?
Could you help me out here?
I desperately need some fashion advice.
Joy?
I need your opinion too, please.
We've been looking through
all of these magazines.
[Tina] The wedding dresses.
[Florence] The wedding dress here.
We've got this one.
What do you think?
Very nice.
You really think so?
Yes, actually.
I wanted something in magenta, but Tina,
Tina thought this was better, huh?
She's absolutely right.
No way was I gonna let my mother
walk down the aisle wearing purple.
(Florence chuckles)
My baby is so conservative,
she thinks Al Gore is flamboyant.
(Florence laughs)
(lighthearted jazz music)
It was so nice of you
to cook dinner for me.
You're a really good cook.
Oh, thank you.
I usually make everyone sign
a waiver of responsibility
at the front door, but...
Okay.
In Florida, all the executives
are allowed to go casual.
Oh, I like wearing a tie.
Oh, but this one's so boring.
If you want to look really hot,
you should buy one of those
big, flashy ones, you know?
The ones that look like abstract paintings.
I hate those.
Oh, I think they're wild.
You know what, Wendy?
I'm sorry, I should take you back home.
I'm in no rush.
Well, it's just that it's late,
and I have to get up early tomorrow.
Well, what's wrong?
It feels a little weird, you know.
We work together, and I'm not
sure of anything these days,
I think that's the problem.
I'm sorry to put you through with this,
you've been very sweet.
Okay.
- Okay?
- Great.
(lighthearted jazz music)
Hey.
Susan Prescot's in with Falco.
Susan?
- Hi, hi.
- Hi.
- How are you?
I'm well, thanks, how are you?
- I'm good, I'm fine.
- Good, good.
What are you doing here?
I just needed to talk to Falco
about the Burton account,
I wanted to assure him
that weren't any problems
now that I'm at Lamont and Company.
- Oh, that's nice of you.
- Yeah.
Well, I enjoyed working here.
Hey, how was your father's wedding?
Oh, it's this Sunday.
It hasn't happened yet.
Oh, okay.
Well, he must be very excited.
Yeah, he is.
You know, he was kinda hoping
that you were gonna be my date.
Oh, that's very sweet of him.
Do you want to come to
the wedding with me, Susan?
I can't, no.
Susan, you were there when he was alone,
you were there when he told everybody-
- I'm sorry, Robert.
No, I can't.
You know, I wish that
we were meeting each other
today for the first time.
Why?
'Cause things would be different.
Really?
How can you be so sure about that?
Because I'm not the same
person anymore, Susan.
You know, you can't wave a magic wand
and expect everything to be okay, Robert.
It just doesn't work like that.
We were meant to be together,
and I know it in my heart.
You're the right girl for me,
and I'm not gonna let you go that easy.
But-
- Just meet me at my father's on Sunday.
Don't do this, Robert.
Sunday, noon.
I'm not leaving until you get there.
(Robert knocks)
Come on, Pop, come out!
The anticipation is killing me.
[Frank] I can't open the door.
Open the...
Slide the thing, push the thing.
Oh, boy.
Whoa!
Funny lock on there.
Very handsome.
Very nice.
Good, thanks.
You look handsome.
Yeah, sure.
You do.
Very good.
Hey, listen, I've been
thinking about it, Pop,
I want to buy that house from you.
What house?
Your house!
Our house.
What are you gonna do with a house?
Well, why should other
people have the house?
You're gonna sell it, I want to buy it.
Think about it, will ya?
I bought the house for
$12,000, 30 years ago,
from a Mrs. Wanaburg.
She was a widow,
and she wanted to move
in with her daughter.
And now you want to buy
the house away from me.
Now, what are you gonna do,
come home every night alone with a house?
You don't need a house for that, you know.
Sit down.
You gotta stop comparing your life to mine.
I don't do that.
Oh, the hell you aren't.
I made peace with my life a long time ago,
and you better do the same soon.
I know, I used to watch you and mom
watching TV night, after
night, after night.
I thought that's what
marriage was all about.
It scared me.
What I didn't realize
was, seeing contentment,
that you were happy.
Sorry for judging your life, Pop.
It's okay, it's what a kid does.
Let's not forget this day, okay?
All right.
Let's go in.
(lighthearted music)
What do you think, huh?
Oh, Mommy, you look beautiful.
You think so?
I have something for you.
Something old.
Oh, baby!
Aw!
Have I told you lately how much I love you?
I love you too.
(car honks)
(whimsical music)
Oh!
(dog barks)
Pop!
Hey, what happened to 11 o'clock?
Oh, I'm sorry.
I can't seem to get it together today.
How you doin', you all right?
[Frank] Yeah, sure.
Where's Florence?
Florence spent the night at her house.
We thought it right to
spend the night apart
before the wedding.
It's a good idea.
How we doin' on time?
Not very good.
I figured you might be late,
so I asked Florence to
swing by and pick me up.
Oh, Steven and James are
gonna meet us at the church.
Listen, when I move to Rosedale,
you're gonna come and visit me, aren't you?
Of course.
You know, with those other two,
you never know what's happening.
They live a couple of blocks away
and I never see them.
I'll be there, Dad, don't worry about it.
Where's your boutonnire?
You got your boutonnire?
The what?
The bouton...
The flower.
Oh.
You got a flower?
Here, hold on.
You got one for me?
Yeah.
Let me see, turn around.
Here.
You know, I was thinking this morning,
if your mother hadn't gotten sick,
I wouldn't have to worry
about any of this stuff.
Yeah, well, it happened, Pop.
You can't go through life alone, you know?
When I think about that,
I always feel better.
You amaze me, Dad.
Everybody's gotta be some place.
(Frank chuckles)
Hey.
There she is.
Look at her.
Huh?
Let's go get her.
There she is, my future bride.
Isn't she the prettiest girl in the world?
Hi, handsome.
You nervous?
Yeah.
So am I.
- You ready?
- I'm ready.
So am I.
Hi, Florence.
Hi, Robert.
You look beautiful.
Listen, I just want to tell
you that I'm a lucky guy.
I've had my parents in
my life most of my life,
and so I'm a little protective of them,
and especially my mother's memory.
So, I want to say that I'm sorry.
I want to say I'm sorry if
I've said anything stupid,
'cause I know I have, so.
Oh!
Oh, thank you, Robert.
Thank you.
Oh, honey, just remember that life...
Life isn't about losing people,
it's about loving them when they're here
and cherishing them when they're gone.
Right.
Let's go lock up.
You look terrible.
I'm getting married, not you!
I just have to powder my nose real quick.
All right.
Hurry up, sweetheart.
You okay?
[Robert] Mhm.
You know, you're a good looking guy,
you make good money, people
respect you at your job.
But you're the most insecure,
confused wreck of a man
I've seen in 25, maybe 30,000 years.
You sure you're okay?
Yeah, I'm okay.
Good.
You know what?
Your old man is starting
over, wish him luck.
Good luck, Pop.
Okay.
Okay, come on, boys.
Come on, let's go.
I'll meet you guys there.
Come on, come on!
All right, you're the best man, lock up.
See you there!
I think the whole neighborhood is jealous.
First I get a new car,
and then I find somebody.
Even that Peprocki over there.
I let him park in my spot, just once.
Live and let live, I always say.
Thank you!
Yeah, yeah, thanks a lot.
Good luck to ya.
(lighthearted music)
Am I too late?
No.
No, you're just in time.
Well, I thought about it.
I wouldn't miss your father's
wedding for the world.
And it would be nice to spend
the afternoon with you.
But hurry up, I think
I took somebody's spot.
I just gotta lock up first.
Where are my keys?
They were in the door.
(lighthearted music)
Let's get outta here.
Pop's getting married today.
(upbeat wedding music)
(lighthearted jazz music)
(Multicom jingle)