(ethereal music)
- [Frances voiceover] Frances.
Frances Collins.
I've been married five years,
and that still sounds
like someone else's name.
(upbeat rock music)
(eerie music)
- Hi.
Hello, hey.
How you doing?
Good, yeah.
Got a pile over here.
(eerie music)
(intense rock music)
(door slamming)
(eerie music)
- [Frances Voiceover] I'm not scared
of being alone or lonely.
I'm afraid that by being so alone,
I'll forget how to behave,
which leads to really
embarrassing situations
that I don't want to
witness or experience.
(eerie music)
I work at a collection agency.
We have mottoes like let
them hear your smile.
We aren't allowed to use our real names
when we make our calls.
Most of the time, we get
answering machines and voicemail.
It's strange to think of
all those messages of mine.
Floating around different names.
(eerie music)
On my days off, I never go outside.
My husband calls me the agoraphobic freak.
(steady electronic music)
- Thanks.
Good morning, Franny.
- Good morning.
- Hi.
- I've got a new call,
daily calls summary sheet.
- Great.
- And why don't you
work on these accounts first?
These people haven't
been making their calls.
And then work on the batch.
- [Frances] Okay.
- [Frances Voiceover]
My boss is Snow White.
On acid.
- This gentles owes
about 15,000 dollars.
- [Frances Voiceover ] She's one of those
guess my age type people
who succeed in middle management.
- Take these reports.
Some of them are delinquent of course.
Some of have been paid off.
You may want to loosen them out.
- Alright.
- This is really important.
- Absolutely.
- Thank you.
- You just leave 'em.
- And when you're done,
you can just let me know.
- Alright, thank you.
- You're welcome.
(upbeat dance music)
- [Frances Voiceover] This
job is a freak magnet.
It scares me because
out of all the people,
I've worked here the longest.
- Yes, is Mrs. Maloney there?
This is Mrs. Jones calling.
- Hey, you look like you
could use a cup of coffee.
- Oh, thanks.
- [Kate] I didn't know how you took it,
so I just brought it black.
I hope that's okay.
- Oh yeah yeah, I got my
own, my own stash right here.
- I'm Kate.
I just started a couple of weeks ago.
- [Frances] Oh really?
Frances.
- Frances.
She calls you...
- Franny.
Yeah, I hate it.
So where'd you work before this?
- [Kate] Oh, I worked for
another telemarketing, yeah.
- Oh really?
- [Kate] Yeah, it's kinda
different from collections, but...
- [Frances] So how do
you like working here?
- It sucks.
Yeah, I'm just looking for something
better than where I am.
Before I take off.
(laughing)
So are you going away on vacation?
- Oh.
A little nosy there, aren't you?
- [Kate] Well, it's not like
there's anything interesting
going on around here.
Awful day.
- No, I'm just going to take a trip to up,
up, the coast.
- [Kate] It must be
nice this time of year.
- Yeah, yeah, it's sort of...
- Yeah, so how long are you going for?
- [Frances] Oh, just the weekend.
- Oh, well must be nice.
I wish I could go up there.
- [Woman] Thank you, thanks a lot.
- Well I gotta be getting back to work.
Thanks for the coffee.
- [Kate] Yeah no problem.
- Thanks again.
- [Kate] I'll talk to you later?
- Okay, great.
- Okay.
(upbeat dance music)
- [Frances Voiceover]
Sometimes little things
make me want to die.
- Franny.
- Yeah?
- Could you tell me what this is about?
I don't understand this.
- What?
- It's telling them,
did they send in the
check for 197 dollars?
And then it canceled.
What is this?
- I'm not sure.
I think that that check bounced.
- Well you may want to call Mary Parker.
I think it's important.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
- [Frances Voiceover] God,
she is completely psychotic.
(upbeat dance music)
(people chattering)
I hate eating on my lunch break.
I just hate eating alone.
Besides, it's the only
free time I have all day.
Sometimes I pretend I
don't have to go back.
Boston is like this giant
closet full of clothes
you never would wear,
and can't imagine why
you ever bought them.
(muffled jazzy music)
The only thing I've learned
in this city is stillness.
How you can just not move or talk,
and let everything and
everyone happen around you.
(muffled jazzy music)
(people chattering)
(upbeat dance music)
(dinging bell)
- Okay everybody, it's six o'clock.
Time to go home.
I'll see you all bright
and early tomorrow morning.
Thank you very much.
You've all been a great solution.
Why Franny, it's six o'clock.
You can go home now.
- [Frances] Oh yeah, I just want
to finish up on these calls.
- Oh, you're such a great worker.
Thank you very much.
Can I take these?
- Sure, those have all been done.
- Alright, thanks a lot.
- Okay bye bye.
- Bye.
(upbeat dance music)
- Goodnight Franny.
- Goodnight.
(upbeat dance music)
(energetic rockabilly music)
(people chattering)
(gate slamming)
(mellow rock music)
- Do you have a cigarette?
- Sure, how did you know I was a smoker?
- Just a feeling.
Thanks.
- Smoking's bad for you.
- So what?
- So what.
Can I get you a beer?
- Sure, thanks.
I love beer.
- Really?
- I mean, I just started to drink.
- You just started tonight?
- Yeah.
I never was much of a drinker.
But, now I understand why
people do this, everyone.
And cigarettes, too.
I just started smoking today,
and I think I'm already addicted.
- Gee, today's been a big day for ya, huh?
- It sure has.
(laughing)
- I haven't seen you here before.
- Oh yeah?
Well today's my birthday.
- Well, happy birthday.
- Thank you.
- So what's your name?
- Um.
Natasha.
- Natasha?
- Yeah.
- What is that?
- It's Russian.
- Russian, that's different.
- You think so?
- Yeah, I don't think I ever
met a Russian person before.
- Oh well, I'm not really Russian.
Just my parents liked the name Natasha.
What's your name?
- That's a nice name.
Me?
- Yeah.
- Brian.
- So what's a pretty girl like you
being alone on your birthday for?
- It's not like I have any more friends.
- Me neither.
- You neither?
- I don't like any (mumbles) either.
- That's funny.
- So what do you do, Natasha?
Anything special?
- Yeah, I am a...
I'm a stripper.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Well it's not dancer, that's the PC term.
But I don't do it to
support my kid or anything.
- Oh you have a kid?
- No.
I just do it for the fun of it, you know?
- Oh really?
- Uh huh.
- Well I love entertainment.
- Do you?
- Oh yeah.
- Do you ever go to any of those clubs?
- Once in a great while I might pop in.
Maybe I've seen you.
Where do you strip?
- Perhaps.
- Oh, where
do you dance exotically?
I'm sorry.
- You know, downtown.
Maybe we should drink a little bit more.
- [Brian] We can definitely
get a few more beers.
- I think so.
Maybe some shots.
Don't people drink shots?
- [Brian] How about tequila?
- Tequila.
- You can't beat tequila.
- Barkeep, tequila.
- One, two, three.
You didn't finish it all.
- I know I tried.
- Well you did a good job.
- I couldn't do the rest,
I was gonna throw up.
That was good, though.
I want to try something else.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- Whiskey.
Wait, we should toast.
What should we toast to?
- Okay to freedom.
- To freedom.
- To no responsibility.
To fun.
- To fun.
- Is that easy enough?
- To fun and to freedom.
- To fun and wild freedom.
- Drink.
(eerie muffled music)
- Two sambuca.
Por favori.
- Por favor.
- Yeah I speak more than one language.
- Do you really?
- Yeah.
- That's very sexy.
- [Brian] I think that's French.
- Por favor?
It sounds like Spanish.
- Yeah, same thing.
Un.
- Dos, tres.
- How 'bout a beer?
Your beer doing okay?
- I got some left.
- Or you want to do another shot?
- I need a breather.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- I wish we could go dancing.
- Would you like to?
- Yeah.
- We can dance right here, if you want.
I'm not much of a dancer.
- That's it, I'm done.
- Really, you are?
- Yeah.
Let's go sit down over there.
- That's good.
You know they're going to be closing.
We should go.
- We should go?
- Yes.
- But I don't have anywhere to go.
- My place.
- I don't know.
I've never gone to a strange
man's apartment before.
- Now, am I a strange man?
- Yes.
- No.
- You're a stranger.
No, I want to drink this first.
I need to drink this before we go.
If I'm gonna have the guts
to go with you back to your place
I need to drink it.
- Well, maybe we'll accept it.
(laughing)
- I should go back to the office.
That was mine.
- It's out, no more.
(laughing)
Are you, are you okay?
(mumbling)
(rock music)
(upbeat funky music)
(bell dinging)
- [Woman] Okay everybody,
it's six o'clock.
Time to leave.
(energetic rock music)
(eerie squawking)
- [Frances Voiceover] My
sister married this really rich
old guy and told him she
didn't have any family
'cause she's embarrassed
by me and my parents.
She thinks she's Victorian.
Very repressed and proper
but she's really just a bitch.
- What are you doing here?
- I need to talk to you.
- About what?
- Just let me in.
I wanted to ask you if I could stay here
for a couple of days.
- No way, no way.
- You just can't pretend
that I don't exist.
- I have for a number of
years now and it's been okay.
- I slept on the street last night.
I have nowhere to go.
Please.
(ethereal electronic music)
- [Frances Voiceover]
She's got so much stuff
and it's not like I'm
gonna be in her will.
(energetic electronic music)
I've never stolen anything before.
My sister used to, though
but she got caught and stopped.
She used to be really brazen about it.
Like take a jewelry display
right out of the store.
Totally crazy how could she
get away with it, type stuff.
(energetic electronic music)
Thanks for everything, sis.
I wish I could be there to see you explain
all the missing things to your husband.
This calls for a celebration.
(energetic rock music)
- Who put the empty beer
bottle in the fridge?
(clearing throat)
(mystical electronic music)
(playing guitar riff)
(music stops)
What are you doing?
(mumbling) some fucking strange chick.
Well, I don't see the band here.
I see you, me, and some
fucking strange chick
I've never seen before in my life.
This is bullshit!
- Relax.
- Bill, she is not hanging
out with us all day.
- Breakfast with her?
- I'm starving.
Now she's back.
I've been up for like two hours, guys.
(rock music in background)
- I know it must be weird for you
to wake up and see some
strange girl in your apartment
but uh, just slept here,
you know, just passed out.
- You were passed out.
(laughing)
I just put you down on the couch.
- Yeah--
- I don't, I don't even remember
getting home last night.
I was fucked up.
- Yeah, me too.
(laughing)
Your hairs so pretty.
- Thanks.
- [Bill] Was it a typical night for you?
- Well lately but not really.
- Aren't you showing a little
bit too much thigh there?
You cold or something?
- [Frances] No, I don't
know where the rest
of my clothes are.
- I don't think you had any.
- [Frances] I have a coat.
- Maybe you should put it on.
Your, what's your name?
- Uh, Kasey.
Kasey.
- Like and the Sunshine Band?
- Yeah.
- Did I put it on okay?
- [Frances] Oh yeah, it looks really good.
Do you know a lot of bands, then?
- Yeah, well a couple.
One of my exes is from a band.
The Stone Hoagies.
- Really?
- So they do them from home.
- They suck.
(laughing)
- Oh 'cause you guys are awesome.
(rock music in background)
- [Frances] All right,
well I'm starving, so.
- [Man] You're buying, so.
- I'm not buying, Kasey's buying.
- [Bill] I'm getting for breakfast...
(laughing)
- Do you guys know a good place to go?
- [Lisa] Yeah, there's
this real greasy spoon
right down the street called Dominic's.
- [Frances] Oh yeah, cool.
(rock music in background)
So.
(mumbling drowned out by rock music)
No, I'm still fucked up.
I don't know what happened.
(speech drowned out by music)
(ethereal guitar music)
(ethereal rock music)
(energetic rock music)
- [Bill] Let's get out of here.
- Okay, let's go.
- [Frances Voiceover] The
sky was beautiful last night.
Like someone had tripped
and spilled all the stars
and just picked up a few and left.
- We'll see who can come back
with the most phone
numbers from the most guys.
- Wait, why am I getting
their phone numbers?
- 'Cause we're like in a competition.
So we gotta, like whoever comes back
with the most phone numbers
wins the competition.
How am I looking?
- You look good.
- You think so?
- You look fabulous.
- Perfect.
- All right.
- Okay.
- Here we go.
(tense rock music)
(cat howling)
- [Bill] Shit.
(siren in distance)
- What the fuck are you doing?
What is going, what are
you doing in my bed?
- Fucking chill out.
- What the fuck, Kasey?
What are you doing here?
- Lisa--
- Who asked you?
Come on!
- I'm sorry.
- Just fucking relax.
- What do you mean you're sorry?
What the fuck are you doing?
Did you guys sleep together last night?
Did you fuck her?
Did you?
Get the fuck out of here!
How could you fuck my boyfriend?
- [Bill] Get ahold of
yourself, just fucking relax.
- I thought we were friends.
- I'm sorry, Lisa.
Nothing happened.
- What do you mean
you're sorry, you fucking bitch?
Oh my god, did you fuck her?
- Just chill the fuck out.
- [Lisa] What do you mean chill out?
What the fuck happened here?
- Fucking relax.
You're fucking freaking out.
- [Lisa] What the fuck?
What are you doing
here, what are you doing
in my bed with no clothes on?
- Nothing.
- [Lisa] Get the fuck out of here!
- Lisa, just fucking calm down, all right.
- Lisa, we're sorry.
- [Lisa] Don't throw it at
me, you fucking asshole.
- Fucking relax.
- You fucked her, didn't you?
Did you fuck her?
Bastard, I hate you, man.
Fuck you.
Fuck you!
- Chill the fuck out.
Just fucking relax.
Get a fucking ahold of yourself, will ya?
- Don't tell me to relax.
You're gonna fucking be sorry.
(upbeat electronic dance music)
- [Frances Voiceover]
I'm beginning to think
of this office as home.
Scary.
I can do this for a few months.
Then what?
(coughing)
- What the hell is this?
Sweet Jesus.
Are you okay?
- Yeah.
Do you know, um, how do I get out of here
and which way it is to the, um, subway?
I need to get to work.
I have to get to work.
Do you have a light?
Thank you.
- Sure.
- I don't really remember how I got here.
I don't really know what happened, so.
See, I...
I can't go home because,
it's not good there.
I've been getting by on not going home.
I don't know if I can anymore.
Do you live nearby here?
Can we go there now?
I like to get out at night, you know,
because all day long you're
working in an office.
It's very boring.
- [Man] You don't, make
sure, a drinking problem
or anything, do ya?
- A drinking problem?
A problem with drinking?
No, no.
No problem with it.
I just like to drink.
- This door really sticks.
(plates clattering)
Which one would you like?
- This ones fine.
- Okay.
Let me put these away.
I'm sorry, I'm just a
little bit excitable.
I never have people over.
I'm just gonna take my pills.
It's, I suffer from severe anxiety
and uh, and depression.
Um.
This one is um,
it's kind of worn off, it's um.
Klonopin, it's highly addictive.
It's a benzodiazepine and what it does
is it's supposed to block your alphas
and it kind of leave you sterile
and this one is Paxil and I can't remember
what, uh, genre of medication.
It's sort of like the
sister of Prozac drug.
I'm sorry, I'm being weird.
I offered you coffee.
- Oh no, that's all right.
That's fine.
- No.
- Don't worry about it, really.
- No um.
I'm just gonna make some coffee
and um, um.
That's what I'll do.
I'll make some coffee.
(man groaning)
Coffees done.
- Oh great, thank you.
Sure.
- Sugar.
- Yeah.
- Great.
Let me know if it's too strong.
(plates clattering)
You can call in sick if you want.
- Is this phone okay?
- [Man] Yeah, it's a Western
Electric 211 from 1925.
It's um, its a really,
it's a collector's piece.
- Wow.
- [Man] Could you not get any blood on it?
- Oh.
- Thanks.
- Sorry.
(laughing)
Hello, may I speak to Rita, please?
(upbeat dance music)
- Good morning, Rita Jenkins speaking.
- Hi, Rita, it's Frances.
- Oh hi, Franny.
It's 9:30, where are you?
- Yeah, I'm calling in sick.
- But you don't sound sick.
- No, um.
I'm not feeling well today.
Yeah, I'm feeling really really sick.
- I see.
Oh okay.
All right, well then I'll
see you tomorrow morning.
- Okay.
All right, thanks.
Bye.
I think she knows I'm not really sick.
- [Man] Sorry.
(upbeat dance music)
- Yeah.
I think, do you mind if I take a shower?
- No.
The bathrooms right here.
- Thanks.
(upbeat dance music)
(water running)
My bag.
Oh shit.
(upbeat dance music)
(funky industrial music)
- Is Frances here?
She left that at my apartment.
(funky industrial music)
(gasping)
- You don't mind if I sit here?
I'm not bothering you, am I?
I just had to talk to someone, you know.
Just went through an emotional thing.
My husband just died from cancer.
I couldn't stay, I had to leave.
- [Frances] I'm sorry.
- I don't mean to bother
you, I'm really sorry.
- Uh, no, no.
- 'Cause you look like you'd
have your problems, too.
Nothing could be worse than mine,
someone that died.
- Yeah.
- Same thing for you, huh?
- Oh, no, no.
Nothing, I'm fine, really.
I'm sorry about that, your husband.
- I know.
At least he's not
suffering and he just died.
- Geeze.
- It's just hard.
I don't want to go to my
mother's house right now
and my family, just can't cope with them.
I'd rather talk to you even
though I don't know 'ya.
I don't usually sit down and
talk to people I don't know
'cause if you start talking to people
they're gonna think you're
weird but you're not.
They're gonna say, who's that weird lady
with the (mumble) all she
does is walk around talking
to people, but not really.
This is the first time it's like,
I can, like sigh a little.
I'm spilling my guts out,
you know, what's wrong, you
know did something happen
dramatic to you or no just lonely person?
- I'm just tired, that's all.
- Well, you look like
you haven't really slept.
- Yeah, I'm very tired.
- I haven't slept that much
either, since my husband died.
I was over at the hospital
every night, every night.
Hard, you know, seeing
him just thrown away,
getting real skinny.
- Yeah.
- I shouldn't have
bothered you, I'm sorry.
- [Frances] No, it's okay, it's okay.
You're not bothering me.
- No?
- Nah, I got nobody
else to talk to, anyway.
- Do you have a husband?
- Uh yeah, but not really anymore, really.
- No, what happened?
Break up or he's with someone else?
- No, I just left him.
(tense industrial music)
- [Woman] I did it again.
- [Frances] It's okay.
- You know what it is, I'm getting sloshy.
I know, I've been drinking
for a couple of days
so it's like, well once I stop drinking
I'm gonna be sick as a dog.
You're not gonna, uh, take
any of my stuff, are you?
'Cause every time someone comes
they even steal an ashtray.
Or they take home,
as you notice the glass,
the glasses on this.
They take all my nice
ashtrays and my glasses.
But you seem okay.
You won't take my stuff, right?
You don't want my (mumbling).
This was George's chair.
I could never sit in it because it always,
be sitting here watching his stupid TV
but now he's gone, I'm gonna
sit in this chair, you know?
It's my chair now 'cause he's not here.
(tense industrial music)
Oh god, she must of left.
Shit.
Think she left anything?
(tense dance music)
I didn't think she was gonna take it.
She took the whole thing.
Jesus Christ.
She took my glasses and that little thing.
I don't believe it.
This is it, let the
chaos to my house begin.
Shit.
(eerie whistling hiss)
(ethereal electronic music)
(soft dance music)
- [Man] Oh hold on.
Clean it off for a sec.
Just gonna, I'm gonna clean over here.
All right, come on in.
- [Frances] Thanks.
- So.
So.
(mumbling)
Well.
- So, um.
Do you have the money?
- [Man] How much?
I mean what's your, you know,
what are your rates?
Do you have a ballpark figure, you know?
- Well.
I don't know, like $300?
- What's that entail,
what does that include?
What do I get for $300?
Yeah, what do I get?
- Um, um.
I think, just you know, sex?
- [Man] Just sex for $300?
Anal, oral, bondage, games?
I mean, do I get the whole bit?
- Okay, maybe just like $200.
- So anal and the games?
- No, no anal sex.
- No, all right well.
- Maybe--
- I thought, well.
- Look, I just, I just want
to do something, just average.
- Just average?
Average, what's average for,
I mean what do you mean by average?
- Okay, just like $100.
All right, $100.
- $100, okay.
So what does that mean?
Like, what do I get for 100 bucks?
- Well for 100 bucks--
- I mean do you swallow, do you not?
I mean.
- Swallow?
- Yeah.
- I just want to have
old fashioned plain sex.
You know, on my back, you're on top,
let's do it once, with a
condom, and then go to sleep.
- Okay.
- Okay?
That's what I want to do.
- [Man] You shoot dope or anything, heroin
or anything like that?
You're a prostitute.
I mean what I'm supposed
to, I just want to know.
- I don't do anything like that.
- Do you have a john, I mean, a pimp,
anything like that?
- I have no pimp.
- So you're just working on your own?
I mean nobody's gonna crash in
my door in like five minutes
demand more money?
I mean if I give you the
money now, that's it, right?
No surprises later on, no angry boyfriends
or anything like that coming in, right?
I think this is a good deal, right?
- [Frances] I promise there's no pimp.
- Okay.
So, what's your bottom rate and
you said $100 for the night.
What about like half a night?
- Well can I sleep here?
- [Man] Yeah.
- Just plain sex with a
condom and sleeping here.
- [Man] Yeah but sex for half the night.
- And me on lying down.
- But half the night.
I mean you won't even get
on top for a little awhile?
Okay, so it's sex for the
half night, all right?
Then you can sleep here together.
All right.
- That's a deal.
- Okay.
- How bout 50 bucks?
- So, all right.
What about just like 15
minutes of actual sex
and then you can sleep here?
- 15 minutes and sleeping here?
- Yeah.
- Oh okay.
That's good, that's good, that's good.
Okay, less than 50, 35.
- 35, so 35.
- 35, 15 minutes
with a condom, me on the
bottom, and then sleeping.
- Okay, here.
- That's a good deal.
- Yup.
- [Frances] You only got 12 bucks here.
- No.
- That's 12 dollars.
- Shit.
Damn it.
Fuck!
What about...
What will you do for 10?
- 10 bucks?
- [Man] I got an idea.
How much does just talking cost?
- Just talking?
- Yeah.
- Talking and a bottle of whiskey is free.
If you let me sleep here.
- Okay.
- [Frances] Just as
much as you can for $12.
- Okay, any, do you
drugs at all or anything?
- Not really.
I, I--
- I know people.
So, if you'd rather that.
- No, whiskey.
I've never really done this before.
I don't know if you could tell or not
but then you came up
to me and you asked me
and I thought, well hey, well I might
as well give it a try.
- Sorry.
I just hate this thing!
Okay.
Yeah I'm not really, I
don't do this either.
- Really?
You seem so experienced.
There's just a lot of cop shows on TV,
they always got johns.
- Yeah, can I just rest
until you get back?
- Yeah, sure.
Yeah.
So I'll be back in a couple,
you're gonna stay, right?
- Of course.
- Okay.
- Are you ready?
Here we go.
(yawning)
(coughing)
(gasping)
(tense ethereal rockabilly music)
I raise hell every night
With all my friends from town
I drive and I pick them up
Our violence
Knows no bounds
All the cows are all gone
From the meadow
The sheep are all gone
From the fold
The waters all gone
From the wallow
Nothing is left
But the cold
I raise hell
Every night
With all my friends
From town
I drive in
To their house
And we put on our
Violent gowns
All the men are all hungry
And nasty
They never whisper
Just shout
They've all got the worst
Sense of humor
Especially
When we
Pull ours out
I raise hell
Every night
With all my friends
From town
I drive in
And pick them up
Our violence
Knows
Knows no bounds
No bounds