He'll tell him
"Who like God?"
good morning Miss Gutierrez
how are you?
Good morning
I'm great, how are you?
Great
how did you sleep?
What are you making?
Ham and eggs
do you like it?
Of course
did I make it too salty?
It's perfect
don't be silly
well, now you're eating all of it
all of it
hey! no no no!
You can't take this shirt
this is an old shirt
no no this one is new
no let's go
put on an old one for work
you are not going like that
come on
hey man, good morning!
Good morning Leo! what's up!
Why do you get here so late?
Well... I had a huge breakfast
what's going on
breakfast? you're just a lazy ass
let's see when I start working
we'll see who looks lazy!
You said it man
ok then
we'll have some tequila later!
You got it!
I'll see you later!
What's up my Leo
hey
hurry up man
come on
stop busting my balls man
"may God be with you all"
"and with your spirit"
"of the holy gospel"
"according to San Juan"
"glory to you, God"
"among those who had come to Jerusalem"
"to worship god"
"to the easter festivities"
"there were some greeks"
"who came close to Felipe"
"and coming out of Galilia"
"they told him"
"lord, we would like to see Jesus"
"Felipe went to tell Andres"
"Andres and Felipe went to tell Jesus"
"and he responded"
"the time has come for the
song of man to be glorified"
hello!
Whats's up my man
how are you guys?
How is everything going
very good
I'm glad
they tell me you're going to the U.S.
Yes
going north
yes
I'm glad
I finally convinced Emma
and Memo is getting you work
yes he helped me out
I never thought you'd be
a northerner
I didn't either
it's your turn to buy the beers now
I'm expecting it
when?
A week
to where and why so far?
Fresno... with Memo
he has work for me
in the cropfields
ahh... son
things aren't how
how they paint them
money doesn't fall from the sky
and the streets aren't
lined with gold
there is lots of work
you can do well
I won't argue that
but you'll never see your family
you'll never be with them
the americans will suck you dry
here, you want for nothing
this is your town
humble but happy
Emma is pregnant
now everything makes sense
what can I say
only one piece of advice
when you're over there
don't worry about the Americans
worry about the Mexicans with papers
those
those are bastards!
That forgot what it's like
what it means to cross the border
It's sad but true
I'll go for a few years
and come back
that's what they
all say son
that's what they all say
we're passing here
just beyond that is the U.S.
you're going to ask for Javier
just be careful
let's go!
Let's go! run!
Let's go!
The police!
Leo
run!
Go!
Hey!
Don't move!
Where are you going!
Hey! hey!
Come here! come here!
Come over here!
Don't move!
Sir please
shut up!
Shut up!
Where are you going?
Just here
what do you mean here!?
let's see
sir
shut up!
I didn't do anything wrong
what the fuck is this!?
That's all I have!
Please sir!
Nah! nah!
Stop fucking around asshole!
That's all I have left!
Shut the fuck up!
Please sir
let's see what we have here
pick up your shit!
Let's go!
Faster!
Please sir leave her alone!
Please leave us alone
we didn't do anything
shut up!
What's up?
Please that's all
the money we have
please sir!
Goddamit shut up!
Get the hell outta here!
Get your shit!
Get out of here!
Get outta here!
Dirty fucks
bound for Jalisco
board now
let's go!
Shaggy
hurry up!
You're leaving them all
you're leaving all of them!
Don't put your hands
in my lane
you're picking wrong
that's why you're slow
old man!
Come on!
Move faster!
Show him how it's done!
Show these youngsters
how it's done!
Show Leo how it's done!
Too much talking
not enough work
you like all this huh
ok
Now it's time for home work
I know I know
let me see
let's finish what you started
here, what is it?
What are you going to write?
Here
what did your teacher say?
Like
put the words together
ok
And... where do you start?
Dad!
Hello love
how are you?
Good
look
I missed you
I did my homework
oh yeah?
Yes
Olivia
Bobby
Sophia
Leo
how nice
and then a car
she was just waiting for you
Leo
Leo it's time
get up
what time is it?
Don't know
good morning Emma
hello Julia
It's cold
yes
very
well... take care of her
you take care
I love you
my princess
for you
you know
I think I like your's
more than mine
can we exchange?
Poor girl
taste! taste it!
No! no!
No!
I don't want to
I do want something sweet
your lips
my dad
hi dad
what's going on
get in the house
so your getting married fucker
what do you think?
That's good
what plans do you have?
To go north?
I never thought
I'd leave my Jalos
what the fuck
am I doing over there
who knows
but we're going
It's good
for a good future
thank you
to a good future
thanks
I love how you both
came out
cute
thank you!
I loved the picture too
but
cousin when do
get your ring?
That's all you
guys think about
I don't know...
hopefully soon
if he gives it to you
he's taking you north
no no
Leo doesn't like the U.S.
he wants to live
In our town
all our lives
we're happy here
that's what they all say
I'm sure of it
no
No!
Careful
look!
Look! look!
Look mom!
What if we take her out?
You know the answer
why ask me
we haven't been out in weeks
Luciana worries me
Emma things are very dangerous
right now
we can't take that risk
please understand
look mom! look!
Good morning Emma
good morning
hi Luciana
bye
I'm good and you?
What are you doing?
Ok
Bye
come here my love
I need you to go get a kilo
of tortillas
ok mom
I'll be right back
hurry son
tell Mrs. Lucy I'll pay her later
ok
Ok don't take long!
Tired huh
what I most miss is the food
the tortillas taste like paper here
I need some flour tortillas
again!
Luciana was waiting for you
you work all day
we never see you
and now this!
Stop fucking bothering me
I'm getting sick of this
stop!
Should we go far from here?
No
I wouldn't leave Jalos
why do you ask?
Why do I ask
because I want to marry you
I want you to be mine
hello?
At what time?
How is my mom?
No
How?
I can't
what if I get stuck?
If I can't come back soon
what will you do?
Don't worry about that Leo
It's your dad
you have to go
Leo is messing up
come on Leo!
Leo isn't doing his job
never be afraid to cry son
real men cry
daddy! daddy!
Look! Ice cream!
You want an ice cream?
Yes!
Good afternoon
hi
Umm... yes
we wanted an ice cream
Leo let's just go
no daddy!
No!
Come on get up!
Why do you drink so much?
If you're so unhappy
let's go back to Mexico
no one is forcing us to be here
go back for what?
To make no money
I don't want that for us
you don't want that for us?
What is this life?
Alone
closed off
no friends
no family
I was happy with what we had
you wanted this!
You think I want this!
You think I want to deal
with racist bitches!
Like yesterday
huh
huh!
I do it for my daughter
I do it for her and for you
understand it!
We are here in the name of our son Leo
he wants to marry your daughter
and you know what your doing?
Do you know where you're going?
Do you know what marriage represents?
Yes
the highs and the lows
the problems
are you willing your husband anywhere?
Yes of course
you have the example from your mother
she's been a great women at home
I wouldn't expect any less from you
you're willing to make this sacrifices
for your Leo?
Of course
I love him
well what else can I say
then it is so
let's toast
to health
you guys will be fine
you'll see
Leo is a great boy
very responsible
since he was young, hard working
just like his dad
I know
well
can I go look for Leo?
Yes!
Thank you so much
you are welcome
have a great day
thank you
welcome to the family
we can't wait for the grandkids
thank you dad
what are you doing here?
Don't ask, come with me
where are you taking me?
Where is Leo?
You'll see him soon
I am so sick of this!
I can't take it anymore!
Why Leo?
Why God?
Luciana never sees you
you always come home late
drunk
what's wrong?
You can't hear me?
Leo!
Leo
look at me asshole!
If I had somewhere to go!
I would have left already!
This is not a life!
What did you say!
Why do you say that to me!
Huh!
After all the fucking work I do!
Everyday!
For you!
I left my family for you!
I left my town!
For my family, for you!
And you say this to me!
You fucking bitch!
You fucking whore!
Ungrateful!
I followed you
I trusted you
you've become a different person
not a man!
Luciana!
No! no!
No!
We have to go inside!
Get up!
Name of the father
of the son
and the holy spirit
God save you Mary
full of grace
The Lord is with thee
Blessed art thou among women
and blessed is the fruit
of thy womb, Jesus
Holy Mary, Mother of God
pray for us sinners now,
and at the hour of death
you have to go
you have to take her
If people find out
we go to jail
It was an accident
they have to understand
we are illegals here
we are nothing
what do you think will happen to us
you think they'll believe us?
Get up
take her
where?
Where we should have gone
a long time ago
to our town
please
get my daughter out of here
Emma called me
any chance?
Good afternoon honey
my love
I haven't heard from your mother yet
when she arrives
I'll bring her
I miss you everyday
too much
way too much
sometimes I feel like
going with you
but I love your mother
like everyday
I ask your forgiveness
please forgive me
forgive me!
Forgive me my child
Please forgive me!
Please!
Forgive me child!
I want to go with you!
She forgives you
she forgives you
daddy! daddy!
Hi my love
how are you?
I want to see the ocean
yes
of course
I'll take you to the ocean
we'll go all day
we'll sit out in the sun
we'll swim
yes
what do you think?
I want to see my grand parents
and I want to play with my cousins
yes
whatever you want
my child
my darling please forgive me
forgive me