(dramatic music)
- Gentlemen, gentlemen please.
You must take your places.
Gentlemen.
- Ha ha, here's to us before we go
and take that village down below.
- Enough.
Get to your places or
we'll never be on our way.
This is not a time for
drunken celebration.
- Your Grace, we always
celebrate before a raid
and we always drink when we do.
- Shut up, you insect.
This is no game we play.
This painting shall be my legacy,
a record of the beginning
of my reign of greatness.
I think this is my better side.
Shh,
did you hear it?
It's the calm before the storm.
We shall reach down into
that village of weakness
and pull from it that
which will make me the most
powerful man on the earth
The jewel of Polaris.
We shall turn that village
inside out until we find it.
When I have the jewel of
Polaris I will be invincible.
(laughing)
- Your Grace.
I have heard Darbin, the great magician...
- Okay.
- Lives in that village.
He's said to be the most
powerful wizard in all the land.
Are we not to be afraid
of him, Master Falco?
- You dare speak his name in my presence.
For speaking that name
and for doubting my power
your punishment shall
be to never speak again.
- No, no.
- And for any other doubters
now or in the future
the punishment shall be even more severe.
Artist,
a little smaller on the nose I think.
How long we gonna be here?
- Stillness is a virtue, Your Grace,
and patience is its own reward.
- You seem different.
Yesterday you were much taller
and thinner.
Guards,
seize this man.
- It's Darbin.
- You are foolish to challenge me old man.
- The jewel of Polaris.
- You have perpetrated
evil far too long Falco.
I will now send you where
you can do harm to no one.
I send you and your shameless
cohorts into the prison
of this canvas.
- No.
(thunder and lightning)
(coughing)
- I will try to protect you
and all who reside herein
with
the jewel of Polaris.
(animal noises)
(coughing)
(dramatic music)
For so long the jewel of
Polaris has been desired
by evil men.
Please protect this treasure.
Only allow a pure individual,
one worthy of its power
to ever possess it.
- Can't five minutes go by
without you annoying me?
- What's your problem?
- You're my problem you little stain.
- Look, I finished.
- Sorry, but it's raining outside.
- So, go up to your sty.
- Can't, carpet's mean on the blade
and besides dad's up there.
- Of course you never do
anything that might annoy him.
- Why annoy him when I can irritate you?
- You spoiled little brat.
- Toro, toro.
- Get out of here.
- Missed me again.
Face it Kim, you throw like a girl.
- You got that part right,
flat as a pancake brother.
Now are you gonna stop
annoying me or do I need
to get rough?
- Rough, rough, rough,
rough, rough, rough.
- Is there a problem?
- No.
- Good, let's go then.
- You're lucky dad came down when he did.
I had you right where I wanted you.
- Yeah, you wish.
I can't believe I have to babysit you two.
- Who you callin' a baby?
- I'm not a baby.
- I know you're not a baby,
Casey, but you weren't
egging them on were you?
- No, I don't like it when they fight.
I just like the loose change
they drop on the ground.
Cleared 65 cents this time.
- Not too bad.
(gentle music)
Okay, here we are kids.
- Bye dad.
- Bye hon.
The museum closes at eight, don't be late.
- Take care of the kids for me.
- Don't worry dad, everything will be fine
unless Ben drives me to it.
- You don't have your roller
blades in there, do you?
- No way dad.
You know it's against the
rules to skate in the Museum.
Kim would kill me.
Art supplies.
- Art supplies.
- Later dad.
- Okay, here's the deal, freak.
I like my job at the
museum and I wanna keep it.
So, you go do your art report and try not
to embarrass me or get me fired.
Got it?
- Got it.
- Hello Kim.
- Hi Monty.
- Who's your pretty tag along.
- My sister, Casey.
- Nice to meet you Casey, I'm Monty.
- Hi Monty.
- You must be Ben.
Are you the artist in the family?
- The struggling artist.
- Keep practicing.
One day your pictures might
end up on the walls here
at the museum.
- You think so?
- Sure.
- Hey, could we order a pizza?
- Yeah, pizza, pizza.
- We'll see.
As long as you two keep out of trouble.
- Sure, no problem.
- Ben, you need to watch over Casey.
She's your responsibility.
- No way, I got my own plans.
- Ben, I mean it.
- I got my own plans too.
- Ben, you two stick together.
I don't have time to come looking for you.
- All right, all right,
we'll stay together.
Just in case we get separated
we have these walkie talkies.
- Real handful, huh?
Don't worry, I'll check on
'em when I make my rounds.
- Thanks, I'm sure
everything will be fine.
- Bye bye.
- Bye.
(dramatic music)
- The evil Falco depicted in the center
of the painting at right.
Lived in the mid 1600's.
A practitioner of alchemy
and witchcraft, Falco
and his band of outlaws crossed Europe
raiding the countryside
pillaging religious artifacts
believed to bring good fortune.
- Scary looking.
- Everything scares you.
- Look at that one, Ben.
The painter forgot to finish his mouth.
- Freaky looking.
The village painting at the left,
Kaya del Sol was said
to be the last village
raided by Falco before his
mysterious disappearance in 1632.
- Where do you think Falco disappeared to?
- I don't know.
- Got you lookin'.
- You scared the shit outta me.
- Everything scares Ben.
- Speakin' of scary, take a look.
I swear when we first got this painting
Falco's hat was in his other hand.
I figure this painting's haunted.
How about I show you a nicer exhibit?
Probably something more
to your taste, Casey.
What do you say?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, come on.
Now these paintings aren't
as scary as the ones
in the Falco room.
You know, when I just look
at these I get all inspired.
- I like them, too.
- Okay, well look.
I have to finish my rounds
so I'll see you two in a bit.
- Okay, bye Monty.
- Bye bye.
- Yeah, I'm inspired, too.
- Put those on and you're
destined for trouble.
(dramatic music)
(thunder and lightning)
My magician is a good magician.
He can make the storm go away
or make that mean Falco guy reappear,
but as a nice person this time.
He could change anyone into anything.
- Well, he can't turn me
into someone who cares,
now can he?
- You aren't leaving
me alone are you, Ben?
- Sorry C, but I gotta check
out that Falco painting again.
- But, it's haunted Monty said.
- Oooo, the painting's alive, Oooo.
- Quit it, I'm not going back in there.
- You're on your own then.
Testing 123.
Bye baby sister.
The ghosts in the
painting are gonna get me.
Bye.
(dramatic music)
- Coffee break?
- All right, Monty.
Thanks.
Did you find my little migraines?
- Yeah, yeah.
Casey's drawin' away,
but Ben he's already got
to the kingdom of boredom
I'm afraid to say.
- That's usually when he gets
himself in the most trouble.
He always seems to stick
his nose just deep enough
to get it broken off.
- Yeah.
- Or get me in trouble trying.
Maybe I should go and check on him.
I'll be back in five.
- Okay.
(thunder and lightning)
(dramatic music)
- Ben,
Ben,
Ben, where are you?
- Don't be such a baby.
I'll be back in a minute.
- Please save me M.
M the Magnificent, he'll
be able to do anything.
I'll give him a big smile
so he can make people laugh.
(sound of laughter)
(dramatic music)
- Are you lookin' at me?
- Renaissance paintings, who cares?
That one sucks.
Modernism, don't get it.
Hmm, that's cool.
(dramatic music)
Case, you gotta come see this now.
The paintings, they are haunted.
- You can't scare me, Ben.
- I'm serious, Casey.
There's something really
weird going on here.
Whoa, whoa.
- Hello, Ben.
(dramatic music)
(rumbling)
- Oh, ouch.
Where am I?
- Yeah, they're flickering down here.
Okay, ladies and gentlemen,
give us five minutes.
We'll have the lights back on, okay?
- [Ghostly Voice] You comin' or what?
- Yeah, I'm on your way now.
Charlie, it's Monty.
Yes, how's it goin' down there?
(dramatic music)
How we doin' down there?
I've got some uneasy people up here.
- [Ghostly Voice] It's bad,
Monty, but I'll do what I can.
- Yeah, all right.
I'll make the announcement.
- Ben.
Casey.
(dramatic music)
(laughter)
(rumbling)
Oh, oh.
Where are we?
What did you do this time?
- Nothing, what're you lookin' at me for?
- Because you did this.
- I was mindin' my own business.
- I don't know what you did, but
this is the last straw.
You are grounded for life.
- Hey, dad put you in
charge, so if anyone's
gonna be grounded.
- I told you to stay with Casey.
I was working, but did you do that?
No.
- Yeah, but.
- I told you not to touch anything.
But, did you listen?
No.
- Kim.
- You have no sense of
responsibility whatsoever.
- Kim.
- What?
- Do not turn around.
- You there, stop.
- Run Ben.
- Stop.
(dramatic music)
- Whoa, this is too weird.
It's really scary.
(mumbling)
(dramatic music)
- Hello there speed racer.
- I think something bad happened to Ben.
- No, it's just a mean old storm.
Come on, let's go look for him.
- What will we tell Falco
if we can't find him?
- If we find nothing we tell him nothing.
- If these guys don't hurt
you I promise you I will.
- Get a life, come on.
- What's going on?
What's happening?
- I think we're inside the painting.
- What?
- Inside the painting, the
village landscape painting.
At the museum did you see
that painting of Falco?
All the men were gone
and I noticed smoke was comin'
from the village landscape.
Come on.
Those two dudes that were chasing us.
He must be Falco.
He hasn't been around since the 1600's.
I don't know how, but
somehow this painting's alive
and we're inside of it.
- Great, so you've shrunk
us to microscopic size.
Funny, I didn't think your
brain could get any smaller.
- But, I didn't do this, Kim.
When I got to the Falco room the painting
was already smoking.
I didn't do anything.
- Of course, it's always, I didn't do it.
- But, I really didn't.
- I don't care if you didn't do it.
You better undo it because
I want out of here now.
(scream)
- Ben said the pictures were different,
then he started screaming
and that was it.
Look, Monty.
It is different.
All the people are gone.
- I always knew this room was haunted.
- Look Monty,
an earring.
Kim was here, too.
- Looks like it.
Don't worry, Casey.
Everything's gonna be all right.
I'm sure they'll be back soon.
I'm sure they're just tied up somewhere.
- Okay, Monty.
(dramatic music)
- You know, one of us
must have been adopted.
- Very funny.
- I'm serious.
There's no way we both
have the same genes.
- Believe it and weep,
baby, same gene pool
and you're from the shallow end.
- Ahhh.
- Silence child.
What are you doing here?
Think you'll be able to find it here?
Think we, the proud people of this village
would just bow down to
you and let you have it?
- Are you talking to us?
Is he talking to us?
- I don't know.
- Shut your mouths.
You tell Falco we won't
go quietly and we'll never
give up the jewel of Polaris.
- He thinks we're with Falco.
- [Both] We're not with Falco.
- Two of his men were just chasing us.
- We're here by mistake.
- Oh, you did make a mistake
and now you are our prisoners.
Danko, look.
Look at the capture we've made.
We'll be heroes.
- Heroes.
- Listen, little man,
you've got this all wrong.
- My name is Palmay, not little man.
Palmay.
- Okay, Mr. Palmay, like I said.
We're not with Falco.
We're just a couple of
kids that got sucked up
in a painting, okay.
- That's ridiculous.
- Yeah, I know.
Maybe I can prove it to you
in a
a battle of the wits.
- Great, emphasize your weakness.
- Shut up.
But, if I win you have to grand me a wish.
- Which is?
- Put me in the village still tied up
and when Falco's men take me prisoner
instead of releasing me, you'll know
we were telling the truth.
The favor is, you have to let my sister go
and help her get home.
- Are you feeling all right?
- That's my favor to you?
- Yep.
All the proof you need.
- On the contrary,
you've proved it already.
The battle of the wits has
ended before it's begun.
Danko, untie them.
- I'll tell you what.
How 'bout you draw me a picture over here
and I go get us some hot chocolate?
- You won't be gone long will you?
- Back before you know it.
- Okay.
- Yeah, all right.
I'll make the announcement, sure.
Ladies and gentlemen, please bear with us.
We'll have the lights back on
in about five minutes, okay?
- [Ghost Voice] Yo, Monty.
- I'm on my way.
Where are you?
(dramatic music)
- What's this jewel look like?
- It's the most beautiful
jewel anyone has ever seen,
as big as my fist,
a gorgeous emerald,
but its power is much more
impressive than its beauty.
- What can it do?
- It can virtually do
anything its owner commands.
- And that's what Falco's after?
- Yes.
Whoever possesses the
assembled staff with the jewel
in place can rule the world.
One man did,
Lescarus the Evil, whose reign of terror
lasted nearly 100 years.
No one could stop Lescarus,
no one.
And when he was finally
defeated by a gathering
of brave wizards, the leaders of the world
decided to separate the
jewel from the staff,
thereby limiting the collective power.
(dramatic music)
The jewel was hidden in this very village,
home of the last peaceful
warlock who possessed the staff.
If the staff was stolen
a messenger would be sent
in the opposite direction
of the thief therefore,
it became virtually impossible
for the thief to beat
the messenger back to this village
where the jewel was hidden.
(dramatic music)
Two years ago Falco stole the staff.
Luckily we were able to learn of the theft
and prepare for Falco's arrival.
- That's a really cute story, but we need
to get going home.
Dad's expecting dinner at eight.
- Well, if you're from
another world as you claim,
only a magician can get you back.
- You're kidding me, right?
- I wish I were.
Darbin, the great magician, was sent
to thwart Falco's invasion.
That was the last time
we saw either of them.
At first we thought Darbin was successful
as there were no signs of Falco.
Now we know the sad truth.
- Yeah, and so do we.
- So, if Darbin's the only dude in town
that can get rid of Falco,
then we gotta find Darbin.
- Okay.
(dramatic music)
- Look.
- That's Falco with his hooligans.
- Hello, ugly old woman.
You see, there's no need for any violence
or any suffering at all.
There's no reason for faces
to look like this one does.
Simply tell me where the
jewel is and we'll all
simply be on our way and your
good, honest, boring lives
can go on as peacefully as before.
Now, we can't get fairer
than that, can we?
But, if you refuse to tell
me the location of the jewel,
I will make you suffer more than you've
ever suffered before.
Boo.
(laughing)
I understand you fled to the forest
when my men confronted you.
- We were scared.
We don't know anything.
- We were scared (mumbling).
You see, I think that
somewhere in the back
of that tiny mind you do.
Tell me, where is it?
Where's the jewel?
- I swear, Your Grace, we know nothing.
(laughing)
- If you know nothing, then
prepare for the education
of a lifetime.
It's gonna be a lot of fun.
You are now my hunter.
You will neither eat
nor sleep until you find
the jewel of Polaris for me
and with your size I expect you to look
under every rug and beneath every stone.
If you find the jewel
then I may return you
to your normal,
we'll talk.
Take him inside.
And, I suppose you have
nothing to tell me, huh?
It's an epidemic.
This whole village is suffering
from tight lip disease.
Well, I've got the perfect cure.
Give a smile.
Oh, you can't.
- We don't know anything.
Why don't you believe us?
- Because someone here
in this village knows
the whereabouts of this
jewel, because I nearly had
the jewel once and I will not fail again.
Do you know what it feels
like to have something
so close to your grasp,
but not quite reach it?
Do you know that agony?
I can see you're having
difficulty imagining this.
Let me help you empathize.
Can't quite reach it, you see.
Do you feel the madness.
I'm just warming up.
- I want to just slap that man.
- Only Darbin knew where the jewel was.
Now that he's gone
it seems that we're doomed.
- Doomed.
- No way.
All we have to do is find Darbin.
- No, no, no, no, it's
too dangerous out there.
- Well, I'm not waitin'
around here until Falco
finds the jewel.
We have to find Darbin
or some other magician
and we're not gonna find either of 'em
sitting on our butts in here.
- You're just gonna walk
right out that front door?
- No, I'm gonna get my skates first.
I plan on rolling out the front door.
- Not me, I'm not going
back out there again.
- Suit yourself.
- Be careful.
Tell no one we're hidden here, no one.
- No prob.
See you later.
- No prob, see you later.
This is the last time I
let you go off on your own.
I'm not goin' after you this time.
(dramatic music)
- Hey, Matthew, run.
- Come out, come out little one.
- Let's go down here.
Here little boy,
here little girl.
- Dust in this pantry.
(dog barking)
(thunder and lightning)
(screaming)
- Man the gates.
- I've got it down here.
- I want you all to know
that we're not going to leave
until we have the jewel.
Resistance is futile.
Take them to the palace
jail and bring the others.
(dramatic music)
- Wipe out.
- Ben, are you there?
Can you hear me?
Ben, Ben, come on, pick up.
- Hello.
Hello.
Casey?
Yeah, it's me.
- Where are you?
- You're not gonna believe it.
We're inside the painting,
me and Kim both.
You remember that village
landscape painting?
Well, it was smoking and
I touched it and I got
sucked into the painting.
I came out of the haystack.
- Ben, I'm scared.
I want you and Kim to come home now.
- We can't just come back.
- Why not?
- Because I think the passageway
only goes one direction.
- No, it doesn't.
- Listen, I've got a crazy idea.
I think a magician could get us back.
Here's what I want you to do.
- So, without a village
magician how do you ever expect
to beat Falco?
- Only with the power up here,
together with the power down here.
- That sounds great,
but you aren't actually
doing anything up here except for hiding.
That's not exactly an offensive maneuver.
Sooner or later some of
Falco's men are gonna
come banging on that door.
- Open the door.
- I was hoping for that.
(pounding on door)
- Open the door.
(dramatic music)
- Hold on just a sec.
- Okay, now are you in the Falco room yet?
- Yeah, me and Monty both.
- Hey Monty, what's up?
- Ben?
Hey, just sippin' hot chocolate with Case.
- Cool, Case, I know it sounds crazy,
but it's the only thing I got right now.
- How can a picture
turn into a real thing?
- I don't know.
It just can.
Hey, you remember that ad for the pizza
that we were gonna order?
Well, when I came into the
haystack it turned into
a real pizza.
Now Case, look at the Falco painting.
- Yeah.
- No Falco, right?
- Right.
- Now look at the landscape.
It's still smoking, right?
- Right again.
But, I just don't know
if this is gonna work
with one of my pictures.
- Casey, it's all we've got right now.
So, what do you say?
Let's give it a try?
- Okay, Ben, here we go.
You do it.
- Well, how am I supposed
to stick it to the picture?
- Monty's about to put
the picture on the wall.
- Wait, wait, wait, don't put it up yet.
I have to know what he can do first.
- Oh, now you're interested
in what he can do.
You didn't care before, did you?
- Casey, don't give me that right now.
We're in big trouble and I need your help.
- What?
Hello.
Ben, you're not comin' in good.
I'm losing you, Ben.
- Not funny Casey.
- Okay, okay.
Just remember this when I need a favor.
- Anything you want whenever you want it.
- Thank you.
- Now, I want you to clear your mind.
Focus all your energy on the magician.
Try really hard to imagine that he knows
everything about the world I'm in,
and this is the most important part.
Focus very hard.
Imagine that he knows
exactly how we got here
and how we can get back, okay?
Now, stay focused,
open your eyes.
Tell Monty to put the
painting on the wall.
Don't break concentration.
Something will happen.
- It's on the picture,
but nothing happened.
- Something will happen.
(thunder and lightning)
- What do you think, Monty?
- I don't know.
I think it worked.
- Ben, the picture's blank.
Did the magician go through?
Ben, Ben.
- Casey, hello.
Did it work?
Hello, Casey,
are you there?
Great, now what am I gonna do?
(rumbling)
- I wish they'd make these
things more in my size.
Oh, good grief.
Excuse me.
Do you know if there's
a phone around here?
I could really go for some Chinese food.
- Is that you, Monty?
Are you the magician that Casey sent?
- M the Magnificent.
- Public speaker.
- I give inspirational
speeches to company executives,
even some presidents.
I once counseled Lincoln.
I told him that he was takin'
his job way too seriously,
that he needed to get
out and see the yards
and go to the theater I said.
That didn't work out so well.
- And a dancer.
- Yes, a little tap,
but I'm more interested
in interpretative jazz
(making musical noises).
- You think this is funny.
We're in really big trouble here.
- Hey, it's just a joke.
It's not my fault.
Casey's the one that gave
me the sense of humor.
Excuse me.
Yell at her.
- Yeah, you're right.
It's just that I got my sister and myself
in a whole mess of trouble and you're
the only one that can get us out.
- Actually, you're wrong there.
I can't help you.
- Why not?
- You wanna go home, right?
Even I, and don't you tell
anyone this, bad for the rap,
even I'm not powerful enough
to send you back home.
- But, I told Casey to make
you able to send us back home.
- No, no, no, no, no, no.
You said, imagine,
imagine that the magician
knows everything about me
and the world that I'm in.
Imagine that he knows
how we got here and how
we can get back home.
At no time did you say, make him be able
to send us back home.
It's all there in black and white.
Clear as crystal.
Look, only the power of the
assembled staff of Polaris
can send you and your sister back home.
- Oh great.
The staff's in the
possession of the most evil
man on earth who's probably
gonna find the jewel
of Polaris at which point
he'll be the most powerful
man on earth.
Can't get any worse.
- Actually, it does get worse.
Do you remember the big bad
electrical storm back home?
Well, I'm afraid when that storm ends
in the real world
so will the passage for another 100 years.
- A hundred years.
Thanks a lot M.
Casey.
Hello, Casey.
Let's just get my skates and go find Kim.
- I mean, another hundred years.
I know it's a long time.
You might wanna get a hold
of Casey 'cause that's
not my doing.
She always.
- Who goes there?
- What are you lookin' at me for?
You're the magician.
Do something.
- All right, all right,
but I'm a little new at
this so get back, way back.
Voila.
- Pigs, that's the best you could do?
- I'm just warming up.
Give me a little more time.
I'll get better.
(dramatic music)
- Falco's men must have taken Kim.
How am I gonna get her too?
- Sorry.
- Let's recap.
I'm lost in another world.
I've lost my sister who's
either mad and looking for me
or has been kidnapped by Falco
and my only help is a
spastic magical moron.
- Hey, watch it.
I did that pig thing without a hitch.
I could do the same thing to
you if you don't watch it.
(dramatic music)
- Palmay?
What happened?
- Who's that?
- Oh, he's with me, he's.
- M the Magnificent.
- Knock it off.
He's a magician that might be able to get
Kim and me back home.
- You know, I could make your
friend here a little taller.
I can't guarantee he'll
be a center for the NBA,
but with a little magic.
- Shut up.
Where's my sister?
- Falco took her and
Danko to the palace jail.
- Okay, so how do we get into the palace?
- We need to see the village
magistrate who's our leader.
He's currently hiding in the forest.
- Well, what are waiting around here for?
Let's go.
(dramatic music)
- I smell rogues.
We better go this way.
- No, no, no, trust me, this way.
- Halt, halt.
- M, take care of them.
- M, take care of them?
(screaming)
- Losers.
What took you two so long?
- Not bad, M, not bad.
- Keep the faith, keep the faith.
Palmay, where we headed to?
Onward.
(dramatic music)
- When I get my hands on
him I'm gonna kill him.
- Ben, can you hear me?
It's Casey, are you there?
- Hello.
- Hey, Ben.
What happened?
I lost you after the picture went through.
- Hey guys, it's Case.
Oh well, the good news is it
worked and he came through.
- I can't believe it worked.
What's he like?
- He's not too bad, but I
don't think he'll be able
to get us home.
- What's wrong?
- I'm in a great deal of pain.
- Oh, okay.
Well,
let me take a look.
Let's see what we've got here.
- Listen, what's the weather like there?
Is it still storming?
- It's still raining really
bad, but why do you care
about the weather here?
Are you in some kinda denial?
- No, Case.
Apparently, part of the
spell is that Kim and I
have to get back there
before the storm ends
or we won't be able to get back at all.
- You guys have to come back.
You just have to.
Can I talk to Kim?
- Not exactly.
- Not exactly?
- Well, Kim's not here right now.
Actually, she's been kidnapped by Falco.
- What?
- It's not my fault she
wanted to stay in the chapel
instead of comin' with me.
I'm sure she's all right though.
Listen, I gotta go so
I'll talk to you later.
(dramatic music)
- Ah, the mysterious damsel in distress.
- Why am I being held here?
- I'll ask the questions, dear.
- Don't call me dear.
- I'm so sorry.
It was very insensitive of me.
Please.
From the look of your
wardrobe I'd say you're one
of Darbin's sorcerer princesses.
Am I right?
- Who is Darbin?
And, where is my brother?
- Oh yes,
the young boy with the magic feet,
another of Darbin's sorcerer apprentices.
Where is your brother indeed?
It's a very good question
and one I'm glad you asked.
Tell me, where is your brother?
Dear.
- It's not my tongue, M.
It's my foot.
- I knew that, I knew that.
Get ready for eternal foot comfort.
Oh, whoa.
Let me try that again.
- No, no, that's all right.
These feet just needed a rest.
They're feeling much better, thank you.
- No, no, no, no, no, I
can do it, I can do it.
I can do it.
Hokus pokus.
- Wow.
These are wonderful.
They're so light and supportive.
- Yes, they are
They look good, too.
Oh yes.
- Smoke, sparks, yelling.
Oh, you two are doing wonders
for our traveling inconspicuously.
- I'm sorry, Ben.
But, these shoes are wonderful.
- Those boots were killin' his arches.
- They're splendid.
Please keep it down.
Can we go?
- Okay, come, follow me.
- They're splendid.
See if you get a Christmas
present from me this year.
- Palmay,
I was worried.
Where have you been?
- Hiding.
Falco's men have taken Danko.
- Yes, I know.
Falco is making Danko shovel
coal into the palace furnace
day and night.
Even big Danko cannot survive that.
Who are your friends?
- This is Ben and M.
- M the Magnificent.
- You know they saved my life.
- Ah, then they are welcome here.
Please come in.
- Have you got anything to eat?
- M, any chance you can turn
this into a root beer float?
- No.
- Falco's rounded up most
of the villagers by now.
The only way Falco will release
our friends and relatives
is an exchange of the jewel.
We must find it.
- Do you have any idea
where we might find Darbin?
Then we are doomed.
- Hey, I can find Darbin.
- Son, you don't know
the danger out there.
- Are you sure about this?
- If I can find Darbin,
then I can use the jewel
as a bargaining chip to get
Kim back and get us home.
It's a no brainer.
Do we have any other choice?
- All right, I'm in.
But, the jewel alone
will not get you home.
You need the staff, too which Falco has.
How are you gonna pull that off?
- How am I supposed to know?
Makin' this up as I go along.
- You don't actually need to find Darbin,
just the map.
- The map.
- Darbin created a map to the jewel.
When he disappeared the
map disappeared with him.
- Darbin.
I think I know that name from somewhere.
Casey, are you there?
- Yeah, what's happenin'?
- Quick, look at the painting.
Who's the artist?
- It says, A. Darbin.
- So the painting must
be the map to the jewel.
Case, do you see any directions or clues
on the village landscape?
- Yeah, it's by a rock with
all these symbols on it.
It's on a scroll that
says, look under the roads.
- Look under the roads.
Great, thanks Case.
Gotta go, later.
- Under the roads.
- There are so many roads to the village.
How do we know which one?
- Don't look at me, I just work for him.
- Under the roads.
I got it.
It's not under any of
the roads in the village,
but I know where it is.
Come on.
(dramatic music)
- I thought the clue was under a road.
- It is.
Like the clue said, under the roads.
(dramatic music)
Darbin's hidden message.
The great jewel of Polaris
can be found in a pit.
The entrance to the cave
can be found 100 paces
from the great stone in the woods.
- That rock is just a
few moments from here.
- The direction to walk
is that which follows
the afternoon shadow.
Before reaching the jewel
deep in the cave's catacombs
challenges await.
- Darbin never made anything easy.
- Mental, physical and psychological tests
must be overcome in order
to possess the great
jewel of Polaris.
- Wow, awful lotta trouble to go through
just to hide a jewel.
Didn't Darbin know about
safe deposit boxes?
Would've saved him and us
a lot of time and effort.
- For anyone less than the strongest,
the bravest,
and most intelligent mortal
shall never exit the cave alive.
- Leaves me out.
- You gotta give old
Darbin points for drama.
What do you say kid?
- Like I said, no brainer.
- All right, but when you
get home you tell Casey
I want a vacation.
No more battles,
no more death defying challenges.
I want a beach,
a towel,
a Slurpee.
Got it?
- Case, are you there?
- Yeah, what happened?
- I found a map.
- Does that mean you're on your way back?
- No, we still have a
really long ways to go.
What's the weather like there?
- Monty says we haven't got much time.
- All right, all right, I gotta go.
Over and out.
(dramatic music)
- You should find the rock a few minutes
beyond those trees.
The cave entrance should be
somewhere on the other side
of the hill.
- Please, take care of yourself then.
- You, too.
- Palmay, I put steel tips in
those sneakers, so if anybody
gives you any trouble.
You know how to take 'em down.
(laughing)
- Hey, here it is.
Circle of spokes,
two lines and the shadow,
so we should go this way.
- Yeah.
- One, two, three, four, five,
what's the matter?
- Nothing.
- I lost my count.
One, two, three, four, five,
what, what's the problem?
- It's just that you're
not interested in me.
You never asked questions about me.
Where's my family?
Brothers?
Sisters?
What are my hobbies?
Nothing.
- M, I'm sorry, okay.
I've got a lot bigger problems
to deal with right now.
We don't have time for small talk.
Have we not stopped
once since you got here?
No.
Look, as soon as we get
some down time we can chat
and you can tell me your
whole life story, okay?
- Well, I am an only child
from a place called Ishing.
It's like Cleveland only
the weather is better.
My hobbies, well, my hobbies
include, I love synchronized
swimming, playing the dulcimer
and strategic needlepoint.
- M, I just lost my count
again, so if you'll please
help me out here and be quiet?
- I'm all out of quiet,
but I think I can help.
98 paces.
So, the entrance is very close.
- Found the entrance, huh?
- So, are you comin' or what?
- You laugh.
No thank you, no great job M,
just laughing at my expense.
I don't know why I do it.
Come on.
Oh, my back.
(dramatic music)
- This may have been a mistake.
- Yeah, tell him that.
- Can you get this thing to work?
- Now I'm the department of power.
I can tell Casey got all the
imagination in the family.
Here, hold on to that.
Lantern, lantern in my sight,
give us a little light.
Voila.
- Okay, one more time.
After I get the jewel and the
staff, then what do we do?
- We go back to the barnyard
where all this started.
I place the staff into
the haystack and poof,
away you go.
- Cool.
- Maybe cool.
Remember it'll only work
if it's still storming
outside the museum.
Let's go.
(dramatic music)
Let's go this way.
I've been wrong before,
but I have a good feeling
about this way.
(mumbling)
- Hey, check this out.
These stones probably have something to do
with the challenges Darbin wrote about.
What do you think M?
- No question about it, Ben.
- What do you think all these
weird symbols are about?
- I have a feeling we're
going to find out pretty soon.
(dramatic music)
- [Ghostly Voice] Only
intelligent pass in,
thinking freely and able
to use the sixth sense
will know which stone would
come next in the sequence
and therefore, should
be placed in the hole.
- An intelligent person
with a sixth sense?
What's that supposed to mean?
- I think ESP is the sixth sense.
Maybe you should wait til
the stone talks to you.
- The next stone in the sequence.
- I think it's the last one.
It's simple like the first one.
Maybe they're like bookends.
- I don't know M.
Maybe the clue's in the instructions.
- Let me see.
(rumbling)
I don't think I was supposed
to stick my head in the light.
- What are we supposed to do?
I can't leave without the jewel.
- Maybe if you pick the
right stone it'll stop.
- A sixth sense, a sixth sense.
- Come on, come on.
- I don't know.
- Just pick one.
- I got it.
Yeah, a sixth sense.
First stone, no broken lines.
Second stone, one broken line.
Third stone, two broken lines.
Three, four, five, six, a sixth sense.
Thank you, thank you.
- Bravo, bravo.
- No more calls please.
We have a winner.
I'll be signing autographs
out in front of the cave
in a half hour, so please
tip your waitresses
and good night.
- And a good night to you my friend.
- Uh oh.
- What's that?
- Uh oh, what'd I do?
M.
- Align the door.
The door Ben.
- M, M, can you hear me?
- Ben, can you hear me?
- M, can you hear me?
- Go on Ben.
I'll meet you out front.
- Okay.
(dramatic music)
- I'm really gonna do this.
- Case, can you hear me?
- Yep, loud and clear.
- M and I got separated.
What's the weather update?
- It's still thundering,
but it's stopped raining.
Ben, are you okay?
- No, I'm not.
I'm really scared Casey.
- Oh Ben, I wish I was with you.
- Great,
room service.
Compliments to the chef.
I think I ordered the brown slop,
not the green slop.
But, thanks anyway.
(dramatic music)
- [Ghostly Voice] You have
entered the final chamber.
Only a mortal strong of
body and mind shall pass
the ultimate test.
To get to the jewel of
Polaris you must prove
you are worthy
or die trying.
(dramatic music)
- They went in the cave?
- Yes, Your Grace.
- Oh goody.
We've got them.
(dramatic music)
- Benjamin Scotound,
you get me out of here.
- Uh oh, busted.
- I wouldn't do that if I were you.
- Who is that?
- It is I, Darbin and who are you?
A boy who has successfully
reached this room
looking for the jewel
of Polaris, I presume.
- Yeah, my name is Ben
and I'm lookin' for the jewel.
- Do you wish to have it
so you can use its power?
- Yeah, but I'm not gonna use it for evil.
I came from the future with my sister
and we accidentally arrived
the same time as Falco.
- Falco, I banished him to the canvas.
- Yeah, well he escaped.
- Ben, you are not in here by accident.
You were sent here to help stop Falco.
Without you the village and
the world will not survive.
Your future will not exist if
Falco takes over the present.
You must help them.
If you do you will help yourself.
- I just don't know if I can stop Falco.
- Close your eyes.
Open your mind.
Open your heart.
Now open your hand.
The jewel of Polaris
is yours.
- Thanks Darbin.
- I'll take the jewel.
- Where's M?
- Your crazy friend is Falco's prisoner.
He said when he gets his magic wand back
he will turn us all into turkeys.
Give us the jewel now
and we won't kill you
and your friends.
- You want the jewel?
Sure, no problem,
go fetch.
(dramatic music)
- You're okay now Ben.
We've got a plan.
- Your friend has evaded
my men and is in possession
of the jewel.
- He's not my friend, he's my brother
and I don't care what he has.
- Well, I hope he's more
cooperative than you are
because if he doesn't give
me the jewel by sunrise
tomorrow will be your final day.
- Could we eat first?
- Shut up.
(dramatic music)
- Hey buddy.
- Sorry M.
- It's okay.
It had a warranty.
And I still have the receipt.
- Quiet.
You may have bested my
guards, but your friend
and your sister are still my prisoners.
If you give me the jewel
I will not harm them.
In fact, I will set them free.
Now you can't get fairer than that.
- Don't do it Ben.
- Listen to Kim, Ben.
He'll never stick to his word.
- First, set them free.
Then, you can have it.
- Ben, no.
- My pleasure.
- He's good.
- Now, give me the jewel.
- You must promise me you'll
never use it for evil.
- No evil?
You're asking a lot.
All right.
It's a deal.
You.
- No, Ben, no.
- I give you my word.
At last (laughing) foolish child.
Evil is too kinda word for
what I plan to do with you.
Oh I'm glad you find that amusing.
- Lookin' for this?
Or this?
Falco, you're not wanted
here or anywhere else.
I send you and your men
back where you belong,
back into the painting.
- No.
(upbeat music)
- Quiet please, thank you.
That was very nice.
Palmay.
- Thank you magistrate.
We want to thank you Ben
for saving this village.
Please kneel.
We award you with our Medal of Honor.
- Thank you.
I wish I could say my trip was wonderful,
but it's been a little crazy.
First of all, I'd like to thank Palmay.
Although he's a little person
he's got a really big heart.
And finally, I'd like to
thank M the Magnificent.
Without his help we would not be here.
With his guidance it
helped me find the jewel
that will forever protect your village.
M, I'm sorry I lost your wand.
You can say something, but
please leave your cursing out.
It can take a little while
to get used to it, okay.
- Thank you, thank you one and all.
I'm so glad you're here.
It gives me great pleasure to say.
- Casey?
- Absolutely nothing.
- I've got Casey.
- Casey.
- Ben, Falco and his men
are back in the picture.
What did you do?
- We did good, Case, real good.
But, we don't have time to
talk about that right now.
Is it still raining there?
- No, I think the storm is over.
- Listen carefully.
I want you to draw a
picture of a lightning bolt,
a quick one.
Put it on the village landscape.
Do it now and if
everything goes as planned
we'll be home soon.
- You got it.
One lightning bolt comin' up.
- Roger that.
Come on guys, let's go.
Sure hope this works.
- Ben,
thank you again for saving
my life and the village.
I'll make sure that your
memory is never ever forgotten.
- I'll never forget you man.
M, I don't know what to say.
You made it all happen.
Without you I was lost.
- Don't sell yourself short.
You made it happen.
- What happens to you now?
- I become an X-Files episode.
- Cool.
- Now, you be sure to tell
Casey hello for me, okay?
- Okay.
- Now, get the heck outta here.
- Okay, cross your fingers.
Oh, spit it out.
- I send these two into the passageway,
back into the place from where they came.
- Where are those guys?
I don't get it.
Ben, Kim, are you there?
Do you hear me?
(dramatic music)
- Oh.
Oh man, that was one wild ride.
- Casey.
(screams)
- [Ghostly Voice] Go
ahead and do something.
- I guess we can thank M for that huh?
- I could've died.
I'm so glad you guys are back.
- Ben, I'm proud of you.
- You're proud of me?
Did you hit your head?
- Hey, don't push it.
- What's with the jacket?
And the pretty necklace?
- Thanks for watching over
her while we were gone.
- Yeah, thanks a lot Monty.
- My pleasure.
There was no watching over her.
This little lady can take care of herself.
- Hey, it looks like we are
having pizza for dinner tonight.
- Yeah, pizza, pizza.
- [Narrator] Falco met
his match and was finally
defeated in the village down below.
As the legend goes his reign ended
when he was outwitted by a young boy
with the help of a great big magician.
(laughing)
(dramatic music)