That night started
simple enough.
It was a launch party for the video
game "Werewolves Awaken Online."
And I was the lead programmer.
The infamous tech mogul Brian Fenris
brought me in right out of school
and proclaimed me
his star protégé.
The event was the start of a big
marketing push to create some buzz.
Brian wanted me to be the poster
boy, the face of his company.
All the media bigwigs, corporate
honchos and celebrities were there.
I hated crowds,
and I really hated parties.
But I did my job,
and I showed up.
I thought I had everything
under control.
We were in a very different
game that night.
We were the game.
We were the prey
waiting to be slaughtered.
Hey, Padre!
I got a confession for you.
You're dead, August.
August? I said you're dead.
See?
I told you,
I'm not the werewolf.
Totally unaware of what's
really going on.
I'm anxious because I'm about to
face the media any minute now.
Let's get introduced
to the players of the game.
If August isn't the
werewolf, that means...
That's Veronica
in the red dress.
She's Brian's lawyer.
Veronica is a God-fearing
conservative
who has brought her
Bible-thumping husband Luke
and sister Betty to the party.
There's this awkwardness in the way
they communicate with one another,
but I just stayed out of it.
Brian? Brian's the werewolf?
No, I'm not.
The narrator runs the game,
he's never the werewolf.
This is my boss, the creator of the
game and founder of Supermoon Media.
Brian Fenris.
He's as intelligent
as he is eccentric.
The lady that he's with
is Nikki.
She's Brian's assistant
and current fling at the moment.
I thought you'd know the rules to the game
that your wife has been working on, Luke.
Oh, really, Nikki?
So you know who
the werewolf is, then?
It's easy.
It's me.
And me.
And you thought I was the wolf.
Well, darling, anybody could
be hiding as the werewolf.
My husband,
or even my sister.
Besides, you seemed like
you had something to hide.
Yeah, I was hiding the fact
that I knew who the werewolves
were the whole time.
You knew it was Betty and Nikki?
Oh, no.
No, I thought it was you, too.
Everything ready?
You're on, team.
Here we have Remy,
our publicist.
His job is to ensure that Brian's
shenanigans stay out of the headlines.
He's banking
on my squeaky clean image
to deflect the focus around
the allegations against Brian.
Excellent.
So, you get the gist of how
to play the game, Natasia?
Well, on the night turns, the
werewolves choose a player to kill,
and on the day turns, everyone,
including the werewolves,
votes to execute someone
trying to kill the werewolf.
Natasia the blogger.
Brian hired her to do his tell-all
story from his perspective, of course.
It's another strategy
to shift Brian's bad boy image.
But that wasn't the only reason
he hired Natasia.
Paranoid, murderous fun.
Of course, it's usually played
with a larger group than this,
that's why it'll be
such a hit online.
I just can't believe that
August didn't show you the
original playing cards
for your feature.
No, he didn't.
Well, you stick with me, and
I'll get you some great footage.
And a private interview.
All right, let's lead
with the stars of the spot.
Nikki and August...
Where are you, man?
Let's go, August.
- I'll see you later?
- You better.
All right.
Remy, really, is this necessary?
Up front, you're the man
of the hour.
Go, August.
- Awesome gameplay, August.
- Thanks.
- Awesome.
I love you, August.
Dude, that's great.
August, I love the beta.
Cool.
Smile harder, August. Social
engineering takes more than one person.
I prefer software
engineering, Remy.
Yeah, I get that, but I've been branding you
up against Brian's dominant personality.
Is this... honestly,
is this really necessary?
Okay, can you get August
out on stage?
- Yeah, of course.
- Show me your teeth.
All right, folks...
He's not kidding about
Brian's personality.
And I can speak from experience.
God knows, sometimes
I just wanna...
- Hi, Stan.
- Stan?
- How'd you know it was me?
- Stan?!
This is my buddy Stan.
Wet met back in college while he
was working on his fourth degree.
He's the smartest guy you'll ever
meet who believes Big Foot exists.
Although he's much older,
I'm definitely
the responsible one.
But he cracks me up.
And he's the only person
I really trust.
Now I have to go clean this up.
She's a wild one.
But seriously,
how did you know it was me?
Your glee is radiant,
Stanley, radiant.
Yeah, so is your misery,
cupcake.
Hey, you wanna see
something cool?
Where are you reaching to?
Original first edition
werewolf playing cards.
- Do you know how rare these are?
- No.
- Dude, they're rare.
- Okay.
Look, you may not know this, but this...
this is a party for our game.
It's not our game,
we just worked on it, remember?
Sure, Brian's game then.
Well, we're not entirely sure
it's Brian's game either.
Look, I just pick the
winners, all right, August?
I don't make excuses
for the losers.
Well, it's Brian's excuses
in front of a jury
that has Veronica
so worried right now.
So you think he stole it too?
I don't know.
I don't really want to know.
I'm just a bit
overwhelmed right now.
A month ago I'm at work, and
none of us even know each other.
Yeah, good times, buddy.
Then suddenly Brian shows up
with buckets of money
and brings a bunch
of strangers online together
through his social engineering.
So, what's wrong with that?
- You know what I don't get?
- What?
How he introduced himself.
Sends me a Facebook gift.
- He sent you a gift?
- Yeah.
All he did was poke me.
You know what poking means.
I can't sit down,
I can't walk straight.
But seriously, who does this?
After four weeks we're just
gonna launch the game with this?
It's a little much,
don't you think?
Yeah, and on time, too.
Last night of the hunter's moon.
Brian's not gonna miss a
marketing opportunity like that.
God damn it, Stan!
Yann?
What the hell
are you doing here?
Winning you back.
I'm not sure how Yannick
even got into this party.
But everyone at work
had heard about this guy.
Brian would lose it on Nikki
whenever Yannick was brought up.
He's Nikki's ex,
and Brian's a jealous man.
I'm not some goddamn trophy
for you to win, Yannick.
If Brian sees you,
he'll kill you.
Remy, too. Hell,
I should kill you myself.
Uh... Nikki!
Give me one reason why I
shouldn't set security on you
and have your ass
dragged back to France.
And make it a good one.
I want you back, Nikki.
I'm with Brian now.
Really?
Does Brian know this?
We have an understanding.
Well, understand
that I love you.
And I know that you
still love me, too.
Not the way you
speak to me sometimes.
I've gotten help, Nikki.
Real help.
You threatened me, Yannick.
But I never did
any of those things.
Can we just talk?
Take off that stupid suit.
Wait here.
I'll be right back.
With the caliber of stunts
Brian can pull off,
this... this is kind
of... shame.
Agile development, virtual
companies, viral launch parties,
that's how business
is done today.
Welcome to the future.
Yeah, but who are
all these people?
I don't know,
look at this douche bag.
You got the viral video invite:
"An intimate gathering with some
of my most intimate friends."
He always has that
angry look on his face.
Leave it to Brian to mix
viral and intimate.
A surefire recipe for genital
crabs meets genital warts
on a dark and rainy night
of chlamydia.
Enough,
you're taking it too far.
- What, you never had crabs before?
- You always take it too far.
- Listen...
- No, I didn't have crabs.
The way he's dragging
you around tonight,
I wouldn't be surprised
if you get
some intimate friends
of your own tonight.
Boom-chaka-boom-chaka
boom-chaka...
Shut up! You're so loud.
Hey, despite your
miserable attitude,
I think we got a chance with
those two hot skanks over there.
I love a girl with a hat.
- Shh! Shh! She's here.
- Wait, you know those muffins?
- Dude, introduce me.
- No, shut up. Not them.
- Is my breath okay?
- Not them. Her.
Don't look, don't look.
You can't be looking.
Why can't... You point,
what am I supposed to do?
- Stop looking.
- It's hard not to.
You're pointing at her and you're
telling me to look over there.
Plus, she's hot.
How do you know her?
She's that girl that
follows me online.
She's your internet stalker?
Shh!
How'd she get in here?
I invited her.
You invited your internet
stalker to the party?
Well, she's not a stalker.
We've been talking online.
Dude, that takes balls, man.
She's really hot for a stalker.
She's not a stalker.
Yann?
Yann, is that you?
Oh, it's you.
You scared the shit...
You're gonna
have to do that again.
That's a pretty awesome looking
shirt you got going on there.
You gotta be kidding me.
Yeah, yeah.
This job brings out
the worst in you, darling.
And what, pray tell,
is the worst in me?
Intemperance.
"But put on
the Lord Jesus Christ
and make no provisions
for the flesh
to grant its desires."
Romans 13:14.
Oh, we're gonna talk about
resisting desires?
Let's ask Betty to join
in our little discussion
about sins of the flesh.
Shall we?
"And let he who is without sin
cast the first stone."
John 8:7.
Are we quoting scripture?
Because I don't think that our Lord and Savior
would approve of your workplace, Sister.
"Be sober-minded, be watchful.
You adversary, the Devil, prowls
around like a roaring lion,
seeking someone to devour."
Peter 5:8.
Yeah, it's time for
another one, please.
Ladies and Gentlemen...
Okay, shush. Brian's on.
Introducing...
the prankster supreme,
the technology guru,
The CEO of Supermoon Media
and all-around lycanthrophile,
Mr. Brian Fenris.
Thanks, Remy.
Remy Lisel, everyone,
the man who put "social"
in "social engineering."
Let's hear it for Remy.
I think a lot of you know
August, my lead developer
and my code-monkey prodigy,
who, without him,
this game would not be possible.
Let's hear it for August.
For those of you
who don't know me,
I am Brian Fenris.
Well, today
is full circle for me.
Or full moon, if you will.
I started Supermoon Media
by printing
"Werewolves Awaken" card games
in my garage.
But today, thanks to August,
and others,
I can announce the launch of
"Werewolves Awaken Online."
360 interactive on your
browsers, your mobiles.
Each week you can be
one of the villagers
trying to survive,
or you could be the werewolf,
secretly hunting and preying,
and eliminating the other
players one by one.
Ahh!
Stan Bachman, everyone.
Maybe the only man who knows
more about werewolves than I do.
Now, I'm sure we all have
questions for Mr. Fenris.
Would you care to discuss
the ongoing litigation
over the lack of credit to the original
"Werewolves Awaken" co-creator?
We're not here to talk
about that tonight.
Melanie, how can you
get any work done
when you're always
flirting with me?
You know, if you lose your job,
I can't support you,
now that you've migrated from
my bedroom to the newsroom.
Hi!
So...
- So that's how it's gonna be?
- How what's gonna be?
I'm finally here...
in person.
There's no computer screen.
And that is how you're
gonna say hello to me?
Well, I guess you showed how
little all that time meant to you.
What?
Oh, hi.
Hi, I'm Stan.
I'm friends with August.
Hello, Stan.
So, Cheyenne, what do you do?
Turns out she's a cam girl,
I just found out.
- A what?
- She...
I take my clothes off
on the internet for money.
Lots of money.
And I'm not ashamed of it.
- Why were you hiding it from me?
- I wasn't hiding anything from you.
So you just forgot to mention what
you do for months and months on end?
Wait a minute!
Are you Sololady23?
I am.
Toehugger1337.
What?
- Yeah!
- No way.
I didn't recognize you
with your clothes on.
You gotta be kidding me.
That's okay.
And do you know why it's okay?
Because I look amazing naked.
Dude, she looks
so awesome naked.
Yeah, see? It's nothing
to be ashamed of.
I don't think it's bad, I just...
I just... this is just
all really weird right now.
Abomination!
You've brought
an abomination on us all!
This land was ours
before you arrived.
Our honored dead
claimed the land in blood.
It's they you insult,
desecrate with this abomination.
Not again.
How'd he get in here?
I don't know.
Uh, Father...
Don't you "Father" me, young pup.
You helped bring this upon us all.
But, Father, surely my generous
weekly donations to the church...
Cannot buy back your soul for
being part of this den of sinners.
This sin, or any other,
the Lord shall flay
thy wolfish visage.
You have truly marked
yourself for the Beast.
Well, the game keeps
coming alive all night long.
The priest character
is part of the
exclusive expansion pack
that will be a gift to all
my special guests tonight.
Get Argus working on patch
to add that skin
as soon as possible.
All right,
how about some drinks?
How about some champagne?
Weak stunt.
That dude is terrible
casting for a priest.
Okay, I'm gonna check
on this PR guy.
Stan, can you show her around?
Yeah, Toehugger,
that makes sense.
Well, you know,
if you got big toes.
If you got big toes...
- So this is where August works?
- And me.
Brian has us both sequestered
here under his watchful eye.
- So, Brian's pretty controlling, you know?
- I've heard.
And what I'm about to
show you, only he,
August, and I have ever seen.
Whatever you do,
you can't tell Brian,
because if he finds out,
he'll kill me.
Okay.
the panic room!
So, you're saying
these are all real?
Real silver, every one.
Just like the silver bullet
around my neck.
Now, if a real werewolf
ever attacked me,
he better watch out.
As you can see tonight,
I'm all about
genuinely immersive games.
There's nothing I love more
than being inside
a visceral experience.
Really?
Really.
Hey.
Hey, August.
I thought I'd check in
after that whole mess.
Everything okay?
Yeah, Father's just always
like that, fire and brimstone.
Father, as in, the priest.
Right. That dude
was pretty intense, man.
Yeah, no worries. You're
coming to the post-party game?
Uh, actually I was gonna...
That was a statement,
not a question. You're coming.
Bring your date.
My date?
Yeah, the hot babe
that Stan's dragging around.
No, no, no, she's not my date.
Like Stan could ever
get a girl like that.
Anyways, it's good geek chic sex
appeal for Natasia's feature.
Hey, you're August, right?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, you created the game.
Well, Brian did, so.
Oh, the old guy, yeah,
he looks like my dad.
He said you created it.
No, well, I did
the interactive game.
He did the original game, so.
Oh, so he's the money guy.
You know, I have a lot of
really great ideas for games.
We could do one.
That's more of a Brian thing.
But you could
introduce me, right?
I... I guess I could, I mean.
You know, it's a lot
of hard work, coding.
A game engine's
based on a framework
that encompasses
a library of modules
that configure
and manage gooeys...
Gooey? What's a gooey?
Uh, it's not important.
It's fine.
You're funny.
You know, I have a lot
of really great ideas for games.
You should introduce me
to your boss.
Uh...
Tell you what.
I want you to see my gooey.
Um... I... I gotta go.
I-I should... I should really go.
Yeah.
What?
Well, I'm just kind
of with somebody,
you know, so we have a thing...
Okay...
Cheyenne,
you're the... you're the best.
You're the best.
You're the most beautiful,
smart, incredible,
amazing girl I've ever met,
and... Ugh! That's horrible.
That's shit. Come on.
Hello?
I-I wanted us to be honest
with each other. You know?
Like, do your parents even know?
Are they concerned?
That's horrible.
Hey, what's going on back there?
Okay...
I know you, okay?
And if we're together,
you don't have to feel like you
need to do this type of stuff.
Stupid.
Stupid, stupid, stupid.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
Cheyenne, I'm sorry.
Are you taking a number 2?
Ahh!
♪ NO SERVICE
TUESDAY, OCTOBER 27 ♪
Damn it!
It won't work, Melanie.
I'm, uh, jamming all reception.
No livestreaming for you.
And the exclusive
is promised elsewhere.
And I bet I know to whom.
- Now, Melanie.
- Save it. I know how you work.
I did not appreciate
that question earlier.
Get your hands off me.
You can control
the world around you,
but you can't control me.
Or what I know.
Hey, babe. There you are.
Uh, yeah.
Brian, may I introduce
Richard, my trainer.
Boyfriend.
I'm her boyfriend.
Ah.
Nice to meet you, Brian. "Bri."
Richard.
Dick.
Melanie and I were just
discussing an exclusive.
Team members are holding
a private after party,
playing the game
we all love so much.
I can guarantee you
one-on-one time
with each and every one of them.
You can even bring along
your, uh... Dick.
Well... that is great.
Um, fine.
Hugs!
This isn't over.
Have a safe drive.
Take care, man.
Yeah, yeah, thank you.
Appreciate the love, man.
Take care.
Thank you.
If the have-nots ever want
to tear down Brian's empire,
he can hole up here for months.
He's got bed, food,
a urine filtration system
that turns your piss
into drinkable water,
kind of like a flat champagne.
- Really?
- Not that I tried it or anything,
but yeah.
- Does he have any guns?
- No, Brian's not into guns.
Too random for him.
But this? This really
represents Brian.
The latest info,
the latest trends,
it's all in the application.
Watch.
♪ GARAGE ♪
On top of the world
and in complete control.
Gonna go see the hot tub.
What...?
What are you doing?
Don't...
Don't... Get...
Oh! You can't do that!
- Ha!
- Melanie!
Oh, my God.
Hey.
How did you get in here?
Secret back door.
Yeah, Brian's a real-life
Bond villain.
Yeah, actually the launch,
it's winding down in there,
so we're supposed to go
to this after party
and do a few more rounds
for the news piece,
so I was thinking maybe
you should head in soon.
For sure.
So, maybe you can... head in?
Oh, yeah. Oh, of course.
- See you guys in there.
- Yeah.
- Nice guy.
Um, listen,
I'm... I'm sorry about before.
I'm just not so sure
about people anymore.
Yes, you mentioned that.
And I don't think
what you do is bad.
Well, I didn't think
that you would.
I mean, you dated a stripper.
Um... a stripper?
Remember when you told me
that you dated a stripper?
Oh, yeah. That.
- I made that up.
- You made it up?
- Yeah.
- I mean...
you make this big stink
about how I make a living,
and then just go
making up stuff?
I was trying to impress you.
- Oh.
- Let's just... Can we just drop it?
Okay.
The sooner we can get out of
here, then we can just talk.
Really... really talk.
But just for the record,
I was completely aware
that you were lying
about the stripper thing.
It was very ridiculous.
- Mm.
- Okay.
Cool.
Shouldn't we see what those
screams were about?
Nah, that's just how Brian
runs his games.
Bastard always has to take it
to the next level.
He just doesn't know
how to relax.
Are you nearly done?
Just one more thing.
What are you doing?
Causing some real damage.
Now for the fuel line.
Hey!
Ah.
Melanie's question,
Father Roman's outburst...
I don't feel confident.
Do you feel confident?
Is Nikki back?
God!
That's Nikki?
- Oh, my God. No.
- Sweet Jesus.
Go on! Go!
All right, everyone,
let's get inside right now.
Hey, buddy... Who are you, man?
Let's go.
In the house, now.
Okay, just calm down.
Brian? What the hell, man?
I know this piece of shit!
I'd know Yannick anywhere!
- Yannick?
- Shut up, you goddamn murderer!
- I didn't do it!
- You abusive piece of shit!
I loved her!
Like hell!
You fucking killed her!
Everyone is inside
asking questions.
- It's him.
- Is that Yannick?
What does it look like?
Stop, we don't even know
what happened here.
Let's get him up
and call the cops.
And no one touch anything
until the cops get here.
Stan, get him up.
Come on, you don't
need to be here.
Come on.
- Hey, what's going on?
- What is going on?
Who is this?
Did he do that to Nikki?
That's Yannick, Nikki's ex.
He said he found her
a few seconds before we did.
Okay, look, everyone,
obviously something
terrible has happened.
WE don't know exactly
what it is, but...
We're calling the cops and we're
gonna wait here until they come.
They're not coming.
I can't reach them,
the line's dead.
What?
Okay, I'm going out
to the junket box.
August, I want you
to keep everybody here.
Nobody leaves!
Remy, come with.
Wait. Wait, where's Melanie?
Melanie and her guy?
They were walking out the
front door before the screams.
Where did they go?
Two murders, Melanie in shock.
The phone's out,
and we're down to one car.
So we're gonna play this smart.
I'm gonna hold the fort,
you're gonna go for help.
What are you gonna do
about Yannick?
Now don't worry, he's not the killer.
I know that.
He was with us the whole time.
But I wanna see him sweat a bit.
So, I've got the emergency
flares from the panic room.
I want you to take
Stan and your girl
and get out of here.
I can't believe this shit.
We're gonna go to the top
of the hill,
we're gonna try and reach a
signal with the cell phones,
we're gonna call the cops,
you guys just stay inside.
Okay? This shit's fucked!
Guys, I'm really worried about
everyone back at the house
because this is the video game
coming to life.
I don't know who it is, but it's got
to be someone connected to the game.
So, I'm pretty sure
it's a werewolf.
Stan.
I'm sorry, but come on.
Full moon, we're cut off.
And did you see those bodies?
They were shredded.
Is anyone getting a signal?
- Eyes on the road!
- What the hell is that?
She has a gun!
Yeah, I have a gun.
I own guns, I like to shoot guns.
It relaxes me.
Does it have silver bullets?
Can you hear yourself?
Who have I been talking to
this whole time?
Look out!
Oh, God.
Okay, just calm down,
everybody. Calm down.
But the lights are out!
I can see that the lights
are out, Veronica.
Where's your
generator, Brian?
In the shed.
Now just relax, all right?
You can't mean to have us go out
there with a killer on the loose.
Or leave us in here with one.
Relax!
Remy, keep everyone here. I'm gonna
go out to start the generator.
And you're coming with me.
- What...
- Come on, Yannick.
Come on!
Cheyenne? Cheyenne!
Cheyenne? Hey!
Are you okay?
Yeah? Come here.
Holy... Oh-oh-oh!
What's...
- Oh, man.
- Oh, my God.
I don't know what that was,
but we're not far
from the house,
so let's get going.
It just ripped
her whole spine out, man.
- Shut up, Stan.
- That is not a human thing to do.
- Stan, shut up.
- There's no way we're dealing with a regular human here.
Will you listen to yourself?
Is this guy an ordinary killer?
He's not an ordinary guy.
He's a psycho killer.
But, August, what about that thing
you crashed your car trying to avoid?
- Large, furry...
- Deer. Goat.
Werewolf.
Calm down.
- Calm down. You're okay.
- I'm okay?
- You're okay.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah.
- Guys.
This is Yannick's shirt.
We gotta get back now.
Shut it down now!
August!
Remy!
- Damn. You really know how to use that gun.
- Yes, I do.
She's got a gun?
She's got 12.
So, did you guys
bring back help?
We didn't get far
before the crash.
Melanie, she's dead.
- From the crash?
- From the werewolf.
There is no werewolf.
Wait, what?
Melanie's dead,
but not from the accident.
She was murdered.
What the hell happened in here?
I mean, we were attacked.
- By the werewolf?
- Veronica: By the devil!
Brian took Yannick with him to
go and start up the generator
while the rest of us waited.
Our flare was dying.
Remy was about to start
another one when...
that's when it struck.
We could hear it come in.
It knocked out Remy.
My brave Luke tried but failed,
and it made its way
to my sister.
And I always look after
my little sister.
I have seen sin.
So much.
And my sin...
my sin has been suppressing it.
Keeping it all quiet.
Brian's thievery.
My sister
and my husband's infidelity.
And no one is blinder
then she who will not see.
And so God saw fit to take my eyes from
me so that I might see more clearly.
But he did grant me
one more mercy.
The light that
chased away the evil
also showed me its face.
Father Roman spoke the truth.
We are cursed
for what we've done.
God showed me the truth.
Remy, what did you see?
I don't know.
I was out of it.
I don't know what I saw.
Luke?
- It was a demon.
- Luke, seriously?
If Veronica says it was a demon,
it was a demon.
Don't any of you guys get it?
There's a monster here,
all right, but it's only a man.
- Yannick.
- No, it's not Yannick.
Think about it.
Who's still missing?
You don't...
- Brian?
- He's finally lost it.
- It's gotta be Brian.
- But Brian...
I mean, it does make sense.
You all know he's crazy.
But not that kind of crazy.
- No, this is absurd.
- Remy, think through it.
Who's been killed so far?
Brian's ex-girlfriends...
Melanie and Nikki.
And both the guys
they had on the side.
- Yeah, but how?
- Simple.
He starts off with Nikki.
Sets up the body.
Then he comes in
like he hasn't seen her.
Is Nikki back?
Leaving Yannick to find the body
and cause all the suspicion.
Then when he goes to check the phone
lines, he takes care of Richard.
And we were away
for like an hour.
He had plenty of time to leave
with Yannick, take care of him,
finish off Melanie,
then try for you guys.
- But what about what Veronica saw?
- The devil.
Yeah, Stan,
where's your costume?
- Costume?
- That stupid werewolf costume you were scaring everyone with.
- The utility shed.
- The utility shed,
where Brian went with Yannick.
- It's so obvious.
- I don't know, August.
- Why would he do this?
- Because he's a short-tempered,
werewolf-obsessed,
control-freak psychopath, Remy.
Come on, Remy.
It makes sense.
But not with
what we know about him.
We've known him
for like a month, tops.
Maybe...
maybe Brian is a werewolf.
Brian's an insane killer
and we've got one gun.
We've got these.
It's not a goddamn werewolf.
Silver's not gonna help.
Dude, werewolf or not,
you stick the pointy end of
one of these into somebody,
you win.
Grab everything.
Stay.
Turn around, Brian.
It's over.
Step aside, or I swear...
Shut up and lose
the stupid costume, psycho!
- Where's Remy?
- He saw something in the woods and ran off.
Guys, uh, guys.
No, no, no, no!
I want you to know
that Luke and I were so...
so sorry.
- I got 'em!
- Beatrice.
- Yes?
- The curse approaches.
You son of a bitch.
You maniac.
I got him!
Damn it, August.
I knew it had to be him.
It's Yannick.
Remy, damn it.
What are you doing?
He can't possibly be the killer.
There's no way.
- Why the hell not, August?
- He has no motive.
Motive?!
This monster has been abusing
Nikki for the past three years.
Christ!
You'r genious Brian
theory was hanging by a thread
and you dragged us out
in the goddamn darkness for it.
- What? Where's Brian?
- He's dead.
Cheyenne and I found him dead.
- But that doesn't mean Yannick...
- Yes, actually, I think it does mean Yannick.
- Bring me that chair.
- No, no. Remy, listen.
Listen to me. We found these
cards on all the bodies.
What does that tell you?
- That Yannick is a crazy psycho.
- No.
It has to be someone who knows
the game as well as you.
Or you. Or you, Stan.
- Stan, you're hearing me, right?
- I don't know, August.
I mean, we found him naked
in the woods covered in blood.
Classic werewolf M.O.
Bela Lugosi, 1941.
December 12th to be exact.
Even a man who's pure of heart
who says his prayers at night...
Remy...
what are you doing?
What we should've done
a long time ago
when we found
this little monster.
Remy, you don't plan on
killing him in cold blood?
No, I don't.
But Veronica will.
I am the instrument of God.
He is my eyes.
And I am His hand.
Jesus, Remy.
What the hell, man?
This is sick!
By Your will, oh, Lord,
I shall cleanse us
of this curse.
Guide my hand
and restore us unto Your grace.
Nobody goddamn well moves,
you hear me?
- Cheyenne...
- No, August.
- Cheyenne.
- I said no, August!
Hey, I don't know you.
Not really.
You know me like I know you.
I do know you.
I know your dad's
favorite advice to give is,
"You die now,
or you die later."
And if we stick together,
no one else is
gonna die, Cheyenne.
Oh, my God.
It's gonna be okay.
It's gonna be fine.
Murderer!
- Betty!
- Stan: No!
Oh no. Oh no.
Betty... Betty.
No.
Please.
No one else is gonna use it.
Just lay it down on the ground.
Mm. Imported.
Smart man.
Smart but...
not smart enough.
You monkeys never are.
I mean, you build all this...
the cottages, electricity,
the Internets.
You light up the darkness.
And now we talk about
the social media.
Bringing the world together.
How many friends do you have?
Who's following who?
But all you've really done
is digitize
the most basic function of
any successful species...
the tribe.
But you forgot
the most basic function.
To keep the wolves out.
Why?
Why are you doing this?
The only reason...
the hunt.
I mean, sure,
the hunger drives it,
but really the hunt is
its own delicious reason.
The chase.
The herding.
The playing.
That's why.
- How long you been planning this, you sick bastard?
- Plan? No, no, no, August, no.
There's no fun in planning.
But why here?
Why now?
I know what you want.
A reason.
An explanation.
But...
I have already given you
the only reason
that has ever mattered
between species.
Predator...
and prey.
The rest is just natural course.
So what now?
You gonna kill us?
Have you been listening at all?!
The hunt is on.
And for the sport of it,
I am going to give you
a head start.
So...
run!
Whoa.
Betty! Betty!
Come on, come on.
Come on.
Hurry! Come on!
Come on!
I love you.
Come on, you son of a bitch.
No!
No. Oh, no. No.
No. No, no.
Okay.
Okay, okay, okay,
okay, okay, okay.
It's a werewolf.
- So what do we do?
- Stan: What?
What do we do now?
How do we stop it?
- How the hell should I know?
- You're the goddamn werewolf expert.
- It's...
- You always know everything!
- How the hell should I know what to do?
Huh?! Tell me!
What are we supposed to do?
- What the hell do you want me to do?
- Hey! Hey!
August, stop it!
Stop it!
I just really need
your help right now
because I don't think I'm as
prepared as you are to accept this.
- I'm sorry. I'm sorry, bro.
- Sorry.
Seriously, I think
we're safe in here.
- Oh, he's in the shed.
- Maybe we can use something to shore it up.
The shelves.
Oh, yes, excellent, because a few
assemble-it-at-home tables and shelves
are gonna be able to stop a monster that
can smash through a fucking steel door.
Well, it'll slow 'em down
so we can get to the...
Feel better?
I know I do.
Oh, you don't know
how good this feels.
The hunger...
My hunger is gone.
First time in 200 years.
The hunger is gone.
My turn is over.
But the hunt is eternal.
Father taught us that.
Forever and ever,
a hunt without end.
The predator's predator.
Father is still hungry.
Stan: August,
what was he talking about?
It doesn't matter.
- No, we're missing something.
- He was messing with us.
He loved this whole twisted
rampage the whole way through.
No, there's something more
to what he said.
We're missing...
You...
Oh, it's you.
Me.
Oh, Remy.
He so liked playing
with his food.
And I love all my children.
No matter
how childish they may be.
You were so young.
What was the point of
killing my best friend?
Killing all those
innocent people?
For what?
For some high?
I'm afraid I'm too old
and too wise
to play the games
of my young pups.
Oh, well, in that case...
Come on.
Go, go, go!
Here we go again.
How long did Stan say that
that door is gonna last?
Not long enough.
Do we have any silver left?
Lost it all.
Except...
What are you doing?
Brian's silver bullet.
He always wore it.
Where's your gun?
It's by the car outside.
Here's the plan...
I'm gonna use that back door...
gonna grab the gun,
you're gonna load this bullet,
you're gonna shoot him
in the heart.
August...
August, this is crazy.
How do you even know
that this is gonna work?
You can do this.
You die now, or you die later.
Hey, Padre!
I got a confession for you!
August...
August, come on.
I love all of my children.
Cheyenne...
Cheyenne.
You did it.
Die now...
or die later.
No.
No, not now.
Not now, Cheyenne.
Not now.
Stay with me.
My wounds had completely
healed by the morning
and fur started to grow.
I hadn't learned
how to control it yet.
Roman's bite had passed on
the disease.
That night consumes me.
It's my obsession.
I have it in me.
Now, I'm the monster.