And you're sure you
wanna tell me your story?
Yeah.
Okay.
State your name.
Tristan Harris.
Where do you want me to start?
I couldn't say.
It's not my story.
Ahhhh.
Oh, god, the quality.
Vinyl, it's so much
better, don't you think?
You know, they should put
record players in machines,
uh, cars, nowadays it's all
about the digital.
With their iPods, the
cellphones with the Bluetooth.
Just listen.
Listen.
Open up your heart,
chappy, and listen.
There's just so much more
authenticity to vinyl.
Not to mention the joy that
you get from going to the store
and purchasing a
physical vinyl record
to take home and play.
There's nothing
compares to that.
I much more prefer that.
I don't understand why more
people don't prefer that.
What else I don't
understand is all these
different interrogation
techniques.
You've got good cop, bad cop.
Dismemberment, torture.
Too much work, it's like the
expression you Americans say.
To go around your zoopa to
get your elbow.
I could torture you in more ways
than you can pray
against, chappy.
But I don't want to get
blood on this shirt.
My mother gave it to me,
she would kill me.
But you know what
I find, chappy?
I have alternative method.
The key, chappy, is family.
If I get your father,
your daughter, your son,
your mother, or your wife,
then, chappy, then you'd
tell me what I want to know.
Would you like to test
this theory, chappy?
You don't believe
me, let's find out.
Time to spill your guts, chappy.
All right, I'll give
you what you want!
See, chappy?
I rest my case.
I have the information.
The chaplain.
Dah, he is naive.
Dah, dah.
Get them out of
Witness Protection,
and Tristan will come to you.
Tristan.
The man who defied his god in
order to save his daughter.
Look out for him, man.
This is a true gangster.
An outlaw.
Where's my wife and daughter?
My apologies.
Straight to business.
I can respect that.
Your respect isn't worth
the bullet to kill it.
You are an example man.
You learn by
example, do you not?
Depends on what I'm
trying to learn exactly.
Exactly who you
are dealing with.
We were missing you today.
We made a poster.
I love it.
We all really miss you, so we
really want you to come back.
Tell
everybody I miss them, too.
We will.
Bye.
Did you sleep okay last night?
Good, how's your headache?
It feels better
than it did yesterday.
Good, can you open your
eyes and follow my finger?
Does the light hurt
your eyes today?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Let's take a listen.
Okay, deep breath.
Good, does that hurt?
- Mm-mm.
- Good.
Okay, can you sit up for me?
All right.
Good deep breaths.
Good.
Covered back up here.
Hi.
Hey.
Have y'all heard
any results yet?
We have, why don't
we talk in the hall?
She's kinda tired, you
get some sleep, okay?
I'll be right back.
You know we've done
a variety of tests
over the last few days and
the last test that we did
was a CAT scan of her
brain and it shows that
she has a brain tumor
called a glioblastoma.
It's rare in children,
but it is a fairly
aggressive form of cancer.
So we're gonna have to do
surgery or how do you fix this?
She'll need surgery
as soon as possible.
That's her best
chance for survival.
You know...
I never thought any
of this was possible.
That this could happen
to us, to Maggie.
She's 10 years old.
10.
She's got her whole
life left to live.
I just don't
understand any of it.
Any of it, and I know that
we're not the only parents
that this will happen to,
but it's so different.
When it's your kid.
And I wanna have faith.
I really do.
And I'm tryin' to be
so strong for you.
And for Maggie, and
I feel so guilty.
That I'm failin' you as a
husband and her as a father.
You are the strongest man
I know, any mother would be
lucky to have you as a
father for her children.
This is not easy.
It's hard on me, too.
But we cannot lose our faith.
Honey, without faith,
we don't have hope.
- Yeah.
- We have to remain faithful.
Without Maggie, though.
I don't have any faith.
Tristan, if you
lose your faith,
and Maggie sees her
daddy giving up,
how is she supposed
to respond to that?
Maggie's dying.
She's going to die.
You heard that doctor.
That doctor does not decide
her fate, any more than we do.
God does.
I know that you're scared.
And I know that you're
angry, I get it.
Maggie is in the hands
of the great physician.
She is in the best
place she can be.
There's no one more equipped
to make her better than God,
and you have to believe
that, you can't let that go.
You're the man of
this house, honey.
You're gonna be
accountable one day.
I can't fight death!
Our daughter is going to die.
Daddy, why are you
yelling at Momma?
Hey, hey, listen.
It's okay, all right?
Let's go back upstairs.
Hold on, Momma.
Dad, we're going
to be all right.
I'm going to be all right.
You and Momma are
going to be all right.
How do you know that, sweetie?
Because I have faith, Daddy.
Come on,
sweetie, let's go to bed.
Bankers.
I don't understand, I mean,
this is why we have insurance.
I mean, you can't do this.
Well, what if...
Well, what if we get
a second opinion?
What do you mean that there's
nothin' that you can do?
I mean, this is why
we pay you guys.
So when somethin'
like this happens,
that you guys are
there to pay for it.
I'll call you back.
Is everything okay?
It's just an angry
customer, how was school?
Bad.
Why was it bad?
Well, I don't wanna
go to school anymore.
Why don't you wanna
go to school, Maggie?
Just...
I want to spend more
time with you and Momma.
Maggie, I wanna
spend as much time
as I possibly can with you.
I understand, but you
have to go to school.
Just like I have to work.
You gotta make good grades so
that you can get into college,
get a good job, raise a family.
Okay, everything gonna be fine.
We both know that
I'm not gonna make it
into the next grade.
Why do you say that, Maggie?
I'm dying, Dad.
Maggie, don't say that.
We both know that.
I can't do anything about it.
Momma can't do
anything about it.
Maggie.
- I don't wanna die.
- Maggie!
Maggie, you are not gonna die.
You're gonna be fine.
I'm gonna do whatever I have
to do, whatever it takes.
Nothin' is gonna happen to you.
I promise.
Okay?
We are gonna figure this out
and we are gonna get
through this as a family.
Are you sure you're okay?
Yeah, I'm sure.
You're gonna be
fine, I promise, okay?
Okay.
Are you Mr. Johnson?
Yeah, give me one second here.
Go ahead and have a seat.
All right, Mr. Harris, thank
you for coming in today.
I wanted to talk to you
about your insurance.
It appears that you've
already capped out
your insurance policy.
What does that mean?
It looks like when you
originally bought this policy,
you bought it with a tier
one catastrophic event,
which means that we'll
pay up to $25,000 for, um,
medical expenses.
Wait, wait, wait.
A tier one?
Yes, sir.
Yeah, there's
actually three tiers.
Can we just elevate
it to another tier?
Unfortunately it's not the
way the insurance policy works.
Now, this would be considered
a pre-existing condition,
and we're not able to change
your policy at this time to...
Well, rewrite the policy.
Well, unfortunately,
I can't just
rewrite this policy.
Why not?
That's just the way
that these policies
were originally written.
Well, she needs
the operation right now.
I understand, sir.
You keep sayin'
that but I don't feel
like you understand,
do you have kids?
I do have kids.
What would you
do in a situation like this?
Well, unfortunately,
knowing the way the insurance
programs work, I don't
see that there's really
anything you're going to
be able to do right now.
I'm afraid I've done all I
can to help you with this.
Well, I don't
see how you've done that.
Would you like the paperwork
to file a grievance?
Well, sir, that's
really the only option
that we have right now.
You're sure you wanna do this?
What are we gonna do?
I don't like this, either!
This isn't easy for me.
I don't like seein' her sick.
And I certainly don't
like seeing her afraid.
I don't wanna lose my daughter!
I will do whatever I have
to do to take care of her.
There's nothin' to worry about.
I promise you, okay?
I promise you.
You do whatever it takes.
Because she deserves
a fighting chance.
You're sure you wanna do this?
Yes.
It's the only way.
You know there's no goin'
back from this, right?
Yes.
Look.
I don't think you do.
Tristan, this decision
isn't just something
you can walk away
from when you want to.
You go through with this, and
this'll be with you for life.
The only way
you walk away from this,
is to be dead or in jail.
And jail would
just buy you time.
Tristan, these people
don't care about you.
If you're in jail,
they will find you.
Goin' through with this is not
only puttin' yourself at risk
but it's puttin' your
entire family at risk.
My family's already at risk.
Look.
I know why you're doing this.
I understand, but
there has to be a...
You don't
understand anything, kid.
I have no choice.
Every man has to be
his own man, I guess.
Bein' a man
has nothing to do with it.
Then what's it about, then?
This is
about a father's promise
to his daughter.
Is Val coming or not?
Any minute now.
He's bringing
the money, right?
Yeah, he'll have the money.
Last chance, Tristan.
Hand sanitizer.
We can't get this at home.
Russia.
You like to fix things, I hear.
It's how I make a living.
So, why do you need my money?
My daughter, Maggie.
How old is
your daughter, Tristan?
She's 11 and I need the money,
for her operation,
and I'll do whatever
it takes to pay for it.
I'm glad to hear this.
Are you?
Yes, I am.
Mr. Harris.
You know what this is?
That's my daughter's
second chance.
Wrong.
Mr. Harris, this is slavery.
We're all slaves to
something, I guess.
Interesting.
But wrong again.
Mr. Harris.
If you take this money,
I own you.
You belong to me.
You will do everything
that I tell you to do,
when I tell you to do
it, and how to do it.
Mr. Harris, this is not a
one-and-done type of situation
that we have here, this is not
your average part-time job.
If you come to me later and
you say that your daughter
is all better and you no
longer need to work for me,
do you know what I will
do to you, Mr. Harris?
Kill your daughter,
right in front of you.
And then I will kill
your pretty wife.
And then I will kill you.
I'll even kill the family
dog for the cherry on top.
I'm sure the kid came here today
to try to talk you out of this.
Because he knows everything
that I'm telling you
is the truth.
Sometimes, family decisions,
tend to cloud a man's
judgment from right and wrong.
I tell you what I will
do for you, Mr. Harris.
I will give you one hour
to decide whether you
want to take this money.
It does not bother me,
one way or the other.
This is strictly business.
One hour, Mr. Harris.
Kid, you come with me.
One hour, kid.
If he does not take
the money, kill him.
Yes, sir.
Dead.
All right, so let
me get this straight.
Your daughter had
a glioblastoma?
Yeah, but it wasn't
the deadliest of forms.
Is she okay?
We'll get to that.
Okay.
Tell me again, why couldn't
the insurance pay for this?
Because of the type of surgery
that it was, the cost, it
put us outside of our tier or
category, whatever we were in.
Got ya.
So, you and your wife
couldn't afford the surgery.
So, you gotta work for some
gangster and he paid for it?
Yes.
What, you didn't
have any other avenue?
Friends, family, a bank,
I don't know, your church?
Look, we didn't have time
to come up with the money.
As soon as we found out about
the surgery, we had to do it.
Got ya.
So, what happened next?
What you watchin'?
Nothing, I
was trying to research
some new insurance policies.
- Did you find any?
- Seems they'd cover Maggie.
- No.
No, not yet.
Where have you been?
Did, uh, did
Maggie go to school today?
No, she didn't feel up to it.
We just stayed at home and
watched movies all day.
I fixed her some supper.
Did she hold it down?
No, she threw it up.
But I managed to get
her to go to sleep.
Yeah, I saw that,
I just tucked her in.
Turned the light off.
I think half the
problem was the fact
that we didn't know
where you were.
Where were you?
What is that?
Where did you get that?
Is that to us?
Tristan, where did
this come from?
The pastor called
me and told me to come to his
office, so I went to his office
and he gave me that check.
I cannot believe this.
Yeah.
Somebody from the church, I
guess, found out about Maggie
and, uh, they wrote the check.
Who was it?
I don't know, he
didn't say, I guess they just,
they wanted to be
held anonymous.
Tristan, our
prayers are answered.
- Yeah.
- You don't seem so happy.
What's goin' on with you?
No, no, I'm happy.
I'm just havin' a little trouble
wrappin' my head
around it, I guess.
I know.
Oh, my gosh, this just
came out of nowhere.
- Yeah, it did.
- I love you.
I love you, too.
That was convincing,
I love you.
I love you, too.
It's good to see you smile.
Can I call the doctor now?
Yeah.
All right, I'm gonna
go take a shower.
Okay.
All right.
Hi, yes, this
is Alexis Harris.
I'd like to make an appointment
for my daughter, Maggie.
Yes, thank you.
Yes, we can do tomorrow.
Nine o'clock?
Thank you.
Bye bye.
♪ Amazing grace
♪ How sweet the sound
♪ That saved
♪ A wretch
♪ Like me
♪ I once
♪ Was lost
♪ But now
♪ I'm found
♪ Was blind
♪ But now
♪ I see
♪ 'Twas grace
♪ That taught
♪ My heart
♪ To fear
♪ And grace
♪ My fears
♪ Relieved
♪ How precious did
♪ That God appear
♪ The hour
♪ I first believed
♪ When we've been here
♪ Ten thousand years
♪ Bright shining
♪ As the sun
♪ Oh, we'll have no less days
♪ To sing God's praise
♪ Than when
♪ We first begun
♪ Amazing grace
♪ How sweet
♪ The sound
♪ That saved
♪ A wretch
♪ Like me
♪ I once
♪ Was lost
♪ But now
♪ I'm found
♪ I
♪ I do
♪ Believe
- How's it going?
- Not too good, sir.
Take him over
there and plant him down there.
All right.
How long are you gonna
let this man slow us down?
- How do you mean that?
- Like it sounds!
You know they're on our
trail from the river by now.
That's right.
Look, you're
risking the whole bunch.
Why don't you use your
head and leave him here?
He's dying anyway.
You can
leave anytime you want.
I find it rather difficult
with no one to talk to.
Since you also are in the
midst of a personal problem,
well, it seems that, in fact,
it appears at least we
have that in common.
I think we've
enough for a first offense.
You're a saint, I'm a sinner.
Hardly that.
Well, I'm right, you know.
It's an ironical
situation, isn't it?
A mutinous young inspector
leading us all to safety,
if possible, and himself to
execution at the same time.
In that case, I think it's he
and I who have the
most in common.
How do you feel?
Did you eat?
I've no
taste in my mouth for food.
You should've,
you'll feel stronger.
- Leave him alone.
- He needs help.
The more he gets,
the more he's
gonna slow us down.
What're you doin'?
I'm reading a book.
Is that okay?
Why don't you go
read it in the bedroom?
Why would you
say that, Tristan?
I wanna sit here and read it,
I haven't seen you all day.
You're readin' a book
and I'm watchin' TV.
How is that seein'?
Can I just sit in
the same room with you?
I'm not bothering you.
You are, I was enjoying
my space until you came in.
I'm not in your space.
You've got half the couch.
Will you please
turn that down?
If you don't like it,
go read in the bedroom.
It's okay, I like
to read right here.
Can you turn that down, please?
I told you, you
can go read in the bedroom.
Why are you actin' like this?
I told you, I wanted
to be by myself.
You've been
by yourself all day.
And I'd like to continue it.
What's wrong with you?
What's wrong with me
is I wanna be by myself.
Why do you always
wanna be around?
Why, tell me why.
Why don't you
tell me why drinking
has taken over your life?
What is so bad here
that you have to drink...
Because it makes
things tolerable.
And I'm intolerable?
I have done nothing to you.
You have no reason
to treat me this way.
Maybe I don't want you around.
You ever thought about that?
Look at me like that,
cry, I don't care.
I just wanna be left alone.
I was
wondering about something.
You're always
Okay.
So, go read your
book somewhere else.
You've said
enough, I'm leavin'.
Thomas, not very important.
Thomas.
- Anything else?
- Yes.
When I woke up before, the
first thing I thought was
I don't want you to go on
thinking that I killed somebody.
I didn't.
The marshal said you did.
I know,
it's my word against his.
Army sends a patrol.
Go on search every couple
of days for Apaches.
They get as close to here as
four or five miles sometimes.
There's a busted mirror
over by that bar.
Get a hold of it.
Hold it up to the window,
let the sun hit it.
What?
Who is Luke?
Luke?
He's the youth
pastor at our church.
You'd know that, if you came
to church with me and Maggie.
Bull.
What are you implying,
Tristan, that I'm lying to you?
Who's Luke?
Tristan, what're you
doin', I'm not lyin' to you.
Tristan, you're drunk, okay?
We're not gonna have this
conversation right now.
- Yes, we are.
- No, we're not.
Yes, we're having
this conversation now!
Now, answer me!
Answer me!
So help me god, you
better answer me.
Snap out of it!
I have had it with you!
I have had it!
What has happened to you?
I am so tired of having to
deal with your drinking,
and your sarcasm.
I prayed for you
to come back to me,
and I feel like all
I do is pray for you.
What's wrong with you, Tristan?
What's happened to you?
So what do you wanna do,
you just wanna give up?
Oh, no, no, no.
You're telling me
that I'm giving up?
It sounds like it.
I miss you!
I miss the man that I married.
Well, I don't know
how to come back!
I am mentally
exhausted, I'm done.
But Tristan, I will
not stay in this house,
while you think that you have
the liberty to push me around.
While you have your
little binge drinking,
because you don't know
how to deal with life,
and you won't let
me be a part of it.
A divorce? No.
Sometimes, yes, I would love it,
but no, 'cause I'm not
gonna walk away from you,
but I will tell you this,
Maggie will not see this.
She will not be a part of this.
You will not treat me this way
because I do not deserve it!
She will not learn that
it is okay for a man
to treat a woman like this.
And more importantly,
she is not gonna see her
father acting like this.
Right now, I don't
trust you anymore.
It's gone.
And I think it's time for
you to wake up and realize
that if you don't start changing
something now, we are gone.
Because I will not put
my daughter in danger.
Yeah, that's how far
you've let this come.
Parts will be
here On Wednesday, yeah.
Yep.
He will talk to you later.
You have something for me?
You're short, Mr. Harris.
It's all there.
You usually do good work,
the best that I've had.
Don't let it happen again.
Wait a minute.
This wasn't our agreement.
You coming into my
place of business.
I don't want people knowing
that I do business
with people like you.
And who's going to
be looking, Mr. Harris?
You run a mechanic shop.
I drive an old car.
It doesn't matter,
it's the principle.
You got something
to say, Mr. Harris?
I wouldn't.
I've got a very
important job coming up,
that you just volunteered for.
You be here tonight
at eight o'clock.
The kid will be
here to pick you up.
Oh, by the way.
You tell your little
daughter, she's welcome.
So, how are you?
I'm really worried
about Tristan.
Is he still drinking?
Sometimes, I feel like
all he does is stare
at that whisky bottle,
though, with that empty glass.
Well, have you talked
to him about that?
No.
You can't talk to Tristan
about anything right now.
Think he's just
really overwhelmed
with everything
going on with Maggie.
Well, she's doing
better, though, right?
I mean, the treatments
are workin'.
Yeah, yeah.
Gosh, there's not
a day that goes by
that I'm not grateful
for that, I just...
I don't know, it's weird,
it's like he blames himself.
Like he feels guilty about it.
The only thing I know to do,
you just have to pray about it.
Well, I am.
I don't know, I just, I feel
like it's one of those things
that's gonna take time.
Sometimes I feel
like it's too late.
Too late for what?
I don't think any
parent's prepared
to have to deal
with this, you know?
Yeah, I'm sure.
I just have one of
those gut feelings.
I don't know, like somethin'
bad's getting ready to happen?
You can't do that, I mean,
worry and stress is like
the worst thing you can do,
it's not gonna help anything.
I know.
You know, every
morning, I wake up,
and I give Tristan over to God.
And then I try to
go about my day,
and I try not to
worry about him.
And then I end up feeling
like an awful wife later,
because I don't know how
to get him to talk to me.
And then Maggie got sick.
And then ever since then,
I've just been walking
on egg shells, just
waiting for him...
I don't know.
I don't know what
it is, but he acts
like he's just gotta fight
this thing on his own.
Like it's him against the world
and he doesn't even see me.
It's like he looks
straight through me.
He doesn't know
that I'm right here.
But I don't even know if
I'm a right fit for him.
You're a great wife and
I know that God put you
and Tristan together
for a reason.
And whatever that reason
is, I know it's a good one.
I mean, the important thing is
that Maggie's
gonna be just fine.
And Tristan's gonna
come around, I mean,
maybe it's a man thing
or somethin' that he,
he feels like he can't
protect his family
or somethin' like that, but
everything's gonna be just fine.
I promise.
I hope so.
It will be.
I hope you're right.
I don't understand why
you think you have a choice.
We always have
a choice, Jacob.
Somebody in your shoes?
They don't have a choice.
Look.
Your daughter's
recoverin', right?
Yes.
Okay, then do you want
everything you've done
up to this point
to be for nothing?
If you're tryin' to
tell me somethin', Jacob,
then just say it.
Imagine Val puttin'
her down permanently.
Alongside your wife,
I mean, I don't know
if you just don't believe what
Val is capable of, or not.
I know who Val is and I know
exactly what he's capable of.
Roughin' people up and
collecting money is one thing,
but robbin' a church is
something completely different,
and I will not be a part of it.
I can't be a part of it.
Man, I know you did not wanna
get caught up in all this,
and I admire what you're
tryin' to do, Tristan.
Look, you do this one job,
and I'm gonna get
you out all this.
How can you say that?
We both know that's not a
capability that you have.
Things aren't
always as they seem.
You're gonna trust
me on this one.
And why should I trust you?
I'm gonna pick you up
here, Sunday mornin'.
Tristan, just remember this.
When the hand reaches out
to pull you back, grab it.
♪ If He knows when a robin
♪ Falls from its nest
♪ And He grieves
when He sees it die ♪
♪ If He kisses the rose
♪ With the morning mist
♪ How much more does
He love you and I ♪
♪ If He cares for the lily
♪ Of an open field
♪ And caresses the petals
♪ With dew
♪ If He acknowledges a tree
♪ When the wind makes it kneel
♪ How much more does
He love me and you ♪
♪ If He'll take out the time
♪ To turn a desert
from its dry ♪
♪ And He'll carve out a river
♪ To the sea
♪ Just to give a little fish
♪ Another place he can live
♪ How much more does
He love you and me ♪
♪ If He has made a place
♪ For all that has been
♪ I've been told and I believe
♪ It's true
♪ He's preparing me a place
♪ That I can not comprehend
♪ That's how much that
He really loves me ♪
♪ How much more than
a fragrant rose ♪
♪ That he gives
life in the spring ♪
♪ For does he love me less
You know, I'm
supposed to trust you.
That was the deal.
But then you go and kidnap
an innocent little girl.
How am I supposed to
trust you after that?
If nobody's cooperating,
what else am I supposed to do?
I don't know,
yell, or somethin'.
But you don't kidnap an
innocent little girl.
That was not a part of the plan.
I'm in charge here!
You're not in
charge of anything,
and you need to get that
through your thick skull.
Because when Val gets here,
you know exactly what he's
gonna do to that little girl.
Exactly.
But I'm supposed to
trust you, right?
Right?
Listen!
No, you listen to me.
I am tired of people
gettin' hurt on my watch.
It's time we play by my rules,
now give me your pistol.
Turn around.
You did this to yourself.
Let's go.
Listen to me.
I'm not gonna hurt you.
Do you understand?
Just get me outta here.
You gotta do
exactly what I say, understand?
- Yes.
- Let's go.
Stop.
Turn around.
You know why you're here, right?
I guess we have
business to talk about,
that you didn't want
anybody else hearing?
- Something like that.
- Really?
- I think you know, Jacob.
- Know what?
That you should probably
give up being a mechanic?
I know that you're
an informant, Jacob.
- I see.
- I have no choice.
You might wanna rethink that.
We both know you're
not a killer.
And we both know that you're
not gonna pull that trigger.
Think about Maggie.
This isn't you, Tristan.
Tristan, I'm a cop.
See?
You're not a killer.
You're just a father tryin'
to save his daughter.
If I untie
you, can you show a badge?
Turn around.
I've been undercover
for four years now.
- But you're just a kid.
- I'm 23, Tristan.
But that's exactly
how I got this job.
See, no one suspects a
kid to be undercover.
Where does this leave me now?
The thing
you don't understand,
is Val is connected all
the way up the ladder.
I need enough to
through life at him,
so he will give up
these other people.
Five, even 10 years, doesn't
matter to these guys.
My family cannot find
out what I've done.
You're not hearin' me.
If you help me, I can get
those charges dropped.
And you and your family
will walk away from this.
How will they be protected?
We will put all of y'all
in Witness Protection.
And that's a promise.
So, what's the plan?
You are late.
No, do not makes
excuses with me.
It is your responsibility to
make sure that he goes nowhere.
You know the location, I
will see you there tomorrow.
Jesus, dude.
Did you kill anybody?
I didn't kill anybody.
Just tune people up and
collected, that's it.
All right, so your daughter's
surgery was a success.
But you couldn't get out from
under this Val Drexel guy?
And he has you goin' around
town doin' all these odd jobs,
and in the midst of all
this, you kidnap some kid?
And this set you off, so
you're gonna go kill Jacob,
but you didn't...
Look, I didn't know
what I was gonna do.
I didn't, I didn't know if I
was gonna kill Jacob or not,
I just knew that I could not
be a part of this anymore.
Couldn't do it anymore.
But the only way that
I could get out of it
was to help Jacob take Val out.
Wow.
So, what happened next?
Val, everything's
under control.
Everything is not
all right for you, kid.
Where am I?
Alexis?
Maggie?
Maggie!
Tristan.
My son.
Daddy?
All of us must die eventually.
Our lives are like water,
spilled out on the ground.
It can't be gathered
back up again.
I don't understand.
Where am I?
Where you're supposed to be.
I don't
understand what's going on.
You don't need to.
But God just
does not sweep life away.
Instead, he provides us
ways to bring us back.
Until you've been
separated from him.
Tristan, my son.
My work cannot be
destroyed as I cannot be.
Everyone will come to know
me in this life or after.
Just as you're being judged,
everyone will be judged when
this day comes for them.
I knew you before you were.
It's finished, Dad.
It's time to come back.
It's time.
Don't be afraid.
Be strong and courageous.
Don't be terrified of this.
For the Lord, your God
walks by your side.
And I've always
had faith in you,
even when you didn't in me.
He will never leave you.
I created you
with a purpose, Tristan.
He will never forsake you.
Now...
Come back, Daddy.
Go and fulfill your purpose.
And do it with faith and love.
As I created you to do.
Because you are forgiven.
Wait a minute.
So, you're telling me
you were clinically dead?
Yes, I was.
And during this time is
when you claim you saw God
during all this?
I'm not claiming anything.
But I know what I saw.
And what I felt.
Okay.
All right, I'll bite.
So, what did God tell you?
That I wasn't
fulfilling my purpose.
- What's your purpose?
- I don't know.
Hm.
What about this
church you robbed?
I think I remember reading
something about that.
"For if you forgive
men their trespasses,
"your heavenly father
will also forgive you.
"But if you do not forgive
men their trespasses,
"neither will your
father forget your"...
Dad?
Yes, sweetheart?
I overheard your
conversation with Mom today.
What've I told you
about eavesdropping?
I know, Dad, it's just that...
Nevermind.
No, come on, what is it?
Well, I was just
curious about Mr. Harris.
What about him, what're
you curious about?
What's gonna happen to him?
What do you mean?
Did he go to heaven?
Or hell?
Well, I hope he went
to heaven, sweetheart.
What do you think will
happen with him and God?
That's between
God and Mr. Harris.
God knows his heart
better than anybody,
and it's up to him to judge
his fate, it's not up to us.
But won't God forgive him?
Why do you ask that?
Because God forgives
all his children.
Right?
Of he does.
So, everybody at the
church will, too, right?
I don't know about
that, sweetheart.
So, what do you
think I should do?
About what, Dad?
About Mr. Harris.
Do you think we should
all forgive him?
If God's forgiven Mr.
Harris, why can't you?
But do you think
he deserves to be forgiven
after everything that he's done?
He done nothing to us,
but everything to God.
That's why God is
the judge and not us.
I can't believe we're
still discussing this.
A man robs a church and now
we're thinking
about forgiving him?
I understand that,
but I still feel we
need to pray about it!
What do we even
need to pray about?
What did Jesus do when the
traitors were in his house?
He kicked them out.
I agree.
That's not the way it went.
They were not his children,
they were lost and of the world!
And I think we still
need to remember here
that Tristan is a child of God.
Amen.
I think he's just a
man who's lost his way.
How do we even know that?
We don't!
He's probably in hell.
I mean...
How can a child of
God rob a church?
I don't understand why we're
still having this discussion!
That's what we've been
trying to get across to you.
No, what I meant was, what
are we really afraid of?
To forgive him?
Of what comes next!
I don't follow you, Burgess.
All right, let me
paint you a picture.
A man robs a church,
the church forgives him.
Every criminal around
the country would be
kicking in the
doors of churches,
and what would that
have for public opinion?
That we condone the
criminals and their actions?
Can't you see?
We don't argue.
We never argue.
All the years that I've
been on this council,
we don't argue.
Lucifer is trying to allow
himself into this church
because of the crimes
of Mr. Harris's.
Now, I am sorry, Pastor,
but there's just no way
that we could forgive Tristan.
I admire that you've got
this council together
to make sure that we do it
right, but there's no way.
Does it matter
what they think?
You should only care
what God thinks.
Pray to him and he
will answer you.
This could be an
opportunity for the church
to show the world God's
compassion for his children.
And maybe help bring
the lost to light.
Sir?
You okay?
Pastor.
Yes, I'm fine.
So, what'd you
guys think about the movie?
- It was great.
- It was scary.
It was?
What about when that guy popped
out from behind the rock,
was it a little scary?
Enough.
That was so much fun, wasn't it?
Yep.
Can we get some money
to play video games?
Yeah, I think
that's all right.
Here you go.
- Sorry.
- It's okay.
How're you doin'?
Let's take a seat for a moment.
Ever since we talked yesterday,
you've been on my heart.
And what you shared,
that was an amazing tale.
But I don't really know
what you need from me.
I just need advice 'cause
I don't know what to do.
I don't have the
answers this time.
Are you sure that God
hasn't already revealed it?
If he has, I don't
know what it is.
Are you listening,
truly listening?
Always.
Because I think he
has spoken to you.
It's like your daughter said.
This is an amazing opportunity.
But when I think of the
word one, unity comes to mind.
I believe, with all my heart,
that if a group of people
could stand together as one,
we can change the world for
the betterment of it all.
And we tell ourselves we
just need to pray about it,
but sometimes before we do
that, we have to ask ourselves,
what exactly do we
do when we pray?
And right now,
we're just talking.
Just talking.
But are we listening?
'Cause if we're not
listening, we're not watching,
and if we're not watching,
how in the world can we see
the opportunity
that lies before us?
Excuse me, Pastor, I
think I speak for all of us
when I say, what are
you talking about?
I'm talking about the
opportunity that lies at hand,
Mr. Burgess, I
don't think you see
the magnitude of the situation.
And I don't think you see
the gravity of this situation.
If you don't get this
right, there's gonna be
a lot of people that
walk out the front door.
And Pastor, you have to
look for a new church home.
What's wrong, sweetheart?
It's just, the more I think
about it, I just wonder,
what if they tell us to leave?
Then we find a new home.
- It's not that simple, Ruth.
- Isn't it?
No, it's not.
Why not?
See? It is that simple.
What does your heart tell you?
That we forgive this man.
Well, maybe I'm just
playing devil's advocate here,
but they're not gonna understand
why the church
should forgive him.
I don't care how smooth
you lay it over to them.
You have to remember, they're
not meant to understand.
They're meant to be led.
So, lead them, show
them the endgame.
And it doesn't matter
if they ask you
to leave the church or not.
Your home isn't the church.
Your home is in the constant
presence of God Almighty.
And whatever God asks you
to do, you do, period.
And it sounds to me like
God is asking you to lead
these people and show the
world what it's forgotten.
I understand the hard
road's never the easiest,
or the most popular,
and I understand that.
But by the same token I am your
pastor and I am your leader,
and we will forgive this man,
as God has forgiven
the rest of us.
And maybe in the meantime
we'll even teach the world what
it's forgotten, whether that
be forgiveness or compassion.
But until then, we
will forgive this man,
for every single child of
God deserves to be forgiven.
All right, well, time out.
You're telling me the
church just forgave you?
The pastor did, but I
went and talked to him,
and I explained everything and
we understand each other now.
And the church is just
okay with this stuff?
You show up, you sing a song,
you put money in the offering
plate, or you take it.
The pastor and I had
a good conversation and
that's all you need to know.
All right, is
that the end of it?
Not quite.
Elaborate.
After the shootout,
Val Drexel escaped,
and no one
could seem to find him.
How did he do that?
It's Val Drexel, I don't know.
Hm, conspiracy.
I see.
What happened then?
Lord.
I'm not much of a prayer guy.
I know I need to be.
I'm gonna try my best.
And Lord, you know my history
and where I come from.
And I didn't grow up with you,
but I'm glad I've found you.
Even though you've been there
along the way, waiting for me.
But Lord...
I'm strugglin'.
I'm tryin' so hard
to follow you.
But this man, this man has
my family and I'm afraid.
I'm afraid to lose them, knowin'
I could've done somethin'.
As much as I don't wanna
sacrifice my faith,
I don't wanna sacrifice
my family for it.
So, I need your help.
I need your help.
I don't wanna be
violent anymore.
I just need my family back.
Please, God.
Please, please.
Please.
I need my family back.
With Val Drexel in the wind,
Jacob did uphold his
end of the bargain,
and he put my family
into Witness Protection.
And you didn't join them?
No.
I couldn't, it...
It was just more dangerous
for my family if I was there,
so I stayed somewhere separate,
I thought that it would be safe.
But I was wrong.
This, this guy, Sergei,
he came outta nowhere.
He somehow figured out
where my family was hiding
in Witness Protection
and he kidnapped 'em,
in order to get
me to come to him,
and do whatever he
needed me to do.
So, what did he
want with your family?
Where's my wife and daughter?
My apologies.
Then tell me
where they're at or not.
Straight to business.
I can respect that.
Your respect isn't worth
the bullet to kill it.
You are an example man.
You learn by
example, do you not?
Depends on what I'm
trying to learn exactly.
Exactly who you
are dealing with.
Wade.
Come here.
Tell me.
How long have you
worked with me?
Seven years.
Hm, seven years.
That is a long time.
Take Wade, for example.
He worked for me for seven
years, and in the end,
was only worth
making example of.
What're you trying to tell me?
That I want Val
Drexel brought here,
or else your wife and daughter
will be my next examples.
And how am I
supposed to do that?
Find a way.
If you weren't my only
option, you wouldn't be here.
So, this guy, Sergei, he's
holding your family hostage
until you deliver Val to him?
Yes.
But I thought you just
said no one could find him?
He found me.
Did you go see him?
It's been very
long time, Tristan.
Yeah, it has.
You are probably
asking yourself,
why this place?
Isn't this where
one comes to deal
with their issues from the past?
Why now, Tristan?
Why you find me now?
I need your help.
Interesting.
What in the world could you
possibly need with this old,
broken down Russian?
So, did you take
Val to Sergei?
No.
But what about your family?
Look, the thing you
need to understand about Val
is why he does what he does.
Okay.
Tell me.
It was about 10 years
ago in Minsk, Belarus.
Val Drexel was actually
an undercover cop, okay?
And he was investigating
Sergei's crime family.
Sergei didn't know
this, but one day,
Val Drexel's little
daughter gets killed,
and it was Sergei that
did it, but he didn't know
that this little girl was
Val Drexel's daughter,
but even still, he
was in enough trouble,
so he had to flee the country.
When he fled the country Val
Drexel followed him, came here.
But his undercover stuff was
still intact and he had to do
whatever he had to do
to get closer to Sergei.
So, that's why Val had
to keep this mobster cover.
But yet, he somehow wound
up on Jacob's radar anyway.
Exactly.
So, Val used you.
No.
We used each other.
I don't know.
This all seems so
incriminating if I publish it.
Look, look, look, don't
worry about my immunity.
I've got that taken care of.
What do you want me
to do with this story?
I don't know,
I'm not the writer.
I just wanna know why
I'm being told about this.
Look, the thing is,
I've made a lot of
mistakes in my life.
But fighting for my family
will never be one of them.
And I've hurt a lot of
people along the way,
just to make sure that my
daughter had a shot at life.
And the things that I've done,
I will have to pay for 'em.
And I'll have to live with them.
And I don't know God's plan.
And I don't pretend to.
I just need you to
write this story...
And let God do his work.
That's all I got,
thanks for the coffee.
Wait!
You never even told me what
happened to your family.
Did Val help?
I mean, what happened to Sergei?
Did you at least get
your family back?
♪ It matters so little
♪ How much you may own
♪ The places you've been
♪ Or the people you've known
♪ For it all comes to nothing
♪ When placed at His feet
♪ It's nothing to Jesus
♪ Just memories to keep
♪ Only one life
♪ So soon it will pass
♪ Only what's done
♪ For Christ will last
♪ Only one chance
♪ To do His will
♪ So give to Jesus
all your days ♪
♪ It's the only life that pays
♪ When you recall
♪ You have but one life
♪ You may take all
the treasures ♪
♪ From faraway lands
♪ Take all the riches
♪ You can hold in your hands
♪ And take all the pleasures
♪ Your money can buy
♪ But what will you have
♪ When it's your time to die
♪ The days pass so swiftly
♪ The months come and go
♪ The years melt away
♪ Like new fallen snow
♪ Spring turns to summer
♪ Summer to fall
♪ Autumns brings winter