[CHILDREN LAUGHING]
I know. I know, I know,
but I can't come today
because, um, Sam's here
and, and my dad,
and Dad's working, so...
I know, I know it's the last
day of summer, Melissa,
but I'll see you
at school tomorrow.
We can do something
at recess, okay?
Okay. Bye, Melissa.
Bye.
[DOG BARKING]
Sam!
Sam.
You said you wanted to play.
I was waiting.
Dad said I could
watch TV.
Good.
And now you're done.
And put Gabriel
back in his cage.
TIM: Doc! Did you
take my phone?
You're in trouble.
No, I'm not.
Come on, lunchtime.
You are such a thief.
You want a sandwich?
You're making lunch? Sure.
[DOORBELL RINGS]
Hello.
Hello. Is your mother home?
Who are you?
I've come...
I'd like to interview
for the nanny position.
The nanny.
Okay, um...
[STAMMERS]
Um, well, I tried to call
but the number was busy
and the address
was on here.
I think you'd better
talk to my dad.
Come in.
You sound like
Mary Poppins.
I'm English.
I knew that.
SAM: Who's she?
That's Sam.Hi, Sam.
I start school tomorrow.
I'm four.
How wonderful.
I'm Gillian.
And I'm Doc.
That's short for Rebecca.
I'm 10.
Hi, Doc.
Hi.
She's a nanny.
You know, like
Mary Poppins.
Where's your umbrella?
[LAUGHS] It's in my case.
Come on. Dad's this way.
Hey, Dad,
she's a nanny!
Uh, hello.
Hello. I'm Gillian Malkin.
I was hoping to interview
for the nanny.
She knows Mary Poppins.
Really?
I'm sorry,
I, I did try to call.
And you know Barney.
Come on, feeding time.
Good luck.
[CHUCKLES]
Don't you just hate
precocious American kids?
Oh, not yet.
This is my first interview.
I keep forgetting
to break her will.
I beg your pardon?My kid...
Break her spirit.
Like breaking a horse?
It's a joke.
Oh, I'm sorry, the notice said
you wanted a sense of humor.
It's okay, my wife's got
the sense of humor.
I keep trying.
She's not home.
Oh, should I come
another time?
DOC: Dad, you want me
to show her the house?
Where would I be
without her? [CHUCKLES]
[SIGHS] Oh, what
a wonderful room.
Mmm.
[SIGHS]
This is so wonderful.
[CHUCKLES]
I keep saying that.
It's okay. Originality is only
5% of the grade.
[CHUCKLES]
Do you have a, a cook,
or a housekeeper?
Annie.
And, uh, this is the, uh,
uh, nanny's room.
This is so lovely.
When did your
nanny leave?
She didn't.
We never had one.
TIM: The most difficult
part of the job
will be taking care
of our daughter.
Oh, no,
Rebecca's delightful.
Not Doc.
Our other daughter.
Oh, she must be
out with your wife.
Should I wait...She's not out.
Asleep?She's not home.
Our other daughter
is Maggie.
She's five years old
and she exists only
in the mind of my wife.
Miss Malkin, if you think
you might want this job
I want you to know
how seriously I take
the subject of Maggie.
She's the most important
part of your job.
Maggie.
DOC: Let's go see
if she's still here.
SAM: Okay.
You've been talking
about my sister.
SAM: Maggie's out with Mom.
Maggie starts
kindergarten tomorrow.
I start pre-school.
That's nice.
Doc, don't you and Sam
have something to do?
Come on, Sam.
I want to see how hard
I can hit you with the ball.
Doc's going to teach me and
Maggie how to play catch.
I hope you take the job
'cause I could
use some help.
I'm afraid that I...
I don't understand.
I'd be amazed if you did.
Maggie is five years old.
Sam is four.
Sam thinks he has
an invisible sister.
Annie thinks she has
a 5-year-old daughter.
Doc and I pretend
to see her.
[CAR HORN HONKS]
[CAR APPROACHING]
That's Annie.
[BOTH SPEAK INDISTINCTLY]
DOC: There you go.
Be careful.
[DOC AND SAM LAUGHING]
[SOFTLY] Hi.
Hi, Mom!
Look, look!
ANNIE: Aw...
[GIGGLES] Hey.
Hey, Mom.Hi, guys, how are you?
Beautiful day, huh?Yeah.
Oh, I got lipstick
on you. Sorry.[GIGGLES] That's okay.
Sweetheart.
This is Gillian.
I know.
Doc and Sam were raving
about you outside.
Well, Doc's right.
You're wonderful.
Oh...
You're perfect. [CHUCKLES]
Perfect?
Oh, yes. I just put up
the notice today
and you're the
first to come.
Oh, I see.
And you're so
far from home.
You're very brave,
isn't she, Tim?
She certainly is.
Well, you won't
be lonely with us.
Look, I don't have
any references.
I've never been
a nanny before.
But I raised all
my younger brothers
and sisters.
The youngest just turned 15.
Um, my mum's been
kind of sick, you see,
for a long time.
You're perfect.
And I'm glad that
you don't have any
references
because we've
never had a nanny
and you've never been one,
so we'll learn together.
[CHUCKLES]
Isn't that right, honey?
Sure. Uh, Annie...
It's $400 a week.
Plus room and board
and use of a car and
two days off, of course.
Oh, that's...
But maybe you want
to discuss this.
Annie, why don't we,
uh, give Gillian a call
in a day or two,
let her know.
And she probably wants
to think about it too.
Don't you, Gillian?
Oh, but, honey,
she just arrived.
She has no place to stay.
Do you?
Your car in the driveway,
it's full of suitcases.
Oh.
She knows Mary Poppins!Oh.
[LAUGHS]
Maggie.
This is Gillian.
Gillian, this is Maggie.
Hello, Maggie.
It's nice to meet you.
Did you leave the front
door open again?
I'll do it.Oh.
Kids, don't run.
Oh!
Well, did Tim
show you your room?
Yes, he did.Is it all right?
Oh, it's wonderful.
Good.
Then it's settled.
Um, okay, well,
Doc you help me
unload the car.
And, uh, Gillian,
you'll want to unpack.
And just let us know if
you need anything, okay?
Okay.
Is this all right?
Welcome to the family.
[SIGHS]
Are you unpacked?Mmm-hmm.
DOC: Do you like it here?
Oh, it's like a dream.
Do you live in the
country in England?
No, London.
Big city, huh?
Hey, you forgot to push.
Come on, you don't hear
Maggie complaining.
SAM: Yes, I do.
Especially about vegetables.
DOC: Okay, come on,
Maggie, no hitting.
[GRUNTS]
Stop it, Sam.
SAM: She punched first.
Sometimes you gotta
separate these two.
You mind pushing
Maggie a while?
Um, no.
Thanks. Come on, Sam.
What are you doing?
Pushing Maggie.
Maggie's in her
room taking a nap.
Your father told me.
That I know
Maggie's not real?
Mmm-hmm.Right.
I do.
She takes a lot of naps.
And how does one know?
You don't always know.
Um, Gillian, why don't you
sit here next to Maggie?
Sam, Maggie, dinner.
Sam, did you
two wash up?
I did. Maggie didn't.
I know you did.
He's just teasing.
Mmm... [SLURPS]
Mashed potatoes
are my favorite.
Maggie, would you say grace?
ANNIE: Amen.ALL: Amen.
Doc's stealing Maggie's food.
I was cutting her broccoli.
Oh, okay.
Sam, eat your own food.
Don't worry about
Maggie and Doc.
So, you come
from a large family?
Um, five kids.
I'm the eldest. Thanks.
And you raised the others?
My mum couldn't, you see.
And my dad passed
away years ago.
What's, "passed away?"
Died.
Her daddy is with the angels.
How old were you when
your mom got sick?
I was about 10.
And you stayed until
the youngest could take
care of themselves?
That's very unselfish.
You postponed yourself.
Honey, she may not want
to talk about this now.
GILLIAN: No, it, it's fine.
Um, I wouldn't say
I was unselfish or
anything that grand.
Of course not, but you are.
And now it's your turn.
I'm sure your
mother agrees.
What's her name?
Emma.
Have you called her to let
her know that you're here?
No.
Oh, well, let's call
her right now.
Honey, it's about
3:00 am there.
Oh, that's right. [CHUCKLES]
Well, please call her
first thing in the morning
and let her know that
she can call you collect
whenever she misses you.
That's very nice, but...
You haven't been away
from home, have you?
Um...
I went to Loch Ness once.
[CHUCKLES]Ooh.
[DOC LAUGHS][SHUSHING]
Hold still.
It's an eyelash.
ANNIE: Okay?
I got it. See?
Now it's good luck.
You got to make a wish
and blow it away.
Oh, no, come in.
This is a busy time.
I've got to put Sam to bed.
You give Maggie her bath.
She'll tell you where
everything is.
Maggie, you can take a
tubby in Mommy's bath.
[CHUCKLES]
Well, she's learning.
We've got to help her out.
All right, um, she likes
the water a little hotter
than warm.
[GRUNTS]
It's been an interesting day.
Oh, I don't know. You think?
Why did Mom do this?I don't know.
Me either.
You have that look.What look?
Your crinkly look.
I have that?
I don't know
why Mom did this.
I don't know if
Gillian can handle it.
It's a lot to ask
of somebody.
Why do we need her?
Mom does everything
for Maggie anyway.
We have to trust
there's a good reason.
Like we trust there's a
good reason for Maggie?
Exactly.
Like we do that.
People grow
and change, Doc.
Even parents.
Nothing stays
the same forever.
Sweet dreams.
I love you.I love you, too.
All right, you can stay
in a couple more minutes.
GILLIAN: That's right.
Tomorrow's a big day.
First days are a little scary
but it'll be fun, I think.
Once you get there
you'll meet lots
of new children
and, and there will
be lots of new toys
and things to play with.
Oh, um, did I get
soap in your eye?
Oh, good. I, I thought I did.
I went out to the
museum site today.
Without me? You rat.
So, what did you think?
Well, all those
skinny columns, um...
It looks kind of like
a giant bicycle rack.
I'm kidding,
it's breathtaking.
Really.
A bicycle rack?
[CHUCKLES] So,
what do you think?
It's intentional,
I like bicycle racks.
Of Gillian.
She'll be great.
I'm sorry I surprised you.
I was going to interview
a few before I said anything
'cause, maybe I wouldn't
find the right person
or maybe I would
change my mind.
I had no idea
you wanted help.
It just seemed
time, I guess.
I mean, you've
been so patient.
I thought we
could use somebody.
Then maybe you wouldn't have
to work at home so much
and you could go
back to your office,
if it's still there.
Wow.
Have I been complaining,
'cause I'm fine, really.
You never complain.
Is everything okay?Sure.
And Gillian will be fine,
once she settles in.
[GROANS]
Oh, well.
Okay, Maggie, your turn.
You'll wear this.
And these.
And these shoes.
ANNIE: I usually give Maggie
peanut butter and jelly.
Sam gets milk,
Maggie gets juice.
And Doc?
She makes her own because
she has to get ready first
so she can catch the bus.
TIM: Okay.
Okay, Sam,
Maggie, let's go.
No, Tim.
We have a nanny now.
Gillian will drive them.
Well, I always
drove Maggie.
I know you did.
But now we have Gillian.
How do we know
she can drive?
Because I drove with
her this morning.
She did fine.
You drove this morning?Yeah, early.
How's she going
to find the school?
Don't forget
to eat Maggie's lunch.
That's what Dad did.Thanks.
Okay, Doc, I'm going
to drop you at the bus.
Have fun, you two.
Hey.
You are so beautiful.
I bet.
Okay.
Bye.Bye.
[EXHALES] Ready?
All right, the school...
First day, Maggie. Let's go.
ANNIE: They should be
getting out any minute.
GILLIAN:
I could have done this.
I know, but it's Sam's
first day of school
and I've never
had a nanny before.
I guess I have
to ease into this.
Of course.
[SIGHS]
You know, if you want to go
and talk to your friends...
No, that's okay.[SCHOOL BELL RINGING]
Tim always drove
Maggie to school.
I don't really
know anybody.
WOMAN: Bye, children,
see you tomorrow.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
Hi, hi, hi.
How was your
day at school?
Good.Do you like
your teacher?
SAM: She's nice.
I made you something
in school today.
You made this?
They have a machine.
ANNIE: Oh.
Do you like it?
I love it.
I really love it.
Do you want one?Oh, I'd love one, Sam.
But it can't say "Mom."
GILLIAN: [CHUCKLES] All right.
How did you make it?Hi.
They have this machine that
can make any kind of button.
That's great.Especially like these.
ANNIE: Hi, honey,
how was your day?
Did you have a good day?
Did you make new friends?
Yeah.
That's nice, Sam.
[KIDS LAUGHING]
ANNIE: Okay, let's
go down the slide.
Be careful.
[LAUGHS] You go first.
Hold on.
[LAUGHS]
Good job.
Are you okay?
Good.
Mom.
Maggie said I couldn't play
in the sandbox with her.
You tell your sister
I said if she doesn't
stop saying that
that she can't play
in the sandbox.
Okay. She has to go
to the bathroom.
I'll take her.
I'll go with you.
[SAM MUMBLES]
Sam, we're going
to show Gillian
where the bathroom is.
We'll be back
in one minute.
It's okay,
I'll watch him.
Thank you.Oh, that's all right.
You from London, eh?
Yes, are you
from London?
Within the sound
of Bow Bells.
I'm Peg.I'm Gillian.
It's nice to meet you.
SAM: Come on, Matt, let's go.
Yeah.
ANNIE: Do you
want a family?
I think so.
It's so odd to me.
There are so many
people in the world
who live alone.
It's just foreign to me.
I've never been alone.
The most alone
I've ever been was
on the flight here.
I could never
have done that.
Why did you?
Partly for the money.
Shh.And...
Partly because
if I'd stayed at home
I knew what my life
would be, more or less.
Before I'd even lived it.
We'll be right
here, honey.
Uh, if you're not
going to use that...
My daughter's in there.
[CHUCKLES] Are you crazy?
You got another kid?
You think a dragon
could blow it down?
Wouldn't the
soldiers stop him?
They can't see him.
The dragon's invisible?
Mmm-hmm, like Maggie.
Oh.
Can you hear the dragon?
Of course, when it's roaring.
I just can't see him.
SAM: My mom can see Maggie.
I do sometimes.
But I always can hear her,
and I always can feel her.
Especially when
she punches me.
Maggie's different.
ANNIE: Hey, pretty.
I can't believe
you guys actually
used to wear this stuff.
Watch it.
I never saw you
look like this.
You and Dad should
go out some time
dancing or something.
What, and leave
you guys alone?
Are you nuts?
My beautiful Rebecca.
[DOC GIGGLES]
Hey, are you still up?
Bedtime, Doctor.
Oh, come on.
Let me have one
more chapter.
Uh-uh-uh.Please, please, please.
Bedtime.
Okay.
Good night.Good night.
[GIGGLES]
It still looks like
a bicycle rack.
Really?
[CHUCKLES]
Does Sam seem like
he's coming down
with something?
Mmm-hmm.
He caught it from Maggie.
Right.
You were going to say...
[SIGHS] Nothing.
I'm just thinking.
About Gillian?
It's been three weeks.
And every time she takes
Sam and Maggie to school,
she just opens the door
and lets them out.
As opposed to...
Walking them in.
How do you know?
'Cause I've been
following her.
Oh.
[SIGHS]
Other than that?
She's great.
WOMAN: That's good.
Now, over there, we have
the little tart, Caroline.
She's a Georgia peach.
Pit, that is.
Spends most of her time in the
pool with her guv's stepson.
And there's Ramona,
over there.
No, I told you
not to let go!
PEG: She's Romanian,
nanny for life.
Rules the roost.
Temper on her like
you won't believe.
They love her.
They bought her a house.
Her own house?
She'll have a party
now and again.
I'll take you.
Gillian, we've been chums
now, what, couple of weeks?
Uh-huh.Mind a silly question?
Fire away.
What's with the swing?
Oh.
Invisible friend.
Nice to have a little
playmate, isn't it, Sammy?
Mmm-hmm.
You and your friend
want to come over
to the sandbox
and play with Matthew?
Yeah.
SAM: Come on, Maggie.
He's not going
to hurt you.
Can Maggie play
with your truck?
You can just
dump it in the sand.
She'll get it.
I told you, Maggie.
He's nice.
WOMAN: All right,
gather everything up.
I want you to put it
in your backpack.
Tell you one thing, Gill,
American men have got it
over the Brits
on two counts.
Great teeth and great bums.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
Have you found
yourself one yet?
Oh, um, I don't have
much free time.
Oh, don't let these
Yanks work you to death.
Peg?Yes, love?
How would you describe
a nanny's responsibility?
Oh, easy.
Try to keep the little
buggers from drowning.
Try to keep yourself
from drowning them.
What if there was some
kind of, situation?
Situation?
A scandal?
You're not
pregnant, are you?
Stop.
It's for a friend.Oh, depends.
Americans are very
fond of shrinks.
You know, head doctors.
[CHUCKLES]
I've read that.
They hang their dirty
laundry anywhere.
Thrive on telling each other
the most intimate details.
So what, do you go to
one of them for advice
or something?
Well, if that's the kind of
trouble you think you're in.
But I don't need
the money, Mum.
Because they provide
everything, really.
I don't need money
and you do.
All right, next month
I'll keep some.
Is Sally checking in
on you every day?
I'm not worried,
I just love you.
[ANNIE LAUGHS]
I'm going to get
Maggie now.
No, no, you don't.
Ah, she's...
Um, yes, I'm happy.
Really.
[ANNIE LAUGHS]
She got away again.
Okay, I'm going to
get you next time.
Yes, I, I miss you too.
ANNIE: See?
You toss it into the
deepest part of the pond.
[CHUCKLES]
It is fun to be sick
a little and miss school.
A day for us.
But you're really fine now,
so tomorrow, school.
Okay?
[SIGHS]
ANNIE: I'm thirsty, are you?
[GASPS]
Look.
Hey, Gilly.Hey.
How was school?
Fine.
So, this is real
English cooking?
I love this.[GIGGLES]
It's good of your mum
to let me do this.
It'll blow her
socks off.
[IMITATING ACCENT]
Can I help?
Does that make it
less English?
[GIGGLES]
Don't be such a twit.
Um, you can stir that pot.
Okay.
Doc, I was thinking...
You get two weeks'
vacation at Christmas.
Mmm-hmm.
Your parents gave me
a ticket home, to be
with my family.
I'll have to hurry
on your present then.
When you going?
Um, in four weeks.
And...
I was wondering if you'd
like to come with me
and have an
English Christmas.
Why would I want
to leave here?
I thought perhaps you
could use the rest.
Get away.
From what?
Well, the stress.
What stress?
Of Maggie, you know.
Why would I need to
get away from Maggie?
Maggie's not real.
TIM: Here come seconds.
Mmm.
Great meal, Gilly.
This is really
delicious, Gillian.
Oh, I'm so pleased
you like it.
Sam's doing fine.
Doc, some more
Yorkshire pudding?
I'm pretty full.
Oh, perhaps Maggie
would like some.
Wonderful.
Mmm.
This pudding doesn't
taste like dessert.
[GIGGLES] It's a different
kind of pudding, honey.
It's fantastic,
this is a great meal.
I could have never
made this. [GIGGLES]
Oh, it's easy.
In fact, it's easier when
there are more people.
That's it.
A dinner party.
You, you could invite
your friends and I'll cook.
An English feast.
Yeah, a party!
It's a wonderful
idea, Gillian.
It's really nice
of you to offer
and I'm sure it would be fun.
It's just...
I'm pretty tired
when I finish work
and this house is sort of...
A retreat.
Sorry to be an ogre.
ANNIE: Yeah, you can
have one in your room.
Okay.
Pretty.
[GASPS]
Is she okay?
Oh, yeah.
She just pricked her
finger on a thorn.
Honey, be careful.
ANNIE: Okay, let's see.
Isn't that pretty?
Perhaps we should
start again.
GILLIAN: I'm sorry.
I guess I don't know
how to do this.
But you do know
how to talk.
That's all we do here.
You say you didn't
come here for yourself,
but for the family
who employs you.
Yes.How did you find me?
The telephone book.
Do you know anything
about psychiatry?
Not much.
Normally, when someone
comes to see a psychiatrist
and they claim they're
coming for someone else
usually they're lying.
I don't lie.
And they say that.
Look, these people
need help.
All right, let's
say I believe you.
Your concern's misplaced.
What do you mean?
I shouldn't worry?
It's the 4-year-old boy
you should worry about.
The older child knows
the sister isn't real?
Mmm-hmm.
Well, I would say, probably,
this fantasy is bonding
her closer to her father
and her mother.
It, uh, allows
her to help them.
And her sense of reality
is probably, more
or less, unimpaired.
This might even enrich
her in some way.
Oh.
However, the 4-year-old.
His sense of reality
is impaired.
He has no way
of distinguishing
between what is real
and what isn't.
Oh, God.
[SIGHS] What should I do?
In a case like this,
someone may need to intervene.
The family clearly won't.
I can't.
We have
governmental services
that can provide assistance.
You could talk
to someone there.
That's really all I can say.
[SIGHS]
I'll only charge
you half the hour.
I could use a little
time to myself.
ANNIE:
Oh, that's wonderful, Sam.
Guess what kind
of whale it is.
Um, baby beluga?
No.Monstro?
Is it Moby Dick?
The rainbow whale
who forgot his rainbow?
Maggie, Mommy
already said that.
Hi, Mrs. Wood,
I'm Tim Beeman.
Hi.TIM: My wife, Annie.
Hi.Hello.
Our daughter, Doc, and this
is our nanny, Gillian Malkin.
Hello.Hi, nice to meet you.
And this is my sister, Maggie.
We noticed you were
demonstrating some
puppets over there.
Uh, could we take a look?
Oh, of course.
Sam made a wonderful one.
Sam, you want to show
Mom and Dad your puppet?
SAM: Okay.Come on, Sam.
Thank you.Come on, Mom.
Come on, Maggie.
Rebecca, how are you, dear?
I remember you.
Fine, thank you.
My nickname's Maggie.
We will, Maggie,
just a minute.
Sam, we're going to go
next door for a minute.
Do you want to stay here and
we'll come back and get you?
Mmm-hmm, mmm-hmm.
WOMAN: Natalie,
show me your picture.
Tim, I don't see any
of Maggie's drawings.
Well, maybe they got lost.
Mom, look.
Maggie's drawing.
Oh, Maggie.
It's beautiful.
Of course, let's put it up.
Hi, Jenelle.
Did you show your
mom your artwork?
Yeah, it's beautiful.
Shouldn't we...
Doc!ANNIE: Mr. Felix.
I'm Annie Beeman.Oh, hello.
Hi. I just wanted
to tell you how much
I admire your work
with the children.FELIX: Oh, thank you.
I see how you encourage
their imaginations and
stimulate their curiosity.
That's very kind of you.
You're...
Would you excuse me
for a minute?
[GAGGING]
I'm going to throw up.
Oh, honey.
Let's go. Um, Gillian,
can you go get Sam?
Sure.Let's go.
[GAGS]
I'm sorry, Mrs...
Is Doc okay?
Fast asleep.
Annie...Hush.
[HUMMING LULLABY]
Annie...
Quiet.
I'm singing to your heart.
GILLIAN: I have no
idea why she does it.
WOMAN: Really?
You've been there
three months.
You must have some idea
what caused her to create
this psychosis.
I don't know, I mean, it
doesn't make any sense
because in every other
way, she's so normal.
Could he abuse her or them
and you're just
not aware of it?
Of course not.
They are wonderful people.
Mr. Beeman is a saint
and so is she.
She lives in a fantasy
and he enables her to
do it and makes their
10-year-old help.
That's wonderful?
You make them sound awful.
You came to me because
you were worried
about the children.
And child abuse is
what I investigate.
Because it's a crime.
You are completely
twisting my words.
I'm sorry I came.
I'm just repeating the story
that you told me, that's all.
May I have those
notes please?
No.
Are you sure you're just not
afraid of losing your job?
You do have a green card.
[SNIFFS] Mmm.
Smell those, Maggie.
Mmm. Are those good?
And look, raspberries,
your favorite.
I'll take these.
ANNIE: Sam?
Sam?
Sam!
Hey. I missed you.
Mom.
What, baby?
Are there other
people like Maggie
that I can't see?
I don't know.
I can't hear them.
Let's go home, baby.
I asked Maggie.
She said she doesn't know.
Let's all go home. Okay?
Oh, I'm sorry, honey.
I was off somewhere.
No, you're not very sick.
It's just a little fever.
[INHALES]
I guess Mommy's frightened.
You know, mommies and
daddies get frightened
too sometimes.
No. Not of the bogeyman.
Let's say our prayers.
Now I lay me down to sleep.
I pray the Lord
my soul to keep.
If I should die before I wake,
I pray the Lord
my soul to take.
Sweet dreams, honey.
I know. I'll come back
to check on you.
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
TIM: Come on in.
There's room for
a circus in here.
I don't want
to disturb you.
No, it's okay.
[SIGHS]
I guess Maggie
has a fever.
I guess she does.
I've never seen you
out here at night.
Does that mean you're
out here every night?
Is that all right?
Sure. What's it for?
It's my secret luxury.
To sit in warm, bubbly
water under the stars
and look at the silhouette
of the mountains
and listen to the birds.
Pretty far from England.
I must sound really silly.
Never be embarrassed of
being delighted, Gillian.
That's something
Annie taught me.
She seems sad tonight.
I've never seen her like that.
She's worried.
She put the baby monitor
in Maggie's room.
Could I...
Ask me how it started?
I'm sorry.
I wondered when you would.
No, I should let you
enjoy this in peace.
You're very good
at all this.
I'm sort of amazed.
Sometimes I just
want to cry for Annie.
Then I think of what
you must feel. And Doc.
You want to know why she
does it? How it started?
That's fair.
You're kind of family by now.
Are you hungry at all?
Sure.
It was, uh, five years ago.
One morning I was
sitting here, having coffee
like I do every morning.
Annie comes into the
kitchen and she goes
to the stove and...
She had her back to me.
But when she turned,
I could see she was
sterilizing baby bottles.
And, and she was holding
something in her arms
something I couldn't see.
She said,
Maggie had kept her up
all night with colic.
It seemed we had a new baby
whose name was Maggie.
I thought it was a joke.
Then Doc came in
and Annie asked her
if Maggie had kept her
awake with her crying.
My heart stopped.
I didn't know what to do.
Did you take her
to see someone?
Psychiatrist? Sure.
We went to one
of the best in town.
We get to the door
of his office
and Annie looks at me
with tears in her eyes
and says,
"Please don't make
me go in there.
"He'll take away my baby."
Well, I had a pretty good
idea what he'd say
so I went in alone
and listened.
I got as many professional
opinions as I could.
I learned that she
would almost certainly
be institutionalized.
I couldn't do it.
Did you say you
were hungry?
Starving.Good. Me, too.
I knew this had
to be something so
deep and desperate
and I thought what terrible
damage it might do to her
to just rip it away.
She wouldn't do this without
some extraordinary need.
Did you talk to her about it?
If it was something she
could have talked about
I don't think it
would have happened.
You know, for a long time, we,
we lived just for each other.
My career was just taking off
and if I had a gig
in Paris, we'd go.
Or a weekend seminar in
Stockholm, we'd just go.
We loved our life.
I'd come home in the
middle of the day...
Then Doc came along, and life
began to revolve around her.
Annie loved being a mother.
Ooh... She was in heaven.
I was spending more
and more time at work.
I was hot all of
a sudden and...
You know, when that happens,
you just want to go with it.
So, I was gone
a lot of the time.
I think Annie blamed
herself for the change.
She figured she'd
messed up somehow
that her, her attention to Doc
was somehow driving us apart.
So, she did the only
thing she could do.
Do it again, only,
do it right this time.
[SIGHS] Maggie.
The funny thing is,
Maggie did make
everything right again.
I came back.
I was totally
focused on my family.
I thought having another child
would make Maggie go away
but getting pregnant... Sam...
I think just reinforced
her conviction
that Maggie had made
everything right.
What about Doc and Sam?
I just don't know.
I think Doc's stronger for it.
We're partners.
We talk about it.
If there are scars...
And I look for them,
I don't see them.
Sam?
Sam's okay, for now.
For now.
But, what if...
I mean...
What if...
I'm wrong?
[EXHALES]
Well...
I do ask myself that.
When do you
think it will end?
When Annie says it does.
Come on, Sam.
Whoa!
Hold on, hold on!
[ROLLER COASTER WHOOSHING]
DOC: Doesn't that
look fun, Sam?
[LAUGHING]
MAN: Six to a car.
Watch your step.
Step right on up.
[KIDS SHOUTING]MAN: All right.
Oh, I'm sorry, Miss.
You're gonna have to
wait down there 'cause
it's six to a row.
Oh.Maggie, you and Gillian
go together, okay, honey?
Come on, Maggie.
[FERRIS WHEEL CREAKING]
Six to a car,
watch your step.
Thank you.
No, uh...
[PEOPLE EXCLAIMING]
[PEOPLE WHOOPING]
[LAUGHING]
Whoo!
DOC: It's beautiful up here.
Look at this.
The beautiful ocean.
So pretty. [LAUGHING]
I love it.
Whoo!
Watch your step.
BOY 1: Pizza!BOY 2: All right.
Where's Maggie?
She, she's right here, Annie.
She was on my lap.
You just didn't see her.
Maggie's lost.
She didn't ride with Gillian.
It's okay, Mom,
we'll find her.
She couldn't
have gone far.
Annie, I, I thought
she was in my lap.
They wouldn't let
her ride in your lap.
Oh, Mom, it's okay...
Don't worry,
I know where she is.
MAN: Is there a problem?
Yeah, my sister wandered away
but we think we
know where she is.
What does she look like?
She's five years old and
she has brown curly hair,
blue eyes and she's
wearing a jean skirt
and white sneakers
and her shirt is...
[SOBBING] I can't remember
what color her shirt is.
DOC: Um, it's the purple
one with the balloon.
Are you sure?
Yeah, 'cause we had
a fight about it.
She took it out of my
drawer without asking.
MAN: What's her name?Maggie Beeman.
MAN: Okay, I'll put it over
the PA system for you.
Mom, you and Sam stay here.
Gillian and I will go
find her. Come on.
Okay.
[SNIFFLING]
DOC: This is a first.
I can't believe it.
Kids get lost.
I guess it's her turn.
We found her.
What?
Let's go back.
100 on the nose.
You got a fever, baby.
Maybe it's just from
the excitement of the day.
Well, we'll see.
Gillian brought you some
tea if you get thirsty.
With honey.Mmm-hmm.
Oh... All right, but
I want you to sleep.
Which one do you want?
Oh... Gillian,
can you get me
the  Grandfather Twilight
book over there?
Thanks. Okay.
I'll be back in a couple
minutes to hear your prayers.
Good night, Maggie.
She'll be all right?
I think so.
It's just that she's
getting these so often.
It's not like her.
Anyway, uh, let's not
bother Tim with this.
He would just
worry unnecessarily.
I'm so sorry...
About today.
Oh...
It had a happy ending.
Let it go.
I was just... [SCOFFS]
Incredibly stupid.
Oh, let it go, Gilly.
I have. So has Maggie.
Okay.
TIM: Do you like this one?SAM: Yeah.
TIM: Okay.
We need two more.
Two more, coming up.TIM: Okay.
[DOORBELL RINGS]
I'll get it.
That's going to go
on top, right?
Yeah.TIM: Okay.
WOMAN: Is this the
Beeman residence?
Um, Gilly?
Are your parents' home?
Dad!
[WHISPERS] Why?
[RAPID FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
Oh, Annie. Has, has
there been an accident?
No, everything's fine...
I mean there's been
no accident.
I'm Marie Tan Lee,
from the Department of
Children and Family Services.
Are you Mr. Beeman?
Yes, I am.
Could we speak privately?
Gilly, take the children
in the other room.
Now.
Mr. Beeman, we've had a report
of possible irregularities.
Irregularities? What
the hell does that mean?
Mr. Beeman, I need to
speak to your children.
May we come in?My children?
Yes.
A report? From whom?
I'm not at liberty to
say. May we come in?
I will make this as fast
and painless as I can.
No.
These police officers are
here to make sure that I do.
And that I'm able to
have access to your
children, privately.
Listen, Miss...
Whoever the hell you are,
you may not have
access to my children
and you are not
coming into my house.
Mr. Beeman, I am coming in.
That's the law.
The law?
Yes. Whenever we have a report
of possible child abuse
we go to the home involved
to verify the charge or to
dismiss it.
If I have to, I can come in
here and take your children.
That's the law, sir.
Or you can let me in
and let me do my job.
Well...
Why do you have
to see them alone?
Think about it.
Because of some anonymous
report you claim to have
received?
I have received.
Well, who the hell from?
And what abuse?
I can't tell you.
The department's policy
protects the identity
of the informants.
If you let me in
to see your children
I can determine whether or
not this need go any further.
If I find no evidence of abuse
this could end right now.
I'm calling my lawyer.
I don't believe this.
Call him. You have three
minutes before we come in.
Please leave the door open
while you make the call.
Go ahead.
[LAUGHING]
It's a very nice room.
Thanks.[LAUGHING]
I know whose
room that is.
That's my room.
Knock, knock.
Who's there?
Sack.Sack who?
Sack of potatoes
from Sacramento.
[LAUGHING]
Whose room is this?
DOC: It's, um, uh...
SAM: This is Maggie's room.
So.
You'll be hearing from us.
Goodbye, guys.
What does that mean?
Thank you, Mr. Beeman.
[HORNS HONKING]
Tim, is everything okay?
TIM: [OVER PHONE]
Yeah, it's fine.
Where are you?
Stuck in traffic. Are you
sure everything's okay?
TIM:  Annie, what is this?
We're fine.
[SIGHS]
I had the strangest feeling.
TIM:  Look, just come home.
We're fine.
Okay. Love you.
TIM:  Me, too.[DISCONNECTS CALL]
Well, I guess they're fine.
Oh, honey, you're burning up.
[WEEPING QUIETLY]
[KNOCK AT DOOR]
Gillian.
GILLIAN: I'm so...
I'm the person who
talked to them.
It's all my fault.
I believe you.
What did you do?
I...
When did you do it?
Two months ago.
It was before you explained
everything to me that night.
I, I never thought
they'd come here.
Oh, God, it was
just so awful.
Yes, it was.
What did you do?
I went to one of those
psychiatrist people.
You saw a psychiatrist, and...
He said that Doc was fine
because she knew that
Maggie was a fiction.
But to worry about Sam.
And, you didn't
want to tell me.
No, because...Because I was part of it.
So, then you went to the
Child Services Office.
Again, instead of me.
I thought that they
might be able...
But she was so horrible,
and I left.
I was, I was angry and
frightened and I walked away
and I never, never thought
she would do anything.
You saw that woman
who was here?
What did you tell her?
You told her that Annie thinks
she has an invisible daughter.
That I forced Doc into
playing along with it
and that Sam has spent
his entire life around
this insanity.
I know now
that that was wrong.
I love you all.
I was wrong.
Were you?
Yes! It's just what you think
if you don't understand.
That's comforting.
But those people
in Child Services
are not going to understand.
I know.
And I'm, I'm so sorry.
I'm leaving.You're not leaving.
Why?
Because you're going
to help me fix this.
DOC:  Dad?
What can they do?
Nothing.
I don't know.
If she can walk in with
two cops, that was gross.
It was gross.
How'd they know
about Maggie?
It doesn't matter.
It was Gillian. I hate her.
TIM: No, you don't.
She loves you.
Doc... Everybody
makes mistakes.
And you love her.
Not anymore.
She's going to help
make this right.
But what can they do,
take us away?
No!
Let's run away.
Well, there's an idea.
How about an island
in the South Pacific?
Come on, let's do it.
We'll leave tonight.
Mom and you and me and Sam.
Not Gillian.
Honey, they can't do
anything to us, I promise.
But what if they do?
What if they try
to take us away?
Then we run away.
Well, what if they come
with tanks and more cops
and all that?
We sneak out the back
right down to the boat
in the open sea.
You promise?
I promise.
ANNIE: Tim?
Tim, call the doctor.
Maggie's really sick.
Annie, slow down.
If she needs a doctor
I'll take her to him,
like I always do.
No, um, she's too
sick to move.
My God, he'll
make a house call.
He's been her doctor
her whole life.
I don't know.
We'll see, okay?Please.
DOC: Are you all right?Hmm-mmm.
It's going to be okay.
He wasn't available. I'll
just take her to the hospital.
I'm going.Honey, you don't have to.
I know.
Gillian, can you help
me get Maggie dressed?
We're taking her
to the hospital.
[ELEVATOR BELL DINGS]
Okay, honey.
WOMAN: [OVER INTERCOM]
Dr. Grace to room 305.
Dr. Grace to room 305, please.
[PHONE RINGING]
TIM: Honey, you're going
to sit here and I'll go
talk to the nurse.
Oh, don't worry, honey.
Daddy will be right back.
Everything's going
to be fine.
May I help you?
Yes, I, I have this
pain in my stomach
and I'm worried it
might be an ulcer.
Well, we can take a look.
Do you have insurance?
Yes.
Have you read this yet?
Here's one I've never heard
of before... Seismosaurus.
There's T-Rex.
Mr. Beeman?
Oh, wouldn't you
rather Mommy wait here
and when you come back,
you'll be all better?
Good. It'll be
okay, honey.
No. Tim, I want to come.
Well, two to one, outvoted.
I understand you
have stomach pain.
I... Do, yes.
Where?
Uh...
Here.
Could you remove
your shirt, please?
Well, I had this fever
just 24 hours ago
and, and I didn't
call my doctor.
Now the fever's gone,
but this pain in my stomach
I just thought
it might be related.
DOCTOR: Really?
Hmm...
Well, that's pretty
interesting, Mr. Beeman
but honestly, you seem fine.
I mean, I believe you...
Uh-huh.
If your stomach hurts
your stomach hurts.
Right.
Then again, it could
all be in your mind.
Really?
Well...
Hope you feel better.
Thanks. I'm really
glad I came.
Uh, Doctor, excuse me.Yes?
Um, could I have, uh,
one of those lollipops?
Uh... Yeah.
Sure, I guess so.
I have a daughter out front.
Of course.
Thanks.
TIM: Nice doctor.
It's nothing worry about.
Oh, Maggie, you look better.
Was there a prescription?
The usual. Aspirin, fluids.
Everything's going
to be okay. Come on.
Tim?[GASPS]
I'm sorry.
You startled me,
that's all.
Are you okay?
I remember the day
I first saw you.
Oh, God.
I'd do anything for you.
Tim. You're shaking.
Anything, Annie.
Are you worried
about Maggie?
No. No, it's just...
[EXHALES]
I don't know
how to express it.
I want...
I want to take care of you.
I want to tell you
how much I love you.
I love our family.
DOC: Hey, Gilly.
Can I come in?
Sure.
What's the matter?
Oh, it's... Our going
to see that woman at
Children's Services today.
I guess I'm just frightened.
Does your mother know,
do you think?
No. She doesn't.
I'd know.
God, this is just so awful.
Come on, there's
nothing to worry about.
You're going to be great.
You're so sure.
Mostly.
I hope you're right.
Well, like Dad said
if anything does happen
we just run away.
Run away?
He said that?
Yeah.
He said we'd run away
to the South Pacific.
[SOBBING] I don't
want to run away.
Sweetheart.
[SOBBING]Shh...
[SOBBING]
I don't want to...
Shh... Oh, Doc.
Everything's going
to be fine, I promise.
LEE: Mr. Beeman,
you may come in now.
This is Mr. Beeman.
Mr. Beeman, this is
Mrs. Carperhorn
and Mr. Schmidlen.
I have a lawsuit in here.
You invade my home
with armed policemen
threaten me with
insubstantial evidence,
talk to my children alone.
About what, I don't know.
Then send a letter threatening
to take my children away
if I don't appear today
for this meeting.
This isn't even a courtroom
and I could lose my family?
I hope you've prepared
well because I don't
intend to stay here long.
I'm sorry you feel
that way, Mr. Beeman
but, where's your wife?
Her presence was requested.
My wife is at home, sick.
Your wife is the crux
of this thing, Mr. Beeman.
The allegation is
that she believes she
has a nonexistent child
and that you support
her in this fantasy.
That's ludicrous.
Where is your wife?I just told you.
What about your son?
We want to talk to him.
I brought my daughter.
It kills me that she has
to go through this again
and I'm allowing it,
but that's it.
You've got our nanny.
You can see her alone, too.
She's with us
all day, every day.
Ask her whatever you like.
And you can talk to my
daughter. Which I hate!
But you are not
talking to my son.
He's in school.
My wife is sick.
Are we clear on this?
Because if we aren't
and you come back into my life
after today, believe me...
You don't know
what trouble is.
Anything else?
We all understand
your attitude.
We'll talk to your nanny now.
LEE: Now, Gillian, we
know between ourselves,
that you're the one that
started these allegations.
No, I didn't.
Excuse me?
Well, I, I mean I did come
to see you, that's true,
because there was a nanny,
a friend of mine
from the playground
and she had a problem...
She's Irish, actually...
And she was a
little frightened.
So I, I said I would come here
and try and find out
some information for her.
So, I did explain to you
or at least I, I started to
a situation that she was
dealing with in her home
but it was obvious
you couldn't help.
So I left.
And where this nonsense
comes from, I don't know.
That's not true
and you know it.
What's not true?
You told me a story of
a seriously disturbed woman.
A mother of two small children
who believes that she has
a third invisible child.
Do you honestly deny that?
That's the oddest thing
I've ever heard
and, yes, I deny it.
How are you, Rebecca?
Fine, thank you.
Why am I here?
Some children need protecting.
That's why we're here.
So, don't be afraid to
say anything you want.
We're on your side.
Uh-huh.
Now, this thing that we
talked about before, um,
your invisible sister...
Invisible sister?
You have an invisible sister.
My brother has an
imaginary friend or two.
We call one Maggie.
Is that what you mean?
Actually, Maggie was my
invisible friend before
she was his.
It was kind of like
the tooth fairy.
You grow out of it.
Or, do you still believe
in the Tooth Fairy?
No.
DOC: Me, neither.
So anyway, I grew
out of Maggie.
It was fun.
But Sam, he liked her.
So, now Sam's got
Maggie for a while.
You see, Sam
believes in Santa Claus,
the Easter Bunny, the
Tooth Fairy, and Maggie.
You think I should tell him
about Santa Claus
and everything.
Is that why I'm here?
No.
We're trying to determine
if you and your brother
are in a safe environment.
We're fine.
Isn't it true that
your mother thinks
she has an
invisible daughter
and that you and your father
help her with this fantasy?
[LAUGHS]
No. Do you know...
See, this is weird.
See... I don't even
like knowing there's
no Santa Claus.
So, every year, I help
my mom and dad
fool Sam into thinking
there is a Santa Claus.
[SIGHS]
So, we all play
along with Maggie
like we play along
with Santa Claus.
There is a big difference
between Santa Claus,
the Easter Bunny,
the Tooth Fairy
and a particular fantasy
that nobody else has,
like a sister
who doesn't exist.
Really?
She's not a sister.
But that's a good idea!
She could be.
Santa Claus is an established
cultural fantasy.
Now, when somebody has a
fantasy that nobody else does,
Rebecca, that's a
very different thing.
Oh.
Like Martin Luther King.
We studied him.
He had a dream.
No one else had it.
No, not like him.
Like craziness...
Santa Claus is sort of
crazy if you think about it.
I mean, come on. One guy
for the whole world,
in one night?
And the thing is,
I got to tell you
even though I know
there's no Santa Claus,
I still kind
of believe in him.
I don't even tell
my parents this.
You won't tell them, will you?
So, when we're putting out
the milk and cookies and stuff
that I know Dad's going to eat
and the carrot
for the reindeer,
that I know Mom's going to eat
I still believe he's
out there somewhere.
I believe in Peter Pan, too.
So, what are we going to do?
Maggie's fun. Is that bad?
Could you, um, ask your
father to come back in?
Sure.
Mr. Beeman, your daughter
is quite impressive.
It appears that
there's been some mistake.
I hope you understand
that our motives are
to protect the children.
That's why we're here.
I do.
And I'm sorry
about my temper.
I'm glad you people are here
for the people who need you.
I'm glad we don't.
[ALL CHEERING]
[LAUGHING]
[SIGHS]
Doc, there's something
I have to tell you.
It was me.
I'm the one who
caused all of this.
I'm, I'm sorry.
I knew that.
Everyone makes mistakes.
Race you to the car![LAUGHS]
ALL:   He played
knickknack on my gate
With a knickknack,
paddywhack
Give the dog a bone
This old man
came rolling home
This old man, he played nine
He played knickknack
on my spine
[LAUGHING]
TIM:   On my mind
On my wine[GILLIAN LAUGHING]
ALL:   With a knickknack,
paddywhack
Give a dog a bone
This old man
came rolling home
Okay, next. GILLIAN AND DOC:
This old man, he played ten
Yeah?  He played knicknack
on my hen
Your hen?[LAUGHING]
You don't have a hen.GILLIAN: We should get one!
ALL:   This old man
came rolling home
This old man,
he played eleven [DOOR OPENING]
TIM: Did you get it in?[LAUGHING]
TIM: Oop.
[GIGGLING]
Mom! Mommy, look.Here she is.
One, two, three...
ALL: Happy un-birthday![DOC LAUGHING]
Aren't you supposed
to be in school?
Well, Doc and I
were playing hooky
and we ran into Gilly
doing her errands
and, uh, we all decided
to take the day off.
And we got you
something. Look!
Oh!
It's a horse.
A really old horse.
Oh, it's a beautiful horse.
Thank you.
TIM: What's wrong?
Maggie's sicker,
a lot sicker.
I'm doing what
the doctor said.
The fever is back.
TIM: Do you want to go
back to the hospital?
I don't know.
Not now.
Um, could we put
this in her room?
I mean, would you all mind
telling her that it's for her?
DOC: No, no.TIM: Of course not.
[SCRIBBLING]
What is it?
Maggie.
I'm really worried.
Maggie lives in
Annie, remember?
Yeah.
I just feel so helpless.
We are.
Annie has all the controls.
And, when you love someone
you are...
Totally vulnerable.
Children teach you that.
[WHISPERING] What?
A, a what?
Where?
Can you point?
I can't see it.
Must be a beautiful angel.
[SNIFFLES]
And it must be just for you.
Mom, I made you something
in school today.
Oh. [SNIFFLES]
Look at that.
What is it?It's a turtle
made out of clay.
[SOFTLY] Aw...
I'm going to
paint it tomorrow.
But I could give it
to you unpainted.
Painting it would be nice.
You look sad.
Is Maggie okay?
Oh, she's a little sick.
Hi, Maggie.
I made something for you, too.
Actually, Mom, could
I give yours to Maggie?
Of course.
Here, Maggie.
[SNIFFLES] Hey, Sam.
Maggie saw an angel
up there in the corner.
Do you see it?
Yeah, I see it.
Yeah, I think I see it.
Yeah, I see it!
Is Maggie contagious?
No, honey, she's not.
Is Maggie going
to feel better soon?
I don't know.
'Cause I told my teacher
I would like to bring
Maggie for show-and-tell.
Show-and-tell Maggie.
She could just
walk down the hall.
And she said, "Yes."
Well... She has
to get better first.
Okay...
Let's leave Maggie alone
with her angel, okay?
[LAUGHING]
You know what?
Can't be trusted.
Cannot be trusted.[DOC EXCLAIMS]
SAM: Hey, Dad!
[DOC LAUGHS]
ANNIE: Smells great.
Maggie's coming to
show-and-tell with me.
Ooh.When she gets
better, honey.
No, really, you guys,
she's going to be fine.
The fever's going to
break and she'll be fine.
Okay?
Well, it looks like you have
everything under control.
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
[BABY MONITOR
STATIC CRACKLING]
Hey, Mags.
How you doing?
Great horse, huh?
You know why we got it?
Well, I know you know.
I did pretty well, huh?
Move over.
You know all those times
I thought you were a pain?
Wearing your clothes, so
Mom would think you did.
Eating your food...
Fighting with you...
Doing your artwork...
Well, I was thinking,
if you had an
ordinary handicap,
like you were blind or deaf,
I'd be doing a lot of
stuff for you, right?
So, you're invisible.
I just want you to know,
you're not a pain.
[SIGHS]
Oh, Maggie.
You're getting sick a lot.
Something's changing,
I don't know.
TIM: [OVER BABY MONITOR]
We have a wonderful family.
It's not like
any other family,
and we may not make sense
to other people, but...
It's our family
and it works, and...
You're a part of it.
I wish I could see you.
I wish I could hold you
the way Annie does.
But I can hold her,
and I can see her.
And maybe through her...
You feel it.
[SIGHS]
Yeah.
I'm a silly daddy.
[BABY MONITOR
STATIC CRACKLING]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
TIM: Mmm.
Okay, kids.
Let's get a move on.
Time for school.
All right, you guys,
hop, hop.
[SOBBING]
DOC: Mom?
Dad?
[SNIFFLES]
Let me do this.
Kids...
[INHALING DEEPLY]
Your sister died last night...
In her sleep.
It was very peaceful.
Remember that angel that
you saw waiting in her room?
Well, it must have
been waiting for her.
And now Maggie's with God
and with all the angels.
Is Maggie a angel?
Mmm-hmm.
[ANNIE SNIFFLING]
Doc...
You know, too, that
Maggie's with the angels.
Yeah, Mom. I know.
Are you okay?
I'm sad.
For us and for me...
But not for Maggie.
SAM: Mom?What, honey?
Is Maggie with God?
Mmm-hmm.
One day Dad will be with God.
One day you'll be with God.
And Gilly...
And Doc, and me, too.
And then we'll all
come back, right?
I think so.
If God wants us to.
SAM: Mom, next time
I don't want Maggie
to be invisible, okay?
ANNIE: Okay.
[SNIFFLING]
Maggie...
I know your light
is shining brightly
wherever you are now.
But I know
you're still with us...
In our hearts, always.
Maggie, Sam asked me
to say this prayer.
ALL: Now I lay me
down to sleep
I pray the lord
my soul to keep
if I should die before I wake
I pray the lord
my soul to take.
Thank you.
[SOBBING]