Perfect. That was perfect.
And upload.
Okay, and…
Time to start another boring day.
Here you are.
Thank you.
Here you go.
OPEN
A very good morning. How can I be of help?
Now, listen up, young man!
In the old days
everything was better, far better…
CLOSED
I'm taking my lunch break.
Wait.
Hello, I'm…
I'm not sure if this is the right address,
but I'm here for a very secret issue.
Do you understand?
Okay, come on Sebastian, you can do it.
You can do it.
Thank you.
Thanks.
Damn it!
In Nevada, a virus outbreak
of unknown origin continues to spread,
causing a rabies-like response
in those who contract it.
This has led to the public deeming
the outbreak "the zombie apocalypse."
Amidst the epidemic, groups of civilians
are stepping up to do their part
in helping to rescue survivors
stuck in the infected zone.
Let's check in
with one of our correspondents,
Gil Pedretti, on the ground in Las Vegas.
Dear viewers,
I can't tell you
exactly what's going on right now,
but as you just saw, this is reality.
This was really happening.
As we get more information,
we will certainly
give you an immediate update.
That movie looks fucking awesome.
Would you like to see it?
It's not out yet.
Excuse me, sir.
Could you hold these, please?
-My pleasure.
-Very kind.
I have an appointment
for the deposit room.
Yes, please wait.
That way, please.
-I'll leave you to it.
-Thank you.
You speak English? A little bit?
No.
Just a moment.
You speak English? A little bit?
Of course.
So sorry.
Awesome!
Yes.
Silence!
I did it. Yes!
I'm a master!
LUDWIG DIETER
MASTER SAFECRACKER AND EXPLORER
Hi.
Pavel, for the last time,
you can't drink in here.
-Did you see that?
-Where did he go?
He disappears.
Just pretend.
Show me your ID.
-Something's not right here.
-Yes, I'm inclined to agree.
I'm not missing our shot.
If they're inside…
We're going to catch them.
Got him. Cam 52.
What the fuck!
Someone's in our system.
Shit.
Okay! Let's go!
What? Shit!
What the fuck was that?
Fucking Christ!
Shit.
Damn it.
Freeze!
Hands up!
Slowly.
Where are you?
Fucking asshole.
Stop!
Police!
That's my bike!
Fuck you, asshole!
Shit.
Going to Old Town.
Watch out!
We lost him.
Out of the way!
Make way!
Crazy! How did I do that?
Stop the car!
Fuck off!
Shit, shit, shit!
Hello, my dear friends.
It's me again, your great safecracker.
I hope you don't mind,
but the video today…
I know him.
I know this guy.
Oh, fuck! This is the same guy.
Come to my office, please.
Yes. Now.
I found you.
Yes.
So I hope this is super important news
because I--
That's him.
The guy who opens safes,
the safecracker, that's him.
This guy comes out of nowhere. A German
guy who makes shitty YouTube videos.
He's not a criminal.
He's an outsider.
Then who is this guy?
How does he know them?
They found him like this,
through YouTube.
-Okay.
-Yeah.
Maybe he's a patsy.
Look at the poor guy.
They just dumped him on the road.
He's scared shitless like Bambi.
I almost feel bad for him.
And that's all?
-What? Yes, that's all.
-That's all?
Yes, that's all.
Super important information.
You could have told me over the phone.
Nice to meet you, Sebastian.
We are informed about the risk.
What do you mean?
Please follow me.
Who told you about the risk?
You. And when you contacted us,
we took action immediately.
What do you mean when we contacted you?
You did. And as agreed,
we brought transport time forward.
The safe left an hour and a half ago.
-You brought the transport time forward?
-Yes.
Last night,
when you informed us of the risk.
But the transport is already underway.
See, I told you
it was too good to be true.
Why?
It was planned for 5:00.
Hello. This is Interpol.
Are you aware that the safe
scheduled for transfer tomorrow morning
is the third in a sequence of safes,
two of which
have been robbed in the last 72 hours?
One moment, please.
Call the bank.
See if they'll authorize us
moving the vault sooner than planned.
Of course.
Call me if there's a problem.
You're welcome.
Five o'clock!
-Let her…
-Where the hell are they?
Let her! Let her go! Stop it!
Delacroix, asshole.