[hip-hop music playing]
[music slows, stops]
Oh, I need a massage.
[man speaking Spanish]
Oye, cabrón,
what'd you call me?
[speaks Spanish]
Fuck you, man.
Whatever the fuck it means,
that's not me, okay?
[speaks Spanish]
What the fuck?
I got back problems, okay?
[speaks Spanish]
¿Sabes qué?
The only puto here is you.
Okay?
[speaks Spanish]
Stop the fucking truck, man.
Stop the fucking truck, man!
We can go outside
-and I'll show you
who's a fucking...
-[tires burst]
[speaks Spanish]
[distant chattering]
They're all fucked up, man.
-[gunshots]
-[groans]
[whimpering]
[screams]
♪ Me, I am rolling
with my team kinda strong ♪
[car approaching]
♪ Money on money
over more money ♪
♪ Funning and horny,
we throwing more money ♪
♪ It must be the money
♪ That got the hoes be doggin', they know that I'm on it ♪
-♪ They see what I be on
-[barks]
-♪ They know that I'm a boss -[barks]
♪ That Gucci and that Prada,
I got money, I got dollars ♪
♪ And now that I'm on,
I'm on ♪
♪ I'm on, I'm on
-♪ It's all about that
-♪ Money, money
♪ Money, money
♪ I'm on, I'm on,
I'm on, I'm on ♪
-♪ It's all about that
-♪ Money, money
♪ Money, money,
I'm on ♪
♪ Somebody tell the disc jockey turn my music up ♪
♪ Swagger to the max, rings probably big as Jupiter ♪
♪ Captain on the track
♪ On the block,
but ain't no new kids, bruh ♪
♪ Melt the candle wax
make it hot ♪
♪ Even for Lucifer
♪ Indeed,
the tires swerving ♪
♪ And they think
the car was yours ♪
♪ When they see
a ... riding dirty ♪
♪ With a drink
and foreign ... ♪
♪ And you could see
they try to... ♪
-[music stops]
-[gun cocks]
They had more security
than we expected. Um...
There should have been...
Woulda.
Shoulda.
Coulda.
Come here!
You give me
one reason...
Huh?
...why I shouldn't blow
your motherfucking brains out.
It didn't...
It was...
We've done a lot
of good work for you!
Please!
-Did you know...
-You're gonna blow it all...
Do you know how important
this job was?
Because if you did...
then why'd you
fuck it up?
Huh? Why'd you
We... We didn't
fuck it up.
Rhetorical question,
asshole.
Now, either you're
incompetent,
or you're in on it.
Either way,
you're of no use
to me.
Just give us...
Please, please,
please!
Just give us one more shot.
Boss: Oh, I'm...
[sighs]
Are you out of your
fucking mind?
When we took out Gerber,
were we of use to you then?
What the fuck are you doing
out of the kitchen?
[chuckles]
Please, just...
Just give us a chance
to redeem ourselves.
Redeem?
Talk about redemption
with God, cocksucker.
Don't bring that shit
in here with me.
Books.
Boss:
Bullshit, right? Books?
Ain't nothing you're learning
in here that's gonna help
you out there, right?
This one's interesting though.
Come here.
Let me show you something.
[grunts]
Somebody get this
faggot out of here right now.
Get this faggot
out of here right now,
or I'm gonna put a bullet
in his fucking goddamn head.
[chuckles]
[cell phone ringing]
[beeps]
[vehicle approaching]
[rock music playing]
[boss screaming]
Where's my money?
Do you got my money?
Hey, Vet, how you doing?
Keeping busy I hear.
What do you want, Viejo?
[laughing]
Ah, shit.
I got a job
I want you to do.
Okay?
I got a target...
24 hours, in a warehouse.
After that,
they're in the wind,
they're gone forever.
I got my ass on the line
on this. I need your help.
I'm retired.
Huh.
But your son and his friends
aren't, are they?
Are they?
But they will be...
permanently...
if you decide
not to do this.
Why don't you get
Emmett here to do it?
He's chomping
at the bit as usual.
Well, happiness is
a warm gun.
Who is it?
Is that what
this is about?
You know how it goes.
[sighs]
What are the terms?
Viejo: Simple.
Take out the target,
and you and the Three Stooges
are free to go.
I'll send two of my men
with you to observe you.
They'll notify me
when you've accomplished
the mission,
and the matter's closed.
Then you go back to your job
cleaning assholes or whatever
the fuck it is you do.
[laughing]
I'm sorry, this shit
is just funny, toilet man.
And if I refuse?
You're still free to go,
but these three guys...
they're doing this shit
for the last time.
It's the end of the line
for them.
Time's ticking.
Yes.
Everybody hear that?
We got witnesses.
An oral agreement
is a binding contract.
I just read that here.
So word is bond.
[screams] What the fuck
are you doing here?
Get the fuck out of here!
Cocksuckers!
Shit.
[mutters]
Not me.
Don't fuck me.
I'll kill your son.
[hard rock playing]
Pull over.
I gotta take a leak.
It can wait.
Pull over.
I gotta take a leak.
[sighs]
Follow him.
-Man: They say you're
the best that ever was, huh?
-[urine splashing]
Well, that may be...
but a lot of good
that did Dahmer,
when they caught him.
Didn't help Bundy neither.
All I'm saying is, time...
waits for no man.
And you look like
you lost a step or two.
No offense.
I'm just saying...
you look a little sloppy.
[grunting]
What the hell's he doing?
Taking a shit?
I thought he said
he was taking a leak.
Man on radio:
He's taking a dump, boss.
And?
Man:
So what do you want me to do?
Nothing.
I'm gonna kill you.
You, let's go.
Come on.
Stay here.
Hey.
Yo, Henry, where you at?
Fuck!
What the fuck?
-What are you doing?
-Don't worry about it.
El Viejo's gonna flip out.
Fuck him.
What the fuck happened?
He decided he would kill
those two motherfuckers
back there.
Why the fuck
you do that?
[speaks French]
You might as well have left us
where you found us.
You're welcome.
Are you at least gonna tell us
what the fuck is going on?
I'm retired.
I don't kill people anymore.
So... so what now?
So now we find the target
and we get her to safety.
Wait, what?
I don't think you know
who El Viejo is.
I mean, he will literally
chase us down to the ends
of the earth.
Stop talking, slick.
So instead of finishing
that bitch off,
we're gonna rescue her?
Fuck that.
One full magazine.
That's it.
Don't waste it.
-You stay here.
-I'm coming with.
No, you're staying here.
What for?
There's nothing to do here.
There's plenty to do here,
and it will be safe.
I don't wanna be safe.
Are you suicidal?
Yeah.
Fine, but do it here.
Let's go.
Okay, you guys go.
I'll cover your asses.
Alone.
They're here boss,
alone.
Kill 'em all.
Get the target.
You hear me?
Kill 'em all!
Get the target.
Bye-bye, bitch.
[gunshot]
Man, this place
is fucking huge.
She could be anywhere.
If she's even here.
Why don't we just
call out to her?
What the fuck
is wrong with you?
You think we're alone?
You go left.
You go right.
I'll be upstairs.
We'll meet back here.
Get it done.
Hey.
We got company.
Any word?
No one's answering,
but I'll keep trying.
Okay.
-[door opens]
-Woman: It was fantastic.
Oh, honey, of course
we missed you.
It's never the same
without you.
Of course I do.
How could I stay mad at you?
Charlotte told me
to tell you, "Hi."
Are you... asking me out
on a date, sir?
I can't think
of anything better.
Love you too.
Jerk.
[sighs]
Crazy.
This diamond ring
could feed an entire village
in Africa for a year.
It's so beautiful.
Thank you.
And it's from there.
Yeah.
You like what you do?
My father was
in the military.
Brother, uncle...
It's all I've ever known.
So you always wanted
to be a soldier?
No.
I want to be a...
-princess.
-[laughs]
Chinese princess.
No.
Just a princess.
Well, I have everything
I've ever wanted:
Money, jewelry,
cars.
[chuckles]
I am living my dream.
But it's not enough.
No.
Why?
I don't know.
'Sup, girl?
You know where I can find
a pool around here?
No.
They said it was
in this area.
I was hoping maybe you
could help me find it.
Do you know who the fuck I am?
[gunshots ricochet]
[gun clicks]
Shit.
[yawning]
Don't mind me.
I had a long night.
So what's up?
You just chilling?
Yeah, nothing.
My name's Clayton
by the way.
-Ruby.
-Ruby? I like that.
And you are gorgeous.
[grunting]
Typical dumb broad.
See, you give a girl
a couple compliments,
and she melts
right in your damn hands.
The key to my ass...
[grunting]
[screaming]
Little Missy got
some moves, huh?
-Show me what you got.
-You ready for this?
You done fucked with
the wrong person today.
Come on!
The hell's wrong
with you, huh?
[screams]
[grunts]
[gasping]
[grunting]
-Give me the gun.
-No, he's done.
I had him.
What are you doing?
You don't see me
up in your business, do you?
What are you even
doing out here?
Go fucking help your son
and Mack.
From now on,
there's a chain of command.
You don't talk
to me directly.
You need something,
you talk to Junior,
Junior talks to me.
What makes you think
you can make these rules up?
You're not the boss of me.
I'm my own boss.
I don't know who the fuck
you think you are, old man,
but this ain't
the '50s anymore.
You're not needed.
[speaks French]
[shrieks]
What?
You can't touch a girl?
You murder people
for a living, deary.
Chivalry is dead.
You killed it, literally.
Junior: Hey!
Don't you ever put your hands
on my girl again.
I wouldn't have to
if she had a real man.
Oh, yeah?
Who's your real man...
[laughs] Okay.
All right. Yeah.
Yeah, you're a real man,
walking out on Mom and me
like you did.
Come on,
let it all out.
You know, I fucking
hated you growing up.
I wanted nothing
to do with you.
I hated you then,
and I fucking hate you now.
Whatever.
Shut up.
Get your head
back in the game.
Where is Mack?
He should be here by now.
Where the hell is he?
Let's go.
[Junior sighs]
Emmett.
-Emmett.
-What's up, man?
Are you familiar with
the Massacre of Thelonicus?
No, not at all.
Really?
Not at all?
Not at all, man.
Listen to this.
"The anger of the emperor
"rose to the highest pitch,
and he gratified his
vindictive desire
"for vengeance
by unsheathing his sword
"most unjustly
and tyrannically against all,
"slaying the innocent
and the guilty alike.
"It is said 7,000 perished
without any forms of law
"and without even having
judicial sentence
passed upon them;
"but that, like ears of wheat
in the time of harvest,
"they were alike...
cut down."
So the emperor sounds
like a real dick.
I mean, what are
you trying to say?
You want me to kill everybody?
[laughs]
I get it.
Exactly what I'm saying.
Let it come.
[man gasping]
Man: Deep breath.
Breathe out.
Vet:
What the fuck are you doing?
-Mack: I'm interrogating him.
-By torturing him?
You sick fuck.
What is wrong with you?
Oh, man,
you've gone soft.
[grunts]
Fucking psycho.
The fuck you do that for?
He had Intel.
For the remainder of our time
in this warehouse,
your decision-making privileges
are suspended.
Now, if you two
did your jobs...
my target should be
somewhere upstairs.
Let's find her and get
the hell out of here.
[sighs]
[breathes deeply]
Can't let you leave.
I have to go, Tony.
You know too much.
I won't talk.
You know me better than that.
I would never do that.
Take it up
with the big boss.
There's nothing left
for me here.
Please.
I'm sorry.
No.
-[gunshot]
-[thuds]
It's that bitch
from the desert.
Let's fuck her up.
Hold on.
We flank her end,
easy breezy CoverGirl.
No, we're not
gonna do that.
-Why not?
-Because she's not the enemy.
I'm pretty sure that she's
the one firing at us right now.
She's protecting the target,
the same thing we're doing.
We're not gonna
kill her for that.
Sir, I'm pretty sure...
Hey, pretty sure
means shit to me.
You know what it means?
It means I got a half
a piece of ass.
All right, "pretty sure"
means that I don't know
what's going on. All right?
I want confirmed kills,
all right?
Get me confirmed kills. Go.
[grunting]
Send more men.
[laughs]
Hey, Vet, the toilets are
on their way.
You can clean them
tomorrow, okay?
[laughs]
[thunder rumbling]
Viejo: Let it come.
Copy.
[gunshots]
She's fucking crazy.
Let's quit jerking around
and take this fucker out.
All right, Mack and I
are gonna go around.
We'll take her out
from the side, okay?
Let's go.
We're not murdering
this woman.
Not now, not ever.
Get it through your
goddamn heads!
What was that for?
Just ringing the doorbell.
What the hell was that?
It's World War III.
[thunder rumbles]
[thuds]
[sighs]
How many did he send?
All of them.
Anything I can do to help?
Be careful.
Vet:
I'm going after the target.
Go back to the base.
Take defensive positions.
Do not engage.
I'll be back
as soon as I can.
Let's go.
Be smart.
[screaming]
[gasps]
Hands.
-Hands!
-You got me.
Everyone's time to come,
I suppose.
You always dress like this
when you're being hunted?
Put this on.
This ain't no bathing beach.
You're not gonna kill me?
No.
Let's go.
[Target gasps]
Man:
Freeze, faggot.
On your knees.
Hands in the air.
Well, well, well.
If it isn't the man,
the myth,
the legend himself.
Remember me, dipshit?
You should have killed me
when you had the chance.
-[grunts]
-[woman screams]
[grunts]
Yo, Henry,
get your butt up here.
Henry:
I got dibs!
This is gonna
be interesting.
I'm gonna skin
this motherfucker...
alive.
Use him as a carpet.
You know...
some people have...
tigers for rugs.
Some people have bears
for rugs.
Only...
I'm gonna have Vet Jones
for a rug.
When are
we gonna do her?
Oh, we're gonna do her
all right.
We're gonna do her...
and then we're gonna
do her again.
[whimpers]
And when we
do her again...
[yelps]
she's gonna be... done.
Any last words
for you, dipshit?
How about...
"I, Vet Jones,
have been conquered
"by Henry the IX."
Man:
That's got a nice ring to it.
I like it.
That's good.
How about...
"Henry the IX is
my lord and sovereign...
"and I am honored
to die by his..."
[grunts]
[men groaning]
Come on.
Go, go.
Who are you?
I'm gonna stash
you in here.
Why are you doing this?
Would you rather I didn't?
-No.
-Then don't worry about it.
Can you tell me something?
I'm at least entitled
to that.
-You are?
-Yeah.
I don't know
what's going on.
Good.
Can you at least
tell me your name?
What difference
does it make?
Well, what should I call you?
Don't call me.
If I need something,
I'll call you.
-In here.
-In there?
-It ain't the Ritz.
-O-okay.
It ain't the...
[chattering]
Junior:
None of this would
have happened,
and we wouldn't be here
right now if we'd just stayed.
[gunshots]
Stayed home?
This is really
what this is all about?
You want me barefoot
and pregnant, that's it?
You don't want a strong woman
that will call you out
on your bullshit?
Well, fuck you,
'cause this is not who I am.
You have a problem with that?
[gunshots]
What?
[grunting]
[moaning in pain]
Junior?
We're coming out
right now.
Where's your friend?
He went off on his own.
We haven't seen him since.
Thanks.
Let's go.
Hey.
We're not done.
I need you for something.
You up for it?
What is it?
Vet: Guard her.
What are you guys
gonna do?
We're gonna go find Mack.
Can you handle it?
Aye.
Where have I seen
you two before?
We tried to kill you
a few days ago.
Sorry about that.
Yeah, your bodyguard
shot me.
You all right
on ammo?
Inside.
In there?
Yeah, where else?
[laughs]
No fucking way.
Ruby, come on.
Hey, why don't you
get in, Junior?
Or better yet,
why don't you get in?
I'll go find Mack.
It's for your own safety.
I can keep myself safe.
The lioness does the hunting,
in case you've forgotten.
[sighs]
All right, let's go.
A lioness hunts...
while the lion sits
on his ass.
[speaks French]
What?
[gagging]
How's the arm?
What do you care?
I asked, didn't I?
[sighs]
Look.
You can skip
the small talk, okay?
Sitting in a toilet.
Classy.
Excuse me?
I don't sit in shit
for no men.
Well, good for you,
but that man
just saved my life.
Doesn't mean you have
to do whatever he says.
Yes, it does.
See, I don't question shit
in the middle of an operation.
You stink.
So?
I'll take a shower.
A shower cannot
fix this stink.
You done
fucked up now, boy.
[groans]
[screams]
You got one shot.
Make it count.
Come on.
There we go.
Come on, it's almost over.
You're all right.
Come on.
Stand up.
Ruby:
If you give them an inch,
they take a mile.
You have to challenge men
every step of the way,
or they lose respect
for you.
[laughing]
What?
You just have a disease,
that's all.
It's called early 20s
bougie bitch issues.
Wow.
When did you come up
with that?
While you were sitting
in the toilet?
No, it's written
all over your face.
You scream it every time
you open up your mouth.
Okay.
-You wanna settle this...
-Like men?
No, thank you.
[speaking French]
Say what?
Nothing, bitch.
When is your sex-change
operation scheduled?
Hmm?
[gunshots]
As I was saying...
women are stronger
than men.
That's what you
don't understand.
Whatever, Ruben.
Junior: Mack?
Mack!
-We should bury him.
-No.
I'm gonna bury him
out back.
The cops will just
dig him up again.
He was my friend!
I can't just leave him here.
This is where he belongs.
He died like he lived.
Let him rest in peace.
Let's go.
It can't be like this.
It is exactly like this.
There are no 21-gun salutes
in this business.
Now, find Ruby
and wait for me.
Where are you going?
To end it.
Shut up.
I don't want
to hear you anymore.
No worries, a strong man
will come and save you,
fragile woman.
[footsteps, panting]
Hey, baby.
What happened?
It's Mack.
He's dead.
What?
How?
They shot him.
Why didn't you save him?
You should have
saved him!
Got there too late.
Where is he?
I want to see him.
You can't.
It's not safe.
I don't care.
I have to see him.
-Ruby.
-No, I don't care.
I have to see him!
-Where is he?
-We have to stay here.
We're moving out in minutes.
I don't care.
[speaks French]
Where is he?
Listen, please.
Stop shrieking.
I'm not shrieking,
and don't you dare
tell me what to do.
Fine!
I'll find him myself.
-I'm coming with you.
-Don't.
I want to be alone.
[sighs]
She just doesn't listen!
I know.
You know?
What is it you know?
Hmm?
You said, "I know."
What is it that you know?
Well, I was just...
agreeing with you.
[scoffs]
I know she doesn't listen.
You don't know anything.
What could you possibly know
about my girlfriend?
In fact, what are you doing
outside of your toilet?
I was just trying to tell you
what she told me.
What did she tell you?
Nothing.
She's just, uh...
-strongheaded, that's all.
-What did she tell you?
Specifically.
Speak, woman!
She said...
she wears the pants.
-You know what?
-Wait! What?
Okay.
Stay put.
[choking]
[whimpers]
[grunting]
[groans]
Emmett!
Not Emmett.
[grunts]
[echoing thud]
[groans]
Vet: Emmett!
Emmett!
Drum.
What's up, janitor?
Welcome back.
-You gonna play with me?
-You're a sick fuck.
What's that make you, huh?
What's that make you?
An angel?
I'm not a pimple on your ass
when it comes to killing.
Isn't that what
you used to say?
Oh, wait, you retired.
Yeah, that's right.
So what does that...
does that clean the slate?
All this carnage
is your fault.
Yeah, you broke
that contract,
so you're the reason
why all this is happening.
It's blood on your hands.
You're even more destructive now
than you were when you're...
when you were
in your prime, man.
And you retired.
What the fuck does that say?
-This ends here.
-Yeah, of course it does.
I know it ends today.
But I'm gonna
give you an option.
I'm gonna give you one chance
to walk away and surrender.
Leave with a little bit
of dignity.
Otherwise...
it won't be pretty.
I promise you.
[grunts]
We're even.
[groans]
[echoing thud]
Viejo over radio:
Emmett, what the fuck's
going on?
Vet over radio: Viejo.
Come on, motherfucker!
Let it come.
Fuck!
-They got Ruby.
We gotta go.
-Where?
They took her in a car.
Let's go.
-Is she alive?
-Yeah, let's go!
-Fuck.
-Asshole.
Do you want her dead?
Calm the fuck down!
They're not gonna kill her.
They're taking her
to Viejo.
Well, let's go.
We can still catch her.
No, actually we can't.
See what happens when you don't
control your woman?
Dumb bitch.
Call Ruby a bitch again.
Viejo over radio:
Hey, Vet.
Is that you?
That is you.
She's of no interest
to me.
Viejo over radio:
Yeah, well, tell faggot boy
I'm gonna mail her
to him in pieces, okay?
What do you want?
Viejo:
You know what I want.
Vet: You did good back there,
no matter what I say.
Junior:
No, I fucked up.
I let them take Ruby.
Vet:
Stop killing people.
I'm gonna kill
every motherfucker
that I see.
After this, I leave.
-Are you listening to me?
-What?
Uh... no.
No, not really.
What do you care anyway?
We're all going to hell.
This is hell.
I live
my punishment every day.
Haven't slept through
the night in 20 years.
Yeah, well,
I sleep very well.
Thank you.
That's nothing
to be proud of, son.
But I don't believe you.
You haven't crossed
that line yet.
I can tell
by looking in your eyes.
You still got
your humanity.
It's not too late.
Oh, fuck.
[muffled screaming]
No, no, no!
We have to save her!
No!
Vet: You can't go in there.
God damn it!
Fuck!
God!
Take me instead.
Viejo:
Shut the fuck up, asshole.
Put that down.
Let the girl go.
It's me you want.
Viejo:
You know what I want?
Bring me what I want,
and I'll give you
what you want.
Where are you?
Start walking south.
I'm staying with Ruby.
I have to do this.
Good luck then.
Be careful.
[mumbles]
Are you fucking crazy?
You've got to get
out of here.
Stop fucking around
and get out of here!
-You can't help me!
-I gotta...
I can take care
of myself!
I gotta figure this out.
-Junior!
-Shut up!
Don't you ever speak to me
or interrupt me like that again.
-It's just...
-Ah! Don't interrupt me.
You and I are getting
out of here together, okay?
I'm not gonna let you
fucking die here.
So get it through
your fucking head.
-Are you with me?
-Aye.
Are we in this together?
Oui, baby.
15 minutes.
If I'm not back,
I want you to drive
far and fast.
Don't look back.
Don't come back.
-Can I do anything to help?
-No, stay.
Viejo:
Hey, Vet. Vet!
You fucking screwball.
Let it come, motherfucker.
Come and get me!
Throw the gun forward.
[laughs]
Where is she?
She's gone.
It's just me.
I told you just to...
I told you just to bring her.
I...
She's long gone, Viejo.
It's just me.
Me for her.
It's an even trade.
I said...
don't fuck with me!
Now you fucked with me.
Let it go, Viejo.
What the fuck is it
with you guys, huh?
with you guys?
All noble and shit
all of a sudden?
What the fuck, man?
You're going to hell.
Deal with it.
You ain't getting out of it now
with the way you've been,
especially saving the life
of some fucking cheating whore.
You're going to hell,
because if you're
going to heaven...
[laughs]
...so am I.
They're gonna make me St. Peter
in charge of the gate, fuckface.
[muffled shouting]
[panting]
You sure you know
what you're doing?
Positivity, please.
I'm just saying.
Don't just say.
Why don't you focus
on your job?
What's my job?
Silence.
Okay.
-[snips]
-[both gasp]
Okay?
Hang on,
motherfucker.
Come again?
[laughing]
Oh, yeah.
Special guest.
What?
Look at your scrawny
fucking punk ass now.
You have lost a step.
You have.
You ain't got nothing to say?
You ain't talking.
Hey, look.
I live by a code.
I live by a code, man.
Ain't nobody forcing anybody
to join up with this life.
And if they do want to join?
Amen.
They know
the consequences.
You kill people for money.
So does the government.
That makes it okay?
A man's gotta eat.
-[Ruby breathing heavily]
-[Junior whispering]
-[sighs]
-Okay.
All right.
Let Ruby go.
You don't need her anymore.
You know, I've been
thinking that too.
I don't need her.
You know, I don't.
-Fuck you.
-[explosion]
Badavich.
Viejo: Get your hands off her,
or I'll kill you.
[laughing]
15 fucking years,
and not even a kiss goodbye?
A kiss on the cheek? Huh?
A phone call?
Come on, girl.
A motherfucking text?
You're cold.
It can't be
like it was before.
You tell that to Tony?
You would have never
let me leave.
You're god damn right
I wouldn't let you leave.
Why would I
let you leave?
Till death do us part.
Remember that, honey?
We took vows
in the eyes of the Lord.
[sighs]
I kept mine.
I was never
gonna talk.
I didn't care if you did.
I loved you.
And that's bullshit anyway.
Well...
You got what you wanted.
No, I didn't.
Don't turn this around on me.
You got what you wanted.
I wanted to live with you,
and love you in holy matrimony,
and I'm not getting it, am I?
No.
I'm sorry.
The fuck you are.
You fucking lousy-ass bitch.
You're sorry for me?
That's all you got for me
after 15 fucking years?
You and this piece of shit?
That your boyfriend?
Hmm? Hmm?
Maybe I ought
to kill him, huh?
You're both professional liars.
Be sorry about a fucking thing
but getting caught.
Don't jive with
your new morality, does it?
But look,
you shouldn't have to be sorry
because I loved you,
and I love you,
but I will see you in hell.
Okay?
Kill this bitch.
Target:
I still don't know your name.
Vet: It's John.
Target:
Nice meeting you.
Isabella.
Nice meeting you,
Thanks.
You're welcome.
[soft music playing]
[dramatic music playing]