Hey, babe. Finally.
Hi.
Nice to see you.
Congrats on the show.
You look beautiful.
Thanks guys.
You did so good.
The show is amazing, congratulations.
Gentlemen, not bad.
One, two, three.
Yeah it's like
a fixture.
She's everywhere.
She's like the opening of an envelope.
I don't mind
coming here at night.
I'm kind of enjoying it in a way.
It's winter and Yours.
Speaker 1:
Sorry.
So how are you two love birds?
Distressed huh?
Yeah. You should feel good.
Tonight was awesome.
It was really good.
Really.
It's exceptional.
That's what I'm just telling
It's better than I planned.
Charlotte:
Really?
I had high expectation,
Yeah.
My gallery delivers, but
tonight was beautiful and
the work speaks for itself. So,
You're
in your head.
Nothing. Nothing.
It's hard to take.
Compliments, but thank you.
Okay, so we'll stop.
No, don't.
Speaker 1:
Well, here we are.
After years of pestering
me, I finally had to give in and
let Charlotte have her own solo show.
Mostly because I think she
would have left us if I didn't, but in
all seriousness Charlotte, you
are so talented and beautiful
and so lucky to have all these
amazing friends in your life.
Congratulations.
Cheers.
Yay.
Speaker 4:
Charlotte. Charlotte wait.
Charlotte.
Charlotte, hey it's this is JG.
Listen, I been trying to reach you,
but you're not picking up my calls.
So I don't know how else to do this.
Your mom she passed away last night.
Sorry to be the one that had to tell you.
It was just, no one could
really get a hold of you.
Please give me a call back if you want.
I'm sorry. >>
So how long are you gonna be around for?
Until Monday I think.
You'll probably have to hit some of
the old stomping grounds before you take off.
Yeah.
Listen I'm sorry about the voice mail.
Just tough getting a hold of you sometimes.
I know.
It's okay.
Probably should have done a
better job at keeping in touch.
It's my fault.
So do you know the plan for
the funeral or anything?
I think it's already been taken care of.
She left instructions.
She really didn't want a
funeral or anything like that.
So, think it's just gonna
be like a party kind of thing.
Yeah, yeah that's right.
I heard that.
From who?
Just around.
You know how it is here.
Yeah. >>
I have to pick up the ashes tomorrow.
Well,
let me know if you want me
to come with you or anything.
Thanks.
Yeah, of course.
Hello, hello, hello.
The champagne is flowing.
I love it when Chloe starts popping
champagne bottles.
Do you want to open up a bottle of champagne?
I wish I wasn't.
Hey Chloe, remember being wasted at
Kim's wedding?
You were wasted? When?
Wasted.
Please, go inside.
I gotta go home.
So for now, I'll take my time.
For now, I can't
be bothered.
But I learned, a lot of things.
I fudged a lot
of numbers.
Half of my life I've
been watching.
Half of my life I've been waking up.
Birds in the sky could warn me.
Miss
Hey.
How you holding up?
I'm okay.
It's funny you know.
The last time we spoke
she said don't let those
other people get to you,
or something like that.
And I didn't tell her I was upset, or
that anyone was bothering me.
She just knew.
Like,
they always just know when we're hurting.
Do you want to step outside for
a minute, maybe get some fresh air?
Yeah, just give me a sec.
Yeah.
I'm going to go grab my coat.
Speaker 8:
What was that all about?
I'm sorry.
I just had to get out of there.
I don't know.
What are you doing?
Getting dressed.
I got to go home.
Give me a ride to
the station?
Yeah, sure.
You can still come with me, you know.
Yeah, maybe.
I love you.
I know.
Wait!