(Multicom Jingle)
(gentle music)
(gentle jazz music)
(people chattering)
(bright music)
(elevator chimes)
(telephones ringing in offices)
- You need a vacation.
Vacations work wonders.
(laughs)
- What are you doing here?
- I thought I'd pick up
my messages and my mail.
I wanna hit the ground
running in the morning.
Open it.
(laughs)
You know that weird thing
where you just wanna check
to be sure if you still have a job.
- You still have a job, Mary Beth,
but not until tomorrow.
Pot holders.
Oh, thank you.
Oh, gosh.
(laughs)
Why don't I take you
to Pergots for dinner?
- Christine, I can't eat
another restaurant meal.
There's more.
Now Harvey discovered this Amish buffet
right next to the motel.
All all you can eat for $12.99.
- Well, so don't eat.
You can tell me all about
exotic eastern Pennsylvania.
I'm in the mood to listen.
(clanking)
- I'll capitalize it for you.
Alice does not do great in the car.
Come over, have supper with us.
- Nah.
Nah, nothing comfortable domestic tonight.
- What?
- Oh, it's--
- (stammers) It's stupid.
It's really stupid.
I had a bank CD that matured today,
and it was the last one
that we held jointly,
you know, married jointly.
I told it was stupid.
- No, hey.
It's the little stuff
that always clabbers you.
- (laughs) Yeah.
And I know it's for the best.
Besides the damn thing
didn't even make 4%.
(laughs)
- Oh.
Oh, thanks.
(jangling)
(couple whispering softly)
- How are you?
- (giggling) Good.
(horns honking)
- Hi, John.
Love is the air.
- Are they still at it out to there?
- Better out there than upstairs.
I share a wall with that girl.
Her taste in mood music is Tom Waits.
- You don't it to Tom Waits.
You do it to Whitney or Anita Baker.
- You know, John, I'm
sure there was a time
when tenants knew absolutely nothing
about their doorman's love life.
Besides, everybody does
it to Johnny Mathis.
- You're the boss Miss Cagney.
(gun firing)
(woman screams)
- Get down!
(suspenseful music)
(people clamoring)
- My god, he's shot!
- Call 911 somebody's been shot!
(people clamoring)
Hey!
- The guy running with the haircut.
(suspenseful music)
(tires screeching)
(horn honking)
- Police get out of the way!
Joe, stop that guy!
Get out of the way!
Lady!
- I saw him, he was flying.
- Where?
- There.
Dammit!
- Jesus please.
Thank you.
- You got him.
- This is a witness.
John, this is Tran.
Would you take him inside please.
- Oh, boy.
- Thank you.
Now go on right inside.
- Come on.
- Thank you very much.
(dramatic music)
(horn honking)
Come on let's go.
- I'm all right.
I'm okay.
- I know you are.
- Get him up.
I told John to get him up.
- I can't do that.
- He can't breathe like that.
Sit him up.
- Get a look at who do it?
- Some.
Possible gang bang.
- In this neighborhood.
- Bastards, Gabriel isn't in a gang.
Help him!
- Honey, listen to me.
We can't move him, all right.
We can't move him.
It'll just make things worse.
Now the ambulance will be here any minute.
- Oh, god.
- Shh, shh.
(sobbing)
Sorry.
(sobbing deeply)
Come on, we'll wait for
the ambulance together,
and you tell me about Gabriel.
Tell me about Gabriel.
- He's a med student.
He's got exams so we
called it an early night.
(emergency sirens blaring)
I just met him last month.
- It's okay, shh, shh.
All right.
(chimes)
(people chatting)
- I don't see anything on her chart.
We're looking good for now.
But I don't think we
have anything important.
- Who's telling you?
I'm telling you.
- She isn't a minor, sir.
You don't have standing.
- Lee.
Detective Moyer.
- Hi, Lieutenant.
- I was hoping to see Darcy.
- So was I.
This is her father.
(sighs)
- [Christine] Mr. Wylie, how is she?
- She was almost killed last night.
She's traumatized.
- I spoke with the doctor.
She was in shock.
But now she's stable and alert.
I'm about to interview her.
- Mr. Wylie, could I buy you some coffee.
You must have been up all night.
- From Connecticut.
- Are you with the police?
- Yes.
But, I'm really a neighbor of Darcy's.
That's the reason I'm here.
- Is this your case?
- No.
- Then stay out of it.
- Why don't we both stay
out of it, Mr. Wylie,
and let Detective Moyer do his job?
- I won't be long.
(sighs)
- It'll be okay.
- You don't know that.
Don't talk about things you don't know.
- Where were you?
I saw about the shooting on the news.
I tried to call, and I
get nothing but machine!
- I dropped by the hospital--
- Well, you couldn't return a message.
Right there in front of your own building.
- I'm fine.
With that much luck I
could've nailed the bastard.
Mary Beth, we're late let's go.
- They got any kind of leads?
- Well, I saw him ditch the weapon.
So they've got that,
plus a half good physical description.
Plus, a perfect impression
of the sole of his left shoe.
- Where was that?
- In some excrement.
- Excrement?
Dog excrement?
- God, I hope so.
(reports clamoring)
- There's Mr. Kaplovitz there.
(reporters clamoring)
- Well, we're not getting
specific with our strategy.
Let it play out in the courtroom.
- [Reporter] Isn't that
really taking a risk?
- That's our to case.
- Yeah.
The guy is Jan Kaplovitz.
He's the defendant's new attorney.
I don't know who the woman is.
- I'm Raymond's aunt.
I've known him since before he was born.
- See, she's Raymond's aunt.
Raymond Bolzer's the accused.
- The City of New York
and the District Attorney's office
have got to look tough now
because that's the way the wind's blowing.
And they gotta find someone
to execute that isn't rich,
that isn't a black,
or His-Spanish or any color than white,
and you know that's true.
- Thank you, gentlemen,
ladies, we're running late.
- [Reporter] Do you have an
opinion about Judge Brice?
- [Jan] I'm pleased.
- Still drawing a crowd,
eh, Mr. Kaplovitz?
- We don't have your resources
in the District Attorney's office.
We have to do what we can.
- Oh, well, that explains
the white trash defense then.
- Trash, trash, you're the trash.
- Don't stoop to their level, Grace.
- Nobody's gonna call me trash.
(reporters clamoring)
- I got a nine-year-old
controls her mouth better.
- Well, it's her first
chance in the spotlight.
- I'm talking about you, Christine.
- No, they cropped it wrong.
This is wrong.
- [Mary Beth] Good morning.
- Ah, come in, ladies.
- Good morning, sir.
- This is my first look at the visuals.
You've gotta excuse the distractions.
Here just go on to the next one, Tam.
I think they're out of sequence.
Has Cagney offered our standard apology
for pulling you off whatever
you were working on?
- Yes, sir, she's been very gracious.
- Mm-hmm, of course, it's not every day
you get to work on the
first capital murder case
to be tried in this city in a generation.
- Nothing like the death
penalty to open up the coffers.
- Wrong, wrong.
We wanna see the head from
the perspective of the thing.
- What thing?
- The thing,
the passenger side.
- [Mary Beth] I remember this.
Those delivery guys that got robbed.
- [Christine] Mm-hmm.
- Harvey's cousins in the dairy business
were scared out of their heads.
All those delivery guys carry cash.
- This was Lester Purchase, age 57,
shot in the head while delivering produce.
- [Mary Beth] This was Mike Foy's case.
- Still is, I think, that's
what we're doing here.
Old Kaplovitz was outside just
now with the defendant's aunt
beating the reverse
racism drum pretty loud.
- Right, that's the kind of argument
that flies everywhere but in a courtroom.
It's specious, specious.
- How do you like the People's case, sir?
- Is this right, huh?
Alright, no, that's fine.
Just keep going, Tamala.
The case, no, I feel good, I feel good.
It's a good case.
We got two witnesses who
can put him at the scene.
He's got the, "I was
asleep in bed", alibi.
Plus, we've got physical
evidence and trace amounts,
so I feel good, I feel good.
Of course, you don't wanna go into
a trial feeling to confident,
particularly in the
first capital murder case
to be tried in this city in a generation.
(gentle music)
(machine whirring)
- Oh, boy.
He was shot on his wife's birthday.
- Mm, when Mike Foy went
over to give her the news,
she ran out into the
street in front of a car.
- Oh, no.
- [Christine] A real opera, huh?
- Was she killed?
- No, she wanted to die.
But she's still here.
The car didn't hit her.
Anyway.
(people chattering)
Our job is to troubleshoot
Kaplovitz's witness
list into chicken soup.
Our own Trayne if nervous.
We also have another very unofficial job,
which I was gonna tell you about before.
(telephone ringing)
Cagney.
He is.
Thanks, Bill.
(phone resolver slams)
Anyway, I think Doug
Trayne wants as many bodies
put between him and
Detective Foy as he can.
- Mike Foy?
What's not to like about Mike Foy?
- Well, he's in the
building coming to see us.
You can be reminded.
Attaboy, Mike.
Don't bother knocking.
- Look who's here?
- As I live and breathe.
- (laughs) It's been a dog's age.
- [Mary Beth] You're
a sight for sore eyes.
- So you gonna help us
fry this little bastard.
- Nobody fries anything
anymore, Detective.
It's lethal injection.
- How's Maureen?
- Oh, good, good, she's
doing the craft show circuit.
- Kids all grown up?
- Sure, half to year I come
home to an empty house.
- So, Mike, what do you
know about Bolzer's aunt.
Her name is Grace Pound.
Lacey's been going
through the murder book.
- We're working on it.
- Oh.
- Till today we didn't know
how close she was to the kid.
You look great, Mary Beth.
(laughs)
- You always did know when to
lay down a compliment, thanks.
(gentle music)
- [Christine] Hi, John.
- Hi, Miss Cagney.
- Thanks.
- What a world, huh?
- I wanted to tell you
how much I appreciate
your cool head last night, thank you.
- She's back, you know.
- Darcy?
- Yeah, her folks brought
her here this afternoon,
and they weren't gone 10 minutes
when she had one of her weirdo visitors.
- Well, if she feels like company,
that's not a bad thing.
- He was here and gone like that.
- Thanks.
(gentle dramatic music)
Hey, John.
Did you get a look at her parents?
- (scoffs) A look was about it.
Coming and going not one word,
not even to each other.
- You got off lucky.
(heavy sighing)
- So?
- Mm.
- Tell me about it.
(laughs)
(heavy sighing)
What homicide are you and
all these people working on?
(sighs)
- It's People v. Bolzer.
- I saw the news.
I know what it is.
Well, that explains you and
Chris working full time on this.
It's always gonna be money
when the politics are right.
- I have absolutely no qualm whatsoever
about working on a capital case.
You wanna talk about this.
We could talk about it.
- Honey, we don't have to talk about it
if you don't have qualms.
- I don't.
- Then better you than me.
(smoke alarm wails)
(dramatic music)
- Oh, my god.
(lock rattling)
(smoke alarm blaring)
- My board downstairs says Nine G.
(ominous music)
- Open up please!
Darcy!
Open up!
You smell smoke?
Get everyone off the floor.
Call the fire department.
Darcy.
Yes, fine.
Darcy!
- I've already called it in.
Wait here, John.
(ominous music)
- Darcy Wylie!
- [John] Here.
- John, when I tell you
kick the door right down here, all right.
You ready?
Now!
Again!
(dramatic music)
Darcy!
Anybody home?
(smoke alarm blaring)
Darcy!
Darcy.
- What is it?
- Oh, don't come in.
Call an ambulance please.
- What, what'd you find?
- Just do it, John.
(dramatic music)
Oh, Darcy.
(somber music)
(horn honking)
You're gonna have to
navigate this morning, okay?
I haven't a clue where I'm going.
- Well, fine.
But, I thought you knew this witness.
- I'm going to see him at his work.
It's a new address to me.
- Well, you're fine.
We're not even to Croft.
We're fine.
- Toxicology's in on my neighbor.
- [Mary Beth] Yeah.
- Heroin overdose.
- No.
- I should have read her as a junky.
- So accidental OD.
- Inconclusive.
I hate to think that she killed herself.
- Well, maybe it wasn't really suicide.
You know, junkies,
how do they know how pure the
stuff they're shooting is.
- Well, it was pure enough to up her nose.
- Well, that's handier snorting smack.
Now in the old days before AIDS,
you had to slam that poison in your veins.
You needed all the annoying paraphernalia.
Now be safe.
Snort it right up.
No mess, no track marks,
no fear of infection.
Just burn your brains and die.
- Her parents had her right
there in the hospital.
They had a shot of helping her.
You know, straightening her out.
(scoffing) No, not their darling daughter.
- Hot bed for a kid is heartbreaking.
- And, poor John, you know.
Good bless him John my doorman
he calls about the funeral.
He's gonna take a sick day and go.
"No service," he was told.
- Well, maybe some kind
of religious thing.
I mean, regardless what
kind of people they are,
Christine, still it's pretty
much of a rotten shame.
- God, you know, if I'd made some effort.
- Oh, come on Christine.
- Well, I don't mean
I could've made a big
change, but something.
- Oh, wait.
That was Prospect.
I'm sorry.
(sighing)
- I should be talking to the defense.
- [Christine] They're entitled.
- One of the lawyers rolled him downtown
in the Benz bought him lunch.
Then Kaplovitz sat with
him for an hour and a half.
Hey, Ronny!
Ron.
The DA is here.
You guys should've told him
this was a death penalty deal.
- [Christine] Well, it's not a secret.
- Well, I'm just telling
you he didn't know.
Kaplovitz must have laid it on pretty.
- Hey, Ron.
How's it going.
- Hey, how's it going?
- Good, good.
This is investigator Lacey, Mary Beth.
- Hi, Ron.
- Hi.
- Just wanted to keep in touch.
Let you know how the Bolzer case is going.
There's been another
delay surprise, surprise.
But, I think, we can
expect opening arguments
before the end of the month,
and then your testimony should come
one or two days after that, okay?
You're gonna do great I know it.
- They're gonna bring up my priors.
- [Christine] Only if the judge allows it.
- Everybody's gonna hear about
something that happened
to me when I was a kid.
- No, not necessarily.
The judge is gonna decide
if it's even relevant.
Besides the jury will hear
that you're working now.
You're going to school.
It'll all even itself out.
- My church don't believe in executions.
- What church is that?
- If you kill her, that's wrong.
If I kill you, that's wrong.
But if the State of
New York kills someone,
I'm wrong if I don't help them.
I mean, what kind of sense is that?
- [Doug] Did you bother
to point out to him
his obligation to testify.
- Well, I didn't wanna lean on him.
- Alright, I'm not gonna micro
manage how you handle him
as long as we're clear about the mission.
Ron Tally has to get on the stand,
put his hand on the Bible,
and identify Raymond Bolzer
as the person he saw
running from the scene.
Alright, I'll see you in court.
- Right.
- I shouldn't have challenged
the guy on his religion.
You never call somebody
on what they believe.
- What are you talking about?
- I said, "What church is that?"
You know, put him off.
- You didn't say, "What church is that!"
You did it fine.
This is just a nervous kind of case.
You're picking up on it.
Now we're gonna go see Mrs. Seguin
our darling prize witness,
and we'll both feel a lot better.
(soft knocking on door)
Mrs. Seguin.
Hi, there, Mr. Seguin!
I remembered to bring me
empty fruit juice can.
I was just telling Mary.
This is my colleague Mary Beth.
- How do you do?
Don't get up, sir.
- I was just telling Mary Beth
you should see all the things
that Mr. Seguin can do with an empty
32-ounce fruit juice can.
Why he grows tomatoes
out on the fire escape.
And, he can keep roaches
out of his cat food.
Well, all kinds of things.
I can't remember them all.
- Oh, lots of things.
I'm glad you come.
- Well, actually, we
came to see Mrs. Seguin.
But you know you're my guy.
Is she in the store?
- She's got the flu.
- I'm so sorry, sir.
- Do you think we might say hi?
- Well, she's no good,
but sure you can go in.
- Have any of the defense
team been here to see you?
- Yeah, they came.
I told them go to hell.
- Good for you.
May I?
- Sure.
You know, every time I go in
she's lying crooked in the bed.
(emergency siren blaring)
(police radio chatter)
- Here they come.
- Okay.
- A little room.
- Watch your step.
Down, easy.
(people chattering)
- [Doug] A coma.
- The hospital said diabetic coma.
- [Doug] Do people recover
from diabetic comas?
- We shouldn't count on it.
- [Doug] We can't even do a conditional
on video tape, right?
I mean, she's unconscious.
She's out.
- Right.
It's hard to believe.
We just stepped on a land mine, I guess.
- Boy, does this case need a break.
- Tell him we'll stay in
touch with the hospital.
- We'll call you back soon as we know.
- Do that.
(people chattering)
(phone chimes)
- [Christine] Well we did some
real damage today, didn't we?
- [Mary Beth] Don't kid.
I stick my big toe in
this case, it heads south.
- [Operator] Dr. Gross to Nursing Central.
- I'm gonna go see if Lee
Moyer's still at his precinct.
- About your shooting?
- Well, it's not my shooting.
But I'm gonna check in with him.
(gentle music)
- It feels like a hit to me.
But the victim Gabriel Ramos,
was exactly what Darcy Wylie said he was.
A med student,
and they met online at the movies.
The family's from Rhode Island.
Good kid.
Nothing.
- What about Darcy?
- Well, she's the more
logical target of a hit
with her drug history.
- Did you guys talk to my doorman
after Darcy died John O'Meara.
- I spoke to him myself
after the shooting.
- I know you did.
But after you talked to him,
Darcy was released from the hospital,
and John said she'd had a visitor.
"Weirdo", was the word he used.
- Male or female?
- I think male,
and I got the impression
he'd seen him before.
- I'll talk to him soon.
Thanks.
(dramatic music)
- Hey, Mike.
- Mary Beth, there's
somebody I want you to meet.
Delores Purchase Inspector Lacey.
- Mrs. Purchase.
- I'm Lester's widow.
Detective Foy has been keeping me informed
about all the goings on.
- Well, it's quite a case.
We're doing all we can
to get a conviction.
- I am to.
- Mrs. Purchase is a very big
believer in the power of prayer.
- No matter how good a case is,
we always need every single prayer.
Good to meet you.
(telephones ringing in offices)
(cans rattling)
(screams)
- What are you doing?
(washing machine whirring)
You think it's funny scaring
people in the damn dark?
(gasping)
(gentle music)
It's Mr. Wylie.
It's Mr. Wylie, isn't it?
Hi, you're Darcy's dad.
- The lights were too bright.
- Yeah.
Those Darcy's?
- [Matthew] I'm cleaning
out her apartment.
- Look I've got a washer and a dryer.
Come on we'll just take these things,
and we can come back and get
the rest of the stuff
out of the machine later.
This really is the basement from hell.
Come on.
(gentle music)
(cans rattling)
(machine whirring)
I think it's done.
Some of this stuff really does melt.
Would you like a drink?
I don't keep any in the house.
But I'd be heady to go.
- I'm fine.
- Okay.
Then you eat.
- Oh, no, thank you.
- Then keep me company.
Did you tell me your first name?
- Matthew, Matt.
- I'm Christine.
- How do you do?
- Hi.
Listen, Matt, I don't
know where you're from.
- Connecticut.
Stonington.
- Well, this is New York.
Here in New York we
send out for everything.
There are people who can
do that laundry for you,
and we've got cleaning crews
who will take toothbrushes to
the ground if they have to.
And we have movers who will pack
everything up for you in acid-free tissue.
All you have to do is say
the word and sign the check.
So why don't you just get
a good night's rest, huh?
And tomorrow you can just call
and send out for anything
that you want, and be back in?
- Stonington.
- [Christine] Stonington by lunch.
- No, I...
No.
- I understand.
It's a lot to do so soon, so.
- It's fine.
- Well, let me give you a hand.
- Christine, right?
- Christine, this is not your...
This isn't your problem.
It's mine.
Thanks anyway.
(door thuds)
(people muttering softly)
(sighs)
(snoring)
(door thuds)
- What's going on?
- The judge doesn't
wanna wake the defendant.
- Kaplovitz has petitioned
for another 30 days.
- Do you think Brice is gonna grant it.
- It's my guess.
- Motion denied.
(gavel bangs)
Any other business?
Okay, we're done.
Court is adjourned until
Monday morning 8:30.
(people chatting)
- Maybe you ought to consider
adjusting his medication, Counselor.
- I always thought the
ability to sleep soundly
was proof of a clear conscience.
- Yeah, what do you think now?
- Lieutenant.
- What'd you find out?
- Grace Pound lives with her
boyfriend in Staten Island.
- You got an address?
- Wait a second, Lee, there's more.
These neighbors say that in the past year,
a young kid matching
Raymond Bolzer's description
seems to have been living at the place.
- Get a search warrant.
- Thank you.
(gentle music)
(dramatic music)
(dramatic music drowns out voices)
- My boyfriend Andrew is upstairs.
Andrew!
- Hands up, Andrew!
(dramatic music)
(dramatic music drowns out speech)
- I repeat why do you have to be so deaf.
I can't believe anything you people say.
- Grace.
- You're clean put your hands down.
(dramatic music)
- Marijuana in the closet.
You got anything?
- Shoeboxes, this one's full of crayons.
- Alright, where do you want them?
- Those go here on the bed.
- It takes me back to my Thom McAn days.
(laughs)
- We have another watch.
And?
Nah.
We got a ring.
It's gold.
For a man.
- Is it faceted?
Does it have a lot of little
diamond shapes all over it?
- What else?
- Inscription.
Your husband's wedding ring.
- [Mrs. Purchase] Sure, it's
just a bigger version of mine.
You wanna see mine?
- [Mike] Yes, ma'am.
- What's the date of this?
- Sometimes it sticks
on my finger.
I'll get it.
- It's on the tape.
It was right after the homicide.
- [Mrs. Purchase] It hangs
up on the joint there.
There's see the inscription?
- [Mike] I can, but I can't read it.
- [Mrs. Purchase] It's
the date of our wedding.
- [Mary Beth And Mrs. Purchase] 12/28/59.
- I should've been the one to find it.
- What are you so happy about, Mrs. Lacey?
- I think I'm off to Schnide.
- And you, Detective?
- I'm leaving for the day.
Trayne is still working.
- See you tomorrow.
- Goodnight.
- Been good working with you, Mary Beth.
- You certainly have mellowed, Michael,
at least about me.
- Only about you.
- [Christine] Give my love to Harvey!
- Doorman was a big help.
- Yeah, good.
I'll be sure and tell him.
So what'd you find out?
- Well, it looks like the
weirdo that visited Darcy
after she left the hospital
was an old boyfriend.
- Thanks.
You know anything about him?
- Enough to make him our prime suspect.
- Really?
- He's a Costa Rican rich boy,
whose family doesn't want
him in Costa Rica anymore.
So he spends his time collecting art
and supplying to heroin to addicts
with money enough to have it delivered.
- This is going on in my
building, delivering heroin?
- [Lee] Doorman said he hadn't
seen him in several months.
(telephones ringing in offices)
(people chattering)
- Do you think Darcy
could've been clean then?
- Probably.
The hospital drew blood
the night of the shooting,
and when they analyzed it after her death,
proved she'd been clean.
This guy kept pursuing her.
Every week he'd send
her birds of paradise.
You know what they are?
- Yeah, it's a big tropical
flower, very dramatic.
- I thought they were a bird.
Anyway, he sent her
dozens of them at a time.
We tracked them down through the florist.
- So the theory is he's
a jealous boyfriend?
- That's right.
He didn't wanna see her with anyone else.
- Do you think Darcy knew
that's why Gabriel was killed.
- [Lee] Mm-hmm.
- So she kills herself
because she feels responsible?
- That's what it looks like today.
(gentle music)
- Kids.
(somber music)
You didn't come back for your laundry.
- Oh, no, I didn't, did I?
Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- I'm on the phone.
Would you come in?
- No, I don't wanna bother you.
- No, no, please, please.
Come on in.
(door thuds)
I'm sorry, Julia.
Someone was at the door.
Now I don't know what to tell you.
Perhaps your teacher.
How's Ted.
Uh-huh.
Tell your mother that...
Sorry I missed her and everything is fine.
And I'll call tomorrow.
All right.
Okay.
Dandy, bye, bye.
(phone receiver clicks)
Want a drink?
- No, thanks.
I see you've gone native?
- Huh?
- Sending out.
- Oh, yeah.
- Looks like you've made some headway.
- Well, mostly I pick something up,
and I move it to another corner.
- Is the family doing okay?
- Hard to tell.
- This stuff can weigh you mad.
Go home.
- [Matthew] Oh, no.
- Why not?
- I can't.
- [Christine] No.
- Nope.
- I can't be a father right now.
I can't be a husband.
(sighing)
So I guess I just,
need a second wind.
Time.
- Yeah.
You should stay here and take
care of Darcy's business.
But I'm gonna check on you.
Do you mind?
- Not at all.
- If you stop seeing people,
I'll be forced to send out
for one of our New York shrinks.
- He won't know what hit him.
- [Reporter] Coming up next
on the 10 o'clock report.
Are whites unfairly treated
in the justice system?
The results of our exclusive poll,
and we'll be in studio
with Defense Attorney Jan Kaplovitz.
- [Reporter] And now the
news from Washington.
- The guy is a genius.
- What?
- Kaplovitz he's a twisted
genius with this race thing.
You know, race is the
hidden agenda in this case,
and he knows it.
You know it as well as I do.
- Honey, Raymond Bolzer
is accused of first degree murder
in the commission of an armed robbery.
Under the new law,
that is a capital crime.
There's no race in that.
- You know who we have to thank for this?
At who's feet we can dump
the festering problem of race in America?
Richard M. Nixon.
- Watergate, we lost our faith
in government with Watergate.
- No.
- Vietnam, the secret bombing to Cambodia.
- No, though fundamentally, I agree,
that was an act of racism
as much as it was military strategy.
Come on, Mary Beth, think.
Algiers?
- No.
- Helen Kage and Douglas.
- People v. Rubiso?
- Racism, Honey.
- Feels weird white and gold uniforms
that he put on the White House guards.
- He ended the draft.
Nixon ended military conscription.
One at a time we thought
it was to be a great thing.
But let me tell you
something about the draft.
In an army with conscripted forces
everybody's got one thing
in common, Mary Beth.
I don't care where they're from,
what they look like, what race they are,
they all wanna get out.
Nixon replaced it with an
army of the poor and the black
to defend the interests
of the rich and the white,
which by the way were the
Kaplovitzs of the world are wrong.
The issue isn't really race.
The issue is poverty.
It always has been,
and it always will be.
You making tea or hot chocolate.
- I'm making whatever you like.
- Hot chocolate.
And that's my problem as far
as you're concerned Mary Beth.
The day a rich person is executed,
is the day I'm willing
to put capital punishment
on the table for discussion.
But until that day those
executions are only an indication
of the complete failure of the system.
- I work in that system,
Harvey, take it easy.
- Honey, your hands are clean
and your motives are pure.
But the people you're working
for are political jackals.
(gentle music)
- I think we've talked enough about this.
- I'm telling the truth,
Mary Beth, and you know it.
(dramatic music)
(doorbell ringing)
(clock ticking)
- I'm sorry about--
- What's the matter?
- I slipped, clonked my head.
I think it's still bleeding.
- Well, come in, come in.
Let me see.
Yes, it's bleeding.
Of course, it's bleeding come on.
Have you been working all night?
- I don't know, I guess.
- No wonder you're walking into walls.
You're not sleeping.
You really are a mess.
I know you don't wanna talk about Darcy.
But, could you at least
admit you are a mess?
- Sure, I'm a mess.
- Thank you.
This may sting just for a minute.
(gasping)
I know.
- Christine.
- What?
- It wasn't just the drugs, you know.
It was the lies.
Darcy lied, I'd let her.
My other kids lied for her.
Lies were everywhere.
They were all over the house.
We lied to each other.
We lied to ourselves.
- I'm sorry.
- No, no, don't please.
- No.
(gentle music)
- I've made coffee.
- None for me, thanks.
- Okay.
Well, I set out three
different kinds of cereal.
And I've got yogurt in the fridge.
- No thanks, I'm fine.
- Sorry, I'm afraid I
have to go. (stammering)
- I have a lot of things to do too.
- Oh, I know you do.
It's just that.
This time is just so screwy,
and I feel like I shouldn't leave you.
- I'll be fine.
- I know you will.
(gentle music)
(stammering)
I really am late though.
I really do have to go I'm sorry.
But you'll be all right.
Anyway,
I really do have to go.
And, of course, this is...
Thank you.
(door creaks)
(upbeat music)
- [Operator] You have 232 messages
that have not been heard.
- Hi, did you get my message?
- No, we have a problem.
- I don't need this.
- I left you a message an hour ago.
There was a fire on the D train.
- You're kidding.
- No, terrorism.
No lunatic pouring gasoline on himself.
Just a plain little
stinky electrical fire.
Smell my hair.
- I can smell it from here.
- Well, what is the problem?
- Attorney Kaplovitz got
on News One this morning.
I got that from Sharon at the desk.
I personally did not see it.
(laughs)
Kaplovitz goes on television
and he does his normal rant
about this being a white bias case.
And then, he solicits phone calls
from his viewers who agree with him.
But he didn't give his number.
He gave the DA's,
and everybody's voicemail is in overload.
What's yours 6544?
- [Mary Beth] Yeah.
- [Operator] You have 232
messages that have not been heard.
- Seems to be the magic cut off number.
I have 232 on mine.
(telephones ringing in offices)
- Isn't that obstruction of justice?
Our regular messages are in there.
He should be cited.
- Citing is too good for him.
Here, let's get started.
(machine whirring)
(people chatting)
Go away.
- It's Sharon.
- You have more messages do not come in!
- Your daughter's school called
and said that they've been
trying your husband all morning.
- Harvey's working in Jersey.
What'd they say?
- It's the nurse.
- Somebody brought a knife to school.
The nurse called.
Excuse me.
- Go, go.
Go, go!
These games.
Kaplovitz is playing games.
Her daughter could be who knows.
Mary Beth is wading through
public opinion calls,
and the school can't reach her.
What is important here?
What the hell is important?
Certainly not this!
(telephones ringing in offices)
I don't even know his number!
I'm going to do something that matters!
(door slams)
(heavy breathing)
I shouldn't have left.
(bright music)
- I know that.
(children shouting)
- She's okay.
She's okay, sweetheart.
She just cut her hand a little bit.
She's waiting out on the playground.
- Babe, I'm so glad you're here.
What was she cut with?
- A box cutter.
- A box cutter?
You mean that thing with a razor blade?
- Uh-huh.
- Some little punk kid comes
to school with a weapon.
And that's what it is
Harvey, it's a weapon,
and the school let that happen!
Did you confront Mrs. Troy with this
because I would love to
hear her explain this.
- Alice brought the box cutter.
- What?
- Yeah.
She started waving it around
like a martial arts type of
things and she cut herself.
(children yelling)
(church bell tolling)
- I'm sorry.
- [Mary Beth] I'm sorry too.
- Can I still go to
Brittany's birthday party?
- Next year.
(children yelling)
(whistle blowing)
(Matthew sighing)
- [Matthew] You like what you do?
- What do I what?
- I honestly don't know
many police officers.
Do you like it?
- Actually, I don't even think
about it that way anymore.
I do it very well,
and I've been doing it for so long
that it stopped being
about, "Well, do I like it."
It's just what I am.
There's something to be said for,
not that it's always comfortable
because that wouldn't describe it.
But, when I'm working, it's my world.
It's home base.
And I think that means more than just
do you like it or not.
- Maybe.
- Now that's not to say that
once or twice a year I don't start saying,
"Oh, I pissed it all away.
"I'm just a beat cop
who became a lieutenant
"and stalled right there."
But that's just the blues.
What incredible insight.
I don't even know what you do.
- Well, I started
importing exotic hardwoods.
The most beautiful wood in the world.
- Really?
- But I don't do that anymore.
My business grew,
and I got an offer that was irresistible.
So I sold my import business
and I invested in a small
telecommunications company,
which did very well.
And the years have passed,
and now I'm an investor.
- Do you like it?
- I'm good at it.
- You're a very successful man.
- Yes, I am, aren't I?
I'm a very successful man.
- [Harvey] I'm not saying
it's not important, Mary Beth.
I'm saying there's no reason
to keep her away from a birthday party.
- Can't it wait, please,
even for a minute.
(TV show blaring)
TV goes off please.
- This is just what my folks did.
Kid screws up, and suddenly
the whole house falls in punishment mode.
Events get canceled.
Traffic stops.
- No, Harv, we're not getting
off into what happened to you.
- I'm saying that my parents
were wrong, Mary Beth.
- No, Harvey!
Ordinary and normal are over
in this house for a minute!
I want this kid stopped cold by this.
- Don't you think the cut on the hand
is a pretty good lesson in
not to play with knives.
- That's not the lesson
I want her to learn!
- Oh?
- I want her to learn that you
can't prove you're a big girl
by intimidating other children.
There's an element of bullying in it.
- Bullying, Alice?
- I'm gonna put
a stop to it now!
- Well, I couldn't possibly
disagree with you more.
- I'm right about this.
- No way this is just a
case of forbidden fruit.
She couldn't resist.
So she's suffering the consequences.
Nine-years-olds learn
this stuff every day.
- Well, this nine-year-old
is gonna miss out on Brittany's birthday,
and she's gonna lose her
allowance for two weeks.
And there's no TV for a month!
- [Harvey] That is nuts!
- And bedtime is 7:30
until further notice!
(onions sizzling)
- God help you, Alice.
Your mother's learned a
taste for the hard line.!
- [Mary Beth] What did you say?
- I say keep your capital punishment
in the courtroom, Mary Beth.
Save it for Raymond Bolzer.
Oh, I'm taking Alice to the
birthday party tomorrow.
(onions sizzling)
- Oh, geez!
- [Christine] I love these pictures
every single one of them.
- She never got around to
putting them on the walls.
- They're Darcy.
Did she shoot these?
- She was good.
- Very.
Do you know how she managed this one?
- Everyone looks so
natural, nobody's posed.
How did she do it?
- Well, there are cameras
with the lens at a 90-degree angle,
so you're pointing this way.
But you're actually shooting that way.
- So the subject never knows.
- She still had a couple
of cameras I gave her.
And now surprise because Patina and I
we tried rewarding Darcy
for staying clean and sober.
So I gave her every camera I had.
I filled the refrigerator with film
and we never saw anymore pictures.
- Well, it sounds like
you were very good to her.
You paid for this place too, didn't you?
- Yes, I did.
However, we warned Darcy
that if she didn't obey our rules,
she'd have to make her own way
in the world without our help.
So, she takes up with a man
who makes his living selling drugs.
(slams candle in box)
Costa Rican.
And in the first month, he broke her arm.
Yeah.
And I went crazy.
Sight unseen, I hire a completely
unscrupulous private
investigator named Yap.
And we had long phone
conversations Mr. Yap and I
cooking up every scheme in the book.
And in a way it was
wonderful talking to a guy
who would do anything
if the price was right.
- [Christine] You're right that is crazy.
- Yeah.
- You never even met this man?
- Right.
So, (sighing)
We agreed to kidnap Darcy.
We called it an intervention.
So he snatches her.
We put her into Watch Hill for treatment.
My wife Patina never forgave me for that.
And what we had just collapsed
under the weight of Darcy's troubles.
- Was that the end of Mr. Yap?
- Oh, no, of course not.
He called now and then to
offer follow up services.
He even swore that Darcy was
seeing the drug dealer again.
Now Darcy swore,
with every gesture possible,
that it wasn't true.
"Please, daddy, believe me.
(scoffs)
"Please."
And I had to chose between the word
of a gross, greedy, unprincipled stranger,
and the word of my own daughter.
And I believed him.
For the rest of my life
I'm gonna have to live with that.
- You'd been burned before.
It's understandable.
- You can afford to be generous.
You didn't make the choice.
That killed her.
- Matt, somebody's gotta
cut you some slack,
and it's obviously not gonna be you.
So, I vote for me.
- So you're working Saturdays too, huh?
- Hey, trying to make
a dent in my messages.
You?
- I'm gonna grab a bite to eat.
You wanna come?
- Nah, I brought mine.
- Come on.
I'll bring you back.
(bag rattles)
See, you shouldn't eat alone.
This is a beautiful little girl.
And now this beautiful child
takes a weapon to school.
Harvey says I'm making too much of it,
but to me, (sighs)
it's like we're watching her innocence die
in front of our eyes.
- Yeah, well, you see more than him.
- [Mary Beth] No,
Harvey's very perceptive.
- No, don't get me wrong.
I'm saying because you were a cop,
you've seen more than him.
You've seen evil.
You've smelled evil.
You know evil exists.
I go through the same thing with Maureen.
Hell, I go through the same
things with the lawyers.
- [Mary Beth] Yeah.
- I don't care how many crime scenes
a guy like Doug Trayne visits.
- It's not the same.
- Not the same.
They don't know.
No, I don't think you're crazy
for wanting your kid to
stay descent, Mary Beth.
I think, it's the world that's crazy.
(bright music)
- You know I collected cameras for years.
My grandfather he was an architect,
and right after he died,
I started photographing buildings.
Of course, I tried to get Darcy
interested in it but no, no.
She only wanted to take
pictures of people.
- Well, I'm with her.
(bright music)
What do you think of that building?
- Why you like those buildings?
- Well, yeah.
- Well, then get out of the way.
Sit over there.
- Sorry.
- There we go.
(camera beeps and flashes)
(camera whirring)
- I'm surprised a gumball
doesn't jump out of that thing.
- Oh, you wait and see.
This makes beautiful pictures.
- You want buildings, listen,
this cities lousy with building.
Come with me.
- Watch out!
- Oh, I'm so, excuse me.
Oh, god.
Sorry.
(laughing)
How was your weekend?
- My weekend was productive.
I came in Saturday went
through the messages.
(alert buzzing)
- Ma'am, try again, please.
Have you got any keys.
- I know why you're happy.
- I swore I wouldn't let on.
You can tell.
- I was talking about the Yankee's
taking two out of three in Boston.
What are you talking about?
- You won't like it.
You're wrong, but you'll disapprove.
- A guy, a drinker?
- Doesn't seem to be.
- Married?
- Ladies and gentlemen, of the jury,
this is a capital case.
- How married is he?
- We will show you the
scene of the murder.
You will see how the accused
waited in a car borrowed from a friend
and how he followed Lester
Purchase from his delivery
at the Chadwell Market on the 1200-block
of Queens Parkway South
to the Zhukov Brothers
Market on the 1800-block.
You will hear scientific testimony
of a fatal shot to the head,
which the accused
delivered to Mr. Purchase.
And after he had stolen $513 in cash,
and after he had taken the life
of this hard-working man, this good man,
Raymond Bolzer took a
single gold wedding ring
from the third finger of
the victim's left hand.
Now, ladies and gentlemen,
that ring was missing for a long time.
But it was found in the home
of the aunt of the accused,
a woman who says she's
never seen that ring before,
a woman who never knew Lester Purchase.
There is only one link
between Lester Purchase
and the aunt of Raymond Bolzer.
And, ladies and gentlemen,
that is Raymond Bolzer.
(telephones ringing in offices)
(people chattering)
- [Mary Beth] I've got it.
Thank you, ma'am.
You're being used.
- You better believe it.
Used and useful, yes.
- This is not some knee jerk moral thing.
I'm thinking about what he's doing to you.
Hello.
Mister, uh?
Oaks.
Mr. Oaks, please.
- Am I happy?
Let me be happy.
- It's Investigator Lacey
with the District Attorney's office.
Thank you.
You come to me when it's over.
Tell me how happy you are.
- Cagney.
Yeah, Lee, hi, what's up?
Sure.
Sure, yeah.
Right away.
Okay, thanks.
- What's up?
- They're holding a guy
who could be my shooter.
I'm gonna go take a look at him.
- Great.
- Would that be
a kick in the head?
Beep me if you need me.
- Go.
Mr. Oaks, it's Investigator.
Nice to meet you too, sir.
You called last week
about the Bolzer case.
Sure.
No, no, sure.
It matters.
Where is your store?
(people chattering)
- I'll take a look.
- is this fresh?
- Mr. Oaks.
- Oh, you're with the DA?
- [Mary Beth] Investigator Lacey.
- I've been getting
called by someone working
for Bolzer's lawyer every day.
They don't let up.
I've been putting them off
because I wanted to
talk to you guys first.
I don't wanna say or do
nothing to screw things up.
- We appreciate that, sir.
What was it you wanted us to know?
- Well, it's a little thing.
But I'm sure you guys got it wrong.
- [Mary Beth] What?
- I played card with Lester Purchase.
I know him maybe, I don't know, 15 years.
I see him deliver in here twice a week,
and on Tuesday nights we played cards.
He never wore a ring.
- You can't remember Mr.
Purchase wearing a ring?
- Listen, you can believe
me or not believe me.
Don't play with my words.
I never saw Lester Purchase with a ring.
- Yes, sir.
Those are nice.
- They sure are.
- What'd get for those?
- Special today.
The DA Special we call it.
(laughs)
- [Christine] Number five.
- You wanna take another second?
- [Christine] It's number five, Lee.
- Thank you, ma'am.
- [Christine] You're welcome.
- That okay with you, Miss O'Neil?
- Yes.
- Keep number five in the pen.
- You get all the easy cases, don't you?
- Oh, no.
This will get gummed up.
Now we have to find out who hired him.
- "Who hired him?"
Your obsessed Costa Rican boyfriend.
- I called him in, you know.
He claims that when he
heard about the shooting,
his first thought was,
"It should've been me."
- What?
- He says
that the shooter mistook
Gabriel Ramos for himself.
That he had been threatened
to keep away from Darcy Wylie
or else he'd end up dead.
Nuts.
- [Christine] He didn't happen
to say who threatened him.
- (scoffs) No, he didn't have a name.
Of course, he didn't.
But he offered a detailed
description of a giant guy,
fat big, not muscle big,
who claimed to be a private investigator.
(dramatic music)
- And he didn't have a name.
- No, I said he didn't have a name.
Just a description.
He claims that he saw
this guy following Darcy
a few months ago.
Now I'm supposed to
locate this un-named PI,
and find out who hired him
to threaten my prime suspect.
(papers rustling)
I don't believe any of it.
(dramatic music)
But like you said, "This is an easy one.
"I should relax and enjoy it."
Still, you never know.
(gentle piano music)
(gentle music)
- Rough day.
- The ghosts are already dancing.
(sighing)
- Now the important thing is
keep breathing that's all.
Okay?
(people chattering)
You all right?
You look good, Ron?
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Now you just,
you wait here a sec
while I go see if I can
tell how soon before you're called.
All right, tuck your shirt in.
Sit down.
(paper rustling)
- I'm opening an envelop.
I'm removing a ring.
I'm holding a gold ring,
fairly large sized,
with faceted edges,
and an inscription inside.
- Can you read the inscription?
- It says, "12/28/59."
- Is this the ring found
at the home of Grace Pound?
- Yes, it is.
- Your Honor, entered into
evidence is State's 59.
No further questions.
(dramatic music)
- [Mary Beth] You walked
out of here yesterday
with the key to the file cabinet.
- Yes, I did.
Sorry.
- [Mary Beth] Give it to me please.
- Here, hello to you too.
- Thanks.
Christine.
- What?
- Christine, I believe that
the wedding ring I found
is planted evidence.
- What?
- I spoke with a very credible witness.
Lester Purchase didn't wear a ring.
- The ring is in evidence.
- The autopsy mentions arthritis.
Now look at his hand.
See his hand.
Well, his joints are swollen.
But a lot of people with
swollen joints wear rings.
- How'd Bolzer get the ring off?
- Well, I don't know.
- Remember the interview
with Mrs. Purchase?
- Yeah.
- I wanna play you
a piece of it.
Excuse me.
- Geez, Mary Beth.
- Listen to her.
- [Mrs. Purchase] On the
inside it says "12/28/59."
That's our wedding day.
- [Mike] You have the
ring in your possession?
- [Mrs. Purchase] No, sir.
- [Mike] Was your
husband wearing that ring
the last time you saw him?
- Here.
- [Mrs. Purchase] Dear
God, make me strong.
(coughs) Yes, sir.
(tape clicks)
- Her little prayer.
- She's just dreading the news,
"They're gonna tell me
they found his ring.
"Dear God, make me strong."
- Or, "Here comes the lie I have to tell.
(tape rewinding)
- [Mrs. Purchase] Dear
God, make me strong.
(coughs) Yes, sir.
- Mary Beth, you found the evidence.
- Mike Foy led me to it.
I think, he planned the whole thing.
- Hold it.
Hold it.
Did he enter the room before you?
- I went first.
- Was there ever a time when he was alone
with the shoeboxes?
- I was there the whole time.
- [Christine] Did you see him
drop anything into the box?
- No.
- Well, then cut it out!
- Where's the key to the file cabinet?
- I gave it to you two seconds ago.
- I don't have it.
Check your drawer.
- It's not in my drawer.
Don't you remember I gave it to you.
How'd that get in my drawer?
- Was there ever a time that
I was alone with that drawer?
(key jangles)
(sighs)
- The jury's already seen the ring.
It's out there.
Are you certain?
- It's a moral certainty, sir.
I can't tell you I saw anything I didn't.
(sighs)
- Does Foy know what you know?
- We haven't said anything.
- We thought in the event
that he was charged, sir.
- Hey, I don't wanna hear about it.
You're talking about charging
the chief detective in a capital case.
Well, there's nothing to do but drop it.
- There's no direct evidence
that it was planted.
- If Lacey can make her case to you,
don't you think that Kaplovitz
can find a half a dozen people
who knew the victim never wore a ring.
We're dropping it.
(sighing) We're gonna
pay for this big time.
Kaplovitz is way too smart.
We're gonna pay for this.
(groans)
(people chatting in offices)
- When are they putting you on the stand?
- Tomorrow.
No keep going, Alice, that sounded good.
- I'm sorry, Mary Beth.
You're being used
by Foy, by the DA.
You're just part of the politics.
I hate what they're doing to you.
- [Jan] Have you ever seen members
of the police department plant evidence?
- No, sir.
- In 20 years as an officer
in the New York Police Department,
have you ever seen a fellow officer
move, or alter, or fabricate evidence?
- No, sir.
- Are you aware of how restrictive
the Rules of Evidence are, Mrs. Lacey?
- [Doug] Objection, vague?
- Overruled.
- I'm aware of the Rules of Evidence--
- Are you aware--
- Can we let the witness
finish, Your Honor?
- I'm aware of the Rules of
Evidence and I obey them.
- Are you aware that most officers
consider these rules unfair
and impossibly restrictive?
- Objection, foundational?
- Sustained.
(sighs)
- Well, then did you witness
any officer in this case plant evidence?
- No, sir.
- Did you plant a wedding ring
at the home of Grace Pound?
- No, sir, I did not.
- Mrs. Lacey, are you
aware of any statements
by the District Attorney
that the first person to
be executed in this state
under its knew capital crimes law,
will have to be of the white race?
- Objection, foundational.
Irrelevant badgering.
- I withdraw the question.
- Did you refer to my
strategy in this case,
as, "White trash defense?"
- Objection.
When, where, foundation?
- I'll establish foundation, Your Honor.
- Proceed.
- Have we seen each
other before, Mr. Lacey?
- A couple times.
- And was one of those occasions
inside the courthouse in
the presence of Mrs. Pound?
- Yes, sir.
- And on that occasion
did you use the term,
"What trash defense?"
- That wasn't me, sir.
- Oh, but heard those words?
- I'm not sure of the exact words.
- "White trash",
do you remember those words?
- Yes, sir.
- [Jan] Do you remember
who said those words?
- It was said in a light manner, sir.
- Did Mrs. Pound react
to it in a light manner?
- No, sir.
- Would you like being called white trash?
- Objection, badgering.
- Sustained.
- Who used the words, "White trash?"
- Lieutenant Christine Cagney, sir.
You're a disgrace, Michael.
- I don't appreciate--
- I'm ashamed to work with you!
- Come on, you know as well as I do
Trayne's case was falling apart.
He's got his thumb up his ass.
- Yeah, what if this destroys the case?
You talked Mrs. Purchase into lying.
What are you gonna tell her to say
if they put her on the stand?
- She's not gonna testify.
They wouldn't take the chance.
Come on, you did just fine there.
They took their best shot at you,
and you got out alive.
- You are a sworn officer of the law.
What about your shield?
Did you think about your
oath and your shield?
(dramatic music)
- Can't leave it to
the lawyers, Mary Beth.
They'll ruin it every time.
- Wrong, Michael.
No, the only time it ever works
is when the police do
what they are sworn to do!
Come on, Chris.
(dramatic music)
I'm sorry as hell about
what happened on the stand.
- Don't you ever apologize
to me for telling the truth.
That private investigator
you hired Mr. Yap.
- [Matthew] Mm-hmm.
- You used the word, "gross."
- [Matthew] He is.
- He's big.
- Right.
- [Christine] And fat.
- Yeah, he's gross.
- How do you know?
You never saw him.
- What a memory you have.
- [Christine] (laughs) Yeah.
- I suppose when we talked
on the phone, he told me.
(laughs)
(dramatic music)
(elevator chimes)
- Yeah.
I sure will.
Hang on, Lee.
Lee Moyer he called twice already.
- I'm not here.
- She's ducking you, Lee, what can I say?
- I can't talk to him
right now, Mary Beth.
I know I have to talk to him, and I will.
I just can't do it now.
- You don't have to talk
to anybody, Christine.
That's okay.
- (sighs) I'm worse than Mike Foy.
- You are not.
(sobbing)
- He was just trying
to hold a case together
that was failing apart.
At least he was on the right side.
I've been withholding information
about a suspect in a murder trial.
I've been protecting a suspect.
That's why Moyer wants to see me.
And until I came in here
today I didn't care.
- I'll go with you to see Moyer.
But you have got to tell me everything.
- I think the father of Darcy Wylie
hired a private investigator
to have her boyfriend killed.
- And you've been protecting him?
- Yeah, I've been protecting him.
I've been sleeping with him.
- Did you think you had
a future with this man?
- No, that isn't why I did it.
No, I don't have a future with him.
- You know that what you have done
is objection of justice.
- I didn't care.
- Do you care now?
- Yes.
(sobbing)
Sorry.
Will you go with me to see Moyer?
- We can't go now.
Trayne asked to see us
before court starts today.
- You're right.
(door creaks)
- I made my opening
statement on Monday the 5th.
I've learned Mr. Oaks called
this office last week.
If you had met with him earlier,
I could've kept the jury
from hearing about the ring.
I'd like an explanation.
- I don't have an explanation.
- That's crap!
I don't accept that.
I wanna know what you were
doing on Friday the 2nd!
- I apologize, sir.
My daughter had a problem at school.
- Four days, Mrs. Lacey.
- There were hundreds of messages, sir.
Everybody in the building was swamped.
- Yeah, that's right it was a lot of work.
That's what you're paid
to do a lot of work!
What's your excuse?
- We're human beings, sir.
- I'm not talking to you.
I'm talking to her.
- I don't have an excuse.
- Don't give me that.
You're posturing I'm not
gonna let you pull that.
- No, sir.
- I have series questions
about your professionalism
and your competence.
- I do too.
- Come on, Christine.
We'll reschedule this meeting.
This isn't fair.
- [Doug] This isn't fair?
- No, sir, she has a
right to put up a defense.
She won't do it, come on, Chris.
You understand, sir?
- Yeah.
If Cagney wants to pull herself together,
I certainly have no!
(sighs)
(chimes)
- Don't make it all
complicated with Lee Moyer.
Just tell him what you know,
and spare him the love story.
I'm coming with.
- No, this is mine.
- I know.
I'd like to stand by.
- Okay.
(telephones ringing in offices)
(people chatting)
I know Mr. Wylie is in town
if you wanna talk to him.
- [Lee] Mm-hmm.
You get my phone messages this morning?
- Thought I'd come in person.
- The shooter talked.
(dramatic music)
He fingered the old boyfriend
as the man that hired him.
(dramatic music)
- The Costa Rican?
- You said, "This case
would be dead bang simple."
(dramatic music)
- And so it was.
(horns honking)
(engines revving)
(soft knocking on door)
- Hi.
My kids called today.
- Did you have a nice talk?
- Oh, yes.
They said they missed me, and I was glad.
No panic.
- You're going home?
- Yeah.
(gentle music)
- Well, that's good.
That was sort of the idea, wasn't it?
- Christine.
- Yeah.
- I don't know why you were sent to me.
But I know for certain that you were.
- It's good you're going home.
(gentle music)
(dramatic music)
(sobbing)
(sighing)
(utensils scraping)
(Lacey sighing)
- You have to let me do my job, Harv.
You have to respect that I follow the law,
whether that's gonna mean
that a person is executed
or a rotten cop gets exposed or--
- Honey, I do.
I do, sweetheart.
There's never been anybody
I respect like you.
- The kid in her room?
- Mm-hmm.
Sophia called, invited her for pancakes.
She turned it down without even asking.
She's doing her own version of
self-imposed exile, I guess.
I went way overboard, huh?
- No, not really.
What freaked her was having
caused a big fight between us.
- Well.
Do you wanna invite her
in to see us makeup?
- (laughs) No.
- I take it back.
(giggling)
(horns honking)
(engines revving)
- Mrs. Saigon, on the morning of June 4th,
you were waiting for the number 94 bus.
What attracted your attention
about the young man?
- He was watching the guy
taking in the vegetables.
I saw him watching.
- [Doug] And is that young
man in the courtroom today?
- Yes, sir.
- [Doug] Would you
identify him for us please?
- He's the boy at the
table in the gray suit.
- [Doug] For the record,
the witness has identified Raymond Bolzer.
(telephones ringing in offices)
(people chatting)
- [Mary Beth] Package for you.
- Oh.
So what do you think?
I saw you watching the jury.
- I think, Mr. Trayne
is not giving an inch.
I'm impressed.
What do you think?
Ooh, what's that?
- It's a camera.
A gift.
- There's a picture too.
- Yeah, of a building.
- No, it's of you.
It's a good one.
- He never took a picture of me.
(laughs)
I see you.
It's this damn camera.
(laughs)
(tissue paper rustling)
(gentle music)
Can I read this to you?
- Go head.
- "This gift does not compare
"with the gift you gave me.
"Matt."
- Matt.
(gentle music)
(bright music)
(Multicom Jingle)