Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
[music]
♪ Are you right? Can you see? ♪
♪ I was blind, I was blind ♪
♪ There is a world ♪
♪ Waiting ♪
♪ For you and me ♪
♪ Break us two
And break us three ♪
♪ And break us two
♪ I was blind, I was blind ♪
♪ Please, you see
Please, you see ♪
[eerie music]
[woman] She's going to be ugly,
I tell you, like a soldier
coming back from war with half a face
and his legs and his arms blown off.
- [breathing]
- [sighs, mumbles]
Oh, my God.
Are you crazy?
Get that morbid mask off
of your face!
Just... Why don't you grow up?
Get a bed pan ready
in case she throws up.
What an idiot.
Don't worry, Lily.
Oh, still cold from
Aunt You-Know-Who?
Aunt Naggie is only responding to
her never-ending period since birth.
- [woman gasps]
- She means well somewhere deep, deep inside.
Hmm.
She's going to be ugly,
I tell you.
And you... Oh! And you might
as well all just accept it.
Don't lie to her, okay.
Lily has just got to face facts
like a responsible human being,
like a soldier coming back from
war with half a face and his legs
and his arms blown off.
You know what? I bet she's going
to be more beautiful than ever.
- Ugh.
- Right, Lily?
Like at prom when you
looked just like Cinderella
and everyone in the school is saying
Lily's the most beautiful girl.
Are you smiling?
Good. [chuckles]
I can't wait to see you smile
again, Lily.
Okay, I think it's time.
Okay. Just want to check some
of your vitals.
Let's check your...
check your heart rate.
[heart thudding]
- [doctor] That's normal.
- [blood pressure gauge hissing]
That seems normal.
All right, let's do this.
Don't!
Like a mummy in a museum,
a morbid corpse underneath
all those bandages,
ugly as sin.
Would you like me to remove
everybody from the room
before I take off your bandages?
[Lily] I would prefer some stay
and some leave.
Would you like to be more
specific?
Oh, you all go.
I will stay here
with the doctor, mm? And Lily.
We'll handle this maturely.
[Lily] It's okay. Please, all stay.
Let's do this.
Oh, God.
I told everybody,
take her off life support.
But, no. [chuckles]
Now,
the devil to pay.
You f... I hate everybody.
[doctor] Um, let's do this.
[suspenseful music]
Oh! [laughs]
- [women gasp]
- I don't have any words.
Lily, you're beautiful.
[laughs]
- She's beautiful! Whoo-hoo-hoo!
- [woman] No way.
[man's laughter continues]
I didn't expect this to be
so perfect.
Oh, my God.
[laughs]
She looks like a Cover Girl
model.
[man] I knew it, Lily.
Your soul is too beautiful for
any earthly nuisance to temper.
Didn't think we would be using
this.
[playful music]
I don't see anything.
Wait, what do you mean?
I can't see anything.
It was a bad accident.
The optic nerve couldn't
survive.
- That's not true.
- You... you mean temporary blindness?
Cup.
Look up for me, please.
Lily, can you see any light?
How about now?
I'm afraid it's permanent.
[suspenseful music]
[therapist] With practice,
not only would you be able
to read letters but in vast
illustrations and graphs.
I can't force her hands
to read.
She needs time.
[therapist] Was it time
that you need, Lily?
I've worked with Lily three
weeks, grade one basic literacy,
and she still refuses to learn.
At this rate, grade two and three
will never see the light of day.
I'm sorry.
I did not mean to say it that way.
She just... She's not interested.
And if you can please send me
a check
and make sure that
it's spelled out to Lady Mandy,
M-A-N.
And out of sympathy
for a hopeless condition,
I shall ensure a 10% discount.
[door closes]
[dogs barking]
Ow, too tight.
Tight reins on a horse
is how we learn.
We walk one block forward
on this street and take a left.
[dramatic music]
[grunts] Ow!
Did you hear what I said?
Are you deaf and blind?
Deaf, dumb, and blind.
She refuses to walk,
so I'm walking.
- I'll walk her home.
- [jazzy music]
Good luck.
I'll be sending you
my doctor's bill.
What did you do
to that poor guy?
Hey, this asshole is used to
walking into walls his whole life,
so I just gave him
what he's used to.
[chuckles]
I'm so happy to see
that you still have
that evil sense of humor.
You taught it
and I never forget it.
Thank you.
I'm grateful.
[blows]
[scoffs]
You're living like you died.
Better if I was dead.
How do you know that?
I'd be able to see.
When I dream, I can see.
That's not the same
as being dead.
It's like it.
And how do you know
what being dead is like?
Something forbidden told me.
[dramatic music]
The ghost?
No.
You know I'm afraid of ghosts.
No. Seriously, tell me.
Amber,
I don't want to talk about it.
Because you're depressed,
you're going to ruin my life?
You have your own life.
We have been like two peas in
a pod since we were teenagers.
Now all of the sudden,
I have my own life?
Thanks a lot.
Maybe I should be the one
that dies.
- [suspenseful music]
- [inhales, sighs]
Do you remember
the smelly ghost in the closet?
[eerie music]
The closet door just swung open.
Quick, Lily, under the covers!
[laughter]
I hid under the covers
all night scared to death,
calling him the farting ghost.
[laughs]
Eventually,
we found out it was Alfred
who sat down,
who stole the leftover
Thanksgiving turkey.
[laughs]
[suspenseful music]
Is it safe to go out now?
Hold on. Let me check.
Coast is clear,
at least for now.
[owl hooting]
Then we'd scare each other
by saying,
"Look out!
He's right next to you!"
[laughs]
- The ghost is behind you!
- [screams]
[laughs]
That's better, Lils,
like the good, old days.
I was so scared we'd lose you.
You were so down,
but you made it.
You're okay.
You're here.
I'm not.
[suspenseful music]
[birds chirping]
So silly, habits.
[knocking]
[Lily] Yes?
Detective Bonkers
and Detective Truehart.
Thank you.
Lily, we haven't a suspect yet,
but we feel
you shouldn't be left alone.
Why?
Well, we're not so sure
this was an accident.
Why would someone intentionally
want to hurt me?
Not hurt you but kill you.
[ominous music]
Why would anyone
want to do that?
Lily, are... are you aware
of your inheritance?
Well, the inheritance
will go directly to you
because you lived
with your grandfather,
Jean-Michel Chevalier,
in France until you were 18.
And you were his favorite.
Now, if you were deceased,
that inheritance would be split up
proportionately among your family,
which your late grandfather,
he wouldn't have liked,
but that's the law.
Are you saying...?
Yes.
Look, please, just hire an
outside source to protect you.
Why can't you protect me?
Well, we have our hunches,
but no solid evidence.
My God, I just don't know.
Look, I understand.
It's not so pleasant of an idea,
but Detective Truehart and I would
rather err on the side of caution.
[sighs] I understand,
but I don't know who to call.
Well, look, there is a detective
who's quite good,
who I can recommend.
Although,
right now, you haven't received
your inheritance yet.
Is there, uh... would you be able
to afford this?
If available,
I'll have him call you,
and perhaps you can both work
something out in deferment.
How's that?
Okay.
Thank you.
Detective.
Whoa!
Sorry.
Still learning how to navigate.
No problem, miss.
I used to be a knuckleball
catcher back in the minor league.
[chanting in foreign language]
What? Just 'cause it's not
sentient doesn't mean it's absent
of experience, right?
Okay, okay, settle down.
Good afternoon, Lily.
And remember,
you're at a disadvantage.
[suspenseful music]
By the way, miss,
you've got any hidden cameras
here?
I don't think so. Why?
It could be an asset or a detriment
depending upon who set them up.
All right.
Have a good evening.
How are you this glorious
afternoon?
Oh, shut up.
Okay. Good start. [chuckles]
What's with that?
You're asking me?
It's your house.
[suspenseful music]
Your photo journal fell down.
[chuckles]
We were such troublemakers.
Well, you were.
You influenced me.
Well, it takes two to tango.
[chuckles]
Why'd you go quiet?
I'm curious
why the journal fell down.
Because it was hanging off
the ledge.
Things fall, gravity.
What if it were the ghost?
The smelly ghost was my dog.
You know I'm talking
about the real ghost.
There was no real ghost.
Yes, there was.
No, there wasn't.
What about the photo?
It's here somewhere.
[suspenseful music]
I don't want to see it.
Come on.
We'll be late for the lawyer.
[jazzy music]
[Amber] Here we are.
There is a chair right here.
I'm going to help guide you.
Lily, you are more beautiful
than ever.
[Lily] Only on the outside.
[chuckles] I beg to differ.
You are a lovely soul.
Not anymore.
Oh, leaving your frame
of mind to the doctors.
I will provide you with the one
thing I am insanely proficient at,
legal jump rope.
The... the cops haven't found out
who hit me and run yet.
So why do I need to be here?
Being that you survived,
that leaves you still
as the sole beneficiary.
[Amber] Meaning she still
inherits the $500 million?
Minus legal fees, yeah.
So, what are you going to do
with your fortune, Lily?
I don't know.
Well, I'm sure
you'll figure it out.
[grunts] Uh, young lady,
young lady,
would you please hand these
to Lily?
Oh, and here's a pen.
Miss Vegas.
Miss Vegas will act as witness
to the legal signing
of the transference
of monies from the trustees
to her personal account.
- [upbeat music]
- [record scratch]
Young lady?
- Amber.
- Amber, um,
could you please confirm
that all is proper and true
to which Lily is signing,
being that she has no reference of sight?
- [upbeat music]
- [Amber clears her throat]
[lawyer clears his throat]
"I, Lily Chevalier, being of sound
mind on this day, July 20th..."
- And so on and blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
- [Amber continues reading]
God created the universe
in seven days
and it's taking you longer
to read two lines.
It's all standard boilerplate.
Just sign.
Ah, women.
Here,
you're about to be
filthy fucking rich, girl.
- Mm-hmm.
- Anything else?
Ah. Thank you, dear.
It'll take one week for the
transaction to be completed.
Why so fucking long?
Red tape bureaucracy.
If you want to change the law,
become a congresswoman.
- [kisses]
- [sighs]
[Amber] Come on, let's go, Lily.
Oh, young lady,
can you please close the door?
Can you close the door, please?
You definitely cheated
on the bar exam
because there's no way
a slimy turd like you
who can't even get off your fat ass
to handle your client legal papers
could possibly have the energy
to walk to class,
let alone walk the talk.
Hmmm.
Sure.
Blind sign it, Lily.
I'd have someone watch over her
to make sure I get my money.
One, two,
three, four, five, six, seven...
[loud knocking]
Amber, Lily with you?
[Amber] No.
She's not answering.
I'll be right over.
Okay.
- [eerie music]
- [sighs]
[chuckles] How do you think
I make my living?
Hold this.
Thank you.
Oh, yes, almost there.
Well, at least no dead body.
Please.
I wonder where.
I might have an idea.
Come on.
[suspenseful music]
[Lily] You picked the lock.
How could you know that?
My senses beyond sight
are becoming more sensitive.
I heard of that happening,
but how could you know
about the lock?
Also, you couldn't be here unless
you checked the house first.
[Amber] We could have found
a spare.
No, I don't have one.
You ever think about opening
your own detective agency?
Someone's watching.
Been there before you came.
I'm going to pay that no good son
of a bitch a drunken sailor's visit.
Don't.
It could be dangerous.
Someone wants me dead remember?
Who?
I'm not that good
of a detective yet.
- Let's go.
- Yes, let's go.
[cane tapping]
Hey, Lily, hold up.
You've been practicing.
- Are we being followed?
- Yep.
How do you know?
Eyes behind your head?
Eyes in front of my head.
[doctor] Look to the right,
please.
Blind as a bat.
Oh, sorry, by the way.
Unfortunately, the optics, sclera,
retina, fovea, macula, and optic nerve
are irreconcilable.
Then how'd she see
the reflection in the door?
She couldn't have.
But she did.
Sometimes we misconceive certain
events to a particular element
and are mistaken.
Her eyes are gone.
She did not see.
Oh, this is inhumane.
You heard the doctor,
blind as a bat.
Putting her through
all these needless experiments
as if she was a guinea pig...
Just have some decency
and put her out of her misery.
[sighs]
What's everybody
looking at me for?
What are you saying?
You know what I'm saying.
Because I've said it before.
Have some decency
and put her out of her misery.
Have compassion.
I'm going to give you
five seconds of compassion
before I do something
that I won't regret.
[gasping]
Did you just hear what he said?
Oh, my God, are you going to
let him talk to me like this?
- Yes.
- [scoffs]
[sighs]
Assholes.
Good riddance.
Thank you
for all the melodrama.
I'd like to go to sleep now.
I would have slugged her.
[Lily] "As... for... the... end,
but... then... because."
"Your hands read for you."
"Letters to ponder
messages from yonder."
[frightful music]
[disembodied voice] Hi, Lily.
Stay away from the window.
[panting]
The doctor gave me
some medicine
to dilate the pupils
and calm the nerves.
[suspenseful music]
We may hand it off to the feds.
Tell me something new.
Well, no more miracles
till I get paid.
[sighs] Okay, green on the way.
- Asshole.
- [helicopter whirring]
Miracle if he gets paid.
[dramatic music]
[chittering]
Shh, squirrel, be careful.
Your trees are being used
to hide someone watching me.
[chittering continues]
Hi, Lily.
Oh, heh, sorry.
I didn't mean to startle you.
- I'm Dick, private eye.
- Oh, yes, hi.
Sorry, my guard was down because
my attention is on there.
Those four trees with the people
standing behind them?
Oh, yes.
How do you know?
I've been following them.
Can I sit?
[grunts]
Would you like a sandwich?
We have an extra?
Yes.
I packed one extra for you.
[bag rustles]
Why?
I know you were joining
my picnic.
Ah. Hmm.
Peanut butter and banana. Huh!
My favorite.
Yes, I know.
Lily, do you have any suspicion on
why anybody would want to hurt you?
Kill me dead?
I'm a little fuzzy on that one.
Uncle Fun I know
since I'm a little girl.
I can never believe he would
hurt me.
Aunt Jane, she's just timid
and nice.
She couldn't hurt a fly.
Aunt Naggie, whatever.
She's just a sour puss
and her own worst enemy.
What about, um, Amber?
No, blood sister.
Any blood shed by me would be bled by her.
Lily, if it's okay with you, um,
I'm going to keep an eye on you
until I discover the murderer...
- Ah.
- ...before you're murdered.
Yes, better that way.
You have a nice face.
How would you know?
I feel it.
May I?
[soft music]
- I knew it.
- [chuckles]
Yeah, well, I was...
I was hammered in the ring a little bit.
You know, I got the cauliflower
ears, crooked nose, messed-up teeth.
- [both chuckle]
- Not what I'm feeling. Maybe your alter-ego.
- [chuckles]
- How much would you cost?
[sighs] I wouldn't charge you.
Why?
Well, in order for me
to be my best,
my heart's got to be into it,
so no money.
You do this often?
Ah, it's my first one.
So why now?
Time to be my best.
Okay, you can work for free
and kill my murderer.
And then I pay you
with my inheritance.
- Fair? Deal?
- [chuckles] Okay, we'll see.
Okay, let's go.
Them trees are too busy for me.
All right.
[suspenseful music]
You killed her?
Not yet.
So this retainer
is premeditated.
- [Naggie] Yes.
- Let's do this another way.
After the crime, then you pay me
to represent you.
Mm-hmm.
Uh, you're forgetting
your money.
No, I'm not.
I don't do business this way.
After the murder,
you get me off scot-free
and you get 10%.
Of what?
Hmm. [chuckles] You know.
[sighs]
[Naggie laughs]
[phone rings]
[upbeat music]
Johnny Jerkoff.
Where are you?
I am on fire.
Keep playing, pumpkins.
I'm coming.
I can't tell you how many times
I've...
[sighs] Oh, sexy, sexy.
You're my girl.
Hey, you know that Virgin
Islands condo we keep renting?
Yeah, perk man.
I hate you keeping me
waiting like this.
Yeah. The Virgin Islands condo,
it's not a virgin anymore.
That's where
I'm deflowering it.
What's that mean?
I'm buying it, sexy, sexy.
Oh,
that is sexy, sexy.
Now can you hurry up
and get to me?
- Like this?
- Be careful. Yes.
- Ah!
- Oh, I've got it right? I got it?
- Yes, yes.
- I got it. [chuckles]
You're doing okay. [grunts]
Whoa!
I shouldn't have had you
tandem.
[laughs] I'm sorry.
- Are you okay?
- Yes.
Oh. [laughs, grunts]
You're probably better at this.
- Yes, just follow me.
- Okay. All right.
See? [laughs]
Yep, you got it. [chuckles]
[circuit breaker buzzing]
A bullet to the brain
is quick and efficient.
Strangulation.
It takes a little time
but will do the trick.
You need some muscle.
Stabbing.
You have to be careful
with blood spurts
getting on clothes
and everywhere.
I see.
Uh, what else is there?
You can strangle
with your bare hands?
- [shovel scraping]
- [grunting]
This is an umbrella, simple,
but also could be a weapon.
Or you can throw your victim
out of a window.
Just make sure
it's over 10 stories high
or the victim can live,
crawl away,
and reveal your identity.
Okay, but what if I shoot,
stab, strangle,
and then throw him
out a window?
Shh. Have some respect
for the deceased.
[grunts, sighs]
God, forgive me
for what I'm about to do.
[somber music]
Get a grip.
All be under the rock soon.
- Sorry, again, about falling.
- It's okay.
I try to make it a habit
of falling once or twice a day,
you know, just to bring me back
down to earth.
- [Lily] I can see that.
- [chuckles]
- Well, goodnight, Lily.
- Goodnight.
I'll just be out here
and make sure you're okay.
Thank you.
[grunts]
Did you just lie down
on the floor?
Oh, yeah.
Well, I checked in town
and all the hotels were booked
up because of the convention.
You know you can come in
and use my couch.
Thanks,
but against private eye rules.
But neighbors may think you're
homeless and call the cops.
Well, if that's the case,
I'll just, uh...
I'll show them this.
Oh, sorry, forgot the badge.
[chuckles]
It's okay.
Don't let the bed bugs bite.
Wait a minute,
you have bed bugs?
Only mice.
Great.
- Oh!
- Good luck.
Oh. [chuckles] Thanks.
[light music]
[owl hooting]
[suspenseful music]
Who's there?
[dramatic music]
[screaming]
Mouse, mouse, mouse! Oh!
Oh. Oh, hey.
- Dick?
- Yeah.
Are you okay?
Yes.
[electricity buzzing]
It's all clear,
except for the ghosts.
How do you know?
[dramatic music]
[sighs]
Ah, coffee in the middle
of the night.
Ah, I like the craziness.
Yeah.
It helped me sleep.
Reverse brain.
So, uh, you want to tell me
about the magic book?
I don't know.
Hey,
nothing really surprises me
anymore, okay?
I mean, I've had cases ranging
from haunted houses
- to alien abductions.
- [both chuckle]
Those are the boring ones.
- Really?
- Yeah.
I mean, I've had cases
that aren't even my dreams,
things that actually happened.
So look, if you want to tell me
what happened,
I promise I...
I won't laugh at you,
at least out loud anyway.
Okay.
I'll be right back.
[tense music]
- Boo!
- [chuckles]
Oh, you got a braille book.
Are you teaching yourself braille?
Yes, by myself.
That's really cool.
It's totally magic.
Will magic.
What, uh, does that say?
Come on.
Were you born yesterday?
[chuckles]
Let me show you.
[light music]
"You will fall in love."
That's exciting.
"Death is near."
Now, you're just trying
to get me going.
No, that's what it's saying.
What kind of a book is this?
This is a who-done-it,
dime-store novel?
No, it's a beginner's book
teaching letters and simple words.
I-I don't understand.
Dick.
Okay, uh...
All right, I understand.
Keep... Keep going.
"Dick and Jane
and their dog Spot."
"Dick haunted the house.
The abandoned house
near the seacliff.
Wait for others in the
neighborhood to show,
and pretend to be a ghost,
and spook them."
Wait a minute, did you... did you
hire a Dick to investigate me?
- Excuse me?
- A private eye to investigate a private eye?
Why, no.
Well, then how did you know?
The book told me.
Oh, right, some braille book
taught you about my past.
Come on.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to upset you.
[soft music]
Oh, I'm sorry.
Just bringing back a lot of
memories of my childhood and...
Well, you press one button,
and I'm 10 years old again.
It's okay.
[Dick] Listen, um...
it's getting a little late.
I'm going to go
check on my other client and...
leave you here
to heal from my temper tantrum.
Goodnight.
Don't let the bed bugs bite.
I'll see you in the morning.
Goodnight.
Book, where are you?
[suspenseful music]
[clock ticking]
[sighs]
[disembodied voice] You don't
need the book.
[panting]
[disembodied voice]
You can read me in your mind.
Who are you?
[disembodied voice] Now you
can read me anytime, anywhere.
Just think of me.
You need to sleep now.
You're safe for the time being.
Goodnight, Lily.
Who are you?
No, only one per mouse.
Only one trap,
it does not kill two mice.
Man, some people.
What do you expect for 50 cents?
Geez, give me a break.
Some people are cheap,
but not you, Dory,
and not you.
Well, not you, buddy,
you got to die for this.
I'm sorry,
but it's part of the game.
[ominous music]
[Fun] Happy birthday!
- [overlapping voices]
- Happy birthday, happy birthday!
- Hoo-hoo!
- You surprised me.
- [whooping]
- [Jane] Hey, birthday girl!
[laughter]
Come on, birthday girl,
help you down.
Watch out for the balloons.
Are you surprised?
[Fun cheering]
Hey, the merry-go-round.
- [indistinct chatter]
- The merry-go-round.
We were hoping
to catch you off guard.
There she is,
the birthday girl.
Go for a ride! [laughs]
[cheering]
Hey, the merry-go-round,
the merry-go-round.
- There you go.
- The merry-go-round. The merry-go-round.
- Happy birthday.
- Here you go, sweet Lily.
You gotta take that
'cause it's funny time.
Happy birthday, happy birthday.
- Happy birthday, happy birthday.
- [whooping]
Happy birthday, happy birthday,
happy birthday.
Hey, everybody,
it's time to have cake.
- Hey, let's go, baby.
- Cake!
- Cake, cake, cake, cake.
- We got it here.
[marching band music]
Time for cake.
- Happy birthday, girl.
- Happy birthday.
Birthday girl. Now, don't sit down
'cause you gotta have a speech.
- Speech.
- Okay, back up. [chuckles]
I don't know what to say.
Say anything.
Oh, leave her alone.
She just woke up,
probably wishes she didn't.
Please, Naggie,
just for one day, be kind.
It's her birthday.
Probably wishes
she wasn't even born.
Sounds like our Naggie needs
flowers.
Oh, my gosh,
thank you so much.
[laughter]
[Naggie] Oh, my God.
He just squirted water
in her face.
[laughter]
Oh! Oh, double whammy!
All right, girlfriend.
[laughs]
Lily, blow out them candles,
girl.
[blowing]
[laughing]
Oh, you can't see it, but it is funny!
[laughs]
Uncle Fun candle tricks.
[laughter]
Why can't he just grow up?
[party horns blowing]
I know.
I want to tell you all
something incredible.
The most amazing thing
that's ever happened to me.
[disembodied voice]
Do not tell them anything.
[carnival music]
[sighs]
Hey, birthday cake,
birthday cake.
Serve this puppy up.
Here it comes, here.
Oh, that was great. [laughs]
Did you see that?
That was a birthday cake slice.
- Yeah!
- [Naggie] Dessert.
All right.
Happy birthday.
[laughs]
You're an idiot.
- Oh, man.
- You're not going to eat your cake?
[laughter]
I am going to put that big
fork right into your brain.
- [party horn blows]
- [Fun laughing]
Alakazam, alakazu.
Watch this balloon.
I change for you.
- [pops]
- [laughs]
- [balloons popping]
- [yelps]
Oh, how enchanting.
Fortune balloons.
"Suspect one."
What's that supposed to mean?
"Suspect two."
Aunt Jane?
What does your say?
"Suspect three."
Aunt Naggie.
[scoffs]
"Suspect four."
Lily, there's one on your lap.
Can I read it for you?
It's braille.
You don't say.
What does it say?
"Have a happy birthday."
Well... [clears throat]
I don't know about you guys,
but I'm ready to party.
Come on.
Let's all get up and dance
and somebody turn on some music
and let's boogie.
[laughs]
[Fun] I love that game!
Come on, everybody let's party.
[laughs]
Hi.
They're gone.
Drunk and gone.
You?
Drunk? [chuckles]
You lied about your fortune,
didn't you?
How did you know?
Blood sisters means
we understand each other.
There's more suspects.
No shit.
Lils, you need a gun.
I can't see, remember?
What about that private eye
you have your eye on?
I like him.
There was some connection,
but he's on the list.
No, double shit.
He's a suspect, too?
Amber.
Yeah?
Is it possible Uncle Fun, Aunt Jane,
and Naggie would want to hurt me?
Not to mention
I'm a suspect too,
but you know I would never,
ever do anything to hurt you, Lily.
I love you so much.
I would give my life for you.
I know.
I can't believe our family
would ever do anything
to harm you either.
No, no, it can't be.
Let's not think it.
So when's the wedding?
Oh, stop it.
Are you going to invite me?
Am I gonna be a bridesmaid?
[laughter]
The smelly ghost just coming
by you.
[laughs]
- Stop it.
- Come on!
[laughs]
- Stop it. [chuckles]
- [sighs]
I love it
when you get all red like that.
Means it's serious.
Stop.
[light music]
Babe, check me out?
Shh!
She's going to hear you.
- Ah, it's all right.
- She's right there.
Gosh.
[birds chirping]
Thank you.
Cheers.
To?
To when you finally
get down on your knees.
[chuckles]
I'm always on my knees spying.
Well, you know exactly
what I mean.
[sighs] And you know
I'm not the marrying type.
Oh, geez, so you've been saying
for the past three years or so.
[grunts]
I feel like she's going to
hear us.
She can't.
But these blind people,
they have these, like, extra senses.
No. She's too far away
for hearing and smelling.
Don't worry about it.
I mean, why do we got to be here
anyway?
Hey, you know why.
[sighs]
Oh, geez.
Wow.
This is so true.
[Dick] What?
Your affections have been
neglected.
Bottom numbers 39, 40, 49, 48
and 00, could be my lucky day.
- [both chuckle]
- Are you ready?
Yeah.
[soft music]
[Lily] Good day, Mr. Squirrel.
You may be the only one
I can truly trust.
Oh, and there is a black cat
in the neighborhood.
Be careful.
[suspenseful music]
[crickets chirping]
Watch the traps.
Did your girlfriend
throw you out of the apartment?
- [mouse trap snaps]
- [chuckles, groans]
- [groans]
- [sucks in air, chuckles]
No girlfriend.
You're home late.
I'm young.
I want to enjoy life
as much as I can.
How old are you?
Old enough to know I shouldn't
be having this conversation.
Look, I'm just here to keep you
safe.
I'm safe.
Thank you.
You?
Me? I'm a professional,
so no worries here.
Have a good night.
I'll see you in the morning.
Just like that?
- Huh?
- You're leaving just like that?
What am I supposed to do?
Come in and check
if there's someone inside.
Okay. Sure.
[jazzy music]
Is there something
you'd like to tell me?
Uh, no.
I was just, um, looking at...
go into the rooms
and make sure that they're safe.
It's safe.
[Dick] Well, how do you know?
[Lily] My ghost.
Oh, yeah. You mean, um...
you mean your book.
My book is really a ghost.
Lily, have you been drinking?
No, but I can smell alcohol
in your breath.
Huh. I had a little wine
earlier.
[Lily] More than two glasses.
[Dick] Maybe.
Actually, most of the bottle,
Chardonnay.
California, 2008.
It was actually pretty good.
I, um...
Are you going to talk when you
can use your lips to kiss me?
Lily.
Lily, I don't know.
Lily, I don't know about this.
Oh, you don't know
if you're on or out?
- [glass shatters]
- [woman screams]
- [sirens wailing]
- Pity.
One less person on earth, huh?
[woman on PA] We had a 10-56,
woman jumped from the Graft Tower.
One less suspect.
- [helicopter whirring]
- [indistinct radio chatter]
[Lily] Oh, oh, my God!
I knew it!
[moaning]
I knew it! [moaning]
She was pushed.
How do you know that, boss?
'Cause she crawled.
If she wanted to die,
she wouldn't have tried
to get away.
Murder.
Yeah.
[indistinct radio chatter]
[lawyer] My condolences.
- Who'd want to...?
- [lawyer] Some scum of the gutter.
Sign there
and the house is legally yours.
I don't want it.
Aunt Jane willed it to you.
Take my advice,
pick up your pen,
sign right there.
Otherwise, the house forfeits
to the state bureaucratic crooks
who murder by red tape proxy.
Take some time off
from the hustle-bustle.
Go up north to beautiful nature.
Aunt Jane's house, it's far removed
from the noise and the tumult.
In fact, take the whole group.
All of you,
spend the weekend there,
recharge your batteries.
But my electric car
just won't go that far.
You'll ride with me.
It'll be fun,
a road trip to the country.
Nice. I can drive Lily.
See, there you go.
Now all of you,
get out of here and go pack.
And, um, bring some bear spray.
Wait.
There's bears up there?
Oh, yeah, and lions and tigers.
Just keep wearing
that perfume you got on
and you won't have any problem.
[upbeat music]
[sighs]
Smells beautiful.
We're going to have
a beautiful time.
What are you doing?
- Feeling the vibrations.
- Oh.
I miss the feel of driving.
I have an idea.
Huh?
You'll see.
You're going to drive.
Amber, I'm blind.
And I'm crazy. [chuckles]
We both are.
[upbeat music]
I don't want to get you killed.
You're doing fine.
Hey. A little...
a little this way.
Perfect.
Okay.
Just keep going straight.
You're doing great.
Okay. A little this way.
Oh, back to the left.
Good. Okay.
Just keep going.
Trust yourself.
You've got this.
We haven't passed
another car in 20 minutes.
Honestly, I think you're a
better driver without your eyes.
- [tires screech]
- Watch out!
[tires screech]
- [engine turns off]
- Did we just almost die?
[chuckles] Yep.
It was worth it.
[upbeat music]
[laughs]
[somber music]
- [Amber] Six steps to go.
- [Lily] Six?
[Amber laughs] Hopefully, your stair
climbing is better than your driving.
Thank you.
See, you're doing great. All right.
Almost there. Halfway.
There we go.
Get a little in.
All right. [groans]
What's wrong?
Holy shit.
Have you seen this place?
Did you see this before?
Come on, girl.
Straighten up.
Walk like a lady. This is...
[chuckles] This is fancy.
What... How did Aunt Jane
get this money?
[choir vocalizing]
[gentle music]
♪ Are you right?
Can you see? ♪
♪ There is a world ♪
♪ Waiting ♪
♪ For you and me ♪
♪ Break us two
And break us three ♪
♪ And break us two
♪ I was blind, I was blind ♪
♪ Please, you see
Please, you see ♪
A toast to Aunt Jane.
[laughs]
All right.
Give me your tired,
your poor,
your hungry.
Your weak.
Your huddled masses,
yearning to breathe, breathe.
- [laughs]
- Amen!
- Amen.
- Oh, well, maybe.
[chuckles]
- [faint knocking]
- [sputtering]
Who could that be?
How the hell do I know?
[chuckles]
- I guess we're going to find out.
- Come on.
[faint knocking]
Ah, Sharksdale.
[chuckles] Didn't think you'd have
all the fun without me, did you?
But you weren't invited.
Ah, page three, the small print.
E pluribus unum,
Sharksdale will have exclusive
and all inclusive visiting
rights whenever deemed necessary.
And, well, folks,
ah, it's necessary.
Blood diamonds from Murano?
Wow.
[clears throat]
I am here to babysit you all,
keep things civil,
make sure you don't tear
each other's hearts out.
[laughs]
Come on.
Where are the drinks at?
I want to get buzzed.
Am I going to have to order
some illegal drugs?
[sighs, groans]
[sighs, laughs]
[grunts, kisses]
Here's what I'm talking about.
Ah, whoo!
[Amber] You are so lucky
you couldn't see that.
- [knocking]
- [Naggie] Oh, who could that be?
Detective,
what are you doing here?
I'm here to serve and protect.
There's been a murder,
and to be honest,
any one of you could be next.
So think of me as police
hospitality.
How about that?
Let's get the burgers
and sangria flowing.
It feels like a funeral, huh?
[knocking]
- Hey.
- Dick!
- [kisses]
- How do you know?
-I'm a private eye, remember?
Don't trust anybody.
Don't worry.
I got my blow-up bed.
I got my mouse traps. [chuckles]
Hey, where is everybody?
In the back?
Let's party.
- [gentle music]
- [indistinct chatter]
[Sharksdale]
Hey, join the party.
Get yourself a beer.
Lily, oh, Lily.
Hey, how you doing?
How are you?
Good, how are you, man?
Yeah, good, good, good, good.
May I ask, who are you?
Oh, uh, Dick, private eye.
- Oh, good.
- Who are you?
Detective Bonkers.
Um, don't you know each other?
- No.
Well, I bid this closed.
Just enjoy yourselves like this fellow.
And, uh, as long as you don't
get into any trouble
or get on my nerves, you'll survive.
How about that? Hmm?
Same with you, man.
- Same with you.
- All right.
- [chuckles] Good time.
- You have big, strong arms, haven't you?
- Yeah, real strong.
- Real strong.
Whoa.
Fight, fight.
- My money's on the redhead.
- You're too angry, Dick.
Come on, come on, come on.
- [laughs]
- [Naggie] Ooh.
Someone should put her
out of her misery.
[suspenseful music]
Sounds of Lamet.
[burps] Well,
I think I'm going to go to bed
'cause I'm going to get up
early in the morning,
do a little bit of
bird watching,
and I'm going to take
the master suite.
Not a good idea to get
on my bad side, man.
Not a bad idea if you lock your
bedroom door tonight. [clears throat]
'Cause there's a killer
on the loose.
Hey,
are you going to keep watch,
protect and serve-a?
I'm not paid overtime, buddy.
The city's finest,
the city's finest.
All right, everybody.
I'm going in.
See you in the mañana.
- Maybe.
- Check things. [mumbles]
[grunting]
Well, your, uh, your blind vision
is better than my double vision.
[laughs]
Hold up, hold up, hold up.
[laughs] I love you, guys.
I love you.
Oh, yeah.
And by the way,
[mumbles] I am going to be up
all night
in case any of you are in
the killing mood.
Whoever the fuck you are.
[laughter]
[suspenseful music]
All right, ladies.
[babbling]
[owl screeches]
[eerie music]
[sighs]
[inhales, exhales]
Ah! [laughs]
They don't know
who they're messing with.
[laughs]
Whoa.
Yeah. [laughs]
[coughing]
[grunts, groans]
Don't mess with James Bond.
[laughs]
[snores]
- [knocking on door]
- [lock jostling]
[suspenseful music]
[snores, coughs]
[thunder rumbles]
[snoring]
[disembodied voice]
Death approaches.
Why me?
[disembodied voices]
Good versus evil.
I feel afraid,
like when I was a little girl.
[disembodied voice]
That is why I have come.
You're scaring me.
[disembodied voice]
You don't have to fear me.
It's yourself you fear.
[doorknob rattling]
[panting]
[thunder rumbles]
I want to live.
[disembodied voice]
You must face the fear.
[panting]
I don't believe you.
You're only my fucking imagination.
[panting]
[disembodied voice]
You see it?
Take it.
Feel it.
[eerie music]
Shh.
[Lily muffled] Leave me alone.
Come on, nuh-uh, nuh-uh.
You know what lies
in this room, huh?
Uncle Fun isn't having fun anymore
because he lies dead on the bed
with a knife in his heart.
Come here.
All right. All right.
Careful now,
careful,
you don't want to cut yourself.
[Lily] No!
Uh-uh, uh-uh, uh-uh, come here.
All right, and our next exhibit,
Aunt Naggie hanging
from the curtain rod.
- No, no, no! No!
- Uh-uh, uh-uh-uh, come here. Ready for this one?
Bend down. Here we go.
That's it. Bend down.
Look at that.
Oh, poor Sharksdale,
[chuckles]
shot in the head.
Let's go to the next one.
Come on.
All right. Come on.
[grunts] Here we go.
Your dear friend Amber.
Suffocated.
Let's go.
- [Lily grunts]
- [grunts]
I'll just tell you this one,
Bonkers' drink poisoned.
Please don't do this.
Let me go.
Uh-uh, uh-uh, uh-uh-uh. Let's go to
the bedroom, shall we, for the finale?
Come on.
Walk up the stairs.
There you go.
You got it.
That's it, you're going to take
a nice right.
There you go.
Come on, get on there.
[panting]
[Dick] That's everyone.
Just one left.
Don't you love me?
Didn't you?
- Maybe.
- [soft music]
What an evil, ambivalent love.
Maybe.
Careful.
Close to the bullet,
it'll hurt more.
There's no bullet
in the chamber.
Well, you would only know that
if you could see.
Oh, yes, sweetie.
20/20.
I see my guardian angel
has come.
- What?
- Look up.
[ghost speaking Latin]
What's going on?
[Dick] What's going on?
- Huh?
- [suspenseful music]
Love red.
The hit and run
wasn't as you said.
The truck driver
didn't have any idea.
You threw yourself
in the back of his tires
because you desperately wanted
to die.
You couldn't live with whatever
conscience you had left.
This had nothing to do
with your inheritance, did it?
This had everything
to do with your sick,
sick occupation.
You're a serial killer.
Did you love me?
Did you ever love me?
Nope.
Well, liked you a little bit.
[chuckles]
Where do you want it,
lover boy?
I give you that much,
but it has to be fatal.
[ghost speaking Latin]
The night is young and there
is so much prey out there,
lurking in the misty night.
What kind of an evil heart
has a guardian angel?
Who are you?
Good. Shoot the ghost.
I am your guardian angel.
Why do you look like me?
We take the appearance of the most
suited to show you who you really are.
Go away,
I don't want you anymore.
I've been trying to teach you right
from wrong since you were a child.
You have one last chance,
put the gun down.
Remember that story I told
you about when I was a kid,
and I haunted the house?
What of it?
It wasn't me.
- What?
- Look.
- That ghost.
That ghost was
my guardian angel.
Boo.
[gunshots]
I mean,
isn't this evidence?
I solved the case.
Aren't I deserving of a trophy?
Yes.
Ooh. [laughs]
[chuckles] Thanks.
To, um, 39, 40, 49, 48 and 00.
[chuckles]
- [grunts]
- [chuckles]
Yeah.
My lucky day
is now your lucky day.
Winning lotto numbers.
Oh, yeah, right.
Wait a minute.
Are you serious?
$75 million serious.
- Oh, my God.
- My God. That is so sick.
- [chuckles]
- Oh, my God.
Yeah, because it's sick.
[clears throat]
How do... How do you pull
these things off?
I don't know,
just my guardian angel.
Can we just go home?
- Who, me?
- And get all cozy?
Like we're old and gray and
we're gonna have three babies.
Well, uh, that just depends on
if there's any murders tonight.
- [chuckles]
- Oh, there's always going to be murders.
[laughter]
I'm Mr. Berenger.
Berenger, Berenger, and Berenger.
I guarantee you I can triple
your money in three months.
And by the way,
I think somebody murdered my wife,
so could you give me a call?
[suspense music]
Wow.
There you go.
Come here.
[light music]
[eerie music]
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull