(suspenseful music)
(doors thudding)
- [Paramedic] Coming through.
Out of the way.
- What have we got?
- We've got a 45-year-old female in V-fib,
been down 20 minutes,
initiated CPR and arrived.
- Okay, have you shocked her yet?
- Three times, no response.
- One round of epi, continue CPR.
- We're in.
- What have we got here?
- Female, she's in V-fib, down 20 minutes.
We've administered epinephrine,
shocked three times.
One, two, three.
- All right, Dr. Massey, let's focus.
What would you do next?
- Okay, she's still in V-fib.
I'd give her another round of epinephrine.
Defibrillator again.
- All right, people, let's go, let's go.
Where's respiratory?
Come on, let's intubate her.
- Is she gonna be all right?
- Are you a relative?
- Her son.
- Okay, look, I really
need you to wait outside.
- Okay, she's intubated.
Where are those paddles at?
- Charge to 360.
- Charged.
- Clear.
(defibrillator buzzing)
- Charge.
- Charged.
- Clear.
(defibrillator buzzing)
- What's going on?
Can't you do something?
- Nurse, can we get him
out of here, please?
- She's gonna live, right?
She's all we've got, me
and my little sister.
You gotta help her.
- We are doing everything that we can.
The best way for you to
help us to wait outside.
Please.
- Charged.
- Clear.
(defibrillator buzzing)
She's not responding.
Do you want me to call it?
(dramatic music)
- Give me a scalpel and a rib spreader.
- What are you doing?
- Gonna open her chest.
- Here, in the ER?
You're gonna perform open-heart surgery?
- I am just gonna get her started,
I'll let the surgeons do the real work.
Somebody call cardio
to prep a surgery room.
- Putting your hand in the patient's chest
and massaging her heart proper procedure?
- I don't know, I've never done it.
- Look, I realize that
I'm just a resident here,
but you do know that she's dead, right?
- Not until I say so.
(dramatic music)
You got that?
Not until I say so.
(blood squishing)
Come on.
(suspenseful music)
(heart monitor beeping)
- We got it.
(soft piano music)
- How is she doing?
- She's alive, because of you.
- Nah, she's alive
because of the pacemaker
the surgeons put in.
- I know what happened, you saved her.
- She'll be out for a while.
Why don't you go home
to your little sister?
- I called the neighbor, she's sleeping.
I'll stay here, if it's okay?
- Yeah, of course.
- Dr. Wyatt, I'll never be
able to thank you enough.
- You already have.
Sarah, could you order a cot
for Claire Randall's son, please,
and make sure he gets something to eat.
He's so stressed out.
- You know, I doubt the
other attending physicians
would have tried something so risky
to save that woman's life.
- Sometimes you just get lucky.
- That was great.
- [Beth] Do me a favor and...
No, this one here.
- You hear about her Lazarus trick?
- No trick, just good medicine.
- Well apparently, good timing too.
- [Doctor] What'd you mean?
- Have they named the new head of ER?
- It's not over till it's over.
(ominous music)
- What time is it?
- Oh my God, honey, you
are not gonna believe it.
There, there was this woman
in severe cardiac arrest
and Massey was ready to call it.
I probably would have too,
but her son was there and I don't know,
I just felt like I needed...
Jake?
Hey.
I thought you were listening.
- It's two o'clock in the morning.
I'm trying to sleep.
You should be too.
- Honey, I just held this
woman's heart in my hand,
I can't sleep.
- Mm, that's great, honey.
(suspenseful music)
(Beth chuckles)
(Beth exhales)
- Oh.
(ominous music)
- Thanks, dad.
- It better not be tuna.
- Peanut butter.
You try and keep your hands
in your pockets today.
- Honey.
- Mm-hmm.
(lips smacking)
- There's chicken
marinating in the fridge.
(hand thudding)
Come on.
Still nothing.
- Dr. Wyatt?
- Hey.
You're from last night.
- Jamie Randall.
- Right, Jamie.
How, how are you doing?
- Good.
- I just wanted to thank you
again for saving my mom's life.
- Oh, your mother's a fighter.
- Yeah.
Yes she is.
Well, you did most of the work.
The docs upstairs say
that she's doing better
and that she may get out of here soon.
- Well, that's great.
I'm really glad to hear that.
- Damn, that IT guy
was supposed to be here
over an hour ago.
- And what's the problem?
- Oh, it's just, you
know, won't work right.
- Sarah, you're beginning to sound
like one of our patients.
- And you could do better?
- Well, I, I don't know.
Maybe something with the LAN network or...
- Do you mind if I just take a look?
- Oh.
Jamie, you don't have
to do that, that's...
- No, let him.
I could be hours before
that IT guy gets here.
- Okay, try it now.
- No, nothing.
Oh wait, there it is.
- Yeah, that's what I thought.
- What are you, a computer genius?
- Software engineer.
Designer, really.
Mostly video games,
you know the kinds you wish
your kids wouldn't play so much?
- My son just got one
where the dragons are ripping
the arms off of people.
Did you design that video game?
- (chuckles) No, not that one.
I just do a lot of coding, debugging,
not the real nerd stuff.
- Jamie, I would hardly call you a nerd.
- I would.
I've been into computers ever
since I was a little kid.
- Oh, well,
thank you so much.
I, I, I guess that makes us even now.
- Not by a long shot, doc.
- Thank you.
- A nice kid.
(bells tolling)
- If you're gonna write
a paper on biodiversity,
you have to include an invasive species.
That's plants, animals, even microbes.
When they're introduced into a region,
they displace the native species.
- Yeah.
(knocking on door)
- Am I interrupting?
- I have office hours now, Tom.
- Oh, well I don't think Megan would mind
giving us a few minutes alone.
- No, I'm good, Professor Wyatt.
I really get it now, thanks.
Bye, Professor Wyatt.
Professor Saunders.
- What do you want, Tom?
- Stacy left me.
She took the kids.
- She found out about Jenna?
- Yeah, only because Jenna cornered her
in the supermarket near produce.
Apparently, there was an
incident with a cantaloupe.
Stacy's now banned from the market.
- Rule number one, never
sleep with a student.
- I was hoping you could
run interference for me.
- Ah, not a good idea.
- Why not?
- Because my contract is almost up
and I have yet to be published.
- Nothing?
- Nada.
- In two years?
- In two years.
- Oh man.
- Yeah.
- Look, I know you got your own problems.
Any advice on how to save my marriage?
- Well, I can't guarantee
that it'll get Stacy back.
Stop sleeping with your students.
- Oh, come on.
You've never been tempted by a co-ed?
The low rise jeans and their
big eyes staring at you
like you know everything?
- Yeah, sure, I've been tempted,
but unlike you, I didn't follow through.
- Well, I envy you,
and your marriage.
All right now, I'll see you tomorrow.
- Ah so, Dr. Wyatt.
As I'm sure you expected,
cardiology raised a stink
over your handling of
the Randall woman's case,
which didn't exactly follow protocol.
- Sir, I only did what I thought
was necessary at the time.
I certainly didn't mean to...
- No, no, I, I believe you, Beth.
Let me finish.
It was the cardiologist on
call who raised the stink,
but as chief of staff, I told him that
we're in the business of saving lives
and we were damn lucky to
have you there last night.
- Well, I appreciate that, sir.
Thank you very much.
- And I think we'd be damn lucky
to have you as the new head of ER.
- Really?
- The board of trustees hasn't made
their final decision yet.
I'm sure you know that Dr. Doyle
is in contention for the job?
- Yes, I do.
- He's a bit of a cold
fish, if you ask my opinion,
but he's definitely competent.
Plus he has seniority over you.
- I'm aware of that, sir.
- And then there's the matter
that he has no family to speak of,
no other demands on his time
to take his focus away from the job.
- Sir, I am aware of that too,
but my family obligations
have never interfered with my work.
- I believe you, Beth.
So I'd like your professional opinion.
Take a look at these
residency applications
and tell me which of the
hundreds that we've received
we should consider accepting
in our little family.
- Okay.
- [PA Announcer] Dr.
Schadeling to obstetrics,
Dr. Schadeling to obstetrics.
- [Beth] Hey everybody, I'm home.
- Hey.
- Hey mom.
We're gulping down pizza.
- Yeah, I see that.
Sorry I'm late.
- We're used to it.
- Friedman threw something
at me last minute.
But he also told me that
I'm firmly in the running
for becoming head of ER.
- Ah, I would've expected nothing less.
Now, would you like cheese or pepperoni?
- Pizza, Jake?
Can we talk about all this
junk food for the kids?
- Oh, come on, Beth, it's
only a couple of pizzas.
- I told you that there was chicken
in the fridge this morning.
All you had to do is throw
it in the oven for an hour.
- Yeah, well I have midterms to grade,
and pizza just seemed
like the easiest thing.
- I'm trying to be a
responsible mother here,
but I'm working 70 hours a week
and I can't always make
a home cooked dinner,
but I think I can do that in pizza.
- Well, maybe you should
stop trying so hard
and just be here more often.
- I'm doing my best, Jake.
- Yeah, but is it good enough?
(ominous music)
- Maybe he's right.
Maybe I can't have it all.
What do you think?
(ominous music)
In real life?
(serene soft pop music)
Check, please.
- You must be Dr. Beth.
I'm Finn_74.
You weren't leaving, were you?
I'm not that late.
Oh, maybe I am.
Well, then I'm glad I caught you.
- Um...
- That will be on my tab,
and I'll have a Chardonnay.
- I think there's been
some kind of mistake.
- Uh no, I don't think so.
Hey, you wanna get an appetizer?
The stuffed mushrooms here are to die for.
And, you know, I haven't
had a thing to eat all day.
- You know, I, I really have to go.
- What's wrong?
- I thought I was meeting a man.
- And why would you think that?
- Um, your name, Finn.
I, is that your last name?
- No, Connors is my last name.
My first name is Finn.
My dad was a Mark Twain nut.
- What about the flirting?
- So you admit you were flirting?
- No, I was, it didn't...
It was harmless.
- Exactly.
Look Beth, you may have
thought you were meeting a man,
I just thought I was meeting a friend.
I mean, really, what did you
expect to happen tonight?
- I'm not a lesbian.
- I never thought you were.
- Then why did you wanna meet me?
- Because you seemed really nice.
I mean, we really made a connection online
and we're in the same line of work.
No, I'm not a doctor but...
I, I really like being a paramedic,
it's just, it's just hard sometimes.
And, you know, you seemed to understand.
The truth is I've been, um,
on a leave of absence
since my partner committed suicide.
- I'm sorry.
- Thanks.
We just, we just really hit it off and...
I could use a friend right now.
- Well...
all right, then.
To friends.
- To friendship.
(glasses clinking)
- So how'd the drinks turn out?
- Uh okay, I guess.
- Friedman or the board of trustees
give you any clue which way they're going?
- No, uh-huh.
Mostly shop talk about the hospital.
- You have to go to the bar for that?
- Oh, they're having
dinner there afterwards.
(Beth knocking on door)
You paged me, sir.
- Dr. Wyatt.
Come in, have a seat.
Beth, there's been a lot
of discussion at the board
as to who should run the ER department,
but in the end it came down to
the welfare of the patients.
As you know, we're not run by an HMO,
we're a nonprofit hospital run
by a religious organization
and there are certain ethical principles
which need to be upheld.
Your dedication to your patients
demonstrates a deep, ethical commitment
which the board finds exemplary.
What I'm trying to say is
congratulations, Dr. Wyatt.
You're St. Catherine's new head of ER.
- Thank you so much, sir.
And the board.
- Well, don't thank us yet.
There'll be administrative duties
and various committees to sit on,
as well as your regular duties in the ER.
You'll be going straight from
the frying pan into the fire.
- And I will be ready for it.
Thank you, sir.
You won't be sorry.
- I hope not.
- [PA Announcer] Dr. Adams, to the ER.
- Dr. Wyatt,
I understand Congratulations are in order.
- Well, you know already.
- Well the chief told me first
and wanted to smooth things over in case
I had any ideas about
transferring to another hospital.
- So you're staying?
- Of course.
I know that board's
decision wasn't personal
and you're their perfect
family values person,
someone they can trot out at
fundraisers to attract donors.
- Well, it is so nice to know
that we will still be
working together, Doyle.
Saint Catherine's just wouldn't
be the same without you.
Now if you'll excuse me,
I need to check with
administration about my new office.
(Dr. Doyle sighs)
Hello.
Hey.
Guess what?
I got the promotion.
- Yay, mom!
(Beth giggles)
Can I have a promotion too?
- How about the chief of cookies?
- Cool.
- What?
What's the matter?
- Wow.
I didn't think you'd get it.
- Well that explains the
complete lack of support.
- Oh, come on Beth,
you want me to congratulate you
on your new 90-hour a week job?
What about my career?
The dean made it very clear
I have to publish if I want tenure.
Now how am I supposed to do that
if I'm the only one
looking out for the kids?
- Terri, would you take
your brother upstairs
and get ready for bed?
- But it's only 7:30.
- Do you really want them hearing
what we have to say to each other?
- Come on, kids, upstairs, let's go.
Scoot.
- You knew.
You knew this is what I wanted
and you can't start throwing
out the you missed birthdays
then missed recitals and
missed dinners and the,
I mean, it's not, it's not fair.
- And I'm the bad guy for even
thinking about competing
with a sick and dying?
- Hey, my family is my
number one priority.
- Oh, come on, Beth.
If you're gonna go into that quality time
versus quantity argument,
then you should know that you're not
giving your family either one.
Maybe if I or one of the
kids had a heart attack
or got cancer or something, maybe we'd
get higher with you.
- That's a terrible thing
to say.
- It's true!
You're never here.
You missed my dad's recital,
you missed my birthday party.
We were supposed to make cookies
with the girls' names on them.
I hate you!
- Sweetie.
(dramatic music)
Beth.
(door thudding)
(ominous music)
(thunder roaring)
(easygoing jazz music)
- Hey.
- How you doin'?
- I've been better.
- So what happened?
- My family hates me.
- No.
I find that hard to believe.
- Well actually, so...
Jake, he, he only resents
me for sabotaging his career
and our family.
There's my daughter who said
to my face that she hated me.
- Oh, come on, she's just a kid.
She's just lashing out for maximum impact.
I mean, don't you remember
saying horrible things
to your mom and wishing
you could take them back?
- My mom died when I was eight.
- Oh.
- [Woman] Can we get two more?
- Sorry.
- We were driving up the
coast, just her and me,
and we got a flat.
It was really foggy out and
she went out to change the tire
and was hit by a passing car.
She laid there bleeding
while we waited for help.
Thanks.
She died right in front of me.
I always thought that I
could have saved her if,
if I only knew what to do.
- And so, of course,
you became an ER doctor.
- I guess.
- You wanna know why I became a paramedic?
- Yeah.
Why?
- Because they kept coming to my house
every time my mom would OD.
After a while, they knew my name.
They'd even bring me little gifts.
I thought they were so cool.
Practically, the only
attention I ever got.
Trust me, Beth, you have
a very normal family.
Things will look a lot
brighter in the morning.
(easygoing jazz music)
(Beth laughing)
Okay, I don't know if you
should've had that last one.
- Oh, I know, I shouldn't
have, woo, goodness grace.
- Are you okay?
- Never had that one before.
- I think I should call you a cab.
- I don't, no, I can drive, I'm fine.
Oh.
I don't wanna go home.
- (giggles) Well you
have to go home sometime.
- Excuse me, but I can do whatever I want.
- (giggles) Yes, ma'am.
Let me call you a cab, huh?
- You're a good friend.
Take me home.
- Okay.
(ominous music)
(Beth grunts)
(Beth sighs)
(ominous music)
- Where have you been?
- I called.
- You left one drunken
message saying you were sorry.
I must've left a hundred messages
on your answering mach...
- Okay, okay, ssh.
Look, it's been a long night,
can we just talk about this tomorrow?
- Do I have a choice?
- I really need a shower.
(melancholic piano music)
(Beth weeping)
(alarm clock beeping)
(melancholic piano music)
- A little to your right.
- How's that?
- Perfect.
- Well I'd give you a tour but this is it.
- Yeah, no worries.
I just wanted to come by
and say congratulations on your promotion
and that I know I've got a lot to learn,
but I wanna make myself available to you
so that anything you might
need, I'm your go-to guy.
- Well, I'll keep that in mind.
- Okay then.
Cool.
Bye.
- Bye.
First-year residents.
You gotta love 'em.
(laptop beeping)
(suspenseful music)
- And then Richie Williams laughed so hard
that soda came out of his nose.
It was so gross.
- Eww.
- And then Jenny said...
- Oh, hey kids.
Go get washed up, dinner's almost ready.
- Wow.
- I guess you're all
wondering what's going on,
am I right?
- Yeah, dad always makes the meatballs.
- Well,
I just wanted to apologize.
I know that I've been
real busy with work lately
and I've been asking you for
your patience for a long time.
And you've all been really,
really understanding.
So forgive me for being more of a doctor
these days than a mother.
'Cause I love you very, very much.
And I promise that things are
going to change around here.
And I promise that what
happened last night
will never happen again.
(gentle piano music)
- What about the hospital?
- Well, one of the perks
of being the head of the ER
is that I am, I'm in charge
of setting the schedules.
I've arranged for my father
to watch the kids for a couple of days,
you can finish your field
work at the cottage.
And I very well may join you.
(gentle piano music)
(laptop beeping)
(ominous music)
- So just think of them as
all once little caterpillars.
Yeah, it's easy to remember, isn't it?
- I think so, yeah.
- What else do you have?
Any comprehension?
(telephone ringing)
- I got it.
Hello?
Yeah, uh-huh.
Here she is.
Mom.
- Yeah?
- There's the lady named Finn for you.
- Thank you.
I'll be right back.
- [Finn] Hello?
Hello?
- What do you want?
- Hey Beth, was that
Sean I was talking to?
He sounds adorable.
- Just leave my family out of this.
What do you want?
- Oh Beth, stop overreacting.
I mean, calling you at home
is the only way I can talk to you
if you don't answer my emails.
Unless, of course, you want
me popping in at the hospital.
- Look, that's not an option.
- Why won't you talk to me?
I thought we were friends.
- Look.
This whole thing was just a mis...
- It was a mistake?
- A misunderstanding.
Now, I am sorry if I hurt you in any way,
but I have my family to worry about.
- I'm aware of that Beth.
More than you know.
(phone dial tone)
- You're okay, mom?
- Yeah.
Yeah, everything's fine, come on.
Let's go finish up.
(suspenseful music)
- Paris Hilton,
eat your heart out.
(suspenseful music)
- Say hi, Beth.
She's a little out of it right now.
Yeah, she's pretty wasted.
Didn't stop her before, though (giggles),
did it?
Oh no.
She gave me a run for my money.
Oh.
Oh God, oh Beth.
(Finn giggles)
Yeah, you like it like that?
- [Beth] Oh yeah.
- [Finn] Mm, it tastes good.
- Sir.
- This is Dr. Kim and Dr. Soo from Seoul.
- I just need a moment to, um...
clean up my desk.
- I think that's a good idea.
Dr. Wyatt will join us shortly.
Just go down the hall.
Beth.
I am beyond shocked.
I didn't think internet
pornography was your style.
- Sir, someone sent it to me as a joke.
It's not what you think.
- Even so, you better be careful.
Attachments can carry viruses.
- Yes, sir.
- Now I'll try to explain
to our distinguished guests
that our new head of ER,
who was hired for her
high moral principles,
does not normally watch
pornography on the job.
- Thank you, sir.
- You'll be in good hands with Dr. Wyatt.
She'll show you a thing or two,
she has a wide variety of experience.
- Please.
(dramatic music)
Oh no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It should be here, come on.
It's gotta be here.
(dramatic music)
(laptop beeping)
(laptop thudding)
(dramatic music)
(dialog box beeping)
(hands pounding on keyboard)
Can you send this to
radiology for me, please?
- Mm-hmm.
Hey, I noticed on the schedule
you're taking some time off.
- Yeah.
- Chief dragging you to the
West Coast Medical Conference?
- No, no, I'm gonna head up
north to our cottage with Jake.
- Oh, good for you.
Nice to see that you're
relaxing into the new job.
You were pretty tense there
for the past few weeks.
I'd venture to say downright fatigued?
- So nice of you to notice.
I just...
I just thought that something
terrible might happen.
But it hasn't.
- Got a severe abdominal
bleed, taking him to trauma I.
- Just the normal insanity.
(camera clicking)
(suspenseful music)
- [Finn] And you know your mom,
and she turned around and
she handed the guy her exam.
- [Terri] She did not.
(children giggling)
- [Finn] She did.
She said, "If you're gonna
copy my answers, here,
"I may as well give 'em to you."
- [Terri] And then what happened?
- [Finn] Oh, then the professor came over
and took both of their exams.
Do you know that that guy
copied every single answer
your mom had written?
Even the ones that she deliberately mixed
just to fake him out.
- See, I would've made
'em both retake the exam,
staying on opposite sides of the room.
- Hey mom.
- Hey babe.
How come you never told us this story?
It's hilarious.
- Is that why you say
cheaters never prosper?
- I think she says that because it's true.
Isn't that right, Beth?
Hey roomie.
It's been a long time.
(Finn giggles)
Your mom and I were known
as the Laverne and Shirley of Murphy dorm.
- Who are Laverne and Shirley?
- What are you doing here?
- Well, I figured it was
about time I looked you up,
and Jake was kind enough
to invite me for dinner,
so the least I could do was cook it.
- Oh wait, I offered to babysit
so the two of you could
have a girls night out,
but she was determined to
cook us a family dinner.
- Well, that's really not necessary.
- Oh, I insist.
And you know how to determined I can be.
Hey Terri, can I make
you head table setter?
- Yes.
- What about me?
- Hmm, I'm gonna make you
assistant head table setter.
Hop to it.
- [Sean] Who are Laverne and Shirley?
- What great kids you guys have.
- Thanks.
We think so.
(ominous music)
- What's the matter, Beth?
You don't like the food?
- I guess I'm just not that hungry.
- Don't know what you're missing, honey.
- Yeah, it's really good mom.
- I'm sure.
- I'm having seconds.
- Whoa, easy there, cowboy.
Save some for the other ranch hands.
- (giggles) You're funny.
Hey Finn, you wanna watch me play soccer?
We have a game on Saturday.
- Yeah, sure.
I'd love to.
I mean, if that's okay with you guys.
- Oh, well I don't know if...
- Hey, we can always use another person
rooting for our side.
Just be ready to sit
around outside for hours
watching a mob of screaming 7-year-olds
attempting to kick a ball.
- I am so there.
- Well,
it was real nice meeting you, Finn.
- You don't get off that easy,
come here, you (giggles).
Oh, you're lucky you met him first, Beth.
- Honey, could I have a
word with Finn, please?
- Uh-oh, here comes the girl talk.
I'm outta here.
- Goodnight.
- I can't believe you did this.
Now I want you to get
the hell out of my house
and don't you ever come
near my family again
or so help me, God, I will...
- Oh, you better bring it way down, Beth.
And you better get used to
seeing me around your family,
because if you don't,
they might get a copy of
our little home movie.
Not exactly G-rated for the kiddies,
but I have a feeling
Jake's gonna like watching
some girl-on-girl action.
Oh, we're gonna be friends, you and me,
best friends,
or everyone on the board of trustees
at St. Catherine's might find
a little something special
in their mailbox.
You understand?
So if I wanna go to a soccer
game, you don't get to say no.
- And then what?
Set a place for you at Christmas dinner?
Look, you can hurt me all you want,
just leave my family out of it.
- You don't get it, do you?
God Beth, I don't wanna hurt you.
I wanna be a part of you.
A part of your family.
Since my partner died,
I've just been so removed and lonely
and I just need to feel again,
even if that means going
to a kid's soccer game.
- You, you sound like you're going
through survivor's guilt, Finn.
It's affecting your judgment.
I can recommend a psychologist.
I could help you...
- No.
Thank you, doctor.
I am just fine.
I'll see you Saturday.
(lips smacking)
(door thudding)
- Come on, tell me what's the
matter between you and Finn?
- Nothing's the matter.
- Please, your reception of
her was lukewarm at best.
Some might call it downright frosty.
- Just surprised to see her, that's all.
- Beth, Finn told me that you two
had a little falling out of college
and that it had been quite
some time since you talked.
She assumed it was water under
the bridge, was she right?
- Did she say what this
falling out was about?
- She said it was up to you to tell me.
- Huh, isn't that gracious of her.
- Well, you don't have to tell me,
but I just figured after
14 years of marriage,
we didn't have any more secrets.
(Beth sighs)
- It was...
- It was what?
- It was a long time ago.
- Fine, don't tell me.
Just have to go with my own theory,
which was that she stole
your boyfriend in college
and that I should thank her
for keeping you away from the wrong guy.
- Jake.
Honey.
(Beth sighs)
The thing with Finn is,
she's just...
Unreliable,
and maybe it's not such a good idea
for the kids to get too attached to her.
- Right, 'cause it would be bad
if the kids got attached to
someone they could depend on.
- Gosh, wow.
So we're back at this again.
Look, I'm sorry,
I thought I was doing
everything I could to try to...
- Honey, no, no, you are.
I know you are.
I'm sorry.
(soft piano music)
Okay?
Come here.
(soft piano music)
- Come here, I love you (grunts).
(Beth giggles)
(telephone ringing)
- Hey Sarah, I'm gonna
take off for the day,
I've got my son's soccer game,
So I am gonna see you tomorrow, my dear.
- Have fun.
- Thank you.
- ER.
How many?
Dr. Wyatt?
We'll be ready.
Dr. Wyatt, a bus
overturned on Interstate 5.
- Prep the trauma room,
set up a triage area,
call on everyone.
It's code red.
- I'm on it.
- [PA Announcer] Dr.
Truit, nurse station five.
- But the mall's not that
far, you can just drop me off.
Amanda and Jenny are gonna be there.
- Yeah, and I suppose you want 20 bucks
and a ride home too.
- Well, yeah.
- Then that would have to be a no.
- But dad...
- Ah, ah, ah, ah.
Oh, hold that pout.
(cell phone ringing)
Hey.
- Hi, um...
there's been a busload of
patients that are gonna come in.
Tell Sean I'm gonna do
my very best to get there
as soon as I can, but I...
- But you don't know if
you'll make it out on time.
Yeah, I'll tell him.
- Right, and would you tell
him that I love him too?
- Yeah, of course.
- Is Finn there?
- No, no, I haven't seen her.
- Well, maybe she changed her mind.
- Well, you had said she was unreliable.
- Listen, I gotta go.
I'll talk to you later, I love you.
- Love you too.
Hey, Sean.
That was mom on the phone.
There's been a big accident,
she has to stay at the
hospital to help out,
but she's really, really
gonna try and get here
as soon as she can, all right?
And she wants you to know she
loves you very much, okay?
- Sure.
- Hey, there's my star soccer player.
- Finn!
- Hey.
- Come on, I'll show you
the good place to sit.
- Okay.
Hey, where's Beth?
- Caught up at work.
- Oh, that's too bad.
- There's Kylie and her
mom, can I go sit with them?
- Yeah, okay.
Just stay inside the park, okay?
- So Jake, I'm curious.
How did you and Beth meet?
- We were at a wedding.
We were at the singles table
and Beth knew the bride from med school
and the groom was a, well,
he is a colleague of mine.
Unfortunately, that couple just split up.
- Hmm, and how about you and Beth?
I mean, was it love at first sight?
- (chuckles) Ah, not exactly.
She was still doing a
residency, so she wasn't dating.
So it took a lot of persistence on my part
and a lot of rescheduling dates.
- Yeah, it must be hard
knowing that you always
come second to her career.
- Oh, it's not her
career that comes first.
She just has this,
this need to help everybody.
And I can't really resent
that, I mean, it's,
it's what attracted me to
her in the first place.
- Hmm.
- What was that about?
- I don't know, it just sounds to me
like you get a little jealous
when she gives to other
people and not to you?
- Yeah.
Makes me a first-class jerk, huh?
- (chuckles) No, it just makes you human.
So how about you and your work?
I mean, that must be important too.
- Oh, environmental studies.
Forestry management.
- When I was young, my family and I,
we used to go camping up
north near Placid Pines.
- Really?
- Yeah, before they
started all the excavation.
- We have a cottage up near there.
- (chuckles) You're kidding me.
- No, seriously, and in fact,
our house overlooks
that excavation project.
Monstrosity.
- Hey, I have, um, I have strawberries.
You want one?
I have whipped cream too.
(whistle blowing)
- [Sean] Dad!
- Sean!
(ominous music)
- [Man] Just, guys, just back over, okay?
- What happened?
- [Boy] Is he bleeding?
(Sean weeping)
- [Finn] Sean!
- Sean, what happened, buddy?
You're okay?
- My arm.
Ow, it hurts.
- Okay Sean, you just lie
still for me, okay?
- Ow!
- Can you wiggle your fingers for me?
- Ow, ow!
- It's all right.
- It's all right, stay still.
- Okay, sweetie.
I think it might be broken.
He's gonna need an X-ray.
- It's all right.
- I'll get you fixed up
in a jiffy.
(Sean grunting painfully)
- It's okay, Sean.
- Dr. Wyatt, your son's been admitted.
Trauma II.
- What?
- I'll take over.
You're gonna be just fine.
- And then the blind man says, "No thanks,
"I'm just looking around."
(Sean and Beth giggling)
- Hey, mom.
- Hey sweetie.
- I broke my arm.
- Yeah, you did, you okay?
- You would've been proud of him, Beth,
he was a real trooper.
- Was he?
- Yeah.
- That's my boy.
- Glad you could join us, Dr. Wyatt.
- I came as soon as I heard.
- Well, it's definitely a
fracture, but he's young,
it should heal without complication.
You did a good job of splinting it.
- Hmm, thank you.
- You did it?
- Mm-hmm.
- Finn stayed calm and
took control the situation,
which makes her a hero in my book
'cause I was a basket case.
- Yeah mom, Finn was cool.
- Was?
- I just did what I was trained to do.
You would've done the same
thing, if you'd been there.
- Well, then I'm grateful
that you were there.
- All right Sean, let's get
you fixed up and out of here.
- Okay, you're good to go.
- I'll call Kylie's mom
and see if Terri can stay the night.
- Sure.
- Hey.
You know I wanted to be there.
- This isn't the time, Beth.
- But you know that, right?
(solemn ambient music)
- Where's Finn?
- She couldn't wait around at
the hospital forever, kiddo.
- Will she be here tomorrow?
- I'm pretty sure that could be arranged.
- Good.
(solemn ambient music)
(telephone buttons beeping)
- Hi, it's Beth Wyatt.
Oh, he's much better, thanks.
Listen, I was wondering, ah,
could Terri stay with Carly tonight?
What?
What do you mean she left?
With who?
(suspenseful music)
And, and, and you just let her go?
Well, did Finn happen to mention
where she was taking her?
(suspenseful music)
Well, they'd better be home.
Yes, hi,
I would like you to put
up an AMBER Alert for my,
for my daughter.
Terri Wyatt.
It's somebody, somebody took her
and, and, and I don't know where.
No, this isn't a custody dispute.
Her name, a woman, Finn
Connors took my daughter...
- What, what's going on?
- Finn picked up Terri from Kylie's house.
40 minutes ago.
- Well, what are you talking about?
- It only takes 10 minutes
to get here from her house.
- Maybe they stopped.
- Excuse me, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, what?
Dr. Beth Wyatt.
1119 Sapphire Lane.
What was Terri wearing today?
- Black hoodie, khaki pants, pink T-shirt.
Why, why, why would Finn take Terri?
- Because she wants to punish me.
She's 11 years old, she has
long brown hair, brown eyes,
she weighs about...
Where have you been?
Why did you leave Kylie's house?
- Well Finn came over and
I wanted to come home.
- Haven't I told you to never go anywhere
without telling me first?
- I know, but it was Finn.
- I don't care who it was,
you don't go anywhere with anyone,
even if it's someone that you know,
unless your father or
I know about it first,
and you know that.
Why didn't you come home right away?
Where did you go?
What, what did she do to you?
- Oh come on, Beth.
- We just got ice cream.
- Sorry, I was just...
just so worried about you, honey.
I just want you to be safe.
Sorry I yelled at you.
- Hi, yeah, sorry about that.
Ever, everything's fine, she's home.
Okay, yeah, thanks for your time.
Hey.
Why don't you go wash up and
then we'll have some ice cream.
One of you two is gonna tell me
what the hell is going on here.
- (sigh) Look, I'm sorry
if I stepped out of bounds.
I just, I knew you guys
were preoccupied with Sean
and I just thought Terri
could use a little attention.
- Jake already had someone we knew
and trusted watching Terri, thank you.
You're just trying to get
to me through my kids.
- Enough!
I wanna know what the hell this
bad blood is between you two
'cause this has gotta stop now.
Nothing could be that bad.
- Oh yes it can.
- Okay.
If you can't or don't wanna tell me,
I have to respect that.
Finn, I'm sorry,
but you're no longer
welcomed in this house.
I can't have this hostility
in my home anymore.
- [Sean] Dad.
- Look, I hate ending things like this,
but if you two can't work this out,
I have to put my family first.
- I understand, Jake.
(ominous music)
Why did you go, go and ruin everything?
It was all going so well.
I was even bonding with the kids.
- You heard my husband.
You're no longer welcomed in this house.
- Well then get him to change his mind
or I'm gonna post our
little sex video on YouTube
and email it to everyone
in your address book.
You better wrap your head around that
'cause you've got 48 hours
until your world premiere.
(ominous music)
- [Sarah] We need security.
(objects clattering)
- I don't have the right insurance.
- Sir, if you will just
calm down, I will help you.
- You want coverage, huh?
- Please, sir.
(medical items clattering)
- I'll give you coverage.
- [Sarah] Please, calm down, sir.
- What the hell is going on?
- Sir, calm down.
- Another HMO patient.
(objects clattering)
(men grunting)
- Hey!
(Dr. Friedman grunting)
- Oh, it's my back.
- Sir.
- Here, help me up.
(Dr. Friedman grunting)
- Do you have pain in your legs too?
- Yes.
- All right, bring that gurney over here.
- No, no, no, it's all right.
I'll, I'll, we'll just ice it up.
- Yeah, we'll just get you over to X-ray
and then we will see about that ice.
All right, easy, easy.
- Keep your head up this end.
- I hope you're happy.
Spinal stenosis exacerbated by a man
throwing me across the room.
Damn bone spurs digging
into my spinal column.
Do you know what this means?
- That you're gonna miss your yoga class?
(Dr. Friedman chuckles)
- So Beth, I'm gonna be out
of commission for a few weeks,
I'm gonna need you to step up.
- Absolutely, anything you need.
- I'm scheduled to be at the West Coast
Medical Conference tomorrow.
I'm gonna need someone to
go to Seattle in my place.
- Tomorrow.
- I know you had cleared your calendar
so you could spend some time
at the cottage with Jake,
but I'm slated to give the keynote address
on morals and medical ethics,
I need someone I can trust to take over.
- Look sir, I appreciate
your faith in me, but I...
- Good, good, since you have no objection,
then I'll tell the organizers
that you will be
representing St Catherine's.
Thank you, I appreciate that.
(Beth sighs)
- Exciting morning in the ER.
- (sigh) Yeah.
- Sorry I missed it.
How's your son doing?
- Much better, thank you.
- Your friend Finn,
or is she Jake's friend?
Not actually sure.
- No, actually she's,
she's just an acquaintance, really.
- Doyle was saying that
she used to be a paramedic
over at Westfield General.
- Yeah, that's right.
- I told a friend of
mine who works over there
about how she was at the
right place at the right time,
helped your son out and...
Well the thing is is that,
she, um...
- What is it, Massey?
- He's been working there for six years.
He says he's never heard of a
paramedic named Finn Connors.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah, this guy's solid.
(suspenseful music)
- Well, it must be some misunderstanding.
- Right, right.
- Right.
- She must work at like
Valley General or something.
I just thought you should know.
(pager buzzing)
Gotta go.
(suspenseful music)
(cell phone buttons beeping)
- Hi, it's Beth Wyatt.
Yes, yes, I can imagine that you are
surprised to hear from me but...
Listen, I was wondering if you
could meet for lunch today.
It's important that we talk.
Hey.
- Hey.
- Thank you so much for meeting
me on such short notice.
- Everything's okay with my mom, right?
- Oh yeah, yeah, absolutely.
She's healing beautifully.
- Good, you had me worried
there for a sec, doc.
- I'm sorry.
The reason why I called, Jamie, is...
Well, I've got sort of a computer problem.
- Ah, well it's about time
that I get to help you,
what's the problem?
- Well, you see, I belong to one of these
professional forums online,
a message board for emergency
room doctors and nurses,
and well, I think there's someone on it
that isn't who they
say they are, and well,
I was wondering if,
if they give false
information on their profile,
like if there was a way to
find out who they really are.
You know, like, you know,
if there was a way somehow
to trace the account.
- Yeah, just ask the
webmaster of the forum
for the IP address of the person.
- What does that do?
- Ah, the IP address will
track down their server.
- What if you wanna track down the person?
- Oh, that's a little more complicated.
You'd have to hack into their computer.
- Ah.
Can you do that?
- I could, but it would
be, you know, illegal.
Just start with the webmaster,
get him to ban the person from the forum.
- Well, you see, Jamie, the truth is...
this person has been
harassing me and my family.
All I have is her name.
It's the screen name on the
account that was canceled,
and her address.
Now I may have helped your mother,
I have no right to ask you
to do anything illegal,
so if you just wanna leave right now,
I will totally understand.
But if you do do this,
you will find some things out about me,
some things that I'm not
particularly proud of,
which is the reason why
I can't go to the police.
- Doc,
you may be my family's guardian angel,
but I'm sure you're still human.
So, are the burgers here any good?
- Hello?
- Hey.
- Hi.
Where's everybody?
- Kids are upstairs packing
and off to grandpa's they go.
What's the matter now?
- Friedman has to have back surgery.
I need to fill in for him at
a conference in Seattle...
Tomorrow.
- Damn it, Beth.
We had it all planned.
- I know, I know, I know,
and I'm just as upset
about this as you are,
but I'm sure I can sneak
away early on the last day
and come meet you.
- That's not good enough, Beth.
Your dad's coming to
pick up the kids tonight.
- I know, and everything is
going to go according to plan,
except for this one little revision.
I promise I am not gonna let
this ruin our time together.
I promise.
(lips smacking)
Promise.
(cell phone ringing)
- Better get that.
Probably the hospital.
- Hello?
- Tick-tock, Beth.
24 hours are up.
24 more and you'll be an internet legend,
unless, of course, you
come to your senses.
- Look, I am not afraid of you.
I know you never worked
for Westfield General
and I'm gonna find out who you really are.
- Tick-tock, Beth.
(cell phone ringing)
- Hello?
- Hey Jamie, she just called.
- I'm gonna access your phone records now.
- She, she blocked the caller ID.
- Nah, that's not a problem
We'll get her, doc.
I promise.
- Okay.
(suspenseful music)
I will meet you at the
cottage after the conference.
- Don't Beth.
I don't have the energy for it anymore.
- What?
- Promises you can't keep.
(suspenseful music)
(people chattering)
- Name, please.
- Dr. Beth Wyatt.
- Here you are, and I see
you're one of our speakers.
- That's right.
- Morals and medical ethics, I believe.
- Dr. Doyle.
The chief didn't say that you'd be here.
- Oh, I'm not the chosen
one, just a regular attendee.
Dr. Brian Doyle.
- There you are.
- Pardon me.
Dr. Wyatt.
I, I believe you left your
visual aid at the hospital.
- You stole that from my office.
- Look.
Friedman told me you've been
watching porn on your computer.
I thought I could play a practical joke
and CC it to the rest of the hospital.
Petty, I know,
but I was pissed off about
you getting the promotion.
But then I discovered
it was you on the DVD.
- What are you gonna do with it?
- Look.
I'm not the complete
bastard that you think I am,
and you're not what I thought either.
So tell me, is this double
life tearing you apart inside
or are you the most accomplished liar
I've ever met?
- Brian, please.
There's more to this than you know.
- Oh, I'm sure there is.
Now I'm going to listen to your speech
on morals, medical ethics.
If there is one iota of guile
or sanctimonious rubbish,
I'm taking this to the board of trustees.
(suspenseful music)
(cell phone ringing)
- Do you have any news?
- Good news or bad first?
- Well, there's good news?
- Yeah, I was finally able
to hack into her computer.
Let me tell you, she sure knows
her way around a firewall.
- And what did you find?
- Doc, are you sure that you wanna know?
- I have to.
- I doubt you two meeting
online was by accident.
A couple months before he
started chatting in the ER forum,
she's been emailing your husband.
- That's impossible.
- Doc, I can forward you the emails.
You can read them yourself.
Doc?
- Send me the emails.
(suspenseful music)
- Okay.
- [Finn] Yeah, does that feel good?
You like that?
- Whoa.
- Yeah.
Oh yeah, baby.
(suspenseful music)
Are you ready for me?
Oh yeah, get your leg up here.
Oh yeah.
Oh.
Yeah, oh yeah.
(cell phone ringing)
- Jamie.
- Hey, I've done more digging.
Finn had an online
prescription for Rohypnol.
That's the one they call roofies, right?
The date rape drug?
- That's the one.
- She must have slipped
it to you at the bar
because I've just seen the uncut footage
of the video she shot.
You were unconscious the whole time, doc.
- But, but the video had
me moving and I was...
- Well, she must've edited
to make it look like,
you know,
but nothing happened.
- Oh (sigh).
Oh my God, Jamie, you have no
idea how grateful I am to you.
- Doc, I also found more
bad news about Finn.
- Tell me everything.
(dramatic music)
- Dr. Wyatt, we've been looking for you.
The seminar you're speaking
at is right this way.
- Right, you know what?
I can't do this right now.
- I've, I've got something, Brian, Brian.
A sudden change of plans,
Dr. Doyle here will be giving the speech.
- What?
- My notes, if you want them,
they should explain everything.
If not, then just do what you need to do.
Thanks.
- Dr. Doyle, right this way.
- [Beth VOICEOVER] Medical
ethics are concerned
with our conduct as doctors,
so does it really matter
what our personal morals are?
As long as we save lives,
does it matter if we lie or cheat
when we're not wearing that white coat?
- Just give me a second, please.
- Sure.
- [Beth VOICEOVER] As physicians,
we take the moral high ground by putting
the welfare of our
patients above all else,
but in our personal
lives, where do we stand?
And that's where my speech ends, Brian.
I couldn't write any more
because we both know what a lie it is
for me to lecture on morality.
I can't undo what I've done,
but it's time for me to
take a stand for my family,
to fight for them,
to let them know that
I'd give up everything
to make it right.
I'm afraid it's too late, but Brian,
please give me a chance to save my family.
(dramatic music)
- Hi, Jake.
- Beth.
You startled me, wha-what
are you doing here?
- I brought a peace offering.
- Finn...
- Look, things didn't go
quite as I'd hoped with Beth,
but I have a plan.
And I also have some brisee, some pate,
and a bottle of wine.
- Finn, I, I don't really
think this is appropriate.
- But, Jake, I could
really use some advice.
- I'm really kinda busy here.
You're not gonna take no
for an answer, are ya?
- Isn't this better than looking
at a big hole in the ground?
- Oh, all right, I admit it.
I needed the break.
Ah, food, the food is delicious.
- You should see what I can do
when I really set my mind to something.
- What are we gonna say to Beth?
- Leave Beth to me, I'll take care of her.
I'll take care of everything.
- You are very persuasive.
- That I am.
- Whoa.
What do you think you're doing?
- Come on, Jake.
Don't play so innocent.
The way we get along so well,
the chemistry between us.
I mean, you must know this
isn't all of a sudden.
- Whoa, whoa, wait just a minute here.
I was, I was willing to help
you apologize for Beth's sake,
but I didn't think that...
Look, if you think there's
something between us,
you're crazy.
- That's not what you said before.
- What are you talking about?
- You make me feel something
I haven't felt in a long time.
I wonder what it would
be like to kiss you,
to feel your body next to mine.
- Where'd you get that?
- You emailed it to me.
- What?
- My name was Red Rock Girl,
when we met on that online
chat room, remember?
We talked about rock climbing,
you told me all about your family,
about Beth and the kids.
How lost you were.
How your marriage was failing.
How there was no more communication.
No more sex.
Jake, you told me how much
you wanted to touch me.
Well, I'm here now, Jake.
Touch me.
- Get away.
I also said that I would
never go through with it
because despite
everything, I love my wife.
Finn, it's the internet, how
could you take that seriously?
I, I, I didn't even know your real name.
I stopped emailing you.
I canceled my account.
- Which is why I had to go
through Beth to get to you.
- Oh my God.
- Jake, we could be our own
little perfect family now.
That's all I've ever wanted.
Beth won't be in the way anymore.
- What do you mean?
What do you mean?
- Jake!
Jake!
- Hi Beth, I was just gonna tell Jake
about our night together,
or should I just show him the video?
- I never knew Finn in college.
- I kinda figured that out.
- That night that I got drunk,
she took me to her apartment
and I woke up naked in her bed.
- And you videotaped this?
- Well she shot the video to
make me think that we had sex,
but the truth is she
drugged me at the bar.
- She's lying, Jake.
She came onto me.
- I found out more.
You live off daddy's money,
and you were never a paramedic.
But you were in love with one in Spokane.
He rejected you.
He even had a restraining
order against you.
Then a year ago, he turned up dead.
Gunshot wound to the head.
They considered it suicide, but...
maybe you did it.
Maybe you drove him to it.
It's the only way he could be free of you.
- He loved me.
You bitch!
- She had a mental breakdown after that,
spent six months in a psych ward.
She met you online
a couple of months after she was released.
- It's not true, Jake.
He loved me,
just like you.
I know you will.
- Oh.
(Finn weeping)
What's happening?
Is she having another breakdown?
- Lemme check her.
(Finn grunts)
(Beth screams)
- Get.
(women grunting)
I needed an escape, all right?
And then I realized that my responsibility
was to my wife and my kids,
because I love Beth, more than anything.
You got that?
- Well sorry, Jake.
- Let her go, Jake.
- We should call the police.
- If you ever come near my family again,
we will call the police.
- No.
If you ever come anywhere
near my family again,
I'll kill you myself.
You understand?
- I understand.
- Sorry, Beth.
(dramatic music)
(engine revving)
(car roaring)
- Beth!
(body thudding on windshield)
(car roaring)
- Beth!
(dramatic music)
(Beth grunts)
Hang on, I'll get a rope.
- No, I can make it, I can
make it down, just call 911.
- What?
- I gotta help Finn out of the car.
- Why?
- I'm still a doctor.
- Don't, don't, don't, don't do that.
(dramatic music)
Yeah, yeah, there's a car
that's gone over a cliff.
12 Victoria, Placid Pines.
Okay, yeah.
(dramatic music)
- Okay.
(Finn grunting)
Hang on, hang on.
I'm gonna get you out of there.
(Finn grunting)
- You have this thing about
helping people, don't you?
(car creaking)
(Finn grunting)
Just let me die.
- You know I can't do that.
(dramatic music)
Jake!
(car creaking)
Help me get her outta here.
- The car is sliding.
- Come on.
- That's it.
(car creaking)
One, two, three.
(rocks crumbling)
(Finn grunting)
(car thudding)
(car explosion booming)
- That was close.
- She's still breathing.
- Is she gonna live?
- If medevac gets here soon.
(suspenseful music)
- You know, Bethie,
we really gotta work on
our communication skills.
- Do you really think this is
the time to talk about this?
- No.
I think I'll wait till
after I see that video.
- (giggles) Yeah.
(ominous music)