[music playing]
(SINGING) I'm gonna
kiss you all over, baby.
I'm gonna take you there.
So take it slow and easy.
Gonna take our time tonight.
I'm gonna fill you
up with my lovin'.
I'm gonna take you there.
I'm gonna kiss you
all over, baby.
I'm gonna kiss you.
I'm gonna kiss you all over.
I'm gonna kiss you
all over, baby.
I'm gonna take you there.
I'm gonna kiss you all over.
I'm gonna kiss you
all over, baby.
I'm gonna take you there.
I'm gonna kiss you all over.
I'm gonna kiss you
all over, baby.
I'm gonna kiss you.
I'm gonna kiss you all over.
I'm gonna kiss you
all over, baby.
I'm gonna take you there.
[music playing]
CONNIE: Miami-- what can
I tell you about Miami?
Well, this is what's really
happening these days.
The good news, big
money keeps flowing in.
The bad news?
Too many sharks smelling
an easy killing.
So I say, be smarter
than the other guy.
Do your homework.
Know your mark.
I mean, really know your mark.
For instance, I read
in the business section
this morning that
someone called Goldman
just quit some big ad agency.
So I do a little checking
here, a little checking there,
and I'm ready to do business.
Connie Coolidge to
see Mr. Goldman.
I have an appointment.
Well, please take a seat
and I'll have someone see you.
MAN: I don't know to tell you.
Goldman was let go
Friday afternoon.
Took me out to camp with him.
I think he's going independent.
MARSHA: This is a shock.
I even gave notice
at my other job.
You see, I flew in from Chicago.
Well, I have his home number
if you'd like to make a call.
Well, I do have
a slight problem.
Mr. Goldman promised he would
cover any of my expenses,
and I had to lay out
$600 for my plane ticket.
MARSHA (VOICEOVER):
Short and sweet.
Never say more than you have to.
Never stay longer than you need.
600?
Why did I say Chicago?
I should have said
LA and asked for 800.
Anyway, it's not
a bad day's work,
and it's not even lunchtime.
SALESPERSON: Ma'am,
it's our policy.
I'm sorry, but I
really can't do that.
WOMAN: Just charge it to
my room like I told you.
You're just too lazy
to do the paperwork.
235, do you have that?
And tell your boss to call
me when he comes back.
Gift wrapped.
235.
MARSHA: I'll have
the lobster thermidor
and a glass of champagne.
French, if you have it.
WAITER: Thank you, ma'am.
Are you staying at the hotel?
Yes, room 235.
You can charge it.
Oh, and have a bottle of
champagne sent to the sales
girl at the boutique.
I think she'd like Dom
Perignon-- with a note.
Apologies for my
behavior, room 235.
You can charge that too.
WAITER: Very good.
[horn honking]
[telephone ringing]
Hello?
HENRY (ON PHONE): Marsha,
it's your friend, Henry.
What do you want,
old friend Henry?
How'd you like to make another
payment on your brother's debt?
MARSHA (ON PHONE):
How much, Henry?
500 for five minutes.
Sounds like a
pretty good rate.
Who do I have to shoot?
Oh Marsha, Marsha.
You know me.
I mean, your brother Frankie'd
still be in the slammer
if it wasn't for my
expertise as his counsel.
Yeah, I know, my brother
won't even speak to me,
and I'm still paying
for your expertise.
Well, it's time for you to
make another payment, sweetie.
OK.
All right.
What's the poop?
The poop?
Well, the poop is
put on something sexy
and go to the car wash on
third tomorrow morning at 10.
There's a fancy
red sports car that
comes in every Tuesday for the
VIP treatment, only this time,
it's going bye bye to
South America-- that
is, as soon as you
can engage the owner
in a distracting conversation.
[funky music]
[woman vocalizing]
Nice car.
Is it yours?
Yeah.
It's gorgeous.
Thanks.
Uh, do you have any change?
There's a machine in there.
It sells those little
tree air fresheners,
but it only takes dollar bills.
I don't.
I don't have any change.
I'll get some coffee.
They'll break it for me.
Do you want some?
Yeah.
Two regular coffees, please.
No, I'll have a cappuccino.
Thank you.
Cheers.
I'm Cassandra.
Matt.
So, Matt, you can't
be from around here.
Actually, I grew
up in South Beach.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah.
Graduated from the
University of Miami.
What do you do?
I get my car washed.
I do a little bicycling,
a little, uh, windsurfing.
Sounds like a good job to me.
Where do I apply?
I love windsurfing.
WOMAN (ON PA):
Attention, please.
The owner of the
white Mercedes 500,
your car is ready for pickup.
Matt Conrad?
You're not the "Headless
Johnson's Revenge" Matt Conrad,
are you?
Yeah.
My eight-year-old
loves those games.
Thanks.
Tell him he's
gotta file a claim
with his insurance company.
They're not gonna do squat
unless he reports it.
Hey, why don't
you file a report
with your insurance company?
Lady, you got some nerve.
I'm not the one that was
preoccupied with my hormones
and left my car unattended.
Hey, there's no
need to be rude.
Step over this
way, please, sir.
Sir, I'd like to check
the documentation
on some of your workers.
I'm impressed.
The Matt Conrad.
What, it takes a
Lamborghini to impress you?
No, what impresses
me is a guy who's
able to start up a
multimillion dollar
business out of his garage.
I was just doing what I love.
Somebody wanted it.
I got lucky.
Makes two of us.
You have beautiful
eyes, you know that?
You say that to everyone.
No, I-- I don't.
Well, this is it.
Would you like to
come in for a drink?
I'd love to.
Wow.
My entire apartment could
fit in your living room.
Yeah, well.
So all this is yours?
Not quite.
Company owns it.
And you own the company?
No, they just kind
of need me right now,
so they figured
this'd keep me happy.
And are you?
Sometimes.
The shareholders say that
if I'm happy, they're happy.
So.
How about you?
Are you happy?
Uh, sometimes.
Pool, my favorite game.
Do you wanna play a game?
Yeah, I'd love to.
I'm not very good, though.
Oh, come on, rack the balls.
I'll show you how to play.
[inaudible]
You gonna break?
I'm going to break.
Now, pay attention.
Two balls.
Very impressive.
Excuse me.
It's quite all right.
I don't mind at all.
All right, you're
breaking my concentration.
Yeah, yeah.
The excuses are
starting already.
MATT: All right, go ahead.
You're breaking
my concentration.
Oh, isn't that awful?
It's my shot.
That's all you get.
[moaning]
Well, Smokey, gotta
go to work now.
I had a good time.
I just want you to know
I don't make a habit
of this kind of behavior.
So I guess you say
goodbye to number 52
and put another notch
in the old bedpost.
Well, actually, um,
the bed's antique,
So I keep track of my
conquests on my computer.
I'd like to read it sometime.
Mm-hm.
Sorry, I'm just afraid that--
That what?
That I go out with women once
and then I throw them away?
Well?
I like you.
Does that mean
I'll see you again?
Maybe.
Give me your phone number.
Top one's a cellular.
Bottom one's home.
Hm.
You know, you even
look good in my sweats.
You're gonna have to see me
again if you want 'em back.
I'm gonna want them back.
Bye.
See ya.
What do you say, slim?
Nice outfit.
What do you want, Henry?
How's your brother Frankie?
Last time I saw him was
when I put him on the bus.
He hasn't called,
and I can't find him.
I dunno.
I think maybe his pride's
getting in the way.
Call it "guilt."
And your brother isn't showing
much gratitude, letting
baby sister pay his bill.
He's my brother.
He helped me out
when I was a kid.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Well, how'd you like to pay
Frankie's debt in one shot.
Who do I have to kill?
Don't say that.
It hurts my ear.
No, no.
You've got other talents.
You're an artist.
We got this girl who works temp.
And right now she's
working at Steven Hayes,
transferring files onto
hard discs, floppy discs,
and putting it all
on one computer.
Anyhow, she's coming up
with some pretty hot stuff.
Well, we got this one old
broad, she's about ready
to drop at any minute.
She's, uh, been living off of
the interest and the dividends
of a trust fund that her brother
set up for her before he died.
Anyhow, once she keels
over, the entire bundle
goes to this girl, Jean.
She doesn't know who Jean is.
She doesn't wanna know.
But Jean is the illegitimate
daughter of her dead brother,
and is destined
to become the, uh,
sole surviving blood
relative of the dynasty.
Capish?
Yeah.
Go on.
Well, Jean never
knew her father.
She doesn't even know she's
coming into all this scratch.
She's just out there.
You're gonna become
her new best friend,
and you're gonna get to
know every intimate detail
about her.
And when the old
lady dies, boom.
Out goes the old Jean,
in comes the new Jean.
And the new Jean suddenly finds
out that she's very, very rich.
Boom, Henry?
You know I don't do boom.
- Oh, come on.
You know, this is gonna
be nice and clean.
We're gonna take
good care of her.
We're gonna send her on a
nice, long trip to Fiji.
By the time she comes back,
the biscuits are done.
I mean, even if she finds
out, it's gonna be too late.
I dunno.
You have it--
Come on, Marsha.
I'm giving you the
chance of a lifetime.
All I'm asking you is to
inherit a few million.
20%, and your brother's debt is
off the books once and for all.
OK, nothing
happens to the girl.
My brother's debt is history.
I get 30%.
Oh, Marsha.
Come on, don't do this to me.
OK, OK, OK.
Here I got some scratch, 3,000.
Expenses, get
yourself a used car.
Pay cash.
Come on.
I want a receipt.
This isn't like you, actually
putting out money for a job.
Well, you gotta
speculate to accumulate.
I got you an apartment right
across the hallway from hers.
Hello, Jean Ivers.
[knocking]
JEAN: Yeah.
Hi.
I'm sorry to bother you.
I just moved into apartment
15, and I was wondering if you
had some decaf I could borrow.
Uh, sure.
Wait there.
Thanks.
Ah, thanks.
You're a lifesaver.
I'm Maddie.
Oh, Jean.
Welcome to Sunnyside.
It seems like a fun place.
Hey, well, thanks
for the coffee.
I'll get you some
more in the morning.
- No rush.
- Thanks.
Bye-bye.
[phone ringing]
Hello.
MARSHA (ON PHONE): Hey, Stein.
Can I see you?
Not, "hello Mr. Stein.
How are you?"
All right, Mr. Stein,
how the hell are you?
Not bad for an old guy.
Uh, 10:00, our usual place?
STEIN (ON PHONE): Suits me.
Are you all right?
Mm-hm.
Yeah, I just need
to talk to you.
I'll be there.
Bye.
[beep]
[music playing]
(SINGING) All alone, I see you
standing there with nothing
left to show me but your tears.
Sorry I'm late.
I was beginning to think
you had a better offer.
I had an offer,
but it wasn't better.
Cheers.
Something's bothering you.
I'm OK.
Is it that bad?
Let me ask you a question.
If somebody offered you a big
break, something that could set
your life free, but
it involved something
that was against your
principles, would you do it?
Would you?
I dunno.
Marsha, you have your
whole life ahead of you.
And it'll be a good
life, if you let it.
I've been thinking
a lot about the past
lately, lamenting my regrets,
reveling in my accomplishments.
I thought about the time
we met in the art gallery,
and you came up to me as
if you'd known me forever.
You were the most magnificent
woman I'd ever seen.
And then you sold
me the Matthies.
It was a good buy.
I'd have bought out the whole
gallery if you asked me to.
I still have the Matthies.
I know.
It's worth double.
I'll never sell it.
You've never asked me
for anything, Marsha.
And whatever I've given you,
I've gotten back many times
over.
You're the closest I've
ever had to a family.
But if something's wrong,
honey, I wanna be able to help.
It's nothing, really.
I think I'm just feeling
a little bit guilty.
Well, I met somebody,
and I'm afraid I
may have blown it already.
So you slept with a
guy on the first date.
I wouldn't even
call it a date.
So you're having second
thoughts about him,
wondering if he
thinks you're easy,
or perhaps easy to forget?
Exactly.
If it'll make you
feel any better, Marsha,
you are not easy to forget.
What would I do without you?
You'll get by.
I promise.
[laughter]
Hi.
Oh, hey.
Better late than never.
Maddie, remember?
Of course.
Here you go.
You didn't have to do that.
I insist.
Now maybe you can tell
me what there is to do
around here for excitement.
Well, I just walked into this
bar and told 'em I was looking.
Asked me if I could tend bars.
I said sure.
Bingo, I'm a shot girl
at the Duke of Earl.
What is the Duke of Earl?
It's a strip place.
Very upscale, though, so they
call it "exotic dancing."
You know, guys come in,
drink, watch the girls.
So you're a stripper?
No, no.
Hardly.
No, the-- the shot girls
is where the real money is.
You just work the floor
pouring shots for guys,
and they tip you really great.
Sounds good to me.
What are you doing?
Uh, well, I guess I'm
back to waitressing.
I love your place.
Excuse my pigginess.
Don't worry about it.
You should see my place.
Jean, I have a big
favor I have to ask you.
Shoot.
Um, I don't know anybody
here, and I'm having
some money being wired to me.
Uh-huh.
And I don't have
a bank account yet.
So I was wondering if it
would be all right if I could
have it sent to your account.
You know, just for
now till I get setup.
I'll pay the charges and stuff.
Sure, when's it due?
Tomorrow, I hope.
Here, let me get it.
All my account
stuff's in here, so
just let me know
when they send it,
and I'll cash it out for you.
Great.
Thank you so much.
You know, you should
check out the Duke of Earl
if you need a job.
You should come by tonight.
I'm working.
Yeah?
Well, maybe I'll come
by and take a look.
OK.
It'd be fun to work together.
The place is a trip.
Yeah?
Can't wait.
All right, I'll see you.
OK, bye-bye.
[music playing]
(SINGING) One, two--
one, two, three, four.
[cheering]
Driving in my car,
she slides next to me.
She puts her hand up
on my leg, shows me
where her interests be.
Oh, oh, oh, Oh, oh, oh.
Can you feel it?
Yeah.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Can you feel it?
Dance and dance all night, baby.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Can you feel it?
On our way back home, gonna
turn the world around.
I'll take you into the
dark of night, speed south.
Rum and coke?
Hi.
Tabletop.
Woo!
Tabletop!
Ah-hah!
Woo!
Yeah.
$200 to lose the top.
200 bucks for the top.
200 bucks.
$200.
Top.
The top!
200 bucks.
$200 more for the top.
[chuckling]
Sorry, babe, wasn't
worth the extra.
Am I wrong?
What?
Was I wrong?
Are you OK?
What a jerk.
That bastard owes me $200.
Don't worry about it, OK?
Be right back.
Good evening, sir.
I believe you owe the lady $250.
[chuckling]
They've called the police.
Now, give me the damn money, and
get your fat ass out of here.
He gave you an extra 50,
for pain and suffering.
Well, let me buy you a drink.
Two double stoli tonics on
the rocks, please, bartender.
Ooh, what a
night, what a night.
Just another
day at the office.
I'll make some coffee.
I know you need some.
No, no, no, no.
No coffee.
You got vodka?
Double vodka coming right up.
What a jerk.
And you, I don't believe you.
Yeah, well,
seeing is believing.
And I still can't believe
you took your clothes
off in front of all those guys.
Yeah, well, I guess
when someone is waving
the next month's
rent under your nose,
your inhibitions
go out the window.
Yeah, I know the feeling.
So anyway, on
to happier topics.
Tell me about your boyfriend.
Well, I don't even know if
I can call him my boyfriend.
We got real close, real quick.
And I don't know if I'm
afraid of hurting him
or he's afraid of
hurting me, but I
think we need some time apart.
Hm, been there.
Thing is, he's really
cute, incredibly nice.
And you wanna talk about money.
Ah, so finally
the truth comes out!
It helps, but
it's not the money.
I just can't stop
thinking about him.
Hm.
So what about you?
Ugh.
Well, there is this one guy
who comes into the club.
Everyone says he watches
me the whole night.
He never even watches the
show, just little old me.
He wasn't there tonight, but
if he'd just say hello to me--
Ugh.
Oh, you saved my life.
What did I drink?
Not "what," my dear.
"How many."
Get some sleep.
You're gonna feel
lousy in the morning.
MARSHA: Ugh.
WOMAN (ON PHONE): There's a Jean
Ivers to see you, Mr. Kronfeld.
HENRY (ON PHONE):
There's a what?
WOMAN (ON PHONE): A Miss Jean
Ivers is in the lobby, sir.
Well, all right.
I'm coming right down.
Jean Ivers, sir.
What the hell
are you doing here,
calling yourself Jean Ivers?
Would you relax, Henry?
It's OK.
Just get back
there and get on it.
You're seen here, I'm dead.
We're both dead.
Henry, I want out, OK?
She's a really nice girl.
I don't know what you're
planning to do to her,
but I don't want any part of it.
You don't what what?
You don't want what?
I set you up with the
deal of a lifetime!
Oh, no, no, missy.
We go back too far together.
You owe me money!
Now, you follow through on this,
or I'm gonna find your brother,
and I'm gonna end his
debt once and for all.
Just tell me you're
not gonna hurt her.
I already told
you, now just do it.
You better eat, sleep,
and breathe Jean Ivers.
Hey, it's not like you
to fall for a mark, huh?
I mean, what happened
to the old Marsha.
All right, I'll do it.
But after this, we're through.
Clean slate.
And if anything happens to her,
Henry, I'm going to the cops.
Hey, nothing's gonna happen.
Promise.
[dialing]
ANSWERING MACHINE: You have
reached the office of Mr Stein.
Mr. Stein is not
available at the moment.
If you would like to
leave a message, please--
[beep]
WOMAN: Perfectly
still, Mr. Stein.
Perfectly still.
The new girl get here yet?
Yeah, she's
trying on an outfit.
Oh, good.
But I don't think how it looks
on her is gonna be a problem.
Who's that?
Did you see that?
Oh, my gosh.
You got it, baby.
Great!
Hello?
It's open!
MARSHA: HI.
Hey.
Oh, your wire came through.
You want the cash?
Oh, I'm not quite set up
yet. you think you could hang
on to it for a couple days?
Sure.
Try not to spend it.
Guess what?
I got the job.
Get outta here.
I'm a cocktail waitress.
That's great.
- Can you do me a favor?
- Hm.
I left my soda out
on the patio table.
Can you grab it for me?
Yeah.
You wicked girl, you.
You knew, didn't you?
Oops.
Good shot.
Pour.
OK, to, um-- to great wealth.
I think I've reached
the point where I can
safely say that's passed me by.
Don't let it.
Even if you have to
trip it on its way up.
If I had your looks,
I'd go for it too.
It's-- it's not looks.
It's attitude.
There's this older
friend that I have.
He's always given me as
much as I've given him.
Friendship, advice,
companionship, no questions
asked.
He happens to be wealthy, but
he's got such style and grace
that even if he
didn't own a dime,
you'd still wanna
spend time with him.
He's amazing.
Sugardaddy?
MARSHA: No.
No, he's way too
classy for that.
Have you heard
from your boyfriend?
He could be a dead issue.
He hasn't called.
Maybe it's just not meant to be.
[dialing]
Hey, Jody, it's me.
Any calls?
JODY (ON PHONE): Yes,
Matt Conrad called.
He just got back to town, and
please call him at 555-0287.
You go that?
Uh-huh.
JODY (ON PHONE):
He said he'd like
to see you as soon as possible.
Thank you, Jody.
You are a doll.
[music playing]
[giggling]
You are so beautiful.
Come here.
You know, I gotta tell you,
ever since I met you it's--
I don't know what happened.
I was so numb and indifferent.
And now-- I dunno.
Everything just seemed so
black and white before,
and now everything's in color.
You know, I've been happy.
I really like you.
I'm crazy about you.
I don't wanna lose you.
[phone ringing]
Hello.
HENRY (ON PHONE): Hey, slim.
Henry.
We're on the fast
track now, honey.
The old lady's in a coma.
Stick around for an
envelope in the morning.
Oh, my god.
It's really gonna happen.
HENRY (ON PHONE): You're
gonna be rich, kid.
Very rich.
[music playing]
(SINGING) Well, she took me in.
She took me out.
She cried to me
the same old story.
Said she owned it a
crucifix, and so Jesus
is her best friend.
So I took the chance.
I did the dance.
[inaudible] was all her glory.
Saint no more.
She's shy, shy,
shy, Saint no more.
When the carousel
sprang apart [inaudible]
Said she planned it
all 2,000 years ago,
when she was first engaged.
Did you see him?
That's the guy.
He's cute.
Relax.
OK.
Go get him.
[music playing]
(SINGING) Rock my body.
Ooh.
Rock my body.
Kiss me.
Ooh.
Rock my body.
Body kiss, body kiss.
Ooh.
Rock my body.
Body move, body groove.
Body get you in the mood.
Body wet, body sweat,
body wants to if you let.
Body cream, body scream.
Body knows just what you mean.
Body bliss, body lips,
body wants your body kiss.
Ooh, you got the motion.
Yeah.
Ooh, you're poetry in motion.
That's right.
Ooh, ah, oh.
Let's make contact.
Oh, just like that.
Ooh, Rock my body.
Body kiss.
We are the future of
love and sex and melody.
We provide the body.
A physical intercourse.
Let's body kiss.
Yeah.
To a florgy.
[moaning]
Body glance, body dance,
body find a new romance.
Body hot, body rock,
body never wanna stop.
Body in, body out, body
make you wanna shout.
Body down, body up.
Body only wanna fuck.
Love me, somebody.
Kiss me. somebody.
Hold me, somebody.
Scold me, somebody.
Do me, somebody.
Scream me, somebody.
Love me, somebody.
[knocking on door]
MARSHA: Who is it?
MAN: A special delivery.
Oh, thank you.
[phone ringing]
Hello.
Hello, Marsha.
Henry.
Listen, I don't know
how to tell you this,
but I got a call
from the DA's office,
and they're-- they're
asking about you.
I don't know how much they know.
I couldn't get a read, but
you better get out of there
and lie low for a while.
I knew it was too
good to be true.
Where's Jean?
Listen, don't worry about her.
Worry about yourself.
Go to your manager.
Give him some sort of a story.
Go down to Key West.
I-- I got a place down there.
MARSHA (ON PHONE): OK.
Call me when
when you get close.
[music playing]
It's OK, boss, It's OK.
She's on her way to the Keys.
I'm coming back to town.
[phone ringing]
Hello.
Hello?
WOMAN (ON PHONE): Miss Thomas?
Miss Thomas, we just
signed something for you.
It's very important.
Can you hear me?
Miss Tho-- it's very important.
Must call Stein's office.
Hello?
Miss Thomas?
[buzzing]
WOMAN (ON PHONE): Operator.
- Hello, operator.
I'm wondering if
you could help me.
WOMAN (ON PHONE): What's
the number, please?
555-1209.
WOMAN (ON PHONE): Hello?
Hello.
WOMAN (ON PHONE):
Oh, Miss Thomas.
Thank you so much
for calling back.
Something has come
up, and did you know
that Mr. Stein has been ill?
What?
I didn't.
WOMAN (ON PHONE): Listen,
try to get over here.
I can't discuss it on the phone.
We need to see you
as soon as possible.
Hey!
Can you give me a ride to Miami?
Sure, hop in.
Henry, this is Miss Jones.
She's been doing some
document transfers for us.
She always helps to
track down Miss Thomas.
And this is Mr. Stevens.
Mr. Stevens is the trust nominee
for the estate of Mr. Stein.
How do you do?
I'll be brief.
I'm sure you're both
anxious to hear the terms.
Uh, Miss Thomas
has been advised
that she's one of
the beneficiaries
to Mr. Stein's estate.
However, naturally, we're
not aware of the specifics.
Quite.
Miss Thomas?
You can call me Marsha.
Miss Thomas, shortly
before Mr. Stein died,
he created a living trust,
you as the beneficiary
and I am the trustee.
At your direction, however,
I may remain as trustee,
or you may appoint
whomsoever you
wish as a replacement trustee.
Is this clear to you?
Perfectly.
Good.
He also intimated to
me that he trusted
your judgment implicitly.
So I must now ask you
if you wish to appoint
a replacement trustee.
Yes, she does.
And here is the appropriate
appointment document nominating
myself as trustee and the firm
of T Markowitz and Kronfeld
as legal advisors.
Yes.
Very efficient.
Thank you.
May we we know
the exact terms?
Well, the list is quite long.
It's approximately $2 million
in cash, about six million
in stocks, shares,
and other assets.
This is a schedule of the
assets and their disposition.
I will prepare my resignation
paper with your appointment
as replacement trustee.
Those papers have to
be filed in court.
It may take a few days.
Meanwhile, I will
follow your directions.
Miss Thomas, I'd like to
reiterate a conversation
that I had with Henry.
With your permission, of course.
Miss Thomas, Mr. Stein
was a very private person.
Now, while he had
no immediate family,
he did have some
very close friends
and associates who will
not benefit to the extent
that you will.
In short, Mr. Stein
was very discreet.
We feel that it would be
in everyone's best interest
if your windfall, as
it were, were held
with a level of
discretion that Mr. Stein
would have deemed appropriate.
In short, this is
a private affair,
I mean, private matter,
and not for publication.
Mr. Hayes speaks
perfect English.
You don't have to translate.
What Mr. Stein and I did or
didn't do is nobody's business.
I understand, Mr.
Hayes, is that it?
That's it, Miss Thomas.
I'll be in touch,
as will Mr. Stevens.
I'll see you in
the coffee shop.
Thank you.
I've never had
a trustee before.
Well, you got one now, and
we're gonna have a lot of fun.
What did you do with Marsha?
I mean, you are gonna give
her a chunk of change,
like you said, right?
I got a little problem
with that right now,
but we'll work it out.
Right now,m it's best that
you lay low in the house
for a couple of days.
Well, aren't we
going to the Bahamas?
You sure are.
WOMAN: Miss Thomas,
Mr. Stein died
rather suddenly a few days ago.
I'm really sorry to be
the one to tell you this.
Can I, uh, get you
a glass of water?
No.
No, thank you.
It was all very sudden, and
we were all pretty shocked.
He was a wonderful man.
Yes.
Thank you.
[music playing]
[sobbing]
Matt.
Thanks for coming.
It's OK.
It's OK to cry.
He was all I had
when my brother left.
He was always there for me.
This is so unfair.
Feeling any better?
A little bit.
I made you some tea.
I have some things
I have to tell you.
And after I've said
what I have to say,
I hope you'll still
wanna be with me.
What is it, Cassandra?
First of all, my
name's not "Cassandra."
It's "Marsha."
[dialing]
HENRY (ON PHONE): Hello.
They are both in the house.
What do you want me to do?
HENRY (ON PHONE):
I can talk to you
right now, so just sit tight.
Give it a half hour.
And if there's no movement, go
on over to my house and check
on the other girl.
Um, introduce yourself.
Tell her you work for
me and you're there just
to see if she needs anything.
Just make sure she stays put.
Check with me later.
- OK, boss.
Henry, we've begun to
liquidate all the stocks
and other assets as
you've instructed,
selling them at
current market value.
You know, Mr. Stein had sold
off most of his securities,
so the remainder
can be liquidated
within, oh, five business days.
As for the cash
and other assets,
they'll be transferred
immediately.
Yeah, yeah.
Here you go.
The First Bahamian Bank.
Yes, I know it well.
I assume you'll take care of
the regulatory requirements?
As soon as possible.
Ah.
It shall be done.
Henry, I'm awfully sorry
to lose this account.
I'm assuming that you
are not unhappy with us.
Oh, no, no.
Nothing like that.
It's just business.
Ah-huh.
And Miss Thomas is aware
of what you're doing?
Actually, it was
at her direction.
She wants to keep it
liquid, and thought it best
that we keep it all offshore.
She's a very sharp lady.
Thank you.
[knocking]
(SINGING) And I need
someone to believe in.
Just give me someone
to believe in.
Just give me-- and I
was lying to myself.
This is me and no
one else, I know.
Someone to believe in.
Just give me someone
to believe in.
Jose, what are you doing here?
Don't I get a kiss?
Huh?
Of course you do.
How did you find me?
I'm working for him.
He hired me to
keep an eye on you.
Isn't that something?
Jesus, did you tell him that--
No, do you think I'm crazy?
Hang on a minute.
What, so all those evenings
at the Duke of Earl,
what you were working
for him, watching me?
It's great work
if you can get it.
Does he know that
you're here now?
He asked me to come
over and introduce myself.
This is too bizarre.
Did he say anything about us?
I mean, about me and him?
Mm-mm.
I'm strictly field work.
You know, surveillance,
sometimes persuasion.
Whatever he needs
done, I do for a price
and the fringe benefits.
How about a little more
enthusiasm, dear, huh?
You know Henry's
gonna come by.
No, I didn't know.
We'd better hurry up, then.
WOMAN (ON RADIO): This is Tina
Martell, with 93.9 FM Love 94.
And it's another hot,
steamy day in Miami.
Expect a high in the mid-90s.
Here's some music
to match the heat.
[music playing]
(SINGING) Baby, are you
in the mood tonight?
[moaning]
Baby, wanna make love tonight?
Take it slow and easy.
Take our time tonight.
I'm gonna fill you
up with my loving.
I'm gonna take you there.
I'm gonna kiss you
all over, baby.
I'm gonna kiss ya.
I'm gonna kiss you
all over, baby.
I'm gonna take you there.
So take it slow and easy.
We're gonna take
our time tonight.
I'm gonna fill you
up with my loving.
I'm gonna take you there.
I'm gonna kiss you
all over, baby.
I'm gonna kiss you.
I'm gonna kiss you all over.
I'm gonna kiss you
all over, baby.
I'm gonna take you there.
I'm gonna kiss you all over.
I'm gonna kiss you
all over, baby.
I'm gonna take you there.
Take it slow and easy.
We'll take our time tonight.
I'm gonna fill you
up with my loving.
I'm gonna take you there.
I'm gonna kiss you
all over, baby.
I'm gonna kiss ya.
I'm gonna kiss you all over.
I'm gonna kiss you
all over, baby.
I'm gonna take you there.
I'm gonna kiss you all over.
I'm gonna kiss you
all over, baby.
I'm gonna take you there.
I'm gonna kiss you all over.
I'm gonna kiss you
all over, baby.
I'm gonna take you there.
I'm gonna kiss ya.
I'm gonna kiss you all over.
I'm gonna kiss you
all over, baby.
I'm gonna take you there.
What did you mean
by "persuasion"?
Hm?
"Persuasion,"
what did you mean?
Oh, whatever it takes.
What, like you beat people up?
It's generally
helping them to remember
late payments and stuff.
Oh.
Well, is there
something that you
were gonna help me to remember?
No, you were
only half the job.
I had to take out that girl
you work with, Marsha somebody.
Only, I'm still on the case.
You were gonna kill her?
Well, I was gonna
do what I was told to.
I'm gonna be sick.
Come on, I thought you knew.
Come on, hurry.
Get dressed.
Henry's gonna be here soon.
Where is Marsha now?
Where is she?
She's playing with Matt
Conrad over at his place
in the Gables.
HENRY: Jean, it's Henry.
Oh, my god.
Come on, hurry.
Jean?
JEAN: I'm coming.
Come on, get that little
money maker over here.
You OK?
Yeah.
Hey, did you meet Jose?
Uh-huh.
Listen, there's
been a change in plan.
I've gotta go upstate on
business for a couple of days.
Uh, we'll go to the Bahamas
when I come back, OK?
Jose'll take care of you.
Where is he?
I don't know.
I think he--
Jose?
You wanted me, Boss?
I was in the little boys' room.
HENRY: Yeah, come down here.
Yeah, you wanna, uh, grab
the luggage, take it outside?
You can forget about
Marsha for a while.
Stick with this one.
I got some papers.
They're very important papers.
Keep them away from her,
out of sight, and sealed.
Claro?
You got it, Boss.
It's, uh, in the
brown envelope.
What's that?
Something for Henry.
Oh, well, here, I'll take it.
No.
He wants me to keep it safe.
No peeking.
Well, what do you
say we have a drink?
Maybe it'd put us in the mood?
Maybe.
I'll get the glasses.
Ugh.
[honking]
Open up, please.
Please, open up.
Oh, god, it's Jean.
Let her in.
Jean, I'm so glad you're OK.
Do you know what's going on?
JEAN: Mr. Stein had
created a trust for you.
And-- and Henry had
got his hands on it.
MARSHA: Can you
believe this guy?
JEAN: He was playing you
against me and me against you.
Oh, remember that-- that
guy, Jose from the club?
Ugh, did he turn out
to be a nightmare.
Come on, sit down.
- Jean, this is Matt.
- Hi.
Hi.
I've heard a lot about you.
Same here.
All right, take your time.
Tell us from the beginning.
OK.
Oh, first off, you have
to call Mr. Stevens.
He's Stein's lawyer.
That's his number.
And I don't care
what happens to me.
I'm just so glad you're OK.
Nothing's gonna
happen to you, but wait
till I get my hands on Henry.
JEAN: Well, you'd
better move fast,
'cause I think he's trying to
do something with your money.
MATT: Yes, here it is, the Henry
Kronfeld financial records.
Now we can access
his bank accounts.
[typing]
Hm, looks like your friend
Henry is moving everything
to a bank in the Bahamas.
Let's see what we
can do about that.
Let's give the system
10, 15 minutes.
It pays to do a little hacking.
May I get you coffee?
He said it won't be long.
What?
May I get you coffee?
No, no, no.
That's-- that's OK.
WOMAN: If you need a
phone to call the States,
there's one right over there.
Oh, no.
I'm sure everything's OK, yeah.
[door opens]
Mr. Kronfeld, sorry
to have kept you.
Oh, thank you.
May I offer you
something to drink?
Oh, no, no, no.
Let's-- let's just get
right down to business.
You did receive the wire
transfers into my account?
Indeed, we received the wires.
Well, all right, good.
Now, here's what
I want you to do.
I want you to divide
the transfers into three
separate accounts,
and then wire transfer
them to these three different
banks in Switzerland right now.
I'm afraid we can't
do that, Mr. Kronfeld.
What?
I'm afraid we can't do that.
Excuse me.
Did you or did you not,
uh, receive the transfer.
We did.
All right, so
then what's problem?
Mr. Kronfeld, the money
was transferred and credited
to your account here, but
a short time ago, the money
was removed from your
account here and transferred
to a stateside account.
What?
It appears that
of the $8 million
that was transferred into your
account, only $75 was left in.
$75?
That's the amount that
appears on your account balance.
Would you like to leave
it in or withdraw it?
I am the sole
appointed trustee.
I mean, I did not grant you
the authority to do that.
I'm afraid we have no say
in the matter, Mr. Kronfeld.
I suggest you take it up
with your bank in the States.
[phone ringing]
Yes?
WOMAN (ON PHONE): I have a long
distance call for Mr. Kronfeld.
Put it through.
Mr. Kronfeld.
Hello.
Nice try, you bastard.
The $75 is to get
your ass back here,
and we'll settle our
accounts once and for all.
Oh, and don't try using
your credit cards.
We've terminated your accounts.
Are you all right, sir?
Sir?
Can-- can I withdraw
the $75 right now?
All right, now just relax.
See the yellow ball?
That's the two ball.
Now, just hit it real
easy on the side.
Marsha, Marsha, Marsha.
Now, we-- uh, we gotta
work something out.
I mean, and--
And nothing, you bastard.
Where's my money?
It's right where it's supposed
to be-- in my trust account.
I'm the trustee.
You don't touch it
unless I say so.
So long as you're the trustee.
Well, you got the picture.
Well, Henry,
you've been replaced.
I've been replaced, huh?
I've been replaced.
Well, I'll tell you what.
We'll split it 50/50.
It's a win-win situation
for both of us.
No, no more deals, Henry.
Besides, you don't have
much to bargain with.
Oh, what about your friend?
I mean, right now, she's
in a lot of trouble.
Come on, Henry.
Is that the best you can do?
If she goes down, you go down.
[pool balls clack]
I'll tell you what.
We'll flip a coin for it,
Winner takes everything.
No, no.
I don't like games of chance.
How about a game of skill?
Name it.
One game of eight ball.
We play for it.
You-- you don't know
what to think, do you?
Am I conning?
Are you conning me?
I mean, I watched you play.
I could be thinking, "This
is gonna be a piece of cake."
Don't listen to him.
He's conning you.
Shut up!
So what's it gonna be, slim?
We flip a coin or
we play for it?
If you win, I sign
off as trustee,
and your brother's
debt is history.
And if you win?
I'll be generous.
We'll split everything 50/50.
Henry, why the hell
should I trust you?
A deal's a deal.
Tell you what,
you've got the break,
and I'll let you keep shooting
till you sink the first one.
Now, how's that for a deal?
it's your money.
I didn't introduce you.
Henry, this is Matt Conrad.
He's the owner of
that Ferrari you
had sent down to South America.
Oh, well, sorry about that.
Rack 'em.
What the hell was that?
You outsmarted yourself,
you greedy bastard.
Remember the Henry
Kronfeld con rules.
First, know your mark.
Their likes, dislikes,
history, and abilities.
Excuse me.
Take nothing for granted.
Everything is significant,
down to the last detail.
Excuse me.
Not knowing something
can be fatal.
All right.
Shit.
Well, guess the news.
When I was in
college, my brother
Frankie couldn't always
afford my incidentals,
so I played pool.
Three hours a day,
seven days a week.
Now, sign the papers and
get the hell outta here.
Here you go, big man.
Henry, I've got
your dick in a bangle.
Any more shit from you
and I'll turn the handle.
Give me that.
Just sign the papers.
Can I read this first?
Sign it.
So where are you taking me?
What's the big secret?
Oh, you'll see.
I told you, it pays to do
a little bit of hacking.
Do you live here?
Why are you asking?
Yeah, why are you asking?
Is your dad home?
My stepdad is.
Why don't you
get some lemonade.
I'll be right back.
OK, let's have one
lemonade, please.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Frankie?
Frankie!
Oh.
I thought I'd never
see you again.
I didn't wanna cause
you any more trouble.
You're my family.
I was so worried about you.
I've been looking
and looking for you.
I've been cleaning up my life.
I've been on the
wagon for two years,
and I didn't even bet $1 on
the Super Bowl this year.
Oh, Frankie!
I thought I'd never
see you again.
I guess you two have a lot
of, uh, catching up to do.
Um, we have a lot
of catching up to do.
[chuckling]
[music playing]
(SINGING) I don't care
how it's supposed to be,
only what you mean to me, how
I'd feel if you were gone.
You said that we
would never cry.
You said we'd never say goodbye.
But that was long ago.
More than yesterday.
It was once upon a magic moment.
We had suns and silver moons and
the sky was filled with wonder.
It was the greatest
love I've ever known.
You said we'd never say goodbye.
You said that we
would never cry.
That was long ago.
More than yesterday.
It was once upon a magic moment.
La, la, la, la.