[CLASSICAL MUSIC PLAYS]
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYS]
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYS]
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYS]
- [GUNSHOT]
- Banzai!
Get your hands up!
Get down! Get down!
You, get down! Get down!
Put your hands
where I can see them!
Give me the money!
Stay there!
- [WOMAN SCREAMS]
- Give me the money!
Come on!
Fuckin' hurry up!
Stay there!
The money! Hurry up!
[SHOUTS IN JAPANESE]
Come on!
Go, go, go, go!
Get it all in there!
- These are delicious. I'll give you some.
- Come on! Come on! Let's hurry!
Come on! Come on!
Come on!
[ETHEREAL MUSIC PLAYS]
[GLASS SHATTERS]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYS]
[WHISTLES]
[WHISPERING] Hey.
Hey.
This is a bracelet of hope.
Thank you!
[THUNDER RUMBLES]
[ALL SHOUTING IN JAPANESE]
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYS]
[CAR DOORS SHUT]
[ALL PANTING]
Bernice, what are
we going to do?
Whatever we want to do.
We've never been
outside our house before.
Are we free?
Is this what it feels like?
[SIGHS] I think it feels
much better than that.
[ENGINE STARTS]
[TICKING]
[ETHEREAL MUSIC PLAYS]
[GASPS]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYS]
[GASPS]
[SHOUTING IN DISTANCE]
[FIRES CRACKLING]
[WHISPERING INDISTINCTLY]
[SOBS SOFTLY]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
I'm not a prisoner!
Kagome kagome
The bird in the cage.
When, oh, when will it come out
In the night of dawn
The crane and turtle slipped
Who is behind you now?
Good to see you children.
[CHILDREN SHOUT IN JAPANESE]
[ROOSTER CROWS]
[FLIES BUZZING]
[WHIRRING, CRACKLING]
[WESTERN MUSIC PLAYS]
[WESTERN MUSIC CONTINUES]
[FOOTSTEPS THUD]
[SHOUTING CONTINUES]
The Governor!
Come on, let's move!
[KEYS RATTLE]
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYS]
[FLIES BUZZING]
[BUZZING STOPS]
[WOMEN CHANTING "GOVERNOR!"]
[CHANTING CONTINUES]
[CHAINS RATTLING]
[CHANTING STOPS]
[WOMEN LAUGH]
Cocksucker, motherfucker.
[LAUGHTER CONTINUES]
[CROWD JEERING]
Let me see your balls!
[LAUGHTER]
Don't mess my white shoes up!
[ALL SCREAM]
- THE GOVERNOR: Is this him?
- MAN: Yes, sir, Governor.
He's a mean looking cuss,
ain't he?
They say...
you're a veritable phantasm,
that you have slipped through
the firm grasp of the law
more than any other man
on God's great earth.
They also say...
you're the one who robbed the
Bleufeur National Bank in P29,
killing, among others,
three tellers,
two security guards,
a retired Navy colonel,
his mother,
and a small boy,
whose only crime was masticating
a sweet cheery cherry gumball.
Suit, please, Yasujiro.
My granddaughter, Bernice,
has been lost to us, sir.
[CAR DOOR SHUTS]
Ah, thank you, Yasujiro.
Bernice.
I have a fondness
for black leather.
I tell you truly, sir,
my granddaughter,
my sweet sugar pie,
I would have her returned to me.
[REVOLVER COCKS]
I would have her
returned to me posthaste.
And you, sir...
you, sir, I am told,
are the man to do the job.
Bernice.
[SCREAMS]
Bernice!
Bernice! Bernice!
THE GOVERNOR: Uh, Yasujiro.
[SOBBING] Bernice...
[GIGGLING]
[LAUGHTER]
[LAUGHTER INTENSIFIES]
Oh, my gosh.
I've seen better.
♪ My grandfather's clock
was too large for the shelf ♪
♪ So it stood 90 years
on the floor ♪
♪ It was taller by half
than the old man himself ♪
♪ Though it weighed not
a pennyweight more ♪
♪ It was bought on the morn
of the day that he was born ♪
♪ And was always
his treasure and pride ♪
♪ But it stopped,
short never to go again ♪
♪ When the old man died
♪ 90 years without slumbering
♪ Tick tock, tick tock
♪ His life seconds numbering
♪ It stopped,
short never to go again ♪
♪ When the old man died
My, my!
Don't that fit nice and snug.
Just beyond the point
where we now stand
lies a stretch of highway
where evil reigns.
It's ghost!
Ghost, I tell you!
Ooh!
- [SPEAKS JAPANESE]
- [CHILDREN SHOUT]
In the way of the road!
- They can be anywhere.
- Shut up!
Now you see them.
Now you don't.
I said shut up!
Oh, it's alright, Sheriff.
I know many who subscribe
to that...
supernatural mumbo jumbo.
Ghosts...
perhaps.
Or, maybe, it's a bunch
of godless sodomites
that have taken
the land prisoner.
I fear my sweet Bernice
has fallen
into their perverse lair.
I can see why you
want her back.
What did he say?!
I'll kill you!
[CROWD CHANTING]
[CHANTING CONTINUES]
Yahhh!
[GAGS]
[CHANTING CONTINUES]
THE GOVERNOR:
No man is yet to be
a worthy opponent
for my Yasujiro.
I warn you, sir,
to quarrel with me is a mistake
many men have made
never to make again.
Better zip up there.
You don't want
to catch a cold.
[CHUCKLES]
[WHIRRING]
It's a remarkable device,
isn't it?
Let me point out some
of its finer qualities.
Each arm is equipped
with an explosive device.
Oh, it's a protective measure.
These devices are connected
to a neuro sensor,
which can recognize the impulse
of a man intending
to strike a helpless woman.
Should that impulse be detected,
an alarm will sound
and if unheeded,
detonation will occur.
Your trousers are also
equipped with explosives.
The one at each testicle.
[LAUGHS, SPEAKS JAPANESE]
[SPEAKS JAPANESE]
- Boom!
- [LAUGHTER]
Really?
I would have my Bernice
returned to me unsoiled, sir,
so best mind your manners.
Oh, now, I'm sure you've noticed
the charges around your throat.
You attempt to remove
or alter in any way
this magnificent wardrobe...
well,
I think you get the idea, sir.
If you can crawl your dog's hide
into the unknown and the unholy,
rescue my Bernice,
return her to me unscathed
to this very spot,
you will walk away a free man.
SUSIE: No!
Don't give my sister to him!
He's the devil.
A real devil!
[CACKLES]
Da-da-da-da-da-da!
[LAUGHS HYSTERICALLY]
- [CROWD GASPS]
- [CAR DOOR SLAMS]
Well, I assume you have
accepted my offer.
Shin?
Give the man the keys
to his automobile.
HERO: What is this?
Each bulb
on that colorful display
indicates
the passing of 24 hours.
at the conclusion
of three days,
Bernice must speak her name
into
the spectrograms microphone.
It is programmed
to identify her lovely voice.
Once voiceprint recognition
has been achieved,
the device will reward you
with two extra days
to complete your task.
At the end of five days,
if you have not
returned with Bernice
to get your suit
unlocked and removed,
the explosives will
detonate all at once.
I am certain this will prompt
a speedy execution of your task.
You got me, son?
What are you
gonna unlock it with?
Why...
right here.
Godspeed.
Any God can bear
to look upon your face.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYS]
[ENGINE STARTS]
[WOMAN SCREAMS]
[ENGINE TURNS OFF]
[WESTERN MUSIC PLAYS]
Wait!
You cheap villainous maggot!
What a badass.
He's so cool.
[WESTERN MUSIC CONTINUES]
[ENGINE REVS]
Not much time, huh?
Alright.
[BELL RINGS]
[WESTERN MUSIC RESUMES]
[WESTERN MUSIC CONTINUES]
[TIRES SCREECH]
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYS]
[WHIRRING]
[ENGINE REVS]
[CRASHING]
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYS]
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[POWER TOOLS WHIRRING]
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
[MEN SHRIEKING]
MAN: It's alright!
Don't worry!
[HISSES]
[MEN SHOUT IN
DISTORTED LANGUAGE]
Don't touch my arm,
you fuckin' vermin.
I'm not vermin!
I'm a man!
Man right here!
[ALL SHRIEKING]
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYS]
What happened to Stella?
Bernice?
- Bernice?
- I'm not Bernice.
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
[WIND GUSTS]
[OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
[ROCKING CHAIR CREAKS]
[BELL TOLLS]
[CHEERING]
[BELL DINGING IN DISTANCE]
Where did you come from?
Do you want to join us?
There are so many of us.
What's your name?
Can't you speak?
Say something!
Hey! Talk!
[INDISTINCT SHOUTING]
We are almost there!
Hang in there!
[OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
[WOMEN CHANTING]
[WHISTLE BLOWS IN DISTANCE]
[INDISTINCT CHANTING]
[INDISTINCT SHOUTING]
Keep the time from moving!
If time starts moving...
...everything will explode again!
Keep time from moving!
[GROANS]
Thick red blood!
He has thick red blood!
[GROANING]
The Prophecy!
Time will move again!
WOMEN: Thick red blood!
He has thick red blood!
It is time!
Thick red blood!
Maybe someday...
...these children can drink
wonderful water...
No! No, no, no.
Don't touch me.
- Don't touch me. No, no, no.
- ...breathe wonderful air. live in a wonderful world!
Let go. No, no.
- No, no, no, no, no.
- Feel the fresh blood on their faces!
[WOMEN CHANT INDISTINCTLY]
HERO: [GROANING]
[CHANTING CONTINUES]
[MEN SHOUT
IN DISTORTED LANGUAGE]
HERO: No!
I'll karate chop you!
Stop it!
All is in pain.
[CARNIVAL MUSIC PLAYS]
You must surrender to fate.
You have wandered off your path
and stumbled
into unknown danger.
You were fortunate
the Ratman and his rat clan
found you along the highway
and brought you
to the Ghostland.
Perhaps you should
offer him gratitude.
[MEN SHOUT
IN DISTORTED LANGUAGE]
Hi-fucking-yah!
[CROWD SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY]
Ratman! Get the fuck out!
[ALL SCREAMING]
You know something?
You people...
are all fucking nuts.
What brings you to our land?
Who wants to know?
I am Enoch, leader of our tribe.
Who are you?
Nobody.
Just a guy looking for a girl.
Soon as I find her,
I'm out of here.
This is the Ghostland,
my friend.
The land of no escape,
only... endurance and survival.
This is the girl
I'm looking for.
Her name's Bernice.
She disappeared out here
while joyriding with her friend.
Any of you whack-jobs see her?
She was with me!
Still run from home.
But Bernice wouldn't go back.
Did anyone else see her?
- I saw her!
- MAN: I saw her, too.
[INDISTINCT SHOUTING]
Where!? Where is she?
She's up in the mannequins.
Go find her yourself!
No! No, stop doing that.
How dare you?!
I said, don't touch it!
- [MURMURING]
- MAN: Treat it gently.
That's my masterpiece.
She needs darkness to comfort.
Cover the light!
The ghosts
saves souls like hers.
The sweetest and youngest
at first.
The ghosts exploit their fear.
They want power and freedom.
The ghosts are prisoners, too.
But I protect them.
I hide them!
We are not the ones
who hold her captive.
You're coming with me.
Little cookie stay with us!
She can't go out there!
Let's go.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYS]
Then I will have
that child instead.
What's wrong with you?
Talk!
She cannot.
That power has been
taken from her.
This prison has taken
something from us all.
Our voice.
Our hope.
Our courage.
From these innocent children,
the demon has taken the most.
shaken them with such
terrible horror
the the children,
they lose all will to live.
She must reclaim it herself.
If she is to survive.
Everyone!
It's time to read.
Your grandpa sent me to get you!
Now it's time to go
the fuck home!
[SENSOR BEEPING]
Alright. Alright.
Alright. Okay.
Let's just, uh...
Bernice...
we're friends here, right?
- [BEEPING STOPS]
- Let's just...
go the fuck home.
Look. Look.
It's your friends.
Your friends, remember?
Bernice, it's your friends.
See?
N-Now, wait.
Good.
We'll have you singing karaoke
in no time.
[WOMEN CHANT INDISTINCTLY]
Take me with you!
Take me!
- MAN: Me, too!
- Don't take this girl!
The demon is too powerful
to escape.
[SPEAKS JAPANESE]
[INDISTINCT CHANTING]
But the demon!
She murders anyone
attempting to escape.
Turn around!
[SOBS] What are you doing?
[CART CREAKS]
RATMAN:
[SPEAKS DISTORTED LANGUAGE]
Do you work too hard?
Well, that's right.
Power!
It has a lot of power!
I've been working on my truck.
They hear an engine.
They hear anything
with an engine.
They say...
an engine attracts the demon.
Is that so?
Cool. Cool.
You got any fuel for it?
I have fuel, yeah.
I've been taking it from
every car that comes through.
And right there is my oil can.
Nice work, Ratman.
I'll borrow one.
[LAUGHS]
I'll give it to you,
but I won't go with you.
Never! Never!
[WOMEN LAUGH]
[WIND GUSTING]
[SENSOR DINGS]
[THE GOVERNOR
SPEAKS INDISTINCTLY]
- Say your name...
- Alright.
Let's take care
of this right now.
THE GOVERNOR: Speak your name
into the microphone.
Speak your name
Speak into the microphone.
Come on, say your name.
THE GOVERNOR: Speak your name
into the microphone.
Say your name, Bernice!
Say your fucking name,
or tomorrow, we'll explode.
[SENSOR BEEPING]
Alright. Alright.
- Fuck it.
- [BEEPING STOPS]
I'll have you home
by tomorrow night.
Why don't I help you
take it off?
Come on.
Take it off.
Take it...
Take it all off.
Baby, take it off.
Take it... Take it off.
Take it off.
[SCOFFS]
Well, that's quite
a scar you got there.
You get that roller skating?
[CHUCKLES] Whoo!
Take it off.
Take it... Take it off.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Open your mouth.
[CHUCKLES]
Oh! Yeah!
[SENSOR BEEPING]
Fuck you!
[WHIRRING]
[SCREAMS] Oh!
[SHRIEKING]
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYS]
[SPEAKS JAPANESE]
[OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
[WIND GUSTS]
[LAUGHTER]
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYS]
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[TICKING]
- [GUNSHOT]
- Banzai!
Get your hands up!
You get down! Get down!
Put your hands
where I can see them.
Give me the money.
Say there!
- [WOMAN SCREAMS]
- Give me the money!
Come on!
Fuckin' hurry up!
Stay down!
The money! Hurry up!
[SHOUTS IN JAPANESE]
Come on!
Come on! Come on!
Go, go, go, go!
Come on!
Get all of it!
These are delicious.
I'll give you some.
Come on! Come on!
Alright.
What the fuck,
you're gonna shoot a kid?!
[GUNSHOT]
[GLASS SHATTERS]
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYS]
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[GRUNTS]
[ETHEREAL MUSIC PLAYS]
[ETHEREAL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[HEART BEATING]
[HEART BEAT SLOWS]
[HEART BEAT INTENSIFIES]
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYS]
- Did you take your medication?!
- Did you take yours?!
[SCREAMS]
[SOUND DISTORTS]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYS]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SCREAMS INDISTINCTLY]
You coward! Traitor!
[DRAMATIC MUSIC RESUMES]
[WIND GUSTS]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
Bernice.
[GROANS]
It was me.
I'm the one.
I'm sorry.
[HORN BLARES IN DISTANCE]
[GROANING IN DISTANCE]
[SINISTER MUSIC PLAYS]
[GROWLING]
Bernice, no!
Don't touch me!
Who's rubbing up on me?!
Let go of me!
- Let go of me!
- [SENSOR BEEPING]
Stop! Get away!
[WHIRRING]
[GROANING]
[SINISTER MUSIC CONTINUES]
Many years ago,
when I was just a child
There was a catastrophic wreck,
at mile 244...
It was the age of nuclear towers.
There was a massive reactor,
strong enough to power an empire,
...or destroy it.
Beneath it all...
the waste, the boiling toxic waste.
Buried, hidden, unclean.
The hidden secret legacy.
A mighty tanker burdened with
molten nuclear sludge.
On the searing highway
outside of the city... lost control.
It struck a transport carrying
deadly convicted men.
Covering them all with
the scalding atomic disease.
The burning!
The hideous burning!
The fire crept into the soil,
the ancient polluted earth
Every stone and tree had
sucked up the buried poison.
The entire city burst into flames!
[SINISTER MUSIC CONTINUES]
Why didn't anyone help?
[SPEAKS IN DISTORTED JAPANESE]
We called for help!
We called to the powerful
men in the atomic towers.
But the men of the toxic
empire could not confess it.
They must deny it...
Deny them all.
How do I get out of here?
[SPEAKS IN DISTORTED JAPANESE]
You found Bernice. The innocent soul.
Gave her a chance.
You are a hero.
[BEEPING]
THE GOVERNOR: Speak your name.
Bernice, this is grandpa.
I order you to say your name.
THE GOVERNOR: Speak your name
into the microphone.
Say your name
and get in the car, Bernice.
This gentleman will
escort you back home.
Speak your name
into the microphone.
Say your name to
Grandpa's friend, Bernice.
[GASPING]
[RASPY] I am Bernice.
THE GOVERNOR: Speak your name
into the microphone.
[WHIMPERS]
I... am... Bernice.
THE GOVERNOR: Speak your name
into the microphone.
[SENSOR BEEPING]
I am... Bernice!
THE GOVERNOR: Speak your name
into the microphone.
I am Bernice!
[SENSOR BEEPING]
[SOBBING]
[BEEPING SLOWS, STOPS]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Get up.
Get up!
[SOBS SOFTLY]
[GROANS]
Get up!
[SCREAMS, SOBS]
[SOBBING]
[SOFTLY] Get up.
Get up!
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
[INDISTINCT SHOUTING]
MAN: Hurry up, ladies!
Come on!
[INDISTINCT SHOUTING]
Everybody, drink!
It's empty!
I'm sorry!
Governor, you command all the time.
You are the time!
You are the greatest and
most powerful clock.
And your second hand is sharp and
more dangerous than a knife!
WOMAN: Please!
[SPEAKS JAPANESE]
No.
Come sit on grandpa's lap.
I won't!
Get over there!
Make her move!
Hey, Susie. Come on.
[WHIMPERS]
MAN: Come on.
THE GOVERNOR:
It's been two days already.
It's been two days,
and still, she is missing.
He'll get the job done,
Governor. I promise.
- I will...
- Bring me America.
Governor?
Do you understand anything?
Yes, Governor!
[SHOUT IN JAPANESE]
Yasujiro.
Yasujiro!
Here, go... go... go
toss those around some.
- [WOMEN CHEERING]
- Make it rain, baby!
Make it rain!
- [ALL SHOUTING]
- Yeah! Yeah!
Make it rain, baby!
Make it rain!
[LAUGHS]
Bring everyone!
Bring my nice young daughter.
Bring Susie
and her fresh young body.
Stop!
Did you know
when Bernice is coming back?
Do you?!
Bernice will come back!
Oh, is that so?
Well, tick-tock, tick-tock.
Time waits for no one!
Say it!
Tick-tock, tick-tock.
Tick-tock.
- Tick-tock.
- That's good!
That's good!
Now the second hand.
Tick-tock, tick-tock.
Tick... tock. Tick tock!
Yeah! Louder!
- Tick-tock, tick-tock!
THE GOVERNOR: Yes, you will be
my clock until Bernice returns.
- Tick-tock, tick-tock!
- Louder!
- Governor. Governor!
The traitor has returned.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYS]
Did you seduce her?
Give her notions?
Did you tell her to run from me?
No!
It was her idea.
That's a lie.
[LAUGHS]
Yasujiro!
Believe me, Yasujiro.
Please.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYS]
[SIGHS]
It's beautiful.
[LAUGHS]
[INHALES DEEPLY]
I'm so happy.
[LAUGHS]
Tick-tock. Tick-tock.
BOTH: Tick-tock, tick-tock.
ALL: Tick-tock! Tick-tock!
Tick-tock! Tick-tock!
[WEAKLY] Tick... tock.
Tick... tock.
[SOBBING] Tick... tock.
"My great miseries in this world
have been Heathcliff's miseries,
and I watched and felt each
from the beginning..."
She must be dead!
They never should have gone.
They could have broken free.
- No way!
- Quiet, everyone!
Listen to the story.
BERNICE: He's dead!
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
ENOCH: Your voice.
How did you manage
to reclaim it?
Those... those things!
They came out of nowhere.
ENOCH: They cut anything
on that highway.
No one escapes the Ghostlands.
You hear?!
No one!
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYS]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SCREAMING]
I always had the same dream.
[SPEAKS JAPANESE]
WOMEN: What did you see?
The ruins.
The people standing there...
...suffering.
All the people...
I harmed.
But yesterday...
...they came to me.
And they helped.
And I know why.
I understand.
They help me...
because...
I...
am...
radioactive.
[SPEAKS JAPANESE]
WOMEN: What did you see?
[DRAMATIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
You have a duty to complete.
We will give you another life.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYS]
[OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
Ahh!
Hello girls!
Good evening.
There are so many pretty girls.
Don't I deserve a girl tonight?
- You?
- [WOMEN SCREAM]
You are a pretty one, too.
[LAUGHS]
Hey!
Yasujiro!
Who should I pick?
Did you pick already?
Yasujiro-chan!
Brother?
Brother, are you here?
Is this your sister Yasujiro?!
Show yourself now!
Brother!
Brother, are you here!
Show your face!
Kill him!
[WOMEN SCREAM]
Brother wait!
I know everything!
You work for the Governor
because of me.
He promised if you did then
he would let me go, didn't he?
That's a lie!
He is a liar!
Brother...
Please leave him.
[SINISTER MUSIC PLAYS]
[APPLAUSE]
[INDISTINCT CHANTING]
MAN: [DISTORTED VOICE]
My sweet little cookie.
With this peace,
you will finally be mine.
Forever... and ever...
and ever.
[GASPS]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[GROANING]
[BREATHING SHAKILY]
[MEN SCREAMING]
[GUITAR STRUMS,
WOMEN SINGING IN JAPANESE]
[GROANS]
Hey! Hey!
[MAN SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY]
MAN: We have to keep
the clock from moving!
[SHOUTING CONTINUES
INDISTINCTLY]
[CHILDREN LAUGH]
Where did you come from?
Where are you from?
Thank you.
Where did you come from?
Where are you from?
Where I'm from
is not much better than here.
But I'll get you out of here.
I'll get you out of here.
Please.
Thank you very much.
[SLURPS]
[SIGHS]
Mmm.
Delicious.
Oishi!
GIRL: Oishi!
HERO: It's time.
Where are you going?
Wait.
I'm coming with you.
Where are you going?
Hero! Hey! Hero!
Hero!
[SINGING CONTINUES]
[MEN SHOUTING]
You hear this?!
Ghostlanders!
Tomorrow...
we're getting out of here!
- MAN: Impossible!
- [CROWD MURMURING]
It's impossible.
Impossible? Ha!
If you had told me
three days ago
I'd be standing here
with one arm and one...
testicle...
trying to reason
with you bitches...
I would've said impossible, too,
But I'm telling you,
there's a way.
There is no way.
Yes, there is.
And if we don't stop them,
they'll break free.
They'll rule the world.
- Terrorizing and killing!
- [SENSORS BEEPING]
We'll be their prisoners
forever!
[ALL SCREAMING]
No, don't be afraid.
It's just telling the time.
[SCREAMING CONTINUES]
Now, you could stay here,
suffer, survive.
I don't have the time!
I got one day
to tear this shit apart!
Now, you can either help me...
or rot.
[POWER TOOLS WHIRRING]
Ratman!
Hey, Ratman!
I want to make a deal with you.
I know you're intelligent.
You make the deal,
I give you some cheese,
maybe some pickled fish.
Where are you? Ratman!
There you are.
Come on out.
Would you take it easy?
I don't want to hurt you.
I just want to talk to you.
Come on!
What's it going to take
to fire all these cars up
and get the hell out of here?
[GASPS]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYS]
RATMAN: Hero!
I found something cool!
Here!
The last poor you are.
I knew him well.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
[CHILDREN LAUGH]
[POWER TOOLS WHIRRING]
[SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
Step aside!
[INDISTINCT SCREAMING]
We all die!
Everyone dies! Dies!
What's the meaning
of blue butterflies?
If you touch blue butterfly,
you're gonna die.
It doesn't matter anyway!
Ahh!
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYS]
[INDISTINCT SHOUTING]
Forward! Forward!
[OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
[CACKLES]
This is great!
[LAUGHS]
[MEN SHOUTING]
"...and the wild green park,
the valley of Gimmerton,
with a long line of mist
winding nearly to its top...
Hey! Ratman is having fun.
Let's go!
[POWER TOOLS WHIRRING]
[LAUGHTER]
[CHEERING, LAUGHTER]
[TRANQUIL MUSIC PLAYS]
[WIND WHISTLES]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYS]
You really going?
ENOCH: He must go.
Everybody, let's go!
[ALL CHEERING]
Let's go!
[DRAMATIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
[ENGINE IDLES]
Don't you recognize me?
This face...
is not familiar to you?
Psycho.
It crashed into the bus
carrying violent convicts.
It covered them in nuclear waste.
The burning!
The hideous burning!
You're... dead.
Burning in nuclear hell,
like everybody else.
You ever do that?
You ever burn in fucking hell
because your friend
betrayed you?
You were always so much fun
when you had a...
couple of shots of whiskey
in you.
PSYCHO: We used to have
so much fun, didn't we?
Yeah.
We did.
But then you...
started blowing up little kids.
Oh, come on.
Come on.
Ah, Psycho,
all the people we hurt...
ghosts.
They're ghosts.
I always thought they hated me.
But they needed me.
They came to me for help.
Let me help.
Alright.
But I want you to know...
the real predator in this...
is The Governor.
So, you go to The Governor,
you and Bernice,
and you finish it.
Time for us all to be free.
Okay.
Hey!
Thank you.
[EXPLOSION]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYS]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
Da-da-da-da-da-da!
[WOMEN GIGGLING]
- Is he really coming back?
- Maybe not.
Maybe it's a lie.
- [LAUGHTER]
- Who knows?
[CHILDREN LAUGHING]
Here they come!
Listen up!
For the sake of me,
birds will fall from the sky,
lions and tigers
will bow before me.
For the sake of me,
mountains and forests
would burn themselves down.
For the sake of me,
everything will be mine.
Welcome to my animal farm.
Long live the animal farm.
ALL: Forever!
Good! Good, boys!
Alright!
That's great.
There. There!
[WESTERN MUSIC PLAYS]
[WHISTLES]
Bernice!
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYS]
THE GOVERNOR: Bernice!
Oh, my lord! Oh, my God!
My girl!
My sweet honey bee!
[SOBBING] Oh!
The key.
Time to come home, my pet.
Give me the key!
I wouldn't give you a drop
of my piss, you degenerate!
Give me the fucking key,
or I'll slit her throat!
[SENSOR BEEPING]
Give him the key.
Yasujiro!
[SCREAMS]
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYS]
[SCREAMING]
[OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
Yasujiro! Yasujiro!
[SCREAMS]
[OMINOUS MUSIC RESUMES]
[MEN GASP]
[WOMEN SCREAM]
Bernice.
Susie.
Don't leave me alone.
- [MAN SCREAMS]
- [GUNSHOT]
[GUNSHOT]
BERNICE: Get out of the way!
Get out of the way!
[WOMEN GASP, SCREAM]
Bernice, am I gonna die?
No, sweetie.
[WOMEN SCREAM]
[MEN SHOUTING]
[WOMEN SCREAMING]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYS]
[WOMAN SOBS]
BERNICE: Here.
Bernice...
am I gonna die?
Don't be a fool.
You're strong.
Run away.
Leave me and run away!
You're safe here.
You're safe.
I will come back for you.
You're not a prisoner anymore.
I'm not a prisoner?
That's right.
You're not a prisoner.
I'm not a prisoner.
I'm not a prisoner!
Yes.
[MAN SHOUTS]
Hey, bitch!
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYS]
[HEART BEAT]
[SOUND DISTORTS]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC RESUMES]
[GROANS]
[BELL DINGING]
Fuck!
[BELL DINGS]
[WOMEN SHOUTING]
What the...
What the hell is going...
What are you doing?!
Governor, I thought there was going to
be a statue of you in this town!
You're such a loser!
[WOMEN SHOUTING]
You don't have any money!
You are useless.
Loser!
Susie!
Susie-chan!
Susie?
Susie! Susie-chan!
[DOG BARKS IN DISTANCE]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYS]
[BODY THUDS]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SOBBING]
S-Susie, it's Grandpa.
It's okay.
I'm not here to hurt you.
Susie, plum, it's grandpa.
Bernice!
THE GOVERNOR:
I'm not gonna hurt you.
Susie? Susie?
It's Grandpa.
Get the fuck away from her.
You betrayed me, you dirty slut!
Dirty dog bitch,
you back alley trash!
I don't need you!
I get me a new girl
same place I got you.
[WIND GUSTS]
Bernice!
[GROANING]
From all the sweet bitches.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYS]
[SENSORS BEEPING]
[SENSORS CHIME]
Yes!
[DRAMATIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
"But when I got to
the part where Mr...
[POWER TOOLS WHIRRING]
The Governor is dead!
The Hero won!
Hero!
Yeah! Yeah!
[ALL CHEERING]
The Governor is dead!
Hero!
Hero won!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
Everyone!
We are free!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE CONTINUE]
We are free from time!
You can let go!
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYS]
Look, they did it!
Time is starting again! Quick!
Look, it's time!
Get going!
[TICKING]
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE CONTINUE]
[ROOSTER CROWS]
Am I still alive?
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
Yeah.
You're still alive.
[GROANS]
[WOMEN SPEAK JAPANESE]
[SENTIMENTAL MUSIC PLAYS]
HERO: Yeah.
Samurai Town is gonna be
a beautiful place one day.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYS]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYS]
[OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]