** [Multicom Entertainment
Group jingle]
* [music]
[busy kitchen noise]
[Lisa] That looks right. Put a
little of that in there
and save the rest for tomorrow
in pasta bowls.
Put a little oil in it, make it
easier to move.
Bill, [indistinguishable]
That's beautiful. Cover it.
Put it over there.
A little bit more salt
and pepper on those.
It looks great, just great. Now
get it into the freezer right
away, go. Go.
Coming behind you...
Careful.
[Lisa] Hi. Are you a waiter or
a bartender? You want the
owner, Vivian.
-[Marty] No I want you.
-[Vivian] Hello, can I help you?
[Lisa] It's personal.
What are you talking about?
[Marty] Your husband's
in big trouble.
The people he owes want their
money by five o'clock.
Otherwise, there's gonna be a
knock at your door.
[Lisa] I'll be back before
we start serving.
[Vivian] What?
[Lisa] Where is he?
He's at lunch with
an investor.
Come on, Samantha. This
is serious, get him on
the phone.
I would but, he disconnected
his cell phone.
If you find him could you tell
him that hood was here again
this morning!
[T.V. and bar noise]
[Eric] Come on, Gypsy Girl. Come
on, Gypsy Girl. There you go,
come on, come on.
Come on, baby. That's me, that's
my girl! Come on, baby! Whoa!
That's me!
I told you twenty to one,
ready to run. Honey?
[Lisa] This time you've gone
too far. Don't you ever,
ever do that again.
[Eric] Wait, help me here.
What exactly did I do?
[Lisa] It's not bad enough to
embarrass me at work now you've
got people threatening us.
They're coming to
the house, Eric.
[Eric] No they're not. That was
a big misunderstanding. It's
all been cleared up.
Look I'll send Viv a dozen
roses. And it was a lousy thing
to do to you too. I'm sorry.
[Lisa] You're always sorry.
How much do you owe this time?
[Eric] Not a dime. Lisa, I
said I was sorry. Wives
get angry at husbands,
husbands get angry at wives.
It's the ying and yang of
married life.
Right, Jack?
This is for you. Come have
a quick drink with me,
come on.
[Lisa] I'm working a party,
Eric. I'll meet you at the
gallery after work.
[Eric] Lisa?
I like you like this.
Cheeks flushed those wild
untamable strands of hair.
I could always
make you smile.
Let's skip
the gallery.
[Lisa] You're crazy.
[Eric] I'm one
lucky guy.
[Eric] I wouldn't do a
documentary. I see something
more like, the civil war.
[Mrs. Feld] What's
the difference?
[Eric] Well I
see a ah,
a latitudinal history of
um, racing in America.
I-I would um, I would intercut
profiles of the owner of a stud
farm. A trainer, a jockey,
a female jockey,
the stable boy, the racing
fan and then build up to
the climax,
The Derby.
[Lisa] Have you seen any
of Eric's films?
They're thoughtful
without being solemn.
[Eric] Well, she is my
biggest fan. And of course
my toughest critic. Ha ha.
How about if I send
you some cassettes?
[Mrs. Feld] How much would a
project like that cost?
[Eric] Well, you know we're
talkin' about a labor of
love here.
[Mrs. Feld] So what do
you think, dear?
[Lisa] Eric's had three
wonderful documentaries on PBS
and some of his industrials
are little gems.
But I think this might be the
film that wins him his Emmy.
[Eric] Major backer would meet
some very interesting show
business people,
we'd go to premiers, you might
even have to come out to L.A.
[Mrs. Feld] Oh. This would
be tax deductible.
[Eric] We'd work
something out.
We'd have a lot
of laughs.
Hey, hey do you know why
cannibals don't eat clowns?
[Mrs. Feld] No, why?
[Eric] Because they
taste funny.
[laughter]
You wanna hear a
great title,
"Oh, For a Horse
With Wings."
[Mrs. Feld] Oh...
[Eric] Thanks for helping me
with Mrs. Feld tonight.
[Lisa] You don't have to thank
me for telling the truth.
[Eric] Could have mentioned
I haven't had a film in
seven years...
[Lisa] I wanted to believe
everyone of those years
you could do it again.
I could have told
her that, too.
[Eric] Hey, there's no one
like you, honey.
[Vivian] Here you
go. Try that.
[Lisa] Don't be mad
at me, ok?
[Vivian] Hmm?
I'm going into business for
myself. I just signed the
incorporation papers.
[Vivian] Why?
[Lisa] We're in way over our
heads financially.
We just drove Sarah up to
college last week.
Barely been making Bruce's
tuition payments the last
two years.
With the two of
them away...
[Vivian] Look it takes
capital to start a
catering business.
[Lisa] Dad left me a savings
bond. I've got a little over
nine thousand saved up.
Th-that's enough
isn't it?
[Vivian] Oh wow, is
this moving fast!
You think you're a little
spooked by the empty nest?
There's another reason I
need my own business.
Yeah?
I'm...
thinking of
leaving Eric.
Oh my God.
[Lisa] It's a lot worse
than I've told you.
Business is a disaster, his
gambling is out of control,
he takes every penny you pay me
if I don't sneak it right into
my personal account. It's...
I've just been
waiting for Sarah.
Oh he's such a
great guy.
You guys always seem to have
such a good time together.
Honey I'm sorry.
So it's okay?
We'll still be
friends?
Of course we will. We'll
work something out.
I'll talk to Gary, see if
he can't throw something
Eric's way.
[Lisa] He won't take it.
I know him.
[Vivian] Oh but he must see how
desperate things are.
[Lisa] He has no idea. He's
living in a dream world.
[Eric laughing] Ha
ha. I did.
[Gary] All right here we are,
six stores. Specialty
clothing along here...
[Eric] Can I have a
charge account?
[Gary] Espresso bar over
there. And my video store.
I'm keeping the franchise.
[Eric] Well no wonder, this
is a great location.
But I'm having a problem, I
uh, need someone to manage
it for me.
[Lisa] You know movies.
Paid forty grand the
first year.
[Eric] Well what you don't
understand when you're a
graduate of Betty Crocker U,
is that there's just some things
you can't put in the alumni
newsletter.
Eric, you don't have to tell
Princeton magazine you're
managing a video store.
[Worker] Mr. Reynolds, can I
see you for a sec?
Yeah sure. Just be
a minute.
Honey, that was very
sweet what you tried
to do over there.
But what does a girl from
Betty Crocker U know?
It was a joke.
I'm sorry I didn't go to
college. I'm sorry I
embarrass you.
You don't embarrass me. I was
teasing you. We kid around,
that's what makes our
marriage so great.
Oh yeah, our marriage is
paradise. The house is leased,
the furniture's leased,
we're in debt up to here. I
hate living like this.
If you wanted a regular
paycheck you should've
married a janitor.
You think we're talking
about money here.
-I'm a filmmaker.
-You're a fabulous filmmaker.
You just don't make any films.
You love to put me down for
having a dream, don't you?--
I married you because
you had a dream.
I didn't marry a guy who
plays the horses. Or who
plays around.
[Eric] Gary, thanks for the
offer but, I don't think I
was cut out for retail.
[Vivian] What'd he say?
[Eric] But I will take some of
your money in my poker game.
[Vivian] Oh dear.
[Lisa] Excuse me? You-you let
somebody raid my account.
Your teller says I've got
only forty two dollars.
I know I've got more
than nine thousand.
[Mrs. Horvath] Please, sit.
Let's see what's
going on here.
You had that much but you've
been making ATM withdrawals.
Those not mine.
Who withdraws three hundred
dollars a day for a month?
Do you have some ID?
This is a personal account. You
let somebody steal from me.
The system says there are two
cards. What about your husband,
doesn't he have one?
No I told you. It's not
a joint account.
Tell her.
About a month ago a
couple came in. He had a
statement for the account
and she had some I.D., I think a
credit card in your name. Only
uh, she wasn't you.
Um, they said that they
had lost the ATM card
for the account.
And well we issued
a new card.
Was it him?
Uh-huh.
[Lisa] This woman, what
did she look like?
She had beautiful hair.
Beautiful red hair.
* [sad music]
Thank you.
-* [sad music]
-[seagulls]
[-Eric] You wanna watch TV? I
heard that uh...
-[zipping of bags]
what is this?
I went to the bank today.
They were surprised my
hair wasn't red.
Samantha and me?
That's nothing.
Nothing new I think
you mean.
Honey look, we've had some
rocky moments lately, what
couple hasn't?
Forging my signature and
stealing my savings is a
rocky moment?
The kids come first, they
needed money in their
checking accounts.
It's funny I had to give each
of them a hundred the day
they left.
I'll get around to
opening the accounts!
Aye I had a call today.
HBO is this close to picking
up the racing documentary.
That money was mine. My name
was on the account. It was
from my dad...
-my work. I want it back now.
-I'll pay you back.
When I have it.
You used it to pay your
bookie didn't you?
They were comin'
after us.
You've got money. Give it me.
The poker game is rigged.
-Give me what you've got!
-Hey, hey, hey, hey would you
please calm down.
Mrs. Feld is gonna come
through and HBO I can
feel it.
Come on we're on a
roll here.
Come on...
Let go of me.
That woman is not gonna give
you a dime, HBO doesn't know
you exist...
Honey, don't you understand
the power of a dream?
I have to make this film.
[Lisa] Get your story
straight, Eric.
You put a couple of grand
on the ponies so the kids
would have book money,
or so you could win the
Jury prize at Cannes.
Which was it?
Well it was a
spur-of-the-moment thing.
It just seemed like a good
idea at the time.
We were gonna
borrow it,
hit the double, put it back, you
were never gonna know!
Would you take this, it was a
lousy game, I want you to
have it as a down payment.
Give me another shot!
Samantha's history.
I'm gonna quit gambling.
And I'm gonna take Mrs.
Feld's money
and give you ten
thousand dollars
right off the top.
Lisa, listen we have been in
some tight spots before, you
know that.
-I,I don't even
understand what's--
-Three hundred bucks?
You do something like this and
you think you can buy me off
with three hundred dollars?
Hey can we sleep on
this tonight please?
Things are gonna look
a lot different in
the morning.
That used to work, Eric. And
then for years I faked it and
I felt guilty and trapped.
And all the time you had
this other life. And I
felt trapped.
Lisa give me one more
chance. For the kids.
I'm leaving
you, Eric.
You've said
that before.
This time I
mean it.
* [dramatic music]
[dialing on phone]
[Sarah message over phone] Hi
this is Sarah. Guess what? I'm
out. Leave me a message.
Thanks, bye.
[Lisa into phone] It's mom,
it's after two where are you?
I'm on the road on the
way to Canada
and I just realized that I
don't have the new number
at Bruce's dorm.
I, I have something to
tell you guys.
So could you call me
at three one five five
five four one two five
before your first
classes in the morning?
I'll wait for
your call.
Bye, I love
you. Bye.
* [somber music]
[shower running]
[crying]
[phone rings]
Hello?
[Sarah from phone] Mom, thank
God. Bruce and I are going to
the hospital, it's dad.
-[Lisa] What?
-[Sarah] He collapsed in the
drive-way.
Bruce said the doctor told him
it's some kind of stroke.
We'll meet
you there.
The Kingsleys were coming home
from a party, they think it
was about twelve thirty.
[Lisa] Thanks.
[Bruce] The car door was
open and he was just
lying there.
If the domelight hadn't
been on, they wouldn't
have seen him.
What I don't get is
where were you?
What were you doing
in Canada?
Mom?
He must have
needed cigarettes.
There were all these quarters
on the ground. They figured
he'd been robbed.
Mrs. McKeever.
I just showed the cat
scan to the chief of
neurology
and there's
no doubt,
it was a stroke and it
involves the brain stem.
Oh my God.
Now he could live a
few weeks
or he could go on for
a lot longer.
Now given the type of stroke
he's had, he's probably gonna
have some trouble swallowing.
But uh, there's no other
paralysis. And fortunately his
speech hasn't been impaired.
Is he awake? Can
we see him?
Yeah. But he's
still groggy.
Doctor...
really, how
bad is it?
It's hard
to predict.
We'll know more in the next
forty eight hours.
Mom, you had to see us in
person for some big
announcement?
Could we do this
some other time?
You're finally leaving
him weren't you?
[Sarah] He's got me at
left wing right now,
but I think he's moving
me to sweeper for the
Colgate game.
I was counting on
you coming.
[Eric] I'll be there, honey. I
have never missed one of your
games, I'm gonna start now.
Dad, Dad we love
you, ok?
We're gonna stay right here
beside you 'til you get out
of the woods.
[Eric] Never in the woods. I
never liked 'em. How can you
bet with a tree.
This whole thing was just a way
of gettin' us together for a
few hours.
Monday morning I want the two
of you back in class.
Ok, but only if you promise
to be well enough to go
home by then.
So mom can take
care of you.
* [dramatic music]
[Doctor] He's come a long way in
one week. We're gonna have to
discharge him soon.
When will he get off
the feeding tube?
Probably never.
But we can put a shunt inside so
we can feed him directly into
his stomach.
He can move around, maybe even
sip a little liquid or nibble
on something soft.
Basically he's gonna
need help for the
rest of his life.
Oh boy.
Yeah.
So... we're talking permanent
round-theclock nursing care?
Yes. I think you'd be
better off taking care
of him at home.
As long as he's got you, I
think it's a perfectly
good way to go.
[Lisa] Easy, I
got you.
[Eric] Uh,
I'm gonna sleep
better tonight...
having you
next to me.
I moved into
Sarah's room.
Boy, you really
miss her, huh?
Yeah, that's it. No reason to
start confronting reality at
this late date.
I can still make
you smile...
Liking you was never
the problem.
God, Lisa. Did you add
some steps before I
came back?
Ohh, oh...
Don't misjudge the
way things are.
You're Bruce and
Sarah's father...
they'd be here if they could.
Since they can't,
I'm not gonna walk
out on you.
What happens when
I get better?
I'm here now, I think
that's what matters.
I'll uh, I'll make you
love me again.
Could we take this one
day at a time?
The reality is, you're never
going to see me because I'm
going to be out all the time.
[Eric] Doing what?
Trying to pay for nurses,
food, rent, textbooks...
I'm not gonna let you do
it alone. I'll figure
out something.
[coughing]
Ok.
Just try not
to talk.
If that's
possible.
Just one thing, when
the kids ask,
tell them this is the way
you want it to be.
Needs a
valve job.
[Lisa] What kind of money are
we talking about?
Well the dealer will
charge you eight hundred,
I'll do it for six, I'll have it
for you tomorrow night.
Six hundred's a problem
for me right now.
[Art] Put it
on a card.
The cards got taken away, my
husband's had a stroke.
Wow uh, gee I'm sorry. He comes
in here all the time, give him
my best.
I will.
Listen, since you know
us I... I mean,
this is hard.
I don't have a job right now,
but I've never not paid a
bill in my life.
I need a car to
look for work.
Can you fix it and let me
pay you, I don't know, a
hundred a month?
No I couldn't
live with that.
Can I use your phone to call
another tow truck?
You know, I got this
sales rep who has
this gimmick.
Every time he comes in he
gives you something, you
know.
Makes it impossible for him to
leave without an order.
Sometimes it's wine,
hockey tickets.
This week he left
me these.
Looks like they'll
fit perfectly.
You said I had to
pay up front.
I said I wasn't willing to
take money if someone
didn't have any.
-[Lisa] So you're saying--
-[Art] You can use that old car
out there,
pick this one up tomorrow
night. I close at six.
[Lisa] We'll pay
you back.
Sure. Soon as you're husband
gets back on your feet.
I can't depend on
that happening.
Keys are under
the visor.
Thank you.
I meant what I said, I will pay
you back, eventually.
I can tell.
[alarm clock]
[Lisa] Was it bad tonight?
Been asleep at all?
[Eric] No. I'm sorry you get up
every night and do this.
[pouring sound]
[Lisa] You want codeine?
[Eric] God, yes. Could
you, could you just--
-[Lisa] Sure, sure... oh!
-[bottle falling]
[kitchen timer ringing]
-[phone ringing]
-[air drill sounds]
Maskin and son.
Uh Mr. Maskin, it's
Lisa McKeever.
I'm running late and I don't
want to hold you up, so can
I pick up my car tomorrow?
Um, yeah, yeah, yeah. It's
done. Tomorrow'll be fine.
Great. I-I've been handing
out uh, samples of my
brownies all day,
your ideas working,
that's why I'm late.
My idea?
About not going any place
without a free sample
Since nine this morning
I've booked a luncheon
and a baby shower
and in another half, I might
even have a whole bar
mitzvah.
You rent rooms
or what?
I'm a caterer. If I'm lucky and
get a deposit, I may even be
able to pay you.
You sure my keeping the
loner another day is ok?
Oh no, that's ok. I'll
switch'em on the way to
work in the morning.
Ok, I-I gotta go.
Uh hey um, hang
in there.
Ok.
[phone beeps]
* [dramatic music]
[crashing]
Hey! Hey, hey,
shoo, go!
[knocking]
Hello?
* [dramatic music]
She's not smoking
again. Sorry.
No, no. These
are for you.
I didn't get the bar
mitzvah, I won't be
paying you for awhile.
You should see the garbage
people buy out of these
machines.
They'll be gone
by two..
[Lisa] I didn't make
these for sale.
I know but I-I can't eat all
of those. I'll have some
after lunch...
why shouldn't you
make some money?
Actually, that's a
good idea.
Caterers spend most of
their time waiting
around for jobs.
If I lined up a bunch of
places that could sell
fresh baked goods...
You know I usually eat at
the diner across the
street there.
Would you like to get a
sandwich or something?
I would, but I-I have a
twelve thirty meeting.
Right. Yeah well, thanks
for the cookies.
[sighs]
-Ow!
-Sorry.
You know I've taken care
of some very big people
in my time.
Like basketball
players?
Ha, I mean well
known people.
-What the hell is that?
-[sound of leafblower outside]
Just the gardener.
We don't have
a gardener
[Mrs. Skinner] Maybe the Mrs.
hired one. Somebody's gotta
clean up the yard.
* [dramatic music]
[Lisa] I need
commercial ovens.
What if I rented your kitchens
every night you're not using
them, say from six to two a.m.?
You have that
much baking?
Eighteen outlets,
seventy two dozen a day.
Wow!
I could do more. But I gotta get
home by two to change Eric's
nutrient bag.
How's he doing?
Well. You know you and Gary
could stop by any time
you've got a few--
[crashing noise]
What the hell
is that?
* [dramatic music]
Ha. Just have to figure a
way to dampen the noise a
little bit.
Why are you doing
all this for me?
Figure you could use a little
help around here. With the
trees and the raccoons.
I would have got
to the trees.
I think taking care of
a sick husband and
working at night
to start your own business
that's a lot of work for
one person.
I know, but
there's no...
you just can't keep
doing things for me.
I like working with my
hands, kinda relaxes me.
Thanks.
Who's that?
The new handyman.
[commentator on T.V.]
I see you got the
filling station guy
trimming the trees.
It was his idea. We got
to talking when he fixed
the Explorer.
We paying him or what,
what's the deal?
No, he's one of my
brownie customers.
-Damn!
-[remote falls]
Hey, I dropped
the remote.
You drownin'
there or what?
Lisa you know how hard it is for
me to get outta bed.
Thanks, honey. I
am so bored.
[Lisa] Why don't you
call some of those
poker buddies.
Or those guys from the
track who've forgetten
you exist?
I never knew his name,
that mechanic.
[Lisa] Art Maskin.
-[Lisa] Hi.
-[Eric] Hi.
I brought you three
dozen brownies.
Oh.
Half walnut, half pecan.
Good um...
[laughs]
you know, you know um, the
other day when I asked you
out to lunch,
was that meeting just that
meeting that day or you always
kinda busy for lunch?
One of the things about caterers
it's hard work and you need
lunch to keep going.
Oh well you know uh, I'm gonna
finish here one thirty, two.
How about we grab a
sandwich then?
Earlier would be better. I
should be home to relieve
the nurse.
Fine we'll make it a quick
sandwich. Won't even spoil
your dinner.
I'd like that. As
long as...
Yeah?
It's just lunch with one
of my customers.
Lunch means lunch.
See you then.
That new warehouse
club's incredible.
I got a pound of flower and
two hundred pounds of
baking chocolate.
Twenty percent below wholesale.
-[crashing noise]
-[Mrs. Skinner] Oh!
That woman missed her calling.
She's born for vaudeville.
I've gotta go out again. If Viv
calls about the flower,
tell her I'll get it out of her
garage tomorrow.
I thought you were off the
rest of the day?
No, I'm having a sandwich
with a client.
Well push it to tomorrow. We'll
send the clumsiest woman in the
world home and go see a movie.
Sounds like fun. Wish we'd
talked about it earlier.
[Mrs. Skinner] Paper or plastic?
Mark my words, plastic, paper
does it to ya every time.
Must be a big client. Some guy
in the market for a couple of
tons of brownies?
We can do a movie on
Saturday. What shall
we have for dinner?
-Oh...
-[taps bottle]
you know, New York strip medium
rare, cottage fries, and a
caesar with anchovies.
-Right.
-[Mrs. Skinner] What are you
thinking of? He's got his drip.
[Lisa] Oh. Old habits
are tough to break.
Nice to see ya
so happy.
I'm late.
Tell him the trees need some
more work, will ya?
I uh, hope you
like chocolate.
[laughing]
Ok, admit it.
You were giving a formal
luncheon and your twelve guests
came down with pneumonia.
I finished up the ambulance
sooner than I thought so I
closed up early.
Some sandwich. You did
all this yourself?
I told you, I'm good with
my hands. Um, you sure you
don't want another lobster?
No thanks,
I'm stuffed.
Couldn't your dad have
spelled you at the station?
Well I uh, never
knew my dad.
I'm sorry, I assumed from the
way you answered the phone.
No um, when I bought the
station I had to come up
with a name,
so Maskin
& Son.
Sounds stable, likes you
been around forever.
Or, maybe I was just
wishing out loud.
How'd you learn to
cook like this?
I like to eat. When you
live alone there's TV
and cooking.
Thanks.
Mmm.
* [romantic music]
[Lisa] I thought you were
taking me home?
[Art] I am. In kind of a
roundabout way.
* [majestic music]
Is it legal?
Well as long as we stay
under the commercial
lanes FAA's happy.
And you just
do this?
Look. Horseshoe Falls.
When I was a kid I used to sit
on a fence next to this old
country airfield
watching this pilot fuel up
his crop duster.
Kept asking him questions
about how planes flew...
I never figured he'd take me
up for a ride.
And when you
grew up?
I knew it was the one
thing I had to do.
[Art] Look, look,
look down there.
[Lisa] It's so
great up here.
You forget.
You forget everything.
That was the idea.
[video poker sounds]
Hi. How are you?
Need anything?
I'm fine.
Nice lunch?
[Lisa] It was ok.
[Lisa] Business is
picking up.
We're putting on five party
shifts Thanksgiving evening.
I'm not quite sure
what we're gonna do.
We're having dinner
with the kids.
I meant about having
time to cook.
You know what drives me crazy
about you?
The way you think you keep
pulling the wool over my eyes.
I have no secrets
from you, Eric.
Oh no.
You just come in whistling
after a five hour lunch
with the tree trimmer
because there's a bright
golden haze in the meadow.
Art and I have an
occasional lunch.
We're friends.
I'm not allowed to
have friends?
I got two more
Thanksgiving dinners.
Oh, big?
-One's forty people.
-Wow.
[Lisa] I'm interviewing party
chefs this afternoon.
But I still gotta find a place
to do the pre-cooking.
[Art] Do it at my house.
[Lisa] Really?
[Art] Sure.
[Lisa] That would
be great.
I can't get anything
done at home.
[Art] How's he doing?
[Lisa] Better.
Better but,
not great?
You have to understand
the way Eric and I
have been living.
He's a man who never not once
since we've been married ever
cleared the table after a meal.
When Sarah
was born,
we decided we should both
have life insurance policies
in case we were run over by
a truck or something.
He borrowed on the equity until
the company finally cancelled
the policies.
Naturally he didn't tell
me, when I found out I
asked him why,
he looked at me like I
was crazy.
"Native Dancer was even
money" he said.
He also loves his kids
more than any man alive.
[Art] You never
thought of leaving?
[Lisa] I thought
about it.
[Art] Just
never did.
[Lisa] There were all kinds
of good excuses.
Never be able to
support myself...
[Art] At least we're past that.
You're already make more money
than me.
[Lisa] Wasn't
really money.
He was Bruce and
Sarah's daddy.
They were crazy
about him.
I was crazy
about them.
You just don't seem like the
kind of person to put up
with all that stuff.
Affairs, gambling debts,
stolen money...
People change. I'm not
the same woman I was
when I married him.
You know, when my wife left I
realized what total strangers
we'd become.
The people who'd met and
fallen in love...
the ones with the private
nicknames and the ones who
stopped to pet stray cats,
those people had
just vanished!
Why did
she leave?
She never
really said.
And nobody else ever
came along?
Not 'til now.
I thought I was able to
leave him. I can't now.
I don't want you to. I just want
you to know how things are.
It would be really nice right
now if you go wash your hands
or something.
* [dramatic music]
[leaf blower noise]
Viv picked her up, I
don't know where
they were goin'
Viv?
Can I uh, do something for you?
Yeah, save my ears.
Oh, sorry. You know uh, we
really don't know each other.
I'm Art Maskin from
the garage.
Uh, would-would you like
me to uh, drive you
somewhere?
[engine starts]
[brakes squeal]
[leaf blower starts up]
[Eric] Hey! I thought
I told you...
Hey!
Oh did you know that
Eric can drive?
He can barely get in and out
of his wheelchair.
Yesterday while you and Viv
were at Pittsburgh Plaza
he drove himself out to
the mailbox and back.
He's always
done that.
He's milking his invalid
routine. He's not nearly as
helpless as he pretends to be.
He admits
he's lazy.
Does he admit how angry he is?
That's the question.
Nobody likes what a
stroke does to you.
Angry about us.
About us? There's nothing to
be angry about. We're friends.
We are, that's
all we are.
Well you have to grant the fact
that it's after midnight and
you're here could
possibly suggest
something else to him.
I've been totally up front with
him about it being over.
Where's the pineapple?
-Pineapple? Here.
-I'm just taking care of him. He
knows that.
Maybe he does, but he doesn't
like seeing me around. He's
jealous. Ha ha.
He lost the right to be
jealous after about the
first three women...
after he lost all my
money at the track.
It's not about
money for him.
Whose side are
you on?
I think that would be
obvious by now.
I can't...
yet...
* [soft romantic music]
[Eric] What time are the kids
coming home on Wednesday?
[Lisa] I don't know,
they're getting rides.
[Eric] When they were little
remember we used to always
go skating on
Thanksgiving eve.
That was the best
night of the year.
We had that rink
all to ourselves.
[Lisa] Could you put that
down for a minute?
I have all these
dinners I'm doing.
I'm gonna be cooking non-stop
for the next three days.
Well I could peel
potatoes or something.
You never peeled a
potato in your life.
Yeah well I could
learn. To help.
I've invited Art to have
dinner with us Thursday here.
I'm making all the dishes
at work, he'll just
cook the turkey and warm
everything else up.
That grease-monkey is not
coming through this door
into my house.
I don't wanna
hurt you.
I will say this
only once.
I feel like
a robot.
I cater.
I change
your bed.
I shop. I get up in the
night to change the drip.
Every minute of
every day
I think about the fact that I'm
the one who has to earn the
money for tuition,
medicine, doctor bills,
and I pretend to the kids
everything's all right.
I'm not a robot, Eric.
I've said it's over
between us.
What you've done
to me...
it's just over.
What are you really
saying, Lisa?
I'm saying, if you want
Thanksgiving dinner
served in this house,
Art is going
to do it.
Forget Thanksgiving. You're
telling me to my face. You're
involved with the yard man.
I'm saying I
need help.
The kids can help. The
kids are great.
Sarah can bake and, and, and
Bruce and I can figure out
the turkey.
I want Art with me
on Thanksgiving.
Well what if that
isn't possible?
One way or another,
it's possible.
[engine stops]
-[Art] Hello?
-[door handle
shaking]
Eric, Eric, the
doors locked
Hello?!
[Art yelling
and falling]
[Eric] You ok?
Uhh. Yeah I'm ok. Just
kinda had the wind
knocked outta me.
[Eric] She's not home.
And I can't do much to
help you.
Anything feel broken,
should I call 911?
[Art] No, no I'm ok. Just,
just gotta catch my breath.
No don't do-- Whoa, hey,
hey! Ha ha. Hey you on
top of me. Sit back.
[Eric] Look, why don't you just
load me up before one of us
gets killed, ok?
[Art] Ok.
[commercials playing
on T.V.]
Good God, look at that.
I haven't had a beer in
two months.
You want a beer?
Have one.
Can't. Doctor says it's one
of the many ways I did this
to myself.
[beer bottle opening]
[beer bottle spraying]
[laughter]
[gasps]
One more's not gonna hurt
anything now.
No, no it's just for the taste.
One more's just wanna make you
keep on going.
So tell me, Art, what's in this
for you? Besides the chance to
torment a cripple.
Nobody likes to be
alone on a holiday.
Well, to each his own. Being a
fifth wheel doesn't sound too
swift to me.
I'll do whatever
it takes.
Whatever 'what' takes?
That's my question.
To be a part of
her life.
You're unbelievable,
you know that.
You come into my house and
you just, say something
like that.
She needs help. She's
about to snap.
Don't tell me what
my wife needs.
Yeah well, you just don't
seem to get it.
The most important thing
to her, is that you are
taken care of.
And you're gonna do that?
Well don't waste your
time, my friend.
I'm a real pain
in the ass.
[laughing]
Yeah well, you give it
your best shot. But,
it's an act.
And you know that after
just an hour, huh?
I know it because she's
loved you for twenty
three years.
I'm not gonna be able to
eat anything but yogurt
'til Easter.
[everyone laughing]
[Bruce] Turkey was
delicious, mom.
[Lisa] Art cooked
the turkey.
[Art] Um... anybody want
another cappuccino?
[Lisa] No thanks.
[Sarah] Mom makes it too
strong. Could I have
some regular decaf?
[Art] Sure, I'll put a
pot on.
[Sarah] Someone wanna tell us
what's going on here? Who
exactly is Art?
[Bruce] Come on, mom, he's
gonna be back in a second.
Who is this guy?
A friend.
Your mom's business is really
taking off. She's going all
the time now.
But...
I mean is he...
when we're
not here...
I'll say it.
We've been worried since
the hospital about you
two breaking up.
We're not
breaking up.
There's no big mystery here.
Art helps me.
He helps you.
[Eric] She's looking for someone
to help full time at work.
It's a temporary problem. That's
what your mother's saying.
No, it's not temporary.
I'm thinking of looking
for a cheaper house.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, what is
not temporary?
Mom?
Honey, this is
our home.
A ranch would be better for you.
You could get around easier.
Be simpler for you to
eat with us.
With us?
With the family. When you
guys come home.
Made you something. I had
this windshield wiper
hose in my truck.
Great. Now you're gonna feed me
through something you found in
the back of your truck.
I sterilized it. Now we can hang
two bags before you go to bed.
No more waking up
during the night.
Lisa changes them.
She doesn't mind.
No, she loves gettin' up in
the middle of her nightly
five hours.
Real chance to do some husband
and wife bonding.
That was her on
the phone?
Yeah. Apple pie's are cooling.
She'll be here when the mince
meat's done.
When the phone rings in my
house, Art, I'll take the
calls, got it?
-Oh whatever you say. It's your
house.
-[machine beeping]
You know that ranch house you
saw, the one with the
separate apartment?
-[Lisa] I took it.
-[pouring]
Well I was thinking you know
I'm paying eleven hundred a
month here.
How about, I move into
that apartment.
You'd save six
hundred a month.
Well I think it's worth more.
But besides, I could also chip
into my share of the food.
Well that's what you
want isn't it? It
was your idea...
[Lisa] My idea was a cheaper
house. A ranch for the
wheelchair.
[Art] Well we spend all our
time together anyway.
Plus, when Mrs. Skinner's
out, there'll be somebody
in the house.
You think about him
more than I do.
I like him more than I do. He's
in an impossible situation.
And you think having you living
with us is gonna make things
less impossible?
Well, if I lived in the
apartment, wouldn't it
make things simpler?
-[Art] Hhm?
-[Lisa] No.
Don't you understand...
how hard it is having you near
me and having to pretend?
Pretend what?
-That we're just friends.
-* [romantic music]
Fine. We'll keep things just
the way they are.
That feels wrong too.
Like we've got some secret from
him as if we're waiting for him
to die.
Honey, I don't think he's gonna
die. Not anytime soon.
[Lisa] The house is
partially furnished.
Look at that
great tree.
The apartment downstairs
has its own bath.
The kids rooms are twice
what they are now.
[Eric] I thought the apartment
was for one of the kids?
[Lisa] No I rented out the
apartment. For eleven
hundred a month.
That means we're living here for
fourteen hundred instead of
twenty five hundred.
[Eric] Who are the tenants? I
hope they're not noisy.
[Lisa] One tenant, Art.
You're moving in the guy you're
having an affair with?
[Lisa] I'm not
sleeping with Art.
[Eric] Oh yeah right.
[Lisa] Never lied to you,
Eric, I never will. I'm
not sleeping with Art.
The word I used was 'affair',
Lisa. You care to comment on
that?
Eric I promised to take
care of you.
That didn't mean I was giving up
the right to take care of
myself, or be happy.
And he makes you happy.
You admit that.
-He's moving in.
-* [dramatic music]
* [dramatic music]
[Lisa] Eric?
Honey are you
in here?
He must be in his
room. Wait here.
[Art] Lisa!
* [fast dramatic music]
[car screeching
and honking]
[Driver] You ok?
-[Art] You all right?
-[Eric] Let go of my chair.
-[Art] Here, get in here.
-[Eric] I said let go of my
chair!
Did you hear what I said!? You
go back into the house!
[Lisa] We will go inside and
talk about this--
-[Art] Eric... Eric...
[-Eric] We're not gonna talk
about anything! I'm out of here!
-[Lisa] Hold on. What are you
playing chicken with cars?
-[Eric] I am going to Sarah's.
She will get me
an apartment!
[Lisa] Would you come inside and
talk about this like an adult?
[Eric] No! No I wanna talk
about it out here!
So that all of our new
neighbors can see what my wife
and her boyfriend
are doing to me!
Look at' em!
[Lisa] You're impossible and I'm
freezing. Do whatever the hell
you want.
[Eric] That's what I
intend to do.
Where are you taking me? Where
are you taking me?!
-[bar noise]
-[laughter, cauging]
[Art] Way I see it, you've got
the advantage now.
She thinks you tried to kill
yourself over her so,
she'll do anything
you want.
That was
the idea.
It'll never occur to her
that you couldn't stop
because the uh,
wheels were wet.
What do you want?
How can you let her move you
into my house while I'm
still alive?
I want her to
be happy.
And you're willing
to share her?
[thumps chest]
Yeah.
What is this, the Popular
Mechanics version of
Jules and Jim?
You're one weird guy,
you know that?
Well this is, uh, one
weird situation.
Ok. Here's the deal.
There are some obvious
financial advantages
to having a tenant.
As long as he sleeps
in his own room.
And some major
drawbacks.
Like what are the kids gonna
think for example.
Bottom line,
he's willing to do stuff
for me and I'm willing
to let him stay.
Why are you suddenly willing
to look the other way?
I guess I realized out there
today that, you were right.
I don't have any
other choice.
* [dramatic music]
I can't help myself.
I have to be
near you.
[Art] Lisa and I are flying up
to Toronto for lunch.
There's the number in case
you need it. A few catalogs.
-[Eric] Spending the night?
-[Art] Ah no, no we wouldn't do
that.
Ah, you're, you're sure you got
everything you need?
[Eric] Yeah.
-Buy her a nice lunch.
-[Art] All right. I'll see ya.
[boat engine, seagulls]
You think it was ok we flew over
here and left him?
Oh he's fine, he's got a stack
of catalogs he's doing his
Christmas shopping.
You've become the expert on my
husband. Next he's gonna have
you walking in bets for him.
He can talk to me. That's no
reflection on you.
I'm just saying he takes
advantage of people.
I'm not the one
who misses him.
Coming over here
was my idea.
He know's we're here. He
said have a good time.
You're the one who's
talking about him.
[Art] Lisa, Lisa there's
no reason if he builds
up his strength
he can't come
over with us.
I thought we came over
here to be alone.
[Art] You can't have
it both ways.
I mean we can do what we can to
make him part of our lives and
just start living
and enjoy ourselves.
Or we can work shifts nursing
him and get off from what
martyrs we are.
But you and I can not organize
our lives, exclusively around
him.
We have to have
something else.
Who told you you get to
'organize' what I feel
about my husband.
[plane engine]
-[Art] Give a little bit of it.
Let of it, let go--
-[Lisa] Stop giving me advice.
[Art] I'm sorry I did not
mean to sound like I was
giving you advice.
[Lisa] You do it all the
time. You love him.
Admit you love him.
I can wait as long
as it takes.
Honey I can. I mean I'll do
whatever, whatever.
Just love me. Don't try
to understand me.
* [dramatic music]
[news on T.V.]
Oh, hi. Would you look cold.
Would you like a cup of coffee?
Why are you being
so nice to me?
"Love me. Don't try
to understand me.
I don't remember when I had an
afternoon as bad as today. I
was awful to you.
You're right I can't
have it both ways.
I can't ask you to love
me if I never let you
see how I feel.
* [romantic music]
[snoring]
[Lisa] Mrs. Skinner,
is he asleep?
Oh I ah checked him about half
hour ago. He was reading that
Tim Clancy.
[Lisa] Tom Clancy..
Torn Clancy. It must
be exciting he uh,
told me he wanted to be alone.
Heh heh. Ooh...
Thank you for everything.
-Oh, thank you.
-We'll see you tomorrow.
Night-night.
-* [dramatic music]
-[Lisa] You need anything before
I got to bed? Eric?
Mrs. Skinner call nine one one
and Mr. Maskin at the station!
[sirens]
[paramedic] Watch
your step ma'am...
-[Art] Another stroke?
-[Lisa] Heart attack, a bad one.
[Art] Could have happened at any
time. There's nothing you could
have done if you'd been there.
-[Art] Hi.
-Where is he?
[Art] Ah, he's
having angioplasty.
Where's mom?
She's on the phone with the
insurance company. They
want a second opinion.
All right, I gotta find
her. Where is she?
[Art] Uh, down by
the cafeteria.
What are you doing hanging
around her? You have no
right to be here.
Right? I was here with your
mom 'til you and Bruce
could show up.
Our father loves our mother.
People see you hanging around,
they think we're trash.
Sarah, I know you're upset, but
believe me nobody thinks your
mother is trash.
Why can't you just
leave her alone?
I can't take this.
I thought you said the
insurance wasn't gonna pay?
They aren't. It doesn't matter.
I'll borrow the money.
Oh no you won't. You're
starting to climb outta
that hole you've been in
all these years.
Can we talk about
money tomorrow?
[Art] Sure. How's he doing?
He's asleep.
Carpenter thinks the
procedure worked.
[Art] Good. I'll go see
him in the morning.
What is Maxflight Enterprises
and why are they willing to
pay you all this money?
[Art] We'll talk about
money tomorrow.
Art...
It's um, Ted. He's a friend.
Come on, you hungry? Let's
get something to eat.
Oh my God, you sold it.
Hey if I wanna fly I'll rent a
plane. No big deal.
You love that plane
more than anything.
No, not more
than anything.
* [dramatic music]
[Art] Boy, we're gonna have to
start fattening you up.
Hi Sarah, it's mom. Sorry
I missed you again.
Please, one of these
days call me.
[Lisa over answering
machine] Daddy's good.
The doctor's amazed at the
progress he's making.
And I want to talk to
talk to you.
The way we used to.
I love you.
[Lisa] Where's that salad bowl?
[Art] Uh, I think
it's up top.
Art and I are talking about
sneaking off to the track
on Saturday
while you're doing
that wedding.
You're not
strong enough.
Oh that doesn't matter. I'm the
newest project now that the
garbage cans have been secured.
Why do you say things like that?
Is that supposed to be a joke?
You work. Art drives me around
and looks after me. I might
live forever.
A lot of guys would be bothered
having their wife's lover living
under the same roof with them.
Not me. I'm finding
it very broadening.
I never ever knew what was on
sale at Trak Auto. How did I
live? [laughing]
Why are you doing this?
"Wheel of Fortune", I never ever
knew when that was on.
He doesn't make
fun of you.
I'm not making fun of him!
We're the two amigos!
I just don't want the kids to
find out and call him Uncle Art.
Stop it! I'm
warning you.
[Eric] This is no way for
two married people to live.
-[Lisa] This is a way for me to
survive.
-[Eric] What about me?
-[Lisa] You have a choice.
Accept it or say no.
-Oh there's a no-brainer.
But if you say no, you're going
to a home. I mean it, Eric.
Will you skip the
noble wifely crap!
You would love to put me
in a home.
You just don't have the
guts to do it.
I don't have the guts? Art lives
here. I live here. What you do
is up to you.
You're my wife. This
is my house.
This is my house. I signed the
lease, I pay the rent.
I want him out!
* [dramatic music]
[Lisa moaning in
the other room]
* [music swells]
[door slams open]
I'm putting myself in a
home in the morning.
* [dramatic music]
Come over here.
Nobody wants you
to leave.
How was it last night, Art. No
performance anxiety I hope.
[Art] I think Lisa and I think
that we need to talk.
Fine I'll start. I am not
living in this house with
you two anymore.
That's not what we want. Last
night was about you and me,
about the argument we had.
You said some things about
Art that just sounded
so, vicious.
After all he's
done for you.
Well excuse me. I didn't mean to
offend Saint Arthur.
-[Art] Neither of us is proud--
-[Eric] Do you mind!?
May my wife and I have a word
without you sticking your oar
in!?
-He's just trying to help.
-Well surprise, surprise he's
not.
All right then
I'll say it.
We are sorry, Eric.
I am sorry.
It was my idea.
It was a cruel, bad,
unnecessary thing to do.
[Art] I agree.
But Eric, no matter what
happens the three of us
are in this together.
So...
you two just imagine that
I'm gonna let last night slide?
I'd say that ninety percent
of loving is forgiving the
people you love.
I like you, Art. But I will
never ever love you. Ok?
[Art] Nobody knows the rules
here. Don't you see that? We're
all just makin'em up as we go.
Yeah I thought we
were gonna try and
figure out something that had
the remote chance of making
us all happy.
Well then we're all gonna
have to work at it.
Yeah, what does
that mean?
That means you gettin' off
your ass and showing her
you're alive.
You don't think she knows that
after twenty three years?
I think for twenty three
years you've driven down
to the mailbox
when you could
have walked.
Now I think that you
better prove to her
that you can walk.
Yeah well, when I really do
get better, you may just
lose her.
Possible, yeah.
You wanna bet?
[laughs] You're on.
What are you doing?
Oh, trying to prove to
somebody or other that I
can walk to the mailbox.
This is your idea?
No, our roommates. Said if I
made it he'd take me flying.
He's got no plane.
You told me had a plane.
He sold it to pay
for your operation.
You ok here?
Put your coat on. I'm taking
you out for an early lunch.
[Lisa] I've been to the bank.
They'll loan me the down
payment. What'dya think?
Can you get it up
in the air?
[Art] Well uh, it'll
take a little work.
I gotta stick the wing back
on and we'll pick up a new
engine but...
oh hell yes I
can do it.
Then we'll do it. As long as
it takes. You promised.
Promised what?
You promised my husband
a plane ride.
* [light-hearted music]
[Eric] Go on.
[Art] There we go. A little up,
a little more to your left.
[Lisa] All right.
Ok, good. Now just hold
her there darling.
How long do I have
to hold this?
Oh, hour, two.
[Eric] Get down!
[speaks inaudibly]
[clink]
[laughter]
Eric, have you seen my
carving knife, the
serrated one!
Honey are you in
the bathroom!
Eric! Honey are--
Lisa, she just dropped by. It
was a surprise.
She lose her voice? My God, I
thought you had another attack.
I'm surprised you didn't call
Art with the good news.
[Lisa] Sarah you're
being childish.
Is everyone else in town
being childish too?
Dad says not even Vivian
talks to you anymore.
All I care about is your father.
He misses you and Bruce.
-I'm here aren't I?
-So am I.
Yeah well, I don't insist on
bringing my lover with me
when I come.
-Some day you'll understand.
-* [dramatic music]
That my mother was attracted to
greasy finger nails?
Why every wife has to
invent her own life.
Even if that means
torturing your own husband?
I'm staying with your father
because he asked me to and
because I love him.
Art makes me able
to do that.
You admit that?
That's what you don't
understand. Love for two men.
There's a name for
women who do that.
Huh?
* [dramatic music]
Ok, today's the day.
Outside, both of you.
* [dramatic music]
[laughing] Goddamit
we're going flying.
-[Lisa] There it is.
-* [playful music]
[Eric] That looks great.
Oh hey no wheelchair.
You said I had to walk
and I'm gonna walk.
Here take that. This thing
doesn't even look used.
[Art] Well Lisa sanded
every inch of it.
[Eric] I don't know. An airplane
just doesn't seem like the ideal
do-it-yourself project.
[laughing]
We sure this
things gonna fly?
[Art] No not really. We'll
find out. [laughing]
[Eric] So where are you
taking me tonight?
[Art] Lisa and I wanna show
you something special.
[Eric] You're not gonna throw me
out or anything are you?
[Art] No. Not that it
hasn't occurred to us.
[Eric] Ok.
-[Art] Ready?
-[Eric] Yeah.
-[Art] Fingers and toes.
-[Eric] Ok.
* [inspirational music]
[Eric] Wow!
[Lisa] Isn't this spectacular?
This is damn special. Worth
everyone of those steps. I
think.
We thought of it on
our first date.
Oh please, give
me break.
Ok not exactly the first date
but later when things changed,
we knew we had to
show it to you.
Yeah, yeah. You just needed
someone to hold the stick
while you two neck.
Not a bad idea. Come
on, take over.
Ha ha ha ha. Hey straighten it
out. Straighten it out!
[Eric] Art! Art!
[laughter]
Ok let go, I got it, I got it,
I got it, I got it.
Eric it was never right
without you. [laughter]
[electric shaver]
[Art sighs]
Hey, how about you and me go see
if the mail's come in?
You go.
Wanna drive me tomorrow. Get
a racing form.
Bring one
back for me.
Oh come on you're acting
like an old geezer.
Old geezer's have a way of
knowing when it's time.
[Art laughs]
You keep an eye on those
falls for me, will you buddy?
[Art crying]
We have to go to the
hospital now.
[Eric] Thanks.
[Lisa] I haven't
finished yet.
[Eric] For giving me six
months longer than I had
any reason to expect.
[Lisa] You know why
cannibals don't eat clowns?
[Eric] No, why?
[Lisa] They taste funny.
[Eric laughs]
I could always
make you smile.
Someday when you
and Sarah are
watching our
grandchildren play,
you tell her something.
Tell her that she
and Bruce
and all the others
that cut us off,
they really
missed something.
They missed a chance at one
percent of what we had.
I'm glad you have
somebody to love.
And I'm, I'm so sorry I'm
such a lousy husband.
You were the best husband,
for so many years.
* [sad music]
You were a great father.
The kids are going to be
just fine.
In seventy six, you made
me laugh. [laughing]
Remember the one about
the wand and the donut
holes. [laughing]
It took guts
all of it.
A life in
the movies.
Living the way we have.
Making it to the mailbox.
The mailbox.
You're crazy.
No. No, I'm
not crazy.
I love you.
I love you too.
Tell the kids...
that more than anything
when this earth...
* [sad dramatic music]
* [somber music]
[Sarah crying]
Let's go home and have
some lunch together.
Got any party food you
need to move?
I was thinking something simple.
A pasta, with one of your dad's
favorite sauces.
I can't eat in that
house today, mom.
* [somber music]
* [light music]
[Art] What'dya got there?
He always liked looking
at that apple tree.
* [light happy string music]
* [Multicom Entertainment
Group jingle]