(epic music)
(people chattering)
- Good evening, sir.
May I have your name, please.
- Robert Matsuda.
- [Attendant] And where
were you going this evening?
- To Rochester, New York.
- May I see some photo ID, please?
Thank you.
Are you checking any bags this evening?
- Yeah, one.
- That'll be $35 Please.
(phone ringing)
- Hi, I'm Jenny, I called about the room.
- Yeah, come on, come on in.
- [Jenny] Thank you.
- Hi, Robert.
- Hi.
(Jenny giggles)
oh boy, it's raining so hard.
- [Man] No that's good.
- So this would be your room and.
- I'm intruding.
- No no no, come on in.
- Hi.
- That's Adolfo.
- So, yeah it's pretty chill.
We have barbecues.
- Cool, I like that.
- So what are you, what
are you doing in the city
or what do you do?
- Well, I just moved
here to start my masters.
So I.
- Cool,
what are you studying?
- English actually.
- Oh wow.
- Yeah I just, I wanted
a place a little closer.
I've been staying with my boyfriend.
He's right in the financial district
so it's just such a bear
to get out of there in the mornings.
- [Robert] Yeah.
- Okay.
- Oh, kitchen.
- Oh yeah, nice kitchen.
That's really pretty.
(Robert laughs)
- Thanks.
- Oh, did you do that?
- Yeah, but I'm still, I'm still learning.
- Yeah it's, it's nice.
- So what do you do for work?
- Um, I'm a princess.
- What?
- Yeah.
(Jenny laughs)
- You're a princess?
That's a job.
- Yeah,
I work for this company.
They send princesses out to
little girls birthday parties.
- [Robert] Oh.
- I'm a little embarrassed by this still.
- What?
- Yeah.
But, it's fun.
- Whatever.
- It's totally fun.
- I help, I help this old hippie guy out.
I get him his Chinese
herbs and his organic tea
and all that junk.
- [Jenny] That's perfect.
- But it's, you know,
it's for right now, so.
- Yeah, I mean.
So many people.
- Yeah.
- Gigs right now.
- Um, cool well,
let me get your information.
- Sure.
Well I really like the place so.
- Great.
- Well I'm glad to hear that.
- Thank you.
It was good to meet you.
(both laughing)
- All right.
- All right, nice meeting you, Jenny.
- Yeah, right.
See you, bye.
♪ It's like sex is kinda funny ♪
♪ You get to warm it up before
you get it on, get it on ♪
♪ I'm in the kitchen ♪
♪ Getting drip like a fish ♪
♪ Let's peep our key tonight ♪
- Aw, I just love you guys.
(people chattering)
- You make me do it.
Well, maybe that's a good thing.
You wanted to do it.
- Yeah, you read my mind, question mark.
Let's go have a cigarette.
- So debonair.
- You know, I get that a lot.
(both laughing)
- Same.
- Good one, good one Robert.
Thank you.
- So you're having a
good surprise party then?
- This is amazing.
It's so amazing.
No one's ever done
anything like this for me.
- Well, I have to tell you that Adolfo
did most of the invites
but I, it was my idea.
I just wanted to tell you that.
- Oh, thank you.
Really.
Thank you.
- You're welcome.
You should stay here
so I could throw you
more surprise parties.
- Well, maybe you can
throw me one out there.
(upbeat acoustic music)
♪ The bees ♪
♪ Making honey in the trees ♪
♪ A syrup half as sweet ♪
♪ As the songs that we sing ♪
♪ And they're a weeping canopy ♪
♪ And all ♪
♪ The California breeze ♪
♪ Sings with us as it breathes ♪
♪ And rustles all the leaves ♪
♪ Of our weeping canopy ♪
♪ Baby, baby we can't stay for long ♪
♪ Maybe just one more song ♪
♪ Baby we can't stay for long ♪
♪ Maybe, maybe just one song ♪
♪ Rejoice ♪
♪ That the Lord has made this whole ♪
♪ This precious refuge for my soul ♪
♪ With my love I will sing ♪
♪ And there are weeping canopies ♪
♪ And we can't stay for long ♪
♪ Maybe, it just was my song ♪
♪ Am I human ♪
♪ Am I a fool ♪
♪ Baby we can't stay for long ♪
♪ Maybe just one more song ♪
♪ Can't stay for long ♪
♪ Just one more song ♪
(type writer clacking)
- Hello?
Leo?
- [Leo] I'm back here.
- Shit.
You know you left a cigarette
burning on the table.
- [Leo] I'm almost done, come here.
- Seriously, Leo.
How many hours a day do you spend in here?
It's disgusting.
- It's the only place I know
where I can get some peace and quiet.
A little solitude, eh.
With no distractions.
- Well, how bout an office?
- Nah, offices are for bean counters.
People who file reports and lawyers,
accountants, salesmen.
As an artist, you need some ambiance.
Some place that nurtures creation.
- [Robert] And for you, it's the bathroom?
- Exactly.
How do you spell embody?
E-M-B.
There.
Ready to go.
- So Leo, your medication's
on the counter.
Do you need anything else?
- You know where I can
get a peyote button?
Relax kid, I'm just kidding.
What are you doing right now?
- All right, come with me.
- What, where?
- Come with me, trust me.
Come on, just come with me.
The hands of time move.
A steady beat.
I wait.
Reflecting on words I spoke.
Still kindle the fire within my soul.
Now in these final moments,
questions everything about you.
Everything about me.
I wait.
Sunshine.
Rain in the morning.
And you wanna leave San Francisco.
- Leo, that was amazing.
- Thank you.
- Where do you come up with this stuff.
- Ah, sometimes the most vivid ideas
come from the bowels of ones darkness.
Ah, that one I should remember.
So how's that work coming along, hm?
Am I ever gonna get to
see any of those drawings?
- Ah, it's garbage.
- Talkin' bout, it's garbage?
How can you consider yourself an artist
and not want people to see your work.
- Oh I'm not the artist,
you're the artist.
- That's where you're wrong.
You see what I did in there?
You just gotta let it flow.
You have it in you.
I've seen your work, it's excellent.
So you're gonna tell me
you're not gonna miss
anything about San Francisco?
The air, the people, the architecture?
You wanna cut and run?
I cut and run on my whole life.
You wanna cut and run
and you don't believe in your own gift
when other people around you believe
and see that you have a gift
and they just want you to be happy.
You came out here from back
home looking for something.
And because it didn't happen overnight,
you're looking to run again.
I think that you, that's just my opinion.
It might be, it might be.
- Leo.
- What?
- I get where you're coming from but.
- No you don't, you don't get
what you're coming, you set.
- No no no, hold up, hold up a second.
You don't get where I'm
coming from, all right.
You're from a completely
different generation.
I know you're really floaty and flowery
and all this stuff sounds great, you know.
But I'm 25 years old, you're right.
- 25 years old, you have
all the answers, don't you?
- You didn't think I was 25 years old.
- No no.
- Hold on.
Did you think I was 25 years old once?
You think I didn't know everything?
I knew nothing, nothing.
And once I admitted that I knew
nothing, I became teachable.
And all I'm trying to do
is save you some of the
pain that I went through.
If you're willing to be teachable.
- What?
- You do what you have to do.
You ever wonder why you came
out here in the first place?
I mean, you came out here to create.
Create your life, create art.
To recreate something
so completely different
than what was dictated to
you that it really should be.
- I know Leo, it's just,
I don't know if that's enough anymore.
- I know what's wrong?
- What?
- You.
You just keep getting in your own way.
- Okay.
- I'll tell you what,
I wanna buy it from you.
- Buy what?
- That drawing.
If you don't know what good art is, I do.
I'd like to make the investment.
- Leo.
- I wanna be the first one
to own a Robert Matsuda.
300 bucks.
- You don't need to do that.
- I don't need to do anything.
Come on, get the gate.
I gotta take a leak.
(upbeat music)
♪ If these guns were mountains ♪
♪ You could say they're far away ♪
♪ Although they are out of range ♪
♪ You gotta wait a later day ♪
♪ She's my best friend ♪
- Hey.
- Hey, Glen.
- Robert, what's up?
You need a hand?
- Nah, I'm good.
- I gotta take it for you.
- No, it's really okay.
- Piece of cake, I got it.
I got it.
- All right, thanks.
Oh not to the side, this
way, this way, this way.
- Nah it's okay, we'll just.
What you got, it's safe in there?
- Yeah, thank you.
- Sometimes you just gotta
force it in, you know?
Fragile stuff.
There we go, look at that.
Good?
- Yeah.
- All right, let's go get warm.
- All right, thank you.
- Yeah, no problem.
- Jenny tells me you're
headed back east, huh?
- Yup.
- You excited?
- Yeah, yeah I'm excited.
- Nice.
- I heard they just had
a blizzard out there.
- Oh, have you seen any
protein bars in here?
I thought I left it.
- I don't know, I would not know.
- Um, well, I mean,
at least you'll have some
opportunities, right?
- Yeah, that's one way to look at it.
- I mean the economy's bouncing back.
Manhattan's a good place to be right now.
Even Brooklyn's not bad, I mean,
a short commute to the city.
- Well actually I'm gonna be in upstate.
- Oh.
What's that like?
- It's cold.
- I bet.
Well, if you ever need a
place to stay in New York.
- Hello gentlemen.
- Hey.
Good to see you.
- Hi.
- Sorry, sweat all over you.
- Hot, sweaty.
- Yeah.
- Oh how was your party the
other night, by the way?
Sorry I missed that, I
was swamped with stuff.
- It was good.
- [Glen] Yeah?
- Yeah, it was, it was good.
It was really nice that
everyone put it together?
- [Glen] Last hurrah, huh?
Did you behave yourself?
- How you felling this morning?
- [Robert] I'm feeling great.
- Good, good.
- Yeah.
Well, I will head out.
- Feel like getting some take out?
- Um.
- I feel like Chinese
or Thai or something.
What do you feel like having?
- More Thai than Chinese.
Hey.
- [Robert] Hey.
- Can we talk for a sec?
- Hey babe, you want you
spice eggplant thing?
- Yeah, eggplant's good, thanks.
I feel like we should talk about this.
- What's there to say?
I, I think right now is
not really the right time.
- [Glen] Hey, can you
come here for one second?
- And I'm double parked outside.
- [Glen] Is it in your purse?
I can't find your purse anywhere.
- Hold on.
- We'll talk later.
- Okay.
- Okay?
- Sure.
- Adolfo, it was a mistake.
- [Adolfo] Mistake my balls, man.
- [Robert] You realize
what this means, right?
- What?
- I'm that other guy.
I'm the asshole, she's got a boyfriend.
- Bro, she's always had a boyfriend.
It's all good, my man.
- I'm being serious.
- I love Jenny, she's a great girl,
but you've got her on this
fucking pedestal someplace man,
you gotta forget about her.
Did you sleep with her?
- No.
- [Adolfo] Did she blow you?
- So nothing really happened.
Come Monday, you're gonna be in New York
and she's gonna be around
here doing whatever the fuck.
Problem resolved.
- Just forget about it.
- Life goes on, bro.
On to the next one.
- Why do I tell you anything anymore?
(whimsical music)
(cat meowing)
- Hey, cookie monster, shut up!
- Stop.
- No.
What is the cat's name, Malimar
or something, I don't know?
- Stop, please.
- It's some kind of cookie.
Hey, shut up!
- Be nice, be nice.
- What, it sounds like he's in heat
or he's dying or he's both.
- Yeah, he's not in heat, he's fixed.
- [Glen] I'm just tired of it.
It's every single night.
- [Jenny] Be nice, be nice.
- Just one more problem
we won't have to worry
about on the 14th floor.
- Well, what about the
next big earthquake.
(cat meowing)
You'll be buried under piles of rubble.
- Well it's a good thing we have
all these giant parachutes
that you brought home with you.
Are we taking all these things with us?
- [Jenny] Yes.
- I just thought,
maybe you'd give it up by the time we go.
Maybe stop, you know, doing the dress up.
- It's not dress up.
- [Glen] Okay.
- I'm a children's party entertainer.
I don't do this for kicks,
I make money doing this.
- Yeah, I know, I just.
I figured it was a fresh
start, it was a new beginning
and that, you know.
It was a chance for you to--
- It's not like I'm a prostitute,
I'm a children's party entertainer.
I don't need a fresh start.
You were the one who last week,
you said that I make kids happy.
What happened to that?
- [Glen] I know you make
kids happy, it's just that.
- You change your mind so fast,
and excuse me, do you do this
at the office, 'cause uh?
- [Glen] No, I don't take
my pants off at the office.
(Jenny sighs)
- What did you do, there's stuff in there?
- [Glen] It's just, it's just
a pair of headphones, here.
- You hurt my feelings.
I don't like it when you call it dress up.
- I'm sorry, I didn't
mean anything by it, okay?
You know that I really do love
what you do for the children.
If you're happy, I'm happy, I'm serious.
It's always been that way.
Have I ever not supported you?
I always have.
I just don't want to see
you wasting your time.
- [Jenny] I'm not wasting time.
- I know you're not, I just.
I think about this new place, you know,
it's a new beginning.
For you and for me.
I mean, we can really start a life.
It's not just shuttling back and forth,
and I thought that maybe with a new life
you'd want to start a new career, too.
- Okay, I'm happy doing this
and I'm going to school, so,
you don't have to worry about
my career yet, all right?
- What's R-I-T?
- Oh, it's, I don't know,
it's Robert's thing.
It's his college or something.
- Come here.
I'm sorry, okay?
I am.
I just know how much
potential you have and,
just want to make sure that, you know.
When you're ready, you're ready.
I'll be here, okay?
- Suck up.
- That's right.
(light-hearted music)
- Hi.
- You live here?
- Yeah, no.
(Robert laughs)
- I don't live here.
- Okay, where are you going?
- Um, up, stairs.
- Okay.
- Where are you off to, today?
- Well, I'm visiting
this guy I take care of.
The third floor.
- Yeah, what's his name?
- Yeah, Leo.
- Leo!
Leonard, yes.
- What you know him?
- That's who I'm here for.
Yeah, yeah yeah yeah.
Can I, can I?
- As in Leo in apartment five?
- Yes, yes, five.
- You want me to sign for anything or?
- No, no no no.
This is a hand to hand package deal here.
Gotta get it right to him.
Forage on.
Actually I'll follow you
'cause I don't know where I'm going.
- Well it's just that, you
know, I take care of him
and I'm responsible for his place, so.
- Yeah, that's okay.
- I can't really have
people just following me.
- No, that's good, that's good.
Can I use the bathroom though?
I have to pee really bad.
I waited a long time downstairs.
- Okay.
- Number five you said?
Apples, that's good, that's good.
- [Robert] Yeah, he loves
all that organic shit.
- Keeps the doctor away.
Where's the bathroom?
- On the left.
Leo?
Hello?
- Thank you, God.
I was sitting out there
for like five hours.
I thought I was gonna get
another bladder infection.
- Ah, you feel better?
- Oh God, yeah I do actually.
Thank you, but.
- [Robert] But what?
- Wow.
- Everything okay?
- Yeah, there's dead animals everywhere.
What's that about?
What is that?
Is that a dinosaur?
- No, that's a cat.
What's your name again?
- Yeah uh, Sara, Sara Landis.
- Robert.
- Are, are you Hawaiian.
- I'm half Japanese.
But there are a lot of halfies in Hawaii.
- Japanese.
You know I love Japan town.
Sapporo, there's some great
sushi restaurant's there.
We should, we should do that sometime.
You and me, yeah?
What is that?
It's a smoking monkey.
- Hm.
Can I have some water?
- Yeah, sure.
- [Sara] So are you his nurse?
- No, I just, I watch
over Leo a little bit.
- Where are you from anyway?
Are you a native.
- I'm from Rochester.
- I'm from Vermont.
- Cool, same neck of land.
- Oh my God.
You take the 89 to the four to the 80
and your in fucking Rochester.
We're like neighbors.
It's like an hour and a half away.
- Right.
- Well, six hours.
But you know, I mean, it
depends if you get the.
- I'm sorry to cut this short.
I would love to hear where you're from,
it's just not the right time.
- Yeah, yeah.
Can I get that water?
Really thirsty.
- Yeah.
- Thanks.
- Good?
- That was a lot of water.
- Is this gonna affect
your bladder infection?
- I gotta get finished.
No, that's actually good for it.
- And how did you say you knew Leo?
- Yeah, oh we, I told you.
Long, long time ago we met.
We're good friends.
- Okay, you're done with this, right?
- Yeah.
- Good.
- [Sara] Sure.
- So what do you, I don't
know, what do you want?
Ball's in your court.
- Yeah, no, we can't,
we gotta give it to him.
I can't just leave it here.
- Okay, so I guess you
can try back tomorrow.
Maybe tomorrow morning.
Catch him either early in
the morning or late at night.
- Um, let me just, yeah okay.
All right, well here, I'll just.
- I don't even think
it's taking a picture.
- Yeah I got it.
I guess I'll leave it here,
but um,
ah, I don't know.
- Are you okay?
Is everything okay?
I have to go.
Let's go.
- Um, just uh, I'm starving.
Oh, can I get a, what the hell is that?
- Whoa whoa whoa.
Come on, come on.
We really have to get out of.
- That is disgusting.
- Let's go.
- All right.
- You know, I thought you
were a bike messenger
when I first saw you.
- You thought I was a local.
Shut up.
That's awesome.
Oh my God.
You know how lucky I feel right now?
- [Robert] Let's go.
Oh my God.
- Okay.
All right, that's great, thank you.
- Leo will get your package,
it's safe in the house.
Why don't I take your number,
maybe you'll feel better about it?
- Yeah, that's problematic.
I don't, I don't actually have a number.
Uh, but let me take yours.
Go ahead.
Thank you.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
Good, okay.
- I have no idea.
- Yeah, oh yeah.
- Why you're here or where you're going,
but it seems like you're on a journey.
- Yeah.
- And a nice lady, so.
- Okay.
- All right.
- Good luck.
- Yeah.
You're a good guy, Bobby.
You're a good guy.
- It's Robert.
- [Adolfo] Who was she?
- I don't know.
- But was she hot?
- She was odd, or odd hot.
- Hey you got someone coming up here.
Give them a flyer.
- Hey, there's this thing tomorrow night
and it's this party,
and my friends gonna.
Fuck him.
- Robert.
- This sucks, man.
- What are you doing, man?
What the fuck, man?
- Every single fucking time.
- Look how many flyers
you got in your hand.
You can't be acting up,
jumping on people like that.
It's a party, not a funeral man.
There's nothing to be nervous about.
- So what do I say?
- You got someone coming
up right here, right?
You make eye contact.
Don't jump on 'em.
Just say, hey, party tomorrow night.
Hope you can make it.
All right, here she comes, here she comes.
- All right.
- Are you kidding me?
You look like a retarded Travolta, man.
- Really?
- Dude.
It's a party.
Loosen up a little bit.
(phone ringing)
- Hello?
- Hi.
- Hey.
- I'm on a gig right now.
Actually I just stepped
outside for a moment.
We need to see each
other before you leave.
- [Robert] Yeah.
- [Jenny] What about,
tomorrow, have a day?
- [Robert] Okay.
- How bout, 9:30, at Mojo?
- Yeah, yeah.
- Okay, great.
So I'll see you then.
- [Robert] Yeah, I'll see you then.
All right, bye.
- Well?
- Tomorrow at Mojo, 9:30, me and Jenny.
Fuck yeah, boy.
- Got 'em!
- Excellent, excellent.
(phone ringing)
- Hello?
- You're not gonna tell me what to do,
I'm telling you what to do.
- [Sara] No, I'm trying to tell you.
- Keep your mouth shut.
- Bobby.
- Are you Robert?
- Bobby, Bobby.
- Yes.
- Do you have ID?
- This is my boyfriend.
- I do.
- This is my boyfriend, Robert.
- All right, we had a report
of a burglary in progress.
We got here, we found her
in one of the apartments.
- Okay.
- She says that you're her boyfriend.
That you gave her permission
to be in the apartment.
Is that true.
- I was trying.
- Sir, I need you to
focus on my right now.
- Yes, that's, that's my girlfriend.
Here, there you go.
- [Officer] Right, well
the address on here
doesn't match it.
- I understand officer.
I take care of Leo Glass in number five.
I have keys.
- Baby.
I missed you so much, sweetie.
- You have a key?
- Yeah.
- All right, go ahead
and try to open the door.
Let me see if your key works.
- Bobby.
- Keep your mouth shut.
- See I told you, I told you.
- All right that's
fine, come on over here.
One last question.
- Yeah.
- Where's she from?
- She's from, she's from Ver.
- From where?
- From Vermont.
- Are you sure?
- Yes, yes I'm sure.
- All right.
- Thank you so much, officer.
I'm really sorry.
- Okay, let me give
you a little piece of--
- Can I borrow those for the night?
- Let me give you a little
piece of advice, all right?
- Yes.
- Next time you're visiting,
don't break into the place, all right?
If you don't have a key,
wait for a person that has a key.
- Absolutely.
- You get it?
- I don't think so.
Good luck.
- Bobby!
Thank you so much.
(Sara kissing Robert)
(Sara laughing)
Did you see the look on his face
when your key went right into that slot?
He didn't know that.
(Sara laughs)
I'm not gonna fuck you by the way.
Oh my God, it's still here.
Oh God.
- You trying to rob this place?
- [Sara] No, of course not.
- Then what are you doing breaking in
in the middle of the night?
- Well I just needed to get my package.
What's there to rob here
besides dead animals?
- [Robert] Exactly.
- I'm a vegetarian.
- Okay,
cut the fucking bullshit.
- Okay, everyone just
chill out for a second.
- [Robert] No.
- The package, there's no note.
It would have been weird if he came home
and it was sitting in his kitchen.
- You didn't think about this before?
The thought didn't cross your mind
when you dropped it off?
- You got a point.
You got a point.
- Okay, we're leaving.
- [Sara] Bobby, hold on.
- We're leaving.
- You're the only one that knows Leo,
and I need your help.
I have to find him.
- We are getting out of here.
- No, no no no.
You have to help me find him.
We can stay here tonight, Bobby.
- You crazy, you think I'm
gonna help you find him now?
- I'll sleep on the couch.
Come on, Bobby, I
thought you were a nurse.
Aren't nurses supposed to help people?
- I'm here at two o'clock
in the fucking morning
in my pajamas, all right?
- [Sara] No, I know, I
know, you're adorable.
- No, this is, this is not a joke.
Who the hell do you think you are?
What makes you think
that I should be here saving your ass
and how long have you been?
- Okay, okay, listen all right?
I get it.
We got off on the wrong foot, I'm sorry.
And the whole situation is very ah!
I get it, but,
this is a very delicate
situation and if you knew
you wouldn't be talking like this.
You're gonna feel like such a jackass.
- Okay, then explain it to me.
What's the situation?
I'm done.
- What are you some
kind of soulless maniac?
What's wrong with you?
I'm in the street tonight.
Shit!
(whimsical music)
- Ah, blueberry, my favorite.
Hi.
- No.
- Oh God.
- Unbelievable.
- Look, hold on, hold on.
The way I see it is,
you can give in now or later,
'cause we both know
I'm not going anywhere.
- I've given in, okay?
- Take this as an
opportunity to help somebody.
Meet somebody new.
- Yeah well, we've already met.
Enjoy the muffin, all right?
- I promise, I'm really fun.
- Mm-hm.
I think I've already
seen how fun you can be.
- Bobby, wait.
Wait wait wait wait wait.
Bobby wait.
Bobby, wait wait wait wait.
Okay okay, let me break it down.
Um, have you ever, have
you ever had a secret
that you couldn't tell
anybody in your life
that was so important but that,
that some fucked up life experience
wouldn't allow you to get what you needed?
Have you ever, have you ever had that?
- Sure, that's the human condition.
We have have those, so what?
- Look, okay okay, I can help you.
- I think the only way you can help me
is by leaving me alone.
- I'll do anything you need, Bobby.
It's that important.
- I don't need anything from you.
- Just take 10 minutes out of your life
and just take me to a
place that Leonard goes.
10 minutes.
- I can't help you.
This is, it's not my job to,
to take care of your psychological issues.
- Oh Bobby, I see it.
- What do you see?
- I see it, I see it, I see it.
I'm so sorry.
Whatever it is.
I know.
- 10 minutes, okay?
I'm fine, I'm fine.
10 minutes, okay?
So I have no idea if he's
gonna be here or not.
Just letting you know.
I don't want to get your hopes up but,
a lot of times on a sunny
day he does yoga out here.
- This is where he does yoga.
- Yup.
- oh my God, dog.
Dogs!
Hi cuties.
(Sara barks)
God, I didn't realize we were
gonna be mountain climbing.
This bag is so heavy.
Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- Throw it on there.
I'm like a snail, you know?
A snail has a big apartment on its back.
So I just carry.
- Yeah, now I'm like a snail.
- I just, I don't buy
into the whole philosophy
of defining yourself
by the things you have.
I mean that's what the society does.
It it it tries to make you think
that that's how you have to be.
But you don't.
- Well if you don't define
yourself by your things
then why do you carry everything with you?
- What do you mean?
It means everything that
I have is important to me.
Don't you have things that
people important to you gave you?
Like your mom or your
sister or your girlfriend?
You don't have a girlfriend?
- No.
- Are you in love with somebody.
What's her name, Bobby?
- Uh.
Her name's Jenny, okay?
We'll leave it at that.
- Jenny?
I can help you with Jenny!
I know women, I am a woman.
- Yeah?
- I am a woman.
Okay, we'll set it up.
I'll set it up for you.
You just sit back and I'll
take care of everything.
- There's nothing to set up.
I'm leaving, she has a boyfriend.
- Yeah.
- It's complicated.
- [Sara] Boyfriends are tough.
What's he like?
- He's perfect.
- Well what time did they walk in today?
They didn't call, they just showed up?
Yeah, with no appointment?
Well I had I no idea
they were gonna come in.
Sorry, this client came in
and didn't have an appointment
and they wanted us to come
up with a proposal for them
on the spot, I just, yeah.
- I know, I heard, I know.
I hope they give you unlimited
minutes on that thing.
- It's for the greater good, baby.
You want to eat, don't you?
Hey good morning.
How you doing?
- Hey Glen, good morning.
- Good to see you.
- Yeah, you too.
- Dr Hollerman, this
is my girlfriend Jenny.
Jenny, this is Dr Hollerman.
- [Doctor] Hi Jenny, nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you.
- We played doubles last week
at the club for the first time.
- [Doctor] Yeah he beat my butt.
(Glen laughs)
- This guys got a hell of
a backhand, I tell you.
- Really?
- So what do you do?
- Well--
- She's actually getting her MFA.
She's going into publishing.
- It's a MFA in writing.
- That's terrific.
- She's so talented.
- He's a great guy, hold on to him.
- Aw, come on.
- Thank you.
- [Sara] My passion is
traveling, actually.
- [Robert] Yeah.
- I love going somewhere
new, it's so exciting.
And then there's new food and new places.
Where have you been to?
- I've traveled plenty.
- Yeah, where?
- I've been to Toronto and Niagra Falls.
- Toronto, okay, all right.
- That's like being.
- You need to get on an airplane
and go somewhere immediately, I'm serious.
- Yeah, with what money?
- Who cares?
Just get there.
- Okay, so you're traveling the world.
You're a nomad, you're a gypsy.
How long is that gonna last you
before at some point,
you have to figure out how
to put food on the table?
I mean do you want kids?
- Food on the table?
- Do you want to get married?
I mean what about you?
You're asking me all these questions
about love, love, love, love.
Do you have a boyfriend?
What?
I'm joke,
I'm just saying.
You know, if you think that it makes,
it would make me feel better
to talk about my romance.
- Just stop, okay?
No, no no no no, just.
You do not need to be asking
me anything about my life.
You have no right to pry into my life.
You don't know who I am.
You don't know what I've
been through, okay Bobby?
- All right, so I'm just, I'm sorry.
I just, I was just asking.
I'm sorry, we don't have to talk about it.
(phone ringing)
- What up, bro?
- Hey, what's up, man?
- [Adolfo] I'm cooking.
Anyway, what are you doing man?
- [Robert] Well you're
not gonna believe this.
I'm in the Hague
and I'm still with that
chick from yesterday.
- [Adolfo] The nutty one?
- [Robert] Yeah.
(Adolfo laughs)
At first she was pretty crazy and,
I was a little bit surprised.
I didn't know what to
do, but she's not so bad.
- [Adolfo] Why are you in the Hague?
- [Robert] Yeah, you know,
she needs to find Leo
and I need to find Leo,
so at this point I could
really use the money.
He's offered to buy my drawing.
- [Adolfo] What?
- [Robert] Yeah.
- [Adolfo] That's great.
- [Robert] Yeah it's
pretty cool, pretty cool.
But I think it's a real sympathy move.
- [Adolfo] No, oh come on.
No that's validation, baby.
That's nothing less.
A little validation goes all the way, man.
- [Robert] I guess so,
but do you really think
it's worth 300 bucks?
- [Adolfo] Who cares?
(Adolfo laughs)
Listen, are you coming
to the party tonight?
'Cause it's gonna be epic baby, epic.
- [Robert] Yeah, well
hopefully all that hard work
will have paid off then.
(alarm beeping)
- Bobby, Bobby!
Oh my God.
- What's the matter?
- Come on, let's go!
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
Come on, grab my bag, grab my bag!
- What?
♪ Get yourself ready and see ♪
♪ I found myself I was following me ♪
♪ On the conditions of friendly seas ♪
♪ I'm lonely and I'm lonely ♪
♪ Take me without change ♪
♪ People won't change
when you want them to ♪
♪ And I know you will go away ♪
♪ Closer to one way streets and rain ♪
♪ Oh, it's like I'll expand ♪
♪ Regrets and paradise ♪
♪ No dice ♪
♪ You won't have to shake your gears ♪
♪ 'Cause change, people don't change ♪
♪ People don't change
when you want them to ♪
♪ Don't change, people don't change ♪
♪ You still got a lot in front of you ♪
♪ Don't change, change ♪
♪ People don't change
when you want them to ♪
♪ You got a lot trouble ♪
- [Robert] You can at least prepare me
and say hey, listen, we're
gonna steal something today.
Can you just wait outside
or at least have me wait
around the block, but.
- You sound like a
jaded asshole right now.
You were happy and you didn't
want to be anywhere else.
We were in the moment, all right?
So let's, let's stick with that, okay?
- [Robert] Okay.
- And stop being so fucking grumpy.
- There's only on place
I can really think of
that Leo's likely to be at.
- Oh hi.
- Hey,
you haven't see Leo around
at all today, have you?
- No, not yet.
- No?
- Wow.
Wow wow wow wow wow.
This place is amazing, oh my God.
- I know.
- Can we just hang out for a second?
I just wanna look around.
Hey, can we um,
can we grab some valerian
root when we get outta here?
- [Robert] What's that?
- It says it's the 19th century
form of Xanax, herbal form.
- Oh yeah, well if it calms
your ass down we definitely can.
- Ha ha ha ha.
- Right after we learn
how to train a parrot.
- I trained a parrot once.
- Yeah?
- yeah.
- How's it working out?
- I don't know, it's dead.
The travel section.
Hey.
We like travel, right?
- Um, yeah.
- Where we going, where
we going, where we going?
Pick a place, pick a place, pick a place.
- Stop.
- Prague.
- Where's Prague?
- How bout Tibet, Sydney, Peru?
- I'd love to see Tibet.
- What about Brazil?
Morocco, Norway?
- I don't know where I would begin.
I'd love to see the whole world.
- Look.
You could go there.
- That's beautiful.
- You could go, right?
There and walk into that
building and see what's inside.
So what's up with this Jenny, huh?
What's her deal?
- I mean, she's pretty amazing.
She's got a really cutesy sense of humor
and.
- Cutesy.
- She's really charismatic.
- [Sara] Mm-hm, mm-hm.
- She walks into a room and
everyone stops for a second,
it's, she's breathtaking.
- Oh yes, she sounds like
a breath of fresh air.
(Robert laughs)
- She is.
- Have you tried anything with her?
- Well, we kissed last Friday.
- You piece of shit.
- Only once.
What?
- You're scum.
- I know.
But I wouldn't expect,
you're telling me to be brave and explore,
now you're calling, now I'm
scum and a piece of shit.
- Wow, you kissed a girl with a boyfriend.
Oh my God.
Oh my God, oh my God, oh my God.
Look.
- The "Tropic of Cancer."
- Amazing.
- Yeah, you know Leo's
got that in his house.
- Look, okay.
You have to read this book, okay?
It's gonna change your life.
This guy, he just basically
picks up and takes off
and doesn't give a fuck
about anything that he's left behind
and he just goes out into
the world and he just lives.
And he basically just embraces it.
You gotta read it.
Buy it.
I don't have any cash.
God, my nails are a mess.
- They look fine to me.
- No no no no, I have to do a little work,
a little maintenance.
Just one click little
swipe, swipe, swipe, swipe.
See, that easy.
- [Robert] They're cute, they
look like abalone shells.
- Do you like 'em?
Thanks.
- Think it fits your style.
- What are you eating?
- [Robert] Just some noodles and chicken.
- Chicken?
- mm-hm.
- Bobby, animals are our friends, okay?
- [Robert] All right.
- They're our friends,
be nice to your friends.
- Okay, thanks pal.
I really appreciate you
sacrificing your life
so I could enjoy you, your deliciousness
and get my protein and
thank you very much.
- You think you're cute, don't you?
You're not cute.
So talk to me about Jenny.
- I don't want to wallow
in my depression right now.
I have to be excited
about where I'm going.
- [Sara] Let's not think about that.
Have you told her how you feel?
- Sure, she knows I really care about her.
She knows.
We kissed.
That's a connection, she gets that.
Am I gonna just, you know,
tell her how I feel and
screw things up even more?
If it really mattered that much to her,
she would have come to
meet me this morning.
- She doesn't know how you feel, Bobby.
How is she supposed to
give up her entire life
for somebody she can't
even, she doesn't even know?
- [Robert] I'm not asking her to.
- Okay.
Look, you have to tell her how you feel.
If you want her to come
to you she needs to know.
Put it down.
Put it down, gone, gone.
All right.
I'm gonna give you V-L-T,
visual love technique.
It works, it works.
Okay, look at me.
Square up.
Go into your Zen Buddha
place, heart of the Buddha.
And I want you to imagine
that I am Miss Jenny.
Whatever you say, I'm gonna
be completely receptive to.
- Okay.
- Okay?
All right, take your time
and when you open your eyes,
I am Jenny.
- Hey Jenny.
I really want to have things
be really good with us.
- Okay stop, that's pathetic.
(Robert laughs)
- This feels silly, do you have to have.
- Work with me on this, okay?
All right, let's do it again.
- Okay.
(endearing music)
Hey Jenny.
- Hey.
- You look beautiful.
- You're so sweet Robert.
You're always so nice to me.
- What happened the other night?
- I don't know.
I feel so confused about that.
I've been thinking about
what I'm gonna say to you.
- Okay.
- And I, I still don't know what to say.
- Do you feel anything?
Am I, am I an idiot?
Am I alone on this?
- I feel so guilty.
And it's not even,
I don't even just feel
guilty towards Glen,
I feel guilty towards you, too.
- I need to know, do we have a chance?
- Bobby,
Bobby.
(people chattering)
That was so good.
Are you okay?
That's beautiful, come here.
Come here.
(Glen sighs)
- [Glen] Sure beats the
hell out of the office.
- [Jenny] I know.
- I ready your story.
- Falsetto?
- Yeah, and I read it and I loved it.
And I have a friend of mine in publishing.
I forget what company she works for,
but I gave it to her and she read it.
- What'd she say?
- Well, if you're interested,
when the semester's over, she uh,
would like to offer you an internship.
I think she said,
I'm trying to remember
her exact words but,
that you showed a lot of promise
as a young up and coming writer.
- I do.
- Don't you?
(Glen laughs)
I like the way it sounded too.
It was like print that, print that.
- [Jenny] Oh, thank you, baby.
That's uh, that was so thoughtful
of you to show her that.
What made you wanna?
- Well, I mean, it's your future.
It's important to me
and I just want to do
anything I can to help.
So.
- Thank you.
So um, who were you on the
phone with so late last night?
- Ah, Sammy.
It wasn't a work related call, I swear.
Poor guy.
Him and Roxy are breaking up.
- What do you mean?
We just saw them on Friday.
- I know.
Um, I don't know what happened.
She's been, I guess he was just telling me
that she's been acting
really weird lately.
- They seemed fine.
- I know, right?
- That's too bad.
- Yeah.
Got me thinking a little bit.
- What do you mean?
- Just got me thinking about us.
Uh, I know that I work a lot
and I take phone calls sometimes
at inappropriate times.
But I'm only doing it for us.
Because, I just want to make sure that
kind of everything will
be okay for the future.
I love you.
You're the most important thing.
So don't ever think you're not, please.
- No way.
- Jenny.
- Hey.
Good to see you.
- You too.
What are you doing here?
- Oh, we're just, we had the day off
so we're kind of strolling.
- I've seen you before,
around, I'm not sure.
I'm Glen, hi.
- Glen, it's Morgan.
- We, we go to school together.
- Your party the other night was so fun.
- I know.
Where you pretty hung
over the next morning?
- I will never drink rum
for the rest of my life.
- Oh yeah you will.
- You sure.
(all laugh)
- That guy Robert is so cute.
He was cracking me up.
- Oh, yeah.
- Adorable.
- You think so.
Yeah he's pretty fun.
- I don't know why you didn't
hook Robert up with
your friend over there.
- Morgan?
She's really not his type.
- [Glen] She's hot, she's anybody's type.
- Really?
She's hot so that makes
her anybody's type.
- [Glen] Just saying.
- She's hot so she's anybody's type.
- [Glen] She's not an ax murderer, is she?
- Yeah, right.
'Cause if you're not hot,
you're probably an ax murderer,
right Glen?
- Well, guess there's no
better time to do this.
There's tickets to the theater tonight.
- No Exit.
You wanna go to this?
- Yeah, I love musicals.
I just don't know if I
want to take you anymore.
(Jenny laughs)
- Baby, it's not a musical.
- [Glen] Right.
- You would sit through this for me?
- Yeah, you know.
You like the theater.
I want to make you happy.
It'll be fun, we'll make a night of it.
- Yeah, but it's Robert's last night here.
- [Glen] Well um, maybe
we can get out in time?
- Yeah, I don't think so, it's.
- [Glen] Well it's fine,
we don't have to go.
- No, no we, I want to go.
Yeah, I think we should go.
I mean, when else am I gonna get
to drag you to the theater, right?
Depending on how this goes.
- [Glen] Depending on how it goes.
- Thank you.
Thank you so much.
- You're welcome.
- It's perfect.
- Hey Leo, it's Robert.
I haven't seen you
around in a little while
so I hope everything's okay.
But I was by the house and I was wondering
if you still want to buy my drawing.
I didn't see any money there.
So please please give me a
call before I leave tonight.
I'd really appreciate it.
I'd love to say goodbye.
As a side note, there's someone here
that has a package for
you, so give me a call.
All right, take care, bye.
- What's he giving you money for?
- It's a, it's a drawing I did of him.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- So you're like a real artist?
Oh my God!
Bobby, that's amazing!
- I guess so.
- You're like Picasso
or Monet or Terenzio,
I'm so proud of you.
That's amazing, let's go do something fun.
- Well I think he just feels
bad for me to be honest.
- No, come on, you're amazing.
Let's do something fun, let's celebrate.
- Like what, like what?
- I don't know, anything.
Be spontaneous.
Come on, Bobby.
- Let's get outta here.
- Yeah.
(engine choking)
What's going on?
- I don't know, hold on.
- Just, you know, give it a good one.
Wait, hold on, hold on.
Give it a good, you know.
Give it a good solid.
Come on.
- Oh crap.
You know how long I had that car for
and how much money I've put into it?
- Ugh, poor you.
Aren't you leaving anyway?
Why do you need a car?
- My friend was gonna sell it for me.
- [Sara] For what?
Fives of tens of dollars?
- Look, Sara, I think it's
best we go our separate ways.
- [Sara] What?
No.
- I gotta catch a bus home.
- No, Bobby, what about Leo?
What are you talking about right now?
- What about him?
We're not gonna find Leo.
I mean we've looked for him.
How do you expect us to get around town?
- We can, we can, we
can, we can take a cab.
- A cab?
With my money?
I mean, I can't pay for a cab
to wander around the city right now.
- Yeah, okay.
Yeah.
Money's tough, huh?
- What?
- Sara.
- Okay.
Okay.
- Sara, what are you doing?
- Come on.
- What?
- Oh my God,
the keys are in it, come on.
- This is crazy.
You're gonna steal a go-kart.
- Get in the car.
Or whatever this thing is.
- Get, God.
- Get in.
Yes, Bobby.
You in?
Woo-hoo!
♪ Became an ice cream man ♪
♪ Drove around ♪
♪ He gave ice cream to all the kids ♪
♪ All the kids in town ♪
♪ He was a bit weird ♪
♪ All the dogs were run by clowns ♪
♪ I'm thin ♪
♪ All your favorite flavors ♪
♪ It's not cool ♪
♪ Ice cream man ♪
♪ Drove around ♪
♪ Gave ice cream to all the kids ♪
♪ All the kids in town ♪
- You know how it is.
- Yeah, you know what?
I had a pet in school.
- Oh yeah?
- Yeah.
He was this gimp.
- Back in your yard.
- Yeah, it was a gimp that
lived in the neighborhood
and I took him in, I
lured him in with nuts
and I trained him.
Can you believe it?
- Okay.
- I trained him.
I trained him to pee in a
cat box in the bathroom.
- You trained your squirrel
to pee in a cat box?
- Yeah.
Yeah, it was awesome
- Yeah right.
You know I used to play golf.
- You did?
- Yeah, in high school.
- Sunny?
Hey.
(speaking in foreign language)
Wow.
- Bobby, come on, let's go.
- Is everything okay?
- [Man] How's Jeremy?
(speaking in foreign language)
- Do you know this guy?
- No.
Come on.
- Do you want to explain to
me what that was all about?
- No, I don't.
- Huh Sara?
Or should I call you Sunny?
- I told you, my name is Sara
Landis, I'm from Vermont.
- Oh yeah, well I don't know
what to believe anymore.
- What do you want me to say?
What the fuck do you want me to say?
- Well I told you everything about myself.
The one time I ask you
a question about you,
it's like I lit a fire under your ass.
- You know what?
You know what?
- [Robert] What?
What?
- You don't give a fuck about me.
You don't care anything about me,
or my life or my fucking problems.
Go back to your fucked up,
bourgeois world, Bobby.
Go back to your lame ass problems.
- How can you say that?
- And you lame ass fucking
girlfriend, all right?
I don't, you know what?
- [Robert] Do you know what?
- Fuck off.
- Fine, I will fuck off.
Here's your everything.
- Fine!
Fine.
Sunny was a nickname he gave me.
- Who, the guy on the train?
(Sara sighs)
- No.
My husband.
- You're married?
Sara.
Wait.
Wait, hold up a sec.
(dramatic music)
- I apologize for overreacting.
I just uh, I was really
caught off guard by him.
I didn't expect to see him.
- [Robert] Yeah, who was that?
- He's a, he's an old friend.
He's a friend of my husband's.
We used to party together.
- [Robert] Mm-hm.
- I don't think he knew.
- [Robert] Knew, what?
- My husband, he was called
on a long tour in Afghanistan
and I thought he was coming home
but then he got called on a second tour.
- [Robert] It must be really
difficult to be apart.
- You have no idea.
The last time I saw him,
he made me blueberry pancakes.
Brought them to me in bed.
He's gone.
- [Robert] What do you mean?
- He's dead.
(Sara sighs)
He died about a year ago.
I got a knock at the door.
And they gave me a flag and a letter.
Your husband's gone.
That was it, I don't know.
Look, Bobby, you gotta live your life.
Okay, you need to everything that,
that you need to do
everything that you want to do
and say everything that you want to say
and don't hold it back.
'Cause you don't know,
you just don't know.
You don't know what's
gonna happen tomorrow.
You could lose everything just like that.
You get it?
You need to talk to her.
No regrets.
Time's precious.
(phone ringing)
Are you gonna get that?
- It's okay.
- No, get it.
It could be somebody important.
(Sara sniffles)
- Oh, it's Jenny.
- Answer it.
- I don't know.
- Are you crazy?
Answer it.
- Hello?
- Hey.
so I can't believe I'm gonna say this,
but I don't think I'm gonna be able to see
you before you go.
Glen surprised me.
He planned this whole day.
We went to Sausalito
and now I think we're
going to the theater.
I feel like I'm not gonna
get to say goodbye to you.
- [Glen] Hey babe, have you
seen my contact solution?
Who's that?
- Robert.
- Robert, how you doing buddy.
- Hey Glen.
- [Glen] Are you, are you leaving tonight?
- Yeah, I am.
- [Robert] Oh, okay.
What are you, at the airport right now?
- No, I've got a red eye tonight.
- [Glen] Oh, that's rough.
Listen, good luck to you, okay?
And if you need anything
while you're in NYC
just give me a call
and I'll do my best to
help you out, all right?
- Glen, I was wondering,
do you guys want to get together tonight?
- Hold on one second.
- Do you want to hang
out with Robert instead.
- I mean, it's his last
night, but, can we?
Is that okay?
- Yeah, I'll just change the
tickets for another night.
- You sure?
- Yeah.
Hey, Robert, I think we're
gonna scrap the theater plans
so what would you say
for meeting us for a
drink at nine o'clock?
- Yeah that, that sounds great.
- What's going on?
- [Glen] Who's that?
- Nobody.
- [Glen] Are you on a date?
Are you taking a phone call
in the middle of a date?
- No no no no no.
(Glen laughs)
- [Glen] No, that's awesome.
I think you should bring
her, I want to meet her.
- No, she's just a friend.
- [Glen] Okay, whatever you say.
All right, so we'll see
the two of you tonight.
Ocean's, nine o'clock.
All right, I'll talk to you later.
- Okay, bye.
- And?
- And,
I think we have a date.
- Nice.
Hi five.
(rock music)
Bobby!
♪ You say you're not frightful to know ♪
♪ If I'm never gonna go home ♪
♪ Minds feeling what they're
feeling and know where to go ♪
♪ And your humming to
it, turn on the radio ♪
♪ You make a boy feel grown ♪
♪ Few years he's ever known ♪
♪ Listen for a minute ♪
♪ 'Cause you got another hour to go ♪
♪ They go and send it and she livin' ♪
- Thank you.
All right, let's go.
- Wait, hold on, hold on.
I'm gonna, I'll just be right back.
- [Robert] Where you going?
- Give me 10 minutes,
I'll meet you in there.
- It's right here.
- No, I'll meet you in there.
It's fine.
Wait for me.
- All right.
- [Glen] So where is she?
- [Robert] She'll be here soon.
- Who is this girl?
- It's my friend, Sara.
- You just never mentioned a Sara.
- I know, you'll get to meet her.
She's cool.
- [Jenny] All right.
- [Glen] Is uh, is that her over there?
- Yeah, it is.
- Oh, hi.
- Hey.
Wow.
I love this.
How'd you put that together?
Wow.
Jenny.
- Yes, it's nice to meet you.
- Jenny, Jenny, Jenny, Jenny.
Give me a hug.
- [Glen] Good for you, seriously.
I'm really happy for you.
You taking her with you?
- Oh, Sara.
I don't think she's coming with me.
- Love the dress.
- Really?
- She's just a friend of mine.
- Just a friend, hi, hi.
- Hi, I'm Sara.
- Glen, nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you, give me a hug.
Yes.
All right, sorry I'm late you guys.
- [Jenny] That's all right.
- Okay, all right, all right.
Horoscopes, all the way around.
When were you born and
what's your horoscope.
- December 8th, and I'm a Sagittarius.
- [Jenny] He's very much a Sagittarius.
- [Robert] Oh yeah, how so?
- You're very philosophical.
- Yeah, and romantic and passionate,
and at times unorganized and.
- That's true.
Thank you.
- Here, I'll take care of you.
Thanks.
- We should drink to something.
- [Sara] Yeah, of course.
Always toast.
- Glen you bought, you make a toast.
- Okay.
To Robert,
may you have safe travels
and I hope you find
everything you're looking for in New York.
- Thank you.
- Okay, hold up, hold up, I'm sorry.
I need to hijack your toast.
My bad.
To living your dreams,
following your heart,
and trying new things.
- I like that.
- Cheers.
- Why not?
- [Sara] Looks like a party.
How many drinks are there?
- [Glen] Enough.
- 14!
- 14.
- Whoa, very good.
- [Sara] I'm impressed.
- What a bunch of lushes, man.
I'm just gonna run to the restroom.
- You just reminded me I have to pee, too.
I'm just gonna leave my jacket.
- Okay.
- She's a firecracker.
- [Robert] Oh yeah?
- I love it man.
I guess you got your hands full, don't ya.
Listen, um,
I know that, this past year's
been a little rough for Jenny,
she's you know, kind of
had a lot on her plate,
and you've been there through a lot of it.
And, sorta like the other guy in her life.
And I get it, I get it.
And I appreciate it.
I guess what I'm trying to
say is thank you, bottom line.
And, I owe you a lot.
More thank you think.
- Ah, I love your necklace.
- Oh, thanks.
I got it at a thrift shop.
- Oh, that's cool.
So um, are you and Robert, dating?
- Oh, no.
I love Robert, he's
adorable but, I'm married.
- Oh wow, okay.
- Yeah.
How long have you know Robert?
- Long enough to know he's a great guy
and guys like that don't
come around very often.
I'm a better person for knowing him.
Well, I'll see you out there, okay?
- Sure.
- All right well, good luck, Bobby.
Good luck with everything.
- Thanks, Glen.
- What no.
No no no, no no no.
The night's not over yet.
No we still have time.
We should um, we should go dancing.
Yeah, let's go dancing.
- Are you sure?
- I have an early morning tomorrow.
I have some meetings.
- Oh babe, come on.
- Well you know what?
There's this thing that Adolfo's running.
It's at Mighty on Utah.
- Yes.
- Oh, yes.
- I haven't been, let's go for it.
- [Jenny] We have to go to that.
- [Sara] Yes, Jenny.
- I'd really like to say goodbye.
- We, we should go, we really should.
- [Sara] Yes, Glen?
- Baby, come on.
- [Sara] Glen.
- Come on, you want to dance.
- [Sara] Come on, one more drink.
- We have enough time?
- Well do you have room
for another Manhattan?
- Yeah, if she's paying for it.
- I'm paying for it.
- All right, let's go.
- Okay.
- You have cash, right?
- Robert, oh!
You showed up, baby.
You showed up in style, man.
What is this?
- Glen wanted to do it.
- Hello.
- Hey.
- Oh, look at you.
- [Adolfo] How you been?
- Hey, Adolfo.
- Glen,
what's going on man?
- How you doing?
I was not waiting for a cab.
- I can see that.
I can see that, bro.
- Hey Danny, let this guy in.
Party people.
So, what's going on?
- I'm gonna check my purse.
- I'm Sara.
- Hi, Adolfo.
- Adolfo, oh my God.
I've heard so much about you.
- So you're the crazy chick.
- What?
- The incredibly sane chick
who's company I really enjoy.
- Bobby.
What are you telling your friends?
- Are you guys like, hooking up?
- Bobby and me?
- Yeah?
- Oh my God, isn't that cute.
He's not my type.
- He's not my type either.
- Hey, there you are.
- Hey baby.
- Hey Jessie.
- Hey, how's it going big guy?
- [Robert] Good to see you.
- Good to see you too, man.
Oh, we're gonna miss you
when you're in New York.
- [Robert] I know, I'm
gonna miss you guys, too.
Jessie, this is Sara.
- Hi.
- Hi Sara, nice to meet you.
- [Robert] Sara, this is
Jessie, Adolfo's boyfriend.
- Thanks for coming out.
- [Sara] Sure.
- You look great tonight.
So do you by the way.
- [Robert] Oh, thank you.
- Right?
(upbeat dance music)
♪ I'm standing here ♪
♪ Lost in me ♪
♪ This innocence ♪
♪ I will ♪
♪ I will reveal ♪
♪ And if our dreams ♪
♪ Don't seem complete ♪
♪ The feeling I need ♪
♪ Is it good for me ♪
♪ Don't fall asleep ♪
♪ Or think your dreams ♪
♪ Can't compete with reality ♪
♪ Reality ♪
♪ My night's complete ♪
♪ It's pure I mean ♪
♪ The air breathe ♪
(Jenny laughs)
- [Robert] Hey.
- Hey.
You were getting down out there.
I can't wrap my mind around the fact
that you're just not
gonna be here tomorrow.
- [Robert] I'm glad it all worked out.
- Yeah, me too.
So, Sara's cool.
- Mm-hm.
She's a riot.
- [Jenny] She's damn funny.
- Sara's a good friend.
- Good.
- So are you.
- You're a good friend.
You're the best.
- Just wish we had more time.
- For what?
- For everything.
- There you guys are.
My gosh, I was looking all over for you.
I can't believe you left
me alone with Adolfo.
He's crazy, I mean I'm up at the bar
and he was like trying
to give me drinks I
don't like, it was crazy.
This was a great idea, by the way.
I'm really glad we came out tonight.
I canceled my meetings tomorrow morning
so let's just go for it.
You guys want another drink?
- [Jessie] I love your
outfit tonight by the way.
Is this vintage?
- Um, yes it is.
I don't know, I just threw it on.
(phone ringing)
- Is that your, your phone.
- Oh, I don't have a phone.
Oh, it must be Bobby's, hold on.
- You got it?
- Shit, can you hold?
- Yeah yeah yeah, let me take it.
- Sorry.
- No problem.
- Oh, uh.
I gotta take this, sorry.
- [Jessie] Okay.
- Hello?
- What we should do, we should
go wine tasting next week.
My friend Sal owns the winery.
We can stop by his place,
it'll be a lot of fun.
The one with the great big tree.
- Leo called, I talked to him.
- Yeah?
- I think I'm gonna go see him.
Well, off to see Leo.
- So, this is it.
- For now.
I've got something for you.
But, before I give it to you,
you have to promise me that
you're not gonna get mad.
- I promise that I won't be mad at you.
- Pinky swear?
Wait, okay.
We're solid, right?
Okay, here.
I'm sorry.
I needed some leverage,
I didn't know if you were gonna ditch me.
I apologize, Bobby.
(Bobby chuckles)
You said you wouldn't be mad at me.
I'm really glad we met.
I feel like we met for a reason.
I don't know what it is, but,
thank you.
Thank you.
Okay, come here.
I hate goodbyes, I'm gonna go.
- I just gotta ask you something.
- What?
- What's in the box?
- I don't know.
You gotta ask Jeremy.
- Who's Jeremy?
- My husband.
- Stay in touch.
Talk to you later.
- I'm gonna miss you so much.
- [Robert] I'm gonna miss you, too.
(dramatic music)
- Bye.
- [Leo Voiceover] Passing stranger.
You do not know how
longingly I look upon you.
You must be he I was seeking
or she I was seeking.
I have somewhere surely
lived a life of joy with you.
All is recalled as we flit by each other.
Fluid, affectionate, chaste, matured.
You grew up with me,
were a boy with me,
or a girl with me.
I ate with you and I slept with you.
Your body has become not yours only,
nor left my body.
Mine.
Only.
You give me the pleasure of your eyes,
face,
flesh.
As we pass you,
you take my beard,
my breast,
hands.
In return I am not to speak to you,
I am to think of you
and I sit alone, awake.
At night alone.
I am to wait.
I do not doubt that I
am to meet you again.
I am to see to it that I do not lose you.
(people chattering)
- [Attendant] Are you checking
any bags this evening?
- Uh yeah, one.
- That'll be $35 please.
(phone ringing)
- You know what?
Cancel my flight.
- [Attendant] Cancel your flight.
Are you sure?
- I'm sure.
- [Attendant] All right.
Just be aware that cancellation
of all non-refundable tickets
results in $150 administration
fee, plus the difference
between the previously
purchased fare and the new fare.
Can I reschedule your flight to Rochester?
- Actually, I'd like to book a new flight.
- [Attendant] Final destination?
(jet engine roaring)
(whimsical music)