(water running)
(soft music playing)
(snapping beads)
(water continues)
♪ ♪
(dripping)
(snapping)
(sighs)
No! Mommy doesn't do that.
She washes the right ear
before the left.
(snapping beads)
Sorry.
♪ ♪
(steam hissing)
Miles:
Get to bed. (sighs)
Go to sleep.
When's Mommy coming home?
Mommy's in Heaven.
We talked about this.
Selim:
But she'll come home, right?
Like, you go to work
and you come back.
Mom's not coming home.
Selim: Never?
Let's get some rest, okay?
Okay.
Don't forget to
tuck in Ummi.
Okay.
(sighs)
Good night, Selim.
Good night, Ummi.
Love you. (kiss)
♪ ♪
-Miles: Night.
-(light clicks)
(door creaks, shuts)
-(footsteps creak)
-Otis: Hey.
(sighs)
Mrs. Johnson brought by
a casserole.
You should eat.
I'm good. I already ate.
-Come on, you gotta
keep up your strength.
-I'm fine.
I'll eat later.
Alright.
-Night.
-Good night.
(soft music playing)
♪ ♪
(yawns)
(clock ticking)
(muffled alarm)
(alarm blaring)
(alarm stops)
(clicking, ticking)
(bright piano playing)
♪ ♪
(record static)
(toast pops)
♪ ♪
(sighs)
(door opens)
Good morning!
(opens cabinet)
(shuts cabinet)
Morning.
(door shuts)
(puts down spoon)
-Ah. Good, good.
-Selim: Ah.
-(muffled chatter)
-Ow!
-(brushing continues)
-(Selim groans)
(egg timer ticking)
Otis:
You're not helping.
We're gonna be late.
I know.
(shuts door)
(ticking continues)
(steam hissing)
(click)
Hey, hey. Come on, big man.
We got to get going.
-(egg timer rings)
-Oh, see? It's time to go.
Which one you wanna do?
Selim, which one you wanna do?
Hey, hey, we gotta put
the Legos down for a second.
Which one? I like this suit.
Which one you wanna do?
Hey, son!
What you wanna do, son?
We got to get going, baby.
-Uh...
-Hm?
This.
Okay, well-- (sighs)
Alright, well...
(stammers) Okay.
What are you gonna
put the vest on with?
(giggling)
(sighs)
-You sure?
-Mm-hmm!
-You sure.
Okay. Okay. Alright. Alright.
-You sure you don't
want the suit?
-Yeah.
(sighs)
(dog barking outside)
-Hold still.
-(moans)
-(ears ringing)
-(whimpering)
-I need Ummi.
-Miles: Hm?
I need Ummi!
♪ ♪
Okay, go find Ummi,
but come right back
-'cause we almost done. Alright?
-Selim: Okay.
-(rummaging)
-Where'd you put her last?
-Is she in the bed?
-(whimpering)
I can't find Ummi!
Where'd you put
her last, Selim?
(crying)
See-- (sighs)
I don't need this right now,
not right now.
Not right now. Come on.
(sighs)
Selim!
He's wearing that?
-(rummaging)
-Yep.
He can wear
whatever he wants.
-(rummaging)
-(Selim crying)
Son, are you crazy?
People are gonna talk!
-I don't care what
people have to say.
-Yeah?
Well, you should care.
-I don't care what Selim wears.
-(Selim crying)
Boy, this is your wife's
homegoing service.
-Have some respect.
-He's his own person.
-Let him be who he wants to be.
-You can't coddle him forever!
I'm not coddling him, Pop!
Selim does not process things
the same way that we do!
Ah, that's not normal.
♪ ♪
It's not normal.
Stop saying that
he's not normal.
That doll is not normal!
Stop saying that
he's not normal!
-People are not
gonna see autism!
-You think I don't know that?
-Then we gotta teach him
before the world does.
-I'ma teach him.
You can't forever.
-He's only 10.
-He's soft!
Stop saying that he's soft!
(sighs)
Hey, look, uh...
He'll forget all about
that doll real soon.
That doll was the last
thing that she gave him
before she went
in the hospital.
♪ ♪
Did you take Ummi?
(rummaging)
Did you take Ummi, Pop?
-You get your head together.
We can talk about this later.
-(Selim crying)
-(ears ringing)
-(Selim panting)
(gasping)
(heart pounding)
(Selim crying)
(car alarm blaring)
(alarm stops)
Breathe.
Breathe, breathe, breathe.
-Who created the traffic light?
-Garrett Morgan.
Good. Good, breathe.
Breathe with me,
breathe with me.
Okay. Okay.
-Who created the curling press?
-Madam CJ Walker.
Okay, good. Good.
What about the filament?
-Lewis Latimer.
-Good.
-(patting back)
♪ ♪
Good, good... Alright.
-Miles: Come here.
-(Selim groans)
(heavy breathing continues)
♪ ♪
(sniffs)
(sniffing, crying softly)
(inhales, exhales)
(heavy breathing)
(inhales)
(deep breathing)
(breathing continues)
-(patting)
-Yeah. Hey.
Come here.
-(gasps)
-Come here, come here,
come here, come here.
-(slapping)
-(deep breathing)
-(Miles sobbing)
-Mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
(sobbing)
(gasping)
(sniffling)
(sniffs)
(loud sigh)
(sighs)
(groaning)
(sniffling)
(sniffles)
-(panting)
-(closes closet)
(patting)
(sniffs, sighs)
(claps)
(snapping)
-Hey, big guy.
-(snapping beads)
-Hey.
-(snapping)
You ready to go?
Yeah.
(soft piano playing)
♪ ♪
(inhales)
(inhales, exhales)
(door shuts)
♪ ♪