Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
The hardest part of
the lockdown for me was...
just being...
you know, before the lockdown,
everything was free,
like I could leave my house,
I could do whatever I wanted.
I was looking forward
to everything
we were gonna do
with the band.
Like, I was in the middle of
a show for
my high school musical.
Just one month ago,
I was out in San Diego
with my friends
and we were having
a really good time.
And then one month later,
everything's
locked down and then
the whole world's going crazy
and I don't know what to do.
My friends
are literally my life.
And when that happened,
I felt very, very alone.
I definitely felt very lonely.
I definitely felt lonely.
It kind of felt like...
the world was telling you that
you couldn't live your life.
Being a high schooler,
friends is all of
your high school
and so not having
their support,
you feel very alone.
[sirens wailing]
[reporter]
Tonight, there's concern
as COVID cases rise
in nearly half the country.
[second reporter] We turn now
to the Coronavirus pandemic.
There are new concerns about
another surge in infections.
The number of cases in the US
is nearing 30 million
and the death toll
has topped 545,000.
And for
the first time in weeks,
the CDC's national
ensemble forecast
is predicting deaths
will not decline.
[man] In L.A. County
for teachers and for students,
just how best to respond to
the Coronavirus outbreak.
L.A. County public schools
announcing that they
will be shutting down,
effective Monday.
How that's going
to play out with
the hundreds
of thousands of students,
we don't yet know right now.
♪
[coughing]
- [boy] Mom?
- Um...
Yeah, I just don't think
it's gonna be possible.
- Mom?
- Well, I'll talk to Jesse,
see what's happening
with her schedule.
♪
[mellow music]
[people chatting]
- Bye, Mom.
- Bye.
- Hi.
- Hi! Like the car?
[girl with hat]
Yeah, I like it.
Careful, Brielle.
Have you been practicing
singing all summer?
- A little bit.
- Just a little bit?
My siblings get pissed at me
when I sing too loud.
Oh. That's what
I love about your voice.
- Thanks.
- Yes.
- It's very loud.
- It's a strong voice, for sure.
- I'm excited to see everyone.
- Me too.
I missed all of you so much.
Well, why don't you get
started with warm ups
- and I'll see you soon, okay?
- Okay.
[all chatting]
- I gotta hop on that.
- Do your thing, do your thing!
It's been so long.
Warm! Oh, it's warm.
[beatboxing]
Eh! Eh! Eh!
♪ Where's Mary? ♪
♪ She's still looking
for her lamb ♪
♪ I know she's my teacher,
but I would, hot damn ♪
♪ I'mma pass the mic
to my main man, Sam ♪
♪ Let him lay the plans ♪
♪ My name is Sam,
and I'm the man ♪
And, that is how
you ruin a mic, Sam.
I need to see the following
students after class,
Kerry Dason,
Lawrence Bender and Amy Shore.
- Ooh!
- Don't worry, it's good news..
- So, who wants to go first?
- I'll go first.
Okay.
Did you work on your song?
It's a little bit rough.
That's okay. Let's hear it.
So when are we getting
a real music teacher?
Are we going to get
one eventually?
Sorry to disappoint you, Gary,
but you're stuck with me
for now. I'm still looking.
♪ When I close my eyes ♪
♪ I can see her smiling ♪
♪ In the middle of the night,
she whispers to me ♪
♪ In the candle light
she's dancing ♪
♪ And holds me in her arms ♪
♪ I close my eyes
to find her ♪
♪ She's everything ♪
♪ To me ♪
[cheering]
That's great.
Do we have a second verse?
Not yet. We're still trying
to figure out who's story.
Yeah.
Basically, the idea is that
the queen's song inspires
the kids of the forest.
Kids of the forest?
Yes, that is what we are
calling our lovely dancers.
Okay.
The queen is under
some sort of spell,
but she needs to break
out of it,
but we don't really
know how yet.
Maybe it's love.
That could be it.
Well, work on the story first
and then come back
- to the music later, okay?
- Oh, Mary,
are we doing this
the night of prom?
Yes, if I can find you
a teacher by then,
that is the plan.
Okay? I'm gonna go work
with strings
and I will see you all
after lunch.
- Thank you.
- Thank you, Mary!
Do you want to work on
the story at lunch?
- Me?
- And Amy.
Sure.
- You going to the pier?
- Yeah.
- See you there.
- Let's go.
Bye.
Ooh, you going to the pier?
- Nate just asked you out.
- Shut up!
[knocking]
Hey, we were
gonna go work during lunch,
is it okay if we do this later?
Kim Lacey saw you at
the last showcase.
Kim Lacey?
What did she say?
She's interested in
representing you.
She's bringing the head of
the agency to see you
- in the next showcase.
- Wow.
You worked hard for this.
You deserve it.
We don't even have
a music teacher,
is there going to be someone
to help us with this?
Don't even worry about that.
I will find you a music teacher
and in the meantime,
- I'm here for you.
- Okay.
Okay.
Mary?
This is gonna be a good
opportunity for all of us,
like, we're all
gonna be performing
- at the showcase, right?
- Yeah, sure it is.
Do me a favor,
don't tell anybody about this.
I understand.
But this is your time to shine.
You can't take
everybody with you.
- Okay.
- Get out here.
Bye.
- Sup, guys?
- Hey, Matt. How you doing?
How you doing, bro?
You know, she was trying
to help you, right?
- Who was?
- Brielle.
- With what?
- With Amy!
She brought up prom
so you could take Amy to prom.
No, she wasn't.
You gotta learn to read
between the lines, man.
- Brielle's smart like that.
- She's hot, too.
Dude, I'm actually
scared of her.
She's crazy! She's a crazy hot.
She's hot.
But she might stab you.
Crazy hots are my thing, man.
She's coming.
Okay, put that shit away, man.
Okay, forget it.
Let's smoke it over there.
- Don't.
- Look, relax.
Do me a favor,
just don't leave, man.
I got you, man.
Hey, Gary, come here.
I wanna tell you something.
What is it? Is it good?
Is it good? Is it bad?
Is it something about me?
- Gary?
- Be right back, okay?
Have fun.
- Hey.
- Oh, hey.
What's up?
Uh, not much. Um...
Um...
Are you hungry? I'm hungry.
Oh, but it's kind of pricey.
Maybe we can grab,
like, a hot dog.
I don't eat hot dogs.
Oh, uh...
Maybe... I think there's
a pizza place nearby.
Hey, it's okay,
I'm not hungry.
Oh, um...
So what were you thinking?
About what?
The story... that we're
writing.
Oh, right, the queen story,
- Right.
- Yeah, uh...
I think we make it
like more romantic.
Really?
Yeah, I wrote this song.
It's not done yet.
It kind of reminds me of you.
But if you want to hear it,
we can...
Sure.
Okay.
- You have headphones?
- Yeah, uh...
- this one's mine.
- Those are weird headphones.
This one's yours.
[gentle piano music]
- Just simple ballad.
- I can see what you mean.
- Could be a duet, too.
- Yeah.
- So you get the idea, right?
- Yeah, kind of.
So like in general, what do
you think that she wants?
Uh...
She wants...
friendship, uh...
romance.
What else?
I guess someone...
she can trust.
Okay.
Someone she can share
her secrets with.
I like that.
Maybe we should hear it again.
Yeah. Yeah.
Cool. Good idea.
[slow rock instrumental]
♪
Like a motif.
- Yes!
- It keeps coming back.
Yeah, I like that part a lot.
[indiscernible chatting]
- [giggling]
- So did you guys do anything?
No.
You just sat there listening
to music the whole time?
Mh-mm.
I mean, at least
a couple of hours.
And then we realized it
was already dark.
You are so in love.
It is disgusting.
I'm not in love.
I just like him, okay?
You know you used to hate him
because he ignored you.
He's not ignoring me now.
Did he ask you
to be his girlfriend?
No.
But he's coming over tonight.
What? What am I supposed to do?
We're just going
to listen to music.
I invited Gary too.
[soft rock music]
[Nate] Gary, get ready, we're
going to go to Amy's house.
- [knocking on door]
- [man] Gary.
Gary, why is this door locked?
Open the fucking door!
What are you doing?
Yes, you say that shit
every time!
- Piece of shit!
- Get the fuck away from that!
- [fighting]
- You piece of shit!
I'm gonna kick
the fuck out of you.
[Gary] I didn't mean to!
[man] Yeah, you say
that shit every time.
Get up!
Get up, you fucking waste
of piece of shit!
[dramatic music]
[laughing]
[indiscernible chatter]
- This is it?
- Yeah.
- You ready?
- Uh-huh.
This is gonna
change everything.
- No pressure.
- Come on. Let's do it.
Go.
[knocking on door]
- Hey.
- [Nate] Hey.
What happened last night?
I'm sorry about that, I...
fell asleep.
What are you guys doing?
Oh, we're, uh,
we're going to skate park.
Do you want to come with?
I can't.
My mom's not feeling too well.
Oh damn, I'm sorry about that.
- I hope she feels better.
- Thanks.
Okay, then I'll, um...
see you Monday.
Yeah.
- Yeah.
- Have fun.
Hey, Amy? Um...
do you want to go to prom?
I am going.
Yeah, but, like, with me?
Like, as your date?
Yeah, kind of, I guess.
Well, actually, the girls were
all planning on going together.
You'd rather go
with them than with me?
Yeah, kinda...
I guess.
Are you mad about something?
It's just the way
that you say things.
It's not clear.
Like the way that you're
writing the queen in the play.
Does she want friendship
or romance?
It's not clear,
and if it's not clear,
she's going to get frustrated
and confused, so...
All right, um, how about this?
I want you to be
my date at the prom.
And I want you to be
my girlfriend too.
[giggling]
- Is she crying?
- No, she's laughing.
That's not good.
[upbeat music]
♪ She could've been mine,
but now she's gone ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ She left me on read,
and don't answer my calls ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Why must
she treat me this way ♪
♪ Oh ♪ ♪ I'll take the pain
♪ If you promise,
love, you will stay ♪
♪ Is there anyone
who knows my pain ♪
♪ When the one you love
just walks away ♪
♪ And you see the hurt
she puts me through ♪
♪ I'm the one who's down,
who's feeling blue ♪
That was such a dumb idea.
- What happened?
- She said she'd think about it.
What's wrong with that?
If she has to think about it,
then it's a no.
- Not necessarily.
- Let's just go, man.
All right.
Let's get out of here.
♪ I'm shouting at
your door ♪
♪ My love for you
just grows ♪
♪ But all you say is no ♪
♪ So I guess that
I'll just go ♪
♪ I didn't know
what else to say ♪
♪ I was hoping for
an answer today ♪
♪ I've painted a picture
she brushed it away ♪
♪ I'm a Picasso,
she's Monet ♪
[laughing]
I still can't believe
you did that.
It was your idea.
I told you to ask her to prom,
not ask her to marry you.
I don't know, man,
it just came out like that.
It was weird.
This is so complicated.
Life is hard, man.
You gotta get used to it.
Came by your house last night.
What time?
Right around the time
your dad was losing his shit.
I'm gonna head out.
It's getting late.
Hold up, man.
Thanks.
[reporter on radio]
The pandemic is far from over.
New Coronavirus infections are
on the rise across the nation.
Mask mandates are returning
in some places and city...
What's wrong?
You're just like your father.
You ball everything up inside.
What is it?
Nothing, I told you.
Just this...
girl I'm thinking of.
Of course you are.
You're a young man,
you're tempted by
the sharmutas.
Sharmutas, I...
don't think she's a sharmuta.
Whatever that is.
Is she pretty?
Yeah, she's pretty.
She can skate too,
better than Gary.
And when a day goes by
where you can't see her...
you feel it, don't you?
Totally.
[phone buzzing]
- Hey.
Did you think about
what I said?
What's that?
About being my girlfriend.
You were being serious?
You thought I was joking?
[Amy] You're always joking.
I'm not, I'm serious.
Really?
So what do you think?
I'll let you know
when I see you at school.
On Monday.
[Nate]
Give me a hint. Come on.
Nope.
Fine.
[gentle guitar music]
Um...
Okay, I'm just gonna
call, I guess.
- Yeah, you gotta call them.
- I... I am.
Hi, it's Brielle.
Um, the front gate's closed.
Oh, okay, thank you.
They are going
to send someone out.
You look worried, man.
- No, I'm not.
- About what?
Nothing.
Tell me.
Nate's getting married.
What are you talking about?
He proposed to Amy, and she's
officially accepting today.
- You asked her out?
- Yeah.
Oh no, no, no.
He didn't just ask her out.
He went up on her front porch
and announced, "Amy,
"darling, I want you to be
my girlfriend."
[laughing]
And she didn't answer?
Well, she wanted to wait
to do it in person.
[Brielle]
But she was in person.
Well, you know Amy,
she wants to, like,
think things through.
Why are you guys
looking at me like that?
Okay, well, if she says yes,
then you have to kiss her.
- Yeah.
- Yes.
A first kiss says everything.
Stop! Stop!
- Hi.
- Good morning.
I'm really sorry we didn't
get the word out sooner,
but there's no school today.
The staff is meeting about
how to handle this new...
- virus thing.
- Are you serious?
They might need to close for
a while to keep you guys safe.
So what are we supposed to do?
My mom's at work.
Where am I supposed to go?
Yeah, I know, it's a mess.
They'll send out an email
to your parents later today.
I'm really sorry.
How long do you think it'll be?
They say a couple of weeks,
not more than a month.
A month?
Wow, um...
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
♪ It's only a week, dear,
it won't go on for long ♪
♪ It's only a week, dear
Forgive me if I'm wrong ♪
♪ The time will come and go ♪
♪ It'll be over
before you know ♪
♪ Close your eyes
and sing with me ♪
♪ They'll lock us down,
but our spirit's free ♪
♪ It's only a month, dear,
it won't go on for long ♪
forgive me if I'm wrong ♪
♪ You sit alone and wonder why
every day you wanna cry ♪
♪ This is how it's gonna be ♪
♪ Put on a smile
and trust me ♪
♪ It's only a year, dear,
it won't go on for long ♪
♪ It's only a life, dear ♪
♪ Forgive me if I'm wrong ♪
That was beautiful.
And really sad.
Oh, thanks.
The last time
I saw you was where?
At the expo, right?
Yeah, yeah.
Thank you so much
for being here.
- Yeah, of course.
- Yeah,
so I have really good news.
Your test came back negative.
- Yeah.
- Oh!
So, you're hired.
You can start tomorrow.
- Oh, wow.
- Our first class is at 9 am.
I know you must be
a little bit nervous
because you've never worked
with kids before,
and I totally understand.
But you're an amazing musician
and I want you to be really
confident in this role.
Like...
What's wrong?
You're just sitting
on my notebook.
Oh, oh, sorry.
No, no, it's okay.
So here is the schedule
for the rest of the year.
To enter the building,
you'll have
to get tested each week
and we can work around
those dates you mentioned.
Yeah, I'm gonna go see my mom.
Yeah, that's not a problem.
The most important thing
is they have
a really important
showcase coming up.
A major agency is coming
and it should be a big deal,
but I'm having a hard time
getting them excited about it.
Yeah.
Shame.
It must be really hard
for musicians right now, right?
Yeah, that's kind
of why I'm here.
And thank you so much
for being here.
The kids are going through
the same thing.
They've been stuck at home,
literally in lockdown
for months now.
- Mm.
- Yeah.
I'm seeing a bunch
of contact info here.
Everything's on Zoom?
Yes, it means everything
is on Zoom.
Did you not know that?
No, I didn't.
- That'll be interesting.
- Yeah?
Uh, what about
these instruments?
Do they play them still?
Oh no, not anymore, obviously.
You're welcome
to use them, but...
- they won't be here.
- Okay.
Yeah, so grab the sheet and
let's get your paperwork ready.
All right. Let's do this.
So the ninth,
that's when I start?
No, tomorrow.
[reporter]
With the number of positive
COVID tests increasing
dramatically,
government officials have
extended the lockdown orders
for another six
to eight weeks.
Lines continue to grow...
Hey, Gary.
Hey. What are you doing?
Nothing. You?
Nothing.
You wanna play League?
No, I'm trying
to write something
for our new music teacher.
You got that email, right?
Yeah.
It's probably some old fuck
even worse than the last guy.
Not possible.
I mean, what kind of name
is that, Mr. Lars?
Sounds like
a German tuba player.
What I wrote is so dumb.
Let's hear it.
All right, I wrote,
"Almost had a girlfriend.
And then my life ended."
- [laughing]
- I like that. I like that.
It's a crock of shit, bro.
[chuckling]
I'm, like,
losing my mind in here.
All right, man, I'll see you
on Zoom tomorrow.
Catch you later, man. Peace.
Mr. Lars, this is a school.
There's no smoking allowed.
Smoking?
We have security cameras.
[clearing throat]
Thank you.
Sorry.
[scoffing]
It won't happen again.
[mumbling to self]
[playing dramatic melody]
[girl] Good morning, Mr. Lars.
Uh...
[keyboard clacking]
Good morning. Um...
I'm Daryl.
Uh, Mr. Lars, um, Daryl Lars.
I'm your new music teacher.
Um...
What was
that that you just played?
It's just something I'm
writing for somebody special.
For your girlfriend?
Actually, my mom.
Your hair is dope.
Thanks. So, I don't
really know how this Zoom thing
works too well, it's my first
time on here, so bear with me.
Um,
can you guys hear me okay?
Yes.
Maybe we should talk
about our assignment.
It's a great idea.
Um, let's talk about it.
Do you play
anything besides piano?
Yeah, cello,
bass, guitar and violin.
Snooky Young says
real musicians play jazz.
You mean like this?
[playing upbeat jazz tune]
What about classical?
["Prelude in C Major by Bach]
[kids laughing]
♪
Any more questions?
All right,
so let's start this class, um.
Tell me what you guys can do.
- Amy sings.
- Just Amy?
We all sing.
They're just being shy.
'Kay, um, how
about you, um, Stephen?
Uh, I play the piano,
but I suck.
Gary and I
play the guitar.
How long have
you guys been practicing?
Well, I don't
know if you've heard,
but there is this pandemic
going around called COVID,
so we're basically in prison.
Yeah. Can't you see
these bars around us?
I can't take it, let me out!
[all chuckling]
I know the actor is.
Uh, so who can tell me
what this play's about?
It's about this queen
who's trying to find something.
- She's searching for love.
- Whoa we did not agree on that.
Well,
she's searching for something.
Well, if it was love, she would
have said it was love.
[boy] Why is this
so complicated?
Hold on. Uh...
Let's try this, whenever...
whenever I'm confused,
you know, it helps to play.
So, let's try that.
The only way it works,
though, is if you, you know,
sing about something you've
experienced yourself, you know?
- Something real.
- Like what?
Like...
Pain from a breakup or...
when your family member
turns their back on you.
What if it's something
you don't really
wanna talk about?
We all have stuff
like that, um...
You just have to decide if it's
something
you're willing to share.
Uh, let's,
let's just try it, okay?
Um, I'll play something
and you guys just sing
whatever comes to your mind.
Stephen, we'll start with you.
We've never done that before.
That's okay.
Um, just let it flow.
Stephen, we'll start with you.
I got nothing, dude.
Okay, um, I guess I'll start.
♪ I remember laughing ♪
♪ Do you? ♪
♪ I almost had a girlfriend
and then my life ended ♪
♪ When he throws
shade his heart fades ♪
[phone dinging] ♪ When that
attitude seems a little... ♪
[voices echoing]
[tonal beeping]
Heart attack.
Uh, Mr. Lars?
Uh, I'm sorry, I have to go.
So, we're done?
Yes.
That's it for today.
You guys can go ahead and
email Mary for your assignment,
she'll have them for you.
Uh, I-
I just have to go. I'm sorry.
Okay, bye.
♪ I remember
dancing with you ♪
♪ Had a girlfriend,
had my life ♪
♪ And I remember that too ♪
[vocalizing]
♪ In the moon
shade begins to fade ♪
What do you want?
You texted me.
- You need to call your mother.
- You know what?
You know what,
she needs somebody to take her
- to the fucking doctor.
- She doesn't want to go.
Bro. I'm working two jobs
trying to raise two kids.
Okay, I'll call today.
You need to get
your ass down there.
Okay, I'll try again.
Okay? But I work too, Sheila.
Smoking weed
and playing music is not work.
Do you want her
to end up like your father?
- Is that what you want?
- Don't do that.
You know what?
Go see your mother.
[sighing]
[kettle clanging]
[reporter] With the number
of infections rising,
the CDC is recommending
that families avoid large
gatherings during
the holiday season.
For more on this,
let's go to Dana in Washington.
♪ Don't you know
this world is evil, child ♪
♪ Your mother will
protect you for a while ♪
♪ Don't leave me now ♪
♪ You're walking out,
your mother's here ♪
♪ Don't turn her down ♪
Okay, okay.
Not in my house, no!
Get the fuck out of here!
♪ Don't turn me down,
don't leave me now ♪
♪ You're walking out! ♪
♪ Your mother's here,
don't turn me down ♪
♪ Don't leave me now,
you're walking out ♪
♪ Your mother's here,
don't turn me down ♪
[vocalizing]
♪ Won't you stay with
mother for the holidays ♪
[computer chiming]
[beat thrumming]
[computer dinging]
[footsteps]
Hey, Daryl,
your next class is tomorrow.
Yeah, I know.
I needed to talk to you.
Okay.
How'd it go yesterday?
Not great.
Why, what happened?
I just don't think
they're really happy, Mary.
Did someone say
something to you?
No. Not exactly.
Okay, well, we're all going
through a tough time right now.
We just need to let
them know that it's okay.
Tell them
everything's going to be fine.
Oh, we could do some
morning warm ups with them.
Get the blood flowing.
Some exercises,
maybe some jumping jacks.
Jumping jacks?
It's your first day.
Just give it some time.
Look, Mary, I'm not
a teacher, I'm a musician.
So what are
you saying, are you quitting?
I'm sorry.
Okay.
[intense music]
[chanting]
Black Lives Matter!
- Truth or dare?
- Dare.
I dare you
to take off your pants
and jump up
and down in your underwear.
Okay.
- This is for you.
- Gary.
[chuckling]
[laughing]
God, Gary, put some pants on!
Oh my God. Oh my God!
Put your pants on, man.
Okay, Brielle.
- Truth or dare?
- Truth.
If you could trust
anyone in our class, 100%,
- who would that be?
- Anyone in our class?
Yeah.
- Mr. Lars.
- You just met the guy.
There's something about him.
I kind of know
what she means, though.
I mean, for
the first time in a long time,
I'm actually looking
forward to music class.
And guess who he plays with?
- Do you guys have any idea?
- Who?
I saw him online
jamming with... Phantasm.
- Oh, nice!
- They have a show tonight.
- Nate, truth or dare?
- Dare.
I dare you to sneak out
and come see Mr. Lars tonight.
- What time?
- I'll pick you up at 10.
♪
[door clicking]
[laughing]
Oh, my God. Oh, she's calling.
- Hold on. Hey, you coming?
- Amy!
She can hear.
- Oh shit, that's crazy.
Is she okay?
Are you okay?
Um, totally, well,
just, just please let me know
if you need anything, okay?
I'm here for you.
Okay.
Text me. Bye.
- She's not coming.
- Why not?
Her mom has COVID.
- What?
- Wh-What about her?
Like, is she okay? Is Amy good?
Uh, she just texted me.
She says she feels fine.
Does she need anything?
She said to go on without her.
Hey!
You guys go on without me.
All right?
I'll catch up later.
- Hey! Nate.
- Hey! Nate! Hey!
Nate!
Here you go.
[phone buzzing]
I'll be right back, okay?
What?
[Nate]
Hey, Amy, I'm here.
I told you, I can't.
[Nate]
No. Come to your back door.
What? Why?
Just come look.
[soft music]
[chuckling]
Nate?
You're going to get in trouble.
I just needed
to make sure you're okay.
I just, just wanted to see you.
I can't come out.
I need you to understand that.
I know. I just wish
there was something I could do.
Can you make all this go away?
I wish.
Me too.
You know, every night,
I wake up hoping that
this was all just a bad dream.
And everything's
going to go back to normal.
♪
♪ Can we find a place
Where everything is better? ♪
♪ A little place where
Everything's all right ♪
♪ If I could find
A star and wish her dream ♪
♪ Will let her ♪
♪ Let her dream come true
And heal the world tonight ♪
♪ Can we break the spell,
And find a way together ♪
♪ With a simple kiss
And all the love we feel ♪
♪ Can we spread our love
And stop the pain forever ♪
♪ And find a way
for everyone to heal ♪
♪ I would take you there ♪
♪ If I could find a way ♪
♪ A place
where we could share ♪
♪ To make this go away ♪
♪ I would hold your hand ♪
♪ The pain would disappear ♪
♪ Our love will take a stand ♪
♪ Nothing more to fear ♪
♪ Can we find a place
Where everything is better ♪
♪ I want to believe
It's true ♪
♪ If I could find a star, Wish
her dreams would let her ♪
♪ I think I do love you,
Our love could be the start ♪
♪ Can we spread our love? ♪
♪ Can we stop
the pain forever? ♪
♪ Forever ♪
[dramatic vocalizing]
♪
[techno music playing]
[engine rumbling]
Let's do this.
- We are 21.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Mr. Lars?
What are you guys doing here?
- We just wanted to apologize.
- For what?
Well, we weren't exactly the
nicest to you the other day so-
And you came all
this way to tell me that?
You guys want tickets
to this show, don't you?
- Yeah.
- Can you get us in?
No, you guys aren't
old enough to be here.
Come on, dude,
do you know how long
it's been since we've been
able to even leave the house?
How did you guys even find me?
I follow Phantazm online,
and they posted something
about the DL opening,
and I was like, "Hey, we have
this cool music teacher,
- maybe..."
- Actually, I'm not anymore.
- What?
- Yo, DL, we're up.
Go home, okay.
Hey. Did
you quit on us already?
Look, you guys need
a real music teacher, okay?
And I'm not.
I'm not that,
this is, this is what I do.
Come on, let's go.
Hey, Hey, Gary!
I'm sorry, okay.
I know you messaged me,
but I got a lot going on, bruh.
- Forget about it.
- Is everything okay?
You're not my teacher.
Why do you care?
I do care.
Really? Then why don't you tell
Mary to stop this zoom shit?
I'm sick of being alone.
[club music
playing in background]
[gravel crunching]
[somber music playing]
♪
[vocalists vocalizing]
[electric guitar playing]
♪ Reaching out,
and you wanna shout ♪
♪ who's going to save us now ♪
♪ Want you to save us,
Save us now ♪
♪ Feel low, fear has grown,
Who's gonna save us now ♪
♪ Who's gonna save us now? ♪
♪ I'm reaching out,
It's the end of the line ♪
♪ I give it all
and I wasted time ♪
♪ Why won't you save me now ♪
♪ Please won't
you save me now ♪
♪ I want you to save me,
I need you to save me ♪
♪ Oh, won't you save me now ♪
♪ If I could teach
my lungs to breathe ♪
♪ I'd have
the keys to wake me up ♪
♪ Cause I don't
want to be home again ♪
♪ I once was,
get a hit again, no ♪
♪ If I could teach
my lungs to breathe ♪
♪ I'd have
the keys to wake up ♪
♪ Just find
a way to be whole again ♪
♪ I once was,
to be whole again, oh ♪
[guitar solo playing]
♪
♪ Please won't
you save me now ♪
♪ I want you to save me now ♪
♪ I need you to save me now ♪
♪ Oh, won't you save me now ♪
♪ I want you to save me,
I need you to save me, ♪
♪ Oh won't you save me now ♪
♪ I've got
to just save us now ♪
[guitar screeching]
I, I love these kids.
It's my entire life.
And if the school closes,
it's, I don't know what,
um, what they're going to do.
I'm, I'm not
wanting to walk away.
Our music teacher is gone.
[door knocking]
Umm, one second.
Do you still need a teacher?
I'll call you back.
[phone docking]
Yeah,
I do still need a teacher.
But I need one that's
not going to quit on me again.
I'm sorry about that.
Could you do me a favor?
Please sit down
and talk with these kids.
Okay. Well.
They are waiting
for a teacher right now.
Oh.
So I'm back?
Thank you, Mary.
[door closing]
[exhaling]
[kids cheering]
Welcome back, DL.
Thanks, guys,
but it's Mr. Larson here.
Told you he'd be back.
Did you talk to Mary?
Yeah, I did.
When are we coming back?
She didn't say, um, but,
you know, I did talk to her
and I told her to-
No, man tell her, we need this.
She said she would email
you guys and reach out to you
and you know, you guys could
tell her how you're feeling.
Give her some time.
We're out of time.
Maybe we should
all send her an email.
- Maybe.
- This is fucking bullshit!
Sorry. Gary's got some issues.
We've all got issues.
Guys, just drop it.
Look, I know you guys
are going through a lot. So.
I have an idea.
I'm going to log
on to Zoom every evening,
and you guys can come in,
you don't have to say anything,
you just tune in
and I'll be there, playing.
So you don't have
to be alone anymore.
Thank you, Mr. Lars.
How about we get
some work done today?
Yeah, who wants to sing first?
♪ I feel like I'm breaking ♪
♪ And there's
nothing left to do ♪
♪ Drowning from the inside ♪
♪ No one's got a clue ♪
♪ I push it down ♪
♪ I'll figure it out like
I always do, sweeping it up ♪
♪ And covering up,
bruises black and blue ♪
♪ What's a life
if you're not living? ♪
♪ How is it
that no one's winning? ♪
♪ I'm giving all I can ♪
♪ Where's the hope
if there's no tomorrow? ♪
♪ Will we make it, fuck if
I know I've given all I can ♪
♪ Til I can't sta-aa-aa-nd ♪
♪ I can't sta-aa-aa-nd ♪
♪ I can't sta... ♪
[Nate]
Do I have to wear this?
No, it's fine,
we're both negative.
If I ask you any questions
that make you feel
uncomfortable,
you don't have to answer, okay?
Okay.
Overall, how does
learning online compare
to being in the classroom?
Online learning is, um...
presents some challenges.
Um,
it makes it difficult.
You can be honest.
It sucks, I hate it.
Do you feel like
you're learning anything?
No, not really,
I mean, new guy, Lars,
he's great but like
so much he can do, right?
What are the biggest changes
that you see in yourself?
Changes.
I'm losing my mind.
I'm losing pieces.
Because you guys don't get it.
You don't.
[scoffing]
We've been stuck at my house,
I'm staring at a screen
for three fucking hours a day.
Like, it's... I don't see
my friends anymore.
I, I have been locked
in this, just, like house.
Everybody
is just continuing on.
Life continues
and just my life has stopped
and I can't even see
Amy because she's, she's,
I might never even see
her again because she's,
- Because what?
- Because she's sick.
- Because her mom's sick.
- Oh...
No, I don't
want to fucking hug!
I don't want a hug.
I don't want you to
tell me it's going to be okay.
I'm sick of all of you just
saying it's gonna be okay,
because it's not!
You need to fix this right now,
because I can't see my friends.
My, my uncle's
going out every night
and his life continues?
It's okay,
but ours has to stop right now?
I'm done with it, I need
my friends, they need me,
so we can just
share what's going on.
I'm here, I'm listening.
Of course.
I know, I know you are, I-
[heavy breathing]
I appreciate it.
It's just not the same.
There are things
we say to each other
that we would never say to you.
There's a whole other world.
Our world.
That we don't share,
because it's ours.
When you take
away my friends,
it's the end of our world.
It's not okay, it's not.
[shaky breathing]
I'm - I'm sorry.
[tender piano playing]
[shaky breathing]
♪
It's absolutely fine.
[Nate]
You sure?
- Yeah, of course.
- Okay.
Yeah, it's going to be great.
So Nate wants
a little help with something.
Yeah, Mary said
you need help with the song.
- Mm hmm.
- Okay, I'll leave you to it.
Go ahead and have a seat, Nate.
So you want
to work on a project?
Yeah, I wrote a, a song for
Amy.
I thought it would be cool.
She's sick, you know.
Amy's going to be okay, Nate.
But I, I think writing
a song is a great idea.
What do you want it to say?
That I really like her.
[chuckles]
I think she knows that.
[Daryl]
Yeah, I think so, too.
So what else do
you want it to say?
I wish I could help her
and her mom
and I know it sounds stupid,
but they save them, you know?
I wrote the song
and played it for her
and she really liked it.
I played it over and over.
Sounds like it could be a duet.
Yeah, that's what I thought.
I miss her so much.
There's so many
things I want to say, but...
so hard to talk to
her when she's around.
How about you guys do this
as a duet for the showcase?
Yeah, but we
can't record anything
because we're all
stuck at home.
I'll record it.
You just write down
what you're feeling,
but I'll put it up tonight.
- Sounds good?
- Yeah.
All right, let's practice this.
What do you,
what do you want to say?
Something like...
♪ Staring at the skylight,
Writings on the wall ♪
♪ Oh, you look so beautiful ♪
Yeah, something like that.
♪ Shouting from the skylight ♪
♪ Write it on the wall ♪
♪ I love you dear,
Do you care for me at all? ♪
♪ We can be together,
As long as you stay true ♪
♪ I'm yours forevermore ♪
♪ Baby doll,
will you be mine too? ♪
♪ Everything is different,
Now that you're not here ♪
♪ I'm looking
to the skies above ♪
♪ To see if
I can find you there ♪
♪ Maybe in a dream,
You'll come back to me ♪
♪ I'll leave the light on
So that you can see that ♪
♪ This love can only work
If we're working ♪
♪ And I'll work the night
And day through ♪
♪ This love, It takes
two to stay together ♪
♪ And baby all I want is you ♪
♪ Oh, this love ♪
♪ Oh, oh, this love ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ This love ♪
Hi.
- Thank you, honey.
- Yeah.
What did the doctor say?
Well, my fever's gone,
and but he thinks we still need
to remain in
isolation for a couple of days.
I'll be in my room
if you need anything.
- I love you.
Oh, my God.
What's wrong? Honey?
[phone vibrating]
Shit!
♪ I guess I don't belong,
I guess I'm not the one ♪
♪ I hide away from me ♪
♪ I'm not the man you see ♪
♪ So I'll be moving on,
You'll miss me when I'm gone ♪
♪ And I'm the lonely one,
Lost without a gun ♪
♪ I hate the man I see
Trapped deep inside of me ♪
♪ Why can't I
shake this pain? ♪
♪ A bullet in my brain ♪
♪ Free me from this pain ♪
♪ I'm so ashamed ♪
♪ I'm so ashamed,
I'm so ashamed ♪
The reason I asked you here is
because Gary's mother
called me and said
that he snuck out of the house
to meet you at a nightclub.
Yeah, a few of
the kids came to see me.
But I didn't invite them there.
How did they know you
were going to be there?
I was performing
with this band, Fantazm.
Uh, it kind of sounds
like you're trying to like,
accuse me of something.
Gary's mother sent this to us.
What is this?
[Mary] It's a note from Gary.
He attempted suicide
last night.
You know,
you talked me into this.
♪ I cry to you ♪
♪ I sing to you ♪
♪ I love you ♪
[knocking on door]
[man outside door]
Gary, what the fuck?
Why is this door locked?
♪ I live for you ♪
♪ Oh Lord, my light ♪
♪ You know my heart ♪
♪ Savior of grace ♪
[coughing]
♪ I call to you ♪
[woman on phone]
Mom is not okay.
You need to go
over there right now.
♪ I need you ♪
♪ Oh Lord, my love ♪
♪ I want my heart ♪
♪ I want my love ♪
♪ I need you ♪
♪ You're all I need ♪
Eddy!
- Hey.
- How is he?
He's getting better now,
He looks all right.
Here comes Amy.
How are you doing?
Finally out of quarantine.
Just in time.
Is he okay?
He's stable now.
It's so fucked up
that this is what it took
to get us all back together.
Not anymore.
Yeah,
fuck this quarantine shit.
We need each other.
Yeah.
Looks like he needs a hug.
Let's go give him one
Door's locked.
Brielle, what are you doing?
Crazy, huh.
[door unlocking]
[Brielle sobbing and sniffling]
Am I in heaven
or is Brielle in my bed?
You wish.
Everyone here?
Okay, so I understand it's been
a really tough
past couple of months,
not to mention a really
tough past couple of days.
And I just want to make sure
that you kids do not lose sight
of this performance
that's coming up.
You have worked way
too hard and way too long,
and you are far too
talented to get distracted.
And I know that
it's going to be amazing.
[student] It won't
be the same without him.
I know.
And I don't
think there's anything I can do
to get him back.
[phone vibrating]
No, nothing. I can't find
anything on him online at all.
He doesn't have
any shows listed.
I know, okay, I'll
call you if I find anything.
[Nate]
I don't know, Gary.
Brielle can't find him,
and we went to his house
and he's not there.
[Gary]
We'll figure it out, okay?
All right, bro.
I'll talk to you later.
[faint piano playing]
Mr. Lars?
Mr. Lars, is that you?
- [Daryl] Hey, Nate.
- Oh, my God. Mr. Lars,
we've been looking for you
everywhere, are you okay?
[Daryl] I'm, I'm not okay.
I lost my mom, Nate.
♪ Days turning into months,
Watch my life go slipping by ♪
♪ She stays inside my dreams ♪
♪ Sit alone at night
And wonder why ♪
♪ Will she return to me? ♪
♪ She was never really mine ♪
♪ But soon we'll see ♪
♪ Feels like I'm suffocating ♪
♪ She's all I really want
And I want her back ♪
♪ Give my love back to me ♪
♪ Give my love,
Give my love back to me ♪
♪ Give my love back to me ♪
♪ Deep inside my soul ♪
♪ You'll always remain
As the days go by ♪
♪ Its crazy, but I love you ♪
♪ Cross my heart
That you love me, too ♪
♪ Love me, 'cause I don't want
To be lonely, no, no, no ♪
♪ Love me, love me ♪
♪ Try to do my part ♪
♪ To keep my head up,
I play extra hard ♪
♪ It's something weak
To feel so low ♪
♪ I'll be good,
But I feel this loss ♪
♪ I feel their loss
And we feel lost ♪
♪ When I see your light
At the end of this ♪
♪ I just don't,
Just don't, just don't know ♪
♪ When your riding in the
middle and dark for a little ♪
♪ We try to keep perspective
In the dark ♪
♪ When it feels like a riddle,
Ruthless and civil ♪
♪ We try to see the future,
But it's hard ♪
♪ See in the dark ♪
[Nate]
Isolation and loneliness,
it's not a solution.
Something has to change.
Our friend almost died, Mary.
You can't just lock us away
anymore. We need each other.
At some point, we all have
a decision to make.
In light of recent events
and after a lot
of careful consideration,
we have decided it's time
to bring all
of our kids back to school.
Effective immediately,
I'll see you all here soon.
- Kim, hey, hey.
- Hey, it's good to see you.
Good to see you.
So good to see you.
This is Mark.
Oh, I've heard
so much about you.
- Good to see you.
So happy to be here.
Yes, I'm so
happy that you're here.
We will not disappoint.
Amy is so talented and she's
worked really, really hard.
We're really
interested in signing her.
What is she singing today?
Middle of the Night. It's
the one that you heard before.
You can sit right here.
- Thank you.
Hello and thank you for coming.
The performances this
evening are from a play
written by the students.
We hope that you enjoy.
Okay, come in.
♪ When I close my eyes ♪
♪ I can see her smiling ♪
♪ In the middle of the night ♪
♪ She whispers to me ♪
♪ In the candle light,
She stands dancing ♪
Uh, thank you
so much for coming.
I know how big
of an opportunity
this is for all of us, and...
we're so grateful
that you're here but, uh...
there's someone that
really needs us right now.
I'm sorry. Thank you.
Hey, mom.
It's just me, uh.
You know, I tried to call them,
but they blocked me.
And, uh...
I guess I'm all alone now.
I guess it's karma,
cause I left you alone.
And, uh... whoo.
I got you these flowers.
I know you're
going to be with me.
I know you're watching me.
I know you'll stay with me.
[sentimental music swelling]
♪ I believe with the stars
And the moon ♪
♪ You're somewhere out there ♪
♪ Watching over me ♪
♪ Hallelujah, what a dream ♪
♪ I know you're out there,
Watching over me ♪
♪ I see you in my dreams,
I know you're out there ♪
♪ Watching over me ♪
♪ You can say that I believe
I know you're somewhere ♪
♪ Out there,
Watching over me ♪
[car door closing]
You okay?
Yeah.
Aren't you guys are supposed to
be at a showcase or something?
We wanted to dedicate
a song to your mom.
You think
she'd be okay with that?
I think she'd like that.
♪ Watching over me ♪
♪ (I am not alone)
You're watching over me ♪
♪ (You are not alone) Watching
over me, watching over me ♪
♪ (You are not alone)
Watching over me ♪
♪ (You are not alone) Watching
over me, watching over me ♪
♪ (You are not alone)
Watching over me ♪
[waves crashing
and people chatting]
You know what?
I think I'm going to be okay.
We're all going
to be okay, man.
2020 was the worst.
We got a pretty dope teacher.
Yeah. Lars is pretty cool.
I love his hair.
[Amy] Same.
I think I should
probably head out.
My dad's starting
therapy today.
Okay, come on.
I'll give you a ride.
Us too?
Nah, y'all can walk,
he needs it.
Oh, come on.
Come on.
I've been waiting
so long for this.
For what?
Well, a year ago, I asked
you to be my girlfriend.
A year ago, I told you I'd
give you your answer in person.
Well, here we are.
Take that as a yes.
♪ Shout it from the skylight,
Write it on the wall ♪
♪ I love you dear,
Do you care for me at all? ♪
♪ We can be together
As long as you stay true ♪
♪ I'll be yours forevermore,
Baby doll ♪
♪ You'll be mine too ♪
♪ This love can only work
If we're working ♪
♪ And I'll work
the night and day for you ♪
[announcer]
Ladies and gentlemen, Fantäzm.
[drums and bass instrumental]
♪
Thank you,
thank you, thank you.
Let's give
a big round of applause
for our special guest
right here,
Mr. Daryl Lars, everybody.
And I know a couple
of you guys tried to come out
and see us
a couple of weeks ago.
This show is right here
is for you guys,
the students of Santa Monica
Art school. Let's go!
♪ [inaudible]
That you took away ♪
♪ Away ♪
♪ You let your circumstances
Get the best of you ♪
♪ Yesterday ♪
♪ It's a brand new day,
Sing it with me now ♪
♪ Whoa, whoa ♪
♪ Whoa, oh, oh ♪
♪ Let it out now ♪
♪ Whoa, whoa ♪
♪ Whoa, oh, oh ♪
♪ Yeah, oh ♪
♪ With a little hope ♪
♪ And you're gonna find ♪
♪ That the best in you
Is still inside ♪
♪ Oh, you gotta let it shine ♪
♪ Don't let nothing
Bring you down ♪
♪ Even when
it's hard at times ♪
♪ Sing it with me now ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ I say will you sing? ♪
[vocalizing]
♪
[applause]
[somber rock music]
♪
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
♪