[grand music]
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
[seagulls squawking]
[eerie music]
[water lapping]
[bells chiming]
[eerie string music]
[foreboding music]
[muffled engine rumbling]
[music continues]
[objects clattering]
[banging]
[door closes]
[siren wailing in distance]
[wind blowing]
[seagulls squawking]
[somber music]
[water rushing]
[seagulls squawking]
[cage rattles]
[suspenseful music]
[seagulls squawking]
[music continues]
Hi, Daddy.
When'd you get here?
Just now.
I took the ferry.
[laughing]
- Are you all right?
- Yeah.
[laughs]
[Beth]
He seemed happy to see me.
[Bobby] Don't be stupid.
Where you been?
You know?
It's been a long time,
we were worried about you.
All right, I get it,
I'm an asshole.
Yeah, you are.
[keys jingle]
[Bobby] It's gonna be fine.
[door closes]
Come in.
[cutlery clatters]
[Tom]
Thank you Lord,
for these thy gifts
we're about to receive.
Bless this house,
bless this food
and all that we have.
- Amen.
[Tom] Lily and I talked it over.
You wanna stay, you can stay.
I'm gonna stay with Bobby.
[Tom]
Your brother has a family.
Can't have you
livin' on his couch.
While you're here,
you're gonna pay rent.
We'll figure out something
that makes sense.
Patty could probably get you
some shifts at the restaurant.
[Tom] What d'you say?
- Thanks.
- [cutlery clatters]
[Lily speaks indistinctly]
- Thanks a lot.
- It'll be fine.
He doesn't want me here.
[Bobby] What'd you expect?
Hmm?
You want a fucking parade?
It's been like five years. What don't
you give it a little bit of time?
Thought I did.
Oh, you're funny.
Wait. Can we go somewhere for
a little, me and you?
I can't.
I can't, I gotta put the...
I gotta put the kiddo to bed.
You know she's almost six now.
- Wow.
- Wow, yeah.
[door opens]
[door closes]
[drawer opens]
You didn't change anything.
[Lily] You know how he is.
Is everything all right?
Yeah, fine.
The price is down.
You know that?
Folks who've been doing
this for a long time
are going out of business.
Sorry to hear that.
Things are a little
tight around here.
It'll be fine.
[soft plucked music]
[music continues]
[floor creaks]
- [seagulls squawking]
- [engine rumbling]
[water splashing]
[soft music]
[knocking on door]
Just a minute.
[indistinct chattering]
[coffee pouring]
[coins clatter]
[money notes ruffling]
That's not nice.
I heard you were here.
I thought I'd come say hi.
Beth.
Let's hang out.
Why would I wanna do that?
Because you missed me?
You can say it.
Oh. You're all I thought about.
Oh, I know, I get it.
Wait, Beth.
Can you just top me
off real quick?
You know I thought about
you sometimes.
Mm-hmm.
Laying in bed late at night.
[whispers]
I thought about the first time
I let you put your cock in me.
And then I promised myself I'd
never sink so fucking low again.
- [cup shattering]
- What did you do, Dicky?
Nothing.
You're paying for that.
- I didn't even touch it. It's just a mug.
- Out.
- Walk.
- It was this guy.
- Give her some money.
- [woman] Get out.
[chickens clucking]
[door opens]
[drawer opens]
[drawer closing]
[watch jingles]
[car rumbling]
[car door opens, closes]
[woman] Okay.
You're gonna help your mommy?
- [girl] Um, yeah.
- [car doo shuts]
[Tom] Mm-hm. Yeah, I heard you.
[indistinct chattering]
[Lily] Tom.
[Tom] I got it. I got it.
[Lily]
Did she ask for money?
- [Tom] I got it.
- [Lily] Tom.
Where are you going?
Out.
Go to bed.
What were you guys
talking about?
- You deaf?
- Huh?
[scoffs]
[soft music]
What, you couldn't use
the front door?
Past my curfew.
[laughs]
[water rippling]
[music continues]
[Bobby] We haven't come back
for a month and a half.
This fucking guy, Nance,
he's poaching our traps.
I know it.
You tell the cops?
They're not gonna
fucking do anything
unless we catch him
with a trap in his hand.
So do it.
Wow.
[imitates explosion]
[chuckles]
Why didn't I think of that?
Just go fucking do it.
Living in the city, man, that's...
that's made you pretty smart.
When you go there, you start dressing
different, talking different.
Stop fucking talking
to your family and...
Sounds a wonderful place.
[crickets chirping]
[sighs] You're not drinking?
- Why not?
- Just...
not drinking.
[Bobby]
You gonna tell Pop?
- Something happen to you?
- Like what?
[Bobby] I don't know. Look, it's not
like it's a fucking crazy question.
I mean, you, you know,
you come back...
I needed a break, okay? I don't
know, I didn't know where else to go.
- Are you gonna stick around?
- Jesus.
[Bobby] What? Fuck.
[laughs]
Sorry.
Do you wanna know what happened?
[banging on door]
Everything was great.
And, uh...
then you were born.
You fuck...
[laughs]
Fucking so stupid.
[boat engine rumbling]
[tense music]
[water splashes]
What was that?
[music continues]
[Bobby] Hey.
Wait.
[music continues]
[dramatic music]
What do you think that was?
I don't know.
They're not out here fishing.
[boat engine rumbling]
[dark music]
[car engine roars]
Look, hey, just...
Just give it a chance.
He's different these days.
I've heard that before.
[car door closes]
[Tom]
Do you know what time it is?
Went for a walk.
[Tom] With who?
[Beth] By myself.
[Tom] Come over here.
You been drinking?
[Beth] Why, that illegal?
[Tom] You doing dope?
- No.
- Don't lie to me.
You want me to pee in a cup?
I don't wanna worry about
where you are,
or what you've been doing.
Got it?
- I'm not 15.
- Then stop acting like it.
What do you want from me?
Am I supposed to beg
for your forgiveness?
Oh, for...
You're forgiven.
I absolve you of your sins.
Go to bed.
[water running]
[pills rattling]
[banging on door]
[tense music]
[ominous music]
[water running]
[thunder rumbling]
[thunder crackling]
[indistinct chattering]
[women laughing]
[Beth]
I don't remember anything.
Oh wait, wait,
let me see this one.
[laughs]
Nice outfit.
- Aww.
- [Beth] Morning.
[Anne] She brought donuts.
Cute PJs.
- Mm. There you go.
- [Beth] Oh, wow. Oh, I remember this.
- [laughs]
- [Anne] Dear...
What was that?
You don't want donuts?
Dicky, don't be late
for work again.
[Dicky] Yeah, okay, Ma.
Your mom knowing
you're still selling drugs?
Who told you that?
I ain't selling shit.
No?
Guess I had it all wrong.
Guess so.
Maybe go check with your aunt.
[Beth] Yeah,
what was I thinking?
You're just a loser
who lives with his mother.
Oh, yeah?
What's that make you, huh?
You're living back home,
same as me.
[Anne] Dicky, time to go!
There's nothing about us
that's the same.
Meet me tonight.
- I'm busy.
- Come on, meet me at 11.
You know where.
Why should I?
Because I got something
I wanna show you.
We'll see.
[Anne] Dicky.
Dicky!
- Come on.
- Fuckin' A, Ma!
Coming.
Fucking fish market.
It's not fucking
changing the world.
[engine rumbling]
[cage rattles]
He's hauling our get.
Someone is.
And what, you're just gonna
bend over and take it?
You wanna get on another boat?
Be my guest.
[water rippling]
[dark music]
[car engine rumbling]
[crickets chirping]
[music continues]
[Beth] Dicky?
Dicky?
[scoffs]
Piece of shit.
[car engine roars]
[car door closing]
- [rock music]
- [indistinct chattering]
Hey.
Where you been?
[Beth] Think this is funny?
- Little bit.
- Hey, it's Beth.
Beth, who let you back in?
[Dicky ]She's just visiting.
Hey, Beth, you know what
you ought to do?
- Mm-hmm.
- [man chuckles]
Have a... have a drink.
- Yeah, come on, sit down.
- Go fuck yourself.
[man] Whoa.
So what, you came all this way
just to get a look at me?
You told me to meet you.
No, I told you I had
something to show you.
Whatever.
You see it now?
I don't see shit.
See how you're not so fucking
special after all?
[laughs]
[music continues]
Beth.
Beth!
Come on, fuck.
- Beth!
- They're off.
At the bell, it's Dicky.
Come on, Beth.
I'm just joking around.
Where are you going?
I told you to keep
your fucking mouth shut.
[Dicky] I don't know what the
fuck you're talking about, man.
- [man] Shut up.
- [Dicky] I didn't fucking say anything.
- [man] Listen to me.
- [Dicky] Would you just relax?
- What the fuck is your problem?
- [man] Relax, my asshole.
- [car door closes]
- Beth, wait.
[car engine revs]
[rock music]
- [man speaking indistinctly]
- [Dicky] I don't know.
Maybe somebody fucking else
said some bullshit...
- [Beth] Let's go.
- [man] Listen to me.
[Dicky] Listen, I don't wanna
have to fucking fuck you up.
[car horn blaring]
Mind your own fucking business.
- [blow lands]
- [man] Piece of shit.
- [Dicky grunts]
- [man] Keep your mouth shut.
- [car engine revs]
- [man] Get it?
[moans]
- [punch landing]
- [car engine roars]
[heavy metal music]
[car engine roars]
[music continues]
[Dicky] Still mad at me?
- [laughs]
- [Dicky] Jesus Christ.
[door creaks open]
[Dicky] You can't just show up
at my mom's like that.
[scoffs] She loves me.
Yeah, she used to.
You going to meetings
with your father now?
Yeah.
We're best friends.
I'm getting clean too.
I see that.
You know what I mean.
Just this now.
They piss-test you
at the fish store?
That's just temporary.
What'd that guy want?
Hmm?
You owe him money?
Don't worry about it.
[whispers]
I'm not gonna fuck you.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
Then what'd you bring
me here for?
Saw you on the water last night.
What's in the trap?
[scoffs] What's the matter?
Whatever you think you saw,
you forget it.
Come on. Tell me.
I know you want to.
You know what
your fucking problem is?
You think I'm stupid
but I'm not.
[both chuckle]
Right. Okay, so what do
you want from me?
Nothing.
You obviously can't help, so...
I got married.
Did you know that?
I didn't just
wait around for you.
- Whatever.
- We both know why you're here.
So why don't you just say it?
All right.
I need some money.
Ask you father.
- Fucking great idea...
- [Dicky] No, we both...
Listen, we both know why
you're here, all right?
- Let go of me.
- [Dicky] This hasn't changed...
- [groans]
- There's nothing between us,
there never was and
there never fucking will be.
[Dicky] Okay. Okay.
It's just...
It's fucking weird, okay?
Fuck!
That really hurt.
Fuck! It's just some fucking
weed they bring down from Canada.
And I pick it up and
I drop it on the mainland.
Goddamn it!
[peas crunching]
It's like five,
10 pounds at a time.
It sounds like a lot
of work for weed.
What do you know?
It sells for four grand a pound.
So how come you're still
living at your mom's?
I don't get
a fucking commission.
I'm leaving
by the end of the week.
[Dicky scoffs] Great.
Hmm?
No one said you had to come.
[car engine rumbles]
[man] It's not a loan.
You buy 100 of mine, things turn
around, I'll buy it back.
What am I gonna do with them?
I'm not a...
I'm not a pawn shop.
I got an offer from another guy.
Who?
Nance?
I need the money.
I'm drowning.
You sell out to a guy
from the other side,
I wouldn't expect a lot of
sympathy around here.
What's up, ladies?
You ready to get to work?
[Tom] You're late.
You believe this guy,
Uncle George?
You see him breaking
his fucking back?
- Hey, Bob.
- Hey.
I'll see you around.
What's got him?
Don't worry about it.
[indistinct yelling in distance]
[boat engine rumbling]
[cage rattles]
[soft music]
[girl barking]
What the hell is wrong with her?
[laughs]
Where did you steal those from?
[Dicky] Meet me tonight.
I got something
I wanna show you.
- [Beth] Mm-hmm.
- Come on, for real this time.
[scoffs]
[Dicky] Mr. McManus.
What the hell is he doing here?
He just showed up.
I came to see your daughter.
Make it quick.
- Millie.
- [girl] Hi, Grandpa.
[Dicky speaks indistinctly]
He just showed up.
[chuckles]
He doesn't like you.
I'll see you later.
Doesn't like me.
[Tom] What he want?
I don't know.
Nothing.
[Tom] I want you staying
away from him.
- He's harmless.
- He's a liar and a thief.
Who's a liar?
No one here, honey.
[scoffs]
[soft music]
[wind blowing]
[door rattling]
[Dicky] You're only gonna have like
five minutes between when they drop it
and when we get there
to pick it up.
Won't they hear the motor?
They'll think it's us,
we'll think it's them.
And when the shit's not there,
they'll argue about who's lying.
They're gonna know
it's you that took it.
How?
[Beth] I don't know,
when you disappear.
[Dicky]
I dump jobs all the time.
They didn't hire me
for my resume.
What if they know and
come after you?
[Dicky] It's not the mafia, it's
just some fucking fishermen.
Jesus Christ.
[Dicky] You said you wanted to
get out of here.
It could be like 30, 40 grand.
You don't even know?
It doesn't matter.
Whatever it is, it's just a start.
We'll get moving and
we'll figure it out.
[soft soul music]
You got a better idea?
Hey.
I'm not gonna let
anything happen to you.
♪ The thought makes me
very excited ♪
♪ Like a clean hysteria ♪
♪ My countenance expands
when I see your bitter style ♪
[Dicky]
What are you afraid of?
I'm pregnant.
[music continues]
Whose is it?
[scoffs] Doesn't matter.
I'm not going back.
[Dicky] You keeping it?
♪ Wanna uncover
those brittle red hands ♪
♪ Got a dirty ditch
and a little secret ♪
♪ If you don't rope my wrists
then I just might slip ♪
♪ Bang bang ♪
[Dicky] Okay.
♪ Bang bang bang ♪
Okay, what?
I didn't ask your permission.
Okay, I got you.
Oh, just like that?
Yeah.
Just like that.
♪ Mama told me peace be steel ♪
♪ Heavy metal on my hip
feels so real ♪
[music continues]
[Dicky] Are you sure?
[Beth] Shut up.
♪ In your back trunk,
bang bang ♪
♪ Wanna uncover those
brittle red hands ♪
♪ Got a dirty ditch
and a little secret ♪
♪ If you don't rope my wrists
then I just might slip ♪
[birds chirping]
Oh.
You don't work today?
No.
[bright music]
Well...
What about this?
Cute, right?
Is this fun?
Yep.
[hangers rattle]
[Hilde] I heard it,
but I didn't believe it.
You're back and
you don't come see me?
- Sorry, I meant to.
- [laughs]
[Hilde] Oh, you look great.
You shouldn't hide
under all this.
- It's cold.
- Well, look who got soft out there, huh?
- How you doing, Hilde?
- You care?
Come over and see us sometime,
huh?
We've missed you, honey.
- I don't need this.
- It's okay, it's my treat.
- You sure?
- [whispers] Don't tell your father.
[boat engine roars]
[seagulls squawking]
[machinery whirring]
Roy.
What's that about?
Artie's renting him a slip.
[man] Coming through.
[Bobby] What's up? You lost pal?
Come on.
Why don't you go take it
somewhere else, pal?
[man]
Listen, I don't know you.
Go on.
You don't belong here, son.
Go home.
Let's not make this any worse.
Unbelievable.
That fucking prick, Artie.
He's a goddamn disgrace.
[soulful music]
[door opens]
[groans]
Where's Lily?
[Beth] Cleaning up.
Since when do you cook?
Since my mother taught me.
[music continues]
♪ We've make together ♪
You want some help?
♪ I love you ♪
It's okay, I got it.
[Tom] Come on, I can handle it.
Why don't you set the table?
That I can do.
[laughs]
[Tom humming]
[plates clattering]
[crickets chirping]
[knock on door]
[Dicky]
Look, I got it all worked out.
I got a friend down in Portland.
He'll buy it.
[Beth] What friend?
[Dicky]
He works at a dispensary.
Just trust me.
I'll be waiting for you here.
[Beth] And then what?
[Dicky] You meet me and we go,
all right?
[Beth] All right.
♪ Did you come to find yourself
a disappearing act? ♪
♪ Welcome to the Boys Klub ♪
[knocking on door]
[Dicky] Everything all right?
[ominous music]
[footsteps receding]
- [running footsteps]
- [door banging open]
[violin music]
[foreboding music]
[knocking on door]
Sweetheart.
What? What is it?
You're gonna say hello
to your niece?
Hi, Uncle George.
You look just like her.
Why don't you go on and
go to bed, hmm?
Go on. Go on.
[sighs] Don't mind him.
He's been in a mood lately.
So how's your father?
- Oh, you know.
- [Hilde] Yeah.
That's what I told your mother.
And she didn't listen to me.
[crockery clatters]
I need to ask you something.
Go on.
I need to make some money.
Oh, honey.
I wish we could,
but it's not a good time.
[George] You might ask
your father. He's got money.
Quiet down.
I've got something to sell.
What?
Some weed.
You have it with you?
Not yet.
How much are we talking?
Five, 10 pounds.
And I need the cash upfront.
[laughs]
You know I don't have
that kind of money.
[Beth] But you know people
who do, right?
[spoon clatters]
Think you can get it
in a day or two?
[water rippling]
[water splashes]
Jesus Christ.
You gotta be fucking kidding me.
Fuck.
[cages rattling]
What do you think?
Any bigger and he'd eat you.
[imitates chewing]
Eddie here?
Don't move.
[plastic sheet rustles]
[knocking]
Mr. Nance.
[Nance] What is it?
No, that's fine, we can do that.
Well, you just said
you can count on us.
[laughs]
I'll draw it up and I'll have
somebody bring it by.
All right.
No, thank you.
I'll talk to you.
What can I do for you?
You laid across me
down by Cutler.
I'm gonna lose a string of gear.
Uh, is that right?
Yeah.
We're expanding and I got
a couple of new guys up.
[paper tears]
It was a simple mistake,
I'm sure.
My family has been on that
bottom for four generations.
I don't wanna see you
down there again.
You thought any more
about my offer?
It'd be good for both of us.
This visit was a courtesy.
There won't be another.
[knock on door]
[Beth sighs]
[whispers]
Hey, I've got good news.
[whispers] Not tonight, just...
Oh, come on why not?
Let's go for a walk.
I can't. I don't know, I...
I don't feel good.
Everything all right?
Yeah.
- You sure?
- [laughs] Yeah.
- Yeah.
- All right.
Talked to my friend
and we're good to go.
Okay.
Bye.
[foreboding music]
[Tom] What?
Oh.
You enjoying the view
- [laughs]
- [Tom] I... I get it.
[Lily clearing throat]
What is it?
Nothing.
You worry too much.
[waves crushing]
[ominous music]
Hey.
Get dressed.
[ominous music]
[seagulls squawking]
[steady guitar music]
[boat engine rumbling]
[music continues]
[cage rattles]
[seagulls squawking]
[music continues]
- [Beth] It's right there.
- No, it's right there.
Oh, it's right there,
it's right there, I see it.
What's that one?
Is that one Venus?
No, Venus is there.
No, Venus is right there.
- [Beth]No, it's right there.
- [Millie] Oh, there's Pluto.
[Millie speaks indistinctly]
You know that one?
Right there?
[crickets chirping]
It's Venus.
That's right.
You still remember how
to find the North Star?
Yep.
You're gonna need to know
how to find that one.
In case you get lost.
[dog barking in distance]
[rain pattering]
[thunder rumbling]
[somber music]
[thunder cracking]
[music continues]
[thunder rumbling]
[seagulls squawking]
[boat engine roars]
[cage rattles]
What am I supposed to
do with that?
- You got a problem?
- Yeah, they're all empty.
I got eyes.
[Bobby]
These pieces of shit.
We gotta fucking do something.
We can't keep letting them
get away with this shit.
Get back here!
- [gun cocking]
- [gunshot]
Have you lost your fucking mind?
[gun cocking]
[boat engine revving]
Now they fucking know better.
[ominous music]
Dicky!
- [Dicky] What?
- You got a visitor.
[Dicky] Who is it?
The Queen of England.
- [Dicky grunts, laughs]
- [Beth] What the fuck! Shit.
[Anne] What's going on in there?
[Dicky] It's nothing, Ma.
Oh, man, you smell like fish.
- Yeah, you sure it's me?
- Just stop it. What are you doing?
- Stop. Fucking stop.
- Come on, let's get a shower.
- [Anne] Dicky?
- Come on. Relax, Ma, we're fine.
Jesus.
Fuck, man.
Just chill out.
Just goofing around.
[shower curtain rustles]
[water runs]
[Dicky] Uh-oh.
You know, I've been...
I've been thinking.
[water running]
Just be patient.
What if we stuck around
for a bit?
[Dicky] What the fuck are you
talking about?
Just... give it a few more weeks.
See how things go.
[shower curtain rustles]
What, you don't think
this is gonna work?
[water stops running]
What happened?
Huh?
What did I do?
- It's nothing. I just...
- I'm gonna take care of you.
Both of you.
Be realistic. Okay?
[Dicky] What for?
[scoffs]
So what, that's it?
We have fun.
We always did, but maybe...
This is real.
We can do this.
No, we can't.
What, did you get
a better offer?
Well, I'm not the one with some
random guy's baby inside me.
What's that supposed to mean?
[Dicky]
You up for mother of the year?
You're so full of shit.
Yeah, it looks like
I'm making a big mistake.
Yeah, go home.
Go run home to daddy.
But don't come crying
to me again.
You're an asshole.
Yeah, well I'm not the guy
that was fucking a nurse
down the hall while
your mother died.
Go on.
Get the fuck out of here!
- [engine rumbling]
- [man] Tom.
Got a second?
Finish up.
- [seagulls squawking]
- [indistinct chattering]
[officer] I got a call
from North-End PD.
Did you fire a shot at one of
Eddie Nance's boats?
Must be some kind of mistake.
Nance says you threatened him
in his office yesterday.
He's poaching my gear.
If you wanna file
an official complaint...
What'll that do?
Well, if you've got proof,
then we can do something.
Well, he got no right
bein' there, you know that.
You know the deal, Tom.
There's nothing
I can do about that.
Right.
So what are you gonna do?
Are you gonna arrest me or can
I go back to earning a living?
I'm here as a friend, Tom.
You gotta back off.
[Tom] Hm.
[car engine roars]
- [woman] Hey, Tommy.
- [door closes]
- How are you?
- Oh, staying above water.
- I'll get some coffee.
- All right.
Artie?
How's your back?
[chuckles] Can't feel much of
anything right now.
- [Tom] They got you on the good stuff, huh?
- [bottles clink]
It ain't bad.
Well, look...
I was hoping to talk to you
about something.
- Nance?
- [Tom] Yeah.
Heard you guys got into it.
Not really.
These new guys.
They got lawyers.
Cops.
Don't do it the way we used to.
You renting them your slip?
[woman] You know Artie hasn't
been able to go out
since the surgery.
He knows.
[Tom] Well, that can't be easy.
[woman]
We gotta make a living too.
- I understand.
- People might not like it.
- Sweetheart.
- What?
It's the truth.
[Artie]
Can you give us a second?
You know, I like you Tommy.
But you can't come around here
telling us what we can and cannot do.
You're right.
You heard the boss.
Just business.
Nance has been
poaching my lines.
Someone catch him?
I will.
Okay.
If you're right...
you know I'll cut him off.
[Tom] We all gotta stick
together on this.
You know he's buying
the old market by the harbor.
I heard that.
You know which way
this is going.
[Tom] Maybe.
But I don't gotta make
it any easier.
[foreboding music]
[door opens]
[Lily] How's work?
Yeah. Fine.
I ran into Dicky's mom today.
She said it's been
nice seeing you.
Why'd you lie to your father?
He doesn't like Dicky.
[Lily] You shouldn't lie to him.
[paper rustling]
How far along are you?
12, 13 weeks?
When was the last time
you saw the doctor?
Don't worry about it.
This is a big deal.
I know.
I'll figure it out.
- By yourself?
- Yeah.
[cabinet door creaks]
It's okay to be scared.
I got pregnant early on.
Your father thought it'd be too
hard on you and your brother.
He loves you.
He's just...
he's not very good at it.
[crickets chirping]
[Bobby] Hey.
What's that?
What are we gonna do, Pop?
[Tom] Go home.
- Put your daughter to bed.
- No, no, no.
We can't keep ignoring it.
We're gonna lose the business.
Well the first prick
who's tried to come in here
won't be the last.
We gotta do something.
You already did.
Now I'm the one
who's gotta take care of it.
[whispers] Fucking ridiculous.
You know you're not the only one
getting fucked here.
Okay?
I got a family.
I got a fucking mortgage.
Watch your language.
[soft guitar music]
Put one of these in
when you bait them.
Tie it to the door.
- What for?
- Just do it.
[seagulls squawking]
[hums]
[Tom] Millie.
- [Millie] Grandpa!
- [Tom speaks indistinctly] Oh!
[laughs]
Tell me about your day.
- What'd you do?
- [Millie] I saw butterflies.
[Tom] You did?
- How was work?
- Fine.
Go wash up, I got her.
Did you see any bu... did you see
any butterflies today?
- [Millie] Yeah.
- [Tom] I see one right over there.
I saw an airplane.
- [Tom] You saw an airplane?
- [Millie] And a rocket ship.
Really? Wait, you got
something in your ear.
Something...
wait, let me get it.
Oh. Oh yeah, it's got
a lot of ear wax on it.
- [Millie] No, it doesn't.
- [Tom] It's because it was in your ear.
- [Millie] No, it wasn't.
- [Tom] Where was it?
[water runs]
[broody music]
[tools clicking]
[Beth] Is this a good time?
[Tom] For what?
[tools clicking]
- I'm pregnant.
- [clicking stops]
So... okay.
[tools clicking]
[clicking stops]
[Tom] Dicky?
- No.
- [sighs]
Do you know who's the father?
Well, I'm...
just asking.
Right.
Well, what are you...
- What are you gonna do?
- What the fuck do you care?
Oh no, don't do that.
Don't do that.
Don't make me the bad guy.
- I'm not.
- You should have told me.
Okay.
[chair creaks]
All right,
so you'll stay here and...
I'm not asking you for anything.
Why is it so hard
for you to tell the truth?
- Yeah.
- Hey.
You're gonna have to start
acting like a grown up now.
All right?
[foreboding music]
[crickets chirping]
Oh, I got you an appointment
with an OB-GYN
I know at the hospital.
Great.
I can go with you if you want.
Can I borrow your car?
Just wanna go over to
Bobby's real quick.
[car engine hums]
[foreboding music]
[boat engine humming]
[banging on door]
- [door cracking]
- [Beth gasps]
[truck engine roars]
[dark broody music]
[water rippling]
- [door opens]
- There you go.
What's good today?
- I'm sorry.
- I don't give a shit.
I don't know
what I was thinking.
- Can I help you?
- [whispers] I wanna do it.
You can't keep
jerking me around.
Are these fresh?
- Yeah, I'll be right there.
- Just give me another chance.
You're a liar.
I know.
I'm the one taking a risk.
You get that?
I gotta know that
you're serious.
[laughs]
You want me to take an oath?
This isn't a joke.
I need to know that
you're not gonna fuck me.
Right, you were right. I... I...
There's nothing for me here.
I don't gotta do this.
- I know.
- Not with you.
I know.
I got scared, okay?
I don't know what I'm doing.
I just...
I'm sorry.
Okay.
I know it's scary,
but nothing's gonna happen.
- You promise?
- Yeah.
Yeah, I promise.
All right.
This is the coordinates.
The drop is at two AM.
My boat gets in at 2:05.
2:10 at the latest.
So you gotta be gone by then.
- Tonight?
- Yeah, it got moved up.
- But I don't...
- You meet me back at the bar
after and we're gone.
This is it, all right?
This is it.
We can go anywhere
you want after.
Just me and you.
Yeah.
[dark brooding music]
[water splashing]
[machinery whirring]
[cage rattles]
You see it's empty, right?
Yeah.
Maybe.
Mrs. McManus.
I'm sorry, I... I...
I didn't mean to startle you.
Uh, I just needed one moment.
Um, I don't know if you heard,
but I am opening
a processing plant right here
in the next six months.
Good luck with that.
Well...
that's just the thing
right there.
Uh, there's no point in opening
a processing plant
if no one will sell to me.
You got it.
What if you and your husband
own part of the business?
He won't listen to me.
But this is a deal that could be
good for everyone
for a long time to come.
In three seconds, I'm gonna kick
you somewhere you don't want.
Think about it.
Okay?
Talk it over with your husband.
If he doesn't take the deal,
somebody else will.
[soft music]
Fucking multiplying.
Be patient.
I need you to do
something for me.
You're gonna like this one.
[water rippling]
How's work?
[Beth] Fine.
Busy?
I guess.
[door opens, closes]
Hi.
I'll be out back.
[Hilde laughs over phone]
There's no way.
[Beth whispers]
Look, it's gotta be tonight.
[Hilde sighs]
I'll try to get something
together, honey,
but it's not gonna be
full price.
All right.
[dark broody music]
[Bobby whispers] Now go to bed
and close your eyes.
Hey.
Go to the other room.
What's up?
Is this the one I used to
steal from you?
Yeah, I don't need it.
Yeah? What's the matter?
You dyin'?
- Huh? [chuckles]
- Just give it to her.
Yeah?
Look, um...
I'm gonna take the kid
out on the boat.
We're gonna go fishing
this weekend.
You should... you should come.
Okay.
You gotta... you gotta try
to act excited.
You gotta try. We talked about it.
You gotta try to act excited.
- I can't wait.
- Good, that's better.
[crickets chirping]
I'm gonna go give this to her.
[ominous music]
[dark music]
[car door opens]
[car door closes]
[music continues]
Hold up.
[Dicky] What the fuck?
[man] Don't worry about it.
[boat engine revs]
[tense music]
[Beth grunts]
[boat engine starts]
[music intensifies]
[boat engine roars]
[water splashing]
[tense music]
[boat engine roars]
[music intensifies]
[bells chiming]
[intense music]
[boat engine roars]
[music continues]
[water rippling]
[intense music]
[boat engine roars]
[music continues]
[dog barking]
[water rippling]
[boat creaks]
[dog continues barking]
[dark music]
[foreboding music]
[boat creaks]
[intense music]
[pants]
[music continues]
[cage rattles]
[boat engine starts]
[Beth grunts]
[boat engine roars]
[ominous music]
[grunts]
[boat engine roars]
[cage rattles]
Where is it?
[bells chiming]
Maybe we're early.
[boat engine roars]
[intense music]
[car engine rumbling]
[knocking on door]
What happened?
Are you all right?
[Beth] I have it.
For Pete's sake. Come inside.
[door closes]
Wanna wake the whole
fucking neighborhood?
[George]
What's going on out there?
Nothing, just go back to bed.
- [George] Do you know what time it is?
- Yeah.
I don't wanna know where
you got this, do I?
- You have the money?
- I'll get it tomorrow.
[Beth]
You said you'd have it tonight.
I'm not a miracle worker.
- [whispers] Fuck.
- [paper tears]
- [Hilde] What is this?
- What?
[paper rustling]
[thudding]
Did you tell anyone
else about this?
No one else knows.
- Get rid of it.
- Um...
No, I can't touch this.
People are gonna come
looking for this.
- They're not people...
- You gotta know someone.
Even if I did, what the fuck
am I supposed to say, huh?
"Oh hey, I found two kilos
of fucking heroine..."
I need the fucking money.
- No, you don't!
- You gotta know someone.
[whispers] No, you don't.
Not like this.
You don't.
You know I'm not gonna
say anything.
You need to take this
and get rid of it.
Now.
[whispers] I can't.
[Hilde] Yes, you can.
Just go home.
I can't go home.
I... I can't.
[Hilde] Why?
I can't go home.
[cries]
[Hilde] What did you do?
I can't go fucking home.
[sobbing]
[Hilde]
Oh, what did you do?
[knocking on door]
[whispers] You tell anyone
you were coming here?
No.
- [knocking on door]
- [paper rustling]
[knocking on door]
[George]
Come on, are you gonna get that?
[clock ticking]
[sighs]
- Jesus Christ, Bobby.
- [Bobby] Where is he?
- Who?
- Your fucking husband.
- What are you talking about?
- Where are you, you fuck?
What the fuck is going on?
- [grunts]
- [Hilde] Whoa, stop it!
- [Hilde] Bobby!
[grunting]
- [punch landing]
- [grunts]
[pants]
What'd you think,
we wouldn't find out?
Huh? You're done.
This whole fucking town's
gonna know what you are.
- [Bobby pants]
- [Hilde] Get off.
- She know?
- [Hilde] Know what?
He's been poaching our traps.
He's been stealing from
his own fucking family!
[Hilde] All right.
Enough, get up.
[Bobby panting]
You're not working here anymore.
[Hilde] Just calm down.
We'll sit down,
we'll talk about it, all right?
- We got nothing to talk about.
- Bobby, come on.
We're family, Bobby.
[door closes]
You dumb fuck.
[groans]
[cries]
[George] Fuck.
[door opens]
[door closes]
[dark music]
[objects clatter]
[Lily whispers] Tom?
Can't you at least ask him
what he's willing to pay?
[whispering] No. No, I can't.
It's okay.
It'll be all right.
[Lily whispers] Okay.
[door closes]
[brooding music]
[dark music]
[seagulls squawking]
[water rippling]
So?
What?
It was Uncle George.
It's over now,
I took care of it.
[water rippling]
[dark music]
[stairs creak]
[line ringing]
Your clothes were wet,
so I put them in the dryer.
What, is that okay?
Yeah. Thanks.
[Anne]
He didn't come home last night.
- Thought he was with you.
- He's probably just sleeping it off somewhere.
He doesn't do that anymore.
Yeah, I know.
- I'm sure he's fine.
- Look, if you see him,
tell him to call. Just...
let me know he's okay.
Yeah.
[low dark music]
[door closes]
I tried to tell you.
Don't.
I'm sorry.
I didn't come here for that.
We're gonna lose the house and...
My own goddamn brother.
I asked you for help.
[Tom] That gives you the right?
You're gonna sell your boat,
or move out of this town.
Come on.
I'll make it up.
I see you again...
I'm gonna kill you.
You're not the good guy here.
You never were.
[door opens]
[door closes]
Hey, what's going on?
Whatever it is,
running's not gonna fix it.
Don't worry about it.
I can't watch him go
through this again.
He could give a shit.
- That's not true.
- Right.
[Lily] Come downstairs.
Let's talk about this.
You're not my fucking mother.
Yeah.
What would she say?
At some point you gotta take
responsibility for your life.
You can't keep running away.
It's a little late now.
You learn the lesson now
or life is just gonna teach
it to you again.
[door rattling]
[rustling]
Dicky?
[foreboding music]
[ominous music]
Okay, can you walk?
We gotta get outta here,
come on.
- Hey, we gotta go.
- You fucked me.
No, no, no. We, uh...
We... we can fix this.
We'll just give it back to them.
That's what they want, right?
Hey, hey. Dicky.
We'll just give it back to them.
Hey.
You gotta help me, okay?
We can fix this.
- Right?
- No.
Not these people.
Did you know?
Did you know what it was?
[melancholic music]
You were never coming with me,
were you?
[somber music]
[whispers] I wanted to.
[Dicky] I didn't tell them.
But they know.
You gotta go.
They're gonna kill you.
[tense music]
[Nance on recording] Nance Seafood.
Leave a message.
[tone beeps]
Eddie, this is Tom McManus.
Give me a call
when you get this.
Let's talk.
- Go to the police.
- What about Dicky?
You're in a lot of trouble.
You gotta stop fighting
me right now.
[knock on door]
I just put Millie down for a nap.
I'm gonna start supper.
Good, good, good.
- Is everything okay?
- Everything is fine, just give us a second, okay?
Okay.
- It's not his fault.
- I understand.
No, you don't understand, okay?
He just... he just wanted to
take care of me.
Nothing to be done about
that right now.
We have to go get him.
They'll kill him.
Please.
O-okay.
Okay.
We'll go get him together.
And then we're going
to the police.
[paper rustling]
You're my daughter.
And I'm not gonna let
anything happen to you.
[whispers] Okay.
[somber music]
[keys jingle]
[car door shuts]
[Lily] Everything okay?
[Beth crying]
[Lily] What did you say to her?
Take the girls down in the
basement and keep them there.
- [Lily] What's going on?
- Call Frank.
Tell him we need the Staties.
- Tom, what...
- [Tom] Now.
Get them down there and
keep them down there.
[ominous music]
Fuck.
I'm coming out.
[foreboding music]
[car dinging]
[wind blowing]
[suspenseful music]
[door creaks]
[Lily whispering] I need you
to stay right here, okay?
[door creaking]
Get away from the window.
[suspenseful music]
[bag thuds]
[man]
Where's your daughter?
[Tom] Not here.
[man] We need to talk to
your daughter.
You got what you came for.
- Go on now.
- You don't make the rules.
Consider it a friendly request.
It's not up to us.
Get out of the way, Tom.
[Tom] You know I can't do that.
- [punch landing]
- [Tom grunts]
[whispers] The cops will be here
soon. He'll be fine.
- [man speaks indistinctly]
- [punch landing]
- [Lily] Let your father handle this.
- If I don't go out there...
- He can take care of himself.
- They're gonna kill him.
- [footsteps pounding]
- [intense music]
[Beth] I'm here.
She's not here, huh?
Let's go.
- [Tom grunts]
- [gunshot]
- [Tom groans]
- What the fuck?
- Sorry, Tommy.
- [man] Shut up.
- Take her, let's go.
- [Beth grunting]
- [gunshot]
- [gasps]
[gunshot]
[gunshots]
[man grunts]
[gun cocking]
[suspenseful music]
[gunshot]
Daddy?
Daddy? Hey.
Tom? Tom, honey?
[whispering] Please, Daddy.
[Lily] Hold it tight.
- [whimpering]
- [Bobby] Where's Millie?
Inside, she's fine.
[police sirens wailing]
[Beth] I'm sorry.
[cries]
Hear me?
[melancholic music]
[waves crashing]
[Tom] You still remember
how to find the North Star?
You're gonna need to know
how to find that one.
In case you get lost.
[melancholic music]
[boat engine rumbling]
[water rippling]
[soft guitar music]
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
[music continues]