♪♪
[Man]
Sleeping beauty is awake.
We need to leave
in half an hour.
My new cell phone number
is on the kitchen counter.
When you go out,
lock all the doors.
We're gonna be back bright
and early tomorrow morning.
Just in case,
I've put these frozen meals
in there for you.
All you need to do is heat them
three and a half minutes
each in the microwave.
"L" is for lunch
and "d" is for dinner.
[Car starting up]
♪♪
[Doorbell ringing]
What's up?
I was expecting a friend.
Not that you're not
a friend, of course.
Who, Ashlyn?
What are you guys gonna do?
I saw your parents
take off, where'd they go?
I don't mean to be rude,
but I'm getting ready right now.
Uh, we'll talk later, okay?
All righty, if you say so.
[Door locking]
[School bell ringing]
and he gave me
10% higher of a grade.
But... and he wrote
"phenomenal."
But, it's still not,
like, a good grade.
So, I guess he just told
me to do more of the same
and better luck next time.
[Girl]
Yeah, but you wrote it
on carrot juice, right?
Mm-hmm.
Who writes it on that?
Of course you're
gonna get that grade.
But, I like carrot juice.
Yeah, but nobody else does.
Hey.
You must be that new girl
I've heard so much about.
Helen, from New Jersey.
Right?
Yeah.
This is Mark.
And, we have to go now,
or we'll be late for class.
What class do you guys have?
Biology.
Oh, sounds kinky.
Why don't I have biology?
Don't worry, once you
start the fifth grade
it'll be in your schedule.
I promise, just wait and see.
[Music playing]
[Doorbell ringing]
Hi!
Hey!
How are you?
Great.
Look at you, all alone.
[Ashlyn]
You have to read it.
Thanks.
I've read it like ten times.
Watch out for chapter nine.
It is so intense.
[Helen]
I've never had a
dream like that before.
I wonder if it means anything.
What do you mean?
There's a psychic down
on old Thompson road.
My mom has been there once.
Why don't we just go by there
and see what she
has to say about it?
Thanks, but, I'm not sure
I believe in that stuff.
Mark came by this morning
before you showed up.
That guy is just
so... odd.
Yeah, he is a complete loser.
I sometimes think
he's stalking me.
Boys.
I'm so glad I found you.
Since we moved here,
you're really my only
true friend.
I don't know what
I'd do without you.
I've actually really
looked forward to today.
We'll have fun.
Of course.
♪ Nothing ever happens
♪ in the summers
baby ♪
So, I'll see you at
fast bill's at 1:00.
Yeah.
Okay, have fun babysitting.
See ya.
♪ Summers, baby
♪ nothing ever happens
♪ nothing ever
changes ♪
Good morning!
Good morning,
Mr. and Mrs. Henley.
How are you guys doing today?
Fine.
We saw you wave goodbye
to your parents earlier.
Are you gonna be alone?
Yeah, um, I'm on
my way to babysit,
and then I'm gonna
meet a friend,
and she'll be with me.
My parents will be
back in the morning.
Well, honey, don't hesitate
to come over here
if you need anything at all.
We will be here to help.
After all,
that's what neighbors are for.
Thanks, I'll see you guys later.
Bye.
♪♪
[Ringing doorbell]
Hi there, you're just in time.
We're almost ready to leave.
Helen, hi.
Hi!
Hi.
Hi, how are you?
[Woman]
Water bottles are in
the fridge, can you grab 'em?
[Dog barking]
Rufus!
[Baby crying]
It's okay, it's okay.
[Woman 2]
Did you let him in
the bedroom again?
[Baby crying]
[Helen]
Hi, Rufus!
How you doing, boy?
He's just been fed and
just had a diaper change,
so there should be no fussing
coming from him any time soon.
And Rufus has just
been fed as well,
so everyone's got a full tummy.
[Baby crying]
Aw.
Aw, it's okay.
Did you take the new balls?
[Annoyed]
Yes!
[Giggling]
[Baby babbling]
[Barking]
[Helen]
What's up, Rufus?
What is it?
♪♪
[Rubber squeaking]
[Baby babbling]
[Doorbell ringing]
[Woman]
Helen, you have
a visitor.
Hey, how's it going?
Uh, you left your book
in class today.
I found it on a chair
and it had your name in it,
so I figured it was yours.
Thank you, but...
I thought for sure
I'd put it in my locker.
Don't worry about it.
I just thought you might
need it for homework today,
so I brought it right over.
That is so nice of you, Mark.
Would you like some lemonade?
I just made some.
Yes, ma'am,
if it isn't too much trouble.
Not at all.
I'll be right back.
Would you please
get the glasses?
♪♪
[Door opening]
Hi, how was tennis?
You're back early.
Oh, I pulled a muscle in my back
at the end of the second set.
We were almost finished,
of course.
It was just my luck.
You can go now.
I'll have to pay you next time.
I'm fresh out of cash.
Oh, that's not a problem.
Where's Christie?
She just dropped me off.
She had to run an errand.
Now, we'll call you
next time we need you.
Okay, thanks.
I'll see you next time.
Bye.
Ah ah ah ah ah!
Rufus, you stay here!
[Smacking, dog crying]
Thanks again for letting
me borrow your shirt.
It's really pretty.
Yeah, it's totally you.
You know what?
Just keep it.
Really?
Yeah, I have another one
just like it.
Are you sure?
Of course, but...
I must warn you.
About what?
It's a total boy magnet.
[Laughing]
Speaking of boys,
when are you gonna get rid
of some of these Teddy bears?
What do you mean?
If you ever get a boy in here,
you'll freak him out.
I like them.
♪♪
♪ Love song
♪ love song
♪♪
♪ Swimming
against the tide ♪
♪ as I keep control
♪ nothing to do
but hide ♪
♪ from seeing ya
yeah ♪♪
Hi.
Welcome to faaaaast bill's!
What can I get you to drink?
Just a coke, please.
I'm waiting for a friend
and I'm a bit early.
All right.
UN Coca-Cola.
Would like a lot or
a little whiskey in that?
You all right?
Look a little bit sad.
I've just had a strange morning.
Well, I love strange mornings.
Tell me more.
This...
This little girl that
I've never seen before
smiled at me from a car.
Well, that's awesome.
But, not strange, I hope.
No.
What does the 'a' stand for?
Asshole.
[Laughing]
It's Adam.
My mother liked Adam.
My father, Christopher.
So, I guess they both
got their way.
Can I ask you something?
Of course.
Why do people change when
they get to know you better?
Well, kid, that...
Is a good question.
I guess our society
dictates how we should act
in certain ways.
To put on a mask, if you will.
Early on in our lives,
we're told what to do
and how to be.
And when we get to
know someone better,
our true self eventually
shines through.
For better or for worse.
How's that for a lecture, huh?
I think I know what you mean.
Sometimes when I look
at a little child,
I see all that
innocence and happiness.
And it somehow makes me envious.
Exactly, we take that all away.
Are you being stood up by a boy?
No, I... I am
meeting a friend.
Her name is Ashlyn.
I better get back
to my kitchen duties
before my boss man
beats my butt.
I hope your friend shows up.
Was nice talking to you.
Helen.
I guess we're not
strangers anymore.
[Dance music playing]
[Overlapping chatter
and cheering]
What's this?
A jello shot.
You mean there's alcohol in it?
Duh!
Ugh, so good!
I don't want mine.
Come on, just try it.
If my parents found out
I'd been drinking,
they'd never forgive me.
Just have one.
No one will ever know.
That was disgusting.
[Laughing]
[Dance music continues]
[Music playing faintly]
Hi there.
We were just wondering if you
were the Hansens'' daughter.
No, I'm not.
Do you go to flaxfield high?
Yes.
Ah, so you're a
high school girl.
Lots of new things happen to you
when you start in high school.
[Laughing]
I was supposed to meet a friend.
Sorry, but do you know
what time it is?
It is 20 after 1:00.
I can remember
when I was younger,
I was always running late.
[Laughing]
Does your friend
live nearby here?
Yes.
Oh, well, that's nice.
I bet she went home
to freshen up
and change her clothes.
And I bet you she's
gonna be walking
through that door
just any minute now.
You'll see.
[Laughing]
Well, we best be going.
Okie-doke.
[Door closing]
♪♪
[Stammering]
Pl... plee...
Please o...
P-Pl... pl...
Pl-please o-o...
Please o... o...
Please o...
Pl...
Piss off.
♪♪
Hi, I'm really sorry
to bother you,
but I'm going to
visit my friend Ashlyn.
She lives in there.
But, I forgot the code,
and normally, I come with her
and she lets us in.
♪♪
[Knocking]
[Dog panting]
[Barking]
[Woman]
Sorry, child.
This is lucky.
He just wants to play.
[Laughing]
Don't let him frighten ya.
He's just as harmless
as a kitten.
Aren't you, lucky?
Yes, you are.
Such a pretty baby, huh?
Oh yeah.
[Laughing]
[Answering machine]
Hey, this is Ashlyn.
Leave a message.
[Beep]
Hi.
Where are you?
What's going on?
I hope you're okay.
I just stopped by your house
and there's nobody home.
My day has just...
Been really weird
since I left you.
It's...
I don't know.
I really need to talk to you.
Can you... can you
just call me?
Okay.
Bye, I...
I'll see ya.
[TV]
And it's clinically proven
to turn your fat cells
into muscle tissue.
Call now, operators are...
Invigorating natural and
healthy lifestyle.
Side effects may include
constipation, diarrhea,
dizziness,
and suicidal tendencies.
Ask your doctor if...
Stress level will
decrease dramatically
after just two weeks of our
patented, easy-to-use
self-administered enemas.
♪♪
[Woman]
You'll see, once we
move to Flaxfield,
we'll live in a neighborhood
with lots of families
just like ours.
It won't be like here.
There'll be many
children your age.
Maybe, but I like it here.
Helen, we've been
through this 100 times.
Your dad's been offered
a great opportunity.
And just think of
the warm weather.
No more snow or ice.
And 100 degree humid summers.
I promise you you won't melt.
Aw.
[Doorbell ringing]
'Sup?
You alone?
Yeah, my parents
come back tomorrow.
Cool, when's the party?
No.
No party, I mean.
Hey, have you seen Ashlyn today?
No.
You and Ashlyn have become
pretty good friends, huh?
Yeah.
I guess so.
She's nice.
Suit yourself.
To me, she's just another snob.
[Phone ringing]
That's probably her.
Well, I'm out of here then.
Later.
Hello?
[Ashlyn]
Helen, I'm sorry.
I didn't have time to
call you before we left.
My grandma's sick,
and she's had a stroke
and she might never wake up.
I'm with my parents here
at the hospital in Agora.
I'm so sorry.
That's terrible.
I'll call you later
when I know when
we're coming home, okay?
Okay.
My thoughts are with you.
Thanks.
I just got your message.
What's going on?
Don't worry about it.
I'm fine.
I... I hope your
grandmother will be okay.
Thanks, bye.
Bye.
[Phone clicking]
[Doorbell ringing repeatedly]
Hey, what's up?
I saw Heather leave.
Listen Mark, I need to
call my parents right now.
Ashlyn's grandmother's sick
and she just called me
from the hospital.
Aw.
Well, can you hang out later?
No.
I'm sorry.
♪♪
[Woman]
Ooh, almost!
Almost got it!
Chase, that's beautiful.
Hey, Trevor!
Hello, Stephanie.
Gather round.
I've got a great
story to tell you.
Come on, chase, you are
going to love it.
All and none are innocent.
All and none are guilty.
The truth, it never took place.
But, don't worry.
Sometimes even the blind
squirrel finds the acorn.
[Woman laughing]
Oh, Timmy.
Look, see?
The lady loves her dog.
[Soft music playing]
Why do they have to play
such bland elevator muzak?
It's an insult.
What did you want, to eat
your vinaigrette salad
while headbanging
to some heavy metal?
Heavy metal is worse than this.
Heavy metal is worse than
just about anything.
What music do you listen to?
You even remotely thinking
that I like heavy metal
is a grave insult,
and it really just shows
how brainwashed you are.
Nice.
Please, go on.
Yeah, I bet you and, uh,
little newbie here
just listen to the stuff
that's being crammed
down your throats by
the corporate machine.
Like the good little puppets
that you are.
Please enlighten us,
because we are just dying
to download any recommendations
coming from you,
aren't we, Helen?
I like any music that moves me.
It's all about the passion.
Not like the crap
they play here.
Child?
I believe you were daydreaming.
I was just remembering.
Haven't we met before?
Aren't you a friend of Ashlyn's?
Yes, I'm Helen.
And I'm Mrs. Straub.
Nice to meet ya.
So, how is our
miss Ashlyn today?
Ashlyn's grandmother
got sick this morning.
Ohh, that's terrible.
Her and her parents
had to leave.
Oh.
Yeah, I'm very
sorry to hear that.
And my parents are
also out of town.
You mean to tell me
that you're all alone?
I was supposed to have
been with Ashlyn today.
Oh, you poor little thing.
Is there anything
I can do for you?
Thank you, but I'll
be fine, honestly.
My parents will be home
first thing tomorrow morning.
Beautiful child like you
shouldn't be all alone.
Why don't you come back
with me to my house?
I have a beef stew,
I can heat it up.
I'm not sure if I...
Oh, come on, it won't
be any trouble at all.
Thank you, but...
And you know, afterwards,
I could follow you back home
so you won't have
to go home alone.
That's very kind of you.
I am a little uneasy
about going back alone.
Then you have nothing
to worry about, child.
Whew, do you feel a little
bit of a chill in the air?
And please, don't thank me.
Do you know why?
Because I'm already
enjoying your company.
Come on, let's go!
Don't dawdle, child.
Let's go!
Let me see.
Here we are.
Oh, Nordic, we're home, boy.
[Laughing]
Here we are.
Hello, Nordic.
Did you miss me, boy?
Oh, Nordic, come here, boy.
Nordic, I want you
to meet Helen.
Helen, this is Nordic.
He's so cute.
Why didn't you
bring him to the park?
Well, he doesn't really
like to be out
for extended periods of time.
You know, it's really
good to get them
when they're young,
so you can train them.
That's a good boy.
That's a good boy, oh!
How long have you had him?
Six years.
Six beautiful years
since my husband passed.
I'm sorry to hear that.
Oh, don't be sorry, child.
He was lucky.
One night, he went
to bed, fell asleep,
never woke up.
[Laughing]
He never had to suffer.
We should all be so lucky.
Isn't that right?
Isn't that right, Nordic?
Why don't you
have a seat, child?
Sit there and I'll
warm up the stew.
It's a good boy.
Good boy.
[Sighs]
Would you like...
Oh, well...
He's quite a hit
with you, isn't he?
He is, he's such a loving dog.
I came in here to
ask you something,
and I don't know what
it was, so...
Oh, yes!
Would you like your iced tea
sweetened or unsweetened?
Unsweetened is fine, thanks.
Can I help you with anything?
No, no, you just sit there
and get acquainted with Nordic.
Careful, he can be a flirt.
Good Nordic.
[Chuckling]
[Mrs. Straub humming]
♪♪
[Humming continues]
[Panting]
♪♪
[Dog barking]
[Car engine revving]
Think of number
between zero and 31.
No rush.
Take a deep breath.
It will soon
appear in your mind.
Eighteen.
You can let go of
my hands now, child.
Now, I want you to pick a card.
Just...
Pull it up.
♪♪
It's good.
Tell me about dream you had.
It was very real.
Some of it
was... beautiful.
And then some of it
was terrifying.
There were humans, babies.
And there was people
with distorted faces.
Fish faces.
Just when I woke up,
it was as if the dream
was still inside of me.
And the smells were
like nothing I...
Smells?
Well, it seems you have had
an extrasensory
dream perception,
or E.D.P.
They are very rare.
Is this your first one?
Yeah, I think so.
What's extrasensory
dream perception?
[Chuckling]
Dreams are of no relevance
to modern psychology.
But, we both know
better, don't we?
E.d.p.'s a pretty
good buy.
Special sense the
dreamer possesses.
It is a sense that
comes from ties
to our primal ancestors
who had a very profound
unconscious mobility.
You hid an unconscious
extrasensory perception.
And your dream is merely
a manifestation
of your sixth sense.
Sixth sense?
Sixth sense, yes.
So, what does my dream mean?
It sounds as if
your primitive self
is warning you not to trust
what appears to be safe,
or who appears
to be your friend.
I want you to close
your eyes again,
and think about the dream.
I want you to focus on
the most powerful feelings
from within the dream.
Concentrate.
Inhale.
And exhale, slowly.
Once you focus,
I want you to tune your
mind completely to it.
Forgetting everyone else.
Now,
squeeze my hands as
tight as you can
until I tell you to let go.
Relax.
You can let go now, child.
Stop it, child!
Stop, let go, I command you
to open your eyes and stop, now!
[Grunting]
What happened?
What does that card mean?
Get out!
I want you to leave right now.
And please, do not come
back here, ever!
♪♪
[Door creaking]
[Music playing,
faint conversation]
[Boy 1]
Why were you even at
that guy's party, bro?
[Boy 2]
Dude, that's what
I don't even know.
Hey, look who's here?
Freaking finally!
What's going on?
How did you get in?
Through the garage, of course.
Yeah.
I mean, who uses
the home address as
the passcode to get in?
I can't believe...
I tried to call you,
and nobody answered.
And your cell phone's
not working either,
so you might wanna
get that checked out.
That's kinda dangerous.
[Turning music off]
Whatever.
We brought you pizza and drinks.
Good ones, too.
And you're just gonna be
a little bitch about that?
Like, okay.
If my parents were gone,
you know what I'd do?
I'd invite everybody over,
throw a big party, right?
Like, that's money, right?
Guys!
If you came over...
I don't want a party.
I don't feel good, so can
you guys just get out?
Chill out, pussycat.
My parents are coming
home in the morning.
[Laughing]
Wow, what's up her butt?
That's what I was saying!
[Muffled chatter]
Okay, sorry guys,
but the party's over.
So, can you please just get out?
Helen!
You're such a party pooper.
Why do you do this, why?
Whatever.
Gonna leave anyway.
Fuck this place.
Let's go.
[Guy groaning]
Okay, I’m...
All right, one more.
Helen, why don't you
have a piece of pizza?
You gotta eat anyways, right?
[Boy mumbling]
Especially if you're
not feeling good.
[Grunting, girl laughing]
Stop.
You're gonna freaking
drop me and I'm gonna...
[Shrieks, laughing]
Go away, Helen.
Hey, come here.
Okay, seriously,
what is wrong with you?
Trey's hot and he's
totally into you,
so freaking jump on it already.
Bye, Helen!
Oh my gosh!
Oh my god!
Coming through.
Wait for us, brother.
Don't hit my head.
[Engine revving]
What are you doing?
I'm surveying the party scene.
I think you had one hell
of a party here.
Why wasn't I invited?
It wasn't a party.
Oh, really? Well, I saw
your loser friends
Trey and hunter leave.
Why were they here then?
Heather brought them.
Oh, well, I hate
that Gothic bitch.
What, are you friends
with her now, too?
Listen, I'm on my way to bed,
I do not feel good.
Can you please just go?
So, what exactly have
I done to deserve
you treating me like
shit when you're so nice
to everybody else?
Nothing.
Can you please
just leave me alone?
So, when do your
parents get back?
Soon.
I'll talk to you tomorrow, okay?
I'm going to bed now.
Great, so am I.
Wanna sleep here or at my place?
It's not funny.
Please don't touch that.
It's my mother's,
and it's very fragile.
Now, you need to go.
Please just leave me alone.
Just take my hand and lead me.
Oh, that hurts.
♪♪
[Man]
I'd rather have
Laura than you.
[Woman]
Oh, that's obvious!
That's obvious!
Oh, it's so clear you don't
give a damn about me!
No, I don't, when you call
me a son of a bitch though.
Looks like I may pop you
right between the eyes.
Oh! Don't you dare
threaten me!
Don't you...
I'll call the damn cops...
[Helen]
Somebody just
tried to attack me.
[Woman]
Ma'am, what's your
name and address?
Helen Olsen, 1206 poplar street.
We'll send somebody
over right away.
Please stay on the line.
[Hanging up phone]
♪♪
[Knocking]
[Knocking continues]
Helen Olsen?
Yes, officer.
[Snickers]
Well, who would wanna hurt
a little thing like you?
Can I come in?
[Sighing loudly]
What happened here?
He tried to attack me.
Hmm.
He break in?
No.
Then how'd he get in?
[Stammering]
[Spitting]
Mark! Mark!
Mark.
Dad?
What happened?
She tried to kill me.
Get her away from me.
Don't you move.
I said freeze!
Mark?
Mark!
Damn it!
You, get over here
and hold his legs.
Now!
Mark, stay with me.
[Mark seizuring]
Okay, it's okay, it's okay.
Mark!
Mark?
You are gonna do exactly
what I tell you to do.
You're gonna get
over here and pound on
his chest right now.
Do it!
Pound!
Pound him harder!
You do this!
Get down there!
Told you to pound him!
[Grunting]
You are one dead little girl.
♪♪
Stop, you're not
listening to me.
He's dead.
Yes, she killed him.
Negative, no uniforms,
no uniforms, you get down here.
I'm in pursuit northbound
on Caulfield road
just past rye Lane.
No, you get down here!
You get down here
so we can give this...
Give this fucking bitch
what she deserves!
God damn it!
Unit 27 checking in.
Unit 27, come in.
Yeah, uh, that was
a false alarm.
Just some little girl,
thinks she sees ghosts.
[Laughing]
Paranoid type.
I, uh, talked her down.
So, all is well, left location.
No offense, unit 27
is checking clear.
Roger that.
Got you.
♪♪
[Screaming]
[Crying]
[Panicked breathing]
No.
Oh, no.
No! My baby!
What happened to you?
Just drive.
Fast!
So, what happened?
You look horrible.
[Sobbing]
I killed a cop.
What?
And Mark, he's dead, too.
Are you drunk?
After you left Mark showed up
and I couldn't get him to leave,
and he tried to attack me,
and I hit him on the head
and then I called the police
and then this cop showed up and
it turned out to be his dad.
Are you serious?
Okay, so Mark attacks you,
you call the cops,
and out of all people,
they send his dad.
You didn't know
his parents were cops?
No!
What exactly are you on?
Nothing.
So, what happened with his dad?
He... he was trying to
hit me with his car
and I... I fell over
this fire hydrant
and he hit it.
I looked at him.
He's dead, too.
I just...
I don't know what to do.
Don't you think I should
just go to the police station
and explain everything now?
Trust me, you don't wanna go
to the local police station,
because you'll probably just
run into Mark's mom there.
I'm gonna go pick up
three of my friends.
They're the coolest.
They have their own clubhouse
where they hang out
and play music.
And they're in college,
so please,
try not to act
too immature, okay?
Hey, don't drink it all.
I like it too, you know.
[Heather]
Seriously?
Oh, great.
[Rock music playing]
[Girl]
Hey, what's up?
Hey guys, look who's here?
[Heather]
Hi.
Uh, this is Helen.
What the hell
happened to her face?
She killed a cop today.
[Scoffs]
No, seriously.
Well, in that case,
I wanna shake your hand...
And give you this.
[Music continues]
I know a waiter
who'd really like you.
[Music stops]
What kind of drugs have you
been administering to this girl?
Here, hold that.
All right, let's clean
you up, you hot mess.
Geez, who dresses you, your mom?
Ugh.
♪♪
That'll do.
So...
Tell us more of these
cop killings of yours.
I didn't mean to kill him.
I wish you had,
because all cops
are sadist pigs.
Not all are bad.
But pretty damn close.
I guess that's why
they have that job.
You can't really blame 'em.
What do you mean?
Well, if you're a sadist,
what job would you want?
I'd say a cop would be
a pretty damn good one.
You get paid to get off.
Or a prison guard.
Those are hardcore sadists.
But, what if you're a masochist?
You marry a man.
And if you're a pedophile,
you become a scout leader.
Or a catholic priest.
Hey, how do you get
a nun pregnant?
You fuck her.
Aside from that, Britt.
You dress her up
as an altar boy.
[Laughing]
♪♪
Perfect.
Amazing, I don't even
recognize her anymore.
[Girl]
Check it out.
♪ Come on, motherfucker
[punk music playing]
[Girls chattering]
Hey, kid, you gonna
take this or what?
Yeah, thanks.
♪ Can't get the picture
out of my head ♪
♪ can't change the channel
no matter what's said ♪
♪ can't enjoy
that sunny day ♪
♪ can't make that image
go away ♪
♪ shake it up
and lock it down ♪
♪ take a walk
around my town ♪
♪ dig that rocking sound
[Helen coughing, girls laughing]
How did the car get so black?
Ugh, now I am really
getting B.F.M.'Ed.
What's B.F.M.?
Oh, it's this word.
A private word.
A hoaxes' word we made up.
Can I tell her?
B.f.m. Means to get
butt-fucked in the mouth.
What?
When we came up with it,
just plain old "fuck"
was getting to be too lame.
So, to get
butt-fucked in the mouth
is just a badass expression...
No pun intended...
Ba-dum, chh!
That we came up with.
[Girl]
So, instead of
saying "fuck, yeah"
we say "B.F.M., yeah."
And never say
"that's so fucked."
We say "that's so B.F.M.'Ed."
It's cool.
Nobody understands it.
[Girl 2]
Geez, Heather,
come on, man.
My grandmother drives
faster than this.
Sorry, I...
I guess I really, uh...
B.f.m.'ed
that one.
[Laughter]
The kid's catching on.
♪ Get on out of my way
♪ good day
for rock ♪
♪ it's a good day for rock
♪ it's a good day
for rock ♪
♪ it's a good day for rock
[girl]
Whoo!
♪ It's a good day
for rock ♪
♪ it's a good day for rock
[music shuts off]
[Rock music playing in distance]
[Car alarm chirping]
[Music continues]
Can I have a beer, please?
Can I see your I.D.?
I don't have it.
What can I get you?
Hey, don't serve her.
Go.
Do you know
what B.F.M. Means?
Sorry, my friend's had a
little too much to drink.
[Crowd cheering]
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh
ooh-ooh-ooh ♪
♪ ooh-ooh-ooh
oo-oo-ooh-ooh ♪
♪ ooh ahh
ooh ahh ♪
♪ can't you see
what you're doing ♪
♪ can't you see where
you're going ♪
♪ all this time
you're making a big mistake ♪
♪ yeah
♪ your love is suffocating
♪ your love
is suffocating ♪
♪ your love is suffocating
♪ your love
is suffocating ♪
♪ you're always wanting me
on the floor ♪
♪ you're always
blocking my door ♪
♪ still you're wanting me
more, more, more ♪
♪ your love is suffocating
♪ your love
is suffocating ♪
♪ your love is suffocating
♪ all this time
you're suffocating ♪
♪ me ♪
[Crowd cheering]
[Singer]
Thank you!
Thank you so much for
coming out tonight!
[Live music playing in distance]
♪ Nothing matters
if you don't have someone ♪
♪ nothing matters if you
don't have someone ♪
♪ nothing matters
if you don't have someone ♪
♪ to love
♪ Caught up in
a world of grief ♪
♪ and see your people
in need ♪
♪ self-imposed solitude
works wonders ♪
♪ if you are rude
hey, you gotta go that way!
No, no, it's that way!
Guys, I know the way.
♪ Nothing matters
if you don't have someone ♪
♪ to love ♪
[Crowd cheering,
chanting "shadow"]
[Singer]
We're gonna do
one more song for you.
This one is called
"punk rock agent"!
Let's go!
♪♪
♪ Ooh
♪ yeah
♪ I'm a punk rock agent
wanna play? ♪
make my day... ♪♪
Hi, I'm Doug.
Helen.
So, what'd you think?
It was really great.
Yeah, they seem to get
better and better.
Have you seen them before?
No.
Wow!
You're missing out.
I have to find my friends.
I'll help you.
So, uh, how old are you?
[Boy]
Old enough.
Aren't we all?
[Boy laughing]
The concert was so good!
Yeah, I know.
Hey, look, it's that cop killer.
So, what are you doing now?
I go to Flaxfield high.
[Laughing]
No, I mean, like,
where are you going now?
Do you have a car?
I came with my friends.
Do you fuck?
[Girl]
Don't we all?
Actually...
I'd like to fuck you.
My parents are out of town.
Really?
My parents are out of town, too.
They come back tomorrow morning.
Why don't you go back
with me to my place
so you don't have to be alone?
Look, I promise, I'm not
gonna do anything.
I have a really comfy
couch you can sleep on
and...
I'll drive you home
first thing in the morning.
I don't know, I have
to talk to my friends.
Heather?
[Girl]
This is gonna be fun.
When do you think
we'll be leaving?
I don't know.
We'll probably go back
to their clubhouse and crash.
I have to be back before
my parents get home.
Why don't you go home
with what's-his-name?
Nice catch, by the way.
Doug.
He already asked me
to go home with him.
Well, then go home with him
if he can get you home in time.
Okay.
Just go, have some fun,
and don't do anything
that I wouldn't do.
Okay, thanks.
Good night.
[Helen]
I've had a really,
really weird day.
I can give you a
back massage if you want.
Thanks, but...
I think I'll just
need some sleep.
Thanks for letting
me sleep with you.
[Chuckling]
I mean...
Thanks for letting me
sleep at your house.
I don't wanna be alone tonight.
I understand.
Don't worry,
I'll take care of you.
I'll drive you home
in the morning.
Thanks.
Do you know that
you have really...
Beautiful eyes?
Thanks.
[Doug]
I'll give you that back
massage that I promised you.
I'm really good at it.
I'm really tired.
Where am I gonna sleep?
Oh, you can sleep
right here on the couch.
Thanks.
Don't be nervous.
Relax.
Can you take off your top?
It's hard for me to do
my massage with it on.
I really like your
outfit, by the way.
It's not mine.
Wow.
You've got one incredible body.
Please, don't.
I'm not gonna hurt you, baby.
Doesn't it feel good?
But...
I'm sorry, I don't
think I can do this.
Don't worry, I'm not
gonna hurt you, baby.
I have protection.
[Doug breathing heavily]
[Doug grunting]
[Doug laughs]
I'm sorry.
I just remembered
that my parents
might come home really
early this morning.
Is it okay if you leave soon?
What do you mean?
If my parents come home,
you can't be here.
They could be here really soon.
So, what do you want me to do?
I'm sorry, I just
can't let you...
You can't mean this.
You got what you wanted.
Is that it?
Of course not, look...
I'll give you money for a taxi.
I don't want your money!
♪♪
Hey, shouldn't you
be at home playing
with Barbie dolls or something?
[Tires screeching]
You're not cold in them
there hoochie clothes, are ya?
Do you know there's curfews
for little girls like you?
Do you want me to call
the cops or something?
Are you okay?
Yes.
Do you need my help?
I'll be fine.
Wh-where are you going?
Home.
All right, stop.
Stop!
Where is home?
Flaxfield.
That's where I'm going.
Look, I have a daughter
your age, there is no way
I would allow her to
walk on this highway
at night like this.
Now, we can either walk
together all the way there
or I can give you
a ride in my car.
Are you sure?
Yes, I'm sure.
You're gonna get yourself
killed out here.
Did you see that car?
So, what's your name?
Helen.
I'm Jack.
My friends call me
Dr. Jack.
Thanks for driving
me home, Dr. Jack.
No worries.
You're welcome.
So, uh, what the hell
are you doing
running around on a
highway this time of night?
I... I just need
to get home.
Okay.
Well, we'll get you home.
Thanks.
Been, uh, partying
with your friends?
I wasn't partying.
I know what it's like,
I was your age once.
But, I've gone
straight edge now.
You gotta be careful
what you put
into your system, you know?
Do you think if
someone's a good person
and they do something bad
or make a mistake,
that they can still
be a good person?
Well, yeah, of course, I mean...
You will meet people from
time to time that are...
Well, they're like syringes.
They just wanna suck the
life outta you, you know?
But, not everybody's like that.
I mean, hey, look at me.
I'm a good person.
Migrate to the
good people, you know?
How do you know who's good?
I'll tell you how you know.
You look 'em right
square in the eyes,
right down the barrel.
And if they flinch
or they blink,
then you know.
The eyes are the windows
to the soul, my friend.
If you look deeply into them,
you can see it all.
What's your daughter's name?
Uh, October.
What's your wife's name?
Francine.
Beautiful woman, Francine.
My best friend.
That's nice that
you respect her.
Oh, yes.
Yes, very much so.
Most guys don't respect girls.
Most guys just
take advantage of you
and they make you feel special.
And then they leave
you on a dirt road.
Hmm.
Well, there are many different
types of roads, Helen.
Some are smoothly paved in gold.
Some of them are
bumpy, rocky dirt roads.
Sometimes it's a choice
that you make.
Or a chance that you take.
Well, we're on our way home.
You're in good hands now.
Get some rest.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
♪ Tunnel vision hues
♪ tunnel vision hues
♪ entertaining
the masses ♪
♪ oh
♪ inflating
the evers ♪
♪ inflating the evils
♪ inflating
the egos ♪
♪ entertaining
the masses ♪
♪ oh whoa
♪ and we can't afford
the holy grail ♪
♪ there's nothing
for your voice to tell ♪
[Shouting]
[Grunting]
[Moaning]
♪♪
[Screaming, thud]
What happened?
We just hit a dog,
a big, black dog!
I don't know this street.
Where are we going?
We're just taking
a little shortcut.
A shortcut?
Flaxfield is right off the
highway we were on.
I don't understand.
Where are you taking me?
Trust me.
Taking a little
shortcut to avoid
the traffic on the freeway.
We'll be there soon.
Okay.
Whoa.
Where'd that come from?
Hey. Hey!
Where are you going?
Are you insane?
I was trying to help you!
Fucking whore.
[Car pulling up]
Sir, I'm in pursuit of a girl
that I believe was
just inside your vehicle.
She was inside the vehicle.
I was giving her a ride home.
Well, she started going
berserk on the highway.
I had to pull off the road.
I stop here, and she
gets out and runs off
into the woods like a maniac.
Where did she run?
She ran off
right in that
direction over there.
See, by the big group of trees.
Don't worry, baby.
I'm a doctor.
[Laughing]
♪♪
Whoa, child.
Are you okay?
What in the world are you doing
in these woods at this hour?
I'm lost.
Well, that figures.
These old woods are treacherous.
What's your name, girl?
You by yourself?
Helen.
I'm alone.
Well, uh, where are
you going, Helen, alone?
Flaxfield.
Ah, no worries, then.
You're not far from home.
You see that clearing there?
When you reach that,
the highway's straight
in front of you
through the woods,
you can't miss it.
You turn left at the highway,
it's just a short walk
down to the city limits.
Thank you so much.
I gotta get home.
No problem.
Don't go and get yourself
lost again now, you hear?
♪♪
[Kids laughing]
Helen, you can go in now,
it's been 30 minutes.
♪♪
[Door closing]
[Woman]
Helen?
♪♪
♪ Woke up now
♪ but with
the dream inside ♪
♪ it just sticks
♪ all over
the outside ♪
♪ sweat is running
♪ up and down
my side ♪
♪ Drain the blood
♪ searching for
a way out ♪
♪ toxins fill
my veins ♪
♪ I can't shout out
♪ senses filling
the night ♪
♪ oh, so loud
♪ mosquitomen all that I see
mosquitomen surrounding me ♪
♪ mosquitomen all that I hear
mosquitomen the end is near ♪
♪ whoo!
Ooh ♪
♪ Nothing escapes
hungry insect eyes ♪
♪ realizing there's no
place to hide ♪
♪ ears are filled
with horrific cries ♪
♪ mosquitomen all that I see
mosquitomen surrounding me ♪
♪ mosquitomen all that I hear
mosquitomen the end is near ♪
♪ ohh
♪ Mosquitomen all that I see
mosquitomen surrounding me ♪
♪ mosquitomen all that I hear
mosquitomen the end is near ♪
♪ whoo!
Ohh ♪
♪ Anger's born
nowhere too dark inside ♪
♪ and it gets me
in a hopeless fight ♪
♪ dawn appears but
day turns into ♪
♪ night
♪ mosquitomen all that I see
mosquitomen surrounding me ♪
♪ mosquitomen all that I hear
mosquitomen the end is near ♪♪