I can't breathe!
You know that movie's
gonna suck, right?
How you know it's gonna suck?
You know who that guy is?
Yes,
that's John David Washington.
Washington, right.
How you think Mr. Washington
got that part?
-Showed up to an audition,
did a good job--
-Audition.
That's Denzel Washington's son,
dude.
He doesn't audition
for anything.
It's called nepotism.
If you don't know anybody,
then you don't get anything.
You even know
who your father is?
Fuck you, fuck 12,
fuck Hollywood.
Get out there and protest, bro.
Come on.
Hey, the movie
might not be good, but...
shit, it'd be better
if I was in it.
Yeah, obviously, I would've
taken the chopper and all,
but, I mean, all the seats
were sold out.
And, you know, with Kobe--
God damn, RIP to him--
it's just too soon, baby,
it's just too soon.
But fuck me, I can't wait
to get out of this city.
Yeah, the fuckin' protesters
are all over the place,
just marching around and shit.
I mean, it's like,
give it up already.
You guys won, okay?
You all matter.
Oh, hold on,
hold on, baby.
I gotta do something real quick.
Yeah, you still there, sweetie?
Yeah, I can't wait.
Hey, hey.
- What the...?
- Fuck!
Get him!
Ho-ho-ho-ho.
Damn, it's kinda heavy.
No, no, no, no, no.
Be--be--be smart.
Hey, NYPD!
- Face the wall, face the wall!
Against the fuckin' wall!
Spread your fuckin' legs!
Listen to what I fuckin' say
to you, huh.
What the fuck you doing?
I saw you with something, huh.
What's in it?
What you got?
You got some drugs?
I saw something.
Oh, ho, ho, ho, ho.
-What's this?
-It's nothing.
-What is this?
-It's... my grandmother's.
Yeah sure, it's your grandma's.
It's mine now, cocksucker!
It's gonna look great
on my wife.
Oh, fuck, typical, man.
Crooked pigs.
Hey, you put your hands
on your head,
or I will light you up!
I hear the virus is raging up
in Rikers, motherfucker.
Dude.
Dude, are--are you okay?
You need me to call somebody,
an ambulance or something?
-Stop the--
-You fuckin' prick,
don't fuckin' touch me.
I'm gonna fuckin' kill you.
Hey, man.
- No no, I'm trying
to help you out.
I don't need your help,
nigger.
Fine.
-Shit.
-Fuckin' pig.
♪ Come to me, mama
Oh, yeah ♪
Right now, right now, yeah ♪
♪ Come on, baby ♪
Anybody ever tell you
you're a cute guy, Gus?
Eh, Jean-Michel, what's--
what the fuck, man?
How you doing?
Keep your distance.
I haven't come this far--
I don't have to get sick
from you.
You know, Gus, if you had
one of those masks on,
you'd be a little safer.
I'd be safer, but I wouldn't be
as good looking.
Because I'm trying to keep
those tan lines off.
So, Jean-Michel, you called,
you said you got something
you wanna show me?
Right, right.
Dude, I don't wanna touch that
if it's hot.
I don't wanna get my prints
all over it.
Are you outta your mind?
Dee, da dee, dee,
okay, let me see.
Wait a minute.
This can't be, man.
This is...
This can't be the thing
that I read about.
"Famed necklace stolen
from Christie's during looting."
Holy shit, "It was discovered
on Monday
that during the looting
that took place over
the weekend,
the storage unit for
the auction house Christie's
was broken into
and the items were stolen.
Amongst the stolen items
was a ruby necklace
named The Evening Sun
that was owned by Mary II
that is valued at..."
-Three million bucks?
-Shh!
There's crazy-ass people
around here.
Oh, yes, "Whoever stole this
is going to have
a terrifically difficult time
selling."
- Gus, come on, come on.
- Wait!
"A representative
from Christie's said.
The necklace is a museum"--
museum or museum--
"a museum piece."
- Who cares?
-"Its value lies in its craftsmanship and history.
On top of that,
we have notified--"
this is the problem,
"notified all dealers
and museums
to be on the lookout
for this piece.
We plan to get it back."
I don't know.
I think what you need to do
is take it back to Christie's.
I'm pretty sure they have
"anonymous drop", they call it.
They'll give you
some kind of a reward.
I can't take it back
to Christie's, all right, man.
They're not gonna give me
no reward. Just--just...
-Hook me up with somebody...
-All right, Just calm down.
-Would you please calm down.
-...who can give me
some real money for it.
Calm down.
It's okay.
Give me 24 hours.
But, Gus, I'm trying to get
outta town tonight.
Give me 24 hours.
I can't do this in a minute.
Call me.
You have my number?
You got my number?
Yeah, yeah, but I had to
get rid of my phone.
Listen, I'm gonna call you,
but it might be an unknown
number, all right?
Unknown number's fine.
I'll work on it.
I will work on it for you.
But you just keep yourself safe
in the meantime.
Answer your phone, Gus.
Answer your phone.
Ma?
Ma!
- Oh, Jean-Michel!
- Bluetooth paired.
What are you doing here?
-Oh God, you startled me.
-I'm sorry, Ma.
I was making some deliveries
in the area.
I wanted to come by, say hi.
You don't have to wear that
mask in here.
It's okay. I got my antibodies,
I'm fine.
I know you're a superhero,
but I don't wanna get you sick.
I got my antibodies, I'm fine.
Come here.
Of course.
I want you to take a look
at this piece.
I wanna get your opinion on it.
Do you know what it is?
No, I honestly have no idea, Ma.
It's the Pope, calling me
into the church.
Yeah, yeah, I see it.
I--uh, I see it.
God never tires
of forgiving us.
We're the ones who tire
of seeking His forgiveness.
Sorry, Mom, what,
what was that?
Oh, ah! it's just something
I've been thinking a lot about
that the pope said.
Hey, are you hungry? I'll make
us some veggie burgers.
No, no no, it's okay.
It's okay, really.
I'm getting outta town
for a few days.
I wanted to see you
before I left.
Oh.
So I'm cooking something for us
to eat.
I'm not letting you leave here
without a meal.
Ma, you don't have to cook
for me.
And then you can tell me all
about this trip you're about
to go on.
-You don't have to cook.
-I said I'm cooking.
Listen, son, I'm going away
for a while,
and I want you to take care
of your mother, okay?
I want you to know that
the world you're gonna
grow up in
is a lot better than the one
I grew up in.
But there will be struggles.
So you be strong.
You be good.
And you take care
of your mother.
I'm sorry, Pop.
I mighta fucked up
real big this time.
Hey, Ma, how's Clarice doing?
Uh, I think she's okay.
We--we don't talk a lot.
You know, I think she's real
stressed out about her job.
But at least she's got one,
right?
Look, tell me about this trip
you're about to go on.
No no, it's okay.
It's okay.
I really just gotta go.
There's this girl.
I don't wanna be late.
Is everything okay?
You're acting a little jumpy.
Everything's fine. I'm fine.
I'm fine, really.
Um.
Could I borrow some money?
Oh, so that's why you're here.
Nope. Jean-Michel,
I'm not giving you any money.
You can just take
your little girlfriend
and go where you wanna go.
You know what, Ma? I'm not
doing this with you today.
I'm a just gonna text you
when I get upstate.
Okay, but where are you headed?
Albany, Gloversville,
I don't know.
Okay, I love you.
I love you too, Ma.
Give me a hug.
Oh.
Hey, you found my shirt.
Thanks, Ma.
Jean-Michel?
Yeah, Shavinma?
I was just getting the mail.
Would you like to come upstairs?
Uh, no. No I can't,
I really gotta--
I haven't seen you for a minute.
Just for a second.
Just a second.
♪ I'm good at numbers,
Haven't you heard? ♪
- ♪ I have to control
I have lost everything ♪
Just a moment.
-Hello, Mrs. Coley?
-Uh-huh.
Have you seen your son recently?
I'm Detective Roberts.
This is Officer Ryan over here.
Shouldn't he be wearing a mask?
No, I haven't seen him.
And I think you need a warrant
to speak to me.
Listen, if he happens
to come by here,
would you please give me a call?
We really need to...
What's that smell?
I'm cooking. I've got something
on the stove that's burning.
Ms. Coley, listen, we just need
a few more minutes of your--
Fuck.
She's fuckin' lying,
she's holding something back.
Yeah.
He could be in there right now.
You're right.
What's the next move?
Let's get something to eat.
I'll think about it.
Hey, hold back a second.
I got an idea.
Hey, excuse me, ladies.
My phone just died.
I'm supposed to meet a friend
of mine here, Jean-Michel?
He's about my height,
short braids.
Yeah, yeah, he's upstairs.
You just saw him?
What room's he in?
He's here.
Oh, hey, Jean-Michel.
Is this uh, is this the new
Kristof video?
Yeah.
So what worried you so much
about what you saw
in the government's actions
yesterday?
Kristof, what we witnessed
yesterday out there
was an unprecedented assault
on our rights
as peaceful protesters.
I don't wanna watch videos.
I've been lying around
in my pajamas all day,
and I have to get ready
and go to work.
You still acting,
or what are you doing?
Acting? There hasn't been
any acting work for months.
I also kinda got tired of
playing the young Black waif,
the prostitute,
the go-go dancer,
the sexy friend.
Yeah, so I'm bartending now.
Well, I thought all the bars
were closed.
Well we have a takeout window.
What about you?
You still acting?
Nah, nah,
it's like you said.
Right, the whole industry
is at a standstill.
You still out in Brooklyn?
Yeah. Yeah, for now.
You know, I got all this
back pay to take care of.
Listen, would you wanna
hang out with me after work?
I think I get off at one,
and you could come over here.
I can't.
I got, I got something else
to do later.
Another girlfriend?
No, no. Um.
I'm getting outta town.
Okay.
Finally leave the city,
you know.
All right.
I can't believe I never been
out the country, you know.
I gotta go.
I gotta go to like Africa,
or like Europe
or something like that, right.
Yeah.
I wanna go to Paris.
But first I gotta go to work.
I gotta get ready.
Are you sure
you don't wanna come over later?
Yeah.
Yeah, no no, it's fine.
Um, you know, speaking of...
Shavinma, we really...
You know, I be...
Think you could loan me
some cash?
I don't have any money,
Jean-Michel. Sorry.
Police, open up!
- Shavinma.
- Policia!  Let's go!
Shavinma, get the door!
Give me a second.
Policia, let's go!
Detective Roberts with the NYPD.
Where is Jean-Michael Coley?
We heard he's staying here.
-Who?
-Jean-Michel Coley.
Um...
Who is it, Shavinma?
It's the cops.
Let 'em in.
Let's go.
-Dammit!
-Son of a bitch, fuck!
We'll get him next time.
We'll get him next time!
-Motherfucker!
-We'll get him.
Fuck, he is gone!
Bitch! This guy is making us
look like assholes!
Fuck!
Did you just take my picture?
-What?
-Please, don't, okay.
-No.
-Show me some respect, okay.
No, I did, I'm sorry.
I'm tired, and I'm not
your fucking art project.
I, I'm an ally, and an advocate.
I just, you had this incredible
look on your face.
It was beautiful, and I just
wanted to capture it.
You really should ask people
before you take their picture.
-Could I take your photo?
-No!
I'm sorry.
White people.
Hey, yo, excuse me.
-What's up?
-Where are you coming from?
You came outta nowhere.
I was at the bodega.
You know, they--they got
everything in there
except for a damn toothbrush.
Mm.
What's up? What's up?
Did you forget we were spending
time together today?
Um, I tried to call you,
but your phone keeps
going straight to voicemail.
Oh, my phone is messed up.
I, I had to get rid of it,
you know.
Why?
I could tell you
about that later.
What's up?
What you got going on?
I'm, I'm shooting some
press photos, maybe
for this, you know, famous art,
well, underground famous rapper.
So I'm meeting him
and his manager tonight
for a drink.
Oh, okay, underground famous
rapper, who is it?
Tyson Barrega.
Ooh, Tyson Barrega,
the alpha omega.
Yeah yeah yeah, I know that cat.
I got some of his songs
on my phone, yeah.
Well I had.
Your phone that is gone now?
Yeah, damn I gotta download...
That's dope, that's dope.
I'm sorry, that's dope.
I mean, it's bittersweet
because I was trying
to spend some time
with you today.
Well, you're just gonna
have to spend
some time with me manana.
Oh, manana, manana.
I am sorry, but I don't think
I'm gonna be around manana.
Oh, where you going?
I don't know.
Out west somewhere.
Out west?
Yeah.
You can come with me
if you want.
Go out west with you?
Yeah.
Come on, we've only been seeing
each other a couple weeks.
Yeah yeah yeah, but what a few
weeks they've been, right?
I mean, I been all right.
You been, you been
fuckin' great.
No, I'm serious, you can come
with me if you want.
Yeah yeah, I'll go away with you
and we'll be just like
Bonnie and Clyde.
Yeah, yeah, except
we gonna make it over
in the car in the end, right?
Car.
I'mma go up and change.
Mind if I, uh,
come up and join you?
Mmm, It's a mess up there.
Come on, you know I don't care
nothing about all of that.
No, no, I, for real,
it's, it's a mess.
Mind if I accompany you
to this meeting?
Yeah, you can accompany me
to the meeting.
I'll be right back.
All right.
I'm gonna see you later, right?
Charlie, oh, what the fuck?
I told you you could crash here
for one night! One night!
-I appreciate that, thank you.
-I need you to get the fuck out.
Pack up and go.
I'm watching
the new Kristof video.
I don't care if you're watching
Get the fuck out!
Okay, okay.
I could use a toothbrush.
♪ Did I really? Did I really
Blow your mind though? ♪
♪ Na, you got me confused
With your other fools ♪
♪ And that's why I got
Your wife on the line ♪
♪ And I hope she gets
Every single diamond ring ♪
♪ Niggas kill me
They put they fist up ♪
♪ Got you all thinkin' that
They meant other people ♪
♪ All on the stage like they
Motivational speakers ♪
♪ You pushing 40
With an 18-year-old shorty ♪
What the fuck?
Yeah!
Where did you get this car?
I told you, I...
Don't worry
about where I got it.
Just, just come on, get in.
Did you steal this car?
I didn't--I didn't steal it,
but--but--but, we should go.
Put your seat belt on.
We should go now.
So, where are you meeting Tyson
Barrega and his manager?
At the Great Lawn
in Prospect Park.
Okay, okay,
that's a real romantic spot.
Or practical,
for social distancing.
Mm. Of course, of course.
So, are you gonna tell me
whose car this is?
It's my car.
Okay, bullshit.
Bullshit.
Who is Cary Grant Carroll?
Is that you?
Cary Grant Carroll,
that's the dude
that I borrowed the car from.
Right, and his address
is right there so we can
bring it back whenever we want.
I am just saying that
if I were to steal a car,
I would've picked a nicer one.
Don't forget, I'm gonna be
parked right here.
I'll see you manana.
Mañana,  hey hey,
before mañana--
I'll be at the studio all day.
♪ How would you like to be
Satisfied with me? ♪
♪ I've been counting moments
So long ♪
Woo!
Hey.
Hey!
Woo! Not bad.
Merci.
Oh!
Audrey?
Hello, good to meet you.
-Hi.
-I'm Josh,
Tyson's manager.
-Oh, yeah, I'm sorry.
-Do that one, yeah.
Hi.
Actually, I'm not
too concerned about,
about the virus, so.
Oh.
Thank you for meeting me here.
Just thought, you know, this
was a good safe spot
to meet.
Plus, you know, any chance
to be in the park.
I love your look.
It's like you walked in off
a beach from some painting.
Just like sauntered in.
Thanks, I guess.
It's just an old sundress.
I like your shirt.
Does it say "Alien"?
Yeah, that's what I feel like
I am, an alien.
Like an alien trying
to break apart the system.
Now I got, I don't know,
despite my cynical heart,
I hope we're in the midst
of like a great awakening.
Do you know what I'm saying?
Did you, uh,
did you write that on there
with Sharpie?
Oh yeah.
Yeah, it's a handmade original,
worth some money someday.
Today.
Yeah, I think when we're forced
to devote ourselves
to scrap together a living,
it's like we're incapable
of understanding who we are.
But we've all been unemployed,
so we can all awaken.
What did you do
before quarantine?
I'm a full-time manager.
Is that a Patek Philippe watch?
Yeah, it's an heirloom.
Right.
No, yeah, I guess, um,
I guess we are asleep
for decades
and then everything crashes
and we all wake up.
Let's hope we wake up.
I think there's a lotta people
still fucking asleep.
It's like, wake up already,
you know.
Did you go to the protests?
Uh, no, I mean it still seems
kinda unsafe, right?
I mean, I see them
on social media, though,
and like share a lot.
You?
Oh yeah, of course you have.
I've been seeing your photos.
They're amazing, like brilliant.
Thanks. So, um...
where is Tyson? I thought
he was meeting us here.
Oh, no. Come on,
we're gonna go meet him
at a party nearby.
Don't worry, it's a rooftop
party. Lots of fresh air.
Okay.
-Hello?
-Yo, Gus, Gus.
-Jean-Mich--
-It's me.
-Dude.
-Hey, man,
tell me some good news.
Tell me you found somebody
who wants to spend they money.
Where are you?
This sounds really weird.
I'm at one of them,
the Wi-Fi kiosks, you know.
Hey, give me a second. Boom.
Oh yeah, talk to me.
Tell me what's going on.
You sitting down?
I got a deal.
I can get $200,000.
200K? You said the shit
was worth three million, nah?
You know as well as I do,
that thing is hot.
And this woman, she basically
is this rich heiress
and all she really wants to do
is keep it
in her private collection.
She can't show it to anybody.
She kept saying that.
I could never share it.
I can never wear it.
I can never share it.
You should be happy with that.
I tried other places.
That's the best I can do.
All right.
Okay, okay.
Yeah, I gotta bring up
something else.
I want a cut.
I want 25%.
You're fucking killing me, man.
25%'s a good deal.
It's probably what your agent
and your manager
would give you if they ever
booked a job for you.
-All right.
-Otherwise you wouldn't be
doing what you're doing.
Fuck me, all right, all right.
Gus, Gus, I get it, I get it.
You a businessman, you gotta
take your cut. Fine, whatever.
I wanna meet you tomorrow
night, seven o'clock,
GW Bridge, southeast side.
Little red lighthouse,
you know where that is?
Yeah, the little red lighthouse
under the GWB.
Right, the jeweler's gonna
be there too,
and he's gonna make sure
that it's all, uh, copacetic.
Hey, Gus, I gotta go.
Jean-Michel, seriously,
stay off the news.
I gotta go, man.
I'll talk to you later.
Hello?
He's on the run, man.
I know what that's like.
Jean-Michel, what are you doing?
I'm tired. I wanna be alone.
Audrey, I'm sorry.
All right, I'm sorry, I just,
I had nowhere else
to go tonight.
Jean-Michel,
no one is supposed to be
sleeping here, all right.
I'm not even supposed
to be sleeping here.
Listen, please.
All right, I'll be good.
I'll sleep on the floor
if I got to.
Fine.
You can come up,
but we're sleeping.
-I'm not in the mood.
-Thank you.
So, how'd it go with Tyson?
I didn't even meet Tyson,
just his douchebag manager.
Douchebag, wha, he tried to hook
up with you or something?
This manager, he was gonna take
me to a party
where I'd meet Tyson,
but Tyson wasn't even there,
So... yeah, I don't know,
probably.
Mm, oh, God.
It's times like these
that I wish I had a shower
and not just this bucket.
God, I...
I really hate
this fuckin' city.
I was just gonna say
how much I love it,
in spite of everything.
You know, if I could,
I'd run away to a place
where you could see the ocean.
Somewhere you could get
your food in the street.
Somewhere you might be able
to have a little bit of peace.
That reminds me
of this place I spent
a couple weeks in, in Morocco.
Yeah, I forgot you had
the chance to go to Africa.
Yeah.
Happiest time of my life.
I mean, definitely stressful,
but...
I learned more about myself
there than anywhere else.
For real?
Yeah, I mean,
that's where it all started.
The birthplace, Africa.
Yeah.
I mean, it's kinda different
for you, right?
Because you not Black.
Yeah, I know I'm not Black.
But it's where all humans
came from,
-the cradle of humanity.
-Right, right.
All, all humans.
Uh.
Yeah, no, I, I just hope I get
to make it back one day.
I thought you'd never been.
I--I haven't.
It's complicated.
You know,
it's in the blood.
So...
You gonna kiss me?
Yes.
But only...
if you promise...
next time you say please.
Jean-Michel?
Oh my...
No, it's okay. It's okay, sorry.
Sorry, I didn't... that's okay.
I'm awake?
I'm awake.
It's okay.
Here.
Some coffee, not much but ...
Mm.
I am awake.
-Mm.
-Sorry, yeah,
that's, yeah, it's hot.
It's okay. It's okay.
Remember when I first saw you?
In that play last winter,
before lockdown?
You were so mesmerizing.
I wanted to take
your photograph so bad.
Took a little while longer.
But...
Click, click, click.
Yeah, you got what you wanted.
What are your plans for today?
Nothing.
I'm...
going to Harlem at seven.
I gotta meet up with this guy.
If everything goes well,
I'll be outta town tonight.
If you want,
you could come with me.
We could drive away together.
So, what are you doing today?
What you got going on?
I'm shooting Barrega at five.
And then, um, I'm free.
I was thinking of going
to a protest.
I was thinking that maybe,
maybe,
you might wanna drive out west
with me.
Go out west with you?
I don't even know who you are.
And I don't really know you,
so...
Do you think
we romanticize outlaws?
You know, like,
because they live more free.
Like, they're not constrained
by the rules
the rest of society adheres to.
What are you talking about?
You know what I'm talking about.
I'm talking about Billy the Kid,
I'm talking about Jesse James,
I'm talking about Scarface.
Like...
why do we love criminals
and killers and--and crooks?
I don't know,
maybe people just wish
they didn't have to care,
right?
Maybe, maybe people
wanna be like the Terminator.
Right,
ah, you take what you want.
Ah, you don't care, ah!
Living absolutely free.
So people should be amoral?
I ain't say that.
Do you think that,
do you think that
morals are--are fluid?
What do you mean?
Like, do you think that
our morals are set
by when and where we were born,
by our upbringing?
What if, in another culture,
killing someone because they
own something that you wanted
was totally acceptable?
Like, I mean, eagles,
they're fighting
over scraps of meat
all the time.
Yeah, but we not animals,
though, right?
Okay, so which one is it?
I don't know what
you getting at, Audrey,
but if you talking about racism
in this country, it's wrong.
It's always been wrong.
Of course it's always wrong.
That's not what
I'm talking about.
Look, listen to this.
Okay.
"This is why the most dangerous
creation of any society
is that man
who has nothing to lose."
Yeah, yeah,
that's James Baldwin, right.
So now you quoting
James Baldwin to me.
Just tell me what's going on,
Audrey.
I am trying to decide
if I should
run away with you or not,
okay?
I can't just drop everything
and run away with you,
even if I like you.
Like me? You like me?
I tell you what, Audrey,
I am so glad that you...
like me.
What's with the sarcasm?
I love you, Audrey.
I love you, and I wouldn't be
sitting here asking you
to come with me, if I didn't.
I love you
because you're special.
Because you mean
something to me.
I mean, shoot,
you're like the first white girl
I ever fell in love with.
Huh, I mean,
if anybody found out about this
back home,
they wouldn't believe it.
I'm gonna throw up.
-White girl?
-No, that's what I--
-I didn't even mean it
like that.
Just a white girl,
just a white girl.
That's not what I meant.
I mean, one day, I really wish
we could just like,
see beyond race.
This country
is built on race, Audrey.
You can't see past it.
It comes through the pores.
Well, maybe I'm an optimist.
God, you know,
when I was 12 years old,
my father told me
I couldn't marry a Black man?
When I was about the same age,
my mom said,
don't end up
with no white girl,
she'll ruin your life.
Man.
But they're still our parents.
Yeah.
And we...
still got them, right?
You got what you got.
I got what I got.
Everybody out there, they got
whatever they working with.
You know, we all got
what we got, and we just
trying to do the best
we can with it, that's it.
I just hate that the only thing
people see is my whiteness.
It's not the only thing I see.
I'm serious.
Hey, I...
I see all of you.
If I think about it, I think
I seen about every inch of you.
It's rude to point.
Come on,
I wanna take a picture of us.
You got this.
I have to see how it works.
♪ I know I can do it alone ♪
-♪ All on my own ♪
-Oh, okay.
I'm gonna look off again
for this one.
And you can look into camera.
-Okay?
-You're gonna look away?
-Yeah.
-Scared of me or something?
No!
Wow, these are
really fuckin' good.
You're brilliant. You're like
a genius or something.
I'm not a genius.
This morning, while
you were still sleeping,
I took a look at the news,
and the new Kristof video.
Yeah, what'd you see?
You're the cover
of all the papers.
Kristof dedicated his entire
episode to you.
Fuck, really?
No, they are vilifying you,
saying you're the face
of everything wrong
with the movement.
Fuck, are you serious?
That's not true. That's not it.
Are you being for real with me?
Look.
Fuck it,
is that my fuckin' headshot.
White cop killed by Black man
ignites debate and fury.
What you...
Get the fuck...
He died?
Yo, he fuckin'... he died?
I wanna see the Kristof video.
Good morning, everyone.
Sorry about the eye.
I did not sleep well. It's been
kind of a rough night.
Today, I had something
completely different planned,
you know,
just check the calendar.
You know what, don't look
at that calendar too closely,
because you know, then where
would the surprises be?
What I'm trying to say is I had
a completely different show
planned for today, but then,
you know, whack,
slapped in the face
with a new catastrophe.
But right, isn't that
this whole year, right?
You plan one thing and then,
new catastrophe.
New catastrophe.
And what is today's new
catastrophe, you're asking?
You guessed it.
Jean-Michel Coley.
But you know what?
We're not on lockdown anymore.
And I don't wanna just talk
to you about this myself,
so let's go, come on.
I'm here with Rebecca Harvey
and John Stanfield,
two organizers
of the Black Lives Matter
movement here in Brooklyn.
I imagine you guys
saw the video,
and just wanted to get your
thoughts on Jean-Michel Coley.
Just an hour ago,
the president, you know,
stated that this killing
should completely discredit
the entire movement.
Look, I have no love
for the president,
but I do not condone violence
either.
Mr. Coley should not have shot
this cop,
and I worry that,
I worry that this will set
the entire movement back.
Kristof, yes, Mr. Coley
should not have shot the cop,
but as you could see
in the video, there is no sound.
And we don't know
if he was threatened or not.
Now let me tell you something,
as a Black man,
we are taught to be submissive
to the police
so we won't wind up dead.
Even if we are submissive
to the police,
we still wind up dead.
I don't know, maybe Mr. Coley
got tired of it or whatever.
So do you think Jean-Michel
Coley should turn himself in?
-Yes.
Fuck this, fuck this.
What did the president...
No, no, I don't wanna know
what he said.
I don't care what he said.
I don't fuckin' give a shit
what he said.
-What did he say?
-He, he said
that this proves that
he was right and that
the movement is dangerous
and full of bad people,
and that, you killing the cop
is an attack on America
and now,
you're an enemy of the state.
Yo, fuck him, fuck his hair,
fuck his little fuckin' ties,
fuck the KKK members
he's related to.
Why'd you do it?
I just wanna try to understand.
This young white dude
left a briefcase
right in front of me
while I was working.
You know he was wearing a suit,
a fuckin' ascot,
some shit like that.
I figure it's an opportunity.
I take the briefcase,
I run down the alleyway,
I look inside the briefcase,
fuckin' necklace inside.
It's a necklace
with a ruby on it.
I don't know how much
the ruby is worth,
the necklace is worth,
but I know it's a lot
because it's a gun
right next to the motherfucker.
Then a cop comes
around the corner.
But first I get to throw
the gun in the trash, right,
because you gotta be smart,
you gotta be fuckin' smart.
And the cop runs up behind me,
he's like, yo,
put your hands up on the wall,
put your hands
against the fuckin' wall
or I'll fuckin' blow you away.
He's fuckin' patting me down,
got his hands up
in my fuckin' junk and shit.
Then he reaches inside
my pocket, he pulls
the necklace out.
He's like, oh yeah, yeah yeah,
this is too good for you.
I'mma give this to my wife.
A fucking crooked ass cop,
talking about
"I'm gonna light you up."
Yo, Audrey, I made a move.
I made a move because he...
made a move.
Fuck, man, I don't know.
You have this necklace
on you right now?
Yeah.
Is this real?
It almost looks fake.
Oh, it's real.
It's real.
I think it's called
the--The Evening Sun.
It was at a jewelry store,
Christie's,
over by Fifth Avenue.
They took it during the looting
after the protests.
It's worth like three mil.
Uh.
Yeah.
Nobody wanna touch it, though.
It's a museum piece, so.
Look, I know a guy
who knows this heiress,
and she's gonna buy it
for like 200K.
I'mma take the deal,
and he gonna take $50,000
as a commission.
I get to walk away
with 150 large.
It's enough to start...
something.
It's enough to start a life.
I don't wanna have to
do this alone.
I can, if I got to, but
yo, I really want you
to come with me.
I don't want you to do it alone.
But I don't know, I'm scared.
Right, right, nah, you're right,
because this is fucking crazy.
Right, this is fucking crazy,
because I killed
this fucking cop,
even though he was probably,
he was probably gonna shoot me,
but fuck it, right?
This is fuckin' nuts.
I just, just, just couldn't end
up in jail.
I couldn't do this.
Listen, all right, just...
Look, we don't have to go away
forever, right?
It's not till the end of time.
I just...
I just need
a little bit of time.
Then we can figure out
how to make ends meet.
We could, I don't know,
find a job
or open up a shop or something.
What about acting?
Acting?
Shit, Audrey,
I could do my thing anytime,
anywhere, no matter what,
as long as I got you.
You know, I could,
I could write books in exile,
like, like Dostoevsky.
Do you really think
we can get away with this?
Yeah, I mean,
with the right amount of money
in this world,
you could do anything.
Do you trust this guy
that's selling it for you?
Enough.
Where are you meeting him?
It's this little red lighthouse
under the GWB.
Okay.
You get the money
and I'll finish my shoot
and I'll meet you
and we'll go away together.
For real?
I don't know, maybe.
I mean,
New York's at a standstill.
There's no work.
I owe back rent on this studio.
Maybe.
Hey.
Maybe's fine.
I'll take what I can get.
What you doing?
A bad Marcel Marceau
impersonation.
I don't think it's so bad.
What time are you meeting Tyson
and his manager?
I think at five.
You gotta get going, right?
Yeah, probably.
Don't you have to get going too?
Yeah, yeah, I gotta,
I gotta brush my teeth.
Hey, hey, you can't go out
there like that.
What you mean?
I mean, I'm not even supposed
to be living here.
Put on a shirt.
And, hello? A mask.
You right, you right, you right.
Make sure you follow my lead,
okay?
-Yeah, you got it.
-♪ I'm good with numbers, ♪
♪ haven't you heard? ♪
♪ I have to control
I have lost everything ♪
That was quick. Sorry,
I thought I kept it unlocked.
I thought you were the girl
that paints down the hall.
Can I help you?
I'm Detective Roberts.
This is Officer Ryan.
You Audrey Lasko?
Yes, I am.
Believe you had a relationship
with this guy?
Or that he's here right now?
Excuse me, you can't fucking
barge in here like that!
And wear goddamn masks.
Yes, Jean-Michel and I had
a fling a few weeks ago.
I've seen his face
all over the news.
He killed a cop, right?
-Yeah.
-Look,
I don't know what to tell you.
I haven't seen or heard
from him in weeks.
I have a photo shoot I have
to get ready for in an hour,
so unless you two
have a warrant,
I'm gonna kindly ask you
to leave.
This chick must watch
a lotta procedurals.
Don't call me a chick.
Are you supposed
to be living here?
I don't think you're allowed
to be living in these stu...
I think we're gonna find out
pretty quickly
if Miss Lasko's lying or not.
All we have to do
is go to your super
and get access to those tapes.
Do you have the super's number,
ma'am?
Sorry, I don't.
Audrey, you do know that
withholding evidence
is a felony?
You can go to jail for it.
Pretty girl like you, upstate.
They'll mess you up.
We'll be in touch.
Let's go.
This is Detective Roberts
of the NYPD.
How you doing today?
Listen, I'm gonna need some...
I'm gonna need some footage
from you, from the building.
We got reason to believe
that um...
"What happens
to a dream deferred?
Does it
dry up
like a raisin in the sun?
Does it fester like a sore?
And run?
Does it smell like rotten meat,
or does it
crust, sugar over,
like a syrupy sweet?"
Sweet, sweet.
"Does it,
does it sag like a heavy load?
Or...
does it explode?"
Jean-Michel, what the hell
are you doing here?
The whole city
is looking for you.
Hey, Blake. I figured
you'd be here, man.
I just wanted to come by,
see you.
See this space before I...
before I got out the city.
Well you, you not gonna call
the cops on me, right?
No, I'm not gonna call
the cops on you,
but you know, seeing your face
across the TV,
you know it's got me fucked up,
right?
I mean, I can't believe it.
Sounds like you shot that cop
in cold blood.
Blake, it wasn't like that.
All right, I was scared.
I didn't wanna die.
I don't wanna go to jail.
We all get scared, but we have
to fight that fear.
If you're scared,
then you're foolish.
And if you're foolish,
then you're a goner.
Yeah, yeah, naw, I know. I know.
Your mother must be torn up.
Have you seen her?
Have you thought about her?
Yeah, yeah, I saw her
a little while ago,
but that was before
all the news hit.
Yo, if you trying to make me
feel bad,
I already feel as bad as I can,
so...
Jean, I'm not trying to get you
to do anything.
Blake...
I just wanted to say hi.
And--And tell you that,
you know,
this theater saved my life.
Look, I know things are heated
right now.
I don't like the cops myself.
I nearly got beaten up
at a protest about a week ago.
But you're putting out fire
with gasoline.
I want to defend you,
but what you did was wrong.
You fucked up,
and you're talented too.
And you fucked that up as well,
too.
You need to
do the right thing
and turn yourself in.
It'll help all of us.
It'll help the movement.
Nah, yo, I can't do that.
I can't go to jail, I...
Shit, would you?
Then you need to get
as far away as you can
from here.
To another country.
Blake?
You need to go.
Leave through the rear,
I'll stall her.
I'm here. I'm already here.
Were you talking to somebody?
No no no, I was working
on a monologue.
You know, I used to be
a great actor myself.
I still am.
Like, she forced me
to turn my camera off
while I was having
a massive freakout.
-Ah.
-Oh, she called you out.
She called you all the way out.
- Don't do that to me.
Don't be doin' that to me.
Oh my gosh, yo,
it's Jean-Michael Coley.
Ooh.
Oh, it's the Jean-Michael Coley.
You're my fuckin' hero.
You are my hero.
Don't say that.
Just chill, Just y'all--
The way you shot, bow!
Just keep it down.
Keep it down, all right.
Let's take a picture.
Come on, come on.
One picture. One picture.
-Just one?
-Nah, nah, I'm good.
Take multiple.
Just make sure y'all wait
to post this
like three to five business
days, please.
Okay.
Oh my God, so good.
I got 'em, I got 'em.
All right.
Hey, y'all listen, all right.
Don't go out and do what I did.
What?
It was wrong. It was wrong.
Fuck the police, man. Fuck them.
And, and, and they wrong too.
They wrong too.
But what I did was wrong too.
All right, don't kill no cops.
Don't kill nobody.
-Fuck that.
-That's some bullshit.
Aren't they people too?
Right.
Yo, white lives matter.
Life is about living.
The world don't need that shit
right now, all right.
Y'all stay up. Y'all stay safe.
Where you going?
Wait, wait.
Wait to post them pictures,
all right.
No, bro, whoa.
Until when?
-Show me the pictures.
-Where are you going?
Wait, let me see.
Hi.
Hey, and so we meet again.
You look lovely once again.
Thanks.
I'm so sorry about
the other night,
but, uh, my man is here today.
Tyson, this is Audrey,
the photographer.
-Hi.
-Hi, Audrey, I'm Tyson Barrega.
Nice to meet you.
Yeah, we'll do the elbow.
We can do the double.
Yeah, I don't know why.
I like the double.
Sorry I didn't make it
to your event last night.
I was actually at another event.
Got a little high,
toking it up,
lost track of time.
But you know. So what do you
have in mind for the shoot?
I was thinking maybe we would
start on this playground.
You know, just like,
a kid in the neighborhood,
super casual, nothing crazy.
All right, I'm feeling that.
Does that feel good?
Yeah, but do you think
we'll be needing Josh here?
No, I think we're good.
Yeah, I mean...
Well,
all right then my dude
I love this with the crown
and the lion earring.
-Like a wild thing.
-Yes, yes!
- All right, let's do this.
- Very cute.
Ooh, yeah, I love the arms up.
Mm-hm.
Gorgeous.
So you grew up in the Bronx?
I did, born and raised.
How's your summer been?
Better than expected, actually.
I mean, all the rich white
folks are gone.
Oh yeah.
No tourists.
Folks are in the street
fighting for justice
and freedom and love.
It's been great actually.
Are you nervous about the fall?
Like the fall season,
or the fall of society?
The fall season.
Like, are you nervous about
a second wave or the elections?
I think I'm worried about both.
Think I'm worried about it all.
Feel like I've been living
in this fuckin' bubble, yo.
Like this city
sure ain't this country.
That is for damn sure.
It's another world once
you get out the city.
I don't know, I don't feel
afraid like when I'm in Paris,
but I feel afraid in Oklahoma.
It's like the guests
on Kristof's show said.
This country's still
in the middle of a Civil War.
You watch Kristof?
Don't we all watch Kristof?
I know him.
If you ever wanna take some
pics with him, let me know.
Oh, yeah, I could, I probably
will take you up on that.
-Word.
-I'm just gonna switch
to the digital,
because I just ran out of film.
So, where are you from?
I'm from Miami.
Ooh, I love Miami. Beach vibes.
I love the arts.
I love the people.
And why'd you come to New York?
Um...
You know, I think, think I had
big dreams you know, and
Miami just got a little,
a little too small.
My mom died, and I saved up
a bunch of money
and bought my one-way ticket
here.
A girl of action.
Boom, boom, boom.
I like that.
I don't know about all that.
You ever see this short film
by Michel Gondry?
About a guy who has a camera
for a head
and he keeps bumping
into everything.
It's kind of how I feel.
Nope, no fuckin' idea
what you're talking about.
But I do know,
if you wanna be free,
you just gotta be free.
You just gotta take that jump,
just get out there and be free.
I don't know.
I just believe in love.
Erotic love, romantic love,
love for your brothers
and sisters.
Otherwise, what else is there?
You just die, figuratively.
You got someone special?
You got a lover?
Um, yeah.
I think so.
You think?
I have my hesitations.
Fuck that!
If you love somebody,
you just gotta love them.
You just gotta take that plunge.
I mean, what if you died?
You just got Corona next week
and just died, boom.
What are you gonna do?
Yeah.
Yeah, I don't know.
You wanna take a look?
These are actually looking
really good.
- Let me see, let me see, let me see.
-  -Let me show you.
Ooh, I'm a fuckin' king.
-Yes.
And, I think there's some narc
motherfucker
over there looking at us now.
Oh, fuck, that's a cop
that's following me.
Do you mind distracting him?
Not at all.
I got you, I got you.
I think I'm gonna go see
about that boy.
-Okay.
Okay, take that plunge, girl.
Officer?
Officer, are you an officer?
Officer, excuse me, Officer.
I mean, you ain't gonna
tell me nothing
about that grease
you got up in your hair?
Jean-Michel, what's happening,
man?
Is that like a vacuum cleaner
or something?
Dude, you're getting famous
all of a sudden
since I last saw you.
Hey, keep it low-key,
huh? Keep it low-key.
Yeah, right.
Listen, what's the deal?
You, uh--
Come over here. Let me talk
to you for a second.
So, I thought you said
that the heiress
was the one who was gonna be
buying the necklace.
What's up?
-That's right.
-So what's up with this dude?
That's Franchini.
He's a jeweler.
He's gonna check it out,
make sure it's authentic.
So you got me here
under a bridge
in a strange place,
a new fuckin' face,
just to get it checked out?
Hey, what is the deal?
What's going on there?
Is there a problem?
No, there's no problem.
No problem, no problem.
Okay, so let's see this
necklace then.
Come on, over here by this rock.
Okay, give it to me.
I need to take a sample
of the metal.
Is it okay if I make a tiny
scratch on part of the necklace?
Yeah, do what you gotta do, man.
This is real.
The gold is good,
and the ruby is good.
But I wanna check a few things
just to make sure
it's the actual Evening Sun.
I'm gonna take a couple photo,
okay?
Hey, do what you gotta do.
Just be quick about it,
all right?
I know we gotta be cool
and shit, Gus,
but all I'm saying is we really
out here in the open.
We out here, out here.
We real conspicuous right now.
This is New York. No one cares.
I could be doing this out here
naked, and no one would care.
So what's up? We good?
I need to take a look at it.
Soon as I get in front
of a computer.
I need about 15 minutes.
Shall I call you when I know?
Nah, no no no, we,
we gonna go with you.
You know, my uncle was a cop.
Yeah, what the fuck is that
supposed to mean?
It means I need this job
because I need a job right now.
And I'm a professional.
That doesn't mean I like you.
Franchini, I told you
I'd vouch for this guy.
Whatever you've seen
on television,
I'm telling you he's a good guy.
And, Franchini,
I know you need the money.
All right, you can come with me
to my office.
But, you wait outside
while I verify the necklace.
All right, fine.
So let's go. Andiamo.
Hey, bro,
you're gonna follow us, right?
Yeah, yeah yeah, yeah. Um...
You know, I was waiting for
somebody,
but I'll be right behind you.
All right. So listen,
I know you don't have
your phone, so stay close.
-Come on.
-Yeah, I got you. I got you,
I'll be right there.
-Right behind you.
-Cool, cool cool.
All right.
He's waiting for somebody.
Miche!
Audrey!
Oh my God.
-I love you.
-We have to go.
We gotta go. I love you too.
We gotta go. We gotta go.
I'mma take your bag.
We going. We going.
I'mma take the keys.
You driving, all right.
Its' better, It's better,
trust me.
-I'm driving. Okay.
-We gone, we out we out,
let's go.
Which one is it?
Quick, quickly.
Yo, you can, you can follow
that black SUV up there.
So, did you sell it?
No, no, it's not that easy.
The heiress had her jewel man
come,
and now he's taking pictures
and double-checking
on the internet,
making sure
that's The Evening Sun.
It is The Evening Sun,
but he's gotta make sure
that things are good on his end
so that we can get
outta here, hopefully tonight.
How did things go with Tyson?
Good, he told me to seize love
because it's all we got.
Nice.
And?
I'm good.
You're good?
So you--you got me?
I got you.
All right, all right.
I might have fucked up,
but you got me
so we gonna be all right, right?
Does this car have a stereo?
Yeah.
And in other news,
the search continues
for Jean-Michel Coley
as the shooting
of a white officer
by an African American man
continues to cause
reverberations
through a city and a country
already in the midst
of a major reckoning on race.
Some prominent Black leaders
have called
for Jean-Michel Coley
to turn himself in,
while the NYPD union leader,
Franco Smith, has declared
that this killing shows that
the vilification
of the NYPD has gone too far.
All right.
You know, I didn't even mean
to--to do all that.
May--maybe, maybe I should
just, you know, turn myself in.
No, you're not turning yourself
in, Jean-Michel.
I just don't wanna take away
from the movement, you know.
What you did wasn't right, but
the system is fucked
and it's rigged, against you.
You fucked up
in a fucked up world, so...
you run.
Yeah, but two wrongs
ain't never made a right.
You know, and I, I...
Who knows?
It's bigger than me now.
I gotta think about
the movement.
I gotta think about my family.
Yeah, just,
just pull up right here.
I think, I think this is it.
Franchini and I
be right out.
It'll take maybe 15, 15 minutes.
15 minutes, Gus.
You say 15 minutes,
I believe you. You the man.
I'm the man.
You gonna come through
this time, right?
Yeah.
- Watch me.
- Yeah.
Uh, I think I'm gonna go
into, uh, bodega,
get something, to eat,
or just stretch my legs.
I don't know, you need anything?
Are you sure it's safe
for you to go out.
Yeah, yeah, I'll be fine.
It's right there.
I'll be good.
Okay.
Jean-Michel?
Shavinma, hey.
Damn, you the most famous
brother in New York right now.
Yeah, but, you know,
it's not really like that.
Why didn't you tell me?
What are you gonna do?
I'm gonna run.
I'm getting outta town. Hey, um,
matter of fact, could you,
could you tell
my moms that everything'll
be all right?
Okay.
You think, um,
you think I'm making
the right choice running away?
You should definitely run.
Do not turn yourself in.
Okay.
Yeah.
Jean-Michel?
Be careful.
Be safe.
Who is she?
That girl you were talking to.
Oh, that's, that's Shavinma.
She lives upstairs from my mom.
Why is she looking at me like
that?
We used to date.
Did she just say White girl?
No, no. No, no.
She said, she said,
she said "why, girl?"
Yeah, wh-why. Why you with him?
Hey, Franchini said it's legit.
Of course he said it's legit.
It's legit.
Yeah.
So what's up? What's next?
The heiress is gonna send the
money over to him tonight.
I'll get it,
bring it over tomorrow,
the deal'll be complete.
Whoa whoa whoa, wait,
tomorrow?
Best I could do, sorry.
Fine, fine, Gus, fine,
it's fine.
You don't have a place to stay
tonight, do you?
Brooklyn, 101 Johnson Street,
Number 209.
It's a cyc studio
I help my brother run.
And uh, the heiress,
she's tough.
Franchini, they just want me
to do it.
They want me
to hold onto the necklace.
Gus, are you serious?
I'm serious, but what
I'm asking you, is it cool?
Because if it isn't,
I will tell them to fuck off,
and you could have it.
But I really think
we oughta follow their lead.
Yeah, yeah, Gus.
You know, uh,
you know, you know
I trust you, right?
- Okay.
- You be safe.
You be safe.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Yeah, tomorrow.
Fucking tomorrow.
I think I've shot
in this building before.
Hm. Yeah?
Yeah.
He said 209, right?
Yeah, yeah,
but how can you tell?
None of these doors
got any numbers on them.
Audrey? Audrey, is that you?
- Oh shit.
- Oh my God, it is you.
Ha, Mark.
Air kiss, mwah, air kiss, mwah.
Oh my God,
what are you doing here?
You don't have a shoot
right now at like 11 at night.
Tell me, tell me, how have you
been surviving the summer?
Weirdest summer ever,
am I right?
Hi, I'm so rude.
Hello, I'm Mark.
Uh, Booth.
Booth, weird name, but okay,
elbow handshake.
Ah. I'm all right, thank you.
So tell me, tell me.
So yeah, we are shooting
some publicity shots for him,
because he's dropping a single
tomorrow,
and this magazine
just asked for a couple shots
and we found this place.
What about you?
What are you doing here?
This is where my studio is.
It's right around there.
Just some late-night painting.
I've always been my best
in the middle of the night.
Hm.
Do you know where 209 is?
Oh, Just around there,
to the left, one door down.
Great, thank you so much.
Yeah, oh my God,
great catching up.
You should come by
when you two are done.
I've got a jug of spicy
margaritas in my fridge.
Oh, nice.
Wow, huh.
This space is really
fuckin' dope.
Is this where y'all take
your pictures and all
that stuff?
Mm-hm.
Yeah.
Oh, man.
Do you think it was crazy that
I gave Gus the necklace?
Like, like, like, you know,
he probably gonna do
what he's supposed to do,
but as soon as you trust
somebody, they...
Chill, you're good.
You trust him, right?
Yeah, yeah, you right.
You right.
And then tomorrow
you're gonna get
the money in the morning, right?
Tomorrow morning.
I mean, I don't see why not,
right?
I mean, this, this heiress,
she wants the necklace
real bad,
and she getting it for sale, so.
You scared?
Running away?
No.
Nah, n...
You?
Yeah.
You know what
I'm really scared of?
What?
You know, the news,
politicians,
everybody got an opinion.
Nobody... wants to talk to me.
People wanna vilify me.
People wanna
call me a hero.
I just don't wanna leave
without saying my piece.
I just wanna tell people
what I'm thinking.
Well, what are you thinking?
I, I, I don't fuckin' know.
I don't fuckin' know.
What if we...
what if we could get you
on Kristof's show?
You know, like a,
like a Kristof exclusive,
so you could tell your side
of the story.
Yeah, I mean, that,
that would be perfect.
But, but he's like famous,
famous.
He got like 30,000 DMs right
now. I don't even know him.
Tyson Barrega knows him.
He said he could connect me.
Okay, I'm gonna try,
why don't I try?
Let me, let me just try.
Okay, I'm gonna call him
on WhatsApp,
because I--I think that's harder
to trace.
Hey, Tyson.
Hey, yeah, it's Audrey.
No I'm good, I'm good.
Um, remember how
you were saying you could
get me in contact with Kristof?
Yeah, I was wondering if you
could give me his contact?
I'm with Jean-Michel Coley
and...
No, it's not like that, but
he would like
to do an exclusive
on Kristof's show.
Oh, okay.
Cool, yeah yeah yeah, I got it.
Thank you, thank you.
Okay.
Calling Kristof.
Hello?
Hi, this is Audrey Lasko.
No, yeah. You don't know me.
I'm a photographer. Tyson
Barrega gave me your number.
Yeah, hi. Um...
I'm with Jean-Michel Coley
right now.
No, still at large.
And, he is actually
probably going to be
disappearing more permanently
tomorrow.
And he'd like to do
an interview on your show
to tell the public
his side of the story
regarding the shooting.
Would you be interested
in an interview?
Yeah, of course,
it would be remote.
Yeah, we have Wi-Fi here.
Okay, cool, uh, we will set up.
Thank you.
Kristof will interview you
on his show in an hour.
Are you fuckin' serious?
I, I don't know what the fuck
I'm gonna say.
I'mma set up some lights.
Oh, that looks good.
Thank you.
Oh, wow, you really did
your thing with these lights.
I am a professional.
I know this.
Ready?
Hello, Jean-Michel Coley,
I'm Kristof.
-Welcome to my show.
-Hey, Kristof,
good to meet you. I'm a big fan.
Well, thank you for watching.
It's always nice to meet a fan.
Yeah, no, I got a ton
of respect for what you do.
It takes a lot
to go out every day,
you know, it's intense.
Yeah, and it's, it's tiring.
Uh...
But I can't stop myself.
It's like,
it's like some
sickness inside me.
I feel you, I feel you.
It's like a fire in your belly
or something, right?
Well,
thank you for joining me
and giving me this exclusive.
All right,
so how do you wanna do this?
Do you wanna just tell me
your side of the story?
Yeah, that sounds good.
That sounds good.
Look, I know what I did
was wrong.
It's not like I don't have
morals or something like that.
I just reacted impetuously.
Impulsively.
Because I thought
I was gonna die.
That cop said that
he was gonna light me up.
It's the same shit they said
to Sandra Bland
before she got murdered.
And, and, and I know if you
go back and look at the video,
you could see that I tried
to help him, right?
I tried, but he pushed me away.
He pushed me away me,
he fuckin' spit at me.
He called me...
The officer in question
didn't want my help.
You know, Kristof, you ever,
you ever been stopped
while you was driving?
No, no reason at all.
You ever been followed
in a grocery store
while you was picking up
your almond milk?
I think I've actually never
been pulled over while driving.
Never?
You gotta be fuckin' kidding me.
I don't even wanna talk
about it anymore, man.
You ain't even fully
like white white, right?
Shit.
Listen, I--I snapped.
I was tired.
And I fuckin' snapped.
So if you know what you did
was wrong,
are you planning
to turn yourself in?
No.
No, no no.
I mean my--my--my pops died
in jail. I ca... I can't.
Did you ever read
Crime and Punishment?
By Dostoevsky?
Yeah, I read it, but,
you know, it's been a minute.
Yeah, I been thinking a lot
about the dude in that book.
Now Dostoevsky writes that
the man with a conscience
suffers whilst acknowledging
his own sin.
And that's his punishment,
and his prison.
So you're saying that
you're in your own
prison right now?
Yeah.
Ay, metaphorically speaking,
we all are, right.
Nah, I just,
I get to take mine with me.
I'll tell you this, though.
I ain't gonna end up
in one of them physical ones.
They're gonna have
to put me in a box first.
You okay?
Yeah. Yeah, I'm good.
You sure you're okay?
You seem a little off.
Nah, I'm all right.
I'm all right. Um...
You know, a little tired.
Feel kinda bad for dragging you
into all of this.
You don't have to come
if you don't want to.
I told you I want to.
You know, you kinda crazy.
You know that?
But for real,
I could turn myself in.
I could go to jail.
I could... get three hots
and a cot,
and some peace and quiet,
if I fight for it.
What are you talking about?
It's nothing. It's nothing.
Come on, come on.
Let's wrestle.
I don't feel,
I don't feel like wrestling.
-Let's go.
-Hey, ho.
Come on.
Oh, oh, okay, all right,
here we go.
I am supreme!
Hey, that must be Gus.
See, we're gonna be okay.
Miche.
Yo, Gus. Come in,
come on, come on.
So,
-this is it.
-Yeah?
This is the money.
I already took my cut,
so it's all yours.
Holy shit, Gus.
Gus, you really did it, man.
- Yeah. Yeah, I did.
- Fuck.
You really fuckin' did it.
Gus, man, thank you.
Thank you.
Ah, I guess we all good, right?
All good.
Don't know why I did that.
You okay?
I'm okay. I'm good, I'm good.
Audrey?
Who's that?
Audrey? Audrey, you there?
It's this artist I know
who has a studio on the floor.
I'll handle it. I'll handle it.
-What's up, Mark?
-I thought you'd still be here.
Uh, I need to speak with you.
Oh boy.
What's up, Mark?
Yeah, I racked my mind
all night, and then it hit me.
That guy you were with,
I know who he is.
He's Jean-Michel Coley,
the cop killer.
The murderer.
No, it's not. He's a singer.
Don't lie to me.
I looked him up,
I studied his photos.
In spite of the mask, I never
forget someone's eyes.
I know it's him, honey.
Mark, what did you do?
You called the cops, didn't you?
It's for your own good.
Oh, you fucking...
He's dangerous. I'm sure
he's just using you.
You don't even know
anything about him.
Fucking annihilate you.
Oh my God, my nose. You bitch!
Shit, shit, shit,
he called the cops.
We gotta get outta here.
What the fuck you mean
he called the cops?
I thought you said he was cool!
I thought he was,
but he definitely isn't!
What the fuck?
Come on.
All right,
the money's in this bag.
You, you, you grab
your camera bag.
Let's go, let's go.
Let's go.
-Wait, I need to tie my shoes.
-Yeah, go ahead.
Hold on,
I need to tie my shoes.
Get the keys in the, in the bag,
it's the front pocket.
Freeze, NYPD!
Okay, okay.
Let's go.
Shit! Shit!
Shit!
Something's wrong with the car.
Girl, we gotta go. We gotta go.
Jean-Michel, Audrey, freeze!
We don't wanna shoot!
Fuck, I can't get a fuckin'
angle on them.
Is that the only fuckin' word
you know? Shit, fuck!
Stop, goddammit.
Shit.
Fuck, eight minutes,
eight minutes.
What do we do?
Did we lose them?
I think so. I don't see nobody.
Oh my fucking God.
Babe, you know you a little bit
of a bad-ass, right?
Baby, I can literally
throw up right now.
Throw up?
You musta been like
track superstar or some shit
like that in high school.
Yeah.
We gonna be all right.
What's next?
What do we do next?
We gotta figure out how
the fuck we gonna
get outta here.
How the fuck
do we get outta here?
Shit.
Hey, yo, isn't that...
Wait, I think I have an app for
that.
The Revolt shit,
like the scooter?
Freeze!
Fuck, fuck, fuck.
Fuck!
Baby!
-What are you doing?
-What the fuck, man?
-He's the fuckin' cop killer!
Shut up!
Baby, baby, can you walk?
No.
I blew my fuckin' load.
You got another clip?
We gotta get outta here.
We gotta fuckin' go right now.
Jean-Michel, Audrey, you don't
have to do this!
Turn yourselves in.
Okay, shoot him.
Just fuckin' shoot him!
He's right there!
He's a fuckin' cop killer.
Pull the trigger.
Pull the fuckin' trigger!
What are you waiting for?
Get off me. Get off me!
I'm making sure
you do fucking desk duty
for the rest
of your fucking career.
You're gonna get written up
for this!
-Me?
-Yeah, you! I'm reporting you!
You don't fuckin' deserve
that fuckin' badge.
Hey.
How'd it go?
It was good. I think I got
a couple good photos.
Ah, that's good.
Good is always good, right?
How's the editing?
It's actually almost done.
Exciting. That was fast.
Yeah, yeah, I got this fire
in my belly right now.
Or this sickness.
You, uh...
are you feeling okay?
I can't do this anymore.
This is...
all too lonely.
Lonely, Audrey, I'm right here.
I been here this whole--
But I miss
everything.
And you've...
been distant.
I'm leaving.
-I'm sorry.
-Don't apologize
for what you're feeling,
all right.
Uh, I get it.
I get it, you know.
You gotta do you, and this,
I guess this ain't you.
Ah, shit, it was never
your fight anyway.
Are you leaving today?
No.
Tomorrow.
Mm.
Then, why don't we
try to make the most
of what we got?
♪ I knew I could do it alone ♪
♪ Knew I could do it alone ♪
♪ All on my own ♪
♪ On my own ♪
♪ Alone isn't lonely ♪
♪ The world is my only vice ♪
♪ Death to the old me ♪
♪ There's a new me inside ♪
♪ A new me inside ♪
♪ Day's time ♪
♪ When right ♪
♪ I'll get it ♪
♪ Expect it ♪
♪ I'm growing ♪
♪ No holding back ♪
♪ Which way's the way
To my ground ♪
♪ You could not slow me down ♪
♪ If I fell,
Then I will take off ♪
♪ I look to my own thoughts ♪
♪ Look to my own thoughts ♪
♪ Raising my motion,
Raising my motion ♪
♪ Take control of emo... ♪