[toilet flushing]
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
[water running]
["Just in Time" by Chris Price]
♪ The sky will fall ♪
[electric razor buzzing]
♪ The waters will rise ♪
♪ Four horses comin', and
they talk about demise ♪
♪ 'Cause we showed up just in
time for the end of the world ♪
♪ Just in time for
the end of the world ♪
♪ What a beautiful
day today is ♪
♪ What a shame it
is to say goodbye ♪
♪ What a terrible fate ♪
♪ The masters of
everything fading away ♪
♪ We don't waste time ♪
♪ We don't like to wait ♪
♪ Me and my friends are
always fashionably late ♪
♪ But we showed up just in
time for the end of the world ♪
♪ Just in time for
the end of the world ♪
[snoring loudly]
[rapid knocking]
[cans clattering]
[exhales loudly]
[hammer pounding]
What the hell do you want?
[door creaking]
[door thuds shut]
[panting]
Shit. [exhales sharply]
[phone dialing rapidly]
[ringback tone ringing]
[Operator] Welcome
to Know How Bank's
automated phone system.
Please enter your
account number.
[exhales sharply] Oh, come on.
[numbers dialing rapidly]
[Operator] Please enter
the last four digits
of your social security number.
[numbers dialing rapidly]
Please enter your
secret password.
[exhales sharply]
[numbers dialing rapidly]
Your current available
balance is $280.20.
What?!
[Operator] To talk to a
representative, press one.
Will you-
- [Operator] Please wait
while we connect you
to the next available
Know How banker.
The current wait time is
one minute and 13 seconds.
[hold music playing faintly]
Okay, come on, come
on, come on, come on.
Come on, come on, come on.
[ringback tone ringing]
- Hello?
- Hi, Jackie.
This is Sid Smith, your
tenant at 3282 Franklin.
Really?
I'm confused.
I just got an eviction
notice pinned to my door.
[Jackie responding
faintly over phone]
But I paid April, like
always, on auto-payment.
[exhales sharply] Well, why,
why didn't someone call me?
[Jackie] We did, three times.
I'm sorry. [exhales sharply]
I don't know what happened.
I've been goin' through
some stuff lately.
- Thanks for holding-
- Oh, wait, hold on.
That's the bank
on the other line.
I'll call you right back.
[Know How Banker]
How can we provide
excellent service for you today?
This is Sid Smith.
[Banker On Phone] Mr. Smith,
the identification process
is now complete.
What can I help you with today?
Wait, are you a
robot or a real person?
[Banker On Phone]
My name is Daniel.
Are you a robot?
[Banker On Phone]
My name is Daniel.
- Thank you.
- Fuck!
[Daniel] I'm sorry, I
didn't understand that.
Continue with the questions.
[Daniel] Okay, I can do that.
What can I help you with today?
Last time I checked, I had
over three grand in my account.
Now, there's less than $300.
That's almost $3,000 missing.
You wanna tell me what
happened to my money?
- Okay.
- Huh?
[Daniel] Let me take
a look at your account.
Yes, please.
[Daniel] Mr. Smith,
I see an issue here
with your checking account
that may directly
answer your question.
The IRS sanctioned a levy,
a direct withdrawal from
your checking account
on Monday, March 28,
for the sum of $2,700.
[scoffs] A levy, a what?
They can't do that.
[Daniel] I'm sorry,
please repeat the question.
That's my money!
The bank's supposed
to protect my money,
not give it away
without informing me!
[Daniel] Is there anything
else I can help you with today?
Fuck!
Thanks for using-
[laptop snaps loudly]
[intense dramatic music]
[panting loudly]
[under breath] Fuck.
[inhales sharply]
[groans loudly]
[panting continues]
[inhales sharply]
Dude, I think Ms. Ramirez
has the hots for you, man.
She was looking at her coffee,
and she looked at me and
said, "Mucho caliente."
I knew she wasn't
talking about the coffee.
She was talkin'
about you, my boy.
Yeah, yeah.
[knocking on door]
Just me, man.
- Well, well, well, Mickey.
- Sup?
What can I do
you boys for today?
So, we got a
first time customer.
Never smoked before.
So, who did I bring him to?
Sid.
Sir Sid, at your service.
Yeah, I've smoked before,
but it's good to meet you.
Come on, man, you don't
have to be like that.
It's all right.
I got shit that will knock
your dick into the dirt.
You're gonna be happy
you smoked this weed first.
What are you lookin' for?
So, we need five
grams of your best Kush.
Don't give me that Reggie, man,
'cause last time you gave me
that Reggie, it did not hit.
You got it, Mickey.
That'll be a hund-o.
[rock music playing faintly]
[inhales sharply]
I'll be right back.
[door creaking]
[door thuds]
Yo, his shit is fire.
Top shelf.
It better be, for $20 a gram.
[rock music continues]
Sure this shit will be-
[door creaking]
What?
You were gonna say somethin'?
- No.
- No, no, no, no,
no, no, no, bro.
It's all cool, man.
- We're just lit up, man.
- I'm just messin'
with you guys, calm down.
Relax.
Five g's of the Kush.
[Both] Woo.
What, what?
[drawn out chuckle]
Give me that, man.
You two gotta be
careful with that shit.
Make your kids
come out wrinkled.
- Ooh, shit.
- Vicious shit.
Yeah.
Very funny.
Hm.
- Freebie.
- Oh, man.
For my regular customers.
Peace out, G.
[snaps fingers]
Peace. [imitates explosion]
Hell, yeah, let's get high.
Another satisfied customer.
[rock music]
[door creaking]
[door thuds shut]
[video game powers on]
Yo, yo, yo, LoganRun,
it's Challenger.
I'm back.
What's crackin', brotha'?
[Logan] Yo, Challenger.
Splatter on, brother, what's up?
Just givin' some high
schools that 420 love.
Everybody needs the green.
[Logan] [chuckles] The
Robin Hood of Silver Lake.
We should meet and
smoke one day, for real.
I got some killer shit, too.
You'd trip, and my pad is sick.
There's always bitches
hanging out here
and gettin' high and shit.
Yeah, you always say that.
Still waitin' for the invite.
[Logan] Hey, timing
and lighting, bro.
I need the action,
that's for sure.
[Logan] Yo, on the
balcony, upper right!
[gun firing rapidly]
Crack a sledgehammer!
Nah, I'ma stick
his head up his ass.
No, hold him!
I'll pop him.
Ew!
[loud sound effects]
Guts galore!
[Logan] I'll mash his nuts,
you pop his eyeballs out.
Double power-up, fools!
Yeah, mash him!
No, no, take the tunnel!
[beastlike growling]
So, uh...
How do you get the
girls to come by?
[Logan] What, seriously?
My natural charm, bro.
Jesus, son.
No, I mean, like,
how do you meet them?
[violent squelching]
Ew, that was fucking gross!
[Logan] Turn him inside out!
Guts galore!
Power-up!
Power!
Yo, Tinder.
Dating app.
You're not on there?
No, why, should I be?
[Logan] Pfft, you
missin' out big time.
- Really?
- Yeah, son.
It's a free-for-all, and
the girls are thirsty.
[Game Character]
Enter the war.
So, I'm goin' into war.
Yeah!
Now, stick his head up his ass!
[Game Character
growling indistinctly]
Fuck!
Help me!
Help, Logan!
- Fuck!
- [growling] Game over.
[rock music playing over radio]
[coughing] This
shit's the bomb.
I told you, son, I got you.
[coughing] Oh, I
can fuck with that.
Oh.
Easy, boy.
Don't go gettin' the fear on me.
Good weed will do that you.
I'm not an amateur, man.
[dramatic music]
[water trickling]
My name is Sid Smith.
No.
Challenger.
Height, 5,9".
Weight, 165.
Hair, yes.
Age...
[inhales sharply]
29.
[rock music playing over radio]
Are we safe here, bro?
See, you're startin'
already. [chuckles]
What?
Fear.
[scoffs] Shut up, man.
What, we all live
in fear in L.A.
Not me, man.
You should be.
The big one.
The earthquake, bro.
[inhales sharply] Dude, the 9.0.
It's just a matter
of when, not if.
[faint electronic music]
[phone scrolling]
[Sid's Mother] Sid.
Sidney.
Your brother wants
to speak to you.
[door creaks]
[door thuds shut]
[faint bass music]
[phone chimes]
- [phone chimes]
- I'm looking for a rich,
older woman, who needs
a sexy young man...
No, sexy, young bull
to get her off.
A sexy seductress...
looking for...
a mild-mannered boy-toy.
If you want it, [slurps coffee]
I got it.
Shut the, earthquake man.
Look, wouldn't you
rather know the facts?
I'm just tellin' you.
I know the signs.
Be ready, bro.
Prepare.
There's no way in, no way out.
Freeways fall, the grid's down.
There's no more water, power,
no money, ATM, bank,
boba, nothin', bro.
We ain't gonna
have nothin', bro.
Not even Splatter online.
We're gonna have to sit
there and play Campaign mode.
Done that 100 times
already. [scoffs]
Stop fuckin'
with me, bro, man.
What?
It's just the science.
Take it, man.
- I'm stoned enough.
- Amateur.
[exhales loudly] And...
Choose profile picture.
[phone beeping]
[mumbling to self]
No, no.
Bingo.
[metal music playing over radio]
I don't know,
Mickey, man, that's...
That weed ain't right, man.
You good, bro?
You look like you
smoked crack, not weed.
You tweakin'.
Yo, it's, that,
there's fuckin'
crack in that, man.
No there's not, bro.
- I've been smokin'-
- Yo, [stammers]
it's laced, man.
That's fuckin' crack, shit.
Sid's crazy, man.
Sid wouldn't do
me like that, okay?
This is good shit.
There's fuckin' PCP
in that shit, man.
You playin' with me right now.
No, I don't feel...
[sputters lips]
Oh, God.
- Oh, God.
- You're for real?
Your heart beatin' like crazy!
This is not a drill!
Sid!
♪ Kill everyone ♪
[knocking rapidly]
[panting]
Twice in one day, huh?
No, it's Daeg, man.
He's freaking out.
He got way too high.
He says he wants to go
to the fucking hospital.
What?
He doesn't need to go
to hospital, all right?
Just buy him a
candy bar or Coke,
take him for a walk around
the block or somethin',
just don't fuckin'
bring him here, okay?
Where is he?
- In the car, outside.
- What?
He's been here all fucking day?
Dude, what the
fuck did I tell you
about doin' this
kind of shit, huh?
You trying to get
me busted, huh?
- Huh?
- No.
I will cut you off, bro.
I mean it.
[door slams shut]
[exhales sharply]
[scoffs]
- [phone chimes]
- You've got a match.
"I am rich and dangerous,
"looking for a
young man to spoil."
Perfect.
[exhales sharply]
Yo, yo, yo, LoganRun, you there?
What's up?
[Logan] Yo, what up?
I took your advice,
signed up for Tinder.
[Logan] Smart move.
Bro, remember six months ago,
when we fought the
triple pack from Norway?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, one of those fuckers
- was on here tonight.
- Really?
Who?
[Logan] Thorgensen or
whatever, you remember him?
Pfft, fucking pussy viking.
[phone chimes]
Dude, some chick
responded already.
[Logan] [chuckles] Told you.
Hold on, she
left me a message.
"Sid, I wanna see you tonight.
"You sound hot and
exciting, like a tiger.
"Send me your address.
"I'll be there at 9 PM
sharp, love, Junebug."
- Score.
- Holy, shit, bro.
She's hot, she's 30.
I've never been with
an Asian girl before.
I gotta clean up my place, man.
I'll be back on later.
[Logan] You're gonna
last about a minute, bro.
No, bro, at least two.
[objects scuttling loudly]
[bed creaking]
[drawer slams shut]
- [rock music]
- Oh, yeah, get him, get him!
Crash over!
[chainsaw buzzing]
- Dude, there's hundreds of 'em!
- Disgusting!
I love it!
Nice!
Bro, that's so fucking gnarly!
Crush 'em all!
[door knocking]
Oh, shit.
What time is it?
- Fuck, that must be her.
- God.
- I gotta go, bro.
- Good luck, playa'.
[door knocking rapidly]
[faint electronic music]
[exhales sharply]
[door creaking]
Hey.
You must be Judy.
Who else would I be?
Who are you?
Uh, I'm Challenger.
Are you the same
guy in the photo?
Well, yeah, a
couple years ago.
More than a couple.
I clean up pretty well.
You said you were 30.
I am 30.
[door thuds shut]
What kind of a
name is Challenger?
Uh, my handle.
Well, Challenger,
I think you are
very naughty and very silly,
telling tall tales on
your dating profile,
could get a boy like
you in a lot of trouble.
Maybe.
Maybe I like trouble.
Wow.
So, Challenger, have you
ever played master and servant?
Yeah, I love Depeche Mode.
He serves a 12-inch.
What?
Nothing.
I... [exhales sharply]
look, I honestly didn't think
anyone was gonna show up.
I'm just trippin'
that you're here.
Take off your clothes.
Hm.
[chuckles under breath]
[thuds loudly]
♪ Love me now, on
the last drop ♪
[high-pitched groaning]
♪ Funky now, still
I won't stop ♪
Slow down.
Take your time.
♪ Ask me again, tomorrow ♪
[chuckling]
♪ Ask me again tomorrow ♪
[zip tie zipping]
Ow.
♪ Funky now, on the last drop ♪
♪ Funky now, still
I won't stop ♪
♪ Ask me again ♪
[knuckles crack]
♪ Tomorrow ♪
It hurts.
It does?
Well, it's supposed to hurt.
It's supposed to hurt
just a little bit,
so try to take it,
you stupid baby.
Take it.
Because then, it's gonna
get really, really fun.
- I like fun.
- Do you?
Yeah.
Ow!
Stop!
Stop biting me!
[music grows in intensity]
Ow!
♪ Fuck it ♪
[truck humming]
[dramatic music]
[straining loudly]
[grunting loudly]
[computer ringing]
[groans loudly]
Come on.
[groans loudly] Yes, yes.
Ah.
[groans loudly]
Ow.
[video game powers on]
You there?
Yo, LoganRun.
It's Challenger.
[Logan] Yo, what's up?
I've been on for hours.
Where you been?
[grunts] I'm tied up, man.
[Logan] Oh, you've been busy.
I'm about to log off.
No.
I'm tied up, literally, man.
The Tinder date.
She came over here and
zip tied me to the bed.
I'm stuck.
[Logan] [chuckles]
Hey, shut up, bro.
You're funny.
Bro, I'm bein' serious.
I need help.
[groans] And I'm stuck!
[Logan] [laughing]
Dude, stop it.
You're killin' me, man.
I'm loggin' off,
I got shit to do.
Don't, please.
I'm not jokin' around.
I need you to come
here and untie me.
[Logan] [laughing]
You crazy, man.
I'll talk later.
Wait, don't hang up!
[brief logoff music]
Ugh!
[groans]
[straining loudly]
Why?
Why?!
- What'd you get on that test?
- Why?!
I don't know, maybe a C minus.
I think I failed.
I'm gonna have to take
it again tomorrow.
[door knocking]
[exhales loudly]
Sid?
[door knocking]
Sid, you home?
Sid?
[door knocking]
Should we just
come back later?
Yeah. [scoffs]
Come on.
[door knocking]
[faint dramatic music]
Sid?
[door knocking]
Fuck.
[phone dialing rapidly]
[phone vibrating]
[game ringing]
- [game powers on]
- Yo, LoganRun, you there?
[Logan] Yo,
Challenger, what's up?
I need you to come here, man.
I'm still tied up.
[Logan] [laughing] Bro,
that shit's gettin' old.
Fuck!
Help me, please!
It hurts!
I need you to fucking come here!
[Logan] A-Are you crying?
[crying softly]
I'm in serious pain.
She zip tied my hands and feet.
[panting] Come on, man.
You live in Silver Lake.
I will give you money.
[Logan] Are you
fucking with me?
Bro, how long have we
been playing together?
- A year.
- Yeah, that's right.
You know me.
[panting]
3282 Franklin, a bungalow.
The back door is open.
Please, man.
I need your help.
[Logan] Why you
puttin' this on me?
[groans] 'Cause
you're all I got, man.
Besides, you're the one
who told me to do Tinder.
I wouldn't have met
that chick, otherwise.
She was a psycho, zip
tied my hands and feet.
It hurts, I gotta take a piss.
I need you come
here and help me!
[Logan] Bro, we play online.
That's it.
I don't know you like that.
I don't wanna physically
meet you and shit.
Remember the
Crystal Tower, huh?
I rescued your ass three times.
Saved your ass three
months of catch-up.
[Logan] [scowls] I knew
you were gonna say that.
I fuckin' knew it.
Please!
3282 Franklin.
Hurry.
I will never ask you
for anything again.
I swear it.
[Logan] Fuck!
- Fine!
- Fuck, thank you.
Thank you.
[brief logoff music]
Fuck.
[cries softly]
[traffic hums]
[gate creaks shut]
[door creaks open]
In here, man.
What the fuck?
Dude, she zip tied me, bro.
In the kitchen,
there's some clippers.
Hurry.
I gotta piss so bad, dude.
All right, all right, all
right, relax, relax, relax.
Oh, I'm in agony!
[silverware clatters]
Hurry!
[straining] Oh, thank you, bro.
[grunting] What the fuck?
[exhales loudly]
Thank you, man, you saved me.
[grunts loudly]
Uh, okay, yeah, I'm
officially freaked the fuck out.
[urine trickling distantly]
[Sid] Dude,
thank God you came.
I thought I was gonna die.
What the hell?
You're not 20.
You are an old motherfucker!
What are you, 50?
[groans] No, man,
I just turned 40.
[Sid moans]
- [toilet flushes]
- You're a liar.
What's your game?
- Huh, you catfishing?
- No.
You trying to trick me?
No.
I feel really bad, bro.
Let me make it up to you,
'cause I got smoke.
Yeah, I don't know, man.
I gotta get going.
Oh, come on, man,
just one smoke.
Come on, sit down, sit
down, please, sit down.
- All right, one smoke.
- Thank you, bro.
Hey, give me just one
second, I need to change.
- Yeah.
- Damn, man.
This is embarrassing.
Yeah, no, no problem.
[Sid] I thought she
was gonna eat me, man.
Eat you, huh?
[exhales loudly]
I'm still hurtin'.
[panting]
Whew.
Shit was starin' straight
into my eyeballs all day.
That was the real torture.
[lighter clicks]
[groans]
[inhales sharply]
Oh, it's so good.
Careful, this shit's strong.
[coughing]
- Told you.
- Shit.
So, what's wrong with you, bro?
Why you have some stranger
danger come tie you up?
Man, that shit just
happened so fast,
and I was into it.
She jumped me, and
everything was cool,
and then, boo ya.
Psycho kamikaze.
[exhales sharply]
So, uh, what?
Just you live here?
Yeah, kind of a hermit.
I like it simple.
Man, the lights are dope.
Full emergent, bro.
Perpetual night.
Check it out, even comes
with mood lighting.
Click on the blue square.
[deep bass note plays]
- Pretty dope, huh?
- Ah, tight.
I got fucked.
My job was taken by a robot.
Rendered useless by machines.
Hit me hard a couple years ago,
and that's when I
stuck to gaming.
So, a robot took your job?
Pfft, that's fucked.
Why do you think
I'm called Challenger?
'Cause I never win at anything.
I've never beaten you in a game.
Yeah, that's right.
Never.
That's why I lied
about my age, man.
Look, I don't blame
you for being mad.
I'm a loser.
[scoffs] Nah, nah.
[inhales sharply]
You're funny, bro.
You're all right.
I just need to start winning.
[Logan] Yeah, you
just need a little bit
- of luck, that's all.
- Right?
Hey, I noticed these.
You buy all these
lottery tickets?
[Sid] Yep.
Five years worth.
I mean, you can't win the
lotto without luck, right?
That's what separates the
winners from the losers.
[inhales sharply] You know,
I've never had much luck.
[Logan] Well, then,
that's the issue.
Oh, yeah?
Where do I find luck?
Around the corner,
perseverance, and opportunity.
Mm, [inhales sharply] at
least that's what my mom said.
Perseverance and
opportunity, I like that.
Yeah.
I mean, find luck, and
you'll be laughing.
I used to laugh a lot.
Honestly, bro,
I am high as hell.
I gotta split.
Ladies to see.
[exhales loudly]
Thanks for helping.
You saved my life.
Bros?
Take care, man.
And listen, don't let no
more crazy bitches up here.
All right?
I think I'm gonna
delete the app.
Yeah, you should.
Hey, uh, you get that
good shit on the regular?
- Any time you want.
- Yeah?
Let's swap contact info.
- You got it.
- Yeah.
- Sid Smith.
I'm gonna keep
you as Challenger.
- Call me whatever you want.
- Yeah.
Logan Gibson.
Nice to meet you.
[phone chimes]
Hey, you have some
good shit, by the way.
Keep it.
Take it with you.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
I can fuck with that, thanks.
Go find that luck, man.
[snaps fingers]
Wait, wait, wait,
come back here.
Trade me.
Pfft, I will
definitely trade you.
Appreciate it.
Hey, go find that luck.
Perseverance and
opportunity, brother.
See you in the
game. [door thuds]
[dog barking distantly]
Feel free to come by
and hang out any time.
I'm always here.
[door creaking]
[door thuds]
[keyboard clicking]
L, U, C, K.
Enter.
Oh, what's this?
[keyboard clicking]
24-hour supervised self-burial.
Luck.
[upbeat music]
Hi, everyone.
This is Sasha Molotov,
coming live to you,
straight from my bedroom.
Today, we're going
to meet Sergei Rutka,
who reads lot of stories
online about self-burial.
Yikes.
He decided to try
it for himself.
He was convinced
that burying himself
would bring him good
luck and prosperity
for the rest of
his life, forever.
Let's check it out.
[pig oinking]
So, I watch these vloggers,
these dudes, they do
it on the internet.
Poof, next day, they get money.
Poof, next day,
they got girlfriend.
So, I say to Ivan,
"Ivan, put me in a box.
"We both share in
this fortune, no?"
I help him.
[accordion music]
All right, don't be imbecile.
Don't fuck this up, idiot.
Next day, he come,
he dig me out of box.
We walk down the street,
down there, I see envelope.
50,000 rubles.
50,000.
Then, I enter this contest.
God damn, bro, we won a
refrigerator, brand new.
Wow, I'm glad everything
worked out for Sergei.
Whew, next, we're going
to meet Olga Volkov,
a girl who knows luck and
will do anything to get it.
[Olga speaking in
foreign language]
[Translator] I
was very scared,
but I managed to conquer my fear
and endure the whole
night underground.
[coffin creaking]
[coffin thuds]
[theatrical shriek]
[Olga speaking in
foreign language]
When I came out, I had
no luck for a week,
but then, I landed the
perfect job and found Dimitri,
the man of my dreams.
[Olga speaking in
foreign language]
Be a millionaire.
[laughs]
[cash register chiming]
So, everyone knows
Maksim and Mikhail.
[water splashing]
I bet that you didn't know
that they also did
this challenge.
[speaking in foreign language]
[Translator] I've been down
here for 12 hours so far.
I feel so, so scared, but
I have plenty of water.
I can't wait to get out
and be a rich playboy.
That's crazy.
[Translator] I'm feeling
a bit claustrophobic,
but if Maksim can last
all night, then so can I.
Oh, my gosh.
So scary, oof.
Thankfully, it's the reason
of all of their success.
All of it.
Let's take a look.
[speaking in foreign language]
[Translator] We
model three years.
No job, we do self-burial,
and boom, everybody wants us.
Inground pool, bitch.
We won so much money.
You can, too.
Ah, yeah.
[crickets chirping]
[gravel skidding]
[branches rustling]
[water sloshing]
[faint electronic whirring]
[intense dramatic music]
["Pulling Teeth" by Chris Price]
♪ Hold you up to the light ♪
♪ Think I love you ♪
♪ And it's just like ♪
♪ Pulling teeth ♪
♪ See the girls on the street ♪
♪ See the junkies ♪
♪ And it's just like ♪
♪ Pulling teeth ♪
♪ You and me ♪
♪ We're not good people ♪
♪ We don't have
patience for the world ♪
♪ And our friends, and
all their problems ♪
♪ 'Cause it's just like ♪
[brakes screeching]
♪ Pulling teeth ♪
[bike clattering]
Asshole!
[tires skidding]
["Pulling Teeth" by
Chris Price continues]
[doorbell dings]
Hey, Sid, what's up, buddy?
Hey, Vinny.
One lotto ticket, please.
Yeah, I was expecting you.
Did you ride all the
way from Silver Lake?
You know it.
You know, they sell
tickets there, man.
You won't hurt my
feelings, trust me.
You won't hurt my feelings.
Oh, come on,
you're my lucky star.
If I'm your lucky star,
you're fucked big time, okay?
- Usual numbers?
- No, not today.
Let the machine pick.
Let me try my luck
and go totally random.
Great attitude.
[News Anchor] The jackpot
is simply too hard to resist
for those who rarely play.
[lottery machine whirring]
The California jackpot has
been record-breaking in sales.
Remember, you won $500 before?
Maybe $5,000 this time.
Your lips to
Buddha's ears, buddy.
You know money won't buy
you happiness, Sid, right?
No, but it'd sure
buy a lot of weed.
And weed makes
the world go 'round.
- Sounds like 420 to me.
- That makes the odds
292 million to one, and
the chances of winning
don't necessarily increase
the more you play.
[doorbell dings]
Last year, Americans spent...
Here.
Fresh new batch.
Careful, buddy, it's strong.
Good shit, man.
Like back home.
It's some of the best
I've had in a while.
Keep it.
- Really?
- Yeah, really.
- Forever?
- Oh, yeah.
I'll see you at the
next ticket round down.
Good luck with the ticket.
Thanks, Vinny,
I'll see you around.
[bike brakes screeching]
[grunts]
[truck horn honking distantly]
[doorbell chimes]
- [door creaks open]
- Hello.
Oh, hi.
Uh, I'm looking for Logan.
Logan?
Uh, and who are you?
I'm Sid, his friend.
Are you his girlfriend?
No, I'm his mother.
Oh, sorry, ma'am, my bad.
[chuckles] It's not a problem.
Come in, Sid.
So, what do you do?
Uh, me?
Uh, I'm a small
commodities trader.
Really?
Yeah, for a few years, now.
[chuckles] Okay.
- You have a nice place.
- Thank you.
Thank you very much.
- Logan is right through here.
- All right.
- Okay?
- Awesome wall paper.
Ah, Logan?
[coughs abruptly]
Logan, what's up?
You've never introduced
me to Sid before, Son.
Yeah.
[chuckles sarcastically]
What are you doing here?
I have some amazing news,
man, I have to tell you.
- Okay, um-
- I'd like to hear it.
All right, Logan was just-
- No, no, no, no,
no, no, no, outside.
Whoa, you didn't even
finish your breakfast.
Oh, yeah, uh, I'll
finish it outside.
Mom, it's delicious, thank you.
10 minutes, five minutes.
30 seconds, two
seconds, let's go.
- Outside.
- Nice meet you.
No, yep, thanks so much.
Thanks.
Thanks, Mom.
What the fuck are
you doing here?
I have to tell you something.
You will not believe it.
Did I invite you here?
Well, no, I was
just stoppin' by.
You forgot to mention
the part about living
with your mom, by the way.
[sighs]
Guess that makes us
even on the bullshit.
We play video games
online together.
We are not friends.
I helped you out last night
because I felt
sorry for you, man.
I don't need a
friend in real life.
Can I just tell
you why I came?
- Bro.
- It's important.
It was your idea.
Okay.
You said I had to
find my own luck, right?
Yes.
Well, I found it.
[upbeat electronic music]
Look.
People in Russia are
burying themselves
for 24-hours, for luck.
It's a 24-hour
supervised self-burial,
and it works, bro.
People are gettin'
all kinds of lucky,
gettin' jobs, finding money,
girls, all kinds of shit.
Shh!
Okay, and?
And, and I'm gonna do it.
I'm gonna bury
myself for 24 hours,
and that's how I'm
gonna find my luck.
It worked for all those
people in the video.
- You're crazy.
- I'm serious.
And I want you to supervise it.
You're gonna bury yourself
in a box for 24 hours,
because you think it's
gonna bring you luck?
Do you hear yourself, man?
It's a hoax.
Look at the videos.
It works.
Okay, that's it.
You gotta go, okay?
Get your shit and let's go.
Come on.
Go, go.
[phone chimes]
Here, I sent you the
video, just watch it.
- That's all I ask.
- I'll watch it,
I'll watch it, please, just go.
You can't show up here
unannounced, man, it's not cool.
Dude, you always invite me.
Okay, all right, all
right, I get it, go, please.
- Jeez, okay.
- Jesus Christ.
- Just watch the video.
- Okay.
Okay.
Thank you.
[imitates explosion]
Hey, going so quick?
Yeah, sorry for dropping
by unannounced, my bad.
Oh, no, come by any time.
Logan needs friends.
He's always up in that room
playing those video games.
Yeah, with me, sadly.
Guilty culprit.
Ah, well, at
least you're honest.
I like that.
Thanks, Ms. Gibson.
Make it Diane.
Diane.
- Thanks, Diane.
- Take care, Sid.
Ride safe.
- How's it goin'?
- Hey.
Returning.
All right, Sid,
you can go back.
Thank you.
[faint hip hop music]
Hey, Sid, how you doin'?
V, my favorite bud-tender.
You shaved your head, huh?
Oh, yeah, I needed a change.
[electric razor buzzing]
It was weird, check it out.
It does feel weird.
It looks good, though.
- You think so?
- Yeah.
Oh, thanks.
Um, 30 grams of
the usual, please.
The usual? All right.
Um, this new batch is
a lot stronger, okay?
So you gotta be careful.
You know me well.
The stronger, the better.
I prefer to be comfortably numb.
Yeah, well, that'll
cheer you up for sure.
Oh, my God, that's
beautiful, look at that.
Oh, my God, yes, please.
[V] [laughs] It's good, right?
- Yes, I'll take this, please.
- Okay.
My friends are
gonna love this.
It's always best
when it's shared.
That's sweet.
Good guy.
$200.
- That's for the Kush.
- Thank you.
- This is for you.
- Thanks.
Wow, you look amazing.
I mean, your hair, the blue.
Oh, wow, really?
Yeah, it matches your eyes.
I really like it.
Thank you, thanks.
I just, I did it the other day.
- Really nice.
- Thanks.
What happened to
us going to coffee?
Oh, my God, that
totally slipped my mind.
I'm so sorry.
Slipped your mind.
No, I would love to
get some coffee with you.
All right, this
is the second time,
so don't lose this.
I promise, I cross my heart.
Thanks, V.
[chuckling] Have
a good one, Sid.
[dramatic music]
[grunts]
[groans]
[door thuds]
[dramatic music]
[inhales deeply]
Oh, sweet Jesus.
[inhales slowly] Oh, damn.
[lighter clicks]
[coughing uncontrollably]
[dramatic music intensifies]
[yells]
[yells out uncomfortably]
[static buzzing]
[cries out fearfully]
[static continues buzzing]
Shut the door, asshole.
[panting]
[groaning]
- He better be here this time.
- Yeah, for real.
Seriously, I'm not
coming here again.
[door knocking]
[lips smacking]
Tammy, Tina, my favorites.
What's up, cutie?
Peachy.
What's up?
The last time I saw eyes
that red was Bram
Stoker's Dracula.
Very funny.
Wanna smoke us out?
[exhales sharply]
Nah, I'm kinda tied up.
Come on, we wanna get high.
Well, I feel ya.
You can always buy somethin'.
We're broke.
Can we just get a couple
grams and square up tomorrow?
No fronts, ladies, sorry.
Please, we'll be
really nice to you.
You girls are teenagers.
What do I look like,
Captain Creepy?
Just one joint.
Just come back later
when you guys get
some cash, all right?
[door thuds]
[Both] Loser.
- I heard that!
- Good.
- What the fuck?
- I know.
Big, huge.
[keyboard clicking]
[electronic music]
[door knocking]
[exhales loudly]
[Girl On Video]
Watch me twerk.
I told you no freebies!
Uh, sorry.
Thought you were somebody else.
My name is Joan, and
this is my son, David.
How are you today?
I'm Sid.
- Good, thanks.
- Hello, Sid.
We're visiting new friends
in our neighborhood today,
spreading the word
of our good Lord.
Our goal is to save as
many souls as possible
from the inevitable
upcoming disaster.
- Disaster?
- Armageddon.
As written, it's not
a question of if,
more a question of when.
You see the signs on the news,
global war, nuclear threats
from foreign dictators.
It's a matter of time, Mr.
Smith, or can I call you Sid?
No, Sid's fine.
That's pretty dark.
Well, that's why we're here,
to offer you a way
out of the darkness.
Uh...
I'm not in the dark.
We all are.
I read the Bible.
- So, you're a Christian?
- Agnostic.
[speaks in foreign language]
I can clear that.
So, you're open to the
possibility of God.
Well, anything's possible,
but I prefer science.
It's real, you know?
Graspable, tangible.
No god has ever done
anything for me.
It's so hot.
I'm very sensitive to the heat.
May we continue inside?
Uh...
My place is a mess.
No judgment here.
Sure, why not?
Come on in.
[faint R&B music]
Please, have a seat,
sit down, sit down.
[Girl On Video] Do
you like my big ass?
[laptop thuds shut]
Uh, my portal.
[bells dinging]
Hey, what if an alien came down?
For everyone to see,
in broad daylight?
Would that disprove
the existence of God?
Well, that's not gonna happen.
Really?
How do you know?
That's science fiction, Sid.
Outside, you said that God's
never done anything for you.
You know that you have
to ask Him for help
for Him to answer the call?
Yeah, but God only
saves you when you die,
and none us knows what
happens when we die.
God knows.
[scoffs] See, you gotta believe
to get in the after party.
To me, why can't the
planet, the solar system,
the universe, be God?
God is everything.
He is in everything.
Hm, God, good, devil,
evil, isn't it that simple?
Believe in something greater,
conquer our fear of death,
and add meaningfulness
to the void?
[dramatic music]
Aren't we God,
the makers of man?
[door knocking]
I'll get it.
It was nice talking with you.
We'll meet again later.
Inspiring stuff.
Holy shit.
It's my friend, Logan.
Nice talkin' to you.
- Who were they?
- I don't know.
Some church.
- And you let them in?
- Yeah, just for a minute.
You got problems.
Can I get a joint, please?
For you, I'm gonna
get a fresh one.
One J.
Your idea, bro.
Pretty brilliant.
Oh, what idea?
The 24-hour supervised
self-burial challenge.
Oh, yeah, right.
I told you.
Did you watch the videos?
Yes, I watched the videos.
Do you think it'll work?
Yo, you don't even need luck
for this shit to work, man.
What do you mean?
That's the whole point
of doing it, for luck.
Sid, listen to me.
Those Russian videos, they
have millions of views.
Some have 10s of millions.
Do you know what kind of money
we can make with
those views, man?
No.
10s of thousands, okay?
Nobody in the states has
made a self-burial video.
We can be the first.
I mean, do you know
what this means?
If this shit goes viral, man.
Damn.
- Even if I don't get lucky-
- We just got lucky.
- We?
- Yes, I'm in, bro, 110%.
I'm gonna help you
make the video.
We can even livestream it
to my Facebook and YouTube.
It's set up with tons
of followers, man.
You have followers?
Over 1,000.
Damn.
Sid, this is huge.
This can bring us
millions of followers,
and millions of
new opportunities.
Okay, what do we have to do?
Well, first, we shake on it.
50/50 on all the monies made.
[scoffs] 50/50?
I'm the one going in the box.
- [dramatic music]
- Relax.
It's my gear, my channel.
You wanna do it on
your own, unsupervised?
All right, then
you have to supervise
the entire thing, all 24 hours.
You can't leave me
down there alone.
I won't.
And I can't go into
that box not knowing
if I'm gonna be
homeless when I get out.
If this goes wrong,
and I get evicted,
I need somewhere to go,
man, for like a month,
until I can find another place.
Like your pad.
You have gotta be kidding me.
[voice breaking] I can't
do it otherwise, man.
[panting] I'll die of stress.
Okay, okay, all right,
don't die of stress.
I'll talk to my mom.
Your mom likes me.
Hey, watch it, okay?
I'll talk to her.
This means a lot to me, man.
It really means a lot to me.
I got you.
We gotta dig a hole and
build a box, all right?
I'll come back tomorrow,
and we'll get started.
I can't believe
we're doin' it.
[chuckles] I got you, man.
- I'll see you tomorrow, okay?
- I'll see you tomorrow.
[door thuds shut]
[hip hop music]
♪ I smoke weed like I
like to drink liquor ♪
♪ Smokin' on the backwoods ♪
♪ Smoke weed, kick it
with some strippers ♪
Yeah, let's do the box, though,
like, I can't do that coffin,
that shit freaks me out.
No, I feel you, man.
We shouldn't do a coffin.
- That's just-
- It's like, feet are tied up,
just like when you found me.
All right, so, we
gotta get a pipe,
drill a hole, and stick it in
the top, so you can breath.
Shit, I almost
forgot about that.
You will run out
of air, definitely,
and you will die, so let's
not have that happen.
Yeah, I don't
really wanna die, man.
I don't want you
to die, either.
So, do you know where
we can get a pipe from?
I have a couple
pipes in the back.
Didn't think I
was gonna use them
for breathing,
though, but fuck it.
Perfect.
So, where are we gonna
get some wood from?
Let's get the
pallettes on the street.
People leave them
out all the time.
- Really?
- Yeah, and I got a shed-full
of tools in the back.
Perfect, hammer and
nails, we'll get it done.
All right, so, I'm thinkin',
you know, a little somethin'
like that, you know?
We set up a camera
here, maybe one there,
and then we're good to go.
[Sid] Maybe one
more on that corner.
On this one, too?
We can do that.
- Pipe, so you can breathe.
- To breathe.
Obviously.
I'll take a little bit of that.
And you have
all the materials?
So, this is all the
materials we need right here?
Yeah, so,
[Both] Wood, nails.
- Two by fours,
[Both] Blankets,
batteries, pillows,
Snacks,
[Both] Socks, weed.
♪ Puffs from the joint ♪
[door knocking]
Sid, are you there?
Hey, Sid, it's David.
[door knocking]
- Sid, you here?
- What are you doing, man?
- What?
- Are you trying
to get us killed, bro?
No.
Sid's shotgun shells,
man, have killed people.
I told you.
Let's go.
[dramatic music]
All right, I'll
take care of that.
- Over to the kitchen.
- Sweet.
[hammer pounding]
[wood creaking]
Hit it with a wedge.
[hammer pounding]
[wood creaking]
[drill whirring]
[saw buzzing]
[dramatic music continues]
[box thudding]
Oh, yeah, bro, this is,
yeah, this is perfect.
Yeah, I should fit right here.
- Yeah, right in there.
- Yeah.
Yeah, sounds good.
You, uh, wanna get started?
- Better late than never.
- Might as well, right?
There you go.
All right.
Kinda spooky, digging
a grave on a full moon.
Hey, fuckin' stop
with that shit, man.
What? Sorry, it is.
That's not a grave, it's
just a hole, all right?
Well, that's easy
for you to say.
I'm the one that's
gonna get in the box.
Yeah, but you're
gonna be alive.
I am gonna be alive.
We're doin' this for luck, man.
- All right.
- For luck.
[grunting]
There's gotta be an easier way.
Yeah, bro.
A Splatter-dozer.
[Both] Splatter-dozer!
- I wish.
- Did you bring a joint?
- I always got a joint.
- My man.
Oh yeah.
[inhales deeply]
And the gods have
smiled on us again.
- This'll help.
- If you believe in 'em.
I believe in the rain gods,
and the weed gods,
I just don't believe in God.
Yeah, I believe
in the money gods.
I believe in the
money gods, too.
I just wish they'd
show themselves.
After we're done with
this, hopefully, they will.
[exhales loudly] I think
I got a second wind, man.
You took one hit.
Yeah, that's true.
Can I get another hit, bro?
Mm hm.
[inhales deeply] Sorry,
you know I like to hog it.
[shovel clanking]
Yo, I'm beat, man, I need a nap.
Well, that's it.
I'm done.
Should we get the box?
Well, can't it wait
a couple more hours?
Oh, come on, man, this is
all part of the challenge.
Yo, we've been
up all night, man.
Come on, we gotta get this
done before anybody else.
[sighs] All right, whatever.
Come on, let's go.
[grunts]
Let's go.
You know what you
need is some coffee.
[Logan chuckles]
All right, sorry.
Okay.
[straining] We got it.
[drill whirring]
Look, the cameras have WiFi,
so they'll livestream
to my social platforms
and record everything
simultaneously.
Technology, insane, right?
Yeah.
Now, the livestream,
you can't see everybody,
but they can see and hear you,
so the more you interact
with the camera, the better.
Five feet, should be
three feet above ground.
Should work.
- Hey, you feel that?
- Rain.
Said it was in the
forecast for tomorrow.
Let's get goin'.
[lid creaking]
- You got it?
- Yeah.
There's some bricks
over here, careful.
All right.
All right. [grunts]
One second.
[grunts] All right.
[grunting]
All right.
Here we go.
Gentle, gentle.
I think it fits.
[straining] Just a little more.
Yep.
[box thudding]
Look.
[Logan chuckles]
[lid thuds shut]
How's it looking?
Oh, yeah.
Should we smoke one?
- [chuckles] Yeah.
- All right, let's do that.
[lid creaks shut]
- Looks good.
- Headed your way.
[exhales loudly]
[panting]
Let's see.
[under breath] 24-hour
supervised self-burial.
All right, looking good.
[toilet flushes]
[exhales quickly]
- Yo.
- Okay.
I'm all good.
Hop in the box, I'll test
the picture and the sound.
I'll put all my crap in there.
All right.
[Sid exhaling loudly]
- You got this.
- All right.
[ominous music]
[lid creaking]
[lid thuds shut]
There you are, perfect.
[Sid grunting]
And away we go.
[box thudding]
[Sid Over Livestream]
Not too bad.
[chuckles]
I'm running a test
on the livestream now.
Everything looks good.
- I'm not buried yet.
- Well, as good as.
You know what, here,
take the air pipe.
Fill in the hole,
let's go now, come on.
- Why the mad rush?
- Bro, I'm already in here,
I got everything I need, we
already have the live feed,
come on, let's just go.
Let's rock and roll, bro.
Okay, all right,
all right, fine.
Before I lose my nerve!
Come on, let's get
this party started!
How's that, good?
Woo, I can see!
[chuckles] All right.
[dramatic music]
[sputtering]
Logan, careful, man!
It's raining sand in here.
[flashlight clicking]
[box rumbling]
[exhaling loudly]
That's right.
Come on, you can
drink the water.
[exhales loudly]
[mumbling to self]
What's goin' on?
What's taking so long?
Yeah, I'm gettin'
there, buddy.
- How you doin' down there?
- Doin' pretty good.
I got some dirt in my mouth,
but I'm good otherwise.
Ah, you'll be all right.
I'm sure you've had worse
things in your mouth.
[Sid] Yeah, actually, I have.
[chuckles]
[shovel clattering]
All right, bro,
it's lookin' good.
[shivers] It's
freezing down here.
Yeah, it should
probably warm up
when the sun hits the yard more.
Okay.
You're right, I'm good, then.
Yeah, bro, I
think I'm all done.
- Logan.
- Yeah?
It's freaky as hell, bro.
[chuckles] Look, you'll
be fine, all right?
I'm gonna go inside now,
but I got the cameras on,
so I'll be watching you, okay?
Yeah, I'm okay.
I got my phone.
I'll call you in a few.
[dramatic music]
It's not so bad.
More room than I thought.
I mean, it's a little
cold, but that's all right.
The cold doesn't really
bother me all that much.
My boy, Sid, camera A.
Hi, everyone.
If you can see me, my
name is Challenger,
a.k.a. Sid, Sid Smith.
This is my 24-hour supervised
self-burial challenge.
[viewers laughing]
I'm gonna be in this box
for the next 24 hours,
underground, buried.
Insane, right?
- That's right.
- And I'm doin' it for luck.
I know, I know, it sounds
crazy, but it works.
[laughing]
If I don't die of an anxiety
attack in here first.
[inhales deeply]
My bro, LoganRun, is supervising
and running the live feed.
Thanks to him, [inhales
sharply] I'll be safe.
Yes, sir.
Let's see.
23 hours, 50 minutes to go.
Stay tuned, anything can happen.
[Viewer] He's crazy.
[laughs] My boy.
I'm vaping in my capsule.
Oh.
[imitating rave music]
[viewers chatting]
I am vaping in my
capsule. [coughing]
Holy shit.
Yo!
Thank God, I needed that.
- [Sid coughing]
- Yo, Sid!
What's up?
Yo, it's 200
people watching, bro!
- 200, no way.
- Yes!
Look, just keep doin'
what you're doin',
the chitchat, everything,
bro, it's killing!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
Hey, you guys, it's 200
people watching right now,
because probably
you've never seen
someone bury themselves before.
Stay tuned.
[viewers chatting]
All you have to do is commit.
Stay committed, right, Logan?
Yeah, my boy!
- Yeah!
- I'm goin' back inside, baby!
Woo!
[Sid] Woo, woo!
[viewers chatting]
[viewers laughing]
- ♪ I, I, I, I got my hashpipe ♪
- Oh, shit.
Sid, you have got to see this.
[viewer groaning loudly]
[laughing]
Okay.
[dramatic music]
Wow, 1,000 followers.
[exhales loudly]
Thank you, everybody, for
watching me do this challenge.
It looks insane, but if
you're searching for luck,
or trying to make
some money, like me,
then this could be
the thing for you.
But get help, you can't
do this by yourself.
I'm not superstitious
or anything,
and I don't know how it works,
but just go online and search,
"24-hour supervised
self-burial."
Okay?
Watch the videos.
You'll see what
I'm talkin' about.
Damn it, I forgot to charge
my cell phone and
bring a pillow.
Well, that's what happens
when you start a challenge
to beat the weather.
[laughing]
Yo, yo, I got a gift for you.
What's up?
[coughing] What
are you doin', man?
I'm hotboxing you, bro.
[coughing] Stop,
man, I can't breathe!
[viewers laughing]
Stop it, you madman! [coughing]
See you later.
[Sid coughing uncontrollably]
[viewers chatting]
[laughing]
Look at you, Sid.
Yeah, but you know what?
This sure feels good.
Don't try this at home.
[viewers laughing]
LoganRun is a crazy ass fool,
but I know he's only doing it
out of the kindness
of his heart.
Thanks, bro.
[vape pen bubbling]
[sighs]
[Viewer] What is this?
In a box?
[snoring loudly]
They're burying themselves?
What is this?
[viewers chatting]
[viewers continue chatting]
Not talking a text,
not talking a call,
can you see them okay?
[snoring loudly]
[watch beeping]
Yo, Logan.
Logan?
Where'd you go?
Did you disappear on me?
Logan?
Did you fall asleep?
[ringback ringing]
Come on, man, answer
your damn phone.
[phone vibrating]
Oh, shit.
Yo, hey, sorry,
man, I passed out.
What's up?
Dude, you totally
disappeared on me.
No, man, look, I would
never leave, all right?
I was just in a Kush coma.
- [watch beeps]
- We're six hours in.
Oh, shit, yo, it's 10,000
people watching right now, bro.
- For real?
- Yeah, for real.
[head thuds against box]
I can't believe 10,000
of you are watching.
I hope you're all
enjoying my challenge.
We're a quarter of
the way through now.
Man, the comments
are going crazy, man.
It's like a feeding frenzy.
Just keep doin'
what you're doin'.
Really?
All right.
I'm telling everyone out there
watching to listen to me.
This shit works.
[viewers chatting]
If you want luck, then
you know what to do.
[sighing]
This is crazy, man.
Look, I gotta go take a piss,
but I'll be right
back, all right?
[vape pen bubbling]
[coughing loudly]
[Sid shrieking comically]
[computer alert chimes]
[toilet flushing]
[dramatic music]
11, 18,
80, three,
15, what the fuck?!
Holy shit!
Sid!
Sid.
Woo!
[phone ringing]
Unknown number, could
be some more luck.
[phone beeps]
This is Sid.
[Vanessa] Sid, hi, it's
Vanessa from L.A. Kush.
Oh, hey, V, all right.
Um, how'd you get my number?
Um, it's on file
here at the store,
and I got kinda worried
that you lost my card again.
[Sid] Oh, no, no, I had
your card, I was gonna call.
Mm hm, sure you were.
Well, now, you don't have to.
What are you doin'?
Oh, you know, I'm, uh,
kind of in the middle of
a challenge right now.
A challenge?
Yeah, I'm buried underground,
doing a supervised
self-burial for good luck.
Wait a minute, you're
buried underground right now?
Yeah, we're running
our own livestream
on YouTube and
Facebook, check it out.
LoganRun is the page.
Oh, okay.
And you know what?
I'm really glad you called.
I'd love to see you
when I get out of here.
Ditto.
I knew this
challenge would work,
and the fact that you just
called just proves it.
[chuckling] That's
very sweet, Sid.
[Sid] Seriously.
All right, well, be careful?
Keep getting lucky, and
call me later, yeah?
I will.
Talk to you later, V.
[viewers chatting]
[exhales loudly] Anyone
who tries to tell me
that this challenge doesn't
work is full of shit.
My luck has already changed,
and that phone call
just proved it.
You hear that, Logan?
See your boy in action?
Mr. Cool Breeze,
makin' it happen.
[dramatic music]
[ringback tone ringing]
[panting]
I don't get it.
[viewers laughing]
Did you fall in
the fucking toilet?
Call me.
[viewers chatting]
[ringback tone ringing]
Dude, pick up the phone.
My battery is dying and
it's starting to rain.
[ringback tone ringing]
If only he was there when
I was getting weed, dude.
Like, holy shit, now
he's just gonna die?
This is not a fucking joke.
You're meant to be
supervising me, man.
Call me!
[ringback tone ringing]
- The guy evicted this guy.
- Now, it's getting serious.
[Viewer] Did you get
the link I just sent you?
Logan, bro, pick
up or respond!
[grunts] We talked about this!
[sighs]
Fuck.
[viewers chatting]
Logan!
I thought that when I
was in the box. [laughing]
Logan!
[viewer laughing]
Fucking Logan, man.
Logan!
Let me out of here!
You gotta fucking come back!
Logan!
Okay, fucking calm down.
Calm down, catch your breath.
You gotta relax.
I'm fuckin' freaking out, man.
I'm fucking freaking out.
[phone ringing]
[Vanessa] Hey, it's Vanessa.
Hey, V.
[Vanessa] Um, I saw you
were having some issues.
Can I help you with anything?
Nah, it's okay.
It's just my flakey friend.
Probably crashed out.
He was up late last night.
[Vanessa] You sure?
'Cause watching you
is giving me anxiety.
How do you think I feel?
I'm the one in the box.
[Vanessa] Okay, call me if
you need anything, all right?
I'm watching.
Okay, I will, thanks, V.
[panting] Momma!
Momma!
Woo!
Mom!
What?
[panting]
[laughing]
Why are you panting?
What is it?
What's it look like?
Don't be smart.
Where have you been all night?
I was at Sid's.
Look up the winning
numbers for me, please.
No, Mr. Lazy, you do it.
[scoffs] Okay.
[computer chimes]
Compare 'em, Ma.
Okay, okay, hold on.
- They match.
- Yes.
We're rich.
What do you mean, we're rich?
This isn't real.
Yes, it is, Ma.
Where'd you get this from?
Well, uh, I bought it.
Logan, you don't
buy lottery tickets.
Who's is this?
Okay, Ma, Sid bought it.
You stole this
from Sid, Logan?
Momma, you know I
wouldn't steal, okay?
I was bringing it to you
to ask you what you
think I should do.
It's $300 million, Ma.
Think about it, seriously.
There is nothing
to think about.
This is Sid's ticket, you
need to get it back to him.
Where is he?
Let me out of here!
Mom, I ran all the way
over here, $300 million.
I need you to take this
ticket back to Sid, it's his.
Here, now, get moving.
Get moving.
[panting]
[crying softly]
[grunting]
[viewers chatting]
Let me out!
[shouting indistinctly]
Fuck, calm down, relax.
[panting]
Shit, I have the lights.
Logan, damn it!
He better be here, man.
Chill, bro, he's always here.
Yeah right.
[door knocking]
Sid, you home?
- [door thudding]
- Man.
Bro!
He's never here.
He's so unreliable.
- That's his door.
- Hey, what are y'all doin'?
Uh, we're-
- [Both] Friends with Sid.
- Yeah.
Mm hm, fuck outta here.
Sorry, man, I don't
want no trouble.
[door knocking]
Hey, Sid.
Sid, you home?
[dramatic music]
[straining]
[Viewer] I mean,
he's fine, right now,
but I don't think he'll
make it out alive.
[viewers chatting]
Sid?
You here?
Shit.
[door thuds shut]
[panting] Okay, okay.
All right.
Come on, Sid, come on.
Where you at?
[computer chiming]
Ah, there you are.
Okay, okay.
[ringback tone ringing]
Yo, yo, Sid, are you there?
Fuck!
Where the hell have you been?
6 hours, what, are
you ghosting me, man?
I'm sorry, but, bro, listen
to me, I have some good news.
- [viewers chatting]
- I don't give a shit.
I've been down here
freakin' the fuck out here,
and you just disappeared.
Bro.
You just take
off and leave me.
I could've died down here, bro.
Sorry, my phone died.
Listen to me.
You're not gonna believe it.
Let me get a word
in, man, listen.
[Sid] You broke your promise.
Did you get my messages?
Yes, bro, I got all
20 of your messages,
just shut the fuck
up and listen to me.
- No!
- Yes!
[thuds loudly]
What, jerkin' off?
My luck's been goin'
through the roof.
Girls are callin' me, it's
freakin' unbelievable,
but were you here to see it, no.
Do you give a shit, no.
I could've died down here, bro.
[viewers chatting]
I don't think I can handle
another anxiety attack.
[viewers clamoring]
[viewers chiming offline]
Logan.
God damn it.
Logan, I lost you.
My cell phone's fucked.
It's all wet, I lost you.
Come out to the pipe.
Oh, fuck.
Fuck.
Logan, come out here!
[ominous music]
[rain pattering]
[box creaking loudly]
[box rumbling]
[children faintly laughing]
[children's laughter
grows louder]
[yells out loudly]
[electronic whirring]
Sidney.
[children's laughter continues]
Why are you down here, Sidney?
[Sid screams]
[truck horn blaring]
[box thudding]
Let me out!
Logan!
Ow!
Oh.
[Operator] Please
record your message.
- [phone beeps]
- Hey, Sid, um, it's V.
I, um, I don't know if
it's my phone or not,
but I can't see the
livestream anymore, so, um,
Yeah, I was just calling to
see if you were doing okay.
Ah, cramp!
[cries out painfully]
Um, I hope everything
is going great in the box.
[yelling indistinctly] Ow, ow!
And, um, hit me back.
Let me know that you're
good, that you're okay.
Okay, bye.
[phone beeps]
What do I sound like?
Jesus.
[loud creaking]
[children faintly laughing]
[ominous music]
[gasps]
Sidney, it's not your fault.
I don't blame you.
Mom and Dad don't blame you.
Go away.
I forgive you, Sidney.
[dramatic music]
Sid.
Sidney.
It's not your fault, Sidney.
[child screaming]
[thunder rumbling]
[police car beeping]
[police radio chatter]
Logan, did you move it?
[cries out]
Logan, the pipe's gone!
Fuck!
[water trickling]
Get me the fuck
out of here, man!
I'm serious!
I've had enough.
[ominous music]
[rain trickling]
[water splashing]
[Sid] [muffled] Logan!
Logan!
I'm gonna die!
[screaming]
[thunder rumbling]
What the fuck?
Sid!
Hey!
Oh, fuck.
Sid!
Help!
[grunts] Yo, somebody help!
Sid, help!
The fuck are you?
[Operator] Your call
has been forwarded
to an automatic voice
messaging system.
Logan.
[Operator] When you
are finished recording,
hang up or press one
for more options.
[voicemail prompt beeps]
Fuck. [cries softly]
[panting]
Hey, hey.
I don't know if any of
you are still watching.
you have stopped now.
This challenge is too hard.
It's freezing in here,
and this thing's
filling up with water.
Oh, shit.
[panting]
[camera static buzzing]
I think I need help.
I think I need someone to
come in here and get me out.
[cries softly]
Sid!
Help!
Logan!
[shrieking]
[loud thudding]
[dramatic music]
[grunting]
[straining]
[man talking over radio]
[Man Over Radio] Five,
four, three, two, one.
And we have a liftoff.
[man talking
indistinctly over radio]
[electronic beeping]
[ominous music continues]
[electronic whirring]
[electronic whirring
intensifies]
[booms loudly]
Hey.
Hey, I thought today
was your day off.
I just missed you too much.
Aw.
And I need to find
a friend's address.
Oh, okay.
There we go.
Sid?
'Kay, I'm out.
See ya mañana.
All right.
[door creaks shut]
[ringback tone ringing]
[Operator] At the tone,
please record your message.
- [phone beeps]
- Sid, hey, it's V again.
Uh, so, I'm officially
worried now.
I was watching the livestream,
it ended really abruptly,
I called you a bunch,
you're not calling me back.
So, um, I know this makes me
sound like a nervous ninny,
I'm just, I am really worried,
so I went to the store and
I got your address, and um,
I'm just gonna
come to your house.
Okay?
To check on you, make
sure you're okay.
Unless you call me back
in the next few minutes.
So, if you're
okay, call me back.
Bye.
[phone beeps]
[dramatic music]
Haley Lee's coming
over tonight man.
[Daeg laughs]
You're gonna have to sleep with
Patricia Fatterson, though.
[blubbers lips]
[exhales loudly]
Dude, he's not even
pickin' up, though, today.
[door knocking]
I keep tellin' him
we need to get weed.
Yo!
Hey!
Hey, who's there?
Help me!
What the fuck?
- Where's Sid?
- He's here.
Sid's here.
Help, untie me, please!
How, how do we get in?
[Logan] The back,
go around back.
What the fuck?
Yo, there's some
dude hogtied in there,
told us to go around back.
[Logan] I got a
cramp, man, help!
Fuck!
What do we do?
- Help him.
- Help, I can't move!
Wait, are you sure?
There's a dude
tied up in there!
That's not Sid.
We don't know what the
fuck's goin' on in there.
Sid could be in trouble.
Sid's a drug dealer.
Do what you want, I'm not
gettin' involved in this shit.
I'm out, Daeg.
My parents will kill me.
Pussy, man, we gotta help!
[dramatic electronic music]
[door thudding]
- Hello?
- In here!
What the fuck?
What happened?
- Who are you?
- I'm Vanessa.
I'm Sid's friend, you're Logan?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, okay.
Untie me, scissors, in
the kitchen on the floor.
Scissors?
Okay.
[grunting]
I got it, I got it, I got it.
My hands.
These were a pair...
- Hang on.
- Oh, fuck.
- Thank you.
- Where is Sid?
He's in the backyard.
He's buried!
Come on, help me.
Ah!
Sid!
Shit.
Oh, my God, the pipe fell.
It's flooded.
- Sid!
- Sid, can you hear us?
Sid, are you there?
Oh, my God.
Shovels, dig.
Come on.
Oh, shit.
- [grunting]
- You guys are insane.
He could be dead.
It was his idea, the
fool wanted to get lucky.
Lucky?
Who tied you up?
Don't ask, just dig.
- Sid!
- Can you hear us?
- I'm comin', buddy!
[dramatic music]
What the fuck?
- Help us, please!
- Help us!
Hurry up!
What do you want us to do?
[Logan And Vanessa] Just dig!
Sid!
- Sid!
- Can you hear us?
Sid!
- You ready, you ready?
- Yeah.
Pull, pull, pull.
[all straining]
[All] Sid!
- Sid?
- No.
No, man, come on, come on.
[gasps for air]
[Vanessa] Oh, my
God, oh, my God.
- You're okay.
- We won!
[Sid screaming]
Are you okay?
Oh, my God.
[all exclaiming]
You did it.
- You're okay.
- I'm okay!
[Vanessa] You're okay!
I'm okay!
[all laughing]
What are you guys doing here?
We're here for you, man!
[all exclaiming]
Oh, thank God.
- ♪ You and me ♪
- You are crazy. [laughs]
I know.
[both laughing]
♪ Are all on our
way to nowhere ♪
I can't believe you're here.
I can't believe you're here!
[laughing]
♪ But not very far ♪
♪ Enough to know
when I'm prepared ♪
♪ And the years roll
on like clouds ♪
♪ Must we waste the
time we're allowed ♪
♪ Don't pretend
there's more than now ♪
We're here at Vinny's Market,
and this is where the
winning ticket was purchased,
and this is Vinny, the
owner of the store.
I hope I get some money.
My wife left me for
two Japanese midgets.
Okay, Vinny, okay.
And this is the man of the hour,
our lucky winner of the $300
million jackpot, Sid Smith.
I just wanna thank
everyone for being here.
To my girlfriend, Vanessa,
she saved my life,
and to my best friend and
business partner, Logan Gibson,
who taught me that
anything is possible,
which is why I want
you all to know
that we're starting our
very own gaming company.
That's right, and
I'll be splitting
my winnings with him 50/50.
[check tearing loudly]
- Yeah!
- Yay!
Woo!
Oh, yeah, I got you.
50/50, you know, you can
have half of it, man.
Back to you, Ken.
♪ For today ♪
We did it!
♪ When it's finally
time to depart ♪
♪ I hope see you
after the dark ♪
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
♪ 'Cause you, and me,
and everyone else ♪
♪ We're all on our
way to the sun ♪
♪ And now I see
I'm not by myself ♪
♪ And all of us
had add up to one ♪
["Original Sin"
by The Micawbers]
♪ Sun down upon the cash cow ♪
♪ Packaged hunger like
an insect ready for war ♪
♪ Pushin' down
towards the hemline ♪
♪ Fear's to God and all
those cracks that feather ♪
♪ We shoulda made up
all the intrigue ♪
♪ Want you hungry like a
sermon comin' to town ♪
♪ Forces against the sea limb ♪
♪ Foolish got
against all feeling ♪
♪ Sin, sin, original sin ♪
♪ Oh, won't do the time if she
don't get the fun from it ♪
♪ Sin, sin, original sin ♪
♪ No, she won't do the time if
she don't get the fun from it ♪
♪ Comin' for original sin ♪
♪ Sin, sin, original sin ♪
♪ No, she won't do the time if
she don't get the fun from it ♪
♪ Whoa ♪
♪ Sin, sin, original sin ♪
♪ No, she won't do the time if
she don't get the fun from it ♪