[dramatic music]
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
[plane engine roaring]
[artillery booming]
[Richards] January, 1945,
the last major German
offensive of the war.
The Battle of the
Bulge has collapsed.
Allied Forces in France
prepare for the invasion
of Germany from the West,
having been stockpiling men
and machinery since D-Day,
June 6th, the previous summer.
From the east, Russian
forces are pushing hard,
creating a vice
grip from all sides.
Years of Allied
bombardment have all
but crippled the once mighty
military manufacturing capacity
of the Third Reich.
However, there is one facility
still assembling large
quantities of the V-2 rocket,
the Kohnstein, a
former gypsum mine,
located inside a mountain
in Thuringia, Germany.
The Kohnstein is also
the only major manufacturing
plant remaining for the ME-262,
the first operational
jet fighter in history.
[plane engine roaring]
Here, protected by the
subterranean environment,
the war continues on these
advanced technological terrors.
[Rob] Malcolm, who
is that beautiful woman
in that picture on
the wall behind you?
That's my daughter,
my only child.
She was killed in a
V-2 rocket attack.
So you see, Rob, this is
quite personal for me.
The Germans are
having severe problems
with their supply lines thanks
to your 17s and our Lancasters.
The most recent communications
do not concern the V-9,
they concern the ME-262.
Well my boys are
still seein' 'em.
Our enemy remains a group
of clever individuals,
knowing we would destroy
any convoy or train
with military applications,
the Germans have been
using passenger trains
to transport their goods.
They simply cut the tops
off of passenger cars,
fill them full of goods,
fuel, entire engines at times,
reattach the roof,
making them indiscernible
from an actual train
carrying civilian passengers.
Well, what do you recommend?
A precision bombing
raid using one of your 17s
without the usual escort.
Damn risky.
Most special operations are.
You have the routes
and departure time?
I do.
Well, I'll have to put
the word out for volunteers.
Of course, however, this
pilot that lead the raid
on the mobile airfield...
Yes, Cole Philips,
he's a good man.
Might he be available?
Well, I see you found
your long-lost brother.
Yeah, can you believe it, sir?
Well, I was as surprised as
anybody that he wandered in.
So you did cost Colonel
Richards a P-38,
what you score for us?
Well, Colonel, your
plan worked well.
A lot of planes were blown up
on the ground, mostly 190s.
What about those 262s?
Yes, sir, three were there,
two were destroyed,
one I didn't get to.
Well, I'd say pretty
successful venture.
Thank you, sir.
Major Phillips, I
filled your brother in
on this Luftwaffe Colonel.
Yes, sir, he chased
me part of the way home
in one of his jets.
Really?
Yes, fast but not
very maneuverable.
You got lucky.
I want you to spend some
time with your brother.
Go out, celebrate,
take a night out.
And I'll be back here
tomorrow with Colonel Richards
and we'll set up the briefing
for the next big bombing run.
I want both of you there.
Of course.
You ready to get
back in the sky, Joe?
It's all I've been
thinking about, Colonel,
that and my wife and little
girl back in Georgia.
Yeah, Cole, I want
you to sit this one out.
I've got something else for you.
Am I being taken out
of the sky again, sir?
Well, we've got
some intelligence,
some very good intelligence
on a new supply
train for the 262s.
And I would say it's
about 60% reliable,
but this could be
a wild goose chase.
We believe those remaining
262s are being loaded
on a train heading east,
deeper into Germany.
And we don't know exactly
where they're going yet,
but we do know the route
they're gonna take.
It's a slow-moving
target, a bomb raid.
Well, not in the
traditional sense.
The 262s are actually
not yet assembled.
What's on the train are
all the parts needed
to put these together,
down to the nuts and bolts.
So you want to strike
before they get a
chance to assemble them.
There's one wrinkle though.
The Germans are using
a passenger train.
And so from a distance
it's gonna look like
we're attacking civilians.
And the folks up at headquarters
would not be pleased
if they saw us doing some
barbaric things like these Nazis.
One good payload from a B-17
ought to take care of this.
But as you all saw walking
over here, everyone's gone,
they're out on a
mission right now,
I don't have anything for you.
When are they due back?
About three hours.
Considering
re-fueling, re-arming,
take about four
hours to take-off.
But we don't have
that much time.
What about Lillian,
sir, my old ship.
She's still sitting down there.
Oh, come on now.
Do you think that thing is
really safe, that it would fly?
[Cole] She made
it home okay for me.
Doesn't matter, we
don't have a crew.
Well, all we
need's a bombardier.
And you could do that, Joe.
Hey, I'm just a tail gunner.
All you have to
do is push a button.
Cole, I just got
back from almost dying.
I mean I just got back.
Come on, Joe, you have to go!
Why do I have to go?
Because it's the big one, Joe.
Don't you remember the
movie when we were a kids?
Why was it so important for us
to see that airplane movie, Joe?
[sighs] Because
it was our father.
That's right.
It was the story of our father
and a lot of other fathers.
And that's who you and I are
a continuation of that story.
Well, what we have is something
that's very top secret.
And you're gonna have
to come in really low
so that you can see who's
on the passenger train.
If it's Nazi soldiers,
take it out, blow it up.
If it's boxes and crates
that you see, blow it up.
But if it's
passengers, civilians,
just come on back
home, forget about it.
Hey Joe, before we go I'm
gonna grab a photographer
and have him take a
picture of our plane.
Whatever makes
you happy, brother.
I just gotta push
a button, right?
Right.
Colonel, how do we
find that train?
[plane engine roaring]
Well, according
to the time table,
that train should be leaving
the station any minute.
[train hissing]
Thank you for meeting
me, Herr von Braun.
Your reputation precedes you.
Colonel, I didn't
want to introduce you
to this aircraft until I thought
it could be of use to you.
These are the updated
plans for the ME-163A,
they are calling it the Comet.
Yes, I have seen early
plans for this years ago.
It is famous for the amount
of pilots is has killed
during testing and training.
It took several years to
work out all the problems,
from what I hear.
If they use the same
engines as the 262,
then unfortunately,
there isn't enough
to go around as it is.
They aren't Junkers engines.
This is a light aircraft, and
it has no turbojets at all.
It uses a rocket.
That makes more sense.
This does not have the
appearance of an airplane.
This has the appearance
of a spacecraft.
We can only hope.
The rocket in the Comet
uses a bi-propellant design
that Walker and his
crew copied from my V-2.
Of course, they say
it was vice versa.
I have a few questions.
What about armament?
30 millimeter cannons, the
108s the same as your jets.
But, two not four.
And handling?
Colonel, it will never
turn on a dime like our 109s.
But the fuel delivery system is
actually much better
than your 262s.
As you are more than aware,
quick throttle
movements have resulted
in all manner of problems
with your engines.
Flame outs, engine failure,
et cetera, et cetera.
Yes, yes, but I make
up for these issues
with the speed of the aircraft.
Refresh my memory, Colonel.
What is the top
speed of your 262?
My jets regularly touch
700 kilometers per hour.
The last test
flight for the 163-A
that I attended was in July.
I can verify that the pilot
named Hitmar flew the Comet
to a speed approaching
1,300 kilos per hour.
You cannot possible
approach that with this toy.
That is impossible.
I was there, Colonel.
I saw it with my own eyes.
When can I take delivery?
A number of weeks.
You'll have to go through
your normal channels
at Messerschmidt though.
I am only here to
endorse the aircraft.
Of course, Her von Braun.
And congratulations on
your V-2 rocket program.
But there's one more
piece of information
I would like to know.
Yes?
I have heard fantastical
stories about a rocket
that uses the same
technology as the V-2
and I have heard this
rocket has the possibility
of reaching the other
side of the Atlantic.
I am afraid that
I am not at liberty
to discuss this with
you right now, Colonel.
But that is not a denial.
You noticed.
Colonel, I must take my leave.
Goodbye.
Everything is ready, Colonel.
All right, your cargo
is desperately needed
at the Kohnstein.
You may leave immediately.
Am I to understand
that there's no military
presence on this train?
You are not to
have the appearance
of a military transport.
If you face imminent danger,
you may break radio
silence for 30 seconds.
I will not be far away.
[sighs] Yes, sir.
I remember what you told
me to say on the radio.
[train chugging]
[plane engine roaring]
Anything?
Just what you see.
[plane engine roaring]
So how's fuel?
It's good for now.
[plane engine roaring]
You sure this is the
right stretch of track?
Well, this is where
he pointed me to.
But intelligence is never 100%.
Why don't you turn on the radio
and see if they could tip
us off to where they're at.
[radio crackling]
Good evening, here is
The Dresden Doll once again
to make your nights
a little less lonely.
And now my darlings,
have you ever thought
about how many Americans
have German ancestors?
Do you realize that when
you are bombing Germany,
you may be bombing your
own hereditary homeland?
Perhaps you are
killing your cousins
or perhaps even
your grandparents.
And we all share a
wonderful cultural legacy.
We are of the people,
just as you are.
And all we want to do
is to make a better life
for our folk, just as you do.
We should not be enemies.
Why do you attack us, we
would never attack you.
Have you never heard of the
German American Federation.
We have many friends and
allies in the United States.
And you know the Dresden
Doll is your special friend.
So lay down your arms and come.
We share a bottle
of Schnapps, no?
[both laughing]
Can you believe this bitch?
You gotta hand
it to her, buddy.
She's good at what she does.
[plane engine roaring]
Shouldn't be long now.
Get down to the bombardier
station, get ready.
Aye, aye, skipper.
[upbeat music]
Hey, Cole?
Yeah.
It's good to be back onboard.
[plane engine roaring]
Wait, wait.
Straight ahead, right
out there on the horizon.
Oh, good eye.
Almost good enough
to be a pilot.
[plane engine roaring]
[track chugging]
All right, get back
down, take up position.
Get ready, we're
gonna follow him.
This is to the pilot of
the single American bomber
that is following my train.
Please be advised, this is
not a military operation.
We have no soldiers or
armament on this train.
This is a civilian transport.
Repeat, this is a
civilian transport.
[plane engine roaring]
[wind howling]
[man gasps]
You're a Jew.
You are observant.
Or did this give it away?
What is a Polish
girl doing here?
You speak Polish?
Yes, and French and
German and Russian and Greek
and Latin and of course,
Yiddish and Hebrew.
You Jews think you
are so smart and clever.
Calling yourselves
the Chosen People.
That is what we
tell ourselves.
But often I wish He had
chosen someone else.
What are you doing here?
It is quiet here.
I come here for a
few minutes each day
to pray for my family,
my people and myself.
Do you think He hears
your prayers, Jew?
I can only hope.
But tell me, why is
a Polish girl working
for these monsters?
This of no concern of yours.
I have a name, it is Issac.
What is yours?
My name is Anna.
[Issac] That is a Jewish name.
It is not Jewish,
I am not a Jew!
Anna comes from Hannah,
which is a Jewish name.
No matter, I can report
you for being here.
They will ask you
why you were here
and I will tell them the truth,
I came here to pray but
you to steal some time.
And I think my work is
more valued than that
of an assembly line girl.
You work for them also?
No, I come here
because I enjoy the
atmosphere and the company.
Why do you do this?
For my family,
to keep them alive.
Why are you here?
They promised to cleanse
the Jews from Poland
and destroy the Russians.
And you believe them and
they have made you their slave.
But you are very pretty,
I think they would have chosen
another occupation for you.
Dirty minded little Jew!
Forgive me, but
in a war people do
what they must to survive.
An ugly man could
work an assembly line
as well as an
attractive young lady.
I wanted the other occupation.
Good food, clean dresses.
So?
I had a brother, Stefan.
He was always so
happy and playful.
But they took him away.
They said he was mentally unfit.
I understand.
Anna, I did not see
you, nor you me.
[whispering in foreign language]
I'm gonna need your
help with this, Joe!
I'm gonna fly right
up beside that train.
I need you to look out, see
what you can see inside of it.
You got it!
[train chugging]
[gentle music]
All right, what
do you see, Joe?
[train chugging]
I don't see anything.
Can you see the windows on
the other side of the train,
can you see all the way through?
[Joe] I don't see anything.
And you couldn't
see through the cars
to the other windows.
I don't see anyone,
there's no one on this train.
You can't tell
anything from back there.
I saw one man on this train,
the engineer, that's it.
[plane engine roaring]
Any slower than this
and we won't be flying.
This train's not
in it for the race.
[train chugging]
Hey Cole, Cole, look out!
[plane engine roaring]
Hold on.
[dramatic music]
[plane engine roaring]
That was pretty even close.
Where the hell did
that buzzard come from?
Gonna make on the guns?
No, no, no, get back on the
stick with the bombardier.
Gotta drop those eggs.
[plane engine roaring]
[dramatic music]
Hey, Joe, I'm gonna climb
a couple hundred feet,
get us up above 600 so you
can drop that carton of eggs.
Get ready!
[train chugging]
I'm headed back
to the train, Joe.
I don't see our jet but
I'm sure he's still around.
[plane engine roaring]
[train chugging]
[guns firing]
What are you doing, Cole?
[bombs whistling]
[explosion booming]
[plane engine roaring]
Come on, come on.
[engines roaring]
[train chugging]
What are you doin', Cole?
Look, we gave it our best shot.
But we only had one shot.
It's time to get back, buddy.
[plane engine roaring]
That jet pilot
know what he's doing.
I don't think we're
gonna make it back
in this crate today, Joe.
[plane engine roaring]
[train chugging]
Joe, I want you out of the plane
as soon as we're jump safe.
Okay.
What the hell are you gonna do?
This ain't no suicide mission.
[engines roaring]
[dramatic music]
Stop.
Do you hear me?
Stop the train, now!
[brakes squealing]
Stop the train!
I'm trying!
[guns firing]
[brakes squealing]
[engineer yelling]
[explosion booming]
No, no, no!
[train crashing]
[pilot groaning]
[dramatic music]
[metal crashing]
[both gasping]
[Joe] Easy, easy, easy.
[birds chirping]
[Cole groaning]
Easy.
Oh, damn, I'm gonna
miss that old crate.
We'll get you another one.
You okay?
Yeah, I'm sore.
And my legs hurt.
Just be ready to grab
your pistol at any time.
You should get the Medal
of Honor for that one.
[laughs] Yes, best intentional
crash of a B-17 ever.
[Joe laughing]
What's the story on
Cole and his brother, sir?
Well, it's not good.
Yes, and?
Well, the 17 went down.
But Joe and Cole, they did jump.
So, I'm gonna need a volunteer
to go and pick them up.
That's what I figured.
[sighs] I'm surprised the
Germans ain't shown up yet.
Yeah, their resources are
spread pretty thin right now.
Let's take stock of what
we got in case they do.
I got a pistol and a
flare, what do you got.
I got my pistol
and a chocolate bar.
[both laughing]
Chocolate bar, break out.
I'll trade you my flare
for half of it. [laughs]
That sounds like a fair shake.
There you go.
I'll give you the flare later.
[Joe laughs]
[sirens wailing]
[dramatic music]
[Ellen gasping]
[Maggie] You all
right, sweetheart?
Uh huh, okay.
[Maggie] Bad dreams again.
Yeah.
Well, you never want to
talk about your dreams,
but you can, if you want to.
Well, yes, but this time
it wasn't a nightmare.
But still about
your father, right?
Well, I think any day now
he's gonna be walking
up to the front door
and he's gonna give us both
the biggest hugs in the world.
And this war will all be over.
Well, you know what I think?
I think you need
to get back in bed
and go back to sleep
so you can back
to that dream, that's
a wonderful dream.
Love you, Momma.
I lovey you, sweetheart.
And you know your
daddy loves you too.
I know he does.
[somber music]
I tell ya, I sure do
miss my little girl.
Well, I miss Maggie of course,
but, I'm missing her growing up.
How old is she now?
11, I've missed two
birthdays already.
You reckon you'll
ever settle down?
Hm, maybe I'll find me
a nice French mademoiselle
over here and take
her home with me.
Think Mama would like that?
I reckon she'd be fine with it
as long as you give her
some more grand young ens.
Oh Lord, I guess
that's part of it.
Yep.
[gentle music]
Hey Joe, come on!
Hey, what are you doing, Joe?
Why aren't you up?
The movies, Mom wants
us to go to the movies
with her after supper tonight.
I haven't had any bites yet.
What, come on, Joe,
you have to come.
This is the big one.
What do you mean, the big one?
Are you kidding?
Pilots, war planes, explosions.
Fine, you do whatever you want.
Me and mom will go without ya.
Don't want to but we will.
Mom ain't gonna
go with just you.
Fine, then I'll drive
and leave both of you.
I have to see this movie, Joe.
You do not understand.
[birds chirping]
[footsteps thudding]
Thanks, Ma, that was great.
Yes, ma'am, thank you.
So, when can we
go to the theater?
Hold your horses now.
That movie doesn't
start for another hour.
Will there be cartoons first?
There usually are.
You boys are lucky,
you get to hear what
people are saying.
Do you remember it was
just a couple of years ago
that you had to read the
words when people talked.
But it's hard when you're
first learning to read.
But it made you a
better reader, didn't it?
I suppose.
Cole, why don't you tell us
why tonight's movie
is more important
than some of the others.
Well, it's on account that
it's about the fighter pilots.
The ones who fought in The
Great War, just like our daddy.
It's a memorial to all
the daddies that fought
and didn't come back,
just like your daddy.
Were they all fighter pilots?
Of course not, Joe.
Some of them fired cannons
and some of them rode
in those big old tanks.
But so many of them
were foot soldiers
that fought in those
terrible, terrible trenches.
I prayed and I prayed.
I prayed that there would
never be another war
and that you boys would never
have to go away to fight.
Can we go to the
theater now, Ma?
All right, already,
let's go to the theater.
[gentle music]
Now you tell me
that wasn't the most
amazing movie you ever saw.
Did you like it, Joseph?
I liked it but
I didn't get it.
You didn't get it?
What did you not get?
Let him talk, Cole.
How come when the
pilots shot their guns
the propellers didn't break off.
It's all in the
mechanics, don't you see,
it's all about gears and stuff.
Oh, okay.
Do you know what I want
to be when I grow up, Cole?
What, Joe?
[Joe] A hero.
[Cole] What kind of hero?
A cowboy marshal
from the Old West.
[Cole] The Old West, huh?
I wanna have six guns blazing.
So, what do you want to
be when you grow up, Cole?
Me?
[dramatic music]
I think a...
[plane engine roaring]
Ah, that's a B-38, help me
up, help me up. [groaning]
J-Bomber, 22, thank God.
It's still gonna be
tight for us though.
I'm gonna pop
one of them flares.
Okay, but wait til it's close.
Not too close.
They have limited sight
distance underneath.
Got it.
Joe, I'm gonna put
in some paperwork
with the CO when I get back.
Get you a ticket home.
Okay.
Well, you too.
We're brothers,
we stick together.
Maybe I'll put in a
word for both of us.
I think that's a good idea.
So, why all the cloak
and dagger, Colonel.
You'll understand in a moment.
But let me say as I've indicated
on the other
mission you went on,
this is strictly volunteer.
And this endeavor is top secret
and you'll understand why
when you take a look at that.
Okay, it's a 109,
what about it, sir?
That's what you're going
to fly to get this started.
You've got to be
kidding me, sir.
Of course we had to
patch her up a bit,
get her in flying shape.
Well, obviously.
But how the hell did
you come by this?
Well, this delightful
Nazi pilot landed it
in a field near here.
I guess he had a little
case of self-preservation.
[throat clearing]
How's she fly?
We don't know.
No combat pilot's
taken her up yet.
Maybe you'd like
to be the first.
Wow, you get all
the spiffy toys.
[plane engine roaring]
Who's at the controls?
My brother.
Why doesn't that surprise me.
Around here he's gonna
get shot out of the sky.
Where are they sending him?
[Joe] I don't know,
he won't tell me.
But he's your brother.
That don't mean nothin'.
Joe's right,
Major Phillips isn't
gonna compromise his mission.
Hey, look, he's waving at us.
Everybody wave back.
Hey, Major.
Ah, Major Phillips, you're
gonna get your ass shot off.
[plane engine roaring]
What do you think?
She handles real nice, sir.
That's what I hear.
Oh, your brother here has
decided to stick around.
He's ready to go home but
he wants to wait around here
til you finish the mission.
I guess he can't
stand the suspense.
You're just
stickin' around here
til I get back
from this mission?
You think that's a good idea?
Knowing Mama, I think
she'd be a whole lot happier
if the both of us come walking
up that sidewalk of hers.
I can't argue with that.
But it may not be a
permanent ride home for me.
Are you serious?
We've still got a war to win.
And it ain't over yet.
[wind howling]
Fraulein von Falenburg,
I have heard many
of your broadcasts, so I'm very
familiar with your persona.
However, I know very
little about you.
How did you get
your start in radio.
I was an actress in
Berlin, a theater actress,
not one of those
degenerate cabaret girls.
I had my own company.
We performed the great classics,
Goethe, Schiller and
of course, Shakespeare.
The English do not
appreciate him.
He has the true German spirit.
Of course, I played
Portia and Gertrude.
But my favorite role
is Lady Macbeth.
Out, out damn spot!
Out, I say!
Gone tumor, and it
is time to do it.
Hell is murky.
Fie my lord, fie.
A soldier and afeard.
But need you fear, no that
none can call out power to it.
Yet who would have thought
the old man would have
so much blood in him.
She's riveting,
I must meet her.
[Falenburg] Yes, the
smell of the blood.
I will introduce
you after the show.
All the perfumes of
the lady will not sweeten
this little hand.
Ah, ah to bed, to bed.
There's knocking at the gate.
Come, come, give me your hand!
What's done cannot be undone.
To bed.
[audience applauding]
[people chattering]
Do you know who this man
is at the second table?
That is one of the
leaders of the Reich.
That is Herr Joseph Goebbels,
Minister of Propaganda.
Ah, yes, I'm very
familiar with his work.
Her Goebbels would very
much like to speak with you.
Certainly.
My compliments,
Fraulein von Falenburg.
The British could
learn a lesson or two
from your marvelous
presentation of Shakespeare.
[people chattering]
Shakespeare has the
true Aryan spirit.
This the British no
longer understand.
I understand that
most your repertoire is
of German origin.
That is correct, following
the directive from your office.
Germany has produced the
finest literature in the world.
Your theater company
has done excellent work
at presenting our
glorious heritage.
But tell me, how long til
the end of your season?
A matter of weeks.
[Joseph] Splendid, I may
have something else for you.
An assignment?
Yes, an assignment
on a national platform.
I would like to
know the details.
Fraulein, have you
ever worked on a radio?
Radio?
Oh, no, I have not.
But I am a very quick study.
You have a very
good voice for it.
My associate will
arrange an appointment
in my office next week if
you have the time for it.
I will make the time.
Things were very
difficult in the Republic.
Everyone was starving,
we could barely survive.
The foreigners and the Jews
are corrupting our country.
And then Herr Hitler
came to power.
Well there were jobs, and
the undesirables were gone.
People could come to
the theater again.
They could even have cars.
Herr Goebbels wanted
only pure German art
for the glory of the party.
And so he asked me
to help improve the
quality of the culture.
And so I went on the radio.
To the benefit of all.
Thank you, Fraulein von
Falenburg, for your dedication.
Afternoon, the usual?
[Joe] Yes, ma'am.
Joe, what are you
still doing here.
I heard you got your
papers to go home.
Yeah, I just figured
I'd wait it out,
go home with my brother.
Well, isn't that sweet.
Wait for your brother.
[Men] Whoa!
[Colonel] You hear that,
she thinks you're sweet, Joe.
Don't be startin'
them kind of rumors.
I got a beautiful wife
waiting on me at home.
What can I get
for ya, Colonel?
[Colonel] Whisky, please.
This is Thuringia in Germany.
Down here there's a hill,
or you could call it a small
mountain if you prefer.
It's known as the Kohnstein.
It's outside the
town of Nordhausen.
And it was at one
time a gypsum mine.
These days it's an
underground assembly area
for the V-2 rockets.
I believe you've seen one.
Yes, sir, I have.
As you know, these rockets
have been terrorizing
the people of England.
And that was certainly
Hitler's intention all along.
So as you can imagine,
this has been a high
priority target for the RAF.
But it's in a mountain.
Right.
We may be coming close
to ruling the skies
but the Germans have
a pretty good grip
on the subterranean.
So what can be tried that
hasn't been tried, sir?
Perhaps the 109 you flew.
Does it have the range?
Well as long as the tank
under the belly is full.
Without it, you
won't make it back.
Yeah, if I make
it through the raid,
our own guys will be shooting
at me on the way back.
Mm, it's a bit
tricky, isn't it.
Yeah, just a bit.
What can a single 109 do
that the thousand
British bombers haven't?
Good question.
The only time these
rockets are vulnerable is
when they're being brought
out of the facility.
They truck 'em out on their
own trailers to fuel them.
What's the fuel?
Liquified oxygen
and ethyl alcohol.
Wow, science fiction, sir.
How do we know so much
about the inner
workings of this place?
Well, we have
someone on the inside.
So with the fuel tank I
won't have a belly bomb.
[Richards] Correct.
So what do I
have to shoot with?
The ship only
has two wing guns
and unfortunately,
it arrived empty.
What's the caliber, sir.
13 millimeter, that's
close to our 50 caliber
but the rounds
won't cycle through.
However.
Yes?
The 109 does have a
center lying cannon.
Cannon?
30 millimeter.
And it arrived
loaded, 65 rounds.
[laughs] Yes.
30 millimeter should be enough
to penetrate those tankers.
But they don't open
the doors very often.
This man on the inside,
I'm gonna hope he knows
when those tunnel doors
are gonna be open, sir.
Yes, but never
at the same time.
It changes, every day.
So, I need your man
to get me a message
when those tunnel doors
are gonna be open.
I'll see what I can do.
What should be
the message, sir.
It is, "The time has
come for all good men
"to come to the aid
of their country."
[Pilot] I heard
they're planning
on putting 1,000 planes
in the air next week.
[whistles] 1,000,
that's crazy.
[Pilot] I don't
think it's possible.
Oh, it's possible,
the Brits did it
more than two years ago.
[Pilot] Night raid?
That's right.
Must have been fighters
and bombers together
to get that number.
Oh, actually, it
was 1,046 bombers.
Very few fighters
made that trip.
[Joe] What was the target?
The target was Cologne.
Cologne, but that's still a...
Still a target, yes.
Higher ups in the RAF thought
they could shock the Germans
into surrendering once
they felt the mighty fist
of 1,000 war birds
strike at the same time.
[Pilot] How many
bombers did they lose?
4%, acceptable
losses at the time.
But the losses got
worse after that.
Especially when we beefed up
our daytime operations
early last year.
Was there a major
military target
in Cologne that was
worth that kind of raid?
Plenty of military
sites across the city.
The primary target
was the city center.
First wave went in with
fire bombs, incendiaries.
Created a fire so damn big you
could see it for 100 miles.
Fire also created a
very easy to find target
for the rest of the bombers.
This was two years ago?
Yes, and after that,
the Germans beefed up
their anti-aircraft defenses.
These rockets you
see dropping out
of the sky over London now?
Damn Germans claim it's payback
for us torching their cities.
Didn't they do that to
the Brits first back in '40?
Yes, Joe, that's right and
don't any of you forget that.
You understand?
Yes, sir.
[plane engine roaring]
[dramatic music]
[Cole sighs]
[wind howling]
So where is everybody?
Downstairs eating
with von Falenburg.
[Issac] I have noticed
increased activity.
Are you prepared to send
a message today, Issac?
[Issac] I am.
And do you
remember the message?
[Issac] I do.
The tunnel must be open in
order to move the rockets out.
When the tunnel is open,
you will see daylight
in the far corner
of the facility.
This is very important.
You must sent the message
when the rockets
are in the tunnel.
You must sent it at
that precise time.
Very well, Captain,
I shall do this,
though I feel it will
not end very well for me.
I am leaving, Issac.
I will leave a pistol
with the radio equipment.
Von Falenburg will
likely not return
to her office
until this evening.
Once you have sent the message,
lock yourself in your
office as best you can.
Thank you, Captain.
[Joe] Mind if I join
you for a little bit, sir?
Of course not, but you know
I can't discuss classified
information with you.
I understand that, sir.
I'm just worried about Cole.
I'm afraid he might be in over
his head on this one, sir.
He is an interesting
breed, your brother, Joe.
Seems to thrive on the risk.
That he is, but I think
he's just truly doing
what he can do to
get home safe, sir.
That is a good attitude.
But sometimes, Joe,
I think you may be
mostly just along for the ride.
[laughs] Yeah, it is
a hell of a ride, sir.
Colonel, sir!
[Richards] Yes, Lieutenant.
How come Major Phillips gets
all these secret
service missions.
Because the Major knows how
to handle himself in
precarious situations.
He gets them on account of
he usually don't come back hit.
Yeah, okay.
That is a bonus.
It's back to work, fellas.
I'll report back to you
when I've got more
information for you.
[Pilot] Yes, sir.
Yes, sir, please do.
[plane engine roaring]
[machines whirring]
[lights clicking]
[door creaking]
[engines puttering]
[plane engine roaring]
[switches clicking]
[engines puttering]
Now is the time
for all good men
to come to the aid
of their country.
Now is the time for all good men
to come to the aid
of their country.
That's it, that's it.
[plane engine roaring]
[suspenseful music]
It was Issac.
[plane engine roaring]
Okay, 30 millimeter.
Don't let me down.
[guns firing]
Close the door
to the tunnel, now!
[guns firing]
Did you hear that Captain?
Of course I heard it.
Where is the Jew?
He's disappeared.
You told him to
do that broadcast.
I don't know what
you are talking about.
You will not shoot
an unarmed lady.
I don't see a lady.
[plane engine roaring]
20, I think I can.
[machines puttering]
[gun firing]
[artillery firing]
Maybe 40?
[plane engine roaring]
[gun firing]
Close the door
to the tunnel, now!
[gun firing]
[plane engine roaring]
Give me some lovin'.
[gun firing]
[explosions booming]
[Cole cheering]
[plane engine roaring]
[explosions booming]
[phone ringing]
Hello?
Hello, Malcolm.
Hello, Rob, it's good
to hear your voice.
Malcolm, I have some good
news, some very good news.
Malcolm, Malcolm are you there?
Yes, yes, Rob,
please continue.
The Kohnstein plant,
it has been destroyed.
Malcolm?
100%?
Yes, 100%.
Our plan worked
just like a charm.
Very good, Rob, you
must make your way here
and give me the details.
Heading your way.
[phone clicking]
[somber music]
[Richards] As Major Cole
Phillips headed back west
after torching the
Kohnstein, the adrenaline
that had rushed through him
during the raid
began to subside.
He had executed his
mission with precision
and bravery and no
small amount of luck.
He had prevented the
swarm of chaos and death
that the V-2 rockets
would have caused
if they had reached
their targets
in London and the
surrounding areas.
Armed with a single
enemy fighter
and one vital piece of
intelligence information,
he was able to do what 1,000
Allied were unable to do
over the course of dozens of
bombing raids on the Kohnstein.
Now, flying in the
cloak of darkness,
and at low altitude to try
to avoid other aircraft
from either side,
Cole saw a landscape
that had been decimated
by the conflict that he and
his brother been part of.
As a pilot of a B-17,
all of his raids,
except one of course, were
at very high altitudes.
Putting a physical and
psychological distance
between him and his targets.
The destruction in the German
cities was nearly complete.
But he knew the
destruction would continue
until the job was finished.
You okay, Joe?
Yeah, just kind of thought
we'd have heard something
by now, you know?
We will, soon.
Hope so.
[wind howling]
[suspenseful music]
[Richards] The further west
Cole got the colder it became
in the cockpit of the
ME-109 he was flying.
The clouds came
in, and he realized
he was being accompanied
by a winter storm.
Well, it was January after all.
The crews back at the base
in England has done
a fine job getting
the crashed 109 airworthy
and battle ready.
But they didn't
quite have the time
and the parts they
needed for everything
and the cockpit heaters
didn't have first priority.
I know this for a fact,
I'm Colonel Richards,
Bomber Squadron Commander,
U.S. Army Air Corps.
So at this point, the fact
that he was not traveling
at those bitterly cold,
high altitudes was
probably saving Cole's life.
[wind howling]
[plane engine roaring]
[upbeat music]
[people chattering]
Thank you, Margie.
All right, gentlemen, listen up.
The mission that Major
Phillips went on is classified.
So I can't talk about it.
But what I can tell you is that
there's been several reports
of a radio transmission
coming from a single aircraft
that's traveling west, over
the Channel towards us.
Now that radio transmission
has been heard many times
by a number of sources.
And the contents of that
transmission are as follows.
"I am an American pilot,
"flying west in a
captured German 109.
"I am unarmed.
"Please don't shoot me down."
[men laughing]
All right, at ease now.
The last word is there's
a patrol of Spitfires
that have located this aircraft.
And these Spitfires,
I'm happy to say,
are now accompanying
the 109 back here to us.
What do you think, huh?
[glasses clinking]
We're going home,
Cole, we're going home.
[plane engines roaring]
[gentle upbeat music]
[Cole laughing]
[triumphant music]
[Joe] Hey, I missed you.
It's good to see you.
Hey, I missed you so much.
Mommy said that you had to
jump out of your airplane.
Hey, hold on, honey, let me
tell you how that happened.
Now your uncle was
flying the plane,
and I had to bank
right real hard,
we had these Krauts
coming in behind us
with these jet engines,
and he fell right out
of the side of the plane
where he was a waste gunner.
Couldn't go back
and get him, though,
so we had to let him
use his parachute.
That is not the way
it happened at all.
Don't listen to a
thing your uncle says.
I agree with Maggie.
All right, soldiers, put
your napkins in your laps.
This meal has been blessed,
let's help ourselves.
All right, dig in.
[gentle music]
What are you
doing alone in here?
Everybody's still eating.
You hung up the picture.
Weren't sure you
were gonna like it.
What's not to like?
Apparently now I'm just
a piece of hardware.
[Cole laughing]
How'd you do it, Cole?
[Cole] How'd I do what, Mom?
Joe was behind
enemy lines, right?
How'd you get him back?
That wasn't me, Ma.
That was all Joe, well,
with a little help
from the Resistance.
Oh my word.
[laughs] He can be
a tough character, Ma.
[Ma sighs]
What's for dessert?
Pound cake, your
favorite, come on.
Mm, I'll take a
little more gravy.
It's been a long time since
I've had your gravy, Ma.
[Joe] It sure beats what
they make in the mess hall.
I'll pass it to you.
[Cole] Oh, I don't know.
Yeah, the officer's
mess was pretty good.
Well, they did at least
feed you all something, right?
[Cole] Oh, they did, plenty
of it too, whatever it was.
[Joe] Yeah, might
get enough of this.
I've been waiting, oh my.
Oh, I missed this.
It's so good to
have you boys home.
It's good be home.
I sure missed you guys.
And we definitely missed you.
I know she did.
[Joe] It's gonna be good
to sleep in my own bed.
[all laughing]
Yeah.
Well, Malcolm, Major Phillips
and his brother are back
with the family in the States.
That is wonderful news.
However, I would have liked
to have met the Major.
He did an extraordinary job.
He sure did.
And he told me if we needed him
to come back to finish
it, he would do so.
We all hope that
won't be necessary.
Malcolm, I want to
tell you something.
This Nazi push into
Belgium last month,
it's really got me concerned.
In what way?
I'm wondering what else
they have up their sleeve.
I'm concerned they're gonna drag
this conflict on as
long as possible.
That is a concern.
A prolonged endeavor
would allow them more time
to further develop these
technological terrors
that we've all
been hearing about.
I really wish I knew exactly
what was going on
in the Kohnstein.
[Malcolm laughs]
Malcolm, what are
you smiling about?
Colonel, the reason I've
called this meeting is
today I can help
you with that wish.
Tell me.
You will remember that
I've had a man on the inside.
Yes, yes, but...
He made it back
to London yesterday
and I thought that a
meeting between you and me
and this man should be carried
out as soon as possible.
[Rob] Of course,
where do we need to go?
Andrew, you may come
in and have a seat.
[Andrew] Colonel Thompson,
I've heard so much about you.
Certainly pleased
to meet you, mister?
Andrew, just Andrew.
I prefer to use my first name
only, I'm sure you understand.
Of course.
So you just came here
from the Kohnstein?
I've been back and
forth over enemy lines
several times during the war.
I was at the Kohnstein
up until the point
where your Major Phillips
executed his mission.
Right, so correct
me if I'm wrong.
Are you an American?
[Andrew] Yes, sir.
Not U.S. Army.
No, sir, I was
working in London
in 1940 as a German translator.
Mr. Wilkinson's office
put out the word
that there was a great need
for people who
spoke fluent German.
I was happy to assist.
Back at the Kohnstein,
who did they think you were?
[laughs] A captain in the S.S.
Really?
Well, you are a man
of many talents.
Did anybody else survive?
What about this Colonel Raiden?
Ah, Colonel Raiden, the man
in charge of the ME-262 program.
He was not there that day.
Rumor has it he was meeting
with von Braun about
a new aircraft.
Warner von Braun, the chief
architect of the V-2 rocket?
Correct.
He would stop by occasionally
to check on the progress
of the V-3 which was to
be a much larger rocket.
V-3, I thought they
were calling it the V-9.
It was called many
things over time.
Von Braun's chief
propulsion engineer was
a Jewish man named,
Issac Abromowicz.
He and von Braun went to
college together in Berlin.
A Jew, a Jew
engineering Nazi rockets?
He and his family were slaves.
At my request, Issac sabotaged
the plans for the V-3.
He was with us.
Well, is there any chance
that the Nazis can
restart the plan?
The mission was a success,
the damage was extreme,
there is no longer any
manufacturing capacity
at the Kohnstein.
I just hope Issac made
it out of there alive.
Do you know if
anyone else survived?
The highest ranking officer
was a General Stahkmann.
He was there during the attack
but I'm not sure
what happened to him.
Same goes for Fraulein
von Falenburg.
Who?
You might know her
as the Dresden Doll.
Yeah, our crews talk
quite a bit about her.
She was the voice of the
Nazi propaganda machine.
Was she stationed there?
She arrived from Berlin
several months ago.
What are your
thoughts, Colonel?
Andrew, on any
of your missions,
have you ever had to
terminate somebody?
[sighs] That was never
the primary purpose
of my assignments.
However, during the course of
completing those assignments,
such things have happened.
Malcolm, in regard to
our combined opportunities,
I see three priorities.
And I'll list these
priorities in ascending order.
One priority is this
Luftwaffe Colonel Raiden
and these new jets that
they call the Comet.
Another priority is
Warner von Braun.
The Russians are
looking for von Braun.
We all know that.
What's the third priority?
Why, Adolf Hitler himself.
What are your
thoughts, Andrew?
In regards to termination?
I would agree that
possibly Colonel Raiden,
definitely Hitler as targets.
However, with von Braun,
I think we should consider
acquisition over termination.
Why so?
What makes von Braun
a valuable target
and potentially
incredibly dangerous is
not the man himself
but his work.
His advances in rocket
technologies could,
in the hands of the wrong
governments, be catastrophic.
Regardless, regardless
of what happens
with Germany at this point.
So, Andrew, are you up
for another assignment?
I'm not busy next month.
I'm at your disposal, Marshall.
Of the three
assignments outlined,
which do you believe is best
suited towards your talents?
Let me see what I
can do with Raiden
and von Braun first. [laughs]
And then I'll see what I
can do about Herr Hitler.
[sirens wailing]
Oh, here we go again.
Well, gentlemen, let's
head towards the basement.
About 10,000 V2 rockets
were fired at England.
2,419 of them reached London,
killing 6,184 and injuring 17,981 people.
[somber music]
[dramatic music]
[gentle music]
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
[plane engine roaring]
[dramatic music]