(Multicom Jingle)
(eerie music)
(crickets chirping)
(footsteps creaking)
(window rustling)
(wind chimes chiming)
- (gulping) You scared me!
- Well now you know how we feel.
- Mom.
- [Becky] Oh, please don't Mom me.
- [John] Stacy.
- Uh Lord, you smell of beer.
- Let me handle this.
- Why are you taking her side?
- No one is taking anyone's side.
- Because you stay out till
all hours getting drunk.
You're gonna end up pregnant.
- [John] Becky!
- Like mother, like daughter.
- Now stop it, both of you.
- Don't you let her twist this around.
Johnny go back to bed.
- [Johnny] Fine.
- Fine, she's daddy's
little girl, you handle it.
- Daddy--
- I don't want to hear it, Stace.
- I just wanna live my own life.
- Well then just finish school, all right.
That's all we want, is
for you to graduate,
maybe go to college, even.
You know, make something of yourself
so that you don't wind up waiting tables
and painting houses like me
and driving a cab nights
just to make ends meet.
Stace, there are times in your
life when you make a decision
and that decision it affects
the rest of your life
and if you make the wrong one--
- Me living on my own,
it just makes sense.
- Well it doesn't to us.
Now you're grounded Stacy.
(door thuds)
(upbeat country music)
♪ No time to keep all those promises now ♪
♪ Now is the time for goodbyes ♪
♪ One of these days I've
come a long distance ♪
♪ No stopping me, don't you try ♪
♪ I'm giving back all
those rules you gave me ♪
♪ Maybe they were working for you ♪
♪ All I can I say is
I'm out of here baby ♪
♪ Got me some living to do ♪
- [Johnny] Stacy, Stace?
- Don't come in.
- Dannie's out front.
- I thought you were going to school.
- What are you doing?
- Don't say anything, okay?
Just let us get a head start.
Sorry Johnny
but if I stay the fighting
will only get worse.
♪ Got me a new set of plans I'm making ♪
- Come here.
♪ Freedom's calling to me ♪
- Be strong, okay?
Love you.
♪ Look out the window ♪
♪ At what I've bee missing ♪
♪ Dreams of a life that would be ♪
♪ It's me at last, trading in my past ♪
♪ Running wild and free ♪
♪ You had your say, now I'm on my way ♪
- [Dannie] Ready?
- I was born ready.
♪ They say it's time to
start thinking about ♪
♪ Time to be getting around ♪
- Stacy, Stace?
Johnny?
Jo, hey, where's Stace?
- I don't know.
- Well have you seen her?
- Not since this morning.
Mom the guys are waiting.
- Well go, have fun.
- [Johnny] Okay.
- Dinner is at six.
- [Johnny] Okay, I gotta go.
- Stace?
(dog barking)
(gentle music)
(crickets chirping)
- No we'll call if we hear from them.
Okay bye.
Well you were right, Danielle's gone too.
- Well not for long.
I mean, what, they can't have
more than $200 between 'em.
- Said Dannie took her sleeping bag.
- What do you think they're camping?
(Becky laughs)
Those two think that a
slumber party is roughing it.
No, I think they'll be
home inside of a week
unless someone gives 'em money.
- (scoffs) Don't look at me.
- Runaway, can you believe it?
I mean what is she?
18 going on six?
(Becky sighs)
(John sighs)
(traffic humming)
- Don't even say it.
- Stace!
- No I'm not going back.
- Damn it Stace.
My dad, he says they'll
cut off my college money.
- I thought you were my friend.
- If you're my friend
you'll get in the car.
Stace, come on, please!
Well what choice do we have?
We're down to, we're
down to $60 between us.
- We can get jobs.
- And where are we gonna live
till we get our first check?
What are we gonna eat?
- We can camp out.
We can take buses.
- Stace, will you get real.
This isn't one of your romantic fantasies.
- Yeah tell me about it.
- What are you doing?
- Don't, just don't okay.
- [Dannie] Oh, what are you gonna do?
Walk to Florida?
- Not if you drive me.
- Stacy, damn it!
(bluesy music)
- Where you going?
- Florida to visit my Gram.
- I can take ya as far as Jackson.
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
- Stacy!
Stacy!
♪ Oh, oh, oh ♪
- Running off with Dannie's one thing
but getting in the truck with a stranger?
- I know, I know.
- She's so naive.
- She's also 18.
I mean she's not a runaway, John.
She's old enough to leave home.
She's not old enough, not emotionally.
- Well, she thinks she is.
The law says she is.
I don't know, maybe we
should just let her go.
- Are you crazy?
- Well our folks did it with us.
(scoffs) We were together.
She's out there all by
herself, on her own.
- Like she wants to be.
I'm sorry, okay, I'm afraid for her.
I'm worried about her but part of me is,
part of me is glad she's gone.
I was so tired of fighting all the time
and now it's, it's peaceful.
(gentle music)
(truck hisses)
- Look the road ain't no place for a girl
and brakes are gonna take
a couple hours to fix,
so get yourself something to eat
and there's a movie in the
lounge, big widescreen TV,
couple hours we'll meet back here
and I'll get ya a ride home,
maybe call your folks,
so they won't worry.
Okay?
- Okay.
♪ There's an empty room ♪
♪ And an empty bed ♪
- Excuse me, where's your phone?
- Out back.
♪ With a picture frame inside it ♪
♪ It's my empty life ♪
♪ It's my empty heart ♪
- Right.
- Yep.
♪ Waiting for someone to find me ♪
(phone ringing)
♪ You were right next door ♪
- Oh, there's no hurry
miss, take your time.
(phone ringing)
♪ Never a thought ♪
- Hello?
Stacy?
Hello, hello?
♪ And my two worlds, take me ♪
(dial tone beeping)
- Where is she?
- Oh honey, she hung up.
(Becky sighs)
(gentle music)
- [Trucker] And I'll
call ya from this phone.
(siren wailing)
- Hey, didn't I see you before?
Stuck-up?
- Discriminating.
- Hey come on--
- Don't
- Hey!
Hey, what's he doing, bothering you?
How many times I got
to tell you, huh, huh?
- [Trucker] Can you take
that somewhere else?
- Miss, miss, I'm sorry about that.
Sometimes he's kind of clumsy.
Eddie go check the truck.
He don't mean no harm.
Just sees beauty and can't resist.
(laughs) Where's my manners?
Richard Brown.
- Hi.
- And you are?
- Stacey Sapp.
- Well, maybe you'd let me make
up for Eddie's bad manners.
Uh, unless you're waiting on someone.
- Just Lou, just a guy who gave me a ride.
- Oh I see and then where you off to?
- Home, I guess.
- Well, Stacey if you
don't mind me saying,
you don't sound too happy about it.
But I know just how you feel.
I ran away myself when
I was about your age.
What am I doing?
I'm about to talk your ear
off with ancient history
and you'd probably rather
be watching a movie.
- Oh no, I saw it already.
(Richard chuckles)
- Yeah so I told those Freeborn boys,
hey you don't want this load of birds
I know someone who does.
- And did you?
- Well not right at that moment. (laughs)
See, there's not too much
market for dehydrated chickens
but sometimes trucking's
like poker and life.
You gotta know how to bluff.
- So what happened?
- Well I laid off the entire load
up in Bismarck North Dakota.
Of course I had to take
a loss on dead birds but.
(Stacy laughs)
You know, that's the price
you gotta pay for freedom
sometimes, you know?
(phone ringing)
- Yeah, I do.
- [Waitress] Is there a Stacy here?
- Uh, that's me.
- [Waitress] Phone.
♪ When you're trying to find your way ♪
♪ When you find a new place ♪
- Hello?
Hm-mm.
Thanks for telling me.
Okay, all right.
(gentle music)
(Stacy sighs)
- Bad news?
- Looks like I'm stuck here all night.
Lou's breaks are worse than he thought.
Well I know lots of guys
will take you back to, uh?
- [Stacy] Rockport.
- Yeah good Samaritans,
guys you can trust.
I mean, if that's what
you're really wanting to do.
- What choice do I have?
- Well I guess that kind
of depends, now don't it?
On what you're wanting
to do with your life.
See sometimes there are these moments
where what you decide
changes everything, you know?
- That's something my dad says too.
- Well hey, great minds
think alike. (laughs)
I was just thinking maybe you might like
to head out west, to Vegas?
Well anyways it's just
something to think about
while you're waiting on old Lou.
We're the maroon rig third row over.
It's been awful nice talking you Stacy.
Hey and you got to remember here.
(speaks in foreign language)
No.
It's Latin.
It means never let the
bastards grind you down.
Beautiful.
Make sure the waitress gets change there.
- All set.
- We're gonna wait.
- [Eddie] Hey man with
all the lot lizards,
what do you want with some jailbait hick?
- There's a lot to be said for innocence.
(diners chattering)
(soft rock music)
(truck rumbling)
- Well told you.
- [Stacy] Richard!
- [Richard] Stacy!
- I just thought, I mean,
you know I'm probably gonna go home
but right now I'm not sure.
So I was thinking that
maybe I could ride with you
until I made up my mind.
- Course.
- Great.
I left my stuff with Lou.
- Oh don't worry about it.
- [Stacy] But my clothes.
- I'll buy you new ones.
New clothes for a new life.
- Okay.
- A loan, I didn't bring
that much stuff anyway.
- Sure, come on, climb aboard.
Let's beat it.
Climb back to the other side.
Get comfy, all right.
- I'm telling you, man, she's trouble.
- Last time I checked it's my truck,
unless you feel like walking to Vegas.
Why don't you get in back.
Okay, going for a ride.
(energetic music)
♪ I got me a new set of legs, I'm making ♪
♪ Freedom's calling to me ♪
♪ Look out at the window
at what I've been missing ♪
♪ Dreams of a life that could be ♪
♪ It's me at last, trading in my past ♪
♪ Running wild and free ♪
♪ You had your say, now I'm on my way ♪
♪ Seems it's time to
start thinking about ♪
♪ Time to be getting 'round ♪
(energetic music)
- Man what if she tells someone your name
or where we are?
- She won't.
- You sure there's no watchman?
- Man, these guys they're
too cheap for a dog.
(energetic music)
(crickets chirping)
(glass shattering)
(Eddie screaming)
Man, that ain't nothing, get out the way.
(glass crunching)
(suspenseful music)
(Stacy sighs)
(phone beeping)
(metal rattling)
(phone ringing)
- Hello?
- [Stacy] Hi mom.
- Stacy!
- [Stacy] Can I talk to Dad?
- He's driving the late shift.
Where are you?
- I'm with friends,
they're giving me a ride out west.
I'm leaving home.
- Stacy don't do this.
- Do what Mom?
Live my life?
- What about your father's life?
What about his feelings?
Do you have any idea how worried he is?
How worried we both are?
- Bye Mom.
- No, no, no, oh, don't hang, uh!
(dial tone beeping)
- Everything okay?
- Yeah.
(phone dings)
(Becky sighs)
- Oh.
(truck rumbling)
(somber music)
(upbeat music)
- [Richard] How's he doing?
- He's doing well, he's asleep
but I still think he needs a tetanus shot
since he cut it on the truck door.
- Hey Florence Nightingale, (laughs)
some sack time he'll be good as new.
- Just know what it feels
like to be sick and alone.
- You?
I'll bet you've never been
alone a day in your life.
Well, just because you live with people
doesn't mean you're not alone.
And sometimes, no, a lot of times,
it feels like I was born into
the wrong family or something.
♪ So now give me ♪
- Which is weird when you think about it
'cause I get along great with Gram.
Yeah, she's got this farm with horses
and this house, like
from Gone With The Wind.
And when I go there and
visit in the summer,
I felt like that's where I really belong.
Except, my mom got jealous.
- [Richard] Yeah, how come?
- We're just different,
not like me and my dad.
No, he respects me.
We can talk and he trusts me.
- Yeah and I can see why.
You're good company, Stace.
Hey look at that sky.
Huh?
♪ You and I are going to be together ♪
♪ Till the day we die, baby ♪
♪ You and I are gonna, gonna ♪
♪ Gonna ride into the sunset ♪
♪ Who knows what we'll find ♪
♪ Leaving yesterday behind ♪
♪ Gonna ride, gonna ride ♪
- Well,
I don't see the point of this.
I think she's made her decision
and she's not coming home.
- Becky, we don't know that.
You know, she could be in trouble.
- Well.
- Just record the call, all right
and she might leave some hint
or clue about where she is.
- All right.
- All right?
- Yeah, all right.
Bye.
- Bye.
- [Stacy] What's he doing back there?
- Why don't you go ask him.
(horn beeping)
(door creaking)
- Hey shut the damn door.
Stacy!
Stace, Stace.
I didn't know it was
you, come on, come here.
Come on.
(Richard grunts)
I'm sorry about yelling.
- [Stacy] It's okay.
- Can I trust you?
- Yeah sure I guess.
- Now don't guess.
We're gonna be road dogs,
I mean traveling buddies,
I got to know.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
You remember Freeborn?
That company that lost me all that money.
Well they're paying for this trip.
- You mean, you like?
- Well I call it justice,
retribution, restitution.
Listen here, if it troubles
you, I'll understand.
I'll put you on a ride back to Illinois
first chance we get, no hard feelings.
- What's in there?
- Oh that.
I'll show you later.
- [Stacy] Promise?
- I promise.
Come on.
(gentle music)
- Freeborn Trucking, never heard of it.
- Me neither, til I
started driving for 'em.
- [Cashier] Hm.
- [Man On TV] So did you get the job?
- [Man On TV] Get the job?
Hey, I didn't even get the interview.
(people on television laughing)
- Seems so strange doesn't it?
Stacy could be watching that same program,
laughing at the same jokes.
- Yeah well you're assuming
she's even in the same time zone. (scoffs)
- You know what I mean.
- Yeah I do.
(Becky sighs)
You know sometimes I wonder
if I was too hard on her
because I was worried, you know,
and I loved her so much
and I wanted so much for her.
- I know you did.
She was my little girl,
John, we were friends.
Then one day I just woke
up and I was the enemy.
Anyway you were right,
I did always have to have the last word
but right about now I'd
sure like to hear her voice.
(traffic humming)
- Well, how do these look?
- Hm-mm.
- Like a whore who thinks she's a virgin.
Hey!
- What kind of thing is that to say?
- [Eddie] Man it was just a joke.
- Man apologize, apologize.
- It's okay, it's all right.
(door knocks)
- [Richard] Who is it?
- [Delivery Man] Pizza.
That'll be 16.95.
- Here keep the change.
There'll be none for you.
Not till you tell her you're sorry.
- Richard, it's okay.
- No it's not.
- Come on, man.
Come on.
- [Richard] Want to get the Vegas?
- You buy all this crap for her,
I can't even have a
stinking slice of pizza?
- [Richard] You want pizza?
You want pizza?
(Richard grunts)
- Richard stop!
- You're drunk.
Get out.
You want money?
Here get yourself a room
'cause you sure as hell
ain't sleeping here.
(Eddie crying)
You deaf?
Move!
(Eddie grunting)
- I'll go, I'll go.
- No, I'll go.
(Eddie crying)
- Its okay, it's okay.
- I'm sorry.
I ain't got no rich grandma.
I got no home to go back
to, no money, no folks.
I gotta get to Vegas.
I didn't mean it.
- I know.
- What I said.
- I know, its okay.
- But it's just that
there's already trouble
and you know, you mean the checks?
- You know?
- Yeah, he told me.
- You want to go to jail?
- I didn't steal anything.
- But you know and he knows you know
and you don't trust nobody,
nobody.
- He trusts me.
He does.
- You don't know,
you don't know what he's like.
- Sure I do.
- You don't.
- I do.
- [Richard] Get out.
- Its okay, I'll come get you
in the morning, I promise.
I promise.
Here.
- I'm sorry
- It's too late.
Sorry about throwing stuff.
- Think when the boy
can't hold his liquor,
talking you that way, that bothers me.
- People drink to block out the pain.
- Oh where'd you hear that on Oprah?
- Hey what did I do?
- Nothing.
Come on.
(somber music)
Let's eat.
It's getting cold, come on.
Just people start talking about pain
to me pain's kids crying for their Mamas
except their Mamas never come.
Guys in lockup screaming, somebody help me
and actually just laugh.
- You were in jail?
- No big thing.
Gambling.
I spent six months on a county
farm, chopping cotton days,
nights listening to guys
whimpering in their sleep.
- I'm sorry.
- Then I saw you.
I knew, said there is a
woman who understands,
not a girl, a woman.
- I'm not that special Richard.
- Look at you, you just starting out.
- That doesn't mean I
don't know what I want.
- Huh.
And What's that?
(gentle music)
Oh, well I ain't the lucky one.
- [Stacy] It's not like
I'm a virgin or anything.
- [Richard] I'm gonna
treat you like you one.
You're old enough to understand
what you're offering,
I'd love to accept.
Stacy!
It's too important to rush.
But don't get me wrong,
it's not like I don't
have feelings and desires,
it's just I don't want you thinking
what I feel for you is just
about sex, ya understand?
I'm not willing to risk my life
counting on some woman who's not sure.
You see?
I did once.
- I am sure.
- Maybe.
I sure hope so, for my sake.
(upbeat music)
(phone ringing)
- Ready?
Hello?
- [Stacy] Daddy?
- Stacy, it's good to
hear from you, honey.
We've been worried.
- [Stacy] I'm fine.
- Where are you?
- I'm fine daddy really, like I told Mom,
I'm with some friends.
- Uh-huh, who?
- [Stacy] Promise you won't get mad?
- We're not mad, honey,
we're just worried.
- I was talking to Dad.
- We just want to know you're okay.
- I'm fine, I'm wonderful.
- [Man] I am, I am.
- I met a man.
- A man?
- It's not what you think, Daddy.
- Now Stace, you--
- He loves me and he's a nice guy too.
He's the one who wanted me to call you
so that you know I was okay.
- Well you tell him that
we appreciate that honey.
What's his name?
- Richard.
- [John] Well why don't you put him on,
maybe Richard and I can have
a little talk, man to man.
- Daddy I have to go.
- No, no honey, um.
- Look Stacy, just call us again, okay,
so that we can sleep nights, all right?
- I will.
♪ Suddenly ♪
♪ So alone ♪
♪ Riding ♪
(dial tone beeping)
♪ Everyone's gonna ♪
♪ Have some fun ♪
- Woo, yeah!
♪ On Friday night. ♪
♪ We're gonna raise the roof, 100 proof ♪
♪ Come Friday night ♪
♪ Gonna flirt ♪
♪ Gonna dance ♪
♪ Might even find romance ♪
♪ Gonna feel all right ♪
♪ Come Friday night ♪
(Stacy laughing)
- [Richard] Come on.
(gentle music)
♪ Only love is forever ♪
♪ Ageless feelings, ending never ♪
♪ Life has led us here ♪
♪ To find forever love ♪
♪ Lonely songs and this longing gone ♪
♪ You've brought to my heart ♪
♪ What feels like the start of our own ♪
♪ Forever love ♪
(Stacy quietly singing)
(door clicking)
- What's wrong?
- Nothing darling.
You remember I promised
when the time was right.
Show her.
(Stacy gasps)
There ain't nothing to be afraid of.
That's just protection.
- Against what, who?
- Eddie can we have some privacy.
Maybe I should have told you before.
All right, sit down down.
But there didn't seem any point,
not if you weren't gonna stay.
Now that you are, well, I
guess you know how I feel.
If anything ever happened to you,
I don't know what I'd do.
Now I'm not saying
something's gonna happen
but you never can tell.
There's lots of weirdos out there.
It's okay for now.
But if you come to feel
the same way about me
as I do about you, mm,
then I might need your
help someday, Stace.
(gentle music)
Mm.
I'd like to know I could count on you.
I just might need your help someday.
(gentle music)
(birds chirping)
(Stacy and Richard laughing)
You know I wanted us to be by ourselves
'cause I want to explain
something about myself,
before we go any further.
See Stace, I was married once before.
Yeah I got two girls.
Of course I haven't seen them in years,
ever since their Mama
went off with another guy.
And I haven't had much to
do with women since then.
Not till I met you.
I just thought you should know.
Seeings how, Stace.
(Stacy gasps)
- I'd feel a lot better about this
if I didn't know where the
money for it came from.
- Stace, as soon as we get to Vegas
I swear I'll burn the checks.
But right now for you
I'd do anything anything.
- Anything?
- You and me.
- Oh, oh!
(John and Stacy laughing)
(somber music)
Anything?
- Come on, Stace, we settled the guns.
- Please, Richard, they scare me.
- Know what scares me?
Not being able to defend a woman
I hope will be the mother of my children.
Now I lost one wife.
- You are not gonna lose me.
- Oh you better believe it.
Now Stace, don't take it,
not if you're not serious,
not if you don't mean to stay.
(gentle music)
Forever?
- Forever.
- Yeah girl!
(Richard and Stacy laughing)
(Stacy screams)
Oh, oh!
(Stacy laughing)
- [Stacy] It's not what you think Daddy.
- [John] Now Stace, you--
- [Stacy] He loves me
and he's a nice guy too.
He's the one who wanted me to call you
so that you know I was okay.
- [Becky] You tell him that we appreciate.
- Wait a minute.
- Look folks, I, uh,
I realize how upset you are,
I got two kids of my own
but the reality is that she's 18.
Legally she's not even a runaway
and it's obvious she's with
this guy voluntarily so--
(tape recorder bangs)
- John, wait a second.
- What do you care?
You don't even want her
back in the first place.
- That is a damn lie.
- She disturbs your precious peace.
- Oh don't you use that against me,
don't you dare.
I told you how I felt
and just because I'm not
screaming and yelling
that doesn't mean that I don't care.
There. (sighs)
(traffic hums)
- [Stacy] No, Richard, no.
- You're gonna be my wife.
You got to get past this fear.
You got to be ready.
Now come on honey, take it.
- Hey Rich, maybe we should just
chill out on the gun thing, you know?
- Get out.
This here's family business.
Come on, get out, Keep Watch.
- For what?
- Just get out.
Now honey, a gun is just a tool.
- To kill people.
- Only if they're trying to hurt you
or someone you love and
only if it's loaded.
Now Stace, Stace.
Would you take the damn gun.
- You, you, you're hurting me.
- Don't make me hurt you more.
Now take the gun.
Take it.
(gunshot rings)
(Stacy screams)
- (screams) Ow, my eye.
- Damn!
- What happened?
- Stupid son of a bitch.
Who told you to load it?
- You did.
- Shut up, just check outside.
(Stacy screaming)
Come on, let me see.
Let me see.
- All clear.
- [Richard] Get the stuff.
Come on, let's go.
- Now what'd you say happen?
- Wood shavings got
thrown from a table saw.
- Hmm, yeah it looks like gunpowder to me.
- [Richard] There was
some graphite mixed in.
- Hm-mm.
- Well, you leave that
patch on for a day or two
and put this ointment on
and I'll get you some
pills for the pain, okay?
- Oh god.
- Keep your mouth shut.
- Hey, you're the one
who got us into this.
- That's right and I'm the
one who's gonna get us out.
- Richard this is a hospital.
- Where you're not
staying, forever remember?
- [Receptionist] Dr. Lynn,
please call line one.
- You all right?
Well if you need anything,
anything at all, you
come on back, you hear?
- Thanks Doc, you've been great.
Hasn't he hun?
Come on.
- [Receptionist] Dr. Kim to room 222.
(phone ringing)
- Didn't I warn ya?
You thought you're so damn
smart, so sophisticated, wannabe.
- I know, I was wrong.
Eddie all we have to do
now is walk out of here.
- We?
- Eddie!
- No and don't start crying,
okay, he'd said you'd cry.
- Okay, okay let me just use
the phone please, please.
- Go ahead.
He said you'd try that too.
- All I want to do is get out of here.
I want to go to Vegas
but not with Richard.
With you.
Please.
Come on.
We can go, please--
- Do you think he just
went through the drugstore
to get some aspirin?
What if this is a test?
Huh?
What if he's right outside that door,
he could kill us both.
- Maybe you're not so dumb after all.
You okay?
(Stacy crying)
I keep telling ya, there
ain't nothing to worry about.
As soon as we get to
Vegas we'll get married
and everything will be okay.
Okay?
Stace?
- Maybe before we get married,
maybe I should go home.
- Home?
You are home with me.
(Stacy crying)
Aren't you?
I love you, I do, but you're scaring me.
- Come on now, don't cry.
I can't stand to see you cry.
What'll make you feel better?
Hm?
- Can I please call my folks?
Please.
(gentle music)
(Stacy sniffling)
(phone ringing)
- [Becky] You've reached the Sapps.
John, Becky, Stacy, and Johnny.
Please leave a message.
(answering machine beeps)
- Hi, Mom, Dad, um Johnny,
I just want to tell you guys that I'm,
that I'm okay and then I'm getting married
but not here in Oklahoma
but in Las Vegas.
- Get me that, damn it!
(Stacy screams)
Damn you're just like all the rest of 'em.
No talent, lying, conniving, bitches.
- Richard, Richard, I'm sorry please.
It just snuck out, please.
(Stacy crying)
- Go downstairs.
Move everything from the
truck to the caddy part side,
remember forever.
Y'all screw up, something happens,
a whole lotta people beside
us could end up dying.
I wouldn't want that on my conscience.
Go ahead.
I ain't gonna hurt you.
Don't you know I love you?
Don't you know I'd do anything for you?
- Please Richard, please.
- I told you.
- Ow!
- Don't put it on
if you don't mean to stay.
Didn't I tell you that?
- I love you, Richard,
but you are scaring me,
don't you understand, I am scared.
(Stacy crying)
- Oh, well I've been
thinking, I've been thinking,
the only, the only reason
we can get in trouble
is the checks, right?
- What if I was to tell
you I figured a way
not to write any more.
Hey, get some money so we
can throw those checks away.
Would you like that?
- Yeah.
- Good, good, good.
Okay here's what we're gonna do.
(suspenseful music)
(truck whooshing)
Get it done?
- Switched the plates
and locked the truck.
- Good boy, start the car.
- Come on man, why don't
we just let her go?
I mean this is crazy.
- Come on.
- I don't think I should do this.
- Hey you're gonna be my wife, remember?
- I know but please, my folks--
- Don't worry, don't worry.
I'll help you convince 'em.
- Richard--
- Hey, who's more important?
Me or them?
Okay.
(phone ringing)
- Hello?
- [Richard] Hey John, how's the Sapps?
- Who is this?
- Daddy?
- [John] Stacy?
- Daddy, I want to come home.
- [John] Where are you honey?
- I can't tell you.
- Are you in Oklahoma?
- All I can tell you is
he wants $30,000.
Ow!
(Stacy screaming)
- You listen here.
I'm done with her.
You want her, you got her for 30 grand.
You got two days now and remember no cops
or I'll send her back a piece at a time.
(dial tone beeping)
(John whimpering)
(Richard laughing)
Yeah that was pretty convincing, huh?
Good job, baby.
(Becky crying)
(traffic whooshing)
- I'm telling you, this is a
shakedown not a kidnapping.
- And that attitude's why
I'm glad the FBI is here now.
- Look Sapp, we're the
ones who called the FBI.
- We're not ruling out anything.
- Thank you.
(Richard snoring)
(door creaking)
(suspenseful music)
- Stacy, Stacy, come on.
Shh, come on.
Hurry up, come on.
- Going somewhere?
- Run!
(Stacy screams)
(Richard and Eddie grunting)
- [Stacy] Eddie, the gun, here.
- Don't move, freeze!
- You think I'm gonna let
you take her away from me?
- No man, I don't want to,
it's just that this ransom thing,
it's gonna bring the cops
down on us, you know?
- Us?
There ain't no us.
Not anymore.
It's her and me.
Well, come on man, do it.
Do it big man.
(suspenseful music)
Ain't so easy killing a
man face to face, is it?
Give me that.
- I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
- Oh god, Richard, please don't hurt him.
(Stacy screams)
- You're history.
You tell anybody, so is she.
(suspenseful music)
(upbeat music)
♪ Gonna live my life ♪
♪ Without you ♪
- So you want to go home, huh?
♪ My mistakes ♪
Hey I'm talking to you.
- Don't want do this, not anymore.
- Yeah, well you're gonna.
♪ Oh who I'd rather be ♪
- Do you hear me?
♪ Nearly got it complete ♪
- Give me that damn thing
♪ You and me ♪
♪ I'm breaking free ♪
- I'm sorry, hun.
(phone beeps)
Okay look, you make another call.
I'll tell you a secret.
Hey five hours, we'll be in Rockport.
Yeah that's right,
all night while you've
been boozing and sleeping
I've been headed to the last
place they'd ever expect us.
(upbeat music)
♪ Oooh ♪
- Just feel like I should be here.
- Yes sir.
I understand that
but just hanging around makes you tense.
Now it'd much better if you just
go about your normal routine.
(phone ringing)
- Hello?
- Put your wife on.
- Becky.
- Just keep him talking.
- Hello?
- All right you listen
and you listen good.
You got the money?
30,000, we don't--
- Maybe you could ask that
rich mom of yours down in Florida.
Maybe she could sell
one of her thoroughbred.
- [Becky] Please don't--
- Just get it.
I'll call tomorrow night
and tell you wear to deliver.
(phone beeps)
- Why did she tell him about Florida?
(somber music)
- Home sweet home, honey.
- Please just let me go.
(traffic humming)
Dad!
(Stacy screaming)
- Stacy?
Stacy!
(tires squealing)
- [Stacy] Dad!
(horn beeping)
(tires squealing)
- Stacy!
Oh god.
- You're here?
- It's just that they caught some guy
who claims he was with Brown and the girl.
- Yeah this guy, Eddie Lowell,
street kid from Newark.
He was with brown when he picked her up.
- What do we got on Brown?
- Uh, he spent his
childhood in a foster home,
since then in and out of
mental hospitals and jail,
drugs and assault.
The man is unpredictable,
we assume he's dangerous.
- Do we tell them that?
- No, not unless it's
absolutely necessary.
Family's under enough strain as it is,
well, with John losing his
job and everything, all right?
- Right, okay.
- Let's go.
- Please, please just let me go.
I won't tell anyone, I promise
you can just disappear.
- I plan to, out of Miami,
down to the islands.
There's still time.
You can still change
your mind, come with me.
If you love me, if you ever loved me--
- I loved you.
If I loved you, you're
the one wanting to leave,
desert me.
- How can I marry you?
When they catch you they're
gonna throw you in jail or...
- Or what?
- I don't want you to die.
I don't want anybody to die.
(somber music)
- Well you see then,
it could have been Stacey
that John saw yesterday.
- It's possible.
- Well what do we know
about this Richard Brown.
- We're still checking on that.
We know he's a trucker.
The Oklahoma State Police found his rig
parked at a truck stop just where
Eddie Lowell said it would be
when they picked him up in Texas.
- Would he really hurt her?
- Look, uh, we always have
to be prepared for the worst
but the good good news is
from what we know now Stacey
really wants to come home.
(phone ringing)
- Hello?
- Don't talk.
You so much as breathe
wrong, she gets hurt.
You double-cross me and she dies.
You got that?
- Yes.
- [Richard] You got the money?
- Not yet, the banks won't loan it to us
and my mother-in-law
has to sell something.
- Yeah, well you got less than 24 hours,
after that she's dead.
- What do you expect us to do?
- (sighs) You deliver the money, alone,
to the Golden Waffle in
Great Plains, Kansas,
8:00 a.m. tomorrow
and remember Daddy, I
know what you look like.
(suspenseful music)
- When do we leave?
- We don't, Mr. Sapp.
Now I understand how concerned
you and your wife are
but we can't put anyone else at risk here.
- But you heard him.
He knows what I look like.
If you try to use one of
your agents, he'll know.
- If you can't keep your
head and follow orders
that's a risk we'll have to take.
(suspenseful music)
(kitten meowing)
- Aw.
(gun clicking)
(cat meowing)
- [Agent] The most important bit
is going along with the plan.
- But what happens to Stacy
if he finds out you don't have the money?
- Won't get that far, son.
As soon as the FBI sees
him, they can grab him.
- Yeah they won't do anything
to put her in danger.
- Yeah right.
- Look Johnny, I'm not
gonna lie to you, okay.
Things could go wrong
but Mr. Harris and his agents
are doing everything they can
to make sure they don't
and what I need from you is for you
to stay here with your
mom and be strong, okay?
(somber music)
(Becky sighs)
- Told you, put the damn cat outside.
- Please let me keep
him, he'll make me happy.
- Like I don't, right?
Come here, come over here.
(cat meowing)
Not gonna hurt you.
You know, all I ever
want, all I ever wanted
is to make you happy
and you could be still.
Stace.
(cat meowing)
Come with me, please.
I love you.
Please.
(gentle music)
(birds chirping)
- Hey Johnny, wake up.
- Becky, there's nothing you can do there.
- If you were me, where would you be?
At home, waiting for the phone to ring
or with your husband and your daughter?
- At least leave the boy.
- No.
- No, can't do that.
He already feels responsible
and well if anything were to happen
he should be with his family.
Look I know you're just
trying to do your job, okay,
but feeling for people
isn't that part of it?
(gentle music)
- Let's go to Kansas, step on it, will ya?
(diners chatting)
- Here you go.
(ominous music)
- Ever read Romeo and Juliet?
Forever, even in death
but don't worry nothing's gonna happen
but if it does, I promise
I'll kill you first.
(cat meowing)
Come here.
Is that him?
- That's him.
(suspenseful music)
(phone ringing)
- Careful, could be watching you.
- Golden Waffle.
Who?
If your name is John Sapp,
there's a guy on the phone
who wants to talk to you.
- All right.
(suspenseful music)
- There you go.
- Yes?
- [Richard] Sapp.
- Now what?
Now she dies, I told you no cops.
- What cops?
There are no cops.
- Yeah there better not be.
- Look please for God's sakes,
can we just get this over with?
- Patience Daddy, patience.
- I see him.
(suspenseful music)
- Can you get a shot?
- Negative, he's using
the girl as a shield
and he's using binocs.
- Miss.
- Look Jed, we gotta move.
Brown's expecting Sapp to
walk out of here right now.
- Hold, hold.
Where's your restroom, Miss?
- [Richard] Come on Daddy.
- Look, what are you doing?
He's already suspicious.
He'll know.
- We got to move.
We can't risk any more lives.
- Put this on, take your shirt off.
- [Richard] Where are you?
Come on, come on.
- John, now look at me.
You carry the bag out in front
of you so Brown to see it.
You take the stairs over there.
When you get to the top of the stairs
he can't see you anymore.
That's where Don here is
gonna take your place.
- Now go.
- No he'll see it's not me.
- It'll never get that
far, never get that far.
Our snipers will take him out before then.
- But look, just let me do it.
- Look Sapp,
I'm gonna say this you
as straight as I can.
Either do this my way or
we're gonna get somebody else.
Okay, button your shirt, come on.
- Come on Daddy.
(suspenseful music)
What took you so long?
- Everybody take position
but be careful he's watching.
Team two you get a shot, you take it.
(suspenseful music)
Come on Daddy, come on baby.
Come on, come on.
- He's starting up the stairs now.
Team two.
- He's pulled back.
- What's wrong?
- Wait till he sees me
and I'm gonna over run 'em.
- Don't do it.
No, he's following orders.
He's bringing the money,
you don't have to hurt him.
- A woman shall leave her father's house
and claim onto her husband.
- Oh no.
- Forever.
- No.
- Give me the bag.
- You're sure?
- I'm sure, Mr. Sapp.
- No don't kill him, no, Daddy.
(Stacy screaming)
- Stacy!
- Watch out, Daddy, it's a trap.
- [Jed] Damn it.
- Let me go, let me go.
- We got him, get him up.
- Come on, let's go, let's go.
Come on.
- [John] Stacy!
(police siren wailing)
(suspenseful music)
(glass shattering)
(gunshot ringing)
- Pull back!
(glass shattering)
(gunshot ringing)
(diners screaming)
(gunshots ringing)
- Hold you fire right there.
Hold your fire.
(police siren wailing)
(gunshots ringing)
(people screaming)
- [Police Officer] He's got a second car.
- [Police Officer] Get in the car.
- [Police Officer] Get down, get down.
(gunshots ringing)
(Stacy screaming)
(Officers shouting)
- [Police Officer] Get down.
- [Police Officer] Hold your positions.
- [Police Officer] Stay there.
Get down!
(suspenseful music)
- What the hell is happening?
- We're still status quo sir.
(door knocks)
- Mr. Sapp, I brought you.
- [John] Oh, thank God.
I'm glad you're here.
- Is Stacy okay?
- What's happening
- Mr. Harris is assessing the situation.
We have a right to know.
I'm sure they'll
communicate with they know.
(gunshots ringing)
(Stacy screaming)
- [Richard] Quiet.
(Stacy sobbing)
(phone ringing)
- Hello?
- Who the hell are you?
- FBI, Special Agent Harris.
Brown, let the girl go now.
We have you surrounded.
- Let her go, let her go.
- [Stacy] No, he's hurting me now.
(gunshots ringing)
(suspenseful music)
- [Dispatcher] One down, 29.
(Dispatcher speaking faintly)
One, three, four, One, three.
- Look all we want to
know is if she's okay.
Oh God.
- Now the truth is at this point
we're not sure what happened over there.
- So she she could be.
- But we're not jumping
to any conclusions.
- Oh my God.
- Now look, we'll be in
this next room right over.
All right?
(somber music)
(phone ringing)
(Richard grunting)
- Richard, Richard, come on.
Brown, this is Harris, FBI.
Richard pick up the phone.
Come on Brown, pick up the phone.
We have to talk here.
We can work this out
but you gotta pick up
the phone and talk to me.
Come on Richard, pick up the phone.
We have to talk, come on.
Come on.
This is Harris.
Come on, Richard, pick up the phone.
- Stace, answer the damn phone.
COme on!
- [Jed] Richard, I gotta know
what's going on in there.
You gotta talk to me now.
You gotta talk to me Richard.
Come on Richard, pick up the phone.
Harris, FBI, pick it up.
- Hello?
- Hello, she's alive.
Hello, Stacy.
Stacy, my name is Jed
Harris, I'm with the FBI.
- [FBI Agent] She's alive.
- Oh God.
- Oh good.
Thank God.
Oh!
- Stacy, Stacy can I,
can I speak with Richard?
- They want to talk to you.
He says no.
Okay all right, that's all right Stacy.
I'll tell you what.
You, you sort of be our goal
between here, all right?
- I want to talk to my dad and my mom.
- [Jed] Look Stacy,
there's not really time
to do that right now.
- I'm know I'm gonna die anyway.
- No wait, wait don't
hang up the phone now.
Hold on Stacy, we'll get
your folks right now.
They're right in the next
room, just wait a second here.
Hold on stay there.
It's Stacy.
- Stacy.
- Yeah.
- [Becky] Stacy.
- We need her to cooperate, okay?
- [Stacy] Daddy?
- [Becky And John] Stacy.
(Stacy crying)
(somber music)
- I am so, so sorry.
I'm so sorry
for everything, Mom, I'm so sorry.
I love you.
- Oh honey, now you listen to me, okay?
No matter what's happened,
I want you to hear me
now, honey, we love you.
I love you honey.
- I love you too.
- I'm so scared.
- Yeah, I know you are.
- We know honey.
Listen you need to talk
to Mr. Harris, all right?
Cooperate with the FBI.
- It's not gonna do any good.
- Please Stacy.
- NO, no Stacy,
Stacy look, honey, do
you do it for me, okay?
Will you do it for your dad?
- All right.
- Okay Stace, look I
need a favor from you,
I want you to ask Richard
if he'll hold his fire
until I can get my men
out of the parking lot.
Will you do that for me now?
- They want to know if they can
pull out of the parking lot?
- What will they give us?
- How do I know?
- You hungry?
So am I, tell 'em.
- He said he'll let you do it
if you bring him some food.
- All right, you tell him he's got a deal.
- They said it's a deal.
- One more thing, tell 'em, they screw up
I'm gonna have to kill you.
(somber music)
- He said, if you screw up
he's gonna have to kill me.
(engines revving)
(suspenseful music)
- DO you have a shot?
- [Don] Maybe.
- Damn.
- Send in the food.
- Go on, open it.
Eat, go on eat.
Eat!
Give some to the cat, too.
- Aren't you hungry?
- Just keep eating.
You have to eat to keep your strength up.
- How much energy you think dying takes?
Go on.
(somber music)
- Well they've sent in the food
and they've established contact.
- So they can negotiate?
Right?
- [John] That's right son.
- I want to pray.
(peaceful music)
Um.
I know we're not a very religious family
and I hope that you didn't
think we're hypocrites
or anything but Lord please,
please hear our prayer
and let our Stacy be safe.
- Amen.
- [Johnny] Amen.
(crickets chirping)
(suspenseful music)
(phone ringing)
- Did you really think I'd fall for that?
(gun clicks)
(gentle music)
(people chattering)
- Details are still sketchy
about the hostage drama
that has been unfolding the past 12 hours
at this downtown motel.
Neither police nor FBI will comment
but KCRP has learned that the gunman
is believed to be a criminal
with a history of mental disturbance
and that he has allegedly
kidnapped an Illinois girl
and is holding her for.
(Television thudding)
- No, no Richard, the power just went out.
(Richard grunts)
Ow!
- Get up, get up!
(Stacy whimpering)
Stace, Stacy, I'm sorry.
Honey, I'm sorry.
- Please no, please let's surrender.
- Surrender?
- [Stacy] Please, before
someone gets hurt.
- That's what happens in war, come on.
- I'm not in a war.
Please, not if you let me.
(Stacy crying)
- Look honey, look at me.
I told you, didn't I?
Forever, didn't I?
Come on, take your gun.
Come on.
Take it.
- No!
- Stace, it's an order, take it.
- No, no.
Kill me.
Come on.
We're gonna die together anyway.
I don't want them to do it.
I want you.
Come on, please.
Please I can't take it anymore.
Please.
(Stacy crying)
(gentle music)
- No, I'm crazy.
I've been crazy for years.
Died, I died long before
I before I met you,
and dying here, don't mean nothing to me.
Oh but you, no woman's ever been willing
to lay down their life, not for me,
not for the likes of me.
And if you die, then their
won't be nobody to remember,
will there?
I really do love you, remember me, okay?
Forever.
- Forever.
(gentle music)
(Stacy crying)
- You there?
- [Jed] We're right here Richard,
what can we do for ya?
- She's coming out.
(Stacy crying)
- He's agreed to let her go.
- Oh God, let's go.
- Oh my god.
- Stay here Johnny.
- [Officer] Just right as we are.
Come on let's go.
- [Officer] Line it up.
Let's move, let's go.
(phone ringing)
- Hello Richard, may I
speak with Stacy, please?
Hello Stacy?
I need you to walk over to the door
and come out the door with
your hands up over your head.
Do you understand me?
- What about my kitten?
- Stacy you'll just have to
leave the kitten for now.
- No, no, no, no, no, he'll die.
- All right Stacy, do this
for me will you please?
When you come out the door
hold the kitten in both hands
but hold it out away from your body, okay?
(Becky and John sigh)
(gentle music)
- What do you want me to tell them?
- Tell 'em the truth,
tell 'em I loved you.
- Remember, what you told me?
Never let the bastards grind you down.
Oh God, I wish I could
take all your pain away.
Please, please don't die.
(gentle music)
(cat meowing)
- Here she comes.
Get her downstairs,
everybody else hold your positions.
If that man makes a move you take him out.
- [Don] My pleasure.
(gentle music)
- Let's go.
- Go, go, go.
Come on, go, go.
- Walk fast.
- Come on, come on, your free.
(somber rock music)
(gun clicks)
- I am telling you he will surrender.
- Just take him out.
- Stacy, what makes you
so sure he'll surrender?
- Because he's not evil.
- He fooled me.
- He's been hurt all his life.
- Stacy!
(gentle music)
Thank god.
- Oh God.
Honey, it's good to see you.
Oh Lord.
(suspenseful music)
- Oh yeah.
Bye-bye.
- Nobody fires till I give the word.
- I wouldn't do this.
I realize that.
- [Reporter] The gunman is
still holding his weapon
as the FBI continues to go negotiate.
- Shoot him, shoot him.
- No!
(suspenseful music)
- Richard, Richard this is Harris.
All right Richard, don't
move, don't do anything,
you just hear me now.
I know you're hurting up there,
there's no reason you got to die.
Come on, Stacy's safe.
Hold your fire, hold your fire.
Richard put down that weapon.
Just come to the door with your
hands over your head Richard.
Now you let Stacy go so
I know you're a good man.
You got a lot of years left,
do something with it Richard.
Come on.
- Richard, please.
Oh Richard, please don't die.
- Come on now.
(suspenseful music)
(peaceful music)
Come on, that's right.
That's right.
- [Officer] Stay right there, okay.
(handcuffs clinking)
- He's not all bad.
- None of us are honey.
(people shouting)
- [Reporter] Oh Richard.
- [Reporter] Richard.
(people shouting)
- Remember, forever.
- Oh.
- [Johnny] What'd he do to you?
- Nothing.
He just loved me.
- Come on, honey, let's, let's go home.
(gentle music)
(people shouting)
- [John] Please.
- Step aside, step aside.
Back, back.
Move along.
I'm not gonna tell you
guys, get back, get back.
- [Reporter] What happened?
What did he do to you?
- Please, everyone get back, please.
Everyone get back.
- No please, just,
all she wants to do is go home
and forget about this.
Please.
- All I want to do is go home.
- [Officer] Move back, let's go.
(solemn music)
(gentle music)
(melodic chiming)
(Multicom Jingle)