(wind howling)
(calm music)
(loudspeaker feedback)
Testing; One, two, three.
I, Patrick Lee, here and
now announce my candidacy
for the president of the United States.
I will be running a totally new campaign.
(indistinct)
(calm music)
In solving problems facing us today.
And I challenge all others
running for this high office
to join me in solving those
problems facing us today,
and may the individual who
solves the most problems
be elected as president of
the United States of America.
(Celeste applauds)
(calm music)
Whoa!
(Lee thuds)
Are you okay?
Huh?
Oh yeah, yeah.
I'm okay, whoa.
Oh gosh.
I'm a little shook up.
Are you sure?
You know, you're bleeding from the head.
What?
Really?
Where are my glasses?
These things?
They're broken.
Damn!
Those are my eyes!
You know, I'm Celeste.
Here, let me help you up.
No, it's okay.
I can take care of myself.
You probably have better things to do.
I can't just leave you here like this.
Yeah, it's okay.
I can take care of myself.
You know, I was on my way to breakfast.
The restaurant's just
a few blocks from here,
have you had breakfast yet?
Wait, you were the one who clapped.
Yeah, your presentation was inspired.
You didn't think it was
boring or a pile of platitudes?
No, you could tell
it was from the heart.
Do you like poached eggs?
So have you held any office,
and I mean any political office at all?
President.
Oh, president of what?
Oberoende, it's a micro nation.
A nation within a
nation, right here in LA.
Well like the Cherokee Nation?
That's my nation, you know?
We have 380,000 tribal citizens.
How about your nation?
Well, we had a few now and
then, and over the years,
but now you're looking
at its sole inhabitant.
Oh, we gotta start somewhere.
We still have time to
get everything together.
So you're with me?
Yeah, I like what you have to say.
But you have to stop
preaching on street corners.
So you've heard of me before.
You could say that.
So how is the campaign gonna be funded?
No problem.
Oh.
I'm so sorry.
So you were saying, that
financing the campaign
is not a problem?
Are you a multimillionaire?
Do I look like one?
No, but I just figured, it might help.
Well, I have enough to
get by, but I'm no Trump.
Actually, those would
donate to the campaign
will fund the solutions to the problems
close to their hearts.
And when we have enough money
to solve a particular problem,
its solution will be implemented.
That's a good idea.
Thanks.
Here.
So how are you gonna get
people to believe in you enough
to part with their hard-earned cash?
Oh well, if I just had
enough charisma I could do it.
I think I may be of service.
So my lack of sight isn't a negative?
Well actually FDR was elected four times
and he was in a wheelchair.
I think your Asperger's
might be more of a problem.
Are your doctor?
No. No, I'm just observant.
Huh.
Well, would you like to visit Oberoende?
Sure, let's go.
My car's just on the corner,
but without my goggles I'm legally blind.
So you need to chauffeur.
(calm music)
I think we're here.
Okay, gimme a second.
All right, you're all set.
I know how this works.
Mind your head.
Ah, okay.
Okay, approaching the stairs.
This is Oberoende.
Nice touch.
What?
The doormat.
Oh, thanks.
And I see you're a CPA.
I am.
Ring the doorbell.
Don't you have a key?
Sure, but just do it.
Okay.
("Oberoende Anthem")
What is that?
Oberoende national anthem.
Shall we?
Okay.
(door beeps)
In we go.
This is my office.
Those are my certificates,
and those are my collection of telephones.
(upbeat music)
Huh?
You can't wear those in public.
Why not?
Definitely a stereotype.
Oh.
If I'm blind, I'm blind.
Maybe an operation could help.
That'll be expensive.
If you plan on being
president, we can find the money.
Oh cool.
So what do you think?
Oh, definitely not another country,
but then again, in your mind it could be.
This is my office,
base of my operations.
And where do you live?
(calm music)
Welcome Oberoende.
(enchanting music)
What do you think?
Yeah, this is more like it.
Beautiful.
We can have a feast in here
and this could double
as a campaign office.
I agree.
Bedrooms are on the third floor.
More stairs.
(calm music)
Is this where you sleep?
Usually.
Looks comfortable.
Oh, it's very comfortable.
Would you like to check it out?
Not now.
(calm music)
Where do you keep your clothes?
Oh, in the closet.
Okay.
Mm-mm.
Nope.
Okay, we need to get you a new wardrobe.
Um, is there something
wrong with my clothes?
One would only have to
look in a mirror to know.
Hmm.
Does this mean you're dressing me up?
Yeah, dressed up you won't look bad.
Yup, we can definitely
make use of this space,
plan a grassroots campaign
starting with your friends.
I don't have any friends.
Don't worry, I have a few.
(men chanting)
(people chattering)
Hi, I'm Patrick Lee.
Thank you for coming here.
Thank you for filling out the cards.
And uh...
Thank you for your donations.
We want you to know
that the money you
contribute to this campaign
will go towards solving the
problems you have identified.
So make sure to write down
the problems you want solved
on the cards you've received.
(audience applauds)
Thank you.
(men chanting)
Do you like the fried bread?
Yes, it's very delicious.
But it's not very healthy.
It's a staple of the
(indistinct) circuit.
It's born of a time
when that's all we had.
Yes, I know that.
I wanna thank you for
putting all this together.
It's very impressive what you did, it's...
Excuse me for a moment.
A good friend of mine is here.
(calm music)
I am Patrick Lee, nice to meet you.
We met.
Have you forgotten my name already?
Samuel Brightcloud.
Oh right, Sam.
Celeste is really something.
Do you know how she got
so many people to show up?
Don't you know who she is?
No.
She could have been the
chief of the Cherokee nation,
she had it in her grasp.
She chose to leave Oklahoma
and come here to California
and many of her followers came with her.
Is she a politician?
No, a born leader, like
Mankiller before her.
Mankiller?
Wilma Mankiller, the first woman Chief
of the Cherokee nation.
(calm music)
("Oberoende Anthem")
I'm coming!
I'm almost there.
Patrick Lee?
Yes.
Oh, I have a package for you.
Is it my new eyes?
That's right.
Oh, thank God for insurance.
(speaking in foreign language)
Hello, this is Catalina
Vargas reporting for KSMX News.
Now while most of you know,
presidential candidates,
there are some that are not
as popular or as famous,
but still have that intent
to win the big prize
come this November.
So today we are gonna introduce you
to a hopeful local candidate
by the name of Patrick Lee.
As we interview him here,
inside his national campaign headquarters
located in Los Angeles.
Good afternoon.
Mr. Lee, I hear you're
running for president
of the United States?
Yes, what do you want?
The Spanish language station?
We talked about it, for Hispanic voters.
I'm Celeste Seedlingsun, I'm
Patrick's campaign manager.
[Patrick] But I don't speak Spanish.
English is fine.
First of all, what is
it that you're wearing?
And also are you playing some
type of virtual reality game?
Oh these?
These are my new eyes.
I can't see you without them.
Oh.
Excuse me, Patrick is legally blind.
You don't need to wear
these for this interview.
Ah, of course.
Mr. Lee, we're actually
wanting to feature you
and do this interview to
put it in our segment,
it's called "Daylight."
It actually airs at the
end of our broadcast,
and it's usually pieces that
are both humorous and unusual.
Do you think I'm funny or strange?
Not necessarily, but besides
the fact that you're blind,
I also understand that you're autistic?
Yes, I have Asperger's syndrome.
And yet you're running for
president of the United States?
Well, I don't think
any of those conditions are a disability.
Actually it helps me to concentrate
on focusing to solve the problems.
Interesting, and how is it
that you intend on winning?
Well, my campaign will
be completely different
from the history of all politics.
I'll be running a totally
positive campaign.
There'll be no money
allocated to media time.
Are we paying for this?
No, no.
This is what we call a
public service announcement.
Oh great, I'll log it in as such.
You know, let's conduct the interview
in front of the desk.
Okay, yeah. Good idea.
- Come on.
- Slowly, Mr. Patrick.
Yes, right you front of the desk.
I'm right behind you.
Gimme a second right here.
Yeah.
I'm just gonna move the monitor.
I got him, perfect.
Oh it's just me, Catalina Vargas.
Okay, we're just gonna
continue our interview.
If you could look straight,
the camera's pointing at us.
Perfect.
Yeah. No, this way.
Great.
So you were saying you aren't interested
in spending any money on media ads.
Oh right, there will be no
money allocated to media ads,
including promoting for myself
or talking bad stuff
about other candidates
running for the high office.
In fact, all the money will go
towards solving the problems
facing us today in America
and around the world.
Wow, that seems like
a really lofty goal.
How do you intend on
carrying out this campaign?
Well, it's simple;
It starts right here, Oberoende.
See, it's a micro nation,
a nation within a nation.
And I'm the president of it, well now,
but I'm also gonna be the president
of the United States later.
We're gonna change everything from within.
Okay, one second.
Excuse me, could you be so kind?
Stay right there.
(speaking in foreign language)
Keep rolling, Jorge.
Keep rolling.
Right here, Mr. Patrick Lee, Yes.
We're gonna continue our interview.
Please tell us more.
Tell us more about what?
About how you were talking
about the different lofty
goals that you have.
Oh, well one of the things
is we're not gonna
waste tax payers dollars
on traveling around the
country all the time-
(phone ringing)
Hello?
[Julia] Patrick, this is Julia.
Julia?
[Julia] Julia Vanderbilt,
the third, your client.
Oh, hi Julia.
[Julia] Look, I really must insist
you continue to do my taxes.
I told you I can't do it.
[Julia] Absolutely unacceptable.
I can't find anyone else of your caliber.
Well, it's not that,
I just don't have any time.
The campaign's taking up all my time.
I've dropped all my clients, not just you.
[Julia] Patrick, Patrick,
we've been together for so many years
and you understand my portfolio.
Plus no one can find
that special loophole,
I could pay you more.
Well, it's not that.
I'm going to be president.
[Julia] Don't be silly.
You don't have a chance in politics,
you're just wasting your time.
Cut, cut, you're not taping this, right?
Sorry Celeste, we
can't have you do that.
Keep rolling, Jorge.
[Julia] What's going on there?
Oh, I think I'm being
interviewed by a TV station.
[Julia] What?
Is this call being recorded?
I think so.
(phone beeping)
That's okay, Celeste
just removed the phone.
Oh, well I have many loyal supporters.
Oh, well talking about loyal supporters,
how are the American people
going to vote for you?
How are they gonna know
about your policies
and your procedures?
Well, the internet will be my vehicle
and my solutions will be
spreading like a provise
on the inter...
(object clatters)
Oh gosh.
I don't like that, what is that?
Oh no, your monitor broke.
Here, let me help you.
What, my monitor?
Yeah, you stepped on it.
It's okay, here.
That's not good for
television, and be careful.
Here, I'm just gonna put it on your chair,
you can deal with that later with Celeste.
Are you okay?
Uh-huh.
Any cuts or anything?
Okay, let me reframe you.
Let's get back to the interview.
Okay, uh-huh.
You were talking to me about solutions
and how they were gonna spread.
It sounded like a virus.
Oh, provise.
It was a word that I coined.
So see, like a virus it
endangers, it spreads,
and it hurts the host from within.
But a provise, it empowers
and it enlightens from within, provise.
So see, our solutions will
go provo on social media.
(phone ringing)
Oh God, another call.
Hello?
I told you I don't have time for this.
I'm bu...
Barb!
No, no, listen.
(Patrick sighs)
Barb.
I can't...
Barb, no I'm here.
Yes.
No, no, no.
I'm running for president.
Yes, of the United States of America.
Yes.
Cut, cut, we didn't agree to this.
(speaking in foreign language)
Sorry, there won't be
any more interruptions.
Okay, thank you.
Mr. Lee, we can actually
finish our interview
right over here.
Do you need assistance?
Yes please.
- Here's my arm.
- Okay.
And we'll just walk over here.
Okay.
All right.
And then if you could just
slightly turn around, perfect.
Turn around?
Yeah, there you go.
- Okay.
- All right.
Let me make sure.
Jorge, you got the angle?
Great, all right.
Now, we were talking about solutions.
What solutions are those?
Oh right, so the
solutions to the problems
that my campaign contributors
specify in their donations.
So people can send you money
and ask for example, to end homelessness?
Yes, and I come up with
a plan to achieve it.
("Oberoende Anthem")
What's that noise?
What's that music?
Oberoende national anthem.
(banging on door)
I'll get rid of him.
(Patrick sighs)
I guess he gave up.
Jorge, let's get back to the interview.
Now, Mr. Lee, why don't you talk to us
about what your current solutions
that you're working on are?
Well, first of all,
we have to compare the
amount of money contributed
to solving a specific problem
and then see how much money-
(car honking)
Patrick, I need to talk to you.
No, no, he's busy right now.
Sorry, this can wait.
You're gonna have to come back later.
Stick with me, man. I need you.
I need you like the
windmill needs the breeze,
like the crop needs to rain,
like the stool needs the pigeon man.
We're inseparable.
Sir, I'm in the middle of an interview.
Chris, is that you?
I need you, man.
The answer is no!
I'm no longer in the tax business.
I'm running for president.
More like falling on your face.
No negativity please.
Well, in a month or two,
you'll be asking me to pick
you up off the streets.
And don't ask you to fund
your little stupid campaign either.
Where's the camera?
[Jorge] Over here.
Really, I have many loyal supporters.
Wait, is this a live feed?
Yes.
How my outfit look?
Sorry, I forgot you blind.
You know this guy's brilliant.
If anybody should be president,
it's my main man right here, Patrick Lee.
I mean, he's a legend
in the field of taxes,
he be doing mine the last few years.
But enough about him.
Check out my late night show,
seven days a week, "Chris' Show."
We got porn stars, guest stars-
("Oberoende Anthem")
(knocking on door)
(speaking in foreign language)
(phone ringing)
Cut!
(calm music)
(birds chirping)
(water sprinkling)
Thank you so much, enjoy.
(speaking in foreign language)
Auntie Lilly, what will you have?
I think I'll try a Jonathan
in memory of Johnny Appleseed.
Hmm, he certainly was a respected man.
Thank you very much.
May these seeds grow into trees
that bear much fruit, Auntie Lilly.
Wado, Celeste.
I hope your campaign blossoms.
May we solve the
problems you've submitted.
Thank you.
I'd like to talk to you.
Sure.
Can you take over for me please?
Hi, welcome to Patrick
Lee's seed for change.
What are we doing here?
Do you really believe this
man can become president?
I know what I know, and I
must do what I believe is right.
I believe we're wasting our time
on this stupid little campaign.
I respect your opinion,
but I know what I'm doing.
Everyone can make a mistake and recover,
but only if you don't go too
far in the wrong direction.
(calm music)
Samuel, what do you think?
Why do you wanna become president?
To solve problems.
You seem to have enough
problems of your own.
It doesn't seem to bother Celeste.
You are just an
accountant, not a politician.
Celeste is a charismatic leader
and a great community organizer.
But things are not always
what they seem with her.
I'm not completely sure
what her motives are,
but the sooner you dissolve your campaign,
the better for her and you.
You don't think I should be running?
I think I've made it very clear.
Probably a lot of
people may feel this way,
but I have a mission.
A mission you will never accomplish.
A mission that I must accomplish!
As president of the United States?
No, as the president of Oberoende.
What is this Oberoende, a
figment of your imagination?
Let me show you.
It's a nation within a nation.
It's a micro nation.
A what?
It's Oberoende.
(enchanting music)
What do you think?
Are you okay?
Celeste designed this for you.
What?
Admit it, this was Celeste's idea.
No.
She at least helped put this together.
This is the seal of Oberoende.
I designed this way before
even meeting Celeste.
Don't lie to me!
(dramatic music)
(Patrick groans)
Please forgive me, I
didn't want to believe you.
But now I know the truth.
What's going on?
I opposed your campaign.
Now I know that we're brothers.
(calm music)
I'm sorry if I frightened you,
but these are sacred Cherokee
symbols that you've assembled.
This must be a sign, a sign
that this was meant to be.
So does that mean you
have changed your mind
about my campaign?
Oh, from now on you are
Patrick Dark Horse Lee.
(knocking on door)
I want to apologize for not believing you.
You know, I came here to
California reluctantly.
I've known you since you were a child,
and I have never really
believed in your visions.
I thought there were just a way for you
to manipulate others.
And what's changed your mind?
(Samuel sighs)
I saw the seal of Oberoende,
exactly as you described
it in your visions.
So now you understand my mission.
If you feel that he will
make a great president,
I believe you must be right.
But to tell you the truth,
rather than him, I believe
you should be president.
I will be.
What?
It was in my vision.
(calm music)
(birds chirping)
(dramatic music)
(siren wailing)
(Patrick groans)
Is something wrong, officer?
I wanna talk to you.
This is not what it looks like,
these are my new eyes.
I'm not an officer, I'm the son of Sam.
(dramatic music)
What?
No, don't kill me!
I can't see you.
The son of Samuel Brightcloud.
He carries, but not as boldly as I do.
(Patrick sighs)
What about the badge?
It's a Cherokee star.
I'm Seco, with NARM,
the Native American
Revolutionary Movement.
Okay.
I believe my father's
welcomed you to the tribe.
They call you brother Dark Horse.
Yes.
It seems like Dark
Horse has a broken leg.
I don't understand.
Don't you usually put a horse
with a broken leg to sleep?
Not necessarily.
I mean, that's assuming he has no value.
But a champion horse
has a career as a stud.
Okay, stud.
Somehow you convinced
Celeste and my father
that your campaign has a chance,
but I don't believe that.
Why not?
Because your philosophies on life
are against human nature.
Because I'm a pacifist?
Are you saying violence
isn't the answer.
It's an answer, it's not a solution.
You're just playing with words.
You can't change someone
by just knocking them,
striking them down.
You must reason with them
and treat them as an equal.
Change 'em from within,
that's the only way you
can really change someone.
Not in the real world.
Power is all people look at.
You're weak, so you're looking
for another alternative.
But the powerful have always ruled,
and the weak have always been rolled over.
It's just the way things are.
I know the way things are,
I'm talking about the
way things should be.
It just seems I'm wasting my time.
I hope you see the light
because my tribe seems
to think you're somebody,
but I don't see anything at all.
Don't worry about it.
One day, the blind will be able to see,
perhaps that day is today.
We'll see about that, stud.
(pensive music)
(Seco scoffs)
In your first line,
you present yourself,
your name and the office
you're running for.
And then, why you're in the race.
A little of your background and
what you hope to accomplish.
Then and only then do
you go into the specifics
of your campaign and why
people should vote for you
rather than anyone else.
Do you think you have all of that down?
I guess.
Pretty much.
Oh, okay.
You're gonna be on a stage next week.
You have to be ready.
Please have the lines and
the speech patterns down.
Do you really think
I should be talking to a crowd of people?
You're running for president.
You can't do everything
from your computer.
Oh, I don't think I'm ready.
Okay.
You know, you have to get
out and meet more people.
Expand your horizons.
I just wanna solve problems.
Shouldn't that be enough?
Okay, we're putting in
some pretty heavy hours,
maybe I should move in.
It could really cut the
travel time back and forth
and I could save the money on rent.
Sure, we should work
more closely together.
I agree.
You do have the extra bedroom.
Oh, right.
I guess that'll be okay.
Then it's settled.
I'll start moving my stuff in tomorrow.
Yes.
I think that'll work.
Okay, let's practice your presentation.
Who am I talking to?
Just pretend there's an audience.
Okay.
It just doesn't feel right.
I'm nervous.
Do you think you'll be less nervous
when there's people actually there?
(Patrick exhales)
Okay, okay, wait.
Don't breathe into the mic.
Let me show you.
I am Patrick Lee and I'm
running for president
of the United States.
I can do that.
Okay.
I'm Patrick Lee,
and I'm running for the
president of the United States.
(Celeste groans)
Do you know what was wrong with that?
No.
Oh, it sounded like you were reading.
There's no emotion at all.
I have to be more excited?
Do you remember the
part about the eagle?
Yes.
Try that.
The Eagle is the symbol of our country.
It represents strength and freedom.
What happened?
What did we talk about?
There's no emotion at all.
Here, I'll show you.
Just watch me.
(Patrick groans)
The eagle is the symbol of this nation.
It represents strength and freedom.
The eagle has a right
wing and a left wing.
Both wings must work in unison
or this great bird cannot fly,
cannot soar majestically through the sky.
Without both wings, both
sides working as one,
this country will not survive.
I want this country to fly, to soar.
And you, you are the
feathers in these wings
that will carry this
campaign to Washington
and the White House.
(Patrick applauds)
Oh man, I mean...
I know the words, but I
can't speak like that.
No.
But when I'm finished with
you, you'll be able to do it.
(enchanting music)
Every person has a voice and
every voice is different.
You just haven't found yours yet.
But when you do, you will be able to soar.
All right, these go in the meeting room.
Okay.
Just a few more boxes
then we're back to rehearsing your speech
for the high school.
Oh, not the speech again.
Yeah.
(phone ringing)
Oh, I'll get it.
Patrick Lee's campaign
offices, how can I help you?
Barb who?
Who?
Hello?
Strange call.
[Patrick] Oh no!
(glass breaking)
Are you okay?
[Patrick] I'm okay.
(glass breaking)
I'm coming up.
(calm music)
(ship honking)
It's beautiful up here, up on the deck.
This ocean air is so refreshing.
I love this breeze on my face.
(waves crashing)
This is a fantastic place to dream.
It's my favorite place in Oberoende.
Sometimes I'll come up here
and imagine I'm on a voyage
to some exotic destinations.
Like the pictures on the walls?
I've never really been to those places.
Even in my mind, I've always been alone.
I don't even know what
happened to my parents.
I guess they couldn't deal
with my peculiarities.
Mine were very intense.
They instilled their goals
and their dreams in me.
They both died young, in a plane crash.
Who raised you then?
The whole community.
I was a child of the tribe
and Sam Brightcloud became my mentor,
though being headstrong
I seldom listened to him.
I barely remember my parents.
I mean, they seemed to
be on the edge of my life
and just disappeared
when I was very young.
You didn't get to know them?
They went their own way.
I was raised first at a foster home,
and then at an institution.
I kept their books since the age of 10,
and they said if it wasn't for me,
they might never have stayed afloat.
(calm music)
Like this boat?
Yeah, like this boat.
(keyboard clacking)
What are you still doing up?
Is that a game you're playing?
I thought you took this
campaign seriously.
You need to get your sleep.
Well, it's a game all right,
but it's a game to save lives.
Another one of your inventions?
Everything, even the game
can have more than one purpose.
Sure, to hook you, to entertain,
to keep you up all night, right?
No.
For instance, this card that I clicked on.
It reads, "The people who are crazy enough
to think they can change the
world are the ones who do."
Great quote.
Do you know who said it?
No.
Sorry, you just lost three points
and have to move back three spaces.
And you're that much
further from your goal.
(Celeste sighs)
I'm not interested in playing any games.
We both need to get more sleep.
You're not even gonna guess who said it?
I guess, you know the answer.
Of course I do.
I'm the one who invented this game.
It's a quote from Steve jobs.
[Celeste] A genius who
is no longer with us.
[Patrick] Do you know why?
He died?
Of what?
I don't know.
Pancreatic cancer, duh?
See this game educates the players,
plus the money that's paid to play
will go towards research
developing new treatments
and eventually a cure.
You know, the person I
respected the most in the world
died of pancreatic
cancer, Wilma Mankiller.
She was the first woman
chief of the Cherokee Nation.
I know.
And she said, "We must
trust our own thinking,
trust where we're going
and get the job done."
(automated cheers)
Yes.
But you're not gonna cure cancer
at three o'clock in the morning.
No.
(Patrick yawns)
One step at a time.
You need to get your
sleep or you won't function.
You know, you're lucky I'm
here to take care of you.
Yes.
(enchanting music)
I'm lucky you're here.
I agree.
(enchanting music)
(Seco grunting)
There you go.
We have to be ready
and in place, Grey Horse.
I need you to flank me
at the 50 yard line.
Yes sir.
(Secco grunting)
One more.
All right, take it.
Good work.
Thanks man.
Be ready to converge on my signal.
If anything looks
suspicious, we take action.
Seco, why are we protecting this guy?
Celeste's orders.
Besides, her and my father
will be on that stage.
Ladies and gentlemen,
the next president of the
United States, Patrick Lee!
(audience applauds)
Hi, I'm Patrick Lee.
And I'm the first solution candidate
running for the president
of the United States.
I want more than just your
votes, because this campaign
is not just a campaign for the presidency.
It is a campaign that will change
the whole political system.
(audience applauds)
Our objective is to find solutions
to the problems facing our
nation and the world around us.
And I'm not going to wait
until I hold the highest
office in this nation.
The process starts right here right now,
because we represent the solution we seek.
Blind leading the blind!
Yes, I am legally blind,
but you don't have to have 2020 vision
to be able to find the solutions
to the problems facing us today.
(audience applauds)
I will not make any
promises that I cannot keep.
The only promise I will make
is that I won't make any promises.
(audience laughing)
(audience applauds)
If other candidates are running a sprint,
I will be running a marathon.
If they are playing checkers,
I will be playing chess.
This is much more than just
a race and just a game.
I challenge any candidate
seeking this high office
to join me in solving the
problems facing us today
in the United States and around the world.
(audience applauds)
The symbol of our nation
is the majestic eagle.
It represents strength and freedom.
The eagle has two wings, the
right wing and the left wing.
We don't need Cheeks and
savages telling us what to.
(gun fires)
(audience gasps)
(people screaming)
Both wings must work in unison,
or the great bird cannot fly.
And these wings will carry this campaign
to Washington and the White House.
[Celeste] Help, call 911!
Patrick, stay with us.
Patrick?
Help!
(speaking in foreign language)
In breaking news;
Independent presidential
candidate, Patrick Lee,
who's branded himself as the
problem solving candidate
has a few problems of his own,
after an unidentified gunman
now in police custody,
fired upon him when he was giving a speech
on a high school football field.
On the international scene,
the tensions between India and Pakistan
over the disputed territory of Kashmir
are continuing to intensify.
(siren wailing)
[Sam] Doctor?
[Doctor] Yes.
Doctor, is he gonna be all right?
Yes, fortunately the bullet
missed his vital organ.
We have stopped the bleeding
and closed the wound.
He is out of surgery and
is now in stable condition.
But is he awake?
Can we see him?
What is it?
It's a skin gun,
it's used during surgery
to replace damaged tissue.
Oh.
Did you use it on me?
It's mainly used for burn
victims and large wounds.
It sprays a small amount
of stem cells on the wound
and it grows into skin,
often hardly leaving a scar.
This is just gonna be a small scar.
(calm music)
(Patrick chuckles)
Cool.
A small scar.
(calm music)
Room 437, this is it.
I hope he's okay.
[Sam] Go ahead.
I didn't know something
like this was gonna happen.
I feel terrible.
What did I do to anger someone so much?
Do you know who did it?
You know, they haven't released a name.
We don't know anything yet.
I'm sorry to disturb you, sir.
But there's a reporter
outside, named Catalina Vargas?
She says she knows you?
Do you think you'd be
up to talking to her?
Sure, yeah.
I think she might be able to
answer some of my questions.
Thanks.
Hi Patrick, remember me?
I was the first reporter
that covered your campaign.
Yeah, right.
Hi. Welcome Ms. Vargas.
You can call me Cat,
and honestly you look really good
considering you're recovering
from an assassination attempt.
Did you know that Theodore Roosevelt
was shot in the chest during
his campaign for president,
and he still finished his speech?
Do you want to see my wound?
Oh.
What can you tell us about
the man that shot him?
We don't have much
information at this time.
How's he doing?
Well from what I know,
physically he's doing well.
But you're concerned for his wellbeing?
Well, I wanna know why,
why would he shoot me?
Well, what I can tell you
is that he has a history of mental illness
and he was also under
the influence of alcohol.
[Reporters] Mr. President!
Mr President!
[Reporter 1] Mr. President,
what's your response
to the recent assassination attempt
on a presidential candidate?
Well, it's terrible.
Now I'm not familiar with this individual
or even that he was a candidate,
but it's an example of just
how dangerous it's becoming
for somebody who wants to
run for an elected office.
Next.
[Reporters] Mr. President!
Mr. President!
[Reporter 2] Are you going
to assign secret service
to Patrick Lee's campaign?
Well, it's really not
my decision to make,
that's for secret service to decide.
Now this candidate doesn't
belong to either political party.
As far as I understand he's
got a very small following,
so it's not likely,
but that's really secret
service's decision.
How's he looking Dr. Zen?
Healing very well Miss Seedlingsun.
Mr. Lee, you are making
excellent progress,
but you will need be to in
a wheelchair for a while
until the swelling around
your spine goes down.
A wheelchair, huh?
Something to look forward to.
Well, we'll see.
A lot of people are rooting
for you, myself included.
A lot of mail is coming
to the hospital for you.
Best of luck for your campaign.
Thank you, doctor.
Okay. I gotta go.
[Patrick] Bring that mail.
All right, see you.
Wow, do you think that's true?
(Celeste chuckles)
You are rising in the polls.
There's nothing like a good tragedy
for people to rally behind the underdog.
I hope I can get out of here soon.
I feel useless.
What can I do now?
Win, you can win.
I'm blind, and autistic.
And the doctor just told me
that I have to be in a wheelchair for...
Ugh, who knows how long.
But your numbers are rising every day,
you're at 1% in the polls.
You must forge ahead.
As an accountant,
I can tell you that 1% isn't
statistically significant.
Of course it's significant,
people are asking for solutions.
They're listening to your philosophies.
Now is the time to run with it.
If only I could.
Look, you can lay here
and feel sorry for yourself,
or you can get back to work.
Well what kind of solutions
are they asking for?
Because of your situation,
they're asking for a solution
to the gun controversy.
Okay then, that's what we'll give them.
Okay.
You have to be in the oval
office to do anything about that.
You don't have the power to do
anything about it right now.
Well, we don't know that until we try.
If we can prevent what happened
to me from happening again,
we can save countless lives.
How many camping offices have opened
while I've been laid up here?
[Celeste] Oberoende is
in 10 cities nationwide
and five countries around
the world have requested it.
Hmm, let's see how much
money has been donated
to solve this particular problem,
and then we'll decide
what direction to take.
(bright upbeat music)
We are gonna miss you, Mr. Lee.
Now don't work too hard, okay?
And be careful,
there looks like there's a
pretty large crowd out there.
Look, Patrick, there's 100 people
waiting out there for you.
Come on, let's go greet your public.
Lose the goggles.
(enchanting music)
Sam, Secco?
Great to see you.
Mr Lee, you forgot your bag!
OMG, is that Patrick Lee?
(girl screaming excitedly)
What's going on?
What's happening!
(gun fires)
(girl screams)
(dramatic music)
Drop the gun!
Put your hands behind your back.
You're under arrest.
Why?
Unlawful discharge of
a firearm, that's why.
But it was an accident.
Someone could have been killed!
He's the one who saved Patrick's life.
Well then you can bail him out
and tell that to the judge.
Come on, move it.
Let's go!
[Sam] Don't worry, Seco, we'll fix this.
Patrick, any comment on
what transpired here today,
as you were trying to leave the hospital?
(Patrick whimpering)
You can't bring a deadly
weapon into a situation
and call it protection.
That includes the police.
I could see solving this gun controversy
is not gonna be easy.
(bright upbeat music)
So the success of the R&D department
has made the manufacturing of the casings,
especially the small needle,
they're right to
specification and work great.
So the neuro toxins are safe, right?
So our research shows
the tests worked great
both indoors and outdoors
at various ranges.
Some people are sometimes
confused afterwards,
but it really works
fine and nobody's hurt.
That's great.
So anyway, what do you think, Patrick?
I think we have a solution.
We did that!
Wow, congratulations guys.
Wonderful.
All right, we've been trying
to solve this for a while.
Yeah.
(enchanting music)
(all applaud)
(birds chirping)
Thank you for coming
to our press conference.
Patrick Lee's campaign polling
has wavered between one
and two percentage points,
so I am aware that most of you assigned
to cover this press conference
are either fledgling reporters
or well seasoned pros
who may well be in line to be replaced
by fledgling reporters.
(all laugh)
Well, we have good news for you,
because today maybe the
turning point in your career.
Patrick Lee is the
first solution candidate
for the presidency.
Today, we will be revealing
one of those solutions,
a solution that will
hopefully save hundreds,
perhaps thousands of lives.
Here to explain it to you
is the next president of the
United States, Patrick Lee.
(all applaud)
(birds chirping)
Good afternoon.
As many of you may know,
I was recently a victim of gun violence.
And it bothered me greatly
to think that others
may have to go through
such a traumatic experience.
The second amendment of our constitution
guarantees the right of
citizens to bear arms,
both for sport and to protect
themselves and their families.
Conversely, other citizens may
feel that in the modern era,
with the protection of the
police and the military,
there's no need to have private firearms
which may lead to mayhem
in the hands of unscrupulous people.
Today, after working with
over Oberoende organizations
across the United States
and around the world,
I want to announce our
solution to the problem.
(woman gasps)
Smart Magic.
But before I answer your questions,
I would like to demonstrate Smart Magic.
And to demonstrate any type of magic,
we will need a volunteer
from the audience.
How about the woman in green?
Okay.
Excuse me, I would need
to wear these to see
because I'm legally blind.
I know politicians have
a thing about the press.
You're not gonna use me for
target practice, are you?
Oh no, no.
Don't worry, I won't shoot you.
Please, introduce yourself.
Susan Wright with Channel Three News.
Great, follow me.
(gun fires)
Wow, that was a great shot.
Thanks, your turn.
Aim at the center of the target,
and pull the trigger.
Try it again.
What's wrong?
It won't fire.
That's because it's a smart gun.
Only someone who's
programmed for it can use it.
Oh wow.
Now, try this one?
(gun fires)
Almost no kickback.
You just shot a magic
tranquilizer bullet,
virtually no recoil.
Anyone else wanna try?
Hello, Uncle Mitch?
Hi, this is Susan.
I heard you were in LA?
Look, this is no standard
press conference.
You have to get a media
van out here right away.
Oh, and if we have a firearms
expert, send them too.
(gun fires)
Wow, that's fantastic.
Thanks.
And that ladies and
gentlemen is Smart Magic.
(audience applauds)
I want you all to give this a shot,
but we also wanna answer
all of your questions.
But before we do so,
I wanna take this opportunity
to announce my running mate.
I'm sure some of you have already guessed.
Please welcome the next vice president
of the United States Celeste Seedlingsun.
(audience applauds)
Thank you.
This is more like it.
(all laugh)
[Woman] All right!
We know we have a difficult race to run,
and it doesn't take a blind man
to see that America needs
visionary leadership
to tackle the problems that
affect us all as human beings.
(all applaud)
We will now take questions.
Celeste.
(all clamor)
Is this brand new weaponry
that you guys are using and
introducing in your campaign?
Not exactly, it is all
based on existing technology.
A smart gun technology
has been around for years
and tranquilizing projectiles
have been used on animals for decades.
We've combined the two into Smart Magic,
smart guns, magic bullets.
(all clamor)
Aren't you Mitch Morgan from INN?
Yes I am, thank you for having me here.
So these bullets can stop an attacker?
Yes, and their accuracy is far superior.
How fast can this so-called
bullet take someone down?
Well, there are two chemicals involved;
The first is a mild neurotoxin
that causes immediate effect
on the nervous system.
The second is the tranquilizer
that slows down all bodily functions,
rendering the attacker unconscious.
[Reporter 3] Patrick, how did you-
(calm music)
(birds chirping)
Usually, public demonstrations
highlight or expose a problem,
but we will be demonstrating
solutions to those problems.
Our objective is to find
solutions and to promote them.
Today we pro walk for smart magic.
All right.
[Man] Yeah.
A pro walk is neither
a march nor a protest.
A march has military connotations
and a protest is against something.
A pro walk is always positive.
It's always for something
never against anything.
Here we have the Smart Magic
sweatsuits we designed for you.
As we wear our hearts on our sleeves,
so must we wear our
feelings and our beliefs.
In our pro walk, we will
wear our words and thoughts.
We don't need to carry large signs
that could be used as a weapon.
We are not going to walk in a huge crowd
that can, to some, seem threatening.
We'll walk single file, five feet apart.
When a light turns red,
please wait patiently for it
to change before continuing
so no intersections are blocked
and no one is left behind.
(calm music)
Today is our first pro
hike for Smart Magic.
If we take our time and
help each other along,
we will all reach the top together
and make a powerful
statement to the world.
(enchanting music)
Come on guys.
Yeah!
Woo!
(upbeat music)
The independent candidate for president,
Patrick Lee's solution
to the gun controversy
is using Smart Magic technology.
Now he and his group made quite a splash
in Los Angeles this weekend,
as they hosted a pro walk.
You'll also see a sign
that is bigger, brighter,
and visible only at night.
Now folks, it comes down tomorrow,
so if you wanna get a selfie,
tonight is your last chance.
Hey, Hey!
Ho, ho!
Smart Magic's got to go.
Four, three, two, one,
keep your hands off my gun!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Ho! Ho! Ho!
Smart Magic's got to go.
Scenes like this are
happening around the country.
Protests and boycotts against gun shops
that have decided to carry Smart Magic.
Some reports claim the
National Gun Association
is behind these boycotts,
but the NGA has officially denied it.
Are we ready with plan B?
Well, we have applications
for Smart Magic franchises,
for entrepreneurs across the country.
We're gonna have a few stores
up and running really soon.
We're here with Judy and Alex Robertson,
franchise owners of a
Smart Magic gun shop.
They are two survivors
of what is now being called
the Smart Magic Massacre.
What time did this take place?
It was about 2:00 AM, Judy
and I plus one of our employees
had stayed late to get everything ready
for today's grand opening.
And we had just turned the lights out
and we were about to head home.
That's when we saw like
the flickering lights
coming towards us
through the front window,
and we received several death threats.
So we were obviously already nervous.
I thought we were gonna die.
It's okay.
We're safe now, dear.
We've obtained security
camera footage of the incident.
The footage you're about
to see is pretty graphic,
so we must ask for viewer
discretion before watching.
[Alex] They approached
the front of the shop
so we grabbed some Smart
Magic firearms and ammo.
They were prepared for confrontation
and they were wearing body
armor, they were well armed.
You can see there.
We hit that man on the
leg with the magic bullet,
the guy went down in seconds.
(gunshots ringing)
(alarm bell ringing)
Our building alarm was triggered
and all three of us started firing back.
(siren wailing)
[Reporter] Alex is that
you saving that man's life?
[Alex] We could hear
the sirens approaching,
any of the attackers that were
still conscious had run off.
So I felt it was safe
that we put out the flame
before the guy was seriously burned.
(radio chatter)
But one question, your
attackers are wearing body armor,
how were you able to take them out?
We were just aiming for their arms,
their legs, their butts,
like any place that was
vulnerable to our ammo.
So none of them were
permanently injured?
No, we're told they're
conscious and under arrest.
Wow, they went down so fast.
We're just as surprised as you are.
I mean, we'd heard all about this weaponry
when we decided to open
a Smart Magic franchise,
but we never expected
it to be this effective.
And if it wasn't, we'd be dead.
Other reports from Smart Magic
locations throughout the US
show sales skyrocketing.
Several major cities across the US
have asked to test the weapons
for their city's police departments.
Even the leaders of the
National Gun Association,
who were originally skeptical,
have asked to meet with
presidential candidate, Patrick Lee.
(all applaud)
We have had a long and
fruitful discussion with Mr. Lee
and Miss Seedlingsun,
along with members of
the gun control lobby.
We have come to the conclusion
that we are in support
of this new solution
to the gun controversy.
While we originally thought Smart Magic
would give a false sense of security
to those who wanted to protect themselves
and their families,
we now accept that it has been proven
to be a viable weapon system.
So much so that the NGA is
joining the gun control lobby
to back Patrick Lee's run for president
of the United States.
Presidential Dark Horse Patrick Lee
stopped by the White House this afternoon
after having a very successful
meeting with the NGA.
Now it has been confirmed
that he is up 15%
in the national polls
and has also been invited
to join democratic
and Republican nominees for
the first presidential debate.
Now this should make
for a very interesting
and amazing opportunity
to see him in the presidential debate.
And now onto international news.
The border dispute
between India and Pakistan
continues to escalate,
which causes more
concern around the world.
(calm music)
(keyboard clatters)
What are those figures?
Have you been working
on this the entire time
instead of rehearsing for the debate?
Well, I think I just
solved another problem.
Oh, what?
I discovered how to
eliminate national debt.
Are you kidding?
You think I spent all that
time just for the fun of it?
Oh, my neck is killing me.
Well, I've actually been spending
a lot of time planning this,
but the missing part of the
solution just came to me.
Wait, so that's a formula
for eliminating the national debt?
Yeah, by cryptocurrency.
I mean, it's not like E equals
MC squared, but it'll work.
Wow, okay.
This is gonna really give
us a hand up in the debate.
Oh, I can't use this
for the debate actually.
Why not?
Well, because I have to implement it
when I'm in the White House.
So?
Did you forget?
We made a promise not
to make any promises.
Okay, but this could
really put us ahead.
No, we have to keep this under wraps.
I can't believe I
didn't see this coming.
Is there anything else
you've been keeping from me?
Well, I have a plan for
eliminating federal income tax.
Can we use that in a debate?
No.
What are we even training for
if we can't use all of your ammunition?
Well, we can use whatever
we've already accomplished.
Okay, but if we win, we can use it then?
Yeah, but we still need the
Congress to go along with it.
Okay.
(enchanting music)
I'll figure out how to say it
without making any promises.
Your hair is getting too long,
we have to cut it before the debate.
Don't wait up for me.
I've got a presentation
with some top educators
about our new way of running
the nations' schools.
Wish me luck.
Well, with your powers of persuasion,
you don't need any luck.
No more playing with numbers.
Focus on the campaign
and memorize those talking points.
(keyboard clatters)
(calm music)
(dramatic music)
("Oberoende Anthem")
Who is it?
(knocking on door)
Back already?
Did you lose your key card?
(enchanting music)
Barb, what are you doing here?
I wanna talk.
About what?
Let me in.
I don't think that's a good idea.
What would you suggest?
Why?
After all this time.
I miss you.
You really hurt me.
You still love me, don't you?
Of course I do, you're the
one who broke up with me.
I changed my mind.
I've been calling you, but
you refuse to talk to me.
I've been a little tied up.
You always used to say you loved me,
but you never had time for me.
I'm sorry, I was busy with my clients,
growing the business.
Yeah, just like you're
busy with your campaign.
We haven't seen each
other in all this time.
What changed?
I'm older now, more mature.
I think we could really make it work.
(calm music)
We had some really good times up here.
Remember that one time
where you and I were fooling around naked,
and that helicopter flew over?
You know, we could try it again.
Now that it's dark.
I really don't know.
I have a whole new life now.
I know, I miss you.
We were meant to be together.
I know that now.
If I felt that you really meant that.
I still love you, but
you broke up with me,
and when I really needed you the most.
I was losing my sight
and the belief in myself,
and you just made it worse.
I'll make it up to you.
I promise, Pat.
Please, just give me a chance.
(calm music)
Wait, you're not doing this
for your citizenship, are you?
No.
No, I've got my green card.
We could tie the knot,
we could make this official.
I have to think about this.
No, don't think.
We could make this work
with me as your wife.
I get it, you really think I can win.
Yes, with me by your side.
You don't love me,
you wanna be first lady.
Yes, but I also love you.
We make the perfect team.
Your brains, my beauty.
I may be blind, but I
can see right through you.
We've been together way
too long for me not to.
What are you saying?
I'm saying we're through,
like what you said when you broke it off.
You son of a bitch!
No cussing, please.
You think you're so powerful
now that you're gonna debate the big guys?
Well, I'm not so helpless
that I can't bring you down.
Well fine, go ahead and try.
I don't care.
You forget, I worked
with you in the office.
I know all of your secrets.
Well, you got nothing on me.
You think you have the upper hand?
Yes, I think I finally do.
We'll see about that.
You'll miss me when I'm gone.
No, I won't.
And ever since you left,
I learned how to stand on my own two feet.
(Patrick groans)
I can see that.
Goodbye, Mr. President.
He's all yours bitch!
I'm waiting.
Oh gosh.
That was Barb.
Who?
My ex-girlfriend, she
wanted to get back together.
Ow.
Well you two did a fine job.
I can't believe I didn't foresee this.
Ow, my good leg!
Barb and I are over, we're finished.
You never told me about her, why?
She's young and attractive,
I just didn't want you to be upset.
I don't wanna lose you.
But we don't have that
kind of relationship,
it's only business.
Yeah, I know.
But I just thought maybe.
When we first met...
Never mind.
I have been so dishonest.
I can't believe it.
You gave up everything for
me, you've been honest.
I don't think I can do this anymore.
Come on, don't give up, okay?
I haven't been entirely
honest with you either.
Really?
I'm a seer.
Yeah, you've been my eyes and my voice.
I can't thank you enough.
No, no, no, no, you don't understand.
I never saw or heard you
announce your candidacy
for the president.
Before the day we met, I had
a vision of it, like a dream.
I have visions, I'm a seer.
And you came all the way from Oklahoma
to help me with the
president, the presidency?
Not exactly.
My vision was that I would be president.
(elevator dings)
(upbeat music)
Ladies and gentlemen,
welcome to the first presidential debate.
I'm Roberta Ann Bartlett,
your moderator for tonight,
coming to you live from
Eastern Missouri University
in St. Louis.
At the podium to the right, we
have Senator William Dempsey.
He's the Republican nominee for president.
(audience applauds)
On your left at the podium,
we have Governor John MCC McCadden.
(audience applauds)
And he is the democratic
candidate for president.
We are getting started a few minutes late,
we've been waiting for
word from Patrick Lee.
He's the independent
candidate for president,
as to whether he is going to be able
to make the debate tonight,
so unfortunately we will
have to start the debate
without him.
I know how much he wanted to be here
since he lept to 15%
in the national polls,
so we will leave his podium on stage
in the event he arrives
to the debate late.
I was going to ask the first
question of Patrick Lee,
instead I will ask the two of you.
What is your opinion of candidate Lee?
Senator Dempsey.
Well, I don't think he's
prepared to be president.
He has no real experience
in any international or
public service position,
and he's not a member
of any political party.
For once, I pretty much agree with Bill.
Lee's lack of experience may be the reason
he is not here tonight.
The presidency is a
very demanding position.
You have to know every aspect
of running this country
and dealing with other countries.
You have to know everything,
from education and employment-
Hi Sam.
Excuse me, Mr. Brightcloud.
Do you know what happened to Patrick Lee?
Do you know why he's not
at the presidential debate?
No comment.
But-
No.
Cut.
Can you tell us where
candidate Lee is hiding?
No comment.
And Miss Seedling, sir?
Same answer.
(Davies shrieks)
I know karate.
Is this TMZ?
Mr. Davies, we met before.
You're one of Patrick Lee's CPA clients,
he did your taxes.
Yeah, he said everything
was legit, right?
Do you buy any chance
know where he is tonight?
He was supposed to be at
the presidential debate.
It's not over, is it?
Well, no.
Look, I know Patrick,
we're really close.
And if I know my man, he'll
make a dramatic entrance
at the last minute and steal the show.
Well, you heard it here first, folks.
Patrick Lee is either
going to steal the show
or be a no-show.
I'm gonna toss it back
to you in the studios.
Well, this has been
a very fruitful debate.
You did not agree on your answers
to the topics put forward,
so I think the public has a
very clear idea before them.
Something has happened
over the last few days
that has threatened this nation
and also the rest of the world.
As you know, the longstanding conflict
between India and Pakistan
has flared up again.
Thousands of individuals have died
on the border between these two countries
and now the leaders are threatening
to use nuclear weapons on each other.
If that happens, millions more will die
if this is not deescalated.
What do each of you feel should be done
to resolve the situation?
First to you, Governor McCadden.
Since we are not one
of the two adversaries
in this conflict,
I feel it is an important
task for the United Nations.
They have already gone
into emergency sessions
in this situation,
and I am hopeful that
the nations of the world
will be able to figure something
out and end this conflict.
After all, India and Pakistan
have a population of
over 2 billion people,
and combined they have
enough nuclear weapons
to not only kill their own populations,
but enough to end all of life on earth.
Senator Dempsey.
Well, I disagree with John
on this important point.
This is a conflict between
two sovereign nations.
Yes, both sides have attacked each other.
Both sides have crossed
one another's borders.
Both sides have suffered casualties.
And at this point it appears
that both leaders are hot heads.
But I believe this is a situation
where the two must come together
to bring an end to this conflict.
Thank you for your heartfelt responses.
We are now gonna go to
your closing statements.
Wait, wait, I'm getting
an important bulletin.
It seems there has been a secret meeting
between the leaders of India and Pakistan,
and they've seemingly
resolved their conflict.
As we speak, troops are moving back
across their respective borders
and all hostilities have ceased.
It seems your answer,
Senator Dempsey is actually taking place.
Thank God.
Now we can have an election after all.
What?
Can you put that on the back screen?
(audience gasps)
We're receiving the official photograph
of this groundbreaking meeting
that occurred less than an hour ago.
(audience applauds)
The Associated Press,
(speaking in foreign language)
(dramatic music)
Well, nobody could have
predicted what transpired tonight.
It looks like we have just
received a preliminary poll
of this evening's presidential debate.
Are you sure this is accurate?
Apparently the numbers
have been confirmed.
The results of our instantaneous poll
on who the American people feel
won this evening's presidential debate;
At 28% governor John McCadden.
32%, Senator William Dempsey.
And at an amazing 40%, independent
candidate, Patrick Lee.
Apparently Mr. Lee has won a debate,
he did not even attend.
We have now learned that the meeting
between the leaders of India and Pakistan
with Patrick Lee and Celeste Seedlingsun
have now been arranged
by Oberoende India and Oberoende Pakistan.
Now it is also confirmed
that in addition to Oberoende
existing in all 50 US states,
they are also in over
100 nations worldwide.
In a stunning development
early this morning,
federal agents raided
the campaign headquarters
of Patrick Lee.
Taking computers, file
cabinets, literally everything
they could get their hands on.
Acting on an anonymous tip,
they are looking for items
related to his former CPA business.
There are allegations that
his handling of client taxes
may be in question.
We have also heard there may be evidence
that the attempted assassination plot
may have been hatched and carried out
by his own campaign team.
[Reporters] Mr. President!
Mr. President!
[Reporter 4] Mr. President,
do you have any comment on the recent raid
on Patrick Lee's campaign headquarters?
There's a rumor going around
that you knew about it beforehand.
That's not true, okay?
Patently false.
We found out about it as it happened,
just the same as you did.
Next question please.
[Reporters] Mr. President!
Mr. President!
[Reporter 5] Yeah, but isn't it strange
that it happened right after
he took the lead in the polls
and right before arriving back in the US?
This is an inconsequential
candidate, okay?
He's not on a ballot in any state,
and this was a coordinated joint effort
between the IRS and the FBI.
And frankly, it should be
solved before the election
so a cloud of distrust doesn't
hang over, Mr. Lee's head.
[Reporter 5] So are you saying
that you agree with the raid?
I didn't say that.
I said, I understand
how these agencies work
and they're just doing their jobs.
No more questions until
we have more information.
[Reporters] Mr. President!
Mr. President!
(bright upbeat music)
It's wonderful to see so
many friends here tonight.
Now I wanna remind you all
that Mr. Lee is not on
the ballot of any state,
so you must write in his name
on your ballot as president
when you vote this November.
Are you nervous?
Yes.
Tell me what's bothering you?
I didn't do anything wrong,
and the whole government's
coming down at me.
Don't worry, the establishment's
just getting desperate.
This will all blow over.
You came outta nowhere
and they don't know how to deal with you.
They're grasping at straws.
They have nothing on you.
I know that,
but how do you know?
I just know, trust me.
Okay.
Can I wear my new eyes?
No, no, absolutely not,
we talked about this.
They're way too distracting.
We want the audience to see your eyes,
even if you're not making eye contact.
But remember to turn your
head from side to side
and address the entire audience.
You don't want me to see them?
No, seeing all those people
could trigger your Asperger's.
What about the sound from the crowd?
Couldn't that trigger it?
Possibly, but that's what
the earplugs are for, okay?
They're not gonna drown
out the crowd completely,
they will muffle it a bit.
Maybe your vision's correct.
Maybe we should switch places,
maybe you should be
running for the president.
I thought I was the teacher,
but I realized, I've learned more from you
about being a good president
and I'm still learning.
Don't worry, I can wait eight years.
Earplugs.
Thanks.
So let's give a warm welcome
to the next president
of the United States,
Patrick Dark Horse Lee.
(audience applauds)
(bright upbeat music)
I am not a man of words, as you know.
I may not be able to see,
but I can hear you, like
thunder in the night.
(audience applauds)
I was told that the audience comprises
of all political parties,
all genders, all ages,
all races, and creeds,
people from every state
of the United States
and many countries around the world.
Please cheer for yourselves.
(audience applauds)
For you represent the change
that the world wants and needs.
I have run a different type of campaign,
and I have let you and your
concerns do most of the talking.
We believe that whatever
we do in our campaign
must have more than one purpose.
And this, this gathering
gathering is no exception.
You are standing on the next solution.
The land that is cleared
for this gathering
will be the solution to
the homeless crisis in LA.
It will be called Angel City.
It will eliminate Skid Row
from the streets of LA.
(audience applauds)
Once this solution is tested,
it could be spread to other
cities in the United States
and around the world.
(audience applauds)
I would like to get a bit
personal for a moment.
(pensive music)
When I was a young man, I was very naive.
Eventually I got into the habit
of something that I was comfortable with,
but that made my relationship
with other people very limited at best,
and computers and other technologies
made it easier and easier
to limit my one on one
personal communications.
When I got older, I started
to miss the companionships
that others took for granted.
I was in a relationship
with a woman much younger.
I wanted to have a family.
I wanted to have a legacy
so that others would
know that I had existed,
and as you probably guessed,
that relationship did not work out.
But I learned something
much more important.
I learned to be independent,
to be self-motivated
and to live my purpose.
Today, I just found out
that two of the candidates
for the major political parties
has accepted my challenge.
From this day on,
they'll be using their campaign donations
to solve actual problems.
(audience applauds)
And their coffers are bigger than mine.
This makes me very happy.
(audience applauds)
And what makes me even
more happy and secure
is that I finally found my family.
You, you are my family.
(audience applauds)
Right in, Patrick Lee!
Even if I don't win this election,
I know that you will carry out my ideas
and my plans will move forward
in the United States and around the world.
(audience applauds)
You, you are my legacy.
And long after I am
gone and only a memory,
you will carry on!
(audience applauds)
(bright upbeat music)
We the people love Lee!
Patrick Lee, lead the way!
(bright upbeat music)