(WATER DRIPPING)
(ENGINES HUMMING)
FEVER: I imagine
everyone's gotten up
at four am at least once
or twice in their lives.
Try doing it seven days a week,
365 days a year.
And try it after half a dozen
beers and five shots of Jager.
-Are you okay?
-Come on, I'm fine.
There's five guys
working this dairy.
I'm not the oldest,
but I've been here the longest.
This was supposed
to be a summer job
while I figured
out a career path.
What the hell was in
those shots,
-wood polish?
-Ha, ha, ha.
That was six years ago.
-How are you this morning?
-Good.
We've all been there.
I'm all right.
♪ (GUITAR PLAYING) ♪
Fever, how you're doing
this morning, bud?
Jesus, I knew I shouldn't
have told you guys.
-We're concerned.
-Last night was rough on you.
-We all hated her anyway.
-That's exactly why.
Eh, I didn't mind her.
Hey, Colonel, get your ass up.
-(EXHALES)
-All right, let's hit it.
(COWS MOOING)
FEVER: My brother,
Randel, wrestled in high school.
A state champion,
three time All American.
We thought every
college in the country
would be handing
him a scholarship.
Hey, that's him.
FEVER: They didn't.
While he'd given up the sport,
he stuck with the exercise
and decided to use his
skills in other ways.
My brother said
he beat up Greg Mills.
Knocked out two of his
teeth and broke his leg.
He took a swing at me.
He said he's one of the
toughest guys he knew.
How'd you do it?
Took him to the ground
and beat the shit out of him.
FEVER: Dairy farming
isn't a job, it's a lifestyle.
When you work and live
at the same place,
pretty soon you start
calling that home.
And those people
you're working with,
they become your family.
The James' farm is
third generation.
And Ms. Elizabeth James
is the last of her line.
She never married,
doesn't have any kids.
But if you're hired on here,
you'll be treated
like one of her own.
I'm not paying you
to work on this shit box.
All right.
(GROANS)
I want you to go
over the hay barn.
I think some critters
have settled in.
I was in there this morning,
the stench damn near
took my head off.
The whole son of a bitch
reeks of piss.
Where's your brother and Wade?
You know, those whole steers
have been lined up
a half an hour in that parlor.
I don't pay you to wander around
and jerk off half the day.
Prototype.
Prototype was
our newest addition.
He joined the crew
after opting out
out of his father's business.
Hey, they were
completely out of glazed,
so they threw in two
lemon-filled for free.
You are gonna be out of a job
if you don't get your ass
in that milking parlor.
(ENGINE HUMMING)
What happened?
What, did you do that?
FEVER: Shotgun and Colonel were
always arguing about their band.
You're indifferent about
this whole thing aren't you?
FEVER: Shotgun
was in it for the music.
(CAR HORN BEEPS)
Colonel had other motivations.
Come on, Shotgun.
I was on my way to the bathroom.
She was on her way out,
we had a moment.
Man, those are
so wasted on you.
See, now why
would you say that?
(ENGINE REVVING)
-Come on, Shotgun.
-Back to work.
FEVER: For two
struggling musicians,
the job was a blessing.
They got a practice
space in the garage
and almost every night off.
(COWS MOOING)
D-1, D-1!
Here we go!
She's got some nerve.
(CAR HORN HONKS)
He's got it.
No mercy!
What do you think?
(SIGHS)
Not looking good.
Got grease all
over my hands, sorry.
Your brother looks pissed.
Yeah, he always
looks like that.
Come on, man,
we're gonna miss it.
-Come on.
-I don't need to watch.
FEVER: I started dating
Shelly my senior year.
She was everything
I've ever wanted.
You haven't said one thing.
FEVER: But most disasters
start that way.
How was the hike?
Because you told me
you were going over there
to use his computer.
-I did.
-Yeah?
Get back in that truck.
-You're overreacting.
-It isn't about the hike.
Okay?
The hike doesn't matter.
You lied, and that's what
tells me this is fucked.
He's a friend.
I read the note, Shelly.
I mean, Jesus,
at least be smart enough
to throw it away.
He knows I have a boyfriend.
I told him all about you.
He seems to be
respecting that.
Looks like you really
set him straight.
You hang out
with your friends.
My friends aren't girls
who wanna fuck me, okay.
Rooker, you know
you can trust me.
No, I don't.
Every single time I turn around,
you step in another turd.
I mean, you wonder
why after five years,
I haven't put a
ring on your finger?
It's shit like this.
You hold it over my head,
like it's some sort of a prize.
I love you.
And I don't fuck around
on you, you know?
It's not enough.
-It is enough.
-Then why every six months
are we putting out another fire?
You want something
that I don't have.
So you need to go out and
find someone who does.
What does that mean?
-Where are you going?
-I gotta work.
-Rooker!
-It's done, okay?
What about your truck?
Keep it.
(HOOD THUDS)
You gave her the truck?
Last thing I'll ever do is
get back in that fucking thing.
Well, I'd drive it.
(HEAVY SIGHING)
Boy did good.
-Get back to work.
-Oh, yeah, sorry.
Oh, Christ.
What's this?
-DELBERT: How are you doin'?
-Hey, don't climb that fence.
Get your ass off the fence!
-Now, you're trespassing.
-I'm Delbert Furgeson.
-Ah, shit.
-I'm looking for
-a Ms. Elizabeth James.
-Yeah, you're wasting my time.
Well, ma'am,
I'm with Del-Furg Foods.
Yeah, I know who you are.
I've been ignoring your calls
and trashing your
letters for weeks.
Well, my partners and I have
made you a generous offer.
(SCOFFS)
Good for you.
Sure would like to
have a sit down with you.
No reason for that.
Boys, go ahead and take lunch.
Go on, get to it,
before I change my mind.
Ms. James, we know how you're
not making out around here.
Yeah, things are looking up.
You and your partners
been in the red
-the past five years.
-Eh, market's been in a rizz.
Market's as strong
as it's gonna get.
I think you know that.
There's more to this than money.
Well, even pride's about money.
People respect you, Ms. James.
Heck, I respect you.
The way you cobbled
together this little co-op,
that's brass.
But you can't compete.
Not in this market.
Now, Del-Furg's a conglomerate,
I'll admit that.
But we have no use for your
property or your house.
Heck, you can keep this
sorry old herd if you want.
We just wanna merge the product.
Stabilize the market,
and let everybody share a
little piece of the profit.
Boy, you're slicker
than a Vaseline flagpole.
Can I be frank?
Your equipment's antiquated.
Heck, you're running
half the head
you should be on this place,
and there ain't much around
here that doesn't need fixing.
Just rebuilt the corrals.
They're fine, I'm sure,
but we could come in here
and subsidize a
complete renovation.
Bring this old time capsule
back into the 21st century.
All you gotta do is
give us the word.
Delbert, you a drinking man?
I can be.
You familiar with
the Cadillac Lounge?
-Yes, ma'am.
-Let me tell you something.
Right now I am knee
deep in cow shit
and all your jabbering
is making my head ring,
so how about I meet
you there tonight.
You bring your company plastic,
and those fancy little
blue jeans you're wearing
and we'll have a conversation.
I like that.
I like you.
I'll see you tonight.
I just saw you yesterday.
Had to pick up a few things.
Having a little get-together.
More beer.
Just like getting together,
I guess.
(LAUGHS)
Three cases?
It's not just us.
Uh, people come over,
-there's music.
-Yeah?
-D-1: It's usually a lot of fun.
-Monique.
Monique, let's speed it up.
We got a line forming here.
I'm on it, Charlie.
All right, 63.27.
FEVER: Randel doesn't drink,
but when we need a few cases,
he's always the first
to volunteer.
He'd never admit it,
but we all know why he goes.
COLONEL: Nothing big,
put a little flier in there.
It's got our contacts,
our phone number,
our next upcoming shows,
hand them out.
-How many you thinking?
-Like 250, 300.
And you just
wanna give them away?
It's promotional material, man.
It's what you do with
promotional material.
Was that girl working?
She mighta been,
didn't see her.
-Uh, these mine?
-Yep, here you go.
-Huh, we need a new name.
-The name is fine.
Come on, man.
There's no ring to it, man.
-People want catchy.
-We can't change the name now.
We have a song on the radio,
and everybody likes the name.
Those are our friends,
we're talkin' business here.
-SHOTGUN: It's fine.
-It's limiting our audience.
Well, Cosby and Will
wanna do a website.
Unless you're a
naked 15-year-old girl,
no one's looking
at your website.
I mean, 75 percent of our
audiences are drunk.
Thirty-five percent are stoned.
And the rest, they're both.
The only chance we got is to
get something into their hands,
and pray to God that
they have it in the morning.
All right.
Let's get outta here, man.
Okay.
Then, that's what I'll do.
I wouldn't suggest it.
If you're having trouble
paying the first,
the second's just gonna
put you further behind.
I'm just looking to float
through for a couple of months.
You've been floating
for the past few years.
Don, I'm expecting
a big summer.
We need a real solution here.
Right now you still have
some real property value.
With the cattle and equipment
I'm pretty sure
-we can pull a profit.
-Don, just give me
my goddamn second mortgage.
(SIGHS)
FEVER: So, gentlemen,
you feeling it?
I feel it.
We'll take it down now.
FEVER: Bored with beer pong,
we started playing bocce ball.
It proved anything could be
turned into a drinking game.
Oh, yeah!
That's concentration, you know?
Just a bit of concentration,
that's all it takes.
D-1: Try not to keep sucking.
This ain't about the last
seven games we lost.
I know, man.
I'm playing like shit.
Yeah, that was the past.
Whatever happened
the last 45 minutes,
you gotta put that
shit outta your head.
-Look at those red balls.
-Yeah.
They're everything that's
wrong with this world.
The bubonic plague, AIDS,
Nazis, Teen Wolf Too.
I want you to think of yourself
as all the reasons
life is worth living, okay?
Internet porn, cherry icees,
Susie Q's.
You are that light
in that darkness.
(EXHALES LOUDLY)
Know that in your heart.
Thank you.
-Thank you.
-Just do it.
(LAUGHTER)
Hey, neuro.
Drink up, gentlemen.
I'm going out
for a couple hours.
You see that sprinkler?
You gotta turn it off.
FEVER: Yes, ma'am.
Just pass me a cold one
and go back to your game.
SHOTGUN: I hate bocce ball.
I hate it, why do we play it?
Let's go again.
Let's go again, all right?
O and eight.
We're going again.
(WATER SPLASHING)
I think we should
go see the old man.
-Did he call?
-No.
I got shit to do tomorrow, man.
-You're on fire.
-What?
-Burning.
-Shit!
(FORCEFUL BLOWING)
Doesn't have to be tomorrow.
Well, we gotta go see Mom.
Stand around half the day,
deal with all
those fucking dogs.
Why would you want to do that?
These got burnt.
It's hot.
Are we gonna hear
any music tonight?
Because George Noory's got
an abduction special
on Coast to Coast.
-We'll go on right now.
-All right.
(BASS GUITAR TUNING)
(DRUMSTICKS CLANKING)
Hey, let's get some work done.
♪ (ROCK MUSIC PLAYS) ♪
♪ Let's stop and think
about this for a minute ♪
♪ Since when do people
sit still in this day ♪
Stop, stop, stop,
stop, stop, stop, stop,
stop, stop, stop.
(MUSIC STOPS)
Fucking mess.
Hey, leavin' a little early,
Delbert?
I made you my offer.
Your offer?
A little fuckin' limp
if you ask me.
You know,
you're a sloppy belligerent.
What makes you think I'd
be attracted to that?
You son of a bitch!
(GLASS SHATTERING)
Goddamn it, woman,
that's a new automobile.
-(LIZ MOANS)
-(DELBERT LAUGHS)
Look at you wollerin'
around in the mud.
Serves you right.
Why don't you come on
back in the house, huh?
Let's see if you got any balls.
Come back here again,
I'll rip your fucking cock off!
It's a goddamn bog out here!
How the hell are
you eating that?
SHOTGUN: You don't
like pancakes and gravy?
I don't even know
why we come here.
We come here because it's
the only place open after 12.
It's the statue.
It's a giant baby
wearing overalls.
-Birdboy's an icon.
-That thing creeps me out.
-You see that guy?
-Who?
Him, right there.
-The big guy?
-Yeah. Is he staring over here?
I don't know,
maybe you know him.
Yeah, he does
look kinda familiar.
Yeah, that's probably it.
-So you're...
-So, I was talking to her...
Not gonna give you
the time of day?
No, and who cares?
-Obviously, she--
-I can't help it, she's so hot.
You do this every
time you see a girl.
-I can't even eat.
-What, man?
Because he's a
goddamn nuisance.
-Look at him over there.
-Okay, will you calm down.
You have your flapjacks.
You have your hot chocolate.
Okay?
You're fine.
-I'm calm, look at me.
-This guy, look at him,
-he's probably hammered.
-Whoa, wait, what happened?
Randel wants to fight some guy.
-What did he do?
-FEVER: Nothing.
No, not nothing.
He's been eyeing me
since we got here.
-Well, let's kick his ass.
-FEVER: Don't encourage him.
You guys probably went to
preschool together or something.
Okay.
Yeah, that was at you.
-I told you.
-Randel. Shit.
Is there a problem?
-You're Randel Lee.
-Goddamn right.
Randel, take
that shit outside.
-It's fine, Dan.
-It's not fine.
I want this out of my place.
We're just talking.
You got into it with
my little cousin, Greg.
-Knocked him around pretty good.
-Hey, Greg was looking for it.
-That's not what I heard.
-Randel, will you tell him?
Oh, yeah, you know,
I could explain it,
but this guy just looks
too fucking stupid
to understand it.
(CHUCKLES)
Yeah.
(GRUNTING)
You wanna go, you wanna go?
DAN: Outside!
You know there's no reason
to fight this guy, right?
That son of a bitch thinks
he can pull that on me?
This is a bad idea.
Nah, so he's a little
bigger than I thought.
All right, what are we gonna do
if he starts kicking your ass?
I guess run like hell.
All right, you and me, we
gotta discuss a couple things
-before we get going here.
-Yeah, what's that?
Like your three butt
buddies over here,
-they're gonna jump in.
-They're not jumpin' in.
Oh, yeah, what about
this guy right here?
He looks like a back fightin'
son of a bitch to me.
-Fuck you.
-Hey, we gonna go
or you just gonna keep
floppin' your lips?
-Let's go, let's do this, baby.
-Kick this faggot's ass, Jack.
(GRUNTS)
-That's fantastic.
-I warned him.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, cut it out.
(CROWD YELLING)
Oh, shit.
(POLICE SIRENS BLARING)
All right,
I'll take care of it.
Just sit down,
let me talk to the boys.
Don't worry about it.
I don't have to tell you,
you're getting off lucky.
However, if you don't
follow up on the promises
that you made to Dan
and his establishment,
I'm gonna haul your butts in
on destruction of property
and disturbing the peace.
Are we clear?
ALL BUT D-1: Yes, sir.
Randel, are you clear?
Yes sir.
Cut them loose.
What about Jack?
Jack's coming with me.
Appears he got himself
into a little knife fight
over in Yettem.
You have a good night.
FEVER: Our parents are divorced.
It got ugly.
Mom got the house.
Dad got the mistress.
All right.
Who's first, Mom or Dad?
Surprise me.
(ENGINE REVVING)
Place looks great, Mom.
Dirt's what's
holdin' it together.
Less than that.
They're fat as hogs already.
Randel, I see you're still
getting along with folks.
Same as usual.
You know your daddy liked
to get drunk and fight.
I don't drink, Mom.
Well, maybe you ought to.
I'll be in the car.
(FEVER SIGHS)
You still drivin' that van?
Dad gave it to me.
Because he could never
get the thing running.
It does now, Mom.
(KISSES)
Well, that's Gene.
Whatever he give you,
is probably
more trouble than it's worth.
Come on, Daddy.
FEVER: Dad was a
national champion team roper.
And I think he always hoped
we'd follow the same path.
With Dad's intensity and
all-night practice sessions,
a once fun activity
quickly turned to torture.
He started entering us in
competitions when we were ten.
By 15 we were
completely burnt out.
-Nice one, Dad.
-Nice job, Daddy.
Sorry about that, Randel.
Come on.
Wouldn't be bad,
you boys not ropin',
if you weren't
so damn good at it.
-Mm-hmm.
-Sorry, Dad.
Just don't like it.
Who beat the hell outta you?
Did I mention Rooker
broke up with Shelly?
Oh, my God.
I loved her.
Seeing some other
guy behind his back.
-Please stop.
-What?
Well, that's a bit of a shock.
I thought that girl had
some nice qualities.
Last thing I wanna
do is get into it.
Arlene is workin'
at the auction.
Mm-hmm.
It's kinda fast paced,
isn't it?
Mmm, I work the door.
Lord knows I don't wanna make
sense of all that mumbling.
(LAUGHTER)
Tell them,
tell them what you did.
Mm, I picked up a
tractor for your daddy.
I love this woman.
-Is it John Deere?
-Uh, Massey Ferguson.
-Those are nice.
-Red, and a bucket.
Yeah, is it new?
-Used, low hours.
-Yeah.
I'm thinking about
getting a bush hog.
Clean up this place.
It needs it.
I don't know how he
could take her seriously.
I just wanted to smash that
sandwich into her face.
-She's not that bad, man.
-He must be barely getting by.
All he does now are
those home town arenas.
Looks like he's
doing all right.
Mom would never him
get away with that.
Oh, hi, I'm Leslie Williams.
-Good to meet you.
-We've met.
(CHUCKLES)
Nice to see you again.
Oh, bad ass.
Look, kid, I'm up in two.
(STUTTERING) Well, you've
already played one of our songs.
-Well, that's great.
-&quot;White elephant&quot;.
-Oh, uh, &quot;Shogun.&quot;
-Shotgun.
But we got a new
name in the air, man.
-DJ: Perfect.
-And a new CD.
Fantastic.
Well, um, we got a couple
of shows coming up
so I put a few
fliers in the case.
Love it.
Keep up the good work, kid.
All right.
Thanks, man.
All right everybody!
This is the Noffinator
comin' to you on 101.3.
(COWS MOOING)
-Easy, easy, Lizzy.
-What the hell is going on?
Take it easy.
The CDFA has always
been fair to me,
but lately I'm feeling
a little pissed on.
This isn't the way
I do business.
-Hell, you know that.
-I know that,
-so get these pricks outta here.
-Well, he's a state guy.
It's best just to let him
have a look around.
They'll be outta here
before you know it.
What are they looking for?
We gotta bug or something?
-(GRUMBLING) Routine.
-Don't bullshit me.
Routine was five months ago.
These guys don't like to get
their pretty little
coats dirty for nothing.
Someone's working
to put you out.
Delbert Furgeson.
He's got some big
friends in Sacramento.
Inspection's just
the first step,
next he's going to go
after your client list.
He'll cut into your
profits if can.
He'll pay them if he has to.
God, that slimy cock sucker.
It's not just you.
He's going after
your partners, too.
(LIZ SIGHS HEAVILY)
All right, pass those
out to everybody, man.
I don't care. Thanks.
Is this what you've
been doing all day?
Yeah, I slipped a copy off
to Phil Noff this morning.
Why the hell is
your name on it?
I knew you were gonna ask that
so let me just say one thing.
Mamas and the Papas.
Mama was always
the front runner.
She was smart enough to know
that a band called Mama
wasn't gonna light any fires
up at the top ten.
Shotgun's too violent.
It's scaring people off, man.
We add the Colonel and it says,
&quot;Hey, I'm violent,
but I'm friendly.&quot;
You take me home,
we're gonna have a good time.
Did you draw this?
Yeah.
Well, the inspiration came.
Damn near drew itself.
-Those guys are gonna kill you.
-Now, man,
Cosby and Will are gonna realize
that sometimes
you need to make sacrifices
for the better of the band.
All right?
Come on.
Does that piece
of shit even run?
Goddamn street racers.
(ENGINES REVVING)
Third stop sign down.
You say when.
-What are you doing?
-I can take them.
You're not driving
a fucking hemi.
You said it was a four, 2800.
-It's a four cylinder, 2110.
-Whatever, it's fast.
It's fast for a Volkswagen,
yeah.
When.
(TIRES SQUEALING)
(ENGINES REVVING)
Watch your RPM.
Woo, fuck yeah!
Shit!
Just pull it over,
pull it over.
(GEARS GRINDING)
Yeah, maybe you should drive
this fucking piece of shit.
-It's a 50-year-old car, man.
-It's a sack of shit.
-I want a Chevy.
-You want a Chevy.
-Everybody has a Chevy.
-They work.
It's a classic.
♪ (ROCK MUSIC PLAYS) ♪
You guys have probably
our single on 101.3.
Yeah, it's like this
emo, alternative,
rock n' roll, dance-dance
revolution type thing.
-Hmm, I like hip hop.
-It's got that too.
-Can I get two more beers.
-Scotch on the rocks, please.
-Hey.
-FEVER: How you doin', fellas?
Buddy, nice to see you.
Guess who we saw?
-I'm leaving.
-Hey, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Easy MacFeve
You can't just shit your pants
and run for the trenches.
You gotta stay on the field.
You gotta show her that
this is your house.
-FEVER: Where is she?
-SHELLY: Rooker?
Drink.
How are you?
FEVER: All right.
Well, they just can't get enough
of Shotgun and the Colonel.
(CHATTERING)
FEVER: It's not appropriate,
it's not what Shelly does.
Jesus, will you look at the
way she's fondling that glass?
PROTOTYPE: Mm-hmm,
like I noticed the lean.
Legs crossed, gentle stroking
of the upper thigh,
dress hiked up just enough
to be revealing
yet maintaining
classy undertone.
Oh, God, this is not the same
girl Fever successfully
took down at the farm.
This is something new.
This is a woman on the prowl.
A tigress, stalking a prey.
Goading it to the
point of exhaustion.
He'll try to fight her off,
but there won't be much
left when it's over.
-I'm going in there.
-No, hey, no.
No amount of brute
force can pry his mind
from those firm, milky thighs.
He's gotta do that
shit all by himself.
Damn right.
What in the hell is this?
You can't change the
fucking name of the band.
You're just the goddamn
tambourine player, man.
You know
that's uncalled for, man.
You know I sing backups.
-Dude, you just wanna get laid.
-Oh, come on, dude.
I'm trying to build
a fan base, man.
-What the fuck's that shit, bro?
-You know what the fuck that is,
-It's fucking in the chest, man.
-You son of a bitch.
COLONEL: Come on, man.
(GROANING)
Get off my fucking foot.
Maybe he's in the back room.
Nope, she's got him.
I know it.
COLONEL: Hey, fuck you
and the horse you rode in on.
FEVER: The boys had
all been pulling for me.
So, I'd like to say
it didn't go down easy.
But I offered her the ride.
He took my fucking car.
COLONEL: Come on, die.
They're my fucking
boots anyway.
All right, scrappy-doo,
let's go, come on.
Great, thank you,
thank you, sir,
because he started it.
Hey, let go of him.
Get up.
FEVER: Shelly owned
a lot of lingerie,
but she never wore it.
To her it was art.
Everybody thought
that was weird but me.
We had so many pictures.
I think I'm done looking,
sorry.
Are you crying?
No.
(CHUCKLES)
I just spilled a little
beer on my cheek.
We screwed this up.
(SIGHS)
-I'm gonna go.
-You can have me if you want.
(ENGINE RUMBLING)
FEVER: Why is that
the worst girls for us
are the ones that
we're most attracted to?
(CHATTERING)
Morning, Fever.
You're supposed to
be beating the Colonel
at a pancake eating contest.
I wish you would stop
telling people that.
-It was a tie.
-You didn't even finish.
I told you from the beginning,
I do not eat hash browns.
So where were you last night?
I slept in the car.
Bullshit.
PROTOTYPE: It's not
looking real good, Fever.
I'm serious.
It's okay, you know,
we've all been there before.
Just don't let it happen again.
(BELL CHIMES)
Wade.
Dad.
I thought you were
never settin' foot
inside this hell hole again.
Yeah, sorry about that.
I haven't heard
from you in six months.
That too.
What brings you by?
I gotta paint something.
Not much of a surprise there.
-Boys.
-Hey, Mr. Kitchanski.
Actually, we need to fix it
and then paint it.
-Mm-hmm.
-I think it's plastic.
Fiberglass.
It's a small town, son.
-Your mother was really upset.
-Sorry, Dad.
Well, I assume you
brought color samples.
D-1.
So, what is that, the arm?
Looks like the left.
It's a leg.
-How can you tell?
-FEVER: Because it's red.
Red overalls and white shirt.
Well, he'd probably get
more customers without it.
All right.
Grab that other leg, Randel.
Colonel, find the crotch.
Just stack the bales, boys,
and call it a day.
COLONEL: All right.
(CLEARS THROAT)
(LAUGHTER)
Okay, it's beginning to look
a lot like Christmas around--
-Oh, my God, that's heavy.
-Exactly, exactly.
-All right.
-The way to my heart.
-That's for you.
-Thank you.
Oh, and Jack, here you are.
There you are.
(LAUGHTER)
-Thank you.
-Okay, guys,
nothing very exciting.
Just some stuff
that I thought might come
in handy for you.
Oh, I love these.
LIZ: Those are so good.
They're from last year,
-but I think...
-Did you get this?
(LIZ LAUGHING)
Where you going?
Where you going guys, where?
This is going down tonight.
I just, I have a feeling.
Oh, my God, what is this?
Aw, this is-- Aw, guys!
This is too much.
This is like totally
over the top.
-We all pitched in.
-COLONEL: Come on, open it.
Oh, my gosh, I'm afraid.
Oh, should I just rip it open?
-Yeah.
-Go for it, just.
Oh, let's see what
you got here, huh?
What is this?
This is, uh, this is a, uh...
(LAUGHTER)
-Oh, this is an HDTV.
-ALL: Yeah.
This is the best
thing on the market.
Full 1080p definition, E86 for
better gamma representation,
literally everything.
It's a Sony.
Oh, my gosh,
that is the nicest thing
in this whole house, huh?
But where are we
gonna put that, huh?
How about here?
Let's put it right here.
Don't you think
it's gonna be a little hard
to see right there?
Where would you put it?
Maybe just here behind you.
That way you can see it
from the couch
-and the arm chairs.
-Yeah, you know,
in case you have like,
folks over, you know,
-for like the Super Bowl or--
-Or the World Cup.
You know, I'd watch ice melt
if it were in HD.
You can watch ice
melting right here, pal.
Okay. Well, yeah, all right.
Well, let's put it there then.
BOYS: All right.
Then let's set it up.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
No, not now, though.
I mean, we have plenty of time
before the super day bowls.
So I want you guys now to go,
and I want you to go
see your parents, okay?
I want all of you
to get out of here
and go see your families.
-FEVER: You sure?
-I'm absolutely positive.
-Okay, all right.
-Merry Christmas.
-Thank you, I love it.
Thank you.
FEVER: It was never easy getting
everyone together for Christmas.
Mom need to have it
at her place.
Dad had to bring Arlene.
It all looks amazing.
Only took me half
the day to cook it.
You always had a gift
in the kitchen.
I have a lot of gifts, Gene.
Yeah, I know you do, Retta.
Guess they weren't enough.
Gene tells me all the time
about what a great
rider you were.
Said he'd never seen anybody
race the barrels like you did.
That was years ago, honey.
But don't worry, I'm sure
your gift will get old too.
So you doin' all right?
Yeah.
And your music,
how's that going?
It's going good, real good.
Well, if you ever
need any help,
if you need anything,
or the band.
We gotta show at the
Cadillac coming up.
Ew! Well, we will
try to make that one.
You always enjoyed the
boys' music, didn't you, dear?
Very much.
I think this is a
little bit dry, don't you?
Thank you.
Get you anything else?
Another coke?
Oh, no, I'm fine. Thanks.
I'm good, thanks.
All right, honey.
Don't know why
he can't just sit
and have a meal with his family.
(LAUGHTER)
Wade!
-WADE'S MOM: Wade, hi.
-MAN: Wade!
(LAUGHTER)
(COWS MOOING)
(PHONE RINGING)
What's got you
callin' me, Dennis?
Yeah, of course I do.
Come on, I'm working.
What do you want?
What do you mean
you can't ship my milk?
Why the hell not?
Dennis Krantz!
Liz, Del-Furg's
the biggest account we have.
-He buffaloed you.
-Sure as hell did.
You act like I don't know that.
We're not stopping,
me and my partners.
I'm not asking you to.
We'll go to state
if we have to.
Excellent,
excellent idea.
Oh, fuck you, Dennis.
Listen, no matter what--
Mark, Mark, I'm getting
a cup of coffee,
I'll be there in three hours,
we're gonna fix this.
Don't say it's too late.
I spent 15 years
working on this.
You're sorry?
Don't hang up. Mark--
Shit.
-That'll be $44.50.
-All right.
Uh, you got five bucks?
Prototype, you got $5?
Yeah.
COLONEL: Nice, thanks.
Excuse me, you mind if I ask
where you guys are going?
FEVER: Summers
in the Central Valley
are like a furnace,
and this was our favorite
way to beat the heat.
-Colonel.
-Mm.
Where'd you find these girls?
Uh, you know, they
just liked the band.
What are they into?
Into?
Yeah, what are they into?
What do they like?
Who knows,
here, offer them a beer.
Just carry on an
intelligent conversation.
Keep the focus on them.
Women just wanna be stimulated.
I can do that.
FEVER: They were right,
it's simple.
Just follow the instructions,
like rebuilding a carburetor.
Hi.
-Hey.
You know
that's gonna kill you, right?
It'll be the epidemic
of our generation.
Ten years from now,
when everybody's talking about
isolated cases of arrhythmia
and malignant growths,
we'll all be addicted.
But that's okay,
because we all knew
what we were getting
ourselves into, right?
Anything that gets your heart
fluttering like a hummingbird,
and synapses firing
at 200 gigahertz
can't be good for you.
It's like smoking.
You know it's bad for you.
You don't need the Surgeon
General to tell you that.
People have been coughing
and hacking up shit
for a thousand years,
but that's the appeal.
I mean, I wish I smoked.
It just looks cool.
Do you wanna beer?
I'll be back here.
(WATER SPLASHING)
Well, you fucked that up.
Fever!
I can't remember the last
time I had my socks off
during the middle of the day.
I mean, when we came out here,
I had the notion
to just get so piss drunk
that I just pitch
off into this river.
But I gotta tell you,
this is... This is...
SHOTGUN: Fun?
It just keeps going, doesn't it?
(PEOPLE SHOUTING)
(WATER SPLASHING)
This could be the
best day of my life.
(LAUGHTER)
I know what happened.
LIZ: How much longer, Rooker?
I mean, we need
to get somebody
who knows how to fix this shit.
I am not paying some
huckster $200 an hour
because you are too lazy
to read the manual.
Give it to me.
(PAGES RUSTLING)
(SIGHS)
Gotta get somebody out here.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
God, they're already playing.
We're missing the fucking show.
FEVER: Hurry your ass up, then.
MIKE: Thanks, guys.
Enjoy the show.
-FEVER: What's up, Mike.
-Hey, how you doin', buddy?
FEVER: Are we good?
Thanks.
Come on, Mike. I've been here
100 fucking times.
Jack Shaw is looking for you.
-When'd they let him out?
-A couple of weeks ago.
He's lookin' to bust you up.
Yeah. Well tell him
to get in line, right?
He's been fucking
a lot of people up
in those amateur cage fights.
If I see him,
what do you want me to say?
Make something up.
What the hell was that about?
Guy's a fucking dick.
-FEVER: Prototype.
-What's up, man?
♪ All the bands
Playing in places ♪
♪ With the same look
On your faces ♪
♪ 'Cause we're in this one
Together ♪
♪ Singin' songs
About the weather ♪
♪ Bees swarm together ♪
♪ Boys makin' passes ♪
♪ At the girls
In the horn-rimmed glasses ♪
♪ All the bands
playing in places ♪
♪ With the same look
On your faces ♪
(CHEERING)
Yeah.
FEVER: Encore.
Thank you guys for
coming out tonight.
Thanks for cancelling the dart
tournament so we could play.
We're Shotgun and the Colonel.
FEVER: That's right, Shotgun.
(CRASHING)
MAN: Hey, get back here, man.
Uh, so these guys,
I think are done.
You got another one, Colonel,
you got another one in you?
COLONEL: Oh, yeah, oh, yeah.
We got one more
song for you guys, so...
Thank you guys and drive safe.
(APPLAUSE)
♪ The street was wide ♪
♪ With indecision ♪
♪ And we were too ♪
♪ The traffic light ♪
♪ Was ripe with wisdom ♪
♪ And it shined
straight through ♪
♪ 'Cause we're
all fightin' for ♪
♪ The place at the
head of the line ♪
♪ But we just sat there and
Felt fine ♪
♪ Because we are exactly ♪
♪ Where we're supposed to be ♪
♪ When I call tomorrow ♪
♪ Won't you please
Just answer me ♪
♪ The boats all sat ♪
♪ And read Bukowski ♪
♪ And the sailors laughed ♪
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
-Shotgun!
-Shotgun! Get up, baby!
Get up, baby!
(PHONE DIALING)
Hey, man,
this is Phil Noff from 101.3,
Listen, Jackie caught
the show last night
and uh, you know,
fucking solid, kid.
We should talk.
Looks like we got a fan.
Your mix is shit.
The lyrics are sophomoric,
and the sound feels like it
came outta someone's bathroom.
But you don't apologize for it,
and that's the turn on.
You guys are raw.
-Coffee?
-Oh, yeah.
Now, time is not on our
side here, gentlemen.
You're a little older than
the labels usually like
-to start with.
-I'm 27.
Hendrix was dead at 27.
Make it 22.
-You?
-Thirty-four.
Twenty-six.
And put out the cigarette.
Now, this next part's
gonna be the toughest.
So, I'm just gonna do
it to the extreme, okay.
I don't want
the rest of the band.
-Oh?
-They're drunk,
they're untalented,
they're-- they're stupid.
Man, I don't know.
I mean, we been playing
with those guys since forever.
Loyalty is noble,
but it doesn't impress me.
I want to manage you guys,
but I am not here
to hold your hand
or be your little buddy.
If I didn't see a chance
of making some money here,
I'd rather be in the
bottom of a glass, okay?
Now, what I did do,
is I sent the album
to a friend of mine,
lives out in Glendale.
Now, he's a talent scout
for Red Diamond Records.
He loved it.
He loved your sound.
Now, what we wanna do,
is we wanna get some
professional musicians,
cut a new album,
take it the rest of the way.
But I am gonna need a contract.
Just your standard, you know,
agent, manager,
client agreement.
Yeah.
Here, man.
Leslie, you might not
wanna sign that right now.
Yeah.
Sure, I get you.
Look it over, okay?
But don't drag your ass.
I am not easily inspired,
and when I am it doesn't tend
to last too long.
Well, it's been a slice.
Well, we'll just look this over,
fill it out, you know.
Take our time.
-Go get them.
-All right.
Goddamn it,
call if you need anything.
-We will, we will.
-Don't do anything stupid.
All right! Woohoo!
(TIRES SQUEALING)
Well, shit.
(CHEERING)
FEVER: The fight had gotten
a lot of attention.
Jack Shaw was scoring off
against a ranked pro.
We were eating it up.
But I've never seen
Randel more focused.
(CHEERING)
(YELLING)
Somebody needs
to chain that guy up.
(TRACTOR RUMBLING)
You boys gotta finish up.
My head's about ready to pop.
I got it.
Keep it half throttle?
-Yeah.
-I got it.
Okay.
(TRACTOR RUMBLING)
FEVER: It wasn't that Randel
didn't understand half throttle,
he just didn't tolerate it.
Shit, shit, shit!
Oh, fuck!
Piece of shit.
Fucking help.
I think, uh...
-Yeah?
-It's a piece of shit.
You broke it didn't you?
Oh, so because I was driving,
it's my fault?
Yes, actually it is.
That's stupid.
Who do you think's
gonna have to fix this?
-I said I was sorry.
-Yeah.
Well, you're tellin' her.
I'm not tellin' her.
I said I'd tell her.
Ms. Liz.
It's Randel.
Oh, Rooker, Rooker!
Ms. Liz! Try to find the phone.
FEVER: I'm gonna get the car.
Hold it, hold it.
Get the van door!
I've informed her
that while the observational
stay isn't mandatory,
the doctor recommends it,
and by ignoring this
she's putting herself
at further risks.
Now, these procedures
are common practice,
and not meant to, as she put it,
pluck a hen's last feather.
Now, the recovery is a
slow and lifelong process.
Those pamphlets will
go over the basic needs
and restrictions of a
recovering stroke victim.
If you need the number
to a specialist or caregiver,
see me at the nurse's station
and I'll be happy to accommodate
you with that information.
Any questions?
Good.
Now, I'm supposed
to wheel her out,
but I'm not going back in there.
You wanna try
and get her in this chair,
you can do it your damn selves.
Gentlemen.
(DOOR KNOCKING)
Don't even think about it.
-To help you.
-Back out, back out.
Back out.
I'm not getting in that thing.
I'm not getting in it.
Rest is your friend,
and rehabilitation
is a team sport.
Lack of sleep may
cause the stroke victim
to become confused or irritable.
Be positive when speaking
to the stroke victim.
What you say is not as
important as how you say it.
Be sure to give your
stroke victim lots of love.
Rooker, pull over, right here.
Right here.
Six pack of Bud,
two packs of Spirits.
-This is a good idea?
-Hell yeah, it's a good idea.
I don't think you're supposed
to drink with this stuff.
Doctor didn't say
anything about not drinking.
It says it right
here in the pamphlet.
Smoking doesn't cause strokes,
it causes cancer.
And I sure as hell
don't have cancer.
All the pamphlets say stroke.
Will you stop with
those goddamn pamphlets?
We'll get your blanket.
We'll set up your bed.
I'll go to bed
when I'm tired,
-thank you very much.
-Watch your step.
Use your cane, all right?
I'm gonna get the door.
I'm right behind you.
Okay? Just in case.
You boys don't
stop fussing over me,
I'm gonna box your ears.
Straight off the other
side of your heads.
If I was keelin' over it
would've happened
-three days ago.
-Don't forget these.
I'm just gonna leave
them out here for you.
She was tired,
irritated and pissed off.
It was good to have her back.
Got your pills, too.
Did you hear that?
Hear what?
That.
(TRUCK RUMBLING)
Should she be driving?
I don't think she
should be driving.
Maybe you ought
to tell her that.
(TIRES SQUEALING)
Excuse me, how much longer
do you think it's gonna take?
Any moment now.
This custard's gonna be soup.
I'll be sure to tell him.
Thank you.
I'm here to see
Delbert Ferguson.
-Do you have an appointment?
-Tell him it's Elizabeth James.
Elizabeth James is here.
Yes, sir.
He's with an appointment.
Would you like to wait?
Not much choice is there?
(PHONE RINGING)
RECEPTIONIST: Yes,
he's with an appointment.
(SIGHS)
Mother Cluckers?
She left a message.
(PHONE RINGS)
Could you read
it to me, please?
&quot;I was going to slap your face,
but I've decided to
kick your ass instead.&quot;
Thank you.
Um, I'll be in my office.
LIZ: We've lost
30 percent of our income.
Over the next three months we're
gonna lose another ten percent.
At the rate we're going
Cal Valley will be bankrupt
in a year.
We don't know shit
about ice cream.
-None of us do.
-Actually it's custard.
You gotta think
progressive, Cal.
This kid, he's basically
got a Ph.D. in ice cream.
It was a dessert university.
Just tell them
about the fat, Dale.
This is a gourmet product
that just out-tasted
every major brand
at this year's Frozen
Taste Off Awards.
Frozen dairy desserts are
good because of their fat.
What we do is we make
our fat particles smaller,
packing as much of that goodness
into each and every bite.
This and my personal
recipe make our custard
richer and smoother
than anyone else.
We're gonna market
it as a specialty item.
Containing only quality organic
cream from Cal Valley Dairies.
We're gonna process and
package it, all right here.
Dale, give us a second.
-Please.
-Yeah.
(DOOR CLOSES)
This kid is going out
of his way.
He's already got
offers on the table.
-What's he need us for?
-Because he's a local boy,
and he wants to stay local.
And because we're offering him
shared control of his product.
-It's a blind investment.
-What isn't?
It's all a bit too wild hair.
Maybe we ought
to consider Del-Furg.
-It's a guaranteed income.
-That guy would sell
his asshole
and shit through his ribs
if someone was offering.
Lest I remind you
he's the reason
we're paying twice
as much to ship our milk.
He's trying to strong arm us.
Now, I don't know about you,
but there's no way
I'll let that son of a bitch
bend me over a barrel.
Dave, you haven't said a word.
What are you thinkin'?
Let me try it.
I'm in.
Best damn thing I ever had.
You're kiddin'.
Do I look like I'm kidding?
FEVER: It was the first time
we'd seen Ms. Liz dream big.
The facility was gonna
produce 80 gallons an hour.
We'd never have to buy
ice cream again.
God, look at that!
-(CLAPPING)
-(CHEERING)
SHOTGUN: What
is up, corn stalk?
You look beautiful.
WOMAN: This is so adorable.
-(SCREAMING)
-(SHOTGUN THUDS)
FEVER: Oh, hey.
LIZ: See if we can get
some of this down him.
You changed the name.
Yeah, well, Shotgun and
the Colonel was too Indie.
Phil says we need something
that reaches off the rack,
you know?
Really grabs you by the balls.
Yeah, but where's Shotgun?
Well, we put Allie
and the girls up front,
so we could
really show them off.
This looks like
a wild west show.
That's just the demographic
we're going after.
Phil says there's a lot of
room in country, you know.
It's not exactly
a defined genre.
Looks like it's gonna
be one hell of a thing.
Be glad you don't
have to build it.
I could help out, you know?
Maybe do a jingle or something.
Think she'd use it
if it was any good?
Hell yeah, why not?
Seems like she's
getting around okay.
Still up before we
are most mornings.
Tough old bird.
The band looks good.
Yeah, they'll
sell some records.
Colonel says you are gonna be
on tour in a couple of months.
Yeah, he's pretty
excited about that.
Hey.
(HEAVY EXHALING)
I do miss this.
We should get going
if we wanna beat the traffic.
I'm gonna go,
the girls are inside.
Getting a little hungry.
♪ (LATIN MUSIC PLAYS) ♪
FEVER: I didn't tell Randel,
but I've been trying
to set this up for weeks.
The hardest part will be
getting him to the door.
I knew the rest would
work itself out.
D-1: Why are we
going here again?
Change of pace.
Heard it was good.
Who said it was good?
Uh, you know her.
It's not bad, huh?
Sure.
Gonna get a beer.
Excuse us.
Jimmy, looks like you
did some remodeling.
Had to, place dried up quicker
than an old lady's crotch.
FEVER: Looks like it worked.
-I gotta take a piss.
-All right.
-Uh, Corona and a Sprite.
-No Corona.
-Uh, Dos Equis.
-Nope.
Modelo, Tecate, Caguama.
The only thing
that's sellin' is Bud.
Monique.
Uh, I know from your name tag.
-I'm Randel.
-Hi.
-You know this guy.
-Yeah, it's okay, Art.
I'm just saying hello.
I shop at Lucky Mart.
Why don't you go pick
up on someone else?
I'm fine.
It's cool.
I'm just saying hi, man.
I don't know you.
I'm not gonna shake
-your fucking hand.
-Arturo!
No need to be rude.
Just get the fuck out of here.
MAN: Fucking cowboys.
-(RUMBLING)
-(SHOUTING)
Get in the fucking car!
Come on!
D-1: Go, go, go, go, go.
Oh, shit!
-(GLASS SHATTERING)
-Oh, shit.
Fuck!
Fucking stupid, Randel!
God.
(POLICE SIRENS BLARRING)
Shit!
Can't say I'm surprised.
(ENGINE REVVING)
Stay in the car.
I think these boys had enough.
Take another step,
you're gonna feel it.
Fuck.
(HEAVY BREATHING)
(RADIO CHATTER)
What if I was
five minutes later?
You think
you'd still be breathing?
Randel, shouldn't you
be wrestling somewhere?
I'm talking to you, son.
My grades weren't
too good, sir.
Well, that's a shame.
That's a damn shame.
Because you sure had
the talent.
(RADIO CHATTER)
MAN: It was a mistake.
Now, I'm here because you
were the best deal in town,
-and now you're not.
-Our price is still
-very competitive.
-No,
you said $1.98 a piece
on the phone.
But that was for
the eight footers.
You read from the
wrong price sheet.
Look, I can get it
cheaper across town.
It's just a few
dollars difference.
No, it's not about the money.
It is about being snookered.
Get that shit off my truck.
Hold on, damn it.
Fine, $1.98 apiece.
I don't like the way
you do business.
Look, lady,
I'm real sorry for the mix up.
How about I make you out
a voucher, we'll make it right.
(ENGINE REVVING)
I won't be back.
Hey!
Come on!
(TIRES SQUEALING)
(CAR HORN BLARING)
Call 911!
Get some help!
(WIND SOFTLY BLOWING)
FEVER:
Ms. Liz hadn't made a will.
And there were no next of kin.
If the dairy was gonna stay
open it was up to us.
And we were willing
to put it all on the line.
DON: Gentlemen.
I'd first like to say
that we are very grateful,
both for your present accounts
and for the opportunity
-you've presented with us today.
-Thank you.
Unfortunately no one
qualified for a loan
to subsidize Ms. James'
incurred debts.
Even with the cosigner?
Right. Well, uh, the problem
is that cosigner,
or cosigners in this case,
typically have assets that can
be leveraged as collateral.
The '63 Bug, '93 Stratus
and '84 Vanagon
don't carry the monetary
value required
to cover a $250,000 mortgage.
However, Rooker Lee did
qualify for a personal loan
of $5,500.
Just fill this out?
FEVER: It was the last
thing any of us wanted to do.
We had to stand in line
and bid like everyone else.
(AUCTIONEER CHANTING)
Sold at $3,500
to buyer number 11,
buyer number 11.
Next ladies and gentlemen,
now we're gonna sell
the '96 Ford pickup.
Do I have an opening bid?
Fifty-five hundred.
I've got $5,500, (AUTION CHANT)
$6,000 (AUCTION CHANT) $6,000.
(AUCTION CHANT)
$5,600.
$5,600...
(AUCTION CHANT)
$5,600 here I go.
$5,600 here going once.
(AUCTION CHANT)
$5,600 going twice.
$5,600 be my last call.
I have sold at $5,500.
FEVER: I paid too much.
But I wanted the truck
and I wasn't gonna haggle
over it.
Starting here today
on the James Dairy cattle guide.
These cattle will be
selling in groups of 15,
and we'll be selling
them by the head.
So much times the money,
ladies and gentlemen
These heifers that
we're about to start with
are two-year-old
breed heifers, guys.
Here we go.
Somebody give $1,250 for them.
At $1,250 here.
Thank you, Mr. Ferguson.
Now 75, at $1,275 anybody
gonna give $1,300 here.
(AUCTION CHANT)
$1,300 and a quarter?
At $1,300 and quarter...
(AUCTION CHANT)
And have here. At $1,355...
All right, then, I'll just have
my boys come by and
-pick up those cows tomorrow.
-MAN: They'll be here.
All right, thanks a lot.
(CHUCKLES)
So this is how you want it?
You gonna do something
stupid and end up in jail?
You're doing this for
her, that's admirable,
but it ain't gonna
change a damn thing.
If this is how it's gonna be,
come on.
(CAR HORN HONKING)
-Randel, Rooker.
-Arlene, go home.
What is that?
You bought the fucking TV?
Well, you got one hell of
a fucking deal on that!
Okay, Randel,
Randel, calm down.
That wasn't for her!
(YELLING)
Hey, I saw that.
Did you see that?
You know, now might not
seem like the right time,
but we could always use
a couple of extra hands
around the ranch.
Give me a call.
Arlene, it's okay.
It's okay, come on.
Let's get you back home.
-You okay?
-Yeah.
I'm sorry.
Randel, come on.
Hey, stop.
She bought the
damn TV for us, man.
You're an asshole.
Get in the car.
Come on.
(ENGINE STARTS)
You're applying for the
night management position?
Yes.
Do you have any
experience in management?
Mmm, this would be my first.
I see.
Would you be willing
to take a lower position?
(CHECKOUT BEEPS)
Paper or plastic, Miss?
Plastic, please.
-Could you double bag it?
-Yes, ma'am.
FEVER: Let's see, MG5A.
-And it's the best one?
-Uh, no.
These are the best ones,
I think.
There's not much difference.
Um, I don't think it's
something you can see.
Right.
Okay, okay.
The hours are strict,
the pay is lousy
and my boss is an asshole.
But none of us felt like
we could work in another dairy.
I'm convinced the universe
knows when you're vulnerable
and that's when it
likes to test you.
Oh shit!
In that moment,
I saw my life with Shelly.
Marriage, kids,
adultery, divorce.
It was ugly and all bad.
Shit!
This was self-preservation.
And self-preservation
isn't always pretty.
Have a good night.
Drive safe.
(CAR DOOR OPENS)
(CAR DOOR CLOSES)
You and that bug are
gonna have a lot in common.
Is that right?
And who's that?
Better set down those bags.
(GRUNTS)
FEVER: I think
Randel's done fighting.
But Jack isn't
gonna be the last.
He's made too many
enemies for that.
(CAR RUMBLING)
Shotgun finally soured
to the direction of the band.
He called it quits
halfway through the tour.
Colonel had to find
another front man.
Shotgun drove 32 hours straight
to a home that didn't exist.
Whether we wanted it or not,
that time in our lives was over.
Ms. Liz and the farm were gone.
Safely in the past where
only we could touch them.
It tastes like shit.
Yep.
(CAR APPROACHING)
-Hey, you're late.
-Hey, what up?
PROTOTYPE: Dad's got us
working 60-hour weeks.
♪ (PLAYING GUITAR) ♪
D-1: Thought you were
working part-time.
PROTOTYPE: Chancekipants,
that is part time.
What's up, dude?
I got yellow this time.
Do you want a beer?
I got you.
(RELAXED MOANING)
-(WATER SPLASHING)
-SHOTGUN: Feels good.
D-1: Gentlemen, cheers.