Shit!
Jeez!
God, darn foxes.
Muffin.
What are you doing out here?
Come inside, come on.
Jeez!
Brynn, you scared
the crap out of me!
What are you doing out here?
You guys let Muffin out,
and he went away.
I... You're supposed to be
asleep in the guest room.
Your mom would freak
if she knew you were
running around out here.
- What's this?
- It's a tie.
A tie? Your dad wouldn't
like you running around
with his nice tie.
- It wasn't Daddy's.
- Uh-huh.
Come on, let's get you in bed.
Charlotte.
Charlotte!
Charlotte Margaret Moon,
wake up!
You're gonna be late
for tennis with Birdie.
You promised Ms. Kelly you'd
help Birdie with her swing.
Now don't keep them waiting.
- Where are we supposed
to take it?
Aubrey? Aubrey,
I can hear you in there.
Why is the door locked?
Come on, let me in.
Go away, Charlotte!
Aubrey, I gotta get my bike,
unlock the door.
Go away!
Very funny, Aubrey,
but I've got a lot to carry
and I need my bike.
Open this door
or I'm telling Mom
that you wore her Chanel dress
to that party last weekend!
You wouldn't dare!
Oh, yes, I would.
Now, open this door
before I'm late for tennis!
Stop sucking Dalton's face
and open the door!
- Holy sh...
- Shhh. Shhh!
What happened
to Dad's golf cart?
I know, what have I done?
Oh, my gosh!
Dad is gonna be so pissed.
Nope. Panic. I'm feeling
panic right now, Dalton.
I'm... I'm gonna be grounded
forever after this, okay?
He's gonna take away my phone,
he's gonna take away my car.
My horse, you, my life!
Alright, Aubrey. Aubrey.
What happened?
Dalton and I went joyriding
in the golf course last night,
and I kind of lost control.
Ouch. There it is,
ripped off like a Band-Aid.
It is so jacked.
What exactly did you hit?
I think it was, like, a fairway
sign or maybe it was a fence.
It just happened so fast.
Aubrey. You are so dead.
She's so right too.
I mean, we can't take it
to the club for maintenance.
They're...
They're just gonna recognize it.
But don't worry, I'm sure
we can figure something out.
Right now I gotta go to work.
I gotta start loading
the beer cart. I'm sorry.
Wait, you're
just gonna leave me?
- Yeah, um, sorry. I gotta go.
- Dalton!
Charlotte.
Do not leave me like he did.
You have to help me with this!
Okay. Alright.
I'll give you some advice.
Pack your Gucci bags
and book a flight.
Dad's gonna freak
when he gets back from D.C.
Charlotte. I am serious, okay?
I don't know what
I'm supposed to do with this.
Please, help me!
Alright, alright.
We'll figure it out.
But after tennis.
You know, you are really pushing
the bounds of sisterhood here.
Alright, I got it.
Meet me at the gazebo at 1:00.
We don't want Mom
to hear our noise.
- Now, help me cover this.
- Okay.
Aubrey.
- Aubrey!
- Fix my makeup.
Good! Good.
Okay.
Alright. See you!
No, thanks.
I feel like I'm gonna puke.
I've got so much to lose here.
Okay, so, I've been
thinking about it
and I have two plans in mind.
Do you want to hear
plan A or plan B?
Plan A, I guess.
Right. So you're going to tell
your friends to come over here
with all the money they've got.
Uh, cash, credit cards,
Starbucks gift cards,
kidneys to sell, anything.
Okay, I think I have
about $60 in here.
Good. That's good, because
you're gonna need to sweet-talk
that creep Tucker up the street.
His dad owns Teed Up Golf Carts,
they'll probably be able
to get it picked up and fixed.
But you're gonna have to
pay him a little extra
to keep it a secret.
Wait, what?
You expect me to seduce
Tucker Gates into helping me?
- He'll never fall for it.
- Oh, yeah, he will.
He's had a crush on you
since, like, ever.
Now go on, put your big girl
panties on and run over there.
And be like, what? "Hi, Tucker.
I know I've always treated you
like you've had herpes,
but will you please
help me now?"
Uh, yeah. Do you want to live
to see your junior prom?
Listen, I'm telling you,
you have to go over there.
Be his damsel in distress,
you know?
"Tucker, sweet sweet Tucker.
Please, hold me.
You just have to be my hero."
No. No,
I won't be able to do it.
What's plan B?
Uh, plan B is kind
of like the truth,
but a little bit twisted.
-You know, like
how the devil does it.
-Ah!
Mom will be so proud
you're putting your Sunday
school lessons to good use.
But I'm desperate,
so let's hear it.
We're going to have to
get rid of the golf cart,
and pretend it was stolen.
Wow. That's actually
a really good idea
if we can pull it off that is.
Yeah. Yeah, it'll be simple.
We'll just have to
go when it's dark,
and push the golf cart
across the golf course
and sink it into the lake.
And tell Mom that you parked
in the driveway or something.
Alright. That sounds doable.
You're gonna have to
get Dalton to come to
the utility doors at midnight,
-and be dressed
for stealth mode.
-Okay.
Wait, but Brynn is
still staying with us.
-What are we gonna
do with her?
-She'll be fine. You know her.
She'll be completely tuned out
with a movie on.
Ah, thank you so much, sis.
Finn, you came.
Well, you sounded
pretty desperate. So here I am.
What's up with the Goth look?
You said to wear camouflage.
-Are we going to
a rave or something?
-Yeah, I wish.
That's who you sent out
to help us?
I'm pretty sure
I'm stronger than he is!
Aubrey, be nice.
I don't see Dalton here helping.
Yeah, you're right.
I should be glad that
you found a replacement.
Finn, thank you
so much for coming out.
I'm pretty sure you're
stronger than you look.
You know, one day
I'm going to fill out
and you will be drooling
at the sight of me.
Right. Okay, now. Come back here
and help me push this.
Alright. You think
Dalton could do this?
Probably, if he didn't ditch me.
Whatever.
It's fine. Alright.
Keep pushing.
Stop!
Charlotte. Charlotte.
Scarlet?
- What are you doing here?
- I know you said not to come,
but we figured you'd need
all the help you can get.
We can't just sit by
in your hour of need.
We will be your lookout.
Scarlet made me come.
- You told them too?
- I had to!
You know I can't keep
secrets from them.
Be happy I brought some muscle.
You mean me or him?
Him, silly. You're our oracle.
Yes!
♪ It's a long way to go
♪ Let go of
all your troubles... ♪
Oh. That's Mr. Allen.
Dalton says he comes here
every Friday and Saturday
to booze it up and go golfing.
Oh, jeez.
It's a bad shot.
♪ Tutti Frutti
Muffin!
Brynn?
Brynn, I told you last night,
you can't be running around
out here.
- Muffin ran away.
- Yup.
Alright, come on, I'll
take you back and tuck you in.
Alright, come on, you guys.
Oh, crap, dude.
-This thing keeps getting
heavier and heavier.
-Yeah, man. I'm spent.
- Babe, I'm here.
- Dalton, you made it!
Yeah, I'm sorry. I got a flight
from work, but I'm here now.
Charlotte, thank God
you brought in reinforcements.
- Yeah, I think your sister's been eating too much again.
- -Oh!
Rude, okay? I am
a beautiful curvy woman.
Too much for you, I'm sure.
And thanks
for defending my pride, babe!
Aubrey, where's
Scarlet and Roxi?
Oh, they're up by the tree.
Roxi said she'll whistle
in Russian when someone comes.
Whistle in Russian?
Really, Aubrey?
Oh, right. Duh!
Alright. Here's the plan.
We're gonna move it closer
to the water and...
Aubrey, you steer it straight
and jump off once it gets going.
I'll take this side.
Finn, you take the other,
-and we'll have
the two beefcakes in the back.
-Alright.
- Thank you.
- Got it?
- Got it. Got it.
- Yeah, got it.
Come on.
- Aubrey.
- Aubrey, are you okay?
Just breathe, breathe.
Holy crap! What was that?
It was a dead body, for sure.
I know what I saw, it wasn't
a guy floating for fun,
looking at the stars,
wearing a dress suit.
Dude, I can't believe it.
That's my first dead body. It...
He looked like a bloated fish,
it's way scarier
than in the video games.
-We have to call
the police.
-No!
- Yes.
- No.
I can't be a part of this.
- My dad would kill me.
- But we got to.
No, it's true. We don't know
how or why he got in there.
Please, I just want to forget
all about it.
Babe, I really don't think
that's a good idea right now.
-I agree with Dalton.
-Please, Dalton,
just take me home.
I'm with Aubrey
on this one, guys.
Aubrey, you're wet and shaking.
No, please, just take me home.
- I'm done.
- She's right.
We should all just go home.
There's not really much
we can do for that guy.
If we just leave it here,
tomorrow morning
one of the morning walkers,
they'll find him,
and they'll report him.
- Okay.
Sure.
Okay, we can do that.
You guys okay? You took off
so fast in the dark.
We couldn't see you.
What happened?
It's, uh, hard to believe,
but we're fine.
- We're all fine.
- Speak for yourself, Charlotte.
Take me home. I'm in shock.
It's crazy
what I'll do for a girl.
We got to get you home. Come on.
Please, just let her
ride with you.
Me, Finn and Charlotte,
we can run back.
Listen, I... I'll talk to
you two tomorrow morning
at the... at the park.
Okay, sounds good.
Oh, good morning, sunshine!
Hey, Mom. Hey, Brynn.
- What? No church today?
- No, we've got Brynn visiting.
I thought we'd just
take it easy this morning.
But, uh, don't we have
to take the food donations in?
Oh, we can take it tomorrow.
Besides, I think
Aubrey was up late last night.
She's probably gonna sleep
till noon, so, come on up,
I've got breakfast, though.
And ride my bikes?
- Not today, Brynn.
- Why not?
Yeah, why not?
Please, ride bikes with Brynn.
I don't think I'll have time.
Then make the time. You know
how much she adores you.
Alright. But I got to see
Scarlet and Roxi at the park
this morning at ten.
- Is lunchtime okay?
- Yeah. Great.
Oh, you know what? You should
ask Grant to join you.
I haven't seen him
around here in so long.
Mom, I don't even hang out
with Grant anymore.
Oh. Well, that's a shame,
you two were such good friends.
Mom? Uh... Mom.
Yeah, honey.
Dad's cart. I, uh,
I think it was stolen.
Oh, honey,
why would you say that?
-Have you checked
the utility room?
-Of course, it's not there.
Well, it's probably
up on the driveway.
You know, Aubrey's always
leaving it out up there.
Yeah, I... I checked there too.
I'm telling you, it's gone.
Oh, no.
Let's go, buddy.
Let's go, buddy. Let's go.
Oh. Hey.
I can't believe it.
That's so terrible.
I know our neighborhood
is filled with drama,
but that's just so unreal.
Oh, my poor Cal.
I mean, he was really,
really shaken up last night.
He didn't say anything to me
on his way home.
Were his parents
waiting up for him?
His mom was,
but his dad's out of town.
I'm sure he doesn't want them
to know anything.
I heard the siren this morning
and saw Chief Bud racing
into the neighborhood.
I just figured some old person
had a heart attack.
Poor Aubrey.
Yeah, she was... She was
pretty shaken up about it.
Wow. Your plan just got
a lot more complicated.
Yeah. This is serious.
Now your cart's
linked to a dead guy.
You're right!
I didn't even think about that.
Oh, what have we done?
So, your mom reported
the cart as stolen?
I assume she will.
After she talks to Aubrey.
Well, that's good.
We got to find out what Chief
Bud thinks about the scene.
Cal's dad says
Chief Bud is ROAD.
- ROAD?
Retired on active duty.
It's military slang.
But my cousin Tanner
still respects him a lot.
He says
he really knows his stuff
after 30 years of policing.
Yeah, I remember Tanner.
Damn. I bet
he looks good in uniform.
Y'all have got to calm down.
He's like a brother to me.
Alright. There's what?
Like, five people staffed there?
I bet it's like a fish bowl.
Scarlet, do you think you could
talk to Tanner this afternoon
and see what you can find out?
Yeah, um, I can make him
some of my lemon pound cake.
That'll get him talking.
Oh, also,
he told me the medical examiner
is a little sweet on him.
So that might help us
get some answers.
Great. I'll see you guys later.
- Bye.
I'm totally coming
with you to see Tanner.
- Morning, Helen.
- Oh, Chief Bud!
You're not at church with Bunny?
No, it's been a busy morning.
Choir is gonna have
to do without me today.
Dixie radioed me and tells me
your golf cart's gone missing.
Yes. And I can't
believe it. I mean,
I've never heard of anything
like that happening around here.
Well, it's rare,
but sometimes things do have
a way of wandering off.
When's the last time you saw it?
Oh, well, Jack's out of town.
Of course, I don't use it.
Um, the girls like
to use it though, actually,
Aubrey was the last one
to use it a couple days ago.
She said she left it
parked in the driveway.
Is that right? You were driving?
Yes.
And when you parked it,
you left the key in it?
Yeah. I mean,
we always leave the key in it.
I was gonna move it down to
the utility room in the morning.
And you didn't think about it
at all yesterday?
Um, no, actually
I forgot all about it.
-So you figure it's
been missing over 24 hours?
-Yeah.
- Charlotte noticed it was gone this morning.
- -Mm-hmm.
- What does it look like?
- Uh, well, it's white.
It has Carolina Panthers
stickers on it.
You know, Jackie
just loves his football.
Well, I think I already
found it this morning.
Oh, that's wonderful.
You know, I just figured
some kids took a joyriding.
- Probably hadn't gone far.
- No, no, it didn't.
But it looks like
it might have been involved
in a bit of an incident.
So, I have to hold on to it
for a few days.
Oh, it's nothing serious,
I hope.
Chief Bud, you there?
- Yes, Dixie. I'm here.
Bunny called. She said you left
your cell phone at home again.
She wants you to pick up
some vanilla wafers
with a banana pudding
on your way home.
Alrighty, darling. Will do.
I'm not sure what to make of
what happened to your cart
right now.
But when Jack gets back,
just have him give me a call.
That's all for now.
You all have a nice day.
Alright, Chief Bud. Thank you!
Mom? You okay?
Oh, yeah.
I guess we'll just have to start
locking things up around here.
- Hey, Tanner.
- Hey, baby girl, how are you?
I'm good. How's your mama?
Oh, you know her. Stirring
the pot around town as usual.
Do you remember my friend Roxi?
Yes, ma'am.
How are you doing, Miss Roxie?
Hotter than ever. Ooh!
Well, if you mean
the weather, it is, um, humid.
So what'd you bring me?
You know I'm a slave
to your baking talent.
Your favorite, lemon pound cake.
Oh, yes.
Hello, Officer Hart.
Looks like you have
some good company today.
Good afternoon, ma'am.
- You're working on a Sunday?
- Oh, no, not really.
I just remembered something
that I needed to talk
to Chief Bud about.
Well, I'm sorry,
he's not here right now. Uh...
- Can I help you?
- Oh, gosh, no. No, thank you.
I'm Scarlet, Tanner's cousin.
This is my friend Roxi.
Oh! Hello! Dr. Sarah Owens.
The county's
new medical examiner.
So nice to meet both of you.
Would you like to have some
lemonade and cake with us?
Oh, gosh, I couldn't.
But, uh... but thank you so much.
You just got some, uh...
some feather. Right here.
Oh! Oh my. How embarrassing.
Thank you. Um...
I'll be back... tomorrow.
- Have a good day, Doctor Owens.
- Bye.
So... you mentioned
I had to earn your cake.
What is it you want exactly?
Nothing big.
Just a little information
-on a recent death
in my neighborhood.
-Uh-huh.
You mean
the demise of Harley Trudeau.
Well, it is the talk
of the town in the station.
Well then, I'm sure
it's not hard to hear
a few tidbits in that
tiny office you all share?
True.
So, what's on your mind?
Well, we're wondering
what killed him.
Is it natural or otherwise?
Yeah, so weird him dying out
on the golf course
in the middle of the night.
What morbidly curious minds
you do have, little ladies.
I like it,
but it's gonna cost you.
This pound cake, a...
peach cobbler next week and
a pecan pie the week after that.
And I want a free
cup of coffee every day.
Miss Roxie is working
from that Java joint
until the end of that period.
Mm. Agreed?
Drive a hard bargain,
Officer Hart.
Agreed.
Yay! Call me later
with the details.
You've been saying that medical
examiner lady is sweet on you,
it shouldn't be hard.
Alright now. Never you mind.
Oh, I got my ways.
Y'all stay out of trouble now.
Alright?
Oh, we will.
- Bye.
Bye.
Hey, what you got?
Oh, no. Hands off. Hands off.
You're like a vacuum, Em.
Don't you dare, don't you dare.
Come on, share.
Why do you always get
the goodies and the girls?
- Poor Em gets nothing!
Don't you feel sad for me?
Yeah. Yeah, as a matter of fact,
I do feel sorry for you
all the time, because you're
nothing but a pathetic beggar.
And don't you be eyeballing
those girls, alright?
-That's my cousin
and her friend.
-Oh, I know that.
Well, they're just kids.
Jeez, what kind of person
do you think I am?
I'm not talking
about them either.
I'm talking about
proper young ladies
that come around here.
You're always catching
their eyes, and I'm just like
grandma's wallpaper,
just kind of hanging there.
Alright. Alright.
You can have a piece of cake.
Just quit whining.
You're ruining my appetite.
Would you open the door?
Where's Cal?
He doesn't want
to join our roundtable?
No. He's sticking
close to home these days.
His mom was pretty upset
he was out so late.
I think he's grounded.
He couldn't talk when I called.
Oh, no boyf' for a few days?
How will you survive?
Don't tease me, Roxi.
He had a traumatic experience
and I wasn't there
to hug him through it.
You can give me a hug
if you want. I'm short of hugs.
Actually, I'm pretty sure
my hug jar is empty.
Finn, you desire
actual human contact?
Ouch!
Hilarious, Roxi.
Oh, get this.
Dish is, the victim,
is Harley Trudeau.
The notorious lawyer
on fourth floor?
It didn't look like him
in the pond.
That's because his face
is all frozen like...
Oh, come on.
His face wasn't that bad.
Okay. That is not funny.
That was the most
horrific experience
I've ever had in my life, okay?
And I saw the Sawmovies.
It's different when it's real.
Come on. Can we please just
remember that Aubrey, you...
correction, "we" are
in big, big trouble here.
-What else did you find out?
-Tanner said the victim is
in his early sixties,
obese and known to be
a heavy smoker and drinker.
Also, his body is believed
to have wounds from both
strangulation and hit and run.
Yeah.
So, the golf cart,
your golf cart is what Chief Bud
thinks he was hit with.
Oh, sugar, honey, ice tea.
This is what I get for lying!
Chief Bud is probably wondering
if the driver was Aubrey
or a thief, right?
He doesn't know for sure,
or else Aubrey would
already be arrested.
Oh, gracious.
I'm going to the big house.
No, no, no, no, no, come on.
I'm sure that's not the case.
I mean, Chief Bud knows
our family from church,
so that probably helps.
And it'll take him a few days
to come to his final decision.
So... all we need to do is
figure out who killed
Harley Trudeau
before Chief Bud can
jump to the wrong conclusion.
No, we have to tell the truth.
Giving my college money
to your dad to fix the cart
is better than going
to prison for murder
and then getting f'ed there.
You know what? I know
when it's time to get out,
and that time is now.
But I'm sorry, Char, but fight
or flight, I gotta fly. Later.
Finn, come on,
we can do this. Guys?
It's not over
till the fat lady sings.
Or until one of us
gets arrested, but...
three days is all I'm asking.
Chief Bud is gonna need
some time to conduct
his investigation, right?
Who's with me?
- I am.
- We are.
- Okay. We're in.
So, where do we start?
-You sure this is
the Trudeau House.
-Yep.
I don't see any other cars,
except for Harley's Jag,
I don't see their cart either.
Maybe she's just out to dinner.
Yeah. We should just probably
wait it out for a bit.
I agree.
Do I hear someone coming?
No, that's probably fine.
Well, that... I guess
that could be...
Oh, well, they're
coming this way, get down.
You think he saw us?
No, I don't think so. That's...
That's Larson, her son,
but I mean,
he doesn't live at home anymore.
What is he doing here?
I don't know.
- Let's go check it out.
- Okay.
- Can you see him?
- Oh, my gosh. There he is.
I don't think he saw us yet.
Okay. He's right there.
He's right there.
Shoot! Someone's coming.
Come on, come on,
let's go. Come on.
Get down, get down.
Shh. I don't want my son to see.
I'll be right back, sweetheart.
Be right back.
- Where is it?
- Where's what?
Where's Dad's will?
I know you know where it is.
Who is that guy?
That's Foster, he's one
of the bartenders at the club.
- What is he doing here?
- I don't know.
- You know what, you're
worthless. Just forget it!
- Sweetheart.
Oh, yeah. Just go to
your little, happy place, your...
Whatever it is
you do these days.
Dad's always been
an asshole to me.
The least you can do
is go find that will.
When I get home...
they'll be on my side.
Come here, sugar.
It's time to play.
Oh, my goodness.
Did I see what
I thought I just saw?
I think so.
Mrs. Trudeau
doesn't seem too bereaved.
Alright. Let's go.
Alright. Let me see
what's going on here.
- Can you see them?
- Not yet.
Oh, there's Foster.
Alright. What is he up to?
- What's he doing?
- Oh.
It looks like, um,
he's making them some drinks.
Alright.
Where's Mrs. Trudeau?
Oh, there she is!
Looks like she's
in some sort of robe.
Okay.
Alright.
Oh, looks like some
swaying and canoodling.
- Canoodling?
- You know, like fun cuddling.
Just let me see.
Oh.
"Hello, bartender.
It's ever so hot.
I'm burning up
just looking at you."
"Oh, why yes, Mrs. Trudeau?
I've got exactly
what you're thirsty for."
"Oh, perfect.
But please call me Winona."
Stop!
Alright.
Oh. Oh, jeez.
She's really going for it.
Oh, I don't think
I can watch this.
I feel like
an unfortunate fly on the wall.
- Let me see.
- No. No!
-Dalton!
-I just don't want you
to see that.
Just let me see.
Oh.
Yeah. Okay.
Um, let's just get out of here,
and you can check up on her
in the morning. Alright.
Hey. Did I wake you?
No. What are you
doing here, Grant?
I don't think you've thrown
rocks at my window
since we were, like, ten.
I just want to talk.
Cal said you are in trouble
but he won't say what.
We're fine.
We're fixing it.
You tell Cal to shut up!
Come on. Why don't you trust me?
I mean, we've been friends
since the fourth grade,
and ever since we hit, like,
puberty, you just
stopped talking to me.
Come on, Charlotte.
What's going on?
No, Grant. I don't need you.
Now go home!
Charlotte! Charlotte!
Charlotte Margaret Moon!
Grant, only my mother
calls me by my full name.
Now go home.
- But...
- Go home.
- Did you take your medicine?
- Yes.
Alright, good. Uh, bathroom.
Did you use the bathroom?
- Yeah.
- Alright.
Do you need some help?
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I got it.
Alright. That's good.
Oh, oh.
- Alright. Let's, uh,
let's sit here for a second.
Brynn.
- Do you have your drink?
- Yes.
Alright, good.
I'm, uh, I'm gonna go
look at something real quick.
- You... find some bugs.
- Okay.
Charlotte, what are you doing?
I'm, uh, looking for bugs.
Looks like there's none here.
Come on, Brynn. Let's, uh,
let's go look someplace else.
Here, you can use
your binoculars
and look for some birds.
- Okay.
- Alright.
Just, uh, stay here
and I'll be right back.
You are so silly.
Brynn, stay hidden.
-You don't want
to scare the bugs.
-What?
Brynn, uh, hand me your spade.
The... the tiny shovel
in your hand.
Give it to me.
Come on.
Careful, careful.
Okay.
Alright, Brynn. It's time to go.
Mm.
Well, hello there.
Usually it's older men
on the golf course
staring in my windows.
But this is a nice surprise.
Have you come here
to comfort me?
I'm flattered.
Usually I like a younger man's
attention, but, uh...
I think you might be
a little bit too young for me.
Now, shoot before
I call your parents
and tell them
what their precious little,
baby boy has been up to.
Don't tell me
there's such a thing.
You mean the kind of like...
Hi, Mr. and Mrs. Carver.
Good morning,
Judge Talbott, Mrs. Talbott.
Ms. Wyatt, I love your hat.
Is there anyone here
you don't know?
Very few. But if your family
lived here as long as mine,
you'd know everyone too,
or at least their business.
Alright, well,
I'll be right back.
I'm going to go
to the bathroom. Okay?
- Hey, Sullivan. Hey, Birdie.
- Hi, Scarlet.
I saw your boyfriend
running across the golf course
the other night.
Shh! Don't tell on Cal.
Morning, Mrs. Kelly.
- Hello, Scarlet. How are you?
- I'm good.
Not sure I'm too hungry though.
Especially after
hearing about Mr. Trudeau.
Oh, I know.
Isn't that just so awful?
Yes. It's hard to believe.
I just feel bad
for Mrs. Trudeau and Larson.
Sullivan, how about you take
Birdie to get some more waffles?
Okay, Mom. Come on, Birdie.
Help me get lots of
whipped cream this time.
-Sadly, I don't think
they'll be missing him much.
-Really?
I'm not saying
Winona did him in.
I think Harley is worth
more to her alive than dead.
But they did
get into it pretty good
at the club's cocktail party
the other evening.
Oh, that party.
It was such a pretty sight.
There were flowers
and candles and garden lights
around the tables.
I took lots of pictures
and I had a...
You were... you were
saying about the Trudeaus?
Oh, yes. So... so, toward the end
of the night, um, about ten,
they took off on their golf
cart, just ranting and raving.
From what I hear,
their son Larson is a bit
of a spender and a gambler.
He and his daddy used
to argue quite a bit about it.
Wouldn't surprise me
if Larson did him in.
He's got a temper on him.
Kind of like his daddy.
Hey. I'm back.
I just heard Mrs. Kelly say
she took lots of pictures
of the club cocktail party.
Really?
Mm.
Be right back.
Can you check on...
Can you check on my jacket?
Well, I for one,
won't be missing that man's
big mouth around the club.
Ranger, my ass.
I don't know, Colonel.
Mr. Trudeau had some
pretty good war stories.
I'm telling you,
there's no way he served.
I served for 30 years. 30 years!
Trust me, he's an impostor.
His tales' as tall as my boat.
I expect you're right, Colonel.
Now, Carlos,
one of the groundskeepers,
says the same thing.
You know he served?
Yes, I do.
Now that's a good soldier.
There's nothing burns me up more
than a prideful bastard
who steals somebody's respect
and glory who rightfully served.
Carlos said he often had
run ins with Mr. Trudeau,
especially at night
on the golf course.
You catch him out there
drinking, pissing,
tosses empties on the greens.
- You believe that?
- Yeah, I believe it.
Why Winona ever hooked up
with a guy like that?
I'd never know.
She deserves better.
I agree, Colonel. I agree.
Let me check
on that breakfast for you.
You are not gonna believe
what I just heard.
Well, you're not gonna
believe what I just did.
I AirDropped her pictures
from the club cocktail party
to my phone.
You are so awesome.
I know. Let's get out of here.
We gotta go visit
my mom at the bank.
Hey, Gina. Going for me?
- No.
- Ouch.
Hey, Char.
Well, hello, lovely lady.
- You come here often?
- Hello, Cal.
Hi, Finn, I see you
both recovered.
Oh, no. The emotional
scars still there.
Well, I'm glad
to hear you're a survivor.
Yeah. And Mom's got me
on a short leash now.
- Thank you very much.
- Yeah.
But I really do
appreciate the sacrifice.
You should, because now he's
grounded from his girlfriend
- and other unsuitable influences...
- Charlotte.
Uh-huh. Cal,
you have a big mouth.
Yeah, I know.
Anyways, enough chatter.
You want to play some
touch football with us?
No, thanks. I don't want
to touch you at all, you freak.
Anchors aweigh!
Cannonball!
Hey! You know what?
Cal, you're a real gentleman.
Scarlet will be so pleased you
treat her best friend like this.
I don't know why she dates you!
Hey, kid,
you're in my personal space.
Yeah.
- Hey.
- Oh. I don't like.
Hey, don't mind her.
Getting your space is
her way of being friendly.
She's autistic.
Uh-huh.
Hey, Larson.
So, can I get you anything?
- I got soda, beer...
- No, thanks.
Oh, you can get me something.
Or am I too poor?
Hello.
I said not to call.
I will get it.
Dude, I will get it.
Stop calling me!
Come on, Jill, let's go.
Babe, we just got here.
- Jill, now, come on, let's go.
- Okay. Just give me one second.
I hate when you're so grouchy.
She's fine.
She's tough.
I just took my eyes off her
for a second.
Come on, Brynn.
-Ow!
-It can happen fast.
That's why I'm here.
- Okay.
- Hey. Hey, Brynn.
Uh, you swallowed any water?
- What?
- You swallowed any water?
- No.
- Um...
- What's your name?
- Brynn.
How many fingers
am I holding up, Brynn?
- Three.
- High five.
Come on, Brynn. I think that's
enough swimming for today.
Hey. When you see Dalton
with your sister,
tell him to call me.
I want to go later for pizza.
That is if you can pull him
somewhere away from
his girlfriend.
Yeah. Okay.
Later, loser!
- Come on, Brynn.
- Okay.
Wow. Brynn and you were
busy little detectives, huh?
I admit it was pretty cool.
Uh, this is everyone we have
in our suspect list so far.
Hey, guys.
Did you guys
solve the murder yet?
Glad you could join us, Cal.
I'm on parole.
So, it's good to be here.
Alright. So based on what
I found in the golf course,
it seems that Harley
was killed in the sand trap
and had his body dragged
into the cove.
Yeah, I think you're right.
But who on your list
could have done that?
- Not Winona.
- But Winona has a motive.
We saw her come home
all liquored up and happy
with a bartender from the club.
Yeah, Foster Davis.
- Foster is a friend of Tanner's.
- Mm.
So, they're having an affair?
Foster is known to be a favorite
with the club cougars.
I think I might be a favorite
- Winona caught me outside her house this morning.
- -What?
Yeah, I thought she was
gonna pull Mrs. Robinson on me.
- Ew!
- Yeah, but she saw me packing
this. It was alright.
That earring that Charlotte
found in the sand trap
could be hers.
Mrs. Kelly doesn't think
Winona would kill Harley.
He was worth more
to her alive than dead.
And it definitely wasn't Foster.
I mean, he might
entertain wealthy women,
but he definitely
would not kill for them.
Well, unless they have alibis,
they're staying on the list.
Ms. Kelly does see
their son Larson doing it.
He's known for his temper
and blowing off his money.
-That earring could
be his fiancée's.
-Yeah.
And the other day at the pool,
I heard him take a phone call.
He seemed really mad about it.
Something about money.
-The Colonel was
mad at brunch today.
-Yeah.
I guess Harley boasted
at the club that he was
a part of the Army Rangers.
The Colonel didn't believe it,
called Harley a liar.
Veterans could take
a serious offense to fakes.
It's called "stolen valor."
It can even get violent.
Well, it sounds like
the Colonel is going to
be added to our list too.
Wait. Well, what about
the fights between Harley
- and the greenskeeper?
- Carlos?
Yeah, he lives in a trailer
behind the ninth hole.
He would have been
on the greens that night
because he patrols it.
I don't see him
killing some rich asshole
just because
he let him get to him.
No. Put him on the list.
There are times
where I'm sneaking across
the golf course at night
to Scarlet's house
and he chases me.
You know, Ms. Kelly said
the Trudeaus were
at the club cocktail party
the night Harley died.
She said they got in a fight
and left together on their
golf cart about ten.
- Oh, I got their party pics.
- Awesome.
Yeah. It looks like
all our suspects were there.
Yeah. And all of them drive
their own carts to the parties.
Yeah, or in Foster's case,
have access to carts.
Scarlet and I went
to my mom's office at the bank.
I'd say Harley doesn't look
like he's hurting for money.
My dad said Harley
and his business partner
had a pretty good relationship.
Alright, we'll take
them off the list for now.
So that leaves us
with Winona, Larson and Jill,
Foster, The Colonel and Carlos.
Well, we do know what time
Harley and Winona
left the party.
Yeah. So, Scarlet,
go back to Ms. Kelly's
and ask her what time all
the other guests left the party.
- Maybe she'll know.
- Oh, she'll know.
When she gets a babysitter, she
stays out as late as she can.
So, we just have to find out
what each suspect was doing
from the time that the Trudeaus
left the party at ten,
and when we found
Harley's body at 12:30.
-Uh, Roxi, do you want
to stake out Carlos with me?
-Sure.
Don't you have a friend
in a lab or something?
Oh, my cousin, Stacy.
She works at a gene lab.
Cool. Do you think
she can run a test on this
and see if it's
a match to Harley?
Sure. She's cool.
And, uh, can you two
follow up on Winona?
Oh, I can't.
I gotta go to the barn
tomorrow and then to work.
Well, I guess
it's just you, Dalton.
- You take Winona.
- Take her where?
Cinderella's ball.
Hello? Are you listening?
Oh, yeah, sorry.
I'm... I'm just hungry.
I'm actually gonna
go meet Vonne for pizza,
- so I'll see y'all later.
- Wait, Dalton.
I thought we were gonna
get dinner together.
Oh, no, it's bro time,
and I gotta talk to him
about the Jet Ski.
Can we have snacks at our next
meeting of the minds please?
Hello? Focus!
Alright, I'm... I'll
take Larson and the fiancée.
Jill works at the wine store
next to the coffee shop.
They come in
after she's done, around two.
Great. Um, I can go over there
and see if they drop any clues.
Scarlet, um, you talk to Tanner,
see if he can, I don't know,
"bro talk" Foster into
telling him what's up
with him and Winona.
Okay, I can talk
to the Colonel too.
- He's friends with my dad.
- Great.
Excellent, we're done.
Okay. Dance off time,
us two versus you two. You in?
You two are on. Come on, Char.
Ew. Could you pick
a cleaner hiding spot?
No. We have to hide!
- And, you know,
blend with nature.
Well, I don't want
to be one with nature.
You know nature and I
don't mix very well.
I know, but you're also
one of my very best friends
who'll do anything
to support me.
This is true.
Oh. This maintenance cart
doesn't seem to have
any damage to it.
It is so romantic to see a guy
speaking softly in Spanish.
Here comes Carlos.
I can't tell
what he's saying
but he seems really upset.
"I'm telling you, man,
stuff keeps going
missing around here."
"I get up the next morning,
and more parts are gone."
"I'll never get this Chevy
running again at this rate."
"You got to see my golf cart."
Bro...
- "Bro, I'm totally
messed it up."
"I hit him so hard.
There was blood everywhere."
Holy sugar, Roxi!
- Roxi.
- Shh!
Roxi!
- Hey!
- We gotta go.
Hey, who's there?
- Hey, Gigi.
- Later, Grant.
I know what
you're up to, Charlotte.
If you think
Cal didn't tell me,
you're crazier than you look.
Carlos made it passed the dog.
- Thank God.
- Good.
- Oh! It's your crush.
- Shh!
Hey, Char.
What are you two doing?
Running from the boogeyman?
Good one!
What are you doing around here?
I was just over at Dalton's.
He and I are going in
on a Jet Ski.
Cool. Those are fun.
You want a ride?
Drop you off at Char's house.
Always.
Girls. Girls!
- Yeah, Mom?
- Oh, it's almost ten.
I've got to go
show a couple homes,
but I'll be back by lunch.
- Okay, Mom.
- Oh, Charlotte.
While I was at the ship's store,
I signed you up
for sailing lessons.
I mean, they were pretty full,
but they had this
last minute cancellation,
- so I was able to get you in.
- Mom.
What did I tell you
about signing me up for things?
Oh. Come on, Charlotte.
You know
how much I love sailing,
and just like Jane Aubrey,
I want you to learn.
Alright, but am I going
to be in a group lesson
with a bunch of little kids?
Mm. No worries. I signed
you up for private lessons.
Okay. Is, uh, is Jay coming
home for the weekend?
I haven't seen him all summer.
Oh, no, honey,
he's gonna be taking
classes all summer long.
I know you miss him.
Uh, look, I gotta go, okay?
- I love you!
- Bye. I love you too.
So glad Mama is gone.
I don't want to face her until
after this craziness is over.
Well, that'll be hard.
Mom wants us to go to
the country club's next party.
Oh, yeah. Dalton promised
we'd go together.
Lately I think he's been
ditching me a lot,
but hope it will be fun.
No... it won't.
Ah, cheer up, sis!
Oh, um, Carlos chased me
and Roxi last night.
- He's looking very suspicious.
- He chased you?
Scarlet texted the list
of the times our suspects
left the party.
According to Ms. Kelly,
the Trudeaus left about ten.
The Colonel at 10:30, and Larson
and his fiancée around 10:45.
Mrs. Kelly stayed
till the party ended at 11.
And as she was walking home,
she saw Foster
driving out of the neighborhood
about 11:15.
So, does that mean
Foster is off the suspect list?
No, because
he just could come back.
Hopefully Tanner has
something to tell us today.
Well, tell me about Carlos.
But you have to hurry it up,
I got to get to the barn soon.
Well, it was both terrifying
and fun all at the same time.
-But I'll tell you everything
once everyone's here tonight.
-Okay.
Hey. Get a load of this.
"Chief Graham still
investigating the death
of prominent local lawyer
Harley Trudeau.
Mr. Trudeau's body
was found in a cove
along The Queen's Crown Golf
Course early Sunday morning.
Mr. Trudeau is believed
to have passed sometime between
11 p.m. and 1:00 a.m. Saturday.
Few details have been released
regarding the suspicious death,
but Mr. Trudeau appears
to have been the victim
of a hit and run
by a small vehicle.
Sources also report
a resident of the exclusive
neighborhood came forward
saying he was out late
walking the court
sometime around midnight
on the night in question
when he saw a unicorn
chasing a white fox."
- Brynn and Muffin.
"This is a curious case indeed.
The investigation is ongoing."
Well... no news is good news.
They haven't said
anything about you... yet.
- Hey there.
- Hey. This cart's kinda flat.
I keep filling it up
but it just gets slow again.
Maybe you should
go get cart two.
It's fine.
I'll fill it when I come back.
No, um, you should
probably go get cart two.
Are you alright?
I'm not sure.
It's just really hot.
Are you gonna be okay to work?
So kind of you to worry.
Well, now I'm afraid
to let you go.
Then don't.
Admit it, you want me.
Dalton, make no mistake.
I'm a woman
and I'm nothing like that little
teenybopper girlfriend of yours.
So the question is...
is the man in you
ready for me?
I think I'd like to find out.
And the little princess,
you'd dump her for me, right?
Maybe.
So, why did you do this job
when I hear you're rich?
My parents have money, not me.
And I'd say we're well-off.
Plus, rich is relative.
Well, relative to me,
you're rich.
Well, I'm not a trust fund kid.
I have to make my own way
like my dad did.
Oh. How boring.
And here I was
briefly interested in you.
Hey, buddy.
Oh. Uh, hey, what's the word?
The word... spider.
Just don't get caught up
in her web.
Hey, Foster. Nice to see you.
Hey, long time, man.
What you been up to?
I hope you ain't been
working all the time.
I've been squeezing in
time for fun, you know me.
Yeah. Yeah, I do.
Ever since you dated
my sister in high school.
Yeah.
Ouch. Don't remind me.
You know, high school is
further back for me than you.
Well, uh, speaking matters
of the heart and, uh...
other body parts...
heard you and Ms. Trudeau
are an item.
Uh, where'd you hear that?
The winds of gossip.
Isn't that true?
Yeah. Yeah, that's true.
Been going on for, uh,
a few months now.
I mean, it's nothing
serious, but, uh,
don't tell anyone. Alright?
Dude.
What's up with that?
She's got, like, what,
25 years on you.
What can I say?
I mean,
she was offering and really,
you know, she's a blast.
Okay.
And what about her, uh,
husband's suspicious death?
That don't worry you now?
Nah, she's a genuine sweetie.
I've known some sly women.
She's not one of them.
It's weird though... her husband
winding up in the lake
while she's waiting
for me in my place.
You sure about that?
Yeah, man. I mean...
Winona and Harley
left the club cocktail party,
uh, about ten or so.
You know,
same time I sent Gina home.
By 10:25, she was sending me
pics from my condo.
Check these out.
You see the time stamp?
You know, they estimate Harley's
time of death after 11. So...
Besides, Chief Bud
found Harley's golf cart
back at the club.
Not a scratch on it.
True.
So you just went
right home after work?
Yeah, briefly.
You're
asking all this officially
or unofficially?
Unofficially. Of course.
Of course.
Well, I'll tell you the same
thing I told Chief Bud. Yeah.
Got home 11:20,
changed, then, uh...
Winona and I went out
to the Chill Martini.
Got there about 20 to midnight.
When did you leave?
Stayed till closing at two.
You know, you ask a lot of these
unofficial questions, man.
No worries, man.
I... just out of curiosity.
-Yeah.
-Chief Bud's working
the case, not me.
Ah. Yeah. Alright.
I doubt that, Tanner.
I mean, you're trying to
beat Chief Bud to the punch
on this?
I admit I'd like him to trust me
a little more, but, uh...
No, that's not it.
This is so unusual.
Harley dying out there
on the golf course like that.
Yeah. Well,
I'm not surprised. I mean...
Don't let these luxury homes
and manicured lawns fool you.
I see and hear plenty.
Sure you do, my friend.
Sure you do.
Why do I keep letting you
talk me into this stuff?
Because I didn't want to go
alone, and you're my friend.
You torture me, Charlotte.
I felt a lot braver last night
when we were playing
Call of Duty,
but I'm just tired.
Here. Have my latte.
This is my payment
for being your bodyguard?
- Half a latte?
- Do you want my cookie?
Yes.
So, what are we supposed to do?
Just talk and act like
we don't notice them.
- But what do we talk about?
- Same thing we always do.
You know, like video games,
skateboarding,
anime stuff... Here they come.
You sure you'll be ready?
I mean...
- Maybe we just need to postpone.
- I'm fine, Jill.
We're not postponing.
My dad and I...
weren't close anymore.
Okay, if you say so.
Oh, shoot. I think they messed
up my drink order again.
You did order me
a skinny soy ginger latte
with organic whip, right?
- Of course.
- Mm.
It tastes funny for some reason.
Oh, my gosh.
I just remembered, I had
the best idea for our wedding.
- Okay...
- Let's decorate your go-kart
to be the escape vehicle
for our reception!
Sorry, hun, I got rid of it.
-What? Why? We had
so much fun on that car.
-I'm sorry, babe.
I had to sell it.
I don't understand, why?
Just trust me, Jill.
I had to get rid of it.
Okay. Jeez, it's like one of
those little trust exercises.
But after our marriage,
no more secrets, okay, babe?
- Just kiss me, beautiful.
- Ah. Sorry, babe, can't yet.
- I'm serious about us taking
a break until after our big day.
Jill, we lived together
for two years now. Come on.
I know, but if we take
a little break it will be
just that much more special.
- You know, our first time
as husband and wife.
Come on now, babe. No pouting.
Hey. Good news.
I've got enough money to pay for
both trips to Paris and Venice.
- Mm.
- And in every country we'll be
doing it along the way.
Please, Larson.
Okay, your cart was awesome,
-but it's not enough
to fund our honeymoon, babe.
-No, of course not.
Don't worry.
I've taken care of it.
We're gonna have
plenty of money soon.
I have... It's another
trust exercise. Okay?
Okay.
- Happy?
- Super!
Let's take a walk down
to the bridal shop,
and you show me what outrageous
dresses you picked out
- to torture
those bridesmaids with.
- Yes!
Oh, now.
What are we going to wear
to the club's
cocktail party tomorrow night?
Oh, wait, I know. I'll wear
floral, you wear gingham.
-We'll look as fresh
as a summer picnic!
-Come on, Jill!
Bill!
This looks ridiculous!
Now you know you can afford
to have the name properly
painted on there.
I will. I will.
Your knee still aching?
Bill, I have told you a hundred
times ago, get that looked at.
Now, why haven't you gone yet?
Marilyn. I've been busy.
I forget it hurts
until it hurts. You know me.
Yes, I do know you.
So if you need me to call
and make an appointment for you,
I will.
You just got to tell me when.
Marilyn, thanks,
but I don't need you
to make no appointment for me.
I do it when I do it.
You just fussing
because you want me
to finish your to-do list.
- My to-do list?
- Yes.
Our to-do list.
Now, we may be divorced, Bill,
but you promised me
you'd help me take care
of our family home.
So I'm gonna hold you to that.
And besides, Jill's wedding
will be here before you know it.
And I know you don't want
to let your baby girl down.
I know that.
So, get that knee looked at,
because you don't do
anybody any good
sitting around
on your bum all day.
Yes, ma'am.
- Hi, Ms. Connor.
- Hi, Scarlet.
Have a good day.
Hello, Colonel.
Hey, Miss Lady, what you up to?
Looking for someone to share
my coconut cupcakes with.
I made them for Daddy, but
he had to fly off to New York.
If that's an offer,
I'd love one.
Think your mom would want one?
Oh, you know her,
she's on a diet.
I should be on
one myself, but...
you only live once and I
don't want to have any regrets.
Mm.
-Miss, you are
one of the best bakers I know.
-Thank you.
It's like it's your super power.
So, Colonel, I noticed
your golf cart isn't
in its usual parking space.
Well, uh, I had...
I had an incident and, uh...
- sent her off for repairs.
- Oh, my!
Um, what happened?
Uh, well, it was late
and dark and I was coming
back from the club,
and, you know, I...
I hit something.
Oh, my. I sure hope
it wasn't a person.
Oh, God. No, it was,
gracious, no, it was...
It was like, uh, it was like a,
you know, it was like a post,
you know, in the parking lot.
- You know?
- Oh.
Oh, oh, yeah, yeah. And anyhow,
take this out, I got to...
I gotta go get dressed
for dinner and, uh...
- No, no, no.
I understand that, but hey.
Yeah, it's time for you to go,
young lady, and, uh...
Yeah. Yeah. And I... I'll be
seeing you and your parents
tomorrow night at the club.
Hey, you have... Yeah.
- Yeah. You have a good night.
- Okay. Bye. Thank you.
Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Bye.
Okay.
Oh, hey, Char. You've finally
come to learn from the master.
Uh, you're
my sailing instructor?
I know, right? Lucky.
Um, alright. So I am
going to take us for a sail.
Uh, I'll just teach you parts
of the boat, sailing terms
while we're out on the water.
Is that cool?
- Okay.
- Alright.
First things first.
Life jacket on.
Safety rule numero uno. Got it?
Alright.
There is not much wind
in here right now.
So, I hope you like the paddle.
You need... you need help?
- You got it?
- Yeah, I got it.
They just crossed...
No, like this one...
This one goes here.
One there. Two...
Sweet. Alright. How much
strength you got in these arms?
-Uh...
-It'll do. Alright.
You want to help me pushing it?
Alright, let's go.
Okay then, we're straight.
Alright. So, the front
is called the bow,
back is called the stern.
Left side is port,
right side is starboard. Got it?
- I guess.
- Don't worry.
The more you sail,
easier it's going to get.
-Hey, you know why
this is called the boom?
-No.
-Why?
-So, when we cross wind,
if you don't duck,
that's the sound is gonna make
when it hits you in the face.
Hey, Scarlet, I want you
to invite another person
to Charlotte's dinner party
tomorrow night.
- Okay. Who?
- Grant.
- Why?
- Well...
I think it'd be
really nice if she sees him.
Hey, Dalton, where are you?
Um, I'm helping my dad
rebuild the deck.
He's probably not
going to let me go right now.
Oh, that sucks.
And I've just been
working a lot.
- We've got to get this done.
- Oh, yeah.
Okay, I understand.
Scarlet and I were just
talking about Char's
dinner party tomorrow night.
You are coming, right?
I'll be there. I promise.
Okay. Bye.
Okay. So, Roxi
can't come tonight.
But we have Finn here with us.
- New cut and all.
- Please, hold your applause.
Dalton can't make it tonight.
We already know
who killed Harley.
It was totally Carlos.
Char even said that the cart
was all banged up
and had blood all over it.
Case closed.
Maybe. But speaking of blood,
Roxi's cousin
was able to test
the blood from the sand trap.
Turns out it was
a match to Harley.
- So we do know where he died.
- Then we're done.
We know who and we know where.
We got to call Chief Bud.
I don't know just yet.
Carlos seems like
a pretty smart guy.
If he were to kill Harley,
he wouldn't leave the cart
next to his camper.
He would have dumped it.
Yeah, but you know who did
get rid of his cart really fast?
-Larsen.
-That's right. We overheard him
say that he sold it.
He told his fiancée,
Jill that he's going to have
some big money coming in.
I knew it.
Larson killed his father
so he could take his money.
That earring
could belong to Jill,
if they were working together.
I think we need
to do a little bit more
investigating on Larson
before we go call Chief Bud.
I don't think
Jill's involved though.
She plays a pretty
clueless bride-to-be.
Maybe the earring
isn't related at all.
The cart manager did tell Dalton
that one of the beer carts
was off for repairs.
He said it was weird because
they usually do it in-house.
What about Foster and Winona?
Are we sure
that they are both clear?
Based on what Tanner said,
Foster and Winona
sound pretty innocent.
You know, Roxi knows the
managers at the Chill Martini's.
Some of her art
is displayed there.
We can have her go and
find out what time they left.
What about the Colonel?
He sounded pretty guilty.
Aubrey, you should tell Dalton
to track down the Colonel's cart
at the local repair shops.
-See if he can find out
what happened to it.
-Okay.
And it has to be
done by tomorrow
because our three days
ends tomorrow night.
If any of you
find anything, text me.
Maybe we'll see some
of the suspects at the club.
Yeah, it's true.
We could probably spy on them
at Char's dinner.
I don't know
why my mother insists
on giving me a birthday party
at the Country Club.
Not exactly my scene.
Because the food is awesome,
and you know she likes
a reason to get dressed up.
Alright,
I want to play some COD.
- Yes.
I'll go get snacks.
I'm so happy we finally
get to spend some time together.
Mm-hmm.
Dalton. Do you think this is
going to turn out okay?
I hope so. It's your little
joyride is gonna cost us all.
Hey! I wasn't out there alone.
-I thought we were
in this together.
-Yeah.
Rapping to the point
where we both go to prison.
- Hey, love birds.
- What are you doing here?
It's called chasing
you down for your half
of the Jet Ski money.
We've only got, like, two
hours till I lose my deposit.
Yeah. Um...
So, this is where you're
always running off to.
Yeah. Come meet
my secret love, Chanel.
Be scared?
It's just a horse, man.
Just a horse?
She's my baby and we're a team.
I trust her that she will
take care of me over the jumps.
She's pretty cool.
But I admit, I've never, um...
I've never been
around a horse before.
Oh. So you do have
holes in your armor.
Don't be afraid.
She's the sweetest.
It's okay. Here.
Just right there. Yeah.
Oh, she's actually soft.
Yeah. Here.
You can give her a treat.
Here.
So, just right there.
- There you go.
- I just like that one.
Okay. I think that's
enough fun on the farm time.
-Let's go.
-That's right.
We got business to do.
You keep dodging me,
I'm gonna be out $1,000.
I've been meaning
to talk to you about that.
- See you tonight, babe.
- Oh!
Okay.
- Almost forgot these.
- Oh, thank you.
Thanks for showing me
your secret love.
She's beautiful.
Well. Hello, Aubrey.
Can I help you?
Hello, Mrs. Graham.
I've got groceries
for the food pantry.
Oh, great!
We can set them on back there
by the other boxes.
I'll make sure it gets
with the rest of the donations.
We were going to bring
them on Sunday, but then...
Well, that's okay.
It's not too late.
The food bank
hasn't even picked up yet.
I've got more
in the front of my truck.
Great. I'll help you.
So, how are you, dear?
I hear you had some trouble
with your golf cart.
Oh. Yeah.
You know...
when I have things
on my heart weighing me down,
I bring my words to God.
There's nothing your
Heavenly Father can't handle.
Just talk to Him.
How about if you take
a quiet moment and go inside
and sit down in the sanctuary?
If you can't find the words...
Well, that's okay.
You don't need to speak.
He hears your heart.
Okay.
Thank you.
Hey, did you see the text?
We're close now. Yay!
Hey, are Dalton and you okay?
Actually, I'm not sure.
Sometimes he's great and
the next thing I know he's gone.
Yeah, I can see
why you feel that way.
I tried to be patient
and he's always focused
on trying to pay
for half of his college tuition
like his dad wants.
But honestly, I think he's
over me and hasn't told me yet.
But are you
really that into him?
I'm starting to wonder.
But I am looking forward
to seeing him tonight.
Are you looking forward
to see anyone tonight?
-No.
-Maybe you should
open your eyes more.
You got some sweet friends
that would make some
good boyfriend material.
- No, Aubrey.
- Okay, if you say so.
Hey, will help me with my hair?
Sure.
Ah, Mom texted.
She's running a bit late.
Dad's flight
was diverted to Raleigh.
She's going there
to pick him up.
Okay. Uh,
shouldn't Dalton be here by now?
Yeah, he's coming, he promised.
Oh. I guess
he's not coming after all.
Excuse me.
Aubrey, it will be okay.
- Hey, Brynn, I like your onesie.
- Brynn, don't run off.
Oh, excuse me!
- Hey, Betsy.
- Hey, sweetie.
I could not get her
to put on her dress,
so I just finally gave up.
You know, with autism, you have
to pick your battles carefully,
because there's so many.
Right. Well, I like it.
She looks party ready.
I know I am. I need a drink.
I'll be right back.
I need to find Brynn.
Why is Grant here?
Oh, Scarlet invited him.
Roxi! I love your dress.
Thanks. Hey, Finn,
Charlotte pulled you out again.
Well, I've been
in high demand lately.
Lucky Finn,
isn't he the popular one?
Grant. You clean up nicely.
Thanks. I'm, uh, trying to get
noticed by someone special.
Come on, Grant,
let's go grab drinks
for everyone while we wait.
Sure.
Is, uh, is this a thing?
No, this is not a thing.
Are you jealous?
Are you flirting with me?
That's what it takes
to get your attention?
Then yeah.
Oh. This is interesting.
Uh, come on, Roxi, let's...
Let's go get those sodas.
Oh, right. Yeah, I love
a good root beer.
Actually, I can't stay.
My uncle's visiting, so I have
to have dinner with my family.
But I just want to say
happy birthday...
Charlotte Margaret Moon.
Hi, Grant!
Bye, Grant.
- Happy birthday!
- Happy birthday, Charlotte.
Okay, Cal.
♪ I don't know
if someone told her
someone here is getting older ♪
♪ And we love her smile
we love her face
she's someone we can't replace ♪
♪ She loved me better
when we started now her
nose... ♪
♪ Who is this girl
we love by far? ♪
♪ Happy birthday
her name is Char! ♪
Wow. Cal, I...
I have no words. That...
Did Scarlet put you up to this?
Yes. Now can we go inside?
I'm starving.
Cal, behave.
Sorry, Cal.
Tables are not ready yet.
Hey, what can I get you?
Uh, three cherry sodas,
- and root beer, right?
- Yeah.
I really do like root beer.
Alright. You got it.
- Uh, hey.
- Hey. What are you doing here?
I've got a date.
Oh, another
country club princess
running up Daddy's tab?
Of course.
That's my favorite type.
Why are you here?
Uh, we're celebrating
Char's birthday.
Uh, where's Dalton?
Is he not your date?
Um, he bailed on me again.
I'm pretty sure we're over.
You know, if that's true,
he should man up and tell you.
Look, you're not
the only one getting dumped.
He completely left me hanging
on the Jet Ski deal.
Oh, I'm sorry.
You lost your deposit?
Yeah. Well...
Aubrey, you look
really pretty tonight.
Oh. Thanks.
I'm sorry,
he made you come alone.
Whatever his reasons,
I hope it was
pretty damn important,
because he is a fool.
Excuse me.
- One, two.
- There it is.
There you go, three.
-Three cherries and I want to
check the back for root beer.
-Okay. Thank you.
- I'll see you out there.
- Okay.
Figured I'd find you here.
Mom, I did what you asked.
Really? You wouldn't
lie to me now, would you?
Your daddy used
to lie to me and I...
- I know you wouldn't lie to me.
- I'm not!
You paid off
all your gambling debts,
all of it, like we agreed?
Yes. I sold my boat, Jet Skis
and the golf cart to do it.
That's my good boy.
Now, would you
pay for my honeymoon?
Of course, baby.
I'll always make sure
we're taken care of.
Thanks, Mom.
Good boy.
And here's that root beer.
Thank you.
Hey, sugar.
Ms. Trudeau.
What can I do for you?
I think you know.
Alright, Winona, simmer down.
I'm gonna go home
and pack an overnight bag,
and then I'm gonna
head on over to your house,
if that's alright with you.
Oh, yes, ma'am.
Toodles.
Found her!
Oh. Oh, there's Gina.
I want to get a drink.
Brynn!
Oh, my goodness.
I am losing my mind.
-Don't worry. I'll get her.
-The host has said
our tables are ready.
Awesome.
"Oh, thanks
for the drink, Finn."
"Oh, no problem, Charlotte."
Brynn?
Where did you get that?
You. You're the unicorn witness?
Aubrey, Carlos
isn't the killer, Gina is.
Yes. And I have proof.
Gina killed Harley.
I'm in the bathroom now, hurry.
Gina is the killer. Her and
Harley were having an affair.
- What? Are you sure?
- Yes, I'm sure.
And I think
Brynn witnessed the murder.
She was on the golf course
the night Harley died.
Gina's after her,
and we have to find her.
Come on,
let's try the parking lot.
We got to tell Chief Bud!
Get off me, asshole!
What's wrong with you?
That's enough out of you.
- Let's get her up.
- I didn't do anything.
Come on now, you get her cuffed,
and we'll sort this out.
Take her in.
Mom and Dad are on their way
back from the airport.
Did you send your friends home?
Yeah. Their parents
are picking them up now.
Brynn. Oh, I was so worried.
Alright, Charlotte.
We did find Miss Young pursuing
your cousin rather aggressively.
I had Sergeant Hart
take her back to the station.
Now. How about you telling me
what's got you so worried?
I know that Gina
killed Harley Trudeau.
And you know this how?
I've got pics of Harley
and her together.
I got them off of her phone.
I'm pretty sure
they were having an affair.
Okay. Anything else?
See those expensive earrings?
Pretty sure
Harley gave them to her.
-Go on.
-She had them on
at the club cocktail party
the night that he was killed.
Brynn was outside
playing around the golf course,
and she found the earring
in a sand trap
near the crime scene.
And that's where I also found...
its match.
You're gonna want
this sandbag too.
Harley's body
was hit by a small car,
a cart in this case.
Look at this.
I took pics of the tracks
around the sand trap,
just after the murder.
Two cart tracks lead into
the trap, three tracks lead out.
And you'll find
Harley's blood soaked
into the sand, if you dig.
See the tracks here? And here?
In this pic, Gina and Harley,
look at his tie.
This is the tie Harley
was wearing the night he died.
You can see it
in the party pics.
I'm sure that Brynn saw Gina
run over Harley with the cart.
That's why Brynn's been
running away from her.
And that's why
Gina chased after her.
Harley's body
was found in the cove.
That's why there are three track
marks leading out of the trap,
and why he had
strangle marks on his neck.
Gina tied his necktie
to the cart hitch,
and dragged him to the pond.
Oh, good Lord!
It's no wonder his head
didn't pop off like a grape.
We've heard enough, Brynn and I
are gonna wait for you outside.
Come on, Brynn,
let's go outside.
Charlotte, you were saying?
So, after Gina
put his body into the lake,
she lost the tie
and lost the earrings.
And that's when
Brynn came and found them.
Your evidence does
suggest that she's guilty.
But what's her motive?
Easy. Everyone at the club
has seen how Gina chases
after the wealthy man.
She finally caught one,
or so she thought.
Harley must have betrayed her,
and she turned to a jilted
lover, green with envy.
She wanted to be
the new Mrs. Trudeau.
You form a convincing theory,
Charlotte.
So good in fact,
I'd say it matches nicely
with our own findings.
Well, what about Carlos Harris?
Did he help Gina? I mean,
Charlotte saw his cart all
beat-up with blood all over it.
Carlos reported that he hit
a deer with his cart a week ago.
His story checks out.
So, I sent Sergeant Hart
to take a visit to the dump.
Beer cart number two was found
behind the trash heap.
And it had the damage you would
expect from hitting Harley.
- Well, what now?
- First off,
while I appreciate your sharp
and inquisitive minds,
and your courage and trying
to keep Aubrey from getting
in trouble...
you need
to let me handle this.
Second off, you and your friends
need to come down
to the station tomorrow
and give me a full statement.
Chief Bud, you there?
Yes, Dixie, I'm here.
Tanner says Miss Young
is singing like a bird.
You better get back here.
Alright, Dixie, I'm coming.
Alright. So you two,
get home safe and sound,
and please try
to stay out of trouble.
You have a good night.
So now you know, my love...
why I did what I had to do.
And why I couldn't tell you.
I will miss you terribly.
You made me feel alive again.
I've never felt
so beautiful and happy...
and for that...
I'll be forever grateful.
I couldn't have
had a better alibi.
A lover.
Winona.
Winona!
- Hey.
- Oh, guys!
- Going somewhere, Foster?
Hold on. Whoa.
- Stop.
- -Why don't you take a seat?
Looks like you've had
quite a night, Mr. Davis?
Where's Winona Trudeau?
I don't know!
Like, she left
about 20 minutes ago.
She's getting away.
She's the one you want.
Better put an APB out on her.
You know, we've been talking to
Gina Young down at the station.
I swear, I had nothing
to do with Harley's death.
Winona fooled me too.
Is that right?
It looks like she left you
a nice little parting gift,
all wrapped in ribbon.
Take it.
I want nothing to do with this.
Alright, Mr. Davis.
How about you give us
a short version of
what went on here tonight?
Winona tricked me.
I thought
we were playing a game.
Next thing I know,
I'm tied to a chair
and she's pointing a gun at me.
What, you didn't see
that one coming?
Continue.
Winona has said that
about a month ago,
Harley told her
he was going divorce her
and marry his secretary.
Winona signed a prenup.
And over the years, Larson
lost favor with his daddy.
So she was determined
to do whatever it took
to maintain their lifestyle.
How'd Gina Young get involved?
Winona said that her revenge
will be even sweeter
if she had one of Harley's
flings do the dirty work.
She said, she was killing
two birds with one stone.
So, she approached Gina.
And you had no part in this?
No, I didn't!
Winona told Gina that Harley
has been cheating on her.
And how he's planning
to run off with his latest
flavor of the month.
That was enough
to fuel the fire.
I mean, Gina went nuts!
Then all Winona had to do
was offer to pay Gina
to kill him.
And that was enough
to seal his fate.
Did she tell you the plan?
Just said, Winona made sure
the drinks kept flowing
to Harley's direction
last Friday
at the club cocktail.
She knew he'd get drunk
and that they'd get fighting,
and then he'd go looking
for Gina after he dropped
her off at home.
And sure enough,
he found Gina leaving the club.
Then... Gina took him
for a ride on the beer cart.
She pushed him out of the cart,
and he's stumbling around,
so she chases him down into
the sand pit and runs him over.
According to Winona,
one groan and he's gone.
That sounds about right.
Don't you think so, Tanner?
I'd say so.
Same story Gina
told us at the station.
You're a lucky man, Foster.
You got an alibi.
Gina claims Winona didn't
want you mixed up in all this.
Thank God.
That's all for tonight,
Mr. Davis.
But I'm gonna need you
to come down to the station
in the morning
to give us your full statement.
Tanner.
Collect that for me, will you?
Yes, sir. Mm.
Toodles, Foster.