Very nice, Penny.
Come on, Professor, cheer up.
We found some really great pieces.
Yes, but not what we came for.
I really went out on a limb
with the university this time.
I guaranteed them that
we'd finally track it down.
Perhaps they're right.
Perhaps the tomb really is a legend,
and I am a fool for believing it.
But we shall continue with
style, right?
Yes, we shall and
we're not finished yet.
We have, let's see,
today is the 8th.
The 8th, the 8th,
why does that sound familiar?
Which means we have five
more days left.
Oh my God, it's my son's birthday.
I forgot to call him.
I am gonna be disowned.
Hello?
Hey Champ, Happy Birthday.
What are you up to?
Oh, Dad, I was just
reading this cool book
that Grandpa got me.
Uh huh.
How are grandma and grandpa?
Oh, great, hey, where are you?
Uh, I'm still at the dig site,
but we should be wrapping
things up here pretty soon.
Oh, okay.
Hey I got this idea from this book,
because when they were
searching for the city of Troy..
Dave, Dave, we have to go,
we have to go right now!
Oh, um, okay, uh,
listen Champ, I'm gonna,
I'm gonna have to call you back.
Okay, something's come up.
Happy Birthday, Buddy.
I want crowbars!
Oh my God!
Is it?
Yes it is.
It's Coronado.
Woo hoo!
And that box gives me the creeps.
Looks like a coffin.
What are you talking about now?
Does it smell funny to you?
You're the one who smells funny.
I'm serious!
What do you think is in there?
One body, Count Dracula.
Oh very funny, what's it say?
Remains.
Remains?
Remains of what?
Remains of my patience,
now come on, give us a hand!
Put that right over here, all right.
(Muttering)
You there,
stop right where you are
and identify yourself.
Hey, hey watch with that thing,
you're blinding me.
It's Dr. McAmmon.
You expect me
to take your word for it?
Let's see some identification.
Look, could you please
get that out of my face?
Huh, why don't you show
me some identification?
Who are you?
Martin Van Leer, Director of Security.
Let's see that ID.
Sorry about that Sir.
It's my responsibility to
safeguard these valuables.
Been at my present position
for six months now, Sir
and you've been gone that
whole time, you understand.
Well, I've been, you know,
digging up
these valuables for the last
six months,
but I suppose I should be
grateful, so no harm done.
How are things going?
Everything's under control.
This is the last load
right here, artifacts.
The treasure came in this
morning, it's all secure.
Good.
Put that on the counter please.
Put this crate over here
on the table and open it up
for me, I'll be working on that
first thing in the morning.
Thank you.
All right,
goodnight Sir and don't worry,
I'll keep an eye on things here.
Bloody hell, that was close.
Yeah, it's taken out the transformer.
You guys stay here,
I'll make a search for breakers.
Chris, where are you?
Over here.
Help me with this crate.
I don't wanna spend all night here.
Ready?
Lift.
Did you hear that?
What?
Something moved, in the crate!
It shifted when we lifted.
Now come and help open this
thing up.
I heard it again.
What?
The box, there's something in there.
You're imagining things.
It's probably a rat!
A big rat.
C'mon, let's hurry up and
finish this
so we can get the hell out.
You can wrap it up if you want.
I'm gonna wait 'til the
lights turn on.
Don't just stand there, push.
See, I told you.
Thanks Kid.
Charlie, hey!
I'm sorry I wasn't able to meet
you, but I had this meeting
and it went late.
It's been crazy around here.
So, did you grow two inches,
is that what happened?
You grew like two inches?
I have got a surprise for you.
No, no, no, not that way,
this way.
Where are we going?
You'll see.
When are we going home?
Well, actually we are home.
This is our new house.
New house?
It's a gift from the university,
a perk actually.
We don't own it, but
we got free use of it.
And there's no mortgage
payment and best of all,
the lab is so close that
I can come home
and have dinner,
even if I'm working late.
But what if we don't like it?
Of course we'll like it.
Come on in, Charlie, take a look.
You moved us already?
Yep, that was one headache
you were able to avoid.
I can't believe it.
What about the old house?
Well, I'm gonna sell it.
Oh, I almost forgot.
I know it's a little late,
but Happy Birthday.
Don't you wanna open it?
I'm sorry I missed your
birthday, Buddy
but, uh, I promise I'm
gonna make it up to you.
All right?
So, uh, why don't we go
see your room, come on.
I'll show you your room.
It's right upstairs.
I think you're really gonna
like it.
Look at that map.
Just think, every time
you come up the stairway,
you can look at that map, huh?
Isn't that nice?
Charlie, this is Marta.
This is our new maid.
And Marta, this is Charlie.
Hello Charlie.
It's nice to meet you.
Well, I have some things to do.
It's all right, what do you think?
We did the best we could.
Of course, you can rearrange
it however you'd like.
Look, Sam even made it, no problem.
Why don't you open the
present, Buddy?
Great.
I thought maybe you'd
like to read up on Coronado.
All you ever think about is yourself.
Did you ever think that
I may not want to move
and leave all my friends behind?
You start school in a couple
of weeks
and you'll uh, make new friends.
And we can go visit the old
neighborhood anytime you like.
You know one of the fascinating
things about Coronado
is the hardships he endured.
You know why he did it?
I don't know.
He was crazy?
No, he was a stoic who
remained totally focused
on his one burning objective, discovery.
And what was the result?
He died.
He discovered new lands that
no European
had ever laid eyes on before
and he went down in history
as one of the world's
greatest explorers.
I don't care about Coronado.
Is the history lesson over?
I just thought maybe
you could be a little bit
more like Coronado and look
at the move
to the new neighborhood as an adventure.
I've got a lot of work to do.
I'll let you unpack and
make yourself comfortable.
You had a long flight.
I'm glad you're here, Charlie.
I made you some cookies.
It's chocolate chip.
Thanks.
Your father is very happy to
see you.
He misses you so much.
Nah, all he cares about are
old bones.
Mm, he's a very nice man,
but I do not like the work he does.
What do you mean?
Digging up old bones?
This is not good, Charlie.
The dead should be left undisturbed.
This is yours?
Yeah.
Dad?
Hey, hey, hey, hey Buddy, Buddy,
it's okay, it's all right,
it's okay.
It's me, it's me, it's me.
You all right, are you all right?
He was right behind me!
What was right behind you?
He, he was.
Who was?
He was, but..
Hey, hey, hey, hey, look,
look, there's nothing here.
It's just us.
This house is haunted.
Haunted, don't be silly.
Come on, you just had a nightmare.
It was no nightmare.
Oh yeah, well there's nothing here.
It's your first night in a
new house,
it's dark, there's a storm out.
Come on, it's late.
I've got a big day tomorrow.
Let's get some sleep, come on.
Ah!
Good morning Mr. Dave.
You get a good night's sleep?
I've had better.
Ah what you need is a good
hot muffin to get you going.
Oh, those smell delicious Marta,
but I've gotta get to the museum
and get ready for this
Press Conference tonight.
Your father works so hard.
Sometimes he forgets to eat.
I put some in a bag for you.
Hey listen Champ, here's $10,
so listen, if you wanna
rent a video or you know,
catch a movie in town or whatever.
Just have fun.
Maybe you should go out today.
Explore the neighborhood,
make new friends.
I already have friends,
I just can't see them anymore.
Mm.
Oh no, I was going to
make some more cookies.
I have no eggs.
Will you go to the store for me?
Sure.
You know where it is?
Yeah, I think so.
Hey, hey, if you're not
gonna put any quarters
in the machine, leave it alone.
Hey, I'm talking to you!
Hey, don't hit the machines.
Hey, take over for me.
Stay alive or you're dead.
Hey Sweet Thing,
change your mind about me yet?
Don't hold your breath.
Come on.
Excuse me.
How nice, someone with manners.
Maybe you could take a lesson.
I'd like to give you a lesson
in love.
One night with me and
you'll forget your own name.
I wish I could forget yours.
Excuse me.
Hi, I'm Nicki.
Hi, I'm Charlie.
You must be new around here.
I haven't seen you before.
Yeah, my dad works at the university.
Egg Inspector.
Egg head is more like it.
Hey, how about a good game of
egg ball?
I guess you are the catcher.
I can be the batter,
'cause I'm gonna knock one
of your eggs over that wall
right there.
All right.
Yeah, here we go, here we go.
Nah, bad pitch,
gimme a better pitch.
All right, go ahead and gimme one.
Hey batter, batter!
Look alive, Catcher!
(Muttering)
Whoa!
Looks like I have to have a
little talk with the catcher.
You did that on purpose
didn't you, you little creep.
Do you know how much these
boots cost?
Let him go, Mitch, you're lucky
he didn't hit you in the face.
It's his face that something's
going to happen to.
You kids,
no fighting around my store!
Go on, get outta here!
We're just joking around.
You got off easy this time,
but next time
I'm gonna make you lick my
boots clean.
See you later, Charlie.
Yeah, I guess I'll see you around.
Careful study has revealed
that he was a visionary
explorer and a dignified
military leader,
reserved, thoughtful, level headed.
These are all words that
would accurately
the stoic and fearless leader.
Coronado dedicated his life
towards the preeminent objective,
pushing the boundaries of exploration,
but the Queen demanded that
Coronado bring back the gold.
Being a man of duty,
he did as he was told,
even though it ultimately
led to his death.
Charlie.
Charlie!
Until now, the death of
Coronado has been the stuff
of legend and speculation.
No one had ever been able
to locate his fabled tomb.
But this summer, after
years of exhaustive research
and excavation,
my team and I finally did it.
And we were able to substantiate
the legend of Coronado's death.
Penny?
Ladies and Gentlemen, Coronado.
Oh, just wait a minute,
where do you think you're going?
My father's in there.
I need to talk to him.
I'm not gonna interrupt this
just because some kid
has his undies in a wad.
Now take a powder!
As he was buried alive (muttering).
I'm not afraid, no, I'm not afraid.
Nope, I'm not afraid, not afraid
'cause ghosts aren't real.
I don't believe in ghosts.
I'm not afraid.. I'm not afraid.
No, I'm not afraid.
Hola Charlie.
Dad!
Dad, Dad, Dad!
Hey Dad, Dad!
Dad!
I told you to stay outta here, Kid.
Martin, Martin, it's okay,
that's my son.
Excuse me.
Yes, Sir.
Hey, hey,
Dad!
Charlie, Charlie, are you okay?
Yeah, Dad, he was after me!
Who was after you?
The ghost, he was here.
Get ahold of yourself.
But Dad he was..
Listen, listen,
I was just giving a speech
telling these people about a man
who knew the meaning
of respect and dignity.
Now, I'd appreciate it if
you'd do a little of the same.
But Dad, he..
I don't want to hear it.
I want you to go stand over there
and not another word, go on.
Sorry Folks,
just a little family drama.
A disgrace, don't you think?
Look at it,
the bones of the dead hauled up
and staked up for public display.
Don't run away again.
I didn't come back from the
nether regions
just to harm a small boy.
But, who, who are you?
I am he who used to be the
man whose bones those were.
Come Boy,
surely you have guessed by now.
It is I,
Frederico Cavrell Disposa De Coronado
Commander of the Queen's Guard
and ruler of New Spain and a
General, all around nice guy.
Unless of course, you are
standing in between me and gold.
Oh, oro, beautiful gold.
And to think how close
I was to claiming it.
Those nasty Mayans tricked me.
But wasn't it their gold to
begin with?
A minor point, Muchacho, a minor point.
Besides, I didn't want all of
it, just most of it.
Wait, I, I don't understand
how and why are you here?
Because of this, this outrage!
This public humiliation!
What are you talking about?
My bones, Muchacho, my bones!
Just thrown here in a heap for
the whole world to gawk at!
It's a mockery!
It's a museum exhibit.
If you don't like it,
just fly off to Ghost Land or something.
I need your help, Muchacho.
What?
Why?
Well, the Mayans, when they
sealed me into that chamber,
they denied me a proper burial,
trapping me in limbo,
a never land between
this world and the next.
And now, your father
has done the same thing.
Limbo?
I don't get it.
Don't you know anything about ghosts?
I need you to take my bones
and bury them
on hallowed ground,
so I can go to my final rest.
Wait, wait a minute, hallowed ground?
You've got to be kidding.
I wish, this is not just.
I want you to take my
bones from this glass tomb
and bury them in a proper cemetery.
You mean steal, don't you?
You want me to steal my
father's exhibit?
Father's exhibit?
These are my bones!
They belong to me!
Well, you're crazy if
you think I'm gonna steal.
My father would kill me.
Well then perhaps he would pay
some attention to you, Boy.
Hey, who asked you?
My father treats me just fine.
Mm, harrumph.
All right,
now hold it right there, Bub.
What are you doing?
I, uh..
And who are you talking to?
What do you mean, him!
Have you no manners, Swine?
I knew you were trouble the
minute I laid eyes on you.
Don't you think for a second
that just because your dad
is some big deal professor
that you're gonna
get any special treatment
from me.
Now, who were you talking to?
I told you that,
that there's nobody.
I'm just talking to myself.
What, do I look like
I was born in a barn?
Well, now that you mention it.
Let's go, come on!
Come on!
See this here?
This is the very latest security
system on the market today.
Once I activate it, anyone
or anything that moves
inside the exhibit hall will
be trapped.
Now, sure you don't
wanna change your story?
Ay dios mios, this
one sure can talk, huh?
Did you hear me son?
No, no, I mean, uh,
there's nobody in there.
Okay, this room is now impregnable
and it takes two keys
to activate the system.
Now your father has one key
and the Dean, of course,
has the other one,
but I'm the only person
that's been entrusted to have
both keys.
And these keys never leave my sight.
As a matter of fact,
I never even take them off.
(Murmurs)
Now I should warn you,
that no one
No one.
Has ever broken
Into this museum, ever and no
one ever will, you know why?
Because I will never drop my
guard, ever.
Oh!
I don't know what your
game is Son, but uh,
I should warn you, I'm gonna
be keeping my eyes on you.
Let's get out of here.
It's probably my fault,
leaving you alone
in this big house, but
you're a big boy now Charlie.
I need to be able to rely on you.
I know.
All right, no real harm done.
Why don't you go on and get
some sleep
and absolutely no more of
this ghost nonsense, okay?
Okay.
All right.
(Foreign language)
Don't do that!
What took you so long?
You move slow as a mule.
I'm sorry, I haven't exactly mastered
the art of teleporting yet.
Que?
Nevermind.
By the way, thanks for
getting me in trouble.
Well it is your fault,
you shouldn't raise your voice
when speaking to ghosts.
Yeah, that's another thing.
Why am I the only one that
can see you?
Because it is you who I have
chosen to help me, Charlie.
But why me, I'm just a kid.
Size is not important.
It's the will to do
the thing that matters.
Didn't anybody ever tell you
the story of David and Goliath?
You can tell me all the
stories you would like,
but I am not going to steal
your bones.
Then you give me no choice,
but to mercilessly haunt
you until you relent!
Go ahead, you don't scare
me anymore, haunt away!
But I am going to sleep.
Hmm.
From the most beautiful place
in the world,
What are you doing?
Such an interesting machine
Tanning products in the world..
Much has changed in four centuries.
Natural oils, tropical fruits, floral..
Hombre, an angel!
Sun care line..
Ah senorita, muy bonita,
come to me my beautiful!
I've killed her!
Where did she go?
Foolish machine,
it brings lust for women
on their promises they can't keep?
What kind of torment is this?
It's called advertising.
Charlie, it's a little late
for TV.
Oh, yeah Dad, I'm sorry,
it was just an accident.
I seem to have an interesting effect
on your machine!
Charlie, that's not funny.
Sorry, Dad, must be broken.
Perhaps you would like to
hear about my real triumphs,
like the time I wooed the
Countess of Segovia.
Her father told me if he
ever found me near her,
he would kill me,
but did that stop me?
Ha, no, when it came to women
or gold, I was fearless.
Well enough, one night I was
trying to sneak into the castle
which was a very dangerous proposition,
because at every entrance
there were fierce attack dogs,
chihuahua's I think they were,
which is not a bad dog if
you marinate them properly.
Anyways, it was dark,
maybe it was light.
Ah, breakfast, there is no
finer time in military camp,
Charlie, than breakfast.
It used to be my favorite
time of day.
Good morning, how'd you sleep?
Mm, like the dead.
Lousy.
Why's that,
there weren't any ghosts were there?
No, Dad you're right,
there are no ghosts here.
None worth listening to anyway.
I resent that.
Well, maybe you can
take a nap this afternoon.
Ay dios mios, Charlie,
you didn't tell me
there were women in camp.
Hola Senorita, muy bonita.
Who's ready for breakfast?
I am.
Me too and you, Senorita,
could be my main course.
Enjoy.
That looks delicious, Marta.
Oh, it is you who looks
delicious, Senorita.
I could devour you whole.
This is the curse of
being a ghost, Muchacho,
to have the appetite but
not be able to participate.
Don't be such a jerk.
What'd you say, Son?
What time do you have to go
to work?
In a few minutes,
now, eat your breakfast.
Yes, eat up, Boy,
you'll need your strength
if you're going to bury my bones.
Fat chance.
What?
Last chance for orange juice,
want some?
Charlie!
I didn't touch it.
Don't, stop it.
Charlie, what are you doing?
It's stuck.
Please go!
What?
I wasn't talking to you.
If I knew life here was
going to be this much fun,
I would have done it
centuries ago!
You okay?
I'm fine, I'm fine.
Go sit down.
Damn it, Charlie!
I didn't do it!
What the hell's gotten into you?
Charlie, that's it, okay,
I've had enough
of these childish pranks, okay.
I have to go to work now.
That man needs to relax.
It is not good for the digestion
to eat and run like that.
I do not think it's so funny, Charlie.
I didn't do it, it wasn't me.
Yes, well maybe you should go outside
before you get into more trouble.
Go.
Aw, don't worry,
I believe you, Charlie.
Shut up!
Charlie!
I'm sorry, I didn't mean it.
Why can't you just find
somebody else to haunt, okay?
Well just bury my bones
and I will leave you in peace, Amigo.
That's that new kid I was
telling you about.
And I'm not your amigo.
He seems kinda weird.
Oh no, please, please be my amigo.
Please, please, please,
please, please.
Yeah, but he's kinda cute.
No!
Now leave me alone.
Hey Charlie, Charlie!
Hey Charlie, you're the sly one,
making good with the senoritas
already, huh?
How's it going?
Great, I was just taking a walk.
This is my friend, Terri.
Hi.
Hello Charlie.
Do you always talk to yourself?
No, I was rehearsing a play.
Really?
Which one?
The Stupid Ghost.
Is it a comedy?
More like a horror story.
Oh, you really know
how to hurt a ghost, oh.
Look Charlie,
I'm having a pool party
tomorrow afternoon at two o'clock.
I thought maybe you'd like to come.
Tomorrow at two, I'd love to.
You're not invited, Birdbrain.
Excuse me,
we're playing a game here.
It's a public court, you know,
we could play too.
What's the score, 30 Love?
I believe it was love.
Ow!
Are you okay?
You think you're so smart.
You don't look so smart now,
do you?
Let go of me.
Senorita's in distress,
do something to help her Charlie.
But that guy will kill me.
Stop him, tell him to unhand her.
Unhand her!
Unhand her?
Who do you think you are,
the Scarlet Pimpernel?
What do I do now?
Who are you talking to, Creep?
When I get through with you,
they're gonna have
to scrape you off this
court with a shovel.
Hey, what are you doing?
You wanna fight, you go outside!
Go on, get out,
before I call the police.
We'll finish this
tomorrow at the pool party.
Be there or I'll come looking
for you.
Don't you have ears?
You're not invited.
Thanks Charlie.
Don't worry, he's just a big jerk.
We'll have fun tomorrow.
Hope you'll be there.
Ahem.
Ah, hey Charlie,
didn't see you standing there.
Hey Dad,
hey I gotta ask you a question.
Uh huh, go ahead.
Well you see, it's about
this guy named Mitch Tuggle.
Oh, oh, yup?
Professor, the reporter from
The Times is here.
Oh, oh, right, right,
right, right, right, right.
T-tell 'em I'll be right out.
Listen Buddy,
can this wait 'til tonight?
Yeah, I guess.
Oh no, no, no, not tonight.
Tonight I gotta do that
special lecture
and then there's a meeting
right after.
Um, tell you what, if you
can hang on until tomorrow,
I'll set aside some time and
we can talk
about whatever it is that you
want, okay?
Tomorrow.
Yeah, tomorrow night then?
I look okay?
Yeah, you look great.
Okay, all right, bye.
Great, tomorrow,
I'll be dead by then.
You're frightened, aren't you Charlie?
No.
It's only natural.
In my expeditions,
I was constantly afraid.
But aren't you the
guy that went fearlessly
to his death saying that he'd
protect the Queen's gold?
Complete rubbish!
I mean it was true, I was
sealed alive in a Mayan chamber,
but I never said any of those things.
Then what did you say?
If I remember correctly,
it was something like,
(Foreign language).
Oh, to translate,
help, get me out of here!
So you were afraid.
Of course I was,
only an idiot wouldn't be.
There is nothing wrong
with being afraid, Charlie,
but a man must not be ruled
by fear.
You cannot run away from
your problems, Muchacho.
So you're saying I should
fight Tuggle?
Only as the last resort.
Fighting is a stupid way
to solve your differences.
Diplomacy should always
be the first tactic.
I don't think this
guy's the talking type.
Well the battle is not always won
by the mightier opponent.
So what should I do?
Andale, Muchacho.
The first rule is to lure your
enemy onto a battleground
of your choosing, one that
you've had time to prepare, mm.
This looks perfect.
Come.
Look Mitch, you and
your Neanderthal friends
are not invited, just get lost.
Look, I'm not here for
sucky little pool party.
I'm waiting for your
little wimp of a friend
to respond to my invitation.
Hey, knock it off!
And what a surprise,
it doesn't look
like he's gonna show either.
It doesn't look like who's
gonna show?
Well, well, well,
if it isn't the return
of the Scarlet Pumpernickel.
I like it when a guy's nice
enough to show
up for his own funereal.
Hey look Tuggle,
I have no reason to fight you.
Is that so, well see,
I've got a reason.
I don't like the look of your
ugly face
and I plan to rearrange it.
Well you have to catch me first,
Fart Breath.
Look everybody, he's friggin' coward.
Come on.
What is this?
Let's go!
Hey, what's going on?
Hola Amigos!
Go get him!
Hey, hey, what's going on?
Let us out.
Yeah, we were just teasing,
let us out.
Don't you just think
we can talk this out?
Okay.
Hey, what's that?
All right, so you wanna talk.
You know, talking is really good.
Charlie look out!
What do I do now?
I don't know,
I guess you have to fight him!
Who are you talking to?
(Foreign language)
Ai, yi, yi!
I'm gonna kill you.
Bueno!
Ai, yi, yi!
Yes!
Ai, ai, ai ya!
Hey, hey look,
I'm really sorry about this.
I mean..
Yah!
Let's just calm down,
I mean we can,
we can work everything out.
Come on, just,
just work things out.
Finito, Muchacho.
Magnifico Muchacho, you did it.
And leave Nicki alone.
Dad, you won't believe it!
I could hardly believe it myself!
Hiya Charlie, look I'm sorry,
I'm in a big hurry.
What happened to you?
Go on, tell him boy.
It was a fight with the guy
I tried to tell you about.
I kicked his butt.
You expect me to be proud of that?
Oh and well you should, Senor.
You should have seen it,
it was a grand spectacle.
Charlie, you have been
nothing but trouble
since you got here,
now I am late for a meeting.
I'm in a big hurry, now,
could you please
just say out of trouble until supper?
It's all right, Muchacho,
he just doesn't understand.
He never does.
Well perhaps if he had been there?
If he had seen it with his
own eyes.
The only thing he ever
notices is when it's bad.
Well then, what are
you going to do about it?
I think I'm really gonna
get his attention this time.
Yes, how?
I'm going to steal your bones.
Yes.
Very good, Charlie, very good.
(Foreign language)
Um, well it's a keypad.
We have to know the code just
to get into the building.
Code?
Yeah, it's a series of
numbers you have to put in
or the alarm will go off
and the police will be here
in no time.
Ese, it is fortunate that the Mayans
did not have such machines.
Oh, darn it.
Don't worry, Muchacho,
I'll take care of it.
Five, zero, seven!
Two, zero!
Four, two, three, seven.
Here's the next problem.
We need the two keys to
deactivate the alarm.
And only one person has both,
Van Leer.
Well then,
we will have to borrow them.
He'll know they're gone.
Well then, uh, when we borrow them,
we will replace them with
dummy keys.
That would work.
But he said he never takes
them off
that chain around his neck.
He has to take them off some time.
Chuck?
Has he been gone all day?
Yes, he go right after breakfast.
I have not seen him since.
That's not like him.
He's been acting so
strange lately, Mr. Dave.
Talking to people who are not there.
I don't know what's the
matter with him.
I hear him swear in Spanish.
I want you to know I did not
teach him this.
Huh, I know I should be
spending more time with him,
but with the exhibit and all..
And those bones being so close,
makes me think.
This weekend, this weekend,
uh, I'm gonna
make time for him.
I'm gonna get tickets to uh,
something, on Saturday.
And church on Sunday.
You should go to confession.
Yeah.
Bueno, do you have the keys?
There right here, they
look just like the real ones.
It's the third time you've asked.
Now would you settle down,
you're starting to make me nervous.
Well, if it was your immortal soul
that hung in the balance
you might feel differently.
Hey, hey, wait, he's here.
Vehicle secure.
What am I doing, he can't see me.
Nah, nah, na na na, nah, nah, na.
Come on Charlie!
Sweetums?
Gracias Senor Jackass.
I'm home!
Woo, stuffy in here Baby.
That's better.
Charlie?
Hey Sweetums, Daddy's home.
Where's my widdle bird,
he's the tweetest widdle bird
in the whole wide world,
yes you are, yes you are!
Do you want some water,
it's so hot in here.
Yes you are, yes you are, bawk.
What a buffoon!
What a buffoon, bawk!
Sweetums!
What did you say?
I said, you are a dolt.
Bawk, you're a dolt!
Sweetums, shame on you
talking to Daddy like that.
Here Baby, have you
been talking to somebody
that I don't know about?
You still my sweet widdle
watch bird, like Sweetum?
Yes you are, you tell me
if there's an intwooder?
Bawk, intruder!
That's right, Sweetums,
that's what we say
when we see a stranger,
but why are you saying it now?
(Mutters)
That man is complete imbecile.
Bawk, imbecile.
Shh!
Sweetums, now don't make
Daddy mad at you uh unh uh.
No more television for Sweetums.
You just behave yourself
while Daddy takes a shower.
Come Charlie, now,
he's going to bathe.
Bawk, intruder!
Shh Sweetums, nice Sweetums,
be good bird
and don't touch that button.
That's a good bird.
I have a treat for you,
lucky I don't kill you
and have you for supper!
Intruder!
Shh, that's a nice bird,
I have a treat for you.
Muchacho, come, it's up to you.
Get the keys while I distract
this infernal bird.
Come, come, come, don't waste time.
We don't have time to lose,
go, go, go, go, go!
Shh, don't see us nicely,
Sweetums I will give you a treat,
just shh, be quiet,
I'll get you a treat.
Intruder.
I'll give you a treat,
I'll give you five treats!
Shut up you stupid bird.
♪ They'll be riding (mumbles) ♪
♪ Six white horses when she comes ♪
Sweetums, nice Sweetums, good bird.
Don't press the button.
Who's there?
Sweetums?
What do I do?
Run, Charlie, run, run, go!
Hi ya big Daddy,
hi ya big Daddy, bawk!
Hey you, you little creep!
You're not gonna get away
that easy!
Get back here!
Okay, now what do I do?
At first,
you must exchange the keys
and then keep on running!
Go, go, go, go, go!
Very nice look!
Don't even try to run, 'cause
you can't get away from me.
Oh my god, stay away from me.
I've got you now.
I'm warning you,
I know how to defend myself.
Who are you?
I'm sorry,
I was chasing a little boy.
Oh you pervert!
Ay caramba!
You all right, Miss?
No, this pervert tried to
attack me.
(Chattering)
Did you take his clothes?
All right, Mister Dangle,
party's over.
What?
Oh, oh no, no, no, no,
you don't understand.
See, um, I was chasing a burglar
and I was in the shower
'cause they took my keys,
that's why I was chasing them, they..
Okay, let me get this straight,
you were taking a shower,
someone stole your keys
so you decided to run
the 50 yard dash, naked.
Not just any keys though,
they were the keys,
the keys to the treasure.
Oh, the treasure keys.
You should have told me,
that makes all the difference.
No, no, you don't get it.
See, they were watching me.
They must have had this planned.
They know that I never take
the keys off
from around my neck,
I always have them on my neck.
Always.
These keys?
Come on.
Hey, hey.
Such an amazing woman warrior.
She has a most extraordinary
aptitude for combat,
don't you think?
I'd like to go back, you know,
to study her form.
Yeah, I bet you would.
You did very good, Muchacho.
It was a grand day!
Yeah, it was.
Hey shrimp!
Isn't it past your bedtime?
Don't you know you can get
hurt staying out after dark?
Come on Guys, let's go get him.
Dad?
Save me Daddy, save me Daddy.
Well, doesn't look like
your dad's gonna be here
to save you, does it?
Look Tuggle,
I don't wanna fight you.
I didn't wanna fight you the
first time.
But you see,
I don't think you get it.
I'm not here to fight you.
I'm here to get payment
for the boots and clothes
that you ruined and I'm
gonna take that payment
out of your hide,
so hold still Charlie.
This will only hurt until you
pass out.
What the hell is that?
I'm warning you Tuggle,
I have powers.
Powers?
I have the power to raise the dead!
I want out of here.
Look, make it stop, you know
I was just kidding with you.
Spirits of the dead, arise!
Come on, Man.
What kind of a freak are you?
Yes!
Impressive Muchacho.
You belong on the stage!
Thanks.
I was just about to be dog meat.
Hombre!
Charlie, what did you do?
Dad, it wasn't me, honest,
it was this guy
named Mitch Tuggle.
Save it!
You know better than to even
be in here.
Dad, it wasn't me.
Not another word!
Things aren't working out too well
between us are they, Charlie?
It's probably my fault.
I guess I'm just not, you know,
I guess I'm just not, uh,
doing it right.
I mean, you need somebody
who is around all the time,
obviously and uh,
and I can't be, 'cause I'm working,
I mean, look, I'd like to be around,
but well, ever since the tomb.
I think you're gonna have
to maybe go live with your grandparents.
At least they'll, they'll be around.
Dad, it wasn't me.
Charlie, go back to the house.
I'm gonna clean up here for
awhile and think about all this.
I owe you an apology, Muchacho.
I have been selfish to
ask you to do what I have.
(Foreign language)
I'm sorry, Charlie.
I deserve to walk in
limbo for all eternity.
I release you of your
pledge to bury my bones.
I've caused you enough sorrow.
Adios, my little Carlito.
Coronado?
I have been selfish to
ask you to do what I have.
(Foreign language)
I'm sorry Charlie.
I deserve to walk in
limbo for all eternity.
I release you of your
pledge to bury my bones.
I've caused you enough sorrow.
Adios, my little Carlito.
Coronado?
Ha.
Good evening Officer.
Come on, Martin, come on,
come on, come on.
All right, all right.
Step, step, step.
I was right, Man,
you've been working too hard.
And when I told you to go out
and mingle,
I had no idea you were
gonna do it in the buff.
Hey, hey, 50 foot drop, woo.
I always knew you were
wrapped too tight, Martin,
but come on, running down
the middle of the street
stark naked, good golly!
Shut up Daryl and take me home.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Hey, put it away!
What does this cover?
Well it wasn't me who
decided to drop trou',
go for a little run down the street
in his birthday suit, was it, huh?
Let me tell you something,
I had to pull
quite a few strings to
get you out of this too.
You owe me, big time.
Thank you Daryl.
What'd you think, you were
back in the ballpark, huh?
Don't you wish.
Selling wieners again?
Get away from me, will ya?
They switched the keys.
I need to get in that place
and I'll be ready for them.
If only I had my glasses,
I could have identified them.
Oh, they thought they were
pretty clever, Sweetums.
But not too clever for Daddy.
Run, Charlie, run, Charlie,
run, bawk.
(Mumbling) Negative.
Okay, that's a permit (mumbling).
(Mumbling)
All right, 10-4, 10-96.
(Mumbling) 10-4.
(Chatter)
I'm sorry, Dad,
but I've gotta do
at least one thing right.
Well, if it isn't the
professor's son.
Visiting hours are over, Boy,
so I guess that makes this
grand theft
and you get to do a nice
long stretch in juvie.
Thought you were pretty
damn smart, didn't you?
Sneaking into my house and
taking my keys,
well why did you do it?
Huh, why'd you do it?
Because of me!
Who else is in here?
Come on, who else is in here?
Who said that?
Don't be afraid of old
Van Leer, speak right up.
It was I,
Frederico Cavrell Disposa De Coronado!
No, no, no, you can't expect me
to believe that because
Coronado's dead
and I've got his bones
right here in this sack.
Now, you come out where I can
see you.
Why don't you come and get me?
Okay, all right, you just
show me where you are, Buddy.
(Foreign language) Down here!
Where?
I'm in the sack.
What?
Well, go on, open it!
Come on!
Come on, open it!
Oh, no.
What are you waiting for,
open it you Baby.
Surprise!
You came back.
Muchacho, what are you doing?
Well, you know I thought I'd
help out this friend of mine
and throw his old bones in
the cemetery.
Well, come Charlie,
we don't have much time.
Better get going.
Oh no, no, no please,
don't hurt me please, don't..
No, no, no, Martin,
Martin, it's me, Dave.
Dave, Dave,
the head was in the bag.
It talked to me Dave,
the head was in the bag!
Look, what happened here, Martin?
Who did this?
The ghost, the ghost.
They took the bones in
the bag and they're gonna
bury them in the cemetery.
Look, Martin,
I want you to call the police,
okay and tell them to
meet me in the cemetery.
I'll call the police and
tell them to meet you at the,
okay, okay Dave,
don't turn the lights out!
I've fallen and I can't get up!
Help me!
Hi!
You made it.
Come Muchacho,
there's no time to waste.
Hey!
Charlie?
That's it, that's it,
it's all over.
You're gonna go stay
at your grandparents'.
Dad..
No, no, no, not a word.
Don't say anything.
I'll get them, I'll..
Don't touch anything,
please, don't touch anything.
From such an educated man,
I had expected
a much more eloquent response.
You're uh?
Don't you recognize me?
You're..
Yes, yes, it is I, Frederico Cavrell,
well you know the rest.
I, I don't believe it.
Come, come Man,
you spent your whole career
looking for me,
don't you have anything
more intelligent to say?
Um, uh, yes, um, could you
tell me about your life, please?
My life?
My life is not important,
it's over.
I'm here to warn you about
your life.
That you're wasting it by
focusing too much on the past.
But, the past is important,
I mean, the things
that you've seen..
Yes, yes, I've seen wondrous things.
I've seen lands where, where
no man has ever been before.
But for all the glory
and all the adventure,
you know the thing that
I regret the most,
is that I never saw my
son grow into a man.
You and I, we spent our whole
life looking for treasure.
What you don't realize is
that the greatest treasure
has been right beside you all along.
I'm sorry, I understand.
I think we should bury his bones.
Gracias Professor.
But what will the
people at the museum say?
Well, uh, I'll replace
them with plaster ones
that I made in the workshop.
They'll never know the difference.
You are a man of honor with
a few tricks of your own.
Bueno, then this is it.
My final adventure.
Well, I was never very good
at goodbyes,
so let's get this over with.
Don't be sad, muchacho,
this is what I wanted.
Are you afraid?
No, I'll be with my son again,
thanks to you Charlie.
This is a fine boy you
have here, Professor.
You take good care of him.
I will, Capitan.
Live a long and prosperous
life, Charlie,
and when the time comes,
I'll see you in paradise.
Goodbye.
Goodbye Charlie, adios!