[ Background Music ]
Aha! Look at that.
Come on now. What do you
think?
Yeah, yeah. Nice shot or
what?
[ Background Music ]
I'm gonna go with hot pink
this week,
oh can you paint those little
Shasta daisies on there.
Oh yeah.
It is summer after all.
[ Laughter ]
That was awesome.
This is what I'm doing all
summer.
Did you girls see what she
was wearing to Ben's party?
I don't even get why he likes
her.
Yeah! Well, maybe we should
bring her shopping
with us next time.
She could obviously use the
help.
Yeah, but shopping is not
gonna help her face.
[ Laughter ]
You're getting pretty
psycho on that bike.
You guys only wish you were
as good.
I'll be sponsored while you're
working fast food.
[ Background Music ]
Hey, you guys are done
today.
Pack it up.
Come in we're setting it up
out back.
Nice, check it out.
Cute
I know.
[ Background Music ]
Who was that?
A friend.
A guy?
Yeah, so?
So we've talked about this.
You're too young to date
and you're way too young to
have a boyfriend.
I can't have a friend who's
a guy?
He looked like more than a
friend to me.
Megan, you're too young.
I'm not playing with you.
Whatever.
Here Mom, these are for
you.
Where did you pick this?
You better not be ruining my
flower beds.
Oh, Cameron, there are bugs on
them.
Take them back outside please?
They're for your party.
Take them outside and then
get downstairs.
I need you to stay down there
until the party is over.
Now go.
[ Background Music ]
Wooh! Where are you going?
Out.
No, I need you to watch
Cameron during the party.
No. You and dad are here.
Besides he's by himself all
the time.
[ Background Music ]
Hey.
It's about time, the party
starts in less than an hour.
I got here as soon as I
could.
Here is your ice.
I don't want it. Take it
outside.
Oh here, here!
Go light the candles?
[ Background Music ]
No, not that one.
You'll ruin it. It's a
decoration.
I never light it.
I meant the ones outside.
Oh, put that out on the
garage.
And I need you back tomorrow
to clean up.
I appreciate you guys
working so hard on that.
I saw you guys.
Love your bracelet.
It is beautiful.
Thank you.
I got them in Bermuda.
Where are you going on your
next vacation?
I don't know.
You know we've been anywhere,
worth seeing...
We have a timeshare that we
plan
to visit before the kids go
back to school.
You're taking the kids with
you?
Sure. Yeah.
We never take the kids.
Too much hassle.
[ Laughter ]
Catered, nice.
Aren't you gonna impress us
with your own cooking, Tara?
Oh, [laughter] I would if I
could.
I don't know how to cook.
I never learned.
Cameron you need to go back
inside.
Go back inside.
I'm hungry.
Oh, I forgot to order the
pizza.
Tara.
Matt, would you go and
order some pizza?
You guys excuse me.
Come on buddy let's get you
something to eat.
[ Background Music ]
[ Doorbell ]
Hey, Josh. What do you
need?
I've been trying to call
you all day.
Yeah, I got your calls.
It's really not a good time.
I got people here.
Do you know that your
company is preparing for
layoffs?
Have you heard anything?
No, I haven't heard
anything
but I'm the vice president of
marketing.
I think if there were
something going on I would
know.
Just keep an eye out.
If there's anything you need
or something I can do, call me.
Alright, alright, I'll do
it. I gotta go.
Read this when you got a
minute.
Alright, I'll do it.
I'll see you later.
[ Background Music ]
What took you so long?
They had me on hold.
Hey, I ate your salmon.
I hope you don't mind.
Yeah, I can see that.
Thanks, Brad.
No problem.
[ Laughter ]
It's intention was to
escape to land but I leaped
into the water and waited oh.
Dad!
How did it go?
What did he say?
He didn't wanna talk.
Well, he's just too proud.
All we could do is pray for
him.
Let's pray.
[ Background Music ]
Father in Heaven, hollowed
be thy name,
our prayers for Matt and his
family.
Please bless Matt that his
heart may be softened,
that he may become a strong,
spiritual leader in his home,
and that he'll accept the love
and support of his family.
He seems to be asking to pray
for,
in the name of thy son, Jesus
Christ, Amen.
Oh, Matt, we forgot about
Cameron.
Would you go check on him?
[ Background Music ]
[ Footsteps ]
Brendan, where have you
been?
[ Laughter and Yelling ]
You should have seen me.
I was catching some serious
air.
Is that what you did all
day?
What about your college
application?
Did you get around the filling
that out today?
[ Background Music ]
Brendan, we were gonna
watch a movie together?
Oh, I know.
I'm sorry, buddy.
Next time, okay?
You clean yourself and go
to bed.
[ Background Music ]
Who ate all the cereal?
I hid that for me.
You can't have all that. Give
me some.
No way.
You always get all the
food!
You gotta be fast.
You two sound like
five-year-olds.
Where are you going, mom?
Mom?
I've gotta go to the store
and then I have a hair
appointment.
What kind of a store?
Can I come with you?
You can go with Brendan.
I can't take him.
The guys will be here any
minute.
Oh, Megan, I guess you're
playing with Cameron today.
Don't even ask. I have
plans.
Oh, and I need to use one of
your credit cards.
Nobody ever takes me.
I'll take you when I go
hiking, buddy.
Where's dad? It's Saturday.
He left before I got up but
I'm pretty sure he went
golfing.
Can I play with Jacob?
No, no one can take you.
I wish I had someone to
play with.
[Background music] Can we have
another baby?
What? What did you say?
Mom cannot have another
baby.
She's way too old.
I am not that old but it
would take a miracle.
Well, I believe in
miracles, don't you?
Look, why don't you go and
play in your room
for a little while, okay?
Or you could play a video game
or watch a movie.
I'm out of here.
Brendan has a new one he
hasn't even seen yet.
Can't you put that on a
dishwasher?
[Laughter] and put the maid
out of a job?
Oh, that's right.
The maid is coming today.
Cameron, can you let her in
when she gets here?
Sure Mom. Thank you.
See you later. Bye.
Guys are here, see you
later buddy.
Bye.
Do you have any kids?
I have a son about your
age.
Can he come play the next
time you come over?
Maybe. Are you home alone
again, Cameron?
Yeah.
[ Background Music ]
Hello?
Hey, buddy.
Where is everybody?
I don't know.
You're all by yourself?
Yeah.
You hungry?
Yes.
Good. More for me and you.
So what did you do today?
I built a really cool model
today.
[ Phone Rings ]
Matt Webster.
Yeah, thanks for calling me
back.
Listen, I don't know if I'm
gonna have
that project done in the
morning.
[ Background Music ]
I would apply if I had any
available credit.
You guys have turned me down
for loan modification and
refinance.
No. Catching up on the
payments is not an option.
I keep telling you, I can't
sell.
The market shifted.
I owe more on the house than
it's worth.
What other options are there?
Foreclosure?
There's gotta be another way.
I have to call you back.
The HR guy is here from
Corporate.
I just saw him down the hall.
What's he doing here?
It can't be good.
You know what, he's
probably here doing an
insurance enrollment.
Maybe. Randy, relax.
We're getting bonuses, right?
We're obviously doing a good
job.
We're indispensable.
Brad and I are going to
lunch.
Do you wanna join us?
I can't. I gotta run an
errand.
Alright.
Dad? Yeah, buddy?
Are we going to go to
church this week?
We didn't go last week.
We didn't?
Yeah, we'll go.
You get dressed. We'll go to
church this week.
Good night, dad.
Good night, Cameron.
[ Steps Approach ]
[ Background Music ]
What's all this?
Just some stuff for the
house.
How much did you spend this
time?
I don't know.
Tara, we need to cut back.
It's not like we can't
afford it.
I'm just saying we need to
be a little more careful
for a while, that's all.
Since when?
Since things are getting a
little tight.
I can barely keep up with the
minimum payments.
Tara, are you even listening
to me?
You need to cut back.
Me? What about you?
You spend just as much as I
do.
Well, we all need to cut
back.
You know what, we're gonna
have a family meeting tomorrow.
Can you please make sure
everybody's here
when I get home from work?
Tara, I'm serious.
No, I can't do it this
time.
You can't or you won't?
Both.
Mom, my house is going into
foreclosure.
Son, I can't keep bailing
you out.
But mom, it's not my fault.
It's the economy. Everybody's
hurting right now.
Not everybody.
Right, Josh. He's perfect.
Everybody can't be Josh, mom.
Josh lives by true
principles.
Besides, you have not changed
the way you're living ever
since I bailed you out.
Matt, I love you too much to
keep enabling you.
How does not helping me
show me love?
I didn't say I wouldn't
help you,
just not the way you're asking
me to.
You need to ask God's guidance
for your family.
What I need is money.
I'm sorry, son.
You're on your own this time.
Catering?
Lights? DJ?
Tara, this is what I'm talking
about.
What is all this?
That's for my 16th
birthday.
We're gonna have to scale
it back or call it off.
No, dad!
You're ruining my life.
Megan, I'm sorry, but we
have to cut back
on unnecessary expenses.
My birthday's unnecessary?
It's not just you.
We all have to cut back.
We have to stop spending so
much money.
[ Background Music ]
[ Phone Buzzes ]
Not now, Josh?
[ Background Music ]
[ Phone Rings ]
Matt Webster.
Matt, mom just called.
She's concerned.
She wanted me to call and
offer some financial advice.
Josh, you don't know when
to quit.
I don't need any help from
you.
If wanted financial advice,
I'd pay you for it.
Now, leave me alone.
You have got to see this.
Come outside.
Not right now, Brad. I'm
busy.
It's awesome.
You gotta see what we did at
lunch.
Come on.
What's going on? You're not
yourself lately.
I've got a lot of work to
do, busy.
I don't have time to be out.
You will forget all about
that when you see this.
What is it?
Check it out.
Come on.
This is yours?
Yeah, it's mine.
You bought this?
It's what I said.
Just picked it up.
What about the layoff
rumors?
You're not worried about that?
No. I decided to buy it now
though just in case.
Without a job, I couldn't get
a loan it.
So you bought a car knowing
you may not be able
to afford it?
Sure, but all will last,
right?
This is a nice chunk of
change.
What about your kids' college
education?
I don't have kids.
Yeah, you do, Brad.
They're not my kids.
They're my wife's.
Her ex can deal with that.
Obviously, nothing's
changed around here.
Cameron, where's everybody?
I don't know.
Have you eaten anything?
No.
Come on, let's make a
sandwich.
So you haven't seen Megan
or Brendan?
You should have seen me, I
got a 40-minute flight.
It was so awesome.
Brendan, are you gonna play
all your life?
When are you gonna get a job?
Dad, I can help make a
sandwich.
And Megan, where have you
been?
Spending every dime we have?
You're as bad as your mother.
What's with you?
You know what?
What's with all of you?
You don't seem to care about
anything but yourselves.
Dad, what's wrong?
All of you just go to your
room.
Enjoy it. You may not have one
next week.
I said go!
[ Background Music ]
I can help you put your
financial house
in order according to biblical
principles.
Read Romans 13:8 and Proverbs
21:20.
Josh. Okay, Josh wise man.
[ Background Music ]
Owe no man anything but to
love one another for he
that loveth blah blah blah
blah blah.
[ Background Music ]
There is treasure to be
desired and oil in the dwelling
of the wise; but a foolish
man.
Great, now I'm a fool.
Thanks, Josh.
I don't wanna go home.
Summer's way too long and my
kids are driving me crazy.
Tell me about it, I cannot
for mine to go back to school.
Yeah.
I'm feeling bad for
Cameron.
He has no one to play with.
Seriously?
Can't you just get him a
nanny?
Excuse me.
Your credit card was declined.
It shouldn't be.
Maybe the strips worn off off.
Hold on. Try this one.
So when do your kids start
school again.
Oh.
This one is declined too.
That's weird.
Okay, I know this one is
alright.
[ Background Music ]
Declined.
Do you have another form of
payment?
[ Background Music ]
[ Coins Falling Out ]
Here, I've got it.
[ Background Music ]
What is going on?
I've been waiting to ask
you the same question.
You just can't wait to go out
and spend every chance you get.
Oh, don't worry, I couldn't
spend a thing.
What do you mean couldn't?
Declined.
Do you have any idea how
humiliating it is
to get declined, especially in
front of my friends?
And not just this card,
three cards.
Everyone in the restaurant was
staring at me.
What is going on? And what is
so funny?
Well, Tara, obviously,
we're over the limit.
What are you doing?
I told you we had to stop
spending.
No, you said we had to cut
back.
No, I said we had to stop
spending.
When were you gotta tell me
about the house?
When we're out of the street?
What difference does it
make?
There's nothing you can do
about it.
No definitely not now, but
I live here too,
I deserve to know about this.
Well now you know.
When did we get so far
behind on the house?
The mortgage adjusted 6
months ago.
We're making twice the
payment.
I don't make that much money
Tara.
We're just not making it.
Well, can we borrow against
the house or refinance?
Don't you get it?
That's how we got in this mess
to begin with.
We keep borrowing against the
house
to pay off the credit cards.
As soon as they're paid off,
they get run right back up
again.
We don't have any money, we
don't have any credit.
And our house is being
foreclosed on.
[ Background Music ]
[ Birds Chirping ]
Dad.
What Cameron?
Lets go to church.
Can't really, Cameron. I'm
too tired.
You said you would take me.
I know buddy.
I had to work late last night
though.
Tara, why don't you take him?
I'm not going if you're
not.
Cameron, I'll take you next
week, alright?
Just go on and get some
breakfast.
[ Background Music ]
[ Phone Chirping ]
Hey Matt, I know, I don't
know when to quit
but I was thinking about you
and felt prompted to call.
I just wanted to encourage you
to read Luke 12, today.
Call me if you need anything,
okay, that's all.
Read Luke 12.
[ Stop Message Click ]
[ Background Music ]
What are you doing dad?
I'm taking some pictures of
some of our stuff.
I have to put some ads on the
internet.
Could I help?
Yeah, you know what?
Go tell everybody there's
gonna be another family
meeting,
alright?
Okay.
[ Background Music ]
Look, we're not getting
anywhere with our debt.
We still owe too much.
On what?
On everything Tara, between
the house, the boat, the RV,
the dirt bikes, we're paying
thousands
of dollars a month and we
don't have it.
So you're saying we're
selling our stuff?
Technically it's not our
stuff.
We don't own any of it.
We Owen a bunch of payments.
My dirt bikes?
They gotta go.
You can't sell those, I use
those.
You didn't pay for them
Brendan.
When you can afford your own,
you're welcome to have one.
What about the house?
I'm trying to sell it.
I'm also waiting on a bonus
from work.
If I can get it by next week,
we might be able
to keep out of foreclosure.
We're losing the house?
As of now.
Look, everyone's gonna have to
start
and take an initiative here,
and Brendan quit doodling
in that sketch book, you need
to get a job!
Dad, don't you think we
should pray
to see what God wants us to
do?
[ Background Music ]
[ Pages Turning ]
[ Singing ]
Tara, I need to talk to
you.
The landscaper quit, my last
my last check to him bounced.
And I had to let the maid go.
You did what?
Come on Tara, we can barely
afford to eat.
Some things have to change
around here.
You know we can afford a maid.
So, who's gonna clean up
around here?
Oh, you know I can't.
You know she can't.
The two of you have to
figure it out together.
Oh.
[ Footsteps ]
[ Background Music ]
[ Phone Dialing ]
Dad!
Yes Megan?
My phone is broken.
It's not broken, Megan.
We only need my phone for
work, yours is expendable.
Expendable?
Thanks for ruining my life.
Josh, what do you want?
Are you ready to talk yet?
Matt, I'm a financial adviser.
Don't you think I can help my
brother?
What do you know?
I know you're in trouble.
I love you, I just wanna help.
You know what?
You think you're so much
better than me.
You just can't wait to rub it
in.
I don't butt into your life, I
don't tell you how
to live or what to do.
All I ever get from you is
judgment.
Judgment? What?
and your self-righteous life,
I'm over it.
Matt, I'm only here because
I care about you.
I wish you could see that.
Look, when you're ready talk,
I'll be here,
that's what brothers do.
Josh, if I want your help,
I'll ask for it.
[ Background Music ]
Excuse me, what you are
doing?
We're repossessing your
vehicle ma'am.
What for?
Well, it says here, due to
non payment.
You can't have it.
Jim, what about the
bonuses?
About my bonus?
As a CEO I'm not even
planning on one.
The economy has hit us hard
and unexpectedly.
Our biggest deals are backing
out.
Jim, you don't understand,
I need this bonus.
Besides I thought they were
based
on last quarter's performance.
What would have been
bonuses are now what we're
operating on.
Listen Matt, I came here to
talk to you about tightening
up the marketing department.
Tightening up?
On what? Jobs?
Expenses?
We're on a hiring freeze.
Nobody gets promoted, nobody's
getting a raise,
nobody is getting a bonus.
Look, you're lucky it's not
any worse.
The sales department is being
restructured.
[ Background Music ]
Well, it's done.
No bonus.
[ Background Music ]
[ Doorbell ]
Matt Webster?
Yeah?
I'm a representative from
your mortgage holder.
I've been authorized to give
you cash for keys.
It's a relocation program.
So what, you're offering
money to leave my house?
Technically, it's not your
house.
It's been foreclosed on, so if
you leave the property
in its current condition and
be out within 10 days,
the bank will provide you with
a check.
You have 24 hours to decide.
You know what?
Do you have a pen?
Sure.
[ Background Music ]
[ Pages Turning ]
Hey Josh, it's Matt.
Yeah, look, this isn't easy
for me.
I don't know what else to do.
I keep it hidden from my
friends.
Hey everybody!
Uncle Matt and his family are
gonna stay with us for a while.
They'll be here this weekend.
Yes! Yeah!
Can Cameron stay in my
room?
He sure can.
Josh, can I talk to you for
a minute?
Sarah, keep reading this. I'll
be right back.
[ Pages Turning ]
Does Tara know about this?
I guess so. Matt's calling
about it.
Why?
Josh, you know she doesn't
like me.
I just don't see this going
over very well.
They don't have anywhere
else to go.
Mom's condo is too small.
I know.
I don't have a problem with
it.
It's just it's going to be
hard, really hard.
We have the room.
It's not what I mean.
What's wrong?
I just didn't know it would
be so hard.
I don't wanna leave.
I know.
I mean, I know we have to
but it's just hard.
Who would have thought when
we moved
in here it would be like this?
We had everything ahead of us.
But you know what, Tara, we
still do.
I'm kind of excited to see
what the future holds.
I don't know how you can be
so positive.
I'm just trying to have
faith, I guess.
You need to read Luke 12.
It really helped.
But we're losing our house.
Look at it this way.
Adam and Eve suffered the
ultimate eviction.
We're just losing our house.
Just losing our house?
I know it sounds crazy.
I'm just finally starting
to realize we don't own any of
this.
It all belongs to God.
[ Background Music ]
Well, I don't know what to
say.
I really we really appreciate
all of your help.
I don't know what we would
have done
if you guys hadn't come today.
Thank you.
[ Background Music ]
I can't even count how many
times I have chased Cameron
through this kitchen.
I can count we had dinner
together.
Cameron, that's not funny.
Megan thought so.
Alright guys, time to go.
[ Background Music ]
Come on Mom.
Look, Josh says they have
plenty of room.
It's gonna be fine.
I feel weird about this.
Tara, it's only temporary.
[ Door Bell ]
Hey, Josh. Come on in.
Hey! Hi guys!
Welcome.
Hi, Sarah.
Good to see you all.
They're ready for bed.
Oh, we're gonna have a lot
of fun.
So much fun...
I'll tell you guys real quick
where you're staying
and then you can both go bring
your things in, okay?
It sounds great.
Okay. Matt and Tara,
we've got you downstairs in
the guest room.
Megan, we've got you set up on
the sofa
in the basement living room.
Brendan, we've got you set
up in the private playhouse
suite out back.
And Cameron, you get to stay
with Jacob in his room.
Yey! A playhouse?
Oh yeah, it's great.
There's electricity out there
and you've got all to yourself.
You only need to come in for
the bathroom.
Thanks. He'll love it.
You guys make yourselves at
home.
There's towels in the closet,
food in the fridge,
and you're welcome to join us
for any activities
that we're doing, okay? We
will.
Thank you guys for everything.
We really do appreciate this.
It's been a long day though.
I think we're gonna go and hit
the bed.
Alright?
We're about to have family
prayer,
would you like to join us? >>
Oh, no, that's okay.
We'll just see you in the
morning.
Alright, guys, good night.
Thank you again.
See you in the morning.
Jacob, please show Brendan
where he'll be staying.
You're so lucky Brendan.
I never get to stay out in the
playhouse.
[ Background Music ]
I don't know if I can take
it.
I have no privacy and Rachel
is way too nice.
She bugs me.
Why don't you go take a
shower and wind down.
Rachel said the towels are in
the hall.
Mom, dad, come check this
out.
[ Background Music ]
What's with the grocery
store in their basement?
Megan get out of there.
You can ask them about it
tomorrow.
I don't wanna ask them.
They think I'm snooping.
You ask.
You are snooping.
What am I gonna do here all
day tomorrow?
I going to be totally bored.
You see how many kids are
here,
the last thing you'll be is
bored.
Tortured maybe, but not bored.
[ Birds Chirping ]
[ Background Music ]
Hey. [ Laughter ]
[ Stirring ]
[ Background Music ]
Do you want a pancake? >>
Breakfast?
Yeah, do you want one?
I have two ready for you
right here.
Thanks. You can eat it.
We already had the prayer.
What time did you all get
up?
6:30.
What have you been doing
since 6:30?
The usual; prayer,
scriptures,
chores, and now breakfast.
But it's barely 9.
Yeah, we slept in a little
today.
We usually get up at 6 o'clock
so we're all done
with breakfast by 8:30.
Where is my mom?
I haven't seen her up yet.
What about Brendan?
He should be probably
playing out in the playhouse.
He's so lucky.
[ Background Music ]
What? Are you here for tea
party?
What are you doing today?
I've gotta get out of here.
Gavin is picking me up in
his two-seat truck.
There's no room for you.
Ride in the back?
Nope. Have fun.
[ Background Music ]
Jacob, Sarah, dinner duty.
What's my job.
Setting and clearing the
table.
Jacob, it is your night to
help me fix dinner.
Could I help? Sure.
Go wash your hands and I'll
get you started
on chopping the vegetables for
the salad.
[ Background Music ]
That's my spot.
I can't do it. I feel so
out of place.
Tell me about it. Move.
[ Background Music ]
Amen.
Cameron, did you tell your
parents we're ready to eat?
Yeah, I told them.
I don't know what's taking
them so long.
[ Background Music ]
I'm gonna grab a plate for
Megan and Tara,
they're not feeling well.
It looks great.
There you go. Thanks.
[ Background Music ]
Maybe tomorrow.
Here. Eat it.
I can't live like this.
I feel totally trapped.
You're not the only one.
Brendan!
[ Birds Chirping ]
Has anyone seen Brendan?
He left early.
Here, can you hold her for
a minute while I get something?
[ Baby Cries ]
Come on.
[ Background Music ]
Tara.
What do you say we clean up
this mess?
[ Background Music ]
I know this has to be hard
for you to come stay here
with us but I really think
you'll feel better
if you had something to do.
I'm doing something.
I can see that.
What we need to do though is
straighten this mess.
It's depressing isn't it?
I'll take these plates up.
Could you finish picking up
the trash?
[ Background Music ]
[ Birds Chirping ]
There. I think this area is
clear enough to vacuum.
I'll go plug it in for you.
[ Background Music ]
[ Vacuum Turns On ]
Thanks.
You can put it in the
garage.
[ Background Music ]
It would be great if we
could eat as a family tonight.
I have some errands to run
with Matt gets home with the
car.
Oh, Okay.
Matt, we need to talk.
Not now Tara.
I wanna go back.
Go back where?
We have no place to go.
And you know we can't afford
anything else right now.
Then get a higher paying
job.
You have to do something.
Oh, I can't live like this
anymore.
Come on, Tara, you've gonna
figure
out a way to make this work.
It's not gonna kill you to
help out.
You think you have it bad?
I'm staying in a playhouse.
I'm so embarrassed to be
here.
My friends will even drive by
here to pick me up.
Do you hear this Matt? We
hate it here.
Do you know what I hear?
Ungrateful spoiled brats.
Don't you guys get it?
Our lives have changed.
This is where we live, this is
how we live.
I don't wanna hear anymore
complaining.
You think you hated here?
Trust me you'd hate the
alternative a lot more.
I don't think any of you are
cut out to live in a cardboard
box.
I can't do this.
[ Background Music ]
It's too hard.
[ Birds Chirping ]
Megan, I would prefer that
you
and your mom ate at the table.
Letting you eat downstairs is
setting a bad example
since our house rule is if
you're healthy
and able, you eat at the
table.
[ Birds Chirping ]
Where is breakfast?
Rachel wants us to eat at
the table.
What? Oh, of course,
we've just been waiting for
her to do this.
She wasn't rude about it.
Oh! She's never rude.
She's just I'm so sick of it
here.
Me too.
Cameron is having a good
time enough.
She just thinks she's so
perfect with her chickens
and her garden and her grocery
store in the basement.
[ Background Music ]
As for my chickens, my
garden, and my grocery store?
How do you think I'm feeding
all of you?
My grocery store, as you call
it, is stores that will feed us
in case of an emergency.
We're glad to help you because
we have food to share.
That's not what I meant, I
was just
I know.
You are used to something else
at your house.
And I'm sorry, you don't have
one anymore.
I am happy to have you here.
I could just use a little more
help.
[ Background Music ]
I'll put this away.
Thank you.
Dinner is at 6 and I need
your help to fix it at 4:30.
Alright.
[ Background Music ]
[ Tearful Gasps ]
Father in heaven.
Please help me to have
patience and love and show
kindness.
And please help me to know how
I can help Tara.
In Jesus name, amen.
[ Background Music ]
Hey, can you help me peel
these?
We added your names to the
Webster family job chart today
so tomorrow, your family will
have job assignments just
like our family.
Hey, after breakfast we'll
finish our history project,
Okay? Yey!
Do your kids get excited
over a history project?
Aren't you afraid all this
home schooling is making them a
little socially backward?
Excuse me?
Well, I mean they spend all
day with you, you teach them,
I just thought maybe
Tara, are you insinuating
that I'm socially backwards?
No. Never mind.
What are my jobs?
You have dishes, which is
unloading and loading all day,
vacuuming the upstairs and the
basement area and garden duty.
What's garden duty?
Watering the garden,
pulling the weeds,
picking the ripe vegetables.
And how do I know when the
vegetables are ripe?
I'll send Sarah out to help
you.
And Megan you have the
bathrooms and taking out the
garbage okay.
I can do that.
Do you think if Megan
and I finish it quickly we
could borrow the car to run an
errand?
I think that would be fine.
I'll ask Josh if he needs his
car.
We need to keep ours here in
case I need
to leave with the kids.
Okay great.
And what about Brendan, what's
he doing?
He'll be mowing the lawn.
[ Chickens Clucking ]
[ Background Music ]
Oh, don't pull that one,
that's a squash.
Sorry.
Here pull the ones that
looks like this.
[ Background Music ]
What happened?
I don't know something
touched me a bug
or a spider, something.
This?
Oh.
This is a rolly roly-poly
bug.
It won't hurt you, look he
plays dead.
Oh, so it's nice.
Yeah. It's cute too don't
you think?
Sure.
[ Background Music ]
Here, Mom wants the
cucumber before we go inside.
You can bring one in.
We are done weeding.
[ Background Music ]
That's a zucchini, here
take one of these.
[ Background Music ]
It's Tara.
[Laughter] Hey.
No, I'm not on vacation.
No I'm sure I told you where I
was, didn't I?
Oh no well, anyway no I just
I've been dying to get out
and I just wondered if maybe
you wanted to join Megan and me
for a girls day out today.
Oh why not.
Are you gonna be with your
in-laws all day?
So there's no way you can go?
Oh, okay, no, we'll we'll miss
you.
Oh yeah definitely, yeah
we'll, no we'll try it another
time,
okay, okay, alright, bye-bye.
[ Background Music ]
There's about 300 dollars
worth in this pile.
Yep thats about my pile
too.
So after we return these
can we spend any of it?
Maybe a little, but I think
dad will be impressed
if we gave him a bunch of
cash.
I do you think we can afford a
quick pedicure though.
Yes.
Cameron. What?
Come here.
I'm going rock climbing with
the guys today.
You remember when I said I'd
take you next time?
Yeah.
Well, do you wanna go?
Really?
Yeah, the guys will be here
in a few minutes, can you be
ready?
Sure. Can Jacob go?
I don't think there's gonna
be enough room this time
with all the guys and gear.
How about taking Jacob next
time?
Okay.
Alright, I'm gonna go get
the stuff.
[ Background Music ]
I just saw the HR guy here
again.
Randy, relax, it's the
sales department.
It's getting restructured.
So he is here to do
layoffs.
For the sales department.
Well, we're safe, right?
Yeah, as far as I know.
[ Keys In Pocket Jingle ]
We should eat there after,
do you want to?
Okay, yeah, sounds good.
What? Mom, what is going
on?
Why are we leaving? We have an
appointment.
Let's climb here.
It's been a while since we've
taken this route.
I've never soloed it.
Dude, that's tough.
It's pretty gnarly at the end.
You don't have any overhang?
You took a couple of falls on
it before.
Yeah but, that was when I
was first figuring it out.
Now it's like a puzzle I've
done a million times.
I know just how to do it.
Just climb with Trad,
Brendan.
I brought my canopy.
Nah, I know I can do it.
[ Phone Rings ]
Matt Webster.
Sure, when do you want to do
that?
Yeah, I can come right now.
Okay, bye.
[ Background Music ]
Watch this Cameron.
Push it on the over hang.
Come on Brendan, you can make
it.
Get up there.
Hey.
That was awesome.
You guys thought I couldn't
make it.
Cameron, did you see that?
Cameron?
Yeah, thanks for coming in.
Yeah.
I hate to be the bearer of
bad news
but you know there's been cut
backs
and it's affecting your
department.
Cameron, hold still.
Cameron.
Don't move.
You guys try and get up.
I'm gonna try and get down.
Help!
[ Background Music ]
[ Rocks Slipping ]
Brendan.
Aaahh!
Cameron!
Matt, Brendan just called.
Cameron was in an accident. >>
What?
They're at the hospital.
Where is Tara? She's not
here.
I'll bring her when she gets
back.
Tell her I'll meet her at
the hospital.
[ Background Music ]
Brendan, what happened?
It's all my fault.
What happened?
I took him rock climbing, I
wasn't watching him,
I didn't know he would climb
up the rope, he fell.
Come here.
[ Background Music ]
Dad? Can we pray?
Yeah, I think we should.
[ Background Music ]
Lord I know I don't deserve
your help.
Please, don't take my child
Lord.
We're losing everything,
please don't take my child
[crying].
Please, I'll do what ever I
have to.
Please don't take him away.
In Jesus name.
[ Background Music ]
Tara, Cameron is in the
hospital.
Wha-what?
Josh call your mom, we're
on our way.
What hap what happened?
He's been hurt.
I'll tell you on the way, I'll
drive.
[ Background Music ]
Any news?
Not yet.
He's still in surgery.
[ Background Music ]
Brendan and I have been
praying.
I have been too.
I think he's gonna be okay.
How do you know?
Just trying to have faith.
When can we see him?
We don't know.
He is still in surgery, it
could be hours.
[ Background Music ]
Are you the parents of
Cameron Webster?
Yes.
We were able to mend and
repair Cameron pretty well.
He's stable right now and I
think he's going to be okay.
When can we see him?
He is sedated right now.
The best thing you can do is
to go home and get some sleep.
He'll be groggy in the morning
but should be ready to accept
visitors.
Thank you Lord for saving
my son.
Did you realize what a good
kid he is?
He's always been so good,
he's easy to forget.
He's just never asked for
much.
He's always entertaining
himself and never was any
trouble.
Realizing that I don't know
any of 'em.
They're growing up so fast.
Soon they're gone and I've
missed it.
It's like I went to sleep.
I don't know when it happened.
I guess this is my wake up
call.
You know why I wasn't home
today, shopping.
Megan and I hit a sale while
my son could have died.
Just makes me sad to think of
how much
of my life was spent doing
unimportant things.
I guess we both got
regrets.
I know we've been doing
this wrong,
but I gotta believe we can do
it better.
I feel like we're getting a
second chance here, Tara.
I don't wanna blow it.
Yesterday I was worried about
where we're gonna live
but I am just grateful to be
alive.
Family is everything.
We gotta start putting it
first.
Look at this.
I found it when I was going
through some things with
Cameron.
Who's is this?
Brendan's.
I didn't know he could draw
like this.
Me neither.
It's incredible.
[ Background Music ]
Buddy, you're awake?
Cameron.
I've never been so happy to
see you.
We bought you some things
honey.
Let's put 'em right here,
alright?
Thanks Mom.
Hey buddy listen the
doctors say you need
to get your rest okay, so
we're not gonna stay.
We'll be back later though.
Alright, get some sleep. Glad
you're feeling better.
[ Background Music ]
I'm so sorry Cameron, can
you forgive me?
[ Moan ]
We love you buddy.
[ Background Music ]
It wasn't your fault.
It was pretty dumb of me.
Brendan, you're being too
hard on yourself.
I knew better.
I'm so stupid.
I wasn't tied in dad.
I soloed it and showed Cameron
by my bad example
that it was okay to climb
without a rope.
He didn't know any better.
You made a mistake.
It's ironic, you don't know
how well you just summed up my
life.
What?
Brendan, you were trying to
look good for your friends.
Try to impress them.
That's what I was trying to
do.
You pushed yourself, ignored
all the risks,
all for your own glory.
That's what I did too.
The only difference is when I
fell I took all of us with me.
Do you realize we lost
everything because of my pride?
So what now?
We tie in and climb again.
This time though we can trust
in our own ability
and we can't do it for our
glory.
This time we gotta do it for
God's glory.
Brendan, the mistake we made
was,
we thought we could do
for ourselves what we can only
do through the Lord.
Does that make sense?
It's gonna be okay.
Cameron's strong, he's gonna
pull out in this, I love you.
And you know what?
I saw your sketch book, I hope
that's all right.
Brendan, I really liked it.
You have some amazing talent.
I'm sorry I didn't see it
sooner.
[ Background Music ]
Matt, what's going on?
Well, with all that's been
happening,
I haven't had a chance to give
you the bad news.
About Cameron?
No, not about Cameron.
But I did lose my job.
I got laid off yesterday.
Look, Tara, I know what you're
thinking but I feel blessed,
we have place to live.
I don't know what I would've
done if I had to lost my job
and the house at the same
time.
Does this mean that we have
to stay here even longer?
Not necessarily.
Josh has some ideas on how to
get me back
on my feet financially.
I just didn't want you to
stress about it.
Well, I don't know what
else could upset me now.
So you won't mind that I'm
selling the Audi?
Oh, Matt.
Don't worry, we're gonna
get another car soon.
This time it's gonna be cash.
[ Background Music ]
[ Knocks ]
Come in.
Okay little brother, I'm
ready to learn.
About time [laughter].
I've been watching you.
You're so patient with the
kids.
I don't know how you do it.
Patience takes practice and
I get plenty of it.
I also read Proverbs 31 all
the time for help.
Proverbs 31.
It's where God describes
what a virtuous woman is.
Oh yeah.
I remember that chapter.
You know Rachel, watching you
has made me remember why I
wanted kids.
[Background music] Cameron was
just such a surprise.
He's just I've just been in
shock
or I think maybe even denial
ever since.
Just wasn't prepared for any
of it.
But I wanna live Proverbs 31.
[ Background Music ]
You will.
I also like the scripture,
"children are inherited
to the Lord" Psalms 3 7:3.
I need that daily reminder.
I love that, I need to live
that.
I'm sorry.
I I'm sorry.
I've been so horrible to you.
It's okay, I loved you
anyway.
[ Background Music ]
[ Laughter ]
Let your light so shine
before men,
that they may see your good
works
and glorify your Father which
is in heaven.
I don't know Josh.
You're saying I gotta use
savings for everything
that my check doesn't cover?
Yes. Without savings you
can never get ahead,
and you only get deeper in
debt.
It's a vicious cycle.
And you're serious?
Your house is paid for?
Yes. And you can do it too.
It only takes discipline and a
plan, small amounts add up
fast.
Mom, these are for you.
Oh, Elijah, these are
beautiful.
Thank you, buddy.
Mwah. I'm gonna put this on a
special place
so everyone can see 'em.
Thanks, buddy.
[ Stirring ]
I know I need to start
saving [background music]
but I don't know how to do it
right now, especially now.
I'm doing everything I can.
I got my resume out there, but
nobody's hiring.
[ Background Music ]
What do you selling today?
Oh, look at the lizards we
made dad.
They're only a dollar.
You want one? No.
I want all seven.
All seven?
Yeah, have you thought of
marketing as an independent?
Okay, that would be 7
dollars please.
Thank you.
I have enough money to go
to the pool.
You mean go into business
for myself?
I wouldn't even know where
to start.
Business is providing
something other's want
in exchange for money or
barter.
That's it. You can do that.
Nothing is that simple
Josh.
Sure it is.
It's so simple the kids
could do it.
Sarah has more cash
at her disposal then I do most
of the time.
Yeah, but where I'm gonna
find business?
Business is everywhere.
Individuals, mom and pop
shops, nonprofits,
Fortune 500 companies, they
all need marketing.
They all need your services.
I can't think of anybody
who needs my services right
now.
You know what?
I can. Come on, I want
to introduce you to your first
client.
Andrew, you got a minute?
Yeah, sure.
[ Background Music ]
I wanted to introduce you
to my brother.
Andrew, this is Matt.
I like your bumper sticker.
Yeah, I'm somewhat of a
collector.
So what's up?
Matt is in marketing.
I thought he could help your
business.
Really?
Well, that's great.
But I don't know that I can
afford any marketing yet.
Well, what if we work out a
deal similar to what you
and I did and barter your
services for now.
Sounds good.
What do you got in mind?
Matt is gonna be buying a
cheap car with cash.
It's gonna need some work.
You get his car running.
He'll get your business
running.
Alrighty.
It's a deal.
Let's do it. Really?
Yeah. Absolutely.
Can I ask you a few
questions?
Sure, go for it.
What's the name of your
business?
Mobile Motto.
I do on-site repairs.
Well, I don't have a shop yet.
How do you advertise?
Word of mouth, referrals.
So no website or anything?
No, no website.
I think I can definitely
step up your business, Andrew.
Sounds good. Looking
forward to it.
Hey, dad. Check this out.
What you got, buddy?
Wow! Nice work.
That's amazing.
Do you wanna see the logo I
made for Josh's business?
Yeah!
Brendan, that is great.
That's professional.
You know what, you should be
my partner.
I'll do the marketing, you do
the design work.
What do you think?
I'd love that dad.
I'll make you proud.
Brendan, I'm already proud
of you.
[ Knock At Door ]
Hi! Hi, Lori, come on
in.
Hey. Andrew told me your
brother
and sister in-law are staying
here
and I just wanna introduce
myself.
Tara's in the other room.
I'll go get her.
Go ahead and take a seat.
Hi. Hi.
I'm Lori. Andrew's wife.
Oh, okay.
Owners of Mobile Motto, right?
Yeah, yeah. That's why I'm
here.
Oh, okay.
I am so excited about the
amount of work
that Andrew's been getting
since your husband started his
marketing business.
He's been getting a lot of
business?
Almost more than he could
handle.
It is such a blessing!
Oh, that's great.
And just a real answer to
our prayers.
I wanted to let you know that
we have referred you
on to several other of our
friend and they're trying
to get their business started
too.
Really? Wow! That's great.
I really appreciate it.
Thanks.
Thank you really.
If there's anything that I can
do for you please let me know.
Thanks, I will.
Oh, and I baked you this
bread as a thank you.
You bake bread?
Yeah.
Now that is something that
you could do for me.
I would love to learn how to
make bread.
I would love to teach you
anytime.
Okay.
Hey, Josh?
Hey, Rachel, have you seen
Josh?
He's out on a date.
Yeah, he takes the kids out
once a week on daddy date.
He's out with Sarah right now.
What do they do on their
dates?
Different things each week.
He usually let's the kids
choose the activity.
You know how cheap Josh is.
He finds fun and endless
things to do for free.
You know what, you just
give me the inspiration I was
praying for.
I'll see you later.
[ Background Music ]
Hey Pal. What are you
working on?
Wow! That's amazing!
Matthew 5:16.
Why did you choose that?
Well, Cameron read it to me
when I visited him.
It really touched him and it
did the same to me.
You did an amazing job
capturing it in your drawings.
Well, this is me, dad.
Before Cameron's accident, I
wasn't doing anything bad
but I wasn't really doing
anything good either.
Not doing anything bad and
doing good are very different
things.
You know what, you're
right.
You're not the only one that's
learning that.
Wait a second, Brendan. That's
it.
Good works.
Good Works Marketing and
Design.
It's a perfect name for our
family business.
What do you think?
I like it.
You get started on the
logo.
We're in business.
You just have to take it
from here.
I don't know Josh.
I don't want to blow it again.
You're ready.
You're on the right track
spiritually and financially.
Yeah, but what if the work
is not there
and I can't afford the rent?
I can't let my family fall
again.
I'm not saying that it's
going to be easy
or that you won't struggle but
you have to have faith.
Josh, faith is the hardest
part.
You understand what didn't
work.
Now you understand God's laws,
all you have
to do is apply what you've
learned and what you know.
That's easy for you to say.
You're naturally a better
father and leader than I am.
I don't know if I have what it
takes.
That's fear speaking and it
will only shut you down.
Forget it.
Concentrate on the vision you
have for your family.
What if I don't have a
vision for my family?
I mean concentrate on the
big picture, your role as a
father.
I don't understand what my
role
as a father has to do with it.
Your role as a father is to
preside over, provide for
and protect his family.
If you do those three things
to the best of your ability
and with the help of the lord
you will be the kind of leader
and father God wants in your
home.
How does my little brother
have all the answers?
I don't but I know where to
find them.
God's way.
[ Background Music ]
You know what Josh there's
something I got to do.
I'll see you later.
[ Background Music ]
[ Crickets ]
[ Laughter ]
Dad, where are we going?
It's a surprise hence the
blindfold.
Okay, go to the right grass.
[ Background Music ]
Right there.
Wow!
I know it's not what you
expected but it's all for you.
Sweetheart, I can't believe
you're 16 years old.
It seems like just yesterday
your mom
and I held you for the first
time.
You were so little.
Now you're a beautiful young
woman
and I'm very blessed to be
your dad.
Thanks dad.
I got something for you.
This ring represents my love
for you.
It's a symbol of my love and
my commitment to lead you.
It's also a reminder that your
heart belongs to me
until the day a worthy man
comes along and takes you in
marriage
and gives you a ring that
symbolizes his love
and commitment for you.
I love you dad.
I love you too.
Happy birthday!
And I promise you'll have a
real party soon, okay?
Okay!
Let's eat.
I got you your favorites.
I hope you're hungry.
Yes, I am.
[ Background Music ]
* The greatest house, the
finest cars. *
* Have we lost sight in who we
are? *
* When worldly gain is all we
see, our life's on sinking
sand. *
* Our life's on sinking sand.
*
* All is gone lost sight in
what is true. *
* Now we look to you, yes we
look to you. *
* Stand strong as our world is
fading, stand strong *
* in Christ, our foundation.
* Stand strong even in
adversity surrounding us *
* in tragedy, we'll stand
strong. *
[ Laughter ]
[ Inaudible Remark ]
[ Background Music ]
* Life is crashing down on us
*
* and all these false
stability's *
* Our hopes and dreams
Hey, can I get everybody's
attention?
I'm glad you guys came,
Cameron is home.
Yey! [ Applause ]
[ Cheers ]
* All is gone lost sight in
what is true. *
* Now we look to you, yes we
look to you. *
* Stand strong as our world is
fading, stand strong *
* in Christ, our foundation.
* Stand strong even in
adversities surrounding us *
* in tragedy, we'll stand
strong. *
Well, the summer started
with the party
and it's ending with one too.
It's summer I won't forget.
It's too bad Cameron's gotta
go back to school so soon.
Well, actually if you
approve I was thinking maybe
he wouldn't?
What?
I've seen too much of a
lifestyle I've grown to love.
I love it way too much to go
back to the old way.
What do you mean?
I'd like to home school
him.
Really?!
I've missed too much of his
childhood.
I don't want to miss another
minute.
I think it's a great idea.
Really?
[ Background Music ]
[ Inaudible Remarks ]
Hey, what do you guys think
of my new ride?
Oh. Wow!
[ Laughter ] That's great.
Check it out.
Megan, what do you think?
Do you still wanna drive my
car?
Oh yeah?
Oh, I almost forgot
something.
I got something for you.
Oh that's perfect.
Look at that.
[ Laughter ]
Well, I'm wanna take you
for a ride.
Come on. Let's go.
Right now? Yup! Just
mom.
Oh!
Alright, we wont wait up.
Alright.
Mint chocolate chip?
Thank you.
Just like our first date.
You remember that?
What kind of shake I had?
Why wouldn't I?
This is where it all began.
We were two kids drinking our
milk shakes
and finding our lives
together.
Here we are again almost 20
years later.
Drinking milk shakes and
starting over,
this time with a new plan.
A new plan.
We could do this, Tara.
I wanna do it different this
time.
This time I want to give you
my best.
This time I wanna give God my
best.
I promise we'll make it work.
[ Background Music ]
Well
Alright, Cameron, you're on
the first row, okay?
This is it. First pick!
[ Laughter ]
Nice.
What do you think?
It's awesome.
Hand me those crutches.
Help you out, buddy?
You guys wanna go pick out
your bed rooms.
Oh yeah. Yes.
[ Laughter ]
Well, we made it.
Tonight is our last night at
Josh and Rachel's.
I think I'm actually gonna
miss it.
Come on.
Wait till you see the inside.
And the question is will it
all fit?
You can always put Brendan
out in a tent.
[ Laughter ]
Josh, I don't know how to
thank you.
You don't have to. That's
what families do.
I think you know that now.
Yeah, but I really
appreciate it.
Can I go home yet? [
Laughter ]
No, I don't appreciate that
much.
We got more work to do.
Oh, Rachel.
This is what you taught me.
The most important things in
life aren't things.
Aren't things.
Amen!
And the best part is I got
it at a yard sale for 2
dollars.
That's almost free.
Dad?
Yeah, honey?
You're right.
I don't need a boyfriend.
I just wanna let you know.
That's my girl.
I'm proud of you sweetheart.
Matt?
Yeah, mom?
I love you.
I love you too, mom.
Look I'm sorry I put you in
that position.
Let me finish.
Matt, you and your family are
so precious to me.
I hope you know that.
Yours and Josh's family are my
legacy
and you're my reason for
living.
And I want you to know that
it's been a great wonderful
privilege
to watch you grow into a man
and into a father
and into a servant of the
lord.
I know your father is so proud
of you.
And I also know he's looking
down on you
and really feeling the joy
that I feel too.
I just had so much in my
heart.
I had to let it spill out.
I love you to mom.
Looks, great. I hope you
guys are hungry.
It's really good.
>>Nice job mom!
What are you doing?
I thought that was for
decoration?
It is. But, you know, this
candle represents who I was,
beautiful maybe, but not very
useful.
It had a better chance of
melting
in storage done bringing down
from use.
I wanna burn myself out from
use.
I want to let my light so
shine before men
that they may see my good
works
and glorify my father which is
in heaven.
I can't tell you how grateful
I am for these difficult trials
that we've been through for
the last couple of months.
If everything haven't fallen
apart we could have never
rebuilt our lives so
beautifully.
I know he loves me.
That is beautiful.
Yes.
I love you too. Dinner
looks great.
Thank you.
Cameron, do you remember
when you ask me
if I believe in miracles?
Yeah.
Well, I do.
Tara?
Mom, are you having another
baby?
Yes!
Are you serious?
[ Laughter ]
Serious?
Oh, wow! It's great.
Wow! This is a celebration.
Let's eat! Let's eat.
Oh wait.
Who's saying the prayer?
Ah, Cameron?
* The greatest house, the
finest cars. *
* Have we lost sight in who we
are? *
* When worldly gain is all we
see, our life's on sinking
sand. *
* Our life's on sinking sand.
*
* All is gone lost sight in
what is true. *
* Now we look to you, yes we
look to you. *
* Stand strong as our world is
fading, stand strong *
* in Christ, our foundation.
* Stand strong even in
adversity surrounding us *
* in tragedy we'll stand
strong. *
* Life is crashing down on us
and all these false
stability's. *
* My life is crashing down on
us and all these false
stability's. *
* Our hopes and dreams they
fade away, *
* our life's on sinking sand.
*
* Our life's on sinking sand.
* All is gone lost sight in
what is true. *
* Now we look to you, yes, we
look to you. *
* Stand strong as our world is
fading, stand strong *
* in Christ, our foundation.
* Stand strong even in
adversity surrounding us *
* in tragedy we'll stand
strong. *
* By pride in earthly
treasure. *
* We will stand.
* No longer in this world are
we measured. *
* Stand strong as our world is
fading, stand strong *
* in Christ, our foundation.
* Stand strong even in
adversity surrounding us *
* in tragedy we'll stand
strong. *
* We'll stand strong.
[ Background Music ]