(spooky music)
(suspenseful music)
(electrical fizzling)
(suspenseful tempo music)
(suspenseful beat music)
- [Woman] That all right?
- Yeah!
It feels good so far!
(upbeat music)
You really think this will work?
- Baby, it'll work.
It's your show.
What do you want?
- I don't know.
What do you got?
(faint singing)
♪ Yes, he's gone forever ♪
♪ I won't miss her ♪
♪ No, no, never ♪
♪ I shot her down ♪
♪ Shot her down ♪
- Oh yeah
(electrical fizzling)
(man groaning)
- Whoa!
Stop!
Ow, whoa, stop it!
(ominous music)
- What's wrong, lover?
(electrical whooshing)
- What the hell happened?
Why did you cut in?
- You had a palpitation increase.
Something scare you?
How was it?
- I liked it.
(woman laughing)
Atmospherics were tight,
motion was naturalistic.
And, yeah, Valery was hot.
- White's getting impatient.
Conference room?
- Five minutes.
(woman giggling)
The host, Valery, how'd you do that?
She looked like this girl
I nailed in high school.
- Well, I referenced your
high school year book,
pulled all the atmospherics off it.
- All right, the sound.
Did you tweak the amplitude settings?
- Self-induced neural transference.
You were really feeling it.
- Hey, don't get cute and
play around with the settings
while my ass is sitting
in the chair, you got me?
- Sure, Lou, it's your show.
- Looks medieval.
Two people are gonna have sex
with this thing and enjoy it?
- Virtual sex, sir.
And, yes, they'll both enjoy it.
- All right.
I want the program ready in one week.
- It can't be done, we
just finished dry runs.
- We have to screen for applicants
and put them through exams.
- Well run the tests on yourselves.
Be your own guinea pigs.
If Virtucom can be traded
publicly by this quarter's end,
we'll have a heap of
funding by next quarter.
- We shouldn't railroad
this into production
without complete testing.
We could overlook other
possible applications.
- Such as?
- What if the VR program
could be used to help
those with sexual
problems or dysfunctions?
- Sex is entertainment.
Sex is profit.
- Amen, Pick.
Nice thoughts, Miss Tessia,
but I just wanna have
people put our headsets on,
sit back and let them dry hump
us all the way to the bank.
(White chuckling)
All right, you got one week.
Can you handle it?
Or do I bring in designers who can?
- We can handle it.
We'll have it ready for you next week.
- Good.
Because I've already picked the city
where we will launch our program.
- Las Vegas, what a joke.
- That's the call, Sharon.
Now White and Pickford set up a deal
with the Plaza Hotel downtown.
Call them up, talk to a guy
named Kevin Pallone, okay?
Look, Sharon, Las Vegas
makes perfect sense.
- What are we making
here, the digital hooker?
(Lou chuckling)
(exciting saxophone music)
♪ It was Saturday night,
about half past eight ♪
♪ I was cruising PCH in my 78 ♪
(quirky band music)
- Thanks.
We'll call.
♪ Driving all night ♪
- You look at the file I sent you?
- Yeah, I can bring it
up for you right now.
- I don't need to see that, Kevin.
Only your department of Vincent
Attractions is losing money
and it's really simple.
Guests gamble.
They see the shows and
they gamble some more,
spending all their time and money here.
- I know how it works, I do
have something coming in.
A virtual pleasures program.
A company from LA is gonna bring it out
and let us test drive.
- Well I don't care if they
light their farts on fire.
Just fill these seats.
All of them!
Pack the place, Kevin,
or pack up your office.
(melancholy music)
(somber bongo music)
(electronic chiming)
(computer beeping)
- Well, you'll need to take
your glasses off for this.
- It feels weird already.
- So, Leah, it says here you're looking
for a tropical fantasy.
- Yeah.
- I think you're gonna like it.
(somber bongo music)
(computer beeping)
Engage.
(computer buzzing)
(electronic whooshing)
(water bubbling)
(exotic beat music)
(Leah huffing)
(water bubbling)
(exciting beat music)
(computer buzzing)
(water bubbling)
(exotic bongo music)
(Leah huffing)
(bird squawking)
(exciting bongo music)
(Leah huffing)
(electronic fizzling)
(computer beeping)
(Leah sighing)
(Sharon giggling)
- Don't forget your glasses.
- Thanks.
Need me to do it again?
(Lou chuckling)
- We'll let you know.
(exciting beat music)
(electronic whooshing)
(computer beeping)
(exciting beat music)
(woman laughing)
White and Pickford are happy.
I hear they're talking about
bonuses and stock options
for both of us.
- We're going too fast.
Something will trip us up.
We need to slow down and
keep the testers around
for a full numerological examination.
- We start the onsites in
Las Vegas in three days.
- Lou, I'm talking about
people's health here.
- People don't care about their health,
they wanna feel good.
Look, the company's throwing a party
at White's house tomorrow night.
You really should try and attend.
- Okay.
- We're building a
virtual reality attraction
that is gonna make you and me and Virtucom
an embarrassing amount of money.
You still with me all the way on this?
- Yeah, I'm with you.
(pleasant music)
(electronic whooshing)
(suspenseful music)
(computer chiming)
(somber guitar music)
(crickets chirping)
- Sharon, what is this?
- Valery took the night off.
Thought I'd give you a special present.
Me.
(Lou chuckling)
- Sharon, this isn't right.
- Oh, it's more than right.
It's perfect.
Your favorite car, favorite music.
Favorite assistant.
We built this, you and I.
Now let's enjoy it.
(suspenseful music)
♪ Yeah, she's gone forever ♪
♪ I won't miss her ♪
♪ No, no, never ♪
(suspenseful music)
♪ Shot her down ♪
♪ Down, down, down ♪
(computer chiming)
(suspenseful music)
- What do you wanna do?
♪ Then I shot her down ♪
- It's your show.
(computer beeping)
♪ But there's something in side me ♪
- What do you want?
♪ I just can't describe ♪
(intense music)
(computer alarming)
(faint saxophone music)
(intense music)
(electrical fizzling)
- Sharon!
What's happening?
- [Valery] What's wrong, lover?
(Lou screaming)
(electrical fizzling)
(siren alarming)
(glass shattering)
- Lou, can you hear me?
(siren alarming)
(suspenseful music)
(dial tone buzzing)
(engine rumbling)
(tires screeching)
- Miss Tessia?
You brought in Mr. Burke?
- Is he gonna be okay?
- Unfortunately, it doesn't look good.
Neurological scans show brain
trauma, possible damage.
- Oh my God.
- But his seizures have stopped
and we have him stabilized for now.
Hopefully he'll wake up
and tell us what happened.
- I hope so.
- The last thing he does
remember is driving to Virtucom
and having sex with a woman named Valery.
- That's impossible.
I found him in the supermarket parking lot
10 blocks from here.
He looked terrible, so
I put him in my car.
- Well, he's lucky to be alive
and he has you to thank for that.
(shredder buzzing)
(dramatic music)
(computer beeping)
(Pickford chattering)
- Soon as the appointment gets finished,
we'll get over there.
- [White] Yeah, good, good.
- Good morning, Sharon.
I was just telling White here that
you and Burke just about
finished the VR testing.
- Mmmm.
- Congratulations, Sharon.
Sorry we pinched the clock on you.
We relied on your ability
to get it ready in time.
- Thank you.
- By the way, have you
seen Burke this morning?
He's supposed to be here for a meeting.
- No, I haven't.
(ominous music)
- Is there a problem, Sharon?
- No, why?
- Miss Tessia?
Is something wrong with the VR testing?
Well?
Do we have a problem?
- I think it's covered.
A little hangup with the sync codes.
Should be fine now.
- Oh, good.
Come on, Pick, we'll start without Burke.
(ominous music)
(upbeat music)
♪ Time for discovery ♪
♪ Time for revelry ♪
♪ Time for the lonely one ♪
♪ To find another one ♪
(people chattering)
- Can we have your attention?
Here comes the good news.
Pick any year,
from the ice age to the space age,
whatever your desires,
the Virtucom VR sex
program gives customers
a safe, customized and
gratifying sexual experience.
Imagine sex anytime,
anywhere you want it
with no risk of pregnancy
or transmitted diseases.
Of course, every VR unit will be checked
for computer viruses, so--
- We need to talk, now!
- Sharon, I'm in the middle
of a presentation here.
- Do you want me to make a presentation?
(ominous music)
- Excuse me.
(people chattering)
- Burke's galvinate
impulses were calibrated.
I don't know why the program overrides
didn't kick in sooner.
- Sharon, your timing is awful.
- Look, I tried to tell you earlier.
- Well,
we can kiss Vegas and the next
production quarter goodbye.
We were doing so well.
- Hey, I didn't build this thing alone.
This is you, me, Virtucom, everybody.
- What are we all supposed to
do now, scrap the whole thing?
What do I tell the
investors, our contractors?
- The truth.
That Virtucom needs more testing
to make sure it's absolutely safe.
Our VR sex program put
a guy in the hospital.
- No, Sharon, you put
(sinister music)
Sorry about that.
(electronic fizzling)
(computer chiming)
Didn't mean to come off
like an asshole last night.
We're hall under a heap of pressure here.
Any word on Burke?
- No change.
Still in ICU.
However,
I've fixed the galvanick inlays
so they won't go ballistic again.
Came in early this morning,
wrote new inlay codes.
It was simple to fix,
only took me 15 minutes.
See here?
When the inlay sends a
respiratory or cardio increase,
this flow circuit automatically opens up.
- Which means the VR users
won't cook their bacon.
- I've backed up the fail
safe with a shadow program.
- You did good work, Sharon.
And you're fired.
- You're serious?
(ominous music)
- This is your last monthly plus severance
and your share of Virtucom stock options.
I'll take the VR sex
protect to Las Vegas myself
and find a new assistant on site.
- This is my work.
Virtucom is using my VR patent.
You can't just cut me loose
because of what happened to Burke!
- And what if Burke dies, Sharon?
Then what?
- I don't know.
I pray that he doesn't.
- This is your mess and this
is how we're gonna clear it up.
- Right.
And you get to keep my VR
patents while I take the bullet.
- That's the deal, Sharon, I'm sorry.
Oh, I've got a meeting.
Look, us the rest of the day
to clear your stuff out of the lab.
(ominous music)
(crickets chirping)
(somber music)
- The logins show Burke's
VR program start to slip
and the sensorium caused
palpitation increased
and neural receptive trauma.
- Burke might have had some hidden medical
or neurological condition
none of us knew about.
But it's fixed now.
- Why didn't you catch the slippage?
You were watching him, weren't you?
- I did step away for a minute.
Look, we're dealing with
a machine and a program
none of us fully understand yet.
I shouldn't have left Burke alone.
I made a mistake.
- A very costly one.
- You just fired me, why am I here?
(foreboding music)
- We may have been a but hasty
with our decision to terminate you.
- With respect to Burke's untimely demise,
we're obligated somehow to
put the program back on track.
- Should've thought of
that before you canned me
and tried to rip off
my VR program patents.
- What if we gave you patents back
and doubled you holdings in the company?
- It'd say you were desperate to debut
the VR sex program in Las Vegas.
- You're the only one besides
Burke who knows how to run it.
- Seems to be a question
of how bad you need me.
So,
how bad do you need me?
(suspenseful music)
(car whooshing)
(faint upbeat music)
♪ I'm all alone ♪
(somber chiming music)
(water sloshing)
(ominous music)
- [Lou Voiceover] We're building
a virtual reality attraction
that's gonna make you and me and Virtucom
an embarrassing amount of money.
(somber chiming music)
You still with me all the way on this?
(dramatic music)
(water sloshing)
- [Sharon Voiceover] We have
to screen for applicants
and put them through exams.
- [White Voiceover] Well
run the tests on yourselves.
Be your own guinea pigs.
(electronic buzzing)
- [Lou Voiceover] What the hell happened?
Why did you cut in?
(siren alarming)
- [Sharon Voiceover] We're going too fast.
Something will trip us up.
We need to slow down and
keep the testers around
for full neurological examinations.
- [Lou Voiceover] We start
the onsites in Las Vegas
in three days.
- [Sharon Voiceover]
Lou, I'm talking about
people's health here.
(dramatic music)
(siren alarming)
Is he gonna be all right?
- [Doctor Voiceover] Unfortunately,
it doesn't look good.
Neurological scans show brain
trauma, possible damage.
He's lucky to be alive.
He has you to thank for that.
(dramatic music)
- [White Voiceover] What
if Burke dies, Sharon?
What if Burke dies, Sharon?
♪ Nothing is wrong if,
baby, less is right ♪
♪ It's why I break cold sweat
in the middle of night ♪
♪ Chilled to the bone,
yeah, through and through ♪
♪ All I wanna do is drive all night ♪
(woman mumbling)
- Okay, thanks.
- [Man] Too bad I told her
that's all you can eat for a dollar!
(man laughing)
- Thanks.
- [Man] What a sore-ass.
- Excuse me, Kevin?
- Yeah.
You are?
- Sharon Tessia.
I'm with Virtucom.
- How's it going?
You get your room squared away?
- Everything's fine.
I'm ready to set up, could use a hand.
- Sure.
(upbeat music)
Let's go.
Lounges,
swimming pools,
golf and tennis courts
aren't enough to compete
with the big houses anymore.
Every major casino has
some sort of water ride,
rollercoaster or amusement
park-type attraction.
Where do grownups go?
Like grownup games.
- Hmmm, let me guess,
card tables and slot machines?
- Obviously but they want more.
We give everything from Swedish rubdowns
to clay tennis courts but it's not enough.
As Vegas grows, real estate's gonna become
a serious, expensive issue
and virtual theme parks are the answer.
- Hmmm.
Don't worry, it won't bite
unless I program it to.
The chair and the headset
take on the sensual impulses
from this console.
As real as it may seem,
it's all just circuits and inlays.
- I have a girlfriend,
and Molly and I, we don't get too crazy.
Keep it in the bedroom, lights out.
- Okay.
Do you have a picture of her?
- Yeah.
Here.
- She's pretty.
You must feel lucky, huh?
- [Kevin] I suppose I am.
- The rodoscanner takes
two dimensional images
and replicates them into full dimension.
This is how we build the atmospherics.
Well,
what do you think?
Look good?
- I guess so.
- Okay, maybe you'd like to
try this with someone else.
(computer chiming)
See anything you like?
(computer buzzing)
Passion.
So, what would you and
Passion like to do for fun?
You know, kinky thrill sexcapades.
(Kevin chuckling)
- Like I said, I'm no lover boy but
I have always had this
fantasy about taking Molly
into the boss's office.
- Nappa's office?
(Sharon laughing)
I think I can work with that.
(Sharon giggling)
All right, Kevin, Passion's ready.
Are you?
(dramatic music)
(computer keys clicking)
(computer chiming)
(computer buzzing)
(electronic whooshing)
(phone ringing)
(somber music)
- [Kevin] Oh.
- Hi, lover.
(phone ringing)
- Passion?
- Pick up the phone.
(phone ringing)
- Hello?
- [Nappa] Kevin, it's Nappa.
What the screw are you doing in my office?
- Shit.
I can't do this.
- Tell him you're busy.
- I can't talk, I'm busy.
(pleasant beat music)
(computer buzzing)
(exciting beat music)
(electronic buzzing)
- [Sharon] Well, what did you think?
(Kevin clearing throat)
- Thirsty.
(faint upbeat music)
- Bio-Virtual Transference.
You're hot and thirsty.
Feeling what you would've felt
if you were actually there.
The amount of transference
varies from user to user.
- This is gonna be huge.
- I wrote the program myself.
Coded all the atmospherics.
- It's brilliant.
Sharon, we'll give you whatever you need.
Advertising, promotion
support staff, anything.
We're gonna make a
killing with this thing.
(upbeat guitar music)
♪ Mom said, you better be a good girl ♪
♪ Mom said, I better check your room ♪
- Long day, Kevin?
You're usually home before I am.
- I'm setting up a new
attraction at the casino.
How was your day?
- About like any other day.
Kevin, did you?
Your face.
Something in your eyes, like
you had sex or something.
- I did have sex.
With a machine.
Something new we're trying at the casino.
Virtual reality sex program.
- Oh yeah?
And who runs this virtual sex machine?
- The designer, the woman who built it.
- A woman?
(dramatic music)
- Come on, Molly.
It's just a machine.
It's like, I don't know,
if you used a machine like a vibrator.
- No, no, it is not the same thing
and I have never used one of those.
- Maybe you should start.
(Molly chuckling)
(dramatic music)
(computer beeping)
(computer chiming)
(computer keys clicking)
- Kevin,
are you out of your freaking mind?
We can't come up with these numbers.
- Why not?
The casino is expanding the hotel suits
and adding a second gaming floor.
Lump it in with the renovation costs.
- Kevin, forget the cost.
What about the possible
litigation nightmare?
Can you imagine if some parent finds out
that their kid put the VR headset on?
- We'll ID everyone, verify their age.
- I don't like it.
What if some old-timer
tries the headset on
and dies of a stroke?
His family's gonna sue us for
millions and probably win.
- We'll cover ourselves with a waiver,
free us from liability.
- I don't know.
(Kevin sighing)
- Look, if this thing goes big,
and I think it will,
you're gonna be happy you spent the money.
- And if it doesn't?
- Then I'm fired and you
can book old magicians
and washed-up lounge singers
for the rest of the summer.
- Hardly encouraging.
- Neither one of you has tried it.
Trust me!
One time with this this headset
is all the encouragement you need.
(exciting rock music)
♪ It's an ancient shaky formula ♪
♪ Been working for years ♪
- [Leah] The lab's finished
with your duel headset platform
and your operating system.
We'll ship it out to you tomorrow.
- Thanks, Leah.
So what's the word on Burke?
- No change.
Still in a coma.
And your story about finding
him in a parking lot,
it's losing water.
- If he never wakes up,
I don't know if any of
this will be worth it.
Call you when I get the
duel headset platforms.
- Okay,
bye.
(ominous music)
(water bubbling)
- It looks like we're ready to roll.
- I'm gonna go to my room
and lay down for awhile.
I'll be back in an hour.
(somber music)
(computer keys clicking)
(computer chiming)
(electronic fizzling)
Most of the time, we'll use
pre-built fantasy constructs.
Things like location,
music, all atmospherics.
Makes the avatars react and
seem as if they were real.
- Ava-what?
- Avatars.
The virtual people inside of the program.
Broken down into pieces of information
that react to other avatars or
other pieces of information.
- So,
if you and me,
our avatars,
took a roll in the digital,
hey, that wouldn't be cheating, would it?
- And what would Molly think of that?
- Yeah.
I'm gonna get a drink at the
rival casino across the strip.
Wanna come?
- Shouldn't you be getting home?
- I'm a big boy.
Come on, Sharon, one drink.
Grab some dinner, maybe play Blackjack.
- I should stay and
give it another dry run.
- You've been in Vegas, what, a week?
You haven't seen anything yet.
Come on, my treat.
You showed me your world,
let me show you mine.
(exciting music)
(slot machine chiming)
(coins clinking)
(slot machine cranking)
(exciting music)
(tires screeching)
Molly landed a job here first.
I came out six months later.
Looked around, didn't find much.
Sat on my ass for weeks.
Finally, a friend of Molly's
talked to somebody at the Plaza for me.
I wasn't computer
oriented but it was work.
Bullshitted my way through the interview
and here I am, booking
has-beens for the casino lounge.
I don't know.
Molly's happy, she has
friends here, but...
I feel stuck.
- Sounds like you're bored already.
- With what, the job or Molly?
(Sharon chuckling)
- I meant the job.
- Right.
I knew that.
(Kevin sighing)
All right, I'll admit it.
(Kevin laughing)
She's a cold fish.
(Sharon and Kevin laughing)
Nothing like Passion.
So,
what's your story?
- Don't have one.
- Come on.
How'd you end up doing what you do?
- I loved computers since I was a kid.
I studied program and
bio-tech engineering at Cal.
Worked the odd bio-tech job here and there
and then I get on the
research team at Virtucom.
- You involved?
Seeing anyone?
- Kevin.
- Come on, you know my deal.
- Well,
I was seeing someone before
I came out here but it ended.
- What happened?
- Nothing, it just ended.
- [Kevin] Sounds like
it ended badly, right?
- I don't like to talk about it, Kevin.
- Sorry.
(upbeat music)
♪ Send me the night life ♪
- It's really beautiful, isn't it?
Especially at night with
the lights and everything.
- This would be something to replicate.
Virtual Las Vegas.
(upbeat music)
(Sharon and Kevin laughing)
♪ I walk alone and I can't find her ♪
- Oh, down here.
♪ Maybe I never will ♪
(Sharon laughing)
(Sharon sighing)
- Well,
thanks Kevin.
I had a great time.
(Kevin chuckling)
- How about a nightcap?
Would be a shame to waste it.
- Kevin, it's late.
(Sharon chuckling)
- You don't want me to come in?
- Well,
it's not that I don't want you to.
But...
- Or do you want me to?
(cork popping)
Woo!
(Kevin laughing)
(dramatic music)
(dramatic rhythmic music)
(upbeat music)
♪ I'm in a scandal ♪
♪ Something I can't handle ♪
♪ I've got a screw loose ♪
(exercise bike buzzing)
- Molly, please, you
gotta do that right now?
- Long night at work again, Kev?
By the way, you reek of alcohol.
- Went out for drinks.
Please, Molly, just let me sleep.
- Who'd you go out with?
- People at work.
- Which people?
- Christ.
Work people.
- I called the casino last night
wondering if you were still there.
They said you and someone
named Sharon left together.
- Please, Molly, I got a big day today.
Just need a little more sleep.
- Let me guess, after
dinner, you and Sharon
went and worked on the
virtual sex machine, huh?
Is that right?
(faint pop music)
(thunder rumbling)
(ominous music)
- The storm's getting worse.
I just put it on autopilot.
How bad it is it?
- It's bad, we've got 10 or 15 minutes.
- Shit, that's not a lot.
There's nothing we can do.
(plane zooming)
- We still have time.
- For what?
(thunder rumbling)
(exciting tempo music)
(exciting beat music)
(thunder rumbling)
(electrical fizzling)
(exciting beat music)
(thunder rumbling)
(plane rumbling)
(thunder banging)
(exciting beat music)
(explosion booming)
(electronic whooshing)
- [Sharon] All right,
Miss Myerson, time's up.
(people chattering)
(faint pop music)
- Thank you.
- Thank you for flying our friendly skies.
- See that?
Our Virtual Pleasures Chair
is safe and enjoyable!
Who's next?
- Right here, man, right here!
- All right, step on up.
- Yes!
Woo!
(people chattering)
(electronic buzzing)
(school bell ringing)
(exciting music)
(computer buzzing)
(ominous music)
(intense beat music)
(computer buzzing)
(electronic whooshing)
Phew, damn!
(guy laughing)
♪ Turn of the century ♪
(upbeat music)
- Good, huh, boss?
- I recommended we use the waiver form.
That should protect the casino
from standard liability suits.
- Fantastic.
- By the way, congratulations
to both of you.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- Great.
- Yes!
(computer buzzing)
(pleasant music)
(door knocking)
- I have a package for you, ma'am.
- I bet you do.
(exciting beat music)
(billard balls clattering)
(metal clinking)
(pots clanking)
That was fantastic.
Wait till I tell my friends back home.
- Please do.
- Sharon, I talked with
White and Pickford.
They say that the duel
headset platform's are coming.
- Oh, it'll be here Friday.
Install, test drive, then we'll be ready.
- I'll run heavy promos over the weekend.
- Perfect, along with the straight profits
from the Virtual Sex Program,
we've allowed funds
for our next expansion.
- The Virtual Pleasures Adult Park.
Not a singles or couples
experience but a group experience.
Plug in, roam from fantasy to fantasy.
- Great, the virtual orgy.
- We've got plans for
other virtual experiences.
Whole theme parks,
extreme sports captured on VR cameras
including crashes.
- Crashes.
Hey, I like that.
(phone ringing)
- Hello?
- Hey, it's me.
I got word from the hospital about Burke.
- And?
- He woke up.
Burke's out of the coma.
- Okay, how is he?
- But it's not good news.
He's completely catatonic.
Won't look or talk to anybody.
Just drools and stares out into space.
- Oh my God.
- The hospital wants
to talk to you, Sharon.
They know that Burke was here at Virtucom.
- [Sharon] How did they find out?
- Who knows?
But they say that they'll
get a police summons
if you don't cooperate immediately.
We could be talking serious
assault charges here.
Sharon?
What're you gonna do?
(adventurous music)
(electrical fizzling)
(explosion booming)
(ships whooshing)
(adventurous music)
(atmosphere whooshing)
(ships buzzing)
(explosion booming)
(atmosphere whooshing)
(ship rumbling)
(computer beeping)
(adventurous music)
(explosion booming)
(ship whooshing)
(gunfire popping)
(adventurous music)
(atmosphere whooshing)
- Wow.
(people chattering)
(faint upbeat music)
(pleasant music)
(computer chiming)
- That's it.
Our restoration move.
- What's this, new program?
- What?
- That?
I've never seen it on the VR menu.
- Oh, old atmospherics
and inlay templates.
- Who's Burke?
- Are you going home now, Kevin?
- Yeah.
I'll see you in the morning.
- Oh, I'm flying to LA.
I'll be back late tomorrow.
- Everything all right?
- Oh, absolutely.
Listen, I've seen you digging and learning
your way around the machine.
Think you can run it without me?
- Sure.
Goodnight.
(dramatic music)
(airplane whooshing)
- His insurance companies
hired a private investigator
to find out exactly what
happened to Mr. Burke
and who should pay for it.
The man is unresponsive and withdrawn.
And he's partially blind in his right eye.
- All right.
One, I'll take care of all
of Burke's hospital bills.
And two, I get one shot at treating Burke,
no questions asked.
- You can't touch him.
- Look, I'm a person of science,
you're a person of medicine, right?
- Well, I am a medical doctor
and I don't really know who you are.
- Well, it's obvious you've exhausted
your medical means to treat him.
- Admit it, you've tried everything.
- Our attempts at treating Mr. Burke
are none of your concern.
- Just say it for the sake of the patient,
you've done all you can.
- Well, we have tried everything, yes.
(heart monitor beeping)
What exactly will that do?
- We're going to install
a medicinal program.
- It's like a virtual doctor.
- Okay, look, I'm gonna finish my rounds
and if he reacts adversely
to the treatment,
you call me immediately.
I don't think I need to go
into what'll happen to us
if this doesn't work.
- Doctor, don't you wanna see?
(dramatic music)
(computer chiming)
(faint upbeat music)
- [Kevin] Hey, how was LA?
- [Sharon] Fine, how
did everything go here?
- Piece of cake.
I installed the duel chair platform myself
and hooked it into the sensorial.
- What?
You imprinted it without me?
- White and Pickford wanted
to get it on the floor
as soon as possible.
- Oh, so you're talking to Virtucom now.
(ominous music)
- Sharon, I know about Burke.
I know how he really
ended up in the hospital.
See, you might have gotten
rid of his VR program
but when the program malfunctions,
it leaves behind a vitals template.
Your little secret just
got very expensive to keep.
- White and Pickford?
- Know everything, they're in my corner.
- Oh, so you're the new errand boy?
They want my program, right?
- For starters?
The rest depends.
What's a prison sentence worth to you?
- You are scum.
(ominous music)
- [Kevin] Molly!
- Kevin, what're you doing?
- Molly, we're just--
- I come in here wanting to see
what's been keeping you
here late every night.
Now I see what, or who, it is.
- I'm Sharon Tessia, I designed
the virtual attraction.
Molly, really, don't get confused.
Kevin and I only work together.
- Well, what about this
sex machine thingy?
- What?
Kevin hasn't told you
about Virtual Pleasures?
- Not in detail, no.
- Maybe you should give it a try.
(ominous music)
In fact, why don't you both sit
in the new duel chair platform?
Try it out together.
- Sharon, I don't think that's a--
- Yeah, Kevin.
Let's see this sex machine gizmo
that you've been building with
your very attractive coworker.
(ominous music)
- Just relax, Molly.
Enjoy the ride.
Besides,
Kevin trusts me, don't you?
- Yeah.
- Of course you do.
Let's see.
How about the office program?
What do you say, Kevin?
Sound good?
(electronic whooshing)
- Oh my God, Kevin.
I can feel you, can you feel me?
- Yeah.
(pleasant music)
- You didn't do this with her, did you?
I mean, in here?
- I already told you,
I was in here with you.
- Okay.
Sorry I was such a crank about her.
She is kinda pretty, you know.
(computer buzzing)
(pleasant music)
(computer chiming)
(intense music)
(computer keys typing)
(dramatic music)
(ominous music)
(intense beat music)
(exciting beat music)
(Molly huffing)
Kevin?
(somber music)
(electrical fizzling)
- Molly?
(ominous music)
Molly, please, I don't know what happened.
I woke up in the hotel
room, my clothes were gone.
Keys, wallet, everything.
Molly, come on!
I had no idea Sharon
was gonna pull that crap
with the VR program.
Will you just stop and
listen to me for a second?
- You think you and your
little sex computer's funny?
That kinky coworker
slobbering all over me, ugh.
- It was just a game, a simulation.
- A game?
It sure didn't feel like a game
and it definitely wasn't a
game when I woke up alone
and you woke up in a hotel!
- She must've cut in somehow
and kept the VR program going.
- Right, you're a creep, Kevin.
Stay the hell away from me.
(somber beat music)
- Excuse me.
I need a business suit
with a modem and T-1 lines.
- Sure.
- Kevin,
we have customers waiting.
You have empty VR chairs,
what's the problem?
- Sharon.
She's reprogrammed the VR
access codes by remote.
I can't turn it on.
(phone ringing)
- How long have they been down?
- All morning.
(phone ringing)
Hello?
Funny.
Reprogram and give me access
to the VR console right now
or we go to the police
with Burke's accident.
- Go tell them we're taking care of it.
Where are you Sharon?
- Nappa, I'm not
surprised you got into bed
with White and Pickford.
- Sharon, be smart about this.
We hold incriminating information.
You hold the VR program patents.
It's that simple.
- Stealing is simple,
even for patsies like you.
The VR machine stays off
today, all day, all week.
I'll turn it back on when
you guys start playing fair.
- [Nappa] Sharon!
(dial tone buzzing)
- [Kevin] Well?
- Can you get access to the
VR program without her or not?
(phone ringing)
- With an extra CPU
and data drives, I may have a shot.
(phone ringing)
- Get started.
Hello?
- Our arrangement stays the same.
If Kevin can download the
VR systems and programs,
I don't see any more need
for Miss Tessia's services.
- I'll make a call.
- Make it clean, no mistake,
she's a slippery fish.
- Don't worry about it.
(ominous music)
(heart monitor beeping)
(computer chiming)
(ominous tempo music)
(somber music)
(computer beeping)
How's it coming?
- We're downloading.
In about an hour I should
have the whole program files
and the sensoriams maximum.
- Call me when you got the whole thing.
(foreboding music)
(computer beeping)
- Kevin, you little snake.
(foreboding music)
(suspenseful music)
(slot machine cranking)
(computer beeping)
(suspenseful music)
(computer chiming)
(door thudding)
(ominous music)
- Too late, Sharon,
but you had to go and play
games with the access codes.
Now you have nothing.
(ominous music)
- Sharon, please, you're
in the middle of a casino.
My casino.
I could have security
in here in a heartbeat.
Finish downloading.
I'm getting security and
you do what you have to do.
(gunshot booming)
(intense music)
- [Guard] Let's go, let's
go, let's go, let's go!
- Next time, I won't miss.
Now Kevin, unhook your data
drives from my VR deck.
- And destroy your own machine?
- Better me than you.
Now unhook them now.
(ominous music)
(gunshot booming)
(man groaning)
(people screaming)
(suspenseful music)
(gunshot booming)
- Don't move, sir!
- I'm George Nappa, casino owner!
That woman is a thief and a murderer!
- [Guard] We'll sort it out
when the police get here.
- [Announcer] Casino owner George Nappa
has been taken into custody
and held for questioning.
The authorities may finally have the goods
on the very famous mob boss.
(upbeat music)
(phone ringing)
- Hello?
- Miss Tessia,
I've got some news for
you about Mr. Burke.
He's fine.
(doctor chuckling)
Fully recovered.
We waltzed right on out
of here this morning.
- 100 percent?
No more lingering seizures
or synaptic traumas?
- None!
He get full vision back
in his right eye too.
I am impressed.
Your virtual doctor did exactly
what you said it would do.
How did you do it?
- Doctor, remember our deal?
- Yeah, yeah, no questions.
- [Sharon] Thank you for
letting me treat him.
I'll call you when I get back.
- [Doctor] Bye, bye.
(upbeat music)
♪ Time for discovery ♪
♪ Time for revelry ♪
♪ Time for the lonely one ♪
♪ To find another one ♪
♪ Time for the secrets to be told ♪
♪ And it's time for
the young and the old ♪
♪ Turn of the century ♪
♪ One foot goes before the next ♪
♪ No secrets, baby ♪
♪ No regrets ♪
♪ Time for the seasons to change ♪
♪ Time for things to be
more easily arranged ♪
♪ It's time for the reasons to be told ♪
♪ And it's time those mysteries unfold ♪
♪ Turn of the century ♪
♪ Time for the girl to get her boy ♪
♪ Time for the sadness ♪
♪ Retreated on joy ♪
(exciting saxophone music)
♪ Yeah, it's been a long, long road ♪
♪ Where it stops, nobody knows at all ♪
♪ Turn of the century ♪