(soft music)
(light orchestral music)
(all laughing)
- I told you he was bluffing!
- It's not how you play the game Carol,
it's whether you win or lose.
- Obviously.
(doorbell rings)
Excuse me.
- [Woman] Hi.
- Hi.
- I'm sorry to bother you
but I was up at the church
and I was waiting for some
people who never showed up
and well my friend got
a little weird on me.
Anyhow I was wondering if
I could use your phone,
if it's not too much trouble.
- Oh of course dear, please come in.
- Thanks.
(line ringing)
No answer.
- I guess I could drive you home.
- Thanks, mister?
- Lake, Kevin Lake.
- Stacy Lockwood.
- Hi.
Sure you don't want to
go home with your friend?
- No way.
(suspenseful music)
(engine revving)
(tires screeching)
- Cheerleading camp was fun,
but what I'm really looking
forward to is next year.
I mean it's not like being
a junior is so great,
but you know friends and all.
- Is your friend upset about something?
- It's alright, she's just kind of weird.
Oh here, turn right.
That's our place, the one
with the light outside.
I guess they're still out.
I'll just go next door.
Thanks, it was really sweet
of you to rescue me like that.
- I'll wait 'til you get inside.
- Okay, bye.
- Bye.
(ominous music)
- [Stacy] Go away!
(Stacy screaming)
(dramatic music)
Help!
- [Man] Stacy?
What's going on?
- [Stacy] Help me.
- Stacy?
- [Stacy] Help me, I've been stabbed!
- Stacy who did this?
(Stacy sobbing)
- I can't feel my legs.
- Call an ambulance.
- I can't breathe.
- It's gonna be alright Stacy.
Just hold on, hold on.
Stacy, hold on, it's gonna be alright.
- I thought the coach's
speech was right on target.
He really...
(all chattering)
- [Man] Step back, step back.
Just give me five minutes
please, thank you.
- [Man 2] There he is now.
- [Man 3] I chased the
car until I realized
what I saw was a knife and came back here.
- What's going on?
- It's Stacy.
- What?
No!
Stacy!
What's going, what happened?
(suspenseful music)
(siren wailing)
(doctors chattering)
- [Doctor] Her respiration
at 24 and dropping.
- [Nurse] And her systolic BP is 40,
I can't read the diastolic.
(machine beeping)
- [Doctor] Full arrest.
- [Doctor 2] We've lost her.
- [Cheerleaders] Okay.
Blue, orange, white!
Go get 'em!
- [All] Fight, fight, fight!
- [Cheerleaders] Blue, orange, white!
Go get 'em!
- [All] Fight, fight, fight!
- [Cheerleaders] Blue, orange, white!
Go get 'em!
- [All] Fight, fight, fight!
- [Cheerleaders] Blue, orange, white!
Go get 'em!
- [All] Fight, fight, fight!
(crowd cheering)
♪ Join the team, we'll do something ♪
♪ Join the chorus and sing ♪
♪ Send the cheer, the cheer away ♪
♪ We'll sing loud and cheer ♪
♪ Ra ra ra ♪
♪ See them out there, see how they run ♪
♪ Hail hail the team ♪
♪ See how they run ♪
(crowd cheering)
(feedback ringing)
- Thank you, thank you very much.
For the sake of our newcomers,
let me reiterate that my name is Ed Saxe.
I mention this only because
I have been told that a
few misguided upperclassmen
have on occasion
(all laughing)
mistakenly referred to me as Ex-Lax.
(audience applauding)
Okay.
It is excellence.
Excellence in the classroom,
excellence on the playing field.
(audience applauding)
And excellence in the community
that distinguishes Santa
Mira from its rivals.
(crowd cheering)
So, today, the first day
of the rest of your lives,
I issue this challenge to
each and every one of you.
I challenge you to be the best.
(audience applauding)
The best son or daughter,
the best student, the best athlete,
the best individual
that it is in you to be.
(crowd cheering)
We live in a competitive world.
The world in which second best
is simply not good enough.
(audience applauding)
And so I ask you,
what is your goal this
year at Santa Mira High?
- [All] To be the best!
- Again!
- [Ed] One more time!
- [All] To be the best!
(upbeat instrumental music)
Be the best!
(crowd cheering)
(dramatic orchestral music)
- I'm going to be.
- What?
- The best.
- Give me a break, Angie.
- I am going to edit the yearbook,
and I'm going to be a cheerleader.
- Come on Angela, you're the
best writer in the school,
but yearbook editor is nothing
but a popularity contest.
And cheerleading, not a chance.
That's reserved for the
it's great to be me crowd.
- And I'm going to be a lark.
- A lark?
You mean like a Meadowlark?
They're such a bunch of snobs Angie.
- They're not.
They're into social service and things.
- Oh right, they do fashion shows
so they can parade in
front of their parents
and hear how gorgeous they are.
- Well I'm going to be one.
- No Angie, Stacy Lockwood
is gonna be a lark.
Meridith Ladd is gonna be a lark,
but you and me, we're
just gonna be you and me.
- Jill you don't understand.
I've got this feeling inside me like,
like I don't know, I'm gonna do things.
I'm gonna be someone.
I want what Mr. Saxe says.
To be the best.
- Well you already are
Angie, you already are.
I have to find out how much it costs
but if we want to go my
mom says she'll drive us.
Angela.
Angie.
Angie have you heard a thing I've said?
- Oh I'm sorry.
- God look at Jamie,
isn't she miss popularity?
- Jill stuff it, she's my friend.
- That was at Saint
Joe's, this is Santa Mira.
She's with them now.
- Hey Angie, come join the party.
- Yeah go ahead, I'll catch
up with you after school.
- [Angie] Hi.
- Hi.
I missed you Ang.
- Oh me too.
How was Hawaii?
- Awesome.
Beaches were unbelievable,
so were the guys.
- Yeah?
- How about you, what did you do?
- Um, you know I just
mostly hung out, you know.
- So, you know the gang, don't you?
- [Angie] Hi guys.
- So anyhow, the substitute,
she's got this unpronounceable name
and she's like four feet tall.
And the first thing she
does is she announces to us
that she has a PhD and we
had to call her doctor.
So listen, Cort he stands up and he says,
"Hey doctor, I've got
this pain in my heart,
what should I do?"
(all laughing)
Look.
- [Woman] Oh it's Monica.
- What is her problem?
- I don't know.
- She used to be kind of cool.
- Yeah, well now she's
kind of a weird, isn't she?
Hey Monica!
Forget your broom?
- I don't need a broom to
fly away from you, you bitch.
- [All] Ooh.
- Cold.
Well you know it's been
really nice talking to you
but you better run along now.
We don't feed strays here.
(all laughing)
Bye!
- [Man] Stacy!
- Jill, it's starting to happen.
- What?
- Everything.
- I just got a job at
the attendance office
and guess who the other girl is?
- I don't know, but from
the way you're acting,
it must be someone important it.
Who is it, Nancy Reagan?
- Stacy Lockwood.
- Oh, the queen bee herself.
Does that make you one of her drones?
I'm sorry Angie I just don't want
to see you get hurt you know.
That's the Stacey does, she hurts people.
I heard she went after Monica again.
- She didn't mean anything by it.
She was just being funny.
And besides, Monica goes out
of her way to fight people.
(horn honking)
♪ I'd love to be your man ♪
♪ So girl, I feel that I know ♪
♪ Feel right down in my soul ♪
Thank you Mrs. Anderson.
- Hey Angie.
Congratulations on the job.
- You'll see, this is
going to be a great year.
Bye!
(solemn instrumental music)
Hi Daddy.
- Oh hi Angela.
How was school?
- It was, you know, school.
- Uh-huh.
- I got a job at the attendance office
with this girl who's really cool.
- That's good Angela,
you know work gives you dignity.
- Yeah.
What'cha doing?
- Carburetor.
All right, now to try it out.
(clock ticking)
(alarm ringing)
(door creaking)
- Hi mom.
- Oh, I didn't hear you come in.
- I didn't want to interrupt or anything.
- Can I have a hug?
How was school?
- I got a job at the attendance office.
- Well that's wonderful dear.
Did you know that Teresa is here?
- Oh, where?
- In the kitchen.
She's making dinner for us.
- Hi.
- Yuck, vegetables.
- I live on them, you should too.
- Terry.
- Yes?
- What's it like, being on your own?
- It's okay.
- No, come on, what's it really like?
- Don't be in such a hurry Angela,
it's not all that it's cracked up to be.
You go to work, pay your own bills,
and you stay at home alone a lot.
- Well maybe it's like
that for some people,
but not for me.
I am going to live in Cabrillo County
in one of those houses you know
that overlooks the sea.
And I'm gonna wake up every morning
to the sound of the waves
and the gulls and things.
- Well how are you gonna do that?
- I don't know.
Maybe I'll be a writer
like Danielle Steel.
- That's a pretty dream little sister,
but somewhere you got to stop
dreaming and be practical.
- I can do it.
I'm a good writer.
Jill says I'm the best
writer at Santa Mira.
- I think you're a good writer.
- Teresa you can do anything
you set your mind to.
That's what Mr. Saxe says and
that's what I'm going to do.
- [Terry] Angela!
(dramatic music)
- You are so bad.
- Well I thought that's
what she liked about me?
(both laughing)
- Hey Delvecchio,
Cort skipped school yesterday
and he needs an excuse.
I was thinking you could
come up with something.
You being such a good writer and all.
- I don't want to get
in trouble or anything.
- Relax, nobody's gonna know.
- Okay.
- Look, make it creative alright?
So what's been happening?
- Did do you hear about Monica?
She goes walking downtown yesterday
dressed like a rerun
of "The Addams Family."
So this little boy sees her
and he screams and runs away.
By the time his mom catches up with him,
he's crying, he's like totally hysterical.
He saw Snow White,
he thought Monica was the
Wicked Witch coming to get him.
(all laughing)
Good morning Mr. Saxe.
- How is our prettiest office
assistant this morning?
How about it Cort, we
gonna take Ramirez tonight?
- Uh no sir.
- No?
- No sir, we're gonna crush 'em.
- Good, that's what I like to hear!
A winning attitude makes a winning team.
(bell ringing)
- [Angie] This should take care of it.
- Cool.
- Guess what?
Student council is sponsoring a ski trip.
It's gonna be in Timberland
and it's an overnighter.
- Yeah?
- Mm-hmm.
- Stacy can I see you for a minute?
- Sure Mr. Saxe.
I'll catch you later Cort.
- Later.
- So, what do you think,
are you gonna come?
The whole school's invited.
- Me?
- Of course you.
It's gonna be a blast.
Besides, it'll give us a
chance to get caught up.
Talk about old times.
- Sure, sure I'll go.
- Okay, great.
I gotta go, bye.
- Bye.
(bells ringing)
- [Mrs. Delvecchio] Everyone?
- Well almost everyone.
Jamie's going.
- And you want to go too.
- Could I mom?
Please could I?
They've got chaperones and everything.
And the boys stay in a different watch.
- I don't know Angela.
- Oh please mom, please,
please, please say yes.
- We'll discuss it later.
- Blessed are the meek,
for they shall inherit the earth.
Blessed are the poor,
for theirs is the kingdom of heaven.
We who live in Santa
Mira have many blessings.
The blessings of good family,
of lovely homes, good jobs,
and the blessings of a beautiful community
that is as close to paradise as
any of us will ever see on this earth.
Angela, it was just yesterday I baptized
you a babe in your mother's arms.
And look at you now.
A lovely young woman.
- It was a wonderful sermon, father.
- Oh thanks,
but I'm afraid some of the younger
members of the parish might of
thought it was a bit stuffy.
- You spoke the truth, father,
and the truth doesn't change with time.
- I suppose not.
Still, one must be
flexible don't you think?
Nice to see you.
Thanks for coming.
- Angela.
- [Angela] Yes, mom.
- I've been thinking about that ski trip.
- Yes, she said yes!
- Okay I get it.
She said yes.
Calm down before you beat
those brownies to death.
- It's just so cool!
I told you this was
going to be a great year.
- Aren't you forgetting something?
- What?
- You don't know how to ski.
- I can learn.
Can't I?
We can learn together.
- No way, I'm not going
anywhere near there.
- Then I'll learn on my own.
- Well there's something else.
- What?
- It costs $75 for the trip,
and then you got to have
skis, boots, clothing.
- I'll earn it.
- How?
(upbeat music)
- What was that?
What was that?
It's your bunny.
It's gonna blow bubbles out.
(both laughing)
Look at this one.
- Yeah look at the price.
This stuff is all too expensive Angie.
You couldn't afford to
buy a boot in this place,
much less a whole outfit.
- I'll ask for credit.
- Right.
Look, we'll check out the rental skis
and we'll see if we can't
borrow a suit from someone.
You look great.
- I look like a pear.
- No you don't, you look fine, really.
- I'm not going.
- Nobody's gonna care how you look.
- I care.
Boys care, everybody cares.
- It doesn't matter, you've
worked too hard for this.
You're gonna go and you're
gonna have a great time.
- [Man] Look out.
- I hate this.
- Come here honey.
- Mom!
- Just a little-
- [Mr. Delvecchio] What'd you do?
- He is so hot, I think
he's gonna ask me to prom.
- [Girl] And what about Cort?
- Why settle for choice
when you can have prime?
(all laughing)
- So what do you suppose Monica was
scribbling in that book of hers?
- I dunno, she still in the shower?
Let's find out.
- You wouldn't.
- Bed time story, girls! (laughs)
Okay, once upon a time,
there was a very strange
little girl named Monica.
Her face was very very white,
and her clothes were very very black.
Now Monica was so weird that
none of the other little
girls would play with her.
She made her diary her constant companion.
And here's what she had to say to it.
Dear diary.
I'm sitting in the back of a
van on my way to Timberland,
all because my parents want me to fit in.
Fit in with Stacy
Lockwood and her toadies?
(all laughing)
I'd just as soon kill myself.
It would be a real
contribution to society.
Okay, she thinks she is so cool,
but I'll bet she's still a virgin.
Ah, now we're getting into
the meat of the story.
- Come on, Stacy, that stuff's private.
- Well excuse me.
What are you anyhow,
Monica's guardian angel?
Back to the story.
She thinks she is so cool,
but I'll bet she's still a virgin.
- You colossal bitch!
- Hi Monica.
We were just, you know,
feeling out the texture of your prose.
- Give me that back you slut!
I will kill you!
- Back off Monica!
Back off.
You haven't got any friends here.
- Monica just let it go, let it go.
She didn't mean anything by it.
- I'd like to kill her.
- No, you don't mean
that, you're just angry.
- What would a wannabe like
you know about it anyway, huh?
Go on, go, get away from me.
Run back and lick her boots,
that's what you're dying
to do anyway, isn't it?
(door slamming)
(brooding instrumental music)
(dramatic music)
- Nice clothes, Angela.
Where'd you get them, a thrift store?
Come on girls, let's hit the slopes.
Are you coming Jaime?
- Yeah I'll be right there.
- (sighs) Angie, why'd you
have to fight with her?
- She was being so mean.
- [Stacy] Hey Jaime,
are you coming, or
staying with the strays?
- All right look.
Just stay out of her way
and she'll forget about it.
Okay?
Are you gonna be all right?
- We are headed for the same sort of
success on the baseball diamond we enjoyed
on the football field
and the basketball court,
and I just want you to
know that I am proud.
Not just of our teams, but of all of you.
Proud of your ability to compete
and of your determination to win.
Which brings me to our last announcement.
Cheerleading trials will be held
at three o'clock this afternoon.
Interested students should
contact Ms. Langdon.
Good luck to each and every one of you.
Will we be seeing you at the
trials this afternoon, Stacy?
- I wouldn't miss it.
- Well that's good,
because you are exactly the sort of girl
we need to represent us.
- I'm trying out too, Mr. Saxe.
- Well good, good for you.
Well back to work.
- Life disappoints us and we turn to God.
(chuckling)
Here I go lapsing into another sermon.
Angela, what's up with school?
Now I understand that you've
turned into a fine young writer.
Oh come come now, don't be shy with me.
I'm no stranger.
- Well I've applied to the yearbook staff.
And I'm trying out for cheerleader,
and I think I'm going to be a Lark.
- A Lark?
- The Meadowlarks, it's a service club.
They raise money for the
rehab center in Santa Flora.
- It's real hard to get into,
but Jaime has a friend who's in it,
and she's going to nominate us.
- Service club?
Now that's fine.
Service and sacrifice.
Those are two words we
don't hear very often.
This is delicious.
- Would you like some more, Father?
- Yes I would!
Thank you.
- Anyone else?
(girls giggling)
- [Girls] Larks!
- Me, you've chosen me?
- Yeah!
- Come on, we've got a lot to do.
- Okay, let me just get dressed.
- Oh no no no, everybody
comes as they are.
(all laughing)
- Come on, hurry!
(all chattering)
- You don't suppose she
looks that good all the time?
- Maybe somebody warned her.
(tapping on glass)
- Ladies, you are the chosen.
The best and the brightest,
the shining stars of the sophomore class.
- The only thing shiny about
me this morning is my nose.
(all laughing)
- I know, I know.
But my mother wrote this, I
promised her I'd read it, okay?
(clears throat)
If you prove worthy and pass the test,
you will be welcomed into a
sisterhood of achievement and service.
And now, let the initiates come forward
for anointment and instruction.
Come on girls, move it!
Kneel.
Do you, Stacy Lockwood,
promise to abide by
the rules, regulations,
precepts and traditions of the ancient
and distinguished order of Meadowlarks?
- I don't know, I'm not crazy
about rules and regulations.
- It's okay we haven't really got any,
just say I do.
- I do.
- Then I welcome you and anoint
you, Meadowlark Lockwood.
(all laughing)
Now rise, and fare thee
well in your quest.
(upbeat rock music)
(all cheering)
All right, he's yours.
- Me?
- Yes, go get him!
(all cheering)
(all laughing)
(all screaming)
Okay Angela my love.
Oh he's all yours, you get him.
(all laughing)
(horn honking)
- Angela?
- Yeah?
- [Terry] Mom said that you
made the Larks, congratulations.
- Thanks.
Terry, did you ever wish
you were someone else?
- Yeah, all the time, why?
- I don't know.
There's this girl.
Sometimes she's not very nice,
but she's so good at everything.
- What things?
- Everything!
People things.
- [Terry] You're good at people things.
- No I'm not.
- People like you.
- She doesn't.
- Look Angela,
we'd all like to be someone
else at some time or another.
We are who we are.
Just accept it and do the
best with what God gave you.
- I can't.
I won't.
I want to be better than just me.
I see a boat, it's
sails swollen with wind,
pushing against the current.
A V stretched out behind it marking
the waters where is has been.
And I see me, adrift on a windless sea.
No companion to give me succor,
no compass to give me bearing,
no port to give me hope.
(all chuckling)
- You're quite the
critic, aren't you Cort?
Okay, why don't we hear
what kind of a poet you are?
Well?
(Cort clearing throat)
- [Cort] I see a beaver gnawing on a tree.
(all laughing)
- I'm warning you, Cort.
- No, it's okay, it's an animal.
I see a beaver gnawing on a tree.
Hot and frenzied, wild and free.
- That will be enough, Cort.
- I look at the beaver, I look a the tree.
I look and I wonder, why not me?
(all laughing)
- Very good Cort.
So good I want you to trot on down to
Mr. Saxe's office and read it to him.
Stacy, why don't you go next?
- Okay.
Face like a ghost, hair black as sin,
the witch of Santa Mira
scratches her chin.
She cackles, she gloats,
she summons her broom,
and flies like a banshee
right out of the room.
- I could kill you, Stacy Lockwood!
- Monica.
Stacy I think you'd better apologize.
I'm sorry Mrs. Chadfield,
it was just a poem,
it wasn't about her.
(bell ringing)
(all chattering)
- We can do it, let's go.
Go, Warriors, go.
That's not right.
(all laughing)
- That's okay, you can start over.
- (exhaling) We can do it,
let's go, Warriors fire it up.
We can do it, let's go,
Warriors fire it up!
- Good, good.
Very nice Angela, but your
moves are still a little loose.
Stacy, you seem to have a handle on it.
Come over and run through it for us.
- Ready, okay.
We can do it, let's go,
Warriors fire it up!
- Excellent Stacy.
Okay everyone listen up.
Final tryouts are Wednesday.
The winners will be announced on Friday
at the closing assembly.
Everybody got it?
- Yeah, we've got it!
- Okay good.
Hit the showers.
(all chattering)
(bell ringing)
- Angie!
- Today's the day.
- For what?
- Yearbook staff.
Mr. Ludlow is posting the names
outside the journalism room.
- [Girl] I made yearbook staff!
(girls shouting in glee)
- So?
- I didn't make it.
- What?
Sure you made it,
you're the best writer in
the whole sophomore class.
- I didn't make it, Jill.
- There's gotta be some kind of mistake.
Let's go talk to Mr. Ludlow.
- I didn't make it, Jill!
Look don't worry about
it, it's not a big deal.
- Angie, you've got a lot going for you.
You're sweet, you're smart.
You're a lot smarter than I'll ever be.
Everybody likes you, you Lark.
You're gonna be a cheerleader,
I mean what else do you want?
Angie.
- Today in our last gathering
before the summer break,
(audience applauding)
we have a attempted to
recognize and to honor
those scholars and athletes among you
who took to heart the challenge
that I issued at the beginning
of the academic year.
To be the best.
And now to close our program
and our year together,
I would like to introduce four girls
who rose to that challenge.
The four new members of the
Santa Mira cheerleading squad.
And I'd like to ask each of them to please
join us up here as her name is called.
Meredith Ladd.
(audience applauding)
Congratulations Meredith.
Courtney Clay.
(audience applauding)
Congratulations Courtney.
Trish Brennin.
(audience applauding)
Good for you Trish.
And last but not least, Stacy Lockwood.
(audience applauding)
Let's hear it for the girls!
(dramatic music)
- Are you okay?
Come on Angie.
Angie?
(Angie sobbing)
My mom's waiting, I gotta go.
- Mom sent me looking for you.
Are you gonna get in,
or am I gonna have to
pace you all the way home?
- What's that?
- Dad's latest acquisition,
he's gonna resurrect it for me.
Come on, get in.
(dramatic music)
Cucumber?
- I hate cucumbers.
- I know, it was a joke.
You want to tell me about it?
- It's nothing.
My life is over, that's all.
(both laughing)
- You're gonna do it.
- I've never done this before Jill!
- That's what guys wanna hear
when you, you know. (laughs)
- (laughs) I don't think I'll ever know.
Guys don't even know I exist.
- Oh, here we go again.
Nobody likes me, everybody hates me,
think I'll eat some worms!
(Angie laughs)
Give it a rest, Angie.
- What, I am serious!
- You're always serious.
(both laugh)
- I wonder what you have
to do to be popular.
- I'll tell you what you could do.
Come to Roger's party
with me on Saturday night.
He said I can invite whoever I want.
So come with me, relax,
have a little drinky-poo.
Believe me, if you stop being so uptight,
guys will notice you.
- That's it!
- What?
- The party, that's perfect!
I'll invite Stacy to the party
and I will make her my friend!
Jill that's perfect!
Jill?
(line ringing)
Oh.
- [Mrs. Lockwood] Hello?
- Mrs. Lockwood?
Yeah hi, you don't know
me, but I'm with the Larks.
- [Mrs. Lockwood] Oh I'm sorry dear,
but Stacy isn't here right now.
- Oh, I know, I know.
She's at cheerleader
camp, but that's okay,
because this is actually
supposed to be a surprise.
We're having a dinner for the Larks,
the new Larks, on Saturday night.
- [Mrs. Lockwood] How lovely.
- Yeah but, like I said, it's
supposed to be a surprise.
So um, if you could just
tell Stacy to be ready
at about nine o'clock and
someone will pick her up?
Okay?
- [Mrs. Lockwood] Oh yes dear.
And what should she wear?
- Oh, uh something nice,
but casual, you know.
- [Mrs. Lockwood] All right.
- Great!
Well nice talking to you.
- [Mrs. Lockwood] Thank you.
And may I ask who is-
- Yes!
So they won't be back until late.
- They seem like a nice family.
- Oh yeah, their kids are
so easy to get along with,
they never give me any trouble.
In fact they actually go
to bed when I tell them to.
Oh it's this one.
- Oh.
- Mom, could you leave the car?
- What?
- If there's a car parked in the driveway,
then people will think someone's home,
and I would feel so much safer.
- Angela, you only have
a learner's permit.
You know you have to have someone
in the car when you drive.
- It's only four of five blocks.
You could walk home and
then I could drive it back.
- [Mrs. Delveccio] Angela,
it is against the law.
- I would feel so much safer, Mom.
Please?
- Really?
Well, it's against my better judgment,
but all right.
But just this once!
Okay, here.
- Thanks Mom.
- I'll wait 'til you get in.
- Oh, they always leave
the backdoor open for me.
I'll be fine, don't worry about it!
- Okay, you'll be careful?
- Yes!
- With the car?
- Yes I'll be careful Mom!
- Okay.
Good night dear!
♪ Down at the club before I can want you ♪
♪ Get a piece of the rock ♪
♪ Gonna climb a mountain
and rise to the top ♪
♪ Get a piece of the rock ♪
♪ Piece of the rock, oh yeah ♪
(horn honking)
- Oh, it's you.
- Come on, hop in.
- (scoffing) What's going on Angela?
I checked around, there isn't
any Larks dinner tonight.
- Nope,
that's just something I told
your mom so she'd let you come.
- Come where?
- To a party at Roger Huntley's house.
- A party huh?
- Not just a party, the party.
All the older crowd's gonna be there.
- All right.
Nice wheels.
- It's just transportation.
- What's this, hors d'oeuvres?
- Oh, um, my sister, she
sometimes fixes lunch in the car.
- Now that's real class, Angie.
So uh, who'd you say was
gonna be at this party?
- Oh, the older crowd.
- Think I'm gonna have to
fortify myself for this one.
Come on, turn here.
- Here?
- Just turn, okay?
- What are you doing?
- Did your brain die or something?
What's it look like I'm doing?
- Oh.
Oh, that's okay.
- (laughs) It's just a little grass.
- I know.
I just don't feel like it.
- So, tell me about this party.
- What's to tell?
- (sighs) I don't know, maybe
like how you got invited?
- Um, well I wasn't invited exactly,
it was my friend Jill,
she said that it's okay.
- Oh great.
You're gonna crash and you plan on
taking me along for the ride.
- Oh no, it's okay, Jill said it was fine!
- No it's not okay!
Maybe you're into public
humiliation, but I am not.
- [Angie] But Stacy, it's not a problem!
- You know what, this
is a really bad idea.
You better just take me home.
- That would spoil everything!
- There was never anything to spoil!
Look Angela I'm not going to a
party where I wasn't invited,
and I wouldn't go to that
party if I had been invited.
- Why are you so mean?
- Come on, put a lid on it, let's go.
- I don't understand, I
just want to be your friend!
- (scoffs) Sure.
And I want to fly to the moon.
- I admire you Stacy,
I've always admired you.
You're so pretty and funny and confident.
- You're pathetic.
- All I want is to be like you!
- That's it, I'm out of here.
- Wait, wait, no!
- You know what, you are
even weirder than I thought!
(dramatic music)
Why don't you give Monica a call,
maybe she can be your date.
- No Stacy that's not what I meant!
- [Stacy] Hi, I'm sorry to bother you,
but I was up at the church and
I was waiting for somebody,
but they never showed up.
And my friend got a little weird.
Anyhow I was wondering if
I could use your phone,
if it's not too much trouble.
- [Woman] Oh of course
dear, please come in.
(suspenseful instrumental music)
(tires screeching)
- [Stacy] You wouldn't believe
what happened to me last night.
Angela-
- (scoffs) That nerd?
- [Stacy] Nerd isn't even the half of it.
Then you're gonna love this one.
She tells me how pretty and
funny and confident I am.
- [Girl] Ew!
- [Stacy] I mean I always
knew she was weird, but geez,
it's like she was asking me
out on a date or something!
- [Girl] Wait 'til the
word gets out on this one.
She might as well just dig a hole
and pull the dirt in after her.
(all laughing)
- I would've driven you home.
- You are so weird!
Just go away, go away!
(Stacy screaming)
(tires screeching)
(Angie breathing heavily)
(shower water running)
(knocking on door)
- [Mrs. Delveccio] Angela?
Anela, Jaime's on the phone.
I told her you were in the shower,
but she says she has to speak to you.
Sounds like she's been crying.
- Hello?
You're right, it had to
be some crazy person.
- The sheriff's department spokesman
described the assailant
as a slender teenage girl
with shoulder-length hair.
- The suspect who was wearing-
- That's half the girls
at Santa Mira.
- Red sweatpants and
a brown shirt was seen
driving a light-colored Nova.
In other news today-
- (chuckling) I'm a teenage
girl with shoulder-length hair,
and we have a Nova.
- Don't be ridiculous Angie,
nobody's gonna suspect you.
You're like the nicest girl at Santa Mira.
(dramatic music)
- Amen.
- [Preacher] I know that each
of you gathered here today
has a question in your heart.
You want to know where was God
when this terrible thing came to pass.
There are no easy answers.
God gives us the freedom to do and to be,
and in that freedom we are vulnerable.
- I know, we loved her too.
- This is strictly routine Angela,
so I don't want you to be nervous.
The girl who called Stacy's
mother claimed to be a Lark,
so we're questioning all of the members.
- I understand.
- Now, perhaps you could
start by telling me
where you were the
evening Stacy was stabbed.
- Yes sir, I was
babysitting for Mrs. Moore
from about 8:30 until maybe 11 o'clock.
- Mm-hm.
How about the Nova
registered to your father?
- That's my sister's, really.
I mean my dad let's her drive it,
he's actually fixing up a car for me
for when I get my license.
- [Denning] Mm-hm.
How well did you know Stacy Lockwood?
- Um, I knew her, Sergeant
Denning, but not very well.
- [Denning] But you were both Larks,
you both worked in the attendance office.
You went out for cheerleader
together, am I right?
- (chuckling) Not really, not together.
Stacy kept to her own friends.
- [Denning] Do you have any idea
why anyone would want to kill her?
- No.
No.
Stacy was very popular.
She was maybe the most popular
girl in the sophomore class.
- [Denning] Well, someone didn't think so.
Someone wanted her dead.
- Maybe, um,
it was someone she put down.
- [Denning] Put down?
- Stacy was real funny.
And sometimes her jokes were
at other people's expense.
- [Denning] So you
think someone killed her
because she made fun of them?
- That's just very hard to explain.
She was very popular.
- [Denning] All right
Angela, thanks for coming in.
Angela?
- Yes?
- Would you mind taking
a lie detector test?
We're asking everybody.
- Sure.
(dramatic music)
- [Man] Angela, were you
babysitting from 8:30 to 11?
- [Angela] Yes.
- [Man] Did you kill Stacy Lockwood.
- [Angie] No.
- Sierra Linda country sheriffs
have questioned over 300 individuals
and checked out over 700 Novas
matching the description
of the suspect vehicle.
But today nearly two months after
the brutal slaying of Stacy Lockwood,
they seem no closer to a solution
than at the beginning of
their long investigation.
Frustrated by official failure
to uncover their daughter's killer,
Dick and Dana Lockwood called
a press conference today
to ask the public to cooperate
in solving this crime,
and to urge investigators
to refocus their efforts,
seeking the killer not in
the outlying communities,
but in the Santa Mira student body.
- We've broken our silence today because
school is about to start up,
and we strongly feel that the killer
may be among those
returning to class tomorrow.
Our Stacy was popular.
She was an athlete, cheerleader,
and all-American kind of girl.
She was the establishment,
and we have to ask ourselves if
her killer was not anti-establishment.
Someone who does agree with the way
that the majority thinks and acts.
My wife would like to
say to that individual,
whomever she may be,
that we will never forget
the night we came home
and saw the flashing lights.
The ambulance.
The shock and grief
will be with us forever.
But the grief we have suffered is nothing
compared the pain and terror
that Stacy went through
on that terrible night.
So I say to her killer, who
must be now suffering as well,
come forth.
Come forth, confess,
and ease the pain that
all of us are feeling.
(line ringing)
- Jill?
Oh come on Jill, please be there.
I may not get the courage again.
- There are no bad kids at Santa Mira.
Though we enter our new academic year
under a pall of grief and suspicion,
I want to express my
confidence in all of you,
and I want to remind outsiders
that this terrible incident
happened within the community,
not in the school.
We have suffered a shocking loss.
But we must not let that loss sow
the seeds of distension among us.
- And I volunteered as a
candy striper at the hospital.
- Wow, Angie, sounds to me
like you could be in danger.
- Danger?
- Yeah, of becoming a real socialite.
Candy striper, peer counselor, Lark.
- I just wanna do some good I guess.
- Great, my friend the do-gooder.
Honestly you make me feel like I should
go to church and confess or something.
(all yelling)
- Murderer!
- [Girl] Run, run away!
(girls yelling)
- Like those women in the
Bible with the stones.
- So anyway, I think in
light of what's happened,
we should disband.
And I'm gonna make a
motion to that effect.
- Any seconds?
- Wait a minute, this is all wrong.
The Larks didn't kill Stacy.
If we break up it'll be like
we're admitting we had
something to do with it.
And besides, the Larks are important!
They were important to Stacy,
and they're important to the rehab center.
If we break up...
We just can't break up, that's all.
- I propose we drop the idea
and get on with the elections,
and I want to nominate Angela
for secretary of treasure.
- Oh no no, I couldn't,
I just didn't want to see
everything fall apart because-
- Second.
- Any objections?
Any other nominations?
Okay, all in favor of
Angela, raise you hands.
Well Angie,
it looks like you're our
new secretary treasurer.
(all chattering)
- Hey Angie.
- Darren, how are you?
- Well actually I'm a little bit late.
- Only about 30 minutes.
- Okay a lot late.
- But I bet you've got this
really great excuse, right?
- How'd you know?
Actually, my excuse is
I wanted to talk to you.
See there's this party Friday.
- Yeah?
- I thought you might like to go with me.
- Honest?
- I'm askin' you, aren't I?
- Well-
- Just say yes.
- Yes!
- Great.
I'll pick you up around eight, okay?
Okay so uh, I guess I'll catch you later.
- Oh um, what about your excuse?
- Oh I just remembered, I don't
have a first period class.
So uh, guess I won't need one.
- It's all a bunch of crap.
- What is, Alicia?
- This, peer counseling.
You tryin' to tell me how
to straighten up my act.
It's all crap.
- It's just a chance to talk,
and maybe figure things out together.
- Together, you and me?
Right.
- Well it's better than
getting expelled, isn't it?
Sometimes people who do drugs,
they're maybe dealing
with some kind of problem-
- You want to know what the problem is?
You're the problem.
You and everyone else.
Here you are pretending you care,
pretending you want to help me,
when all you really care
about is being popular.
You and your hotshot friends
don't take jobs like this
because you're like great humanitarians.
It's just another notch in your gun belt.
(dramatic music)
- Wish we had more candy
stripers like you Angela.
Mrs. Hattan again.
Angela would you go and see
if you can calm her down?
- Sure.
(phone ringing)
- Oh, you!
You!
Get away from me, get away from me!
I know what you are!
Help, help, help, someone please!
Please help!
- The gifts of the Holy Spirit,
which you're about to receive,
is a spiritual sign and seal
to make you more like Christ
and more perfect members of this church.
Do you reject Satan, all his works,
and all his empty promises?
- [Congregation] I do.
- Do you believe in God, the Father,
creator of heaven and Earth?
- [Congregation] I do.
- All powerful God, Father
of our Lord Jesus Christ,
by water and the Holy Spirit,
free your sons and daughters from sin
and give them new life.
Send your holy spirit upon them
to be their helper and guide.
This we ask through
Jesus Christ, our Lord.
In the name of the Father,
the Son, and the Holy Spirit.
- [Congregation] Amen.
- Forgive me father, for I have sinned.
- [Girl 1] My dad said
they brought in the FBI,
they're gonna interview
all the Larks again.
- [Girl 2] I don't know why they bother.
Everyone knows it was Monica.
- [Girl 1] She dropped out of school.
- [Girl 2] Good.
She had a lot of nerve
showing her face here,
day after day.
- She had an alibi, you know.
There's no way she
could've possibly done it.
But it didn't matter,
they just kept hounding
her and hounding her.
- Yeah.
- All because she was different.
And you know what?
I did it too.
Stacy mocked her so I mocked her.
Stacy said jump, and I jumped.
You know Angie, I've been
thinking about her a lot lately.
And I'm ashamed to admit it.
I never really liked her.
I was just afraid of her.
And I've been thinking
about her killer too.
Maybe it was, I don't know,
someone like me.
- This is Special Agent Gilwood, Angela,
he's with the FBI.
He's here to try to straighten out
some inconsistencies in your statement.
We checked out your
babysitting alibi Angela,
it doesn't wash.
And we got another reading
of your polygraph test,
you know what it says?
It says you're a liar, Angela.
- That's a little harsh, Dick.
Why don't we let Angela here
tell us what really happened that night.
Angela?
- You're right about the babysitting.
I just, I lied about that
because I wanted the car.
- What did you want the car for?
- Um, there was this movie
playing in Sierra Linda,
and it was R, and I can only see PG.
- [Gilwood] Do you
remember the name of it?
- It was "Reckless."
But I didn't get to see it
because they asked for my ID.
- (laughs) Well that clears up the problem
with the polygraph.
But you know Angela, you
could still help us out.
- How?
- [Gilwood] You could
tell us more about Stacy.
What kind of girl she was.
- She was very popular.
- Did you like her?
- Everybody liked her.
- I think you're mistaken, Angela.
Monica Whitley didn't like her.
- But Monica didn't, she would never-
- But someone did.
Someone disliked her enough to kill her.
In fact the Bureau has worked
up what we call a profile,
which is a description of what
we think the girl must be like.
Would you care to hear it?
- Sure, I guess.
- Let me see.
Oh, a lot of words here.
You know psychiatrists are, huh?
I remember a passage near the end
where they finally get down to it.
Ah, yeah, here it is, here it is.
She is the same age as her victim
and a member of the same peer group,
though her involvement in that group
is peripheral rather than central.
She's impulsive, emotional,
and driven both by fear of inadequacy
and a desire for acceptance.
While her crime was abrupt,
irrational and disorganized,
she is unlikely to exhibit strong emotions
when questioned about
her possible involvement.
Hm, it's interesting isn't it, Angela?
What do you think about it?
- I think it sounds a lot like me.
- That's what we thought too.
In fact we've been doing a
lot of thinking about it.
Look, I'll tell you what.
Why don't you go home and think
about it over the weekend,
and maybe we can talk some more later.
- I can go now?
- Of course you can.
(door clicking)
- It's her.
- Of course it is.
But all the evidence we
have is circumstantial.
Unless she confesses.
- (scoffs) I almost feel sorry for her.
- Don't.
Feel sorry for the girl she killed.
- [Mrs. Delveccio] Joe?
- Yeah, I'm out here.
- What are you doing?
- Oh fixing this gasket.
- You seen Angela?
- No.
- I'm worried about her.
- I'm sure she's all right.
She's probably gone off
with one of her friends.
You know how young people are.
- [Mrs. Delveccio] No.
No, I am really worried about her.
I thought that when things
started happening for her,
the Larks and this
volunteer work, and boys,
that she would somehow
find some happiness.
- [Mr. Delveccio] Well you know,
sometimes I think that
maybe she's ashamed.
She never brings anybody home.
The other kids all have so
much, and we don't have any-
- No, no.
- I mean, really.
- [Mrs. Delveccio] Joe, really,
we have everything that we need.
She, she has such big dreams.
- [Mr. Delveccio] Well maybe
the party will bring her out.
(upbeat instrumental music)
You're our real angel, Angela.
(all clapping)
- [Woman] Oh, very nice.
- All right everyone,
come on, around the tree!
Listen, you four have gone off,
and you've found your places in the world.
And before long Angela will be gone too.
So I would like to begin our
pre-Christmas celebration with a prayer.
Thank you God for our family.
For letting us have this time together.
For the memories of Christmases past.
Bless us and keep us in the days ahead.
Secure in the certain knowledge
that though we now lead scattered lives,
we are never further from
each other than a prayer.
Amen.
- Amen.
- All right everyone, it's time
to draw the names for gifts.
Angela, you go first.
Now remember there are two
weeks left to do your shopping,
so please do not leave it to
the last minute like you always do.
I think everybody has to give
nice presents this year, okay?
And I think just to be safe
we should say another prayer.
Okay?
Lord, sh.
Please bless us and keep
us from cheapskates.
(all laughing)
- Angela, smile!
(upbeat orchestral music)
(all chattering)
Angela, smile.
Theresa, Theresa!
All right, now, ready?
(all chattering)
Thank you, thank you honey,
thank you for coming.
Thanks, bye bye.
Hey, you drive careful, you understand?
Good night.
(laughs)
Oh boy.
- (sighs) Well it was
really nice, wasn't it?
Time to clean up.
- Why don't you just leave those?
I'm gonna come in and help you.
- Joe, relax.
- All right, all right.
Your mother's right, it
was nice, huh? (laughs)
Everybody here.
- Daddy.
- Yes?
- I have something to tell you.
- What's the matter?
- Nothing.
Just that I love you.
- I love you too.
(sighs)
- Mom can we talk?
- Why certainly, dear.
Oh, I'm awfully tired.
Would you mind if I get
ready for bed first?
- No, I understand.
- Good.
(peaceful instrumental music)
- Oh Angela,
I guess I didn't realize
how tired I was last night.
I fell asleep.
- It's okay.
- Can we have our talk now?
- Um, no I'm late, I'm
getting a ride with Melanie,
I wrote you a note instead.
(car horn honking)
- Just some juice?
(timer ticking)
- Thanks.
(alarm ringing)
(dramatic music)
Dear Mom and Dad.
I've been trying to tell you this,
but I love you so much and it's so hard
I'm taking the easy way out.
I just can't be near you when you see this
because I've already caused so much pain.
The reason why I took so long on Fridays
is because the FBI man Mr.
Gilwood thinks I did it.
And he is right.
I can't bring her back, but I'm so sorry.
I would kill myself except maybe
that would hurt you even more.
I've been able to live
with it for a while,
but I can't ignore it.
It's too much for me and
I can't be that deceiving.
I've spoken to a priest,
but I still can't take it.
I need to turn myself in.
With you, if you would come today.
Please forgive me, I need you.
I'm so sorry to have been a
disappointment to you in every way.
I'm even worse than words can
describe and I hate myself.
I need your love.
Please still love me.
I can't live unless you love me.
I've ruined my life, and yours,
and I don't know what to do.
I'm so ashamed and scared.
I love you.
Angela.
- Joe!
Joseph!
Angela.
- Don't hate me, Mom.
(both sobbing)
- [Girl 1] Where's Delveccio?
- [Girl 2] I don't know, sick I guess.
- Yeah?
I heard they arrested someone.
I heard it was a Lark.
- So?
- All the other Larks are in school.
(girl whispering)
- [Girl] It's Angela.
(all murmuring)
- I told you it was Delveccio.
I always did think she was weird.
- Liar!
You guys are all a bunch of liars.
You don't know anything about her.
She's better than all you put together.
(sobbing)
- This is for all of us
a shocking time of grace.
It is for us a time to
look deeply into our values
and to examine our goals.
We're a close-knit community.
You either belong or you do not.
As I agonize over the events
of the last six months,
I wonder if Angela didn't feel
the community's pressure to be the best,
be the brightest, own the
finest and the most expensive.
Felt these pressures and
judged herself a failure.
I wonder if what we're seeing is not the
attitudes of the parents being
visited upon the children.
Now these are painful,
agonizing questions that must be asked.
If we are to survive and
thrive as a community,
I beg you to look deeply into
your hearts and souls for the answer
so that we may assure
ourselves and our children
that no such adversity
will ever afflict us again.
(Jaime sobbing)
- I left her alone at
the ski lodge, Father.
She was my best friend
and I left her alone,
because I didn't have the
courage to stand up to Stacy.
- You must forgive yourself.
And then find the courage
to be her friend now,
when so many are arranged against her.
- But they won't even let me see her.
- Be her friend in your heart.
The rest will come.
- As the trial approaches,
there is talk of community responsibility
in the death of Stacy Lockwood.
Channel 5 spoke to Santa Mira
principal Ed Saxe to pose that question.
- We have heard a lot about the
community role in this unfortunate affair.
Well I reject that.
Did anyone ever consider that
this is maybe just a sick kid?
Believe me there is no
problem with materialism
here at Santa Mira then
there is anyone else.
- [Newscaster] The question remains.
Is it Angela Delveccio who
goes on trial tomorrow,
or the community of Santa Mira?
- Mr. Quan, there is a
rumor that the defense
has offered the DA's office a plea
of second degree and it was rejected.
Can you confirm or deny?
- An offer was made and rejected.
- [Reporter] Could you tell us why?
- We feel we have a
first degree case here,
and it deserves to go to trial.
- But what's the point?
- The point?
- [Reporter] Isn't the
punishment the same,
whether the verdict is first
degree or second degree murder?
- The juvenile code dictates that the
punishment for either time is confinement
to the juvenile authority
until the age of 25.
- Then why go to trial?
- We are trying to serve
the community interest here,
and see justice done.
With calculation and deliberation,
Angela Delveccio lured Stacy Lockwood
from the safety of her home
and drove her to a church.
A church where she gave
Stacy one last chance.
If she would be her friend,
Angela would let her live.
But Stacy fled, and Angela
pursued her with one intent,
and one intent only.
To kill Stacy Lockwood.
It is, Your Honor, a clear
case of premeditation
and murder in the first degree.
- The murder of Stacy Lockwood
was a crime of passion.
Un-premeditated, disorganized.
The spontaneous action of a
confused and desperate child
who's only intention was
to invite Stacy to a party
and ask her to be her friend.
It as as we will prove a clear case
of murder in the second degree.
(all chattering)
- [Girl] Look at her.
She has got a lot of nerve.
- What do you think you're doing here?
This trial is for Stacy's friends!
- This isn't a party, Meredith.
And there aren't any invited guests.
Jill has as much right
to be here as you do.
(dramatic music)
- [Angela] I thought she was going to
tell everyone at school
that I was really weird.
I can't explain it, I don't understand it.
It was like, if I had
been thinking straight,
it never would've happened.
I guess I was really angry,
and I really don't know.
She was just telling me to go away.
And I did it.
It was exactly like I was watching it.
You know how you see a dream,
and then you see yourself doing things?
And it was so much like a dream
that I thought I would wake up.
- [Gilwood] How do you feel about her now?
- [Angela] I keep wishing that
I could push time backwards.
(Mrs. Delveccio sobbing)
I sort of apologized to her in my mind.
Like I think she's in heaven now.
- [Gilwood] Do you think
it was partly her fault?
- [Angela] I remember the
mean things about her,
but I could never think
that it was her fault.
I don't think there's
any reason in the world
that justifies killing someone.
Mr. Gilwood?
- [Gilwood] Yes?
- [Angela] Will the press get my name?
- [Gilwood] We don't release
names in juvenile cases Angela.
But it's possible they
could get it on their own.
- [Angela] I don't see any
reason for living if everyone,
(Mrs. Delveccio sobbing)
I mean if people knew that...
Could I use the restroom?
I think I'm gonna be sick.
- [Mrs. Delveccio] Sweet Jesus.
(Mrs. Delveccio sobbing)
- Why are they doing this to her?
- I don't know.
She confessed, she
admitted she was guilty.
- It's like what Mr. Derning
was telling us about.
New England, the Puritans
would sinners in pillories,
so the townspeople could
come by and spit on them.
- Yeah well I wonder if the Puritans
got all dressed up for their spitting.
- No family wants to see the courts
hold a yardstick up to their loss.
But the evidence, not the
evidence presented by the defense,
but by the prosecution, is clear.
There was no premeditation,
no calculation,
and there was no planning.
And no possible verdict but
murder in the second degree.
Angela herself, she could not
explain her irrational act.
Don't ask why, she had
said, "I don't know why."
She, like all of us, wants to understand.
Wants to know why.
Though the answer will forever elude us.
I suggest that we look to ourselves,
we look to our community,
in our quest to understand.
The pressures are intense here,
nobody wants to be a
hod-carrier in Santa Mira.
No.
You're supposed to be beautiful
and successful and popular.
Perfect.
Now, Angela was none of these things,
and her fear of failure eventually became
too much for her to handle.
It was this fear of public humiliation
that led her to kill in the first place.
In this trial,
in this public airing of
painfully private emotions,
we have submitted her
to the worst humiliation
she could ever have imagined.
I don't say this to excuse her crime,
for a crime she did commit.
But to point out that the community
can be as unforgiving
and pitiless in public
as it sometimes is in private.
For this is a trial that
need never had happened.
This is a clear case of
murder in the second degree.
And had the district attorney's office
accepted that plea in the first place,
we might all of us have a avoided the pain
of publicly reenacting
this terrible tragedy.
- You have been subjected to a scene
of enormous pathos here.
The pathetic tableau of Angela
surrounded by her family as she
listened to her own damning words.
But what of the tears and the
grief of the Lockwood family?
Tears they will shed
and grief they will feel
for the rest of their lives.
And so I ask you, Your Honor,
to consider the plight of the
victim and not the victimizer,
and to return a verdict
that suits the crime.
A verdict of murder in the first degree.
- With the exception
of the tape confession,
this whole case is circumstantial.
Considering the evidence presented here,
I must conclude that the prosecution has
failed to prove it's
contention of premeditation.
The evidence supports nothing more than
a finding of murder in the second degree.
I must further observe,
and we have a kind of "Alice
in Wonderland" situation here.
The juvenile code dictates a sentence of
confinement to the age of 25.
The degree whether first
or second is irrelevant.
And so I find myself wondering
what we have accomplished here.
I hope it was justice,
though I fear it may have been
nothing more than entertainment.
(upbeat orchestral music)
- [Boy] Hey, wait up.
- [Boy 2] Come on.
- [Jaime VOICEOVER] Dear Angela.
There have been some changes in my life,
and I want you to know about them.
I've quit the Larks,
and next year I'm quitting Santa Mira too.
I'm going to back to Saint Joe's
where you and I had so
many wonderful times.
I'm going back, and yet I
know I can't really go back,
anymore than you can, or any of us can.
We can only go forward, and
that's what I hope to do.
And that's my hope for you,
as we both struggle to understand.
Yours always, Jaime Hall.
(brooding instrumental music)
(dramatic music)
(soft music)