( Match strikes )
Eh... being back here
reminds me of...
When we met.
Dude,
we met at that, um...
No, man.
Friggin'...
Jessica?
Yeah, Jessica. D'uh.
Dude, I just think
you need to stop going
out to bars.
I think you need
to shut the fuck up,
sit down, relax,
and listen to my shit.
So you gonna listen
to my shit or what?
All right, all right.
Let's hear this shit.
Please, tell me.
Okay.
Well...
It started...
Over there.
I was, uh...
Hanging out with a couple
of logging buddies, right?
It had been a long day.
Lookin' around,
seein' couples,
single girls, single guys,
all on a mission.
Okay, so...
How many more beers
before the girl walks in?
Oh, plenty.
Many, many, many,
many beers.
(Chuckles)
Anyway, this girl...
She was...
Not from around here.
She was classy.
Elegant.
Mnh. There's not many
of those around here.
No shit, Sherlock.
And if I wasn't ice-skating
uphill enough already,
I didn't have a fuckin'
dollar to my name, man.
I mean, I couldn't
buy my own drink,
much less
buy this girl a drink.
It was impossible.
But when has that
ever stopped you?
Yeah, you're right. I'm
a bold motherfucker, right?
I don't have a problem
with this kind of thing.
This is my thing.
But I was...
I was scared, man.
Something about this girl
really intimidated me.
Something... something
turned me to slush.
I didn't know
what I was going
to say to this girl.
Right then,
my guardian angel flew in.
The bartender.
He's my buddy, Joe.
Okay.
He knows I have flies
in my wallet...
But he also sees
that I want to work
some magic on this girl.
So he winks at me
and says, "Matt,
what'll it be?"
And I say,
"I'll take a pike,
"and for this pretty girl
sittin' over here,
"whatever
pretty girls drink.
Put it on my tab."
Ho ho ho!
Bullshit! Bullshit!
( Laughing )
I'm not lying!
I'm telling you the truth.
Why would I lie?
Wow.
Dude, and her voice,
dude, was so sexy.
She says thank you.
She asked my name.
Before I can ask her
her name, she says
her name's Jessica.
We talked
for about 15 minutes,
and then her friend came
and picked her up.
In the blink of an eye...
She's gone.
Typical.
Yeah.
My...
Heart...
Sank.
My throat was in knots.
( Sighs )
Started heading home.
'Bout a mile away...
Lo and behold...
What do I see?
Jessica and her friend.
No shit.
My heart starts going
bup-bup, bup-bup, bup-bup.
I start running towards 'em
fast as I can...
And right before I get there,
this fucking truck comes,
swoops 'em up!
Man, I've known this girl
for less than an hour,
and I'm already, like,
heartbroken.
I mean,
how pathetic is that?
And as I'm standing there
in my little pity party,
what do I see? The truck
is heading right back
to here.
So what do I do?
I start running right back.
I'm not even joking.
I burst through the door.
I literally almost
run her over.
She looks at me. She says,
"I thought you left."
And I said, "I went for you."
She grabs me, she hugs me.
Mnh.
Damn!
She says,
"I came back for you."
I...
I was in love.
Fuck.
What?
( Sighs )
I hate this story.
I hate it.
It consumes me.
I want to be...
Rid of it.
No, Matt, this is
a good story, man.
This is a good story.
This...
You know what?
This is a love story.
Oh. That's how
it always begins.
Yeah? And in the end?
T.b.d.
Love is just the beginning.
Cataclysm.
A match.
A spark of flame.
Male vocalist:
♪ I feel it on my face ♪
♪ the sun
is in your smile ♪
♪ there is
no second place ♪
♪ I'm burning down
these gates ♪
♪ I feel
the pressure fade ♪
♪ if I'm coming undone,
will you ♪
♪ pray for me? ♪
♪ If I'm crawling along,
will you ♪
♪ will you cradle me? ♪
And if you stumble
upon the truth ♪
♪ will you stay with me? ♪
♪ And if we happen
to find our youth ♪
♪ will it set US free? ♪
♪ I feel it on my face ♪
♪ there is no second place ♪
♪ I'm burning down
these gates ♪
( Heavy sigh )
Wow.
Hello?
Is there anyone here?
Hello, Matt.
Hi.
Hey, can you do me
a favor and speak up?
I mean, quiet as fuck.
What?
Oh.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I won't say "fuck."
I'm sorry. My bad.
Tell me about... her.
About her?
Um, well, I guess
you could say things
weren't going that great.
I didn't really think
about it much,
to tell you the truth.
I wasn't suspicious
or anything.
What? I wasn't!
I'm not a jealous guy!
I'm not!
Okay, fine.
Fine!
Whatever. Maybe the night
before my birthday...
I was a little miffed.
I'll give you that.
Fuck.
Mother fucking!
God damn!
What, can I help you
with something?
Yeah.
Dick.
( Cellphone rings )
Yeah, what?
Dave: Whassup, playa?
Happy birthday, son!
My birthday's
tomorrow, genius.
And you know what?
Can you please,
please start talking
like a white person?
Your "g" voice is really
triggering my gag reflex.
( Over-enunciating )
Okay. All right.
Um, what are you up to?
I'm at king's.
Oh, yeah?
Just gettin' a cold one?
Uh, you know what, man?
Right now's not
a very good time.
Why? What's going on?
Jessica's here.
Oh, sorry!
Didn't mean to
interrupt the date.
No, she's laughing it up
with Bruce Willis.
What's she doin'
with Bruce Willis?
No, not really.
Oh, my god, man!
They just keep laughing!
Fuck! I mean,
what's so fuckin' funny?
She's, uh...
She's with another guy?
Yep.
Well, I'm sure
there's an explanation.
I'm sure there is.
Well, I doubt
it's that, man.
You guys are
gettin' married.
I know. Not to mention,
she's carrying my baby.
Heavenly father.
I still can't
imagine you as a dad.
Dude, I'm gonna be
the best dad
in the whole, wide world,
motherfucker.
Oh, let's not get
carried away.
You gonna
talk to Jessica?
Yeah.
( No audible dialogue )
Babe, hi.
Hi, what's crack-a-lackin'?
Um, this is Tyler swift.
He's the new manager
at the bank.
Matt. Heard
so much about you.
Wow. You must be
really, really new,
'cause I have not
heard about you. At all.
I was just getting
Tyler acquainted
with the specifics
of the bank and...
Mmm.
Say your name's
Tyler swift?
Yeah, that's right.
Well, that's a good name.
Yeah. Why don't you sit down
and join US for a few?
Well.
That's so thoughtful.
Nice guy.
Would you care
for a slice?
No.
I'm trying to watch
my figure.
You know how it is.
Hey, baby, you know what?
We should invite him
to my birthday party.
Wouldn't that be awesome?
Yeah, we have
an after-hours staff meeting.
I'm sorry, baby.
I just found out today.
You're not gonna come
to my birthday party?
No. I'm sorry, sweetie.
I'll make it up to you.
Dang.
What do you mean,
when did it start?
How many times
do I have to tell you,
I'm not a jealous guy.
You son of a bitch!
Hey! What are you doing?
Stuart and I are going
to see Aladdin tomorrow.
Can your friends
do this?
do that?
( Shrieks )
Bitch!
Come on, man.
I was, like, 9 years old.
Gimme a break.
Stuart? Man,
he was a tool.
They have
an appointment coming up.
They?
Wow.
Did jennie really marry
that tool bag Stuart?
What is happiness, Matt?
What is happiness?
I don't know.
I thought we were happy.
Now you're making me
think about shit.
What?
Oh, man! Look!
I'm gonna say "shit."
I can't help it.
It's like a force of nature.
I fell in love with her
for a reason. I mean, right?
I mean...
We were happy.
We were happy for a minute.
( Chuckles )
Probably exactly a minute.
Oh, you!
Such a winner.
And the winner
also brought you dinner.
Tacos!
I love tacos!
( Televised monsters
shrieking )
( Man screams )
( Various televised
screams and roars )
Get in the boat!
Come on, get into the--
I can't-- no. I can't
believe you're wearing that.
You're not even
wearing it right.
( Playful growl )
Well, you know I don't
like the water, man.
Honey, breathe.
I love you.
I love you, too.
Whoa! No!
Aaahhh!
Oh my god!
I'm gonna kill you!
( Shrieking )
Purdy damn good
ice cream.
Ice cream
eating contest?
Really?
Really.
You wanna do this?
I wanna do this.
All right, I'm gonna
kick your ass.
Ready, set, go.
( Chuckling )
Yeah.
Oh my god.
This is good!
Oh, god, did you
get brain freeze?
Ha ha ha ha!
You pussy!
Ah, fuck!
( Laughing )
Hi, please press "send"
when you're ready.
Will you marry me?
Yay!
Oh, my god!
All good things must
come to an end, right?
I just wish
it wasn't on my fuck--
I mean freakin' birthday.
Know what I mean?
( Boisterous shouts )
Dave: Happy birthday!
Go bang yo' bay-bay!
Whoo! Don't
forget to pray!
♪ Happy birthday to me... ♪
( Faint chuckle )
Thank you, baby.
( Jessica shrieks
passionately )
Hm.
Fuck.
What the fuck?
The fuck--?
( Passionate moans
and shrieks )
Matt, stop!
Shut the fuck up!
Right now!
Is that my jacket?!
That's my girl, asshole!
You can keep
your fuckin' mom's house!
How's that for
a come shot, bitch?!
Why didn't you walk away?
All I wanted to do was
leave that dirty bitch...
And her boy toy behind,
believe me.
I couldn't.
Fuck!
Literally.
( Mirthless chuckle )
( Indistinct remark )
What?
She did it to herself.
Mind your own business.
Where's my cash?
I'm sorry,
is there something
I can do for you?
Where's the ring?
What did you do
with the ring?
Jessica.
Sir.
Why are you doing this?
Why?
Sir, I'm gonna have
to ask you to step
into my office, bud.
You broke my heart.
Let's take a walk.
Sit down, please.
Cute.
Look, pal, you're
a fuckin' loser.
I know iyou know it,
ashe knows it.
So what do you got
to say for yourself?
All I want to know
is what the fuck is
going on with my account.
Let's take a look.
Well...
Looks like there were
some pretty big purchases
made this morning
at the mall.
Special occasion?
I can tell by the look
you're not happy,
so we'll have
to open a fraud claim
to start an investigation
to see what happened,
of course.
That could take a while.
But after further review,
mutt,
your account barely had
a dollar in it anyways.
So here's
what we're gonna do:
You've still got my wallet
and jacket. Keep 'em.
Hell, pawn 'em.
I guarantee you,
they're worth more
than your account balance
was anyways.
( Groans )
Look, fuck.
I'll see you
on the other side
of the field.
Have a nice day.
( Mirthless laughter )
See ya.
What? What advice?
You mean that guy bill?
That guy was a loon.
( Bill groaning )
( Small object clatters )
( Gargles )
Yi-yi-yi.
Hey!
Gabor!
I don't have anything
for you yet.
But I'm doin'
the best I can.
Y-You gotta remember
that this business
is forever slow.
And that's it.
Slow?
Yeah.
( Eastern European accent )
Oh, slow.
You know what
I'm gonna do?
What?
I'm going to fuck you
real slow
if we don't get
our money, Billy boy!
You gonna fuck me
real slow?
Why the fuck
you wanna do that?
Why don't you do
something professional,
like snapping my fingers
or breaking my knee?
Shut up.
Enough of your shit.
Okay?
'Nuff of my shit?
You get me?
Yeah, I get ya.
( Passionate shriek )
I got news for ya.
You don't even know
my sexual orientation!
What if all I wanted
to do in the world is
get fucked real slow?
Are you gonna reward me
for not paying you?
Shut the fucking fuck up,
Billy, fuck!
I want the money...
By next Tuesday...
Or I'm going
come back in here
and shovel all this
junk in your ass.
Now, why would you want
to shove all this junk
in my ass?
My ass isn't that big.
Do you fuckin' get me?
Yeah, I can see
right through you, buddy.
You're transparent
like a dead scorpion.
I can turn this thing
into a combat zone
just like that.
And you won't have a chance.
You tell your father
I'm gonna pay him
back in full,
I just don't want to be
taken out by your mob.
We ain't no "mob."
We are eastern European
organization.
( Laughing )
That was a good answer.
Are you gonna leave
or something, or...?
I... been looking
for an antique lampshade.
Something, uh, colorful
but still elegant.
Okay, well, back in
the corner there,
I've got some...
Tons of lampshades.
Why don't you go
pick one out?
Perfect.
Thanks, bill.
Hi.
( Chuckles )
You surprised me.
I should keep my eyes
on the perimeter better.
Welcome to my pawn shop.
Good to see you here.
There's lots of
interesting things to buy.
Cool. Your name's
bill, huh? I'm Matt.
Yeah.
How did you know my name?
Uh, nothing.
Well, look, I was hoping
to sell this wallet
to you.
Oh, shit.
Shit what?
Let me tell you, kid,
owning a pawn shop
sucks balls.
I've been open
for three months.
I haven't sold anything.
Oh, man, I could see
how that would suck.
Wait!
What?
Oh! Thank you!
I am going to focus
more on selling
than I am buying.
You know, part of
the problem might be
that you're selling
all this junk.
You should buy this
beautiful billfold wallet.
Leather.
Two bill compartments.
Six card slots.
Voila!
Does it have a 4-leaf
clover on it?
Um, no. No, it doesn't.
Does it have
bugs bunny on it?
No, no bugs bunny.
A yin-Yang sign?
Could paste one on, maybe.
Nah, I can't take it.
This is all I got, man.
Come on.
Wait. Is that a Bentley-
ettiger billfold wallet?
Yeah!
I can't use it.
Well, you know what?
This is all I have.
Looks like you're
having fun with this,
so, uh, thanks
for nothin', dick.
Hey, wait,
I'll buy the wallet.
You will?
Yeah, I'll give you
twenty dollars for it.
Twenty bucks?
Yeah.
Oh, come on, man.
This wallet is worth
way more than that.
I mean, look,
a rich douchebag manager
had to pay well over
a hundred dollars for
a wallet like this.
That wallet's stolen!
I could tell by the way
you walked in here,
you're desperate
and confused.
You're nothin'
but a fuckin'
stink man.
Look, I'm gonna
level with you:
I've been through
a lot lately, okay?
This guy,
he took my girl.
He took my money.
I don't even have
enough gas to get home.
All I have...
Is this wallet.
Please help me.
You're a fuckin' crack head.
I've heard
these stories before.
What you're gonna do,
you're gonna take
the money I give you
for that wallet,
you're gonna go out
and get high
with your buddies
behind the dumpster,
come back in here
and Rob the store.
A crack head virus,
robbing pawnshop
after pawnshop.
That's what you're gonna do.
All right, look.
Believe it or not,
this guy actually
gave me this wallet.
Okay? How do I prove
to you I'm not a crack head?
I'll tell you how
you can prove it.
I won't take the wallet,
but I'll take your coat,
and a crack head doesn't
want to part with something
that keeps him warm.
Sixty dollars, and that
should fill your tank.
Here you go.
Let me be fatherly to you.
I want you to use that
to better your life.
And get out of the past,
quit carrying that
baggage with you
because your future
begins right now.
And this
isn't your last chapter.
And remember
these four words:
It could be worse.
So you're not done.
You're just
beginning again.
I got this thing
I repeat in my head.
It just repeats
over and over again.
It's-- it's not music,
it's... sweet revenge.
You gotta be nice.
Ha ha!
Yeah, nice don't
cut it no more.
Wow! You meet
all kinds of people here.
I mean, seriously,
how was I supposed to have
the foresight to know
that some old pawnshop keeper
would have prophesied
things to come?
I mean, you tell me.
How's a mere mortal supposed
to see that one coming?
Yeah, you think you know
everything, don't you?
Trust me, that was just
the beginning of the spiral.
Things got a whole lot
weirder after that.
( Engine won't start )
Fuck!
You have bad luck.
What?
What do you want, man?
You have bad luck.
I on the other hand
have amazing luck.
I'm so lucky.
Okay, well, you know what?
Mine's infectious,
so, uh, maybe you should
do yourself a favor
and fuck off.
Oh, but I have so much,
I want to share it!
Look, I don't really
have time for a luck-off
right now,
and you're weird.
You're kind of
freakin' me out.
What do you want?
Why you in such big hurry?
You have big hot date?
What?
Yeah. Big hot date.
You've never heard
this phrase before?
No, I don't have a date. Why?
Oh.
You are the guy who
plays on wrong side
of ball team.
I don't get it.
You know...
Bat from behind the plate.
It's been fun, man.
You take care.
Your story in there,
I heard it.
It hurt my heart.
Look... I want to help.
My heart, uh,
it hurts, too.
You got cheated on, too?
Ni! Cheated.
But I... I feel bad.
You know, I...
Go out, I party
too hard one night,
make love to this
beautiful woman,
then I put it in too long,
and... now I have baby.
Well...
Ah, well, fuck it.
I guess it's been
one of those days.
Hey. Step into my office.
Hey! You're gonna
make my day.
( Clears throat )
In return,
I give you money.
What?
Very exciting!
What, like a job?
Yes! Yes, yes.
Very small job,
very soon.
That's very charitable
of you, man.
Chair-table? What is
this? I have no need
for a chair-table.
No, no, no, no.
"Charitable."
you know, like, one word.
It means "giving,"
you know.
It's a joke!
Come on, man!
I'm funny like you.
Not fucking retard.
Okay. I get it,
I guess, man.
What do you want, man?
Okay.
Shit! Fuck, man!
( Laughing )
Hold gun!
Hold gun.
I want to see.
Okay.
All right, big boy,
put it in your pocket
and pull out fast,
like cowboy.
Is this like a test?
All right. Fast, huh?
Oh! Wow, man!
Very fast! Very exciting!
Okay, give me gun.
You look strong.
You punch hard?
Only way I know how,
motherfucker.
All right.
Punch my hand.
I am big boy, too.
I want to feel
how strong you are.
What? Why?
No time
for second-guessing.
You must do what I tell you,
when I tell you!
Ohh! Oh, wow, man,
that's very painful.
Oh my god,
are you okay?
Ah. This is going
to bruise so much.
Oh, no.
Okay! I take you!
What is your name?
Matt.
Hey, Matt, I'm gab--
aah! Gabor.
Gabor, I'm so sorry.
This is fine.
Well, where do you want--
where do you want to go?
I take you for ice cream.
We talk more. Go.
What? Now we're
discriminating?
Oh, come on.
Seemed like a nice guy.
Mobsters are cool, too.
How the hell was I supposed to
know what was going to happen?
I'll tell you,
I'll never look at
bunnies the same way again.
Gabor: I said no clowns!
( Clown horn toots )
You make the kids cry!
You think this is funny?
( Clown horn toots )
What?
Very not professional!
We will not forget this!
Sorry. I had business
to take care of.
Okay, Matt. Are you ready?
( Chuckles )
You must not be scary
like clown.
Yeah, I think I got that.
Matt, my father
is very powerful.
Do not disappoint.
Okay.
Well, what do you
want me to do?
Put on rabbit suit.
What, a birthday party?
Yes. Put on suit.
Hop, hop, hop,
make kids happy.
I have to make balloon
animals and shit?
Can you?
No, not really.
Fine. But you must
learn for other times,
which there will be
many of.
Are you sure you don't
want me to, like,
I don't know,
deliver something,
guard a door,
drive a getaway car?
I mean, this is lame,
man...!
How can I trust you
if you can't
even make kids laugh?
This is easy.
Hop hop,
and I give you money.
I gotta take a piss.
Good.
And take the suit.
Okay.
( Sudden chuckle )
Finally the day
is getting a little better.
Gonna get a lot better.
Aw, shit...!
Huh! Oh, shit!
Okay, guys, come on.
Come to daddy.
Oh, crap.
Whew.
Tyleyou're
a fucking loser.
( Gasps )
( Distorted voices )
Was that Vicodin?
( Passionate scream )
Just... chill out.
All right.
I'll be right out!
Ohh!
Oh, boy.
Okay. Party time.
I just need to rest.
I'm coming!
( Laughing )
I can do this. All right.
Kids' party.
Okay. Okay, man.
Pull yourself together.
Shit.
Where is he?
I don't see him!
Hi!
( All screaming
and shouting )
Shit!
Aaahhh!
Aah!
Aah! Aah!
Oh, shit!
Everyone is
asking for you.
Think you'll make it
down to the party?
Eh.
I got rid of scary clown.
( Chuckling )
I got candy!
This new guy is good.
The kids love
to play with the rabbit.
Hey!
And your grandchildren...
Help!
...are laughing!
Yes!
( Matt shouting )
Oh, no.
Uh, Gabor... hey.
Matt.
My father...
He likes you.
Oh.
You will work
many parties.
Why, uh...
You know what?
Birthday parties
aren't really my thing.
Listen to me.
That was amazing.
I don't know where
you get this energy from,
but... this is your destiny.
Well, I hope not.
Matt.
I am not lying.
This is most very lucky.
Children love you.
You will be great
father one day.
Hey, um...
Hey, do you have
a doctor here,
by any chance?
Why, you don't get hard?
What?
Your dick.
It is always soft?
What the hell?
No.
No. You know what?
I think you left some
pills in the bathroom,
the kids
might have gotten into.
Oh.
Oh, shit.
Okay, I call doc.
But now, we party.
We drink and forget
about the girl.
Okay.
I never turn down
a free drink.
Let's go to my club.
You know what?
What was that stuff,
anyway, do you know?
I mean, the bottle
said Vicodin,
but, uh, yeah.
It's just... no way.
You know what, too?
Thinking back,
I really should have
peaced outta there
with that 300 bucks,
but I was just--
I was really compelled.
I was compelled.
I just wanted to see
where the day would take me.
And by god, did it
fuckin' take me somewhere.
Welcome to Jurassic park.
Ohh! Man!
Just kidding.
Always wanted
to say that shit.
Good fucking movie.
Dinosaurs. Scary shit.
It was all right.
I don't know.
I was always more of
an e.Man, personally.
What are you,
fucking pussy?!
Hey.
Let's go get
drink and discuss
how pussy you are.
For the record,
Jurassic paryes,
it's a much better movie.
Okay? I mean, it's got
Jeff goldblum. Cool.
Dinosaurs. Rad!
But e.T.'S a tender movie.
I was feeling tender.
Looking beautiful,
baby.
Hi, darlin'.
Hi.
What will it be, boys?
Li'l I.P.A.?
Lemon drop.
Sure.
So, you got
a girl at home, Gabor?
Mnh. Not right now.
Fucking bitches are crazy.
They're all crazy.
Must be the weather here.
Yeah, tell me about it.
Yeah. So what happened
with your bitch?
She fucked Tyler swift.
She fucked Taylor swift?
Holy shit!
That is sexy, man!
( Laughing )
Why you so pissed?
No, no, no.
Tyler swift.
As in attractive
asshole bank manager,
not attractive
goddess singer.
You know what I'm saying?
Shit, is that
a shitty name to have.
Yeah, well.
Not like she cared.
So what happened?
She told you?
No, I caught her.
His dick was still in her
when I started kicking
his fucking ass.
( Sighs )
That fucked, man.
Stupid bitches.
I wish I could watch her
burn alive, man.
I wish... I wish
I could turn on the news
and see a fuckin' story
about a terrible
fuckin' accident
involving her.
You are angry
motherfucker, man.
Baby pie, can you
turn on the news for me?
Sure thing, hot lips.
I love it when
she calls me that.
I don't think
that's a chick.
What? What do you mean?
Of course it's a chick.
The woman,
believed to be
in her mid-20s
with brunette hair
has just been identified.
She and another motorist
were killed tragically
in a high-speed collision...
No fucking way.
Holy shit.
We've just confirmed
with police that the identity
of the female victim is
local waitress Kate strange.
Her family could not
be reached for comment.
( Snaps fingers )
So close.
( Chuckles )
Thanks, honey.
Ah, well.
She sounded like
a bitch anyway.
You know what you need,
my friend?
What's that?
You need love companion.
Love companion?
Mm-hmm.
Hm.
Why, you got, like,
pussy flying around
this place or what?
Yes. I. Do.
Please don't judge me.
I not judge.
Holy Moses!
Who? No, Matt,
that's Mabel.
Moses is, like,
from Bible or some shit.
Hm.
Welcome to Gabor's
international house
of pussy.
( Chuckles )
It's on the house
tonight, honey bunny.
Do with him as you wish.
Mmm!
Who is this big
hunk of steaming love, hmm?
Whoa. You sound... strong.
I'm stronger
than any man can handle.
( Phonograph needle
scratches record )
What's your name, cowboy?
I'm Matt. I was
actually gonna go.
Oh, no you're not.
Yeah, I am.
I'm tired.
( Laughing )
Mmm.
So, uh...
Yeah, you're Mabel,
right?
Mm-hmm.
So what do you like?
Uh, I guess I like that.
Ahh.
What?
Are you a naughty boy?
No, I'm not a naughty boy.
Oh, I think you are!
No....
I think you were
naughty today!
( Laughing )
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Can we just talk, please?
Yeah, okay. Okay.
What's wrong?
I don't know,
I'm nervous.
I haven't been
around such a mature,
beautiful woman like you.
Ohh.
You don't have to be
shy around me, you know.
Mother Mabel
is here to help you,
so just... spit it out.
Well.
Yeah.
Okay.
Well...
Uh...
Whew.
Well, that's
quite the story.
Yeah.
You're telling me.
Now I'm the father
of this baby
that's being carried
inside of this whore,
and...
I'm sorry, but...
I can't think
of anything else,
just frickin'
wringing her throat.
Have you really
thought about this?
Of course I have.
I mean...
No, I mean about why
this happened.
What?
I think what
you've got to do
is you have
to focus on what
really matters here.
I don't know if
I articulated this clearly--
hey. Look.
I've been there.
I've made my mistakes.
God knows
I have paid for them.
But if you don't
figure out why she did
what she did,
you're in big trouble.
No. I'm sorry.
Unh-unh.
There's no excuse--
no excuse for
what she's done whatsoever.
If you don't understand,
then you can't let it go.
You can't move on, so you've
got to understand why.
Why does a woman
fall for a man?
She falls for
the whole package.
She chooses how much
money he earns,
what his job is.
That's what it is.
I know. I know.
I've been where you are.
I-I-I blamed the whole world
for all my problems.
Boo hoo! Sob, sob, sob.
Poor me, poor me!
It was not easy just...
Climbing myself back up
to some good place.
So... you're
in a good place?
Couldn't be happier.
Really?
Of course I'm not happy!
Life is shit!
I'm 65 years old,
and I sleep with drunken
fools for a living.
And Gabor only keeps me
here because I look
enough like a man
so he can get his rocks off
from time to time.
Aha! I knew there was
something with that guy, man.
I knew it.
Look.
You have to walk away
while you still can,
while you can get out of it.
She's gonna regret
that decision.
You know, you can be
sure of that.
But if you don't get up
and get out of here,
you're gonna end up
a 65-year-old barmaid
begging for crack
and making tips.
You beg for crack?
Sometimes.
Wow.
Trust me, honey.
Just take those
sexy legs of yours
and just march on
out of here.
Why don't you?
Where am I gonna go?
Well, I don't know.
Anywhere could be
better than here, right?
Look at you, turning
the tables on me!
Ha ha ha!
I'm kind of institutionalized
within the family.
I used to work
for Gabor's dad.
You don't just
walk away from that.
Oh, that's not true.
Everyone gets
a second chance, right?
If you want it bad enough.
Even Jessica?
Even you?
I'll tell you what.
What?
I'll make you a deal.
Okay.
If you get out of here...
If you woon
getting out of here,
I'll work on forgiving her.
Ooh! ( Laughing )
You're quite
the negotiator here.
Well...
All right.
Thank you for
your insight, miss Mabel.
Ah. Mother Mabel.
Mother Mabel.
Well, thank you.
( Chuckles )
Uh, wa-- um.
Before you go,
on your way out,
could you just--
could you...
Tell... Gabor...
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
You were the ride
of my life.
Right. Thank you.
Good luck!
Thank you.
Yeah, you know what?
That really was
good advice.
It really was.
Yep.
Too bad.
Had to go out and drink
four pink panty droppers.
I forgot every word.
( Laughing )
Ohh.
Ahh!
Fuck!
Hey!
Voices: Matt! Matt!
Matt! Matt! Matt! Matt!
Let's do it!
To Vegas again!
Let's do this again.
Memories, let's do it.
Matt.
What the shit?
Chill out, man.
Here.
Drink vodka.
Thank you.
By the way...
That's the douchebag,
over there.
Who?
Ahh.
That fuck,
he's the one that
ploughed my girlfriend.
The fuck is in my club?
The fuck is in your club.
Next time we go to Vegas,
you guys need to...
Excuse me.
( Swift continues chattering )
Hey!
Something I can
help you with, friend?
Your name is...?
Tyler.
Tyler swift.
Your name is Tyler swift?
So?
What?
Do you fuck mothers?
( Chuckling )
Excuse me?
Do. You.
Fuck. Mothers?
My boy Matt here
is expecting a baby
from that
mother you fucked.
No.
No, he isn't.
What the fuck
did you say, bitch boy?
I said, she sold
that cheap-ass
fuckin' engagement ring
and aborted the bastard.
You fuckin' ass!
That was fucking
mistake, buddy.
She needed help,
so I helped.
Eh... more like encouraged.
Hell.
I just told her to do it.
What you lookin' at, ugly?
( Sniffing )
Smell like...
Smell like pussy!
Fuck no! Motherfucker!
Take him out!
Looks like you all fucked
with the wrong guy
in the wrong club.
( Indistinct grunts )
Shut the fuck up.
( Tyler grunts )
He's all yours, Matt.
Aah!
Look at me!
You think she could ever
love a loser like you?
You were
a seat-filler, pal!
What'd you fuckin'
say to me?
You heard me.
This motherfucker!
( Tyler grunting )
...the fuck down there.
I'm gonna rip your
fuckin' head off.
You hear me?
Gabor: Okay.
Okay, buddy.
Cool off, cool off,
cool off.
Go cool off.
Ahhh!
Fuck!
Now.
Listen to me, swift.
Hey!
Hey, buddy.
You're an asshole.
I get it.
But there's some shit
you just don't joke about.
So I'm gonna ask you
one time...
And don't
fucking lie to me...
His girl really
get an abortion?
You fucking punk.
Hear me.
When your fucking wife
is pregnant,
I'm going to find you,
I'm going to fuck her,
then...
Then I'm going to cut out
the little bastard
and fuck him, too!
You're going to fuck
my unborn son?
What the fuck?
Ywant to die?
Get out of here!
Piece of shit!
Is it hard to understand
me or something?
Oh, shit, man!
Buttfucking! Buttfucking!
That's all they hear,
is "buttfucking"!
What kind of world
do we live in?
It's not about
fucking the butts.
It's about fucking
killing people!
She killed my... kid.
With your engagement ring.
Don't forget that part.
That sort of makes it
really juicy, you know?
( Sighs )
What do you want to do?
You want to kill her?
We could like, uh,
crucify her.
You know, like Jesus.
I need to talk to Dave.
Hey, I know.
What about, uh, Dave?
I mean, he's one of your bros.
He'll vouch for me, right?
Is vouching for you.
Oh.
Oh, I get it.
You guys are just
pickin' on me
'cause I'm the one
that took the bullet.
Did you guys talk to
that prick Tyler yet?
Tyler
had his appointment.
He's gone.
Where did he go?
( Chortling )
Sucker.
I... sorry.
♪ Pop their melons,
I'm poppin' pills ♪
♪ bangin' that puddin'
like a dewalt drill ♪
♪ now, let's go ♪
♪ awol ♪
♪ on that, drywall ♪
♪ 'cause purdies come cheap
at the home depot ♪
♪ with the groupie
groupon coupon ♪
♪ 'cause I go on and on ♪
♪ on and on,
on and on ♪
like the energizer ♪
♪ I spill inside her ♪
♪ deep and hard,
till her eye hurts ♪
♪ then I get my iPhone,
call another gal's phone ♪
♪ 'cause tonight
is goin' down... ♪
( Wet bowel movement )
♪ Say come kitty-kitty,
while I'm rubbin' that kitty ♪
♪ come kitty-kitty,
when I'm rubbin' that kitty ♪
when I'm rubbin' the kitty ♪
♪ come kitty, kitty, kitty ♪
♪ kitty, kitty, kitty,
yeah ♪
Yo yo day-Dave.
Shoot, playa, what's up?
Oh, for real?
A'ight, a'ight.
One sec.
There. Now.
Poop in peace.
Take care of that now.
What up, playa?
Desperate times
truly do call for
desperate measures.
What brings you
to my sanctum?
Come on, man,
just let me in.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Maybe the question is...
Who brings you here?
Really?
Your best friend, Matt.
Remember me?
All right. Good answer.
Come in.
Quickly.
We're all hurting.
I can feel this is
something beyond what
you can handle.
Where is your strength,
your faith?
You have not visited
for some time, and yet
the church remains here,
always here... for you.
Still rambling gospel
rants I see, Dave.
Dude, don't mock my sh--
stuff.
My stuff is legit.
Because I have seen
the unknown
in your unblinking eyes,
I have felt the shadows forming
into your childhood fears,
your heart, like a war drum,
beating frantically
to a distant, dying army,
the smell of...
( Laughing )
See?
It's gettin' to ya.
( Exhales )
All right.
Jessica cheated on me.
With her boss.
Rich douchebag.
She took all my money.
Now I've got mixed up
working for some mob
boss's son.
To top it off,
she aborted my child.
She aborted my...
Child, man!
( Heavy sigh )
( Laughing )
Well. Well... at
least she didn't
pay for the abortion
with the ring you got her.
I mean...
( Chuckling )
No.
She couldn't.
O-Okay. This Princess
needs to die. Let's go.
No, let's just...
Just sit for a minute.
Okay.
( Breathing deeply )
I need a shot.
Nope.want a shot.
Do you want a shot?
Yeah, I would love one.
Thank you.
Is this kosher?
Why do you think we're
always turning away?
We're doing shots, son.
Bottoms up.
My glass is broken.
♪ Aaahhh ♪
Fixed!
Aah!
You know what?
I really...
I swear to god,
I fantasize.
I fantasize about
killing her, man.
Like, over and over
and over again in my head.
It's like thosaw movies.
I want her to be every
character that dies
in those movies.
Well, one thing's for sure.
I know.
She needs to die.
No!
( Scoffs )
Come on, man!
Do you want to be
the villain?
She's the villain!
She killed your child!
We gotta do something
that's gonna last forever.
A tattoo for the soul,
always reminding her
to watch her back.
Fear is an amazing
art, my friend.
Very difficult to master,
but when done right,
can give you
complete control.
And really make
somebody's life crappy.
( Laughs )
What the hell do you
know about fear?
Everything.
I studied...
Religion.
Good point.
Got any ideas?
Not much.
Damn.
Well, you know,
you said you were working
for that mafia boss.
That's a good place
to start.
Yeah, except
Jessica's not having
any birthday parties.
Birthday parties?
Just forget about it.
Are you friends with him?
I don't know, man.
I guess.
Well, you know who is.
Money.
We gotta get some.
And no, Matt,
we're not gonna take money
out of the donation box,
okay? That is...
I know, I know, I know.
It's yours.
Ha.
You hungry?
No.
Want a pizza?
Okay.
Wh... what is it?
It's a vault code.
A vault code?
A vaul-- a vault code?
It's-- it's a vault code.
Holy crap!
( Both laughing )
Yup.
The plot thickens.
Bee-itch.
So, Peter cottontail,
my boys told me
you really needed to talk.
What's up?
Did he just
call me a rabbit?
Gabor, how you doin', man?
Been good and bad.
But mostly okay.
What...
What does that mean?
So, basically, you're
saying you're everything?
It okay, Matt.
Like woman's period.
You go with flow.
Dude, like, seriously,
I mean, why can't you
just say river?
Yes, like river.
And right now,
I am big fat beaver
making tampon dam.
( Laughing )
Like, what the fuck?
Where do you get
this shit from, man?
Who's this?
This is my buddy Dave.
Uh...
Pleasure to meet you.
I... I...
Um....
Matt's told me
so much about you.
Uh...
Well, nothing
incriminating, you know.
He just mentioned you,
uh, to me.
Uh, only me, because
I'm his best friend,
you know, and-- and
I wouldn't say anything.
And... I'm not wired.
If that's what you're thinking.
Jesus, Dave!
( Stammering )
Dave! Mellow out, man!
Come on!
Calm down, man.
God!
Relax.
What are you worried about?
Going to heaven?
Well, uh...
I just hear the lines
are pretty long
this time of year.
( Laughing )
Hey, this guy's funny!
Like you. Maybe we
put him in suit.
Yeah, he loves easter,
too, you know?
Um, again,
with the rabbit?
Um, is this some sort
of mafia code?
Not mafia!
Eastern European
organization.
O... Kay.
Okay, clowns,
what are you doing here?
Tell him.
All right, look.
I, uh, came across something
that might interest you,
and I thought we could
trade for it.
Matt, you are like
full-time employee
already.
I didn't know who else
to go to.
Okay.
Before we get going,
you need to know:
If you fuck me,
I fuck you. Harder.
I don't want to fuck you.
No, you don't, because I
fuck everyone in this city
who tries to fuck me.
Understood.
Good. Now what the fuck
do you guys want?
Look.
What is this?
It's a code
to a vault in a bank,
and since i'm
not a bank robber,
I thought it might
interest you.
I have plenty of money.
I have no need
to Rob bank.
Listen. Gabor, this isn't
robbing a bank, okay?
This is winning the lotto.
It's a cakewalk.
You're not dealing
with panicked managers
fumbling keys.
There's no hero guards
ready to shoot.
The place barely
has any employees.
We don't
even want the money.
So, why?
We want you
to scare the living
daylights out of his girl.
Trauma!
So the bitch works
in the bank, huh,
bunny boy?
And you want big,
scary eastern European
organization
to make her sorry.
Yeah. Let her know that
you'll always be watching.
Make her question every
decision in her life,
and then
tell her one day,
finally,
you will come for her.
And what religion are you?
It's a progressive branch.
We call it...
If you fuck my friend,
I fuck you!
This I understand.
The urban dictionary
defines
the modern use of
the word "clusterfuck"
as any situation with
a large scale of disarray.
Yup.
Yo, what time is it, man?
( Sighs )
Guess he must be stuck
in traffic or something.
I don't know.
I'm worried, man.
Look, they're only
two minutes late.
It'll be all right.
Okay.
Ohh!
Here we go!
I can't believe this
is happening, man.
I swear to god,
I hope that bitch
has a heart attack.
I'm gonna have
a heart attack, okay?
( Chuckling )
Hey, hey.
No problem.
Glad I'm here.
You remember that time
we robbed that video store
and we stole those pogs?
God!
( Both laughing )
I've never seen you
so scared, man.
I've never.
I wasn't that scared.
Come on.
Dude, I've never seen you
more scared in my life.
You were about to
shit your pants.
You were being
such a little bitch!
I think that's when I
decided to become a priest.
( Both laughing )
Pogs!
Pogs were cool.
Oh, they were swell,
weren't they?
( Gunshots )
Holy mother of god!
Holy--!
( Screaming )
Wha--?
( Screams and gunfire )
( Cellphone rings )
Who's that?
Gabor: Matt!
What?
The shit's
going real bad!
Matt? What?
Fuck!
Matt!
Holy--!
Father, forgive me.
Ohh...!
Oh, god.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
What the fuck? Fuck!
Gabor: God! Shit!
I'm not fucking!
Calm down, please,
Gabor. Let's think
about this.
Everyone
is gonna get fucked!
Gabor.
( Indistinct shouts )
Get outta here, man.
Go, go.
I told you!
I told you if you fuck me,
I will fuck you harder!
Dave: Please,
forgive them.
Gabor: You understand me?
What am I gonna tell
my father? Huh?!
( Indistinct remark )
Matt: We can
get out of this!
Gabor: What am I gonna
tell my father?
Gabor, please!
I don't wanna die!
Jesus!
What the fuck
is going on here?
Please.
Are you part of this, Matt?
Drop the gun, bitch!
Dave:
Please, Gabor! Gabor!
Matt: Please...
Please...
Drop the fucking gun!
Please.
Jessica, just drop
the gun, okay?
Jessica: ...Fuck up, Dave!
Shut up, Dave!
I'm not waiting.
I will fuckin' kill you.
No! No.
Please.
Please, not her.
Matt.
What?
You gave up!
What did you expect? Huh?
Love.
Respect.
Baby, you loved me.
I loved you so much.
You know what I wanted?
Was a little fucking loyalty.
I.. I'm done.
I'm done.
Okay?
It's over, it's over.
It's done. Just--
fuck you, Dave!
Fuck you!
Go, quietly. Go.
No!
( Gunshots )
Dave: Matt? Matt?
Matt!
Dave: Oh, my god!
Dave: Come on!
Wow.
I guess this is the part
where I'm supposed
to ask for forgiveness,
say I'm sorry
for all the things
I've done
and all the people
I've hurt?
I didn't want her dead,
okay?
I didn't.
But...
The world...
Will be a much,
much better place
without people like her
walking around.
( Gasps )
Holy shit!
Matt, I don't think
I've introduced myself.
Michael.
Hi.
I'm fucked.
Well, my colleagues, they
aren't charmed about you.
( Mirthless chuckle )
No kidding.
The ruling suggests that
we sentence you to
eternal damnation.
( Clicks tongue )
Fantastic.
But I have a proposition
I'd like to discuss with you.
I got plenty of time.
That's cute.
That's funny.
They've been watching you
from upstairs,
and, well, they were
particularly taken
by what you said
at the end there.
Mm-hmm?
That the world would be
a better place
without women like Jessica.
We agree with you.
You do?
We do.
We'd like you
to work for US.
Matt, the world
has become infected:
Adultery, lies, greed,
corruption.
The lands are
overrun with sin.
We considered taking away
life altogether.
But while we all
agree that mankind
has been corrupted,
there are a lot of
good people left trying
to hold it all together.
It isn't fair to them.
So for them, we'd like
to help clean up the mess.
Matt, we need someone
to act on our behalf.
So...
You want me to be
your hit man?
Exactly.
And you want me to get rid
of the liars
and cheats and whores?
Exactly, Matt.
Clean house.
What if I don't?
Eternal damnation.
( Chuckling )
That's a tough choice.
When do I start?
Right away.
With Jessica.
What?
She survived her wounds.
If she recovers, if she
enters the world again,
she'll hurt others.
May I ask you a question?
Why did you step
in front of her?
You protected her.
Why did you do that?
I trust it will not
be an issue.
We'll be watching.
What?!
I know, man.
I mean, it's hard
for me to believe, too.
No, no. Bullshit!
Look, man,
they gave me a list.
This thing's long.
How long?
Oh, boy.
About two bloody
murderous years.
I mean, if you think
about it, I had to die...
To figure out what
I was supposed to do.
Guess... better late
than never, right?
Jesus, man.
Nah, nah, he already
did his thing.
Between you and me...
I don't think he really
thought it through
the first time.
Well, if he had, I'd be
out of a job, right?
Hold on.
Jessica isn't dead.
Yeah.
She's last on my list.
I guess
you could say she's...
Kinda what keeps me goin'.
Why are you telling me this?
Well... let me see.
Oh, this...
This fucking thing.
Just bear with me
for a second. It's...
( Muttering softly )
Ah.
Okay.
What the fuck is that?
Hey, hey, hey.
No, no, no, no, no.
What the fuck is that?
Calm down.
Calm down. Listen.
I kinda heard you been up
to some bad shit lately.
I didn't want to do this--
what the fuck?!
Hold on. I didn't want
to do this to a friend.
No! No, fuck this!
What are you gonna do?
You're just gonna fuckin'
kill me right here
at this bar?
( Laughing )
I'm sorry,
I already kind did.
I mean...
I dropped it in your glass
while you were taking a piss.
Should be taking effect
already, actually.
I mean... it's kinda weird.
Oh, shit.
There we go.
Whoops.
Okay.
Rest in peace, buddy.
♪ Well, I'm a great
crowd-pleaser ♪
♪ when I'm doin' events ♪
( Indistinct lyric )
When are you gonna realize
that the role of
the white famous rapper
has been filled?
Whoa, whoa!
We all have dreams, 'Kay?
Hmm.
I don't think I'm ever
gonna settle comfortably
into boy wonder.
I hate Robin.
I know.
That's what I'm sayin'.
Robin's a boob, man.
I don't wanna be--
I don't wanna be Robin.
This is why Superman
works alone.
What? What?!
Hey, did you really
just quote that movie?
Dude, I have no idea
what you're talking about.
Aw, man,
are you serious, man?
Hey, seriously, hey,
when we get done
killing all these people,
I'm gonna teach you
some taste, my friend.
Yeah. Hey, daddy dig,
do me a favor and get
in the truck.
( Humorless chuckle )
Funny. Hilarious.
We need to work on
our communication.
Okay, now who's quoting
shitty movies, huh?
What? Are you--?
What?! What?!
Oh, man, are you--
did you really just--?
Holy ffffuck!
( Rock music playing )
Vocalists: ♪ ooohhh ♪
Male vocalist:
♪ if I'm coming undone ♪
♪ will you ♪
♪ pray for me? ♪
♪ If I'm crawling along ♪
♪ will you,
will you cradle me? ♪
♪ And if you stumble
upon the truth ♪
♪ will you stay with me? ♪
♪ And if we happen
to find our youth ♪
♪ will it set US free? ♪
♪ I feel it on my face ♪
♪ the sun is in your smile ♪
♪ there is no second place ♪
♪ no living in denial ♪
♪ I'm burning down
these gates ♪
♪ we'll make it
all worthwhile ♪
♪ I feel the pressure fade ♪
♪ if I'm walking along,
will you ♪
♪ walk with me? ♪
♪ If I Bury myself in you ♪
♪ will you uncover me? ♪
♪ And if you happen
to hear my call ♪
♪ will you wait for me? ♪
♪ And if we're corrupted
by it all ♪
♪ we can be redeemed ♪
♪ I feel it on my face ♪
The sun is in your smile ♪
There is no second place ♪
♪ no living in denial ♪
I'm burning
down these gates ♪
♪ we'll make
it all worthwhile ♪
♪ I feel the pressure fade ♪
♪ I feel it on my face ♪
The sun is in your smile ♪
♪ there is no second place ♪
♪ no living in denial ♪
I'm burning
down these gates ♪
♪ we'll make it
all worthwhile ♪
♪ the pressure fades ♪
♪ The pressure fades away ♪
♪ the pressure fades away ♪
♪ Pressure fades away ♪