[music playing]
Bonnie?
Jackie?
Oh my God, Jackie.
Bonnie Blackwell.
Oh my-- how good to see you.
It's so good to see you.
Thank you for coming.
Thanks for inviting me.
How are you?
I'm fabulous.
And I can be worse--
Thomas Marshall High School!
I mean, look at you.
You still look like
a Greek goddess.
Thanks.
You're looking very
prosperous yourself.
Ah, you don't
have to be so nice.
I can never break those
midnight runs for fast food.
So I know the manager.
Heaven.
Oh my God, you just
make me green with envy.
What are you still doing?
Gymnastics?
No, I gave it up
a long time ago.
Didn't fit in with the marriage
if you know what I mean.
Yes, I do.
The things we do for
that band of gold.
It's a crime sometimes.
My God, it's so good to see you.
What?
What is that?
Oh, God.
It's nothing.
Slipped in the kitchen, caught
it on the refrigerator door.
A little clumsy, I guess.
Clumsy, yeah, I remember
you being clumsy once when--
no, I've never
remembered you being--
Darling, I'll tell you that.
I'd like you to meet
my husband Zach.
He's a great guy.
- Oh, good.
OK.
Zach.
Zach, Honey.
Sorry, I'd like you to
meet a good friend of mine
that I invited, Jackie Prentiss.
We were in the pep squad
back in the dark ages
at Thomas Marshall High.
That's nice.
Nice to meet you.
Honey, excuse me.
Honey, I'm kind of in the
middle of an important business
meeting right now.
Well, do you mind, Honey?
Just thought you
might want to meet.
That's nice.
Isn't that nice what she talked?
So nice.
Go get yourself
something to eat.
Something to drink.
Get something.
But actually-- Hey, guys.
Hey, guys, can I
get you something?
Oh no, anything.
Come on, you haven't eaten any.
No, I guess we're just fine.
Jenny, nice to meet you.
Go get yourself
something to eat.
Oh.
Sorry about that.
Zach's been pretty much
business these days.
He's a commodities
trader for the far East.
Don't ask me what he trades.
There's a lot of
pressure on him.
He does well though.
I don't know even what
I'd do without him.
We can all dream, honey.
Walk me to the bar, huh?
You got to talk?
Bonnie.
Or you can have
another silent epic.
I have nothing to
say to you, Zach.
I think I have
something to say.
I have more important
things to discuss, Bonnie.
More important things
to discuss than fashion
tips, particularly,
with your fat friends.
Oh, yeah, you're
really important stuff.
Hey!
Who the hell you think
you're talking to?
Huh?
No!
Don't hurt me please.
- I don't have to what?
Huh?
I don't have to what?
Hey, Bonnie, shut up!
I put this roof over your head.
I put you these
fine clothes, Honey.
I do, Honey.
Honey, I love you, baby.
And then what do you do?
Huh?
You bitch.
Yeah, you bitch about
having nothing to wear, huh?
I didn't mean to butt in!
I just don't like
being embarrassed
in front of visitors.
Oh, baby, baby.
I'm embarrassing, huh?
I'm embarrassing.
That's what you told that
fat porky you were with, huh?
[screaming]
All right, I let you go.
I let you go.
Look, baby, I let you go.
See, I let you go.
I'll let you go.
Huh?
Hey, you bad mouth
me in public, Bonnie.
And you know what
that does to me.
Huh?
You know what that does to me.
You know what that
does to my business?
Huh?
You have any idea?
You have any idea what you're
saying, you stupid bitch?
You stupid, stupid bitch.
[crying]
Get over there.
Look at this.
What is all of this, huh?
What is this?
What?
You think you piss perfume?
Huh?
Is that what you think?
You piss perfume?
[screaming]
Piss all up in you.
Oh, do you hear that?
Listen, listen,
listen, listen, Honey.
Shut up.
Shut up!
Listen.
You're pissing off the
neighbors again, Bonnie.
[screaming]
You look pathetic.
Shut up out there!
Can't a guy have a
discussion with his wife?
Huh?
God damn it, Bonnie.
Oh, Bonnie.
Come here, Bonnie.
Bonnie.
Bonnie?
Don't play this game
with me, Bonnie.
Bonnie.
Bonnie, open the door.
I swear to Christ, I'll
break this door down.
Open the door.
Bonnie.
Open the door or I'll
break it in half.
It's all right.
You've got to come
out some time, baby.
You've got to out some--
[screaming]
No.
OK, please.
You bailing out on me, Bonnie?
Is that what you're doing?
Yeah, that's what you're doing.
You planned this for some
time, didn't you, Bonnie?
I swear.
What?
You don't think I know
how your head works?
[screaming]
That's how your
head works, whore.
[screaming]
That's how your head works.
You little whore.
[engine starts]
You want to know
how your head works?
I'll show you how
your head works.
[screaming]
[crashing]
[police sirens]
You don't say anybody
did anything, you hear?
Can you believe it?
Break problem.
I guess, that's why
we have insurance.
Can I help you, officer?
SGT. BILL STARR: Save
the charm, Blackwell.
We've been through this.
Well, correct me
if I'm mistaken,
but unless you have
some kind of warrant,
you got no right to be here.
Where's your
wife, Mr. Blackwell?
But my wife is my business.
Hey!
God, this one
needs an ambulance.
This is our sixth call
in the past two months.
Are you willing to
wait for number seven?
Tell him it's
all right, Bonnie.
No.
I want to file a suit.
[beeping in background]
WOMAN [ON LOUDSPEAKER]: Dr.
Flores, dial 182, please.
Dr. Flores, please dial--
Morning.
How do you feel?
Kind of--
Kind of hurts when I breathe.
You have a hairline
fracture on one
rib and your right cheek bone.
You also have a little cartilage
damage on your left shoulder
and a few other bruises
thrown in for good measure.
It'll all heal if
you give it a chance.
Hey, Doc.
Yeah.
You charge extra
for the place?
It's all part of the deal.
There's someone here to see you.
Sergeant.
Mrs. Blackwell.
Is he?
He's still in lock up.
You still want to press charges?
Yes.
I have to now.
If he ever came back home--
I think we can put him
away for a long time.
Time enough for you to get
on your feet and decide
what to do.
I got you something.
WOMAN [ON LOUDSPEAKER]:
Dr. Kravitz, you have
a visitor in the main lobby.
Dr. Kravitz--
Figured I'd get
you some protection.
Thank you, that's very
sweet of you, Sergeant.
Bill Starr, please.
Bonnie.
You must see a lot
of people in trouble
in your line of business.
Why is this for me?
Maybe I just got tired of
acting like it didn't matter,
like it was just part of
the job watching women
take it from creeps like that.
There's nothing
you could've done.
I'm a cop.
I'm supposed to be there.
The whole hero complex, right?
Well, I think you're a hero.
When you get out
of here, come see me.
I'll show you a few
pointers in self-defense.
He won't stay in
jail forever, Bonnie.
You got time.
Just think about it, OK?
[beeping in background]
Oh, my feet are killing me.
Oh.
Want some coffee.
Yeah.
You know, I don't
think women will ever
be totally liberated
until we stop wearing
high heels designed by men.
I know, right?
Give me the milk.
You left the TV on.
I know.
I always do.
Just as a precaution.
You don't have to be
so scared anymore, honey.
The judge put him away
for at least two years.
Yeah, and then what
happens after that?
I mean, just look at me.
I'm on my own, I don't even
have a job or anything.
Whoa.
This is not the Bonnie
Blackwell I remember.
I do not like what the last
eight years have done to you.
Yeah.
Hey, I did this to myself.
That bastard has you running
around like a church mouse.
You know, you used to be such
a jock in high school, had
all the confidence I wanted.
You got to get that
back again, honey.
Become the person
that you really are.
Yeah, you know, I think
you're right about that, Jackie.
Maybe I can do that and get
career at the same time.
Bill Starr's been talking to me.
He had an idea.
Whoa, whoa, wait a
minute, Angie Dickinson.
I did not say that you
should become a cop.
Nobody messes with cops.
Everybody messes with cops.
What do you want to hang around
with the scum of the Earth
for the rest of your life?
Yeah, I think I
did that already.
Zach's going to get out someday,
and I can't spend the rest
of my life afraid of him.
I'm so sick of it.
Just let somebody
else be afraid.
You're scaring
the hell out of me.
[marching music]
TRAINING OFFICER: Go, boy,
let's go, on the wall.
SGT. BILL STARR: If you
really wanted to become a cop,
the first thing
you have to do is
impress your training officer.
It's going to take a
lot of work and study
before they accept you.
Months of testing and training.
I'm ready.
I know I can do it though.
I've always been a good
student, and very athletic.
And you don't even
have to be easy on me.
No chance of that.
Everybody gets the
same treatment.
OK.
Why don't you give that a try?
Sure.
[grunting]
JARVIS: I don't think
it's going to happen.
Give me just a second, Jarvis.
Here, let me show
you how it's done.
I got 20 years on you, kid.
You've got to do a
lot better than that.
You have to be in as good
a shape as the people
you'll be chasing.
Better.
But don't worry,
we'll get there.
[martial arts chanting]
Wow.
God, that instructor's
really tough.
You ain't seen nothing yet.
There's the man you
have to impress.
[grunting]
Oh my God.
A side of beef with an attitude.
A real attitude.
Wow.
You ought to feel like crap.
You know why?
Because you got nothing.
Nothing.
You think you can beat
them just with your body?
You got to use your
mind, your head.
Huh?
I'll tell you what, see
Rodriguez over there?
Watch me handle him.
He's about my size.
[grunting]
Hello, Bill.
- Hey, Lebell.
How are you?
How's Sammy?
She's OK.
Great, great.
This is Bonnie Blackwell,
a personal friend.
I've got a feeling she's
going to be a tough recruit
once I get through with her.
Well, you better make
her nice and tough.
I hate it when they're
too easy to kick around
like Rodriguez over there.
She'll do just fine.
Is he OK?
Hey, Rodriguez, Sleep good?
Sorry, sir.
I guess I deserved that one.
So you still want to be a cop?
Yes, I do.
Can I ask you one
question though?
- Sure.
- Who's Sammy?
My daughter.
Really?
She was in a situation like
you with that husband of yours.
She took a lot of shit.
She lost her first
baby because of him.
My grandchild.
Oh, Bill, I'm sorry.
Fresh meat.
Get over here.
Give me your jacket.
Me?
Yeah, come on,
give me your jacket.
[music playing]
And the glasses.
Now, get in there.
Any of you two
know each other?
No.
Riley, show her the
first step to self-defense.
[grunting]
First rule, be alert.
The world needs more alerts.
Second rule, learn how to fall.
Ronnie, take her
through the routine.
[grunting]
God.
Hey, Bill.
What's an old war
horse like you doing
hanging out with the new guys?
Ah, just fielding
a new prospect.
What, her?
[grunting]
I think your days as a talent
scout are numbered, my friend.
She'll be great.
You look good up there.
The first day is
always the toughest.
Bonnie, I'd like you
to meet John Beaudet.
Super cop, a legend
in his own mind.
- Hi, good to meet you.
- It's a pleasure.
What's a nice girl
like you doing hanging
out with a bum like this?
Learning, a lot.
Well, you came
to the right guy
if you like the
mature veteran type.
I'll be seeing you around.
Jee, that guy seems to be
his own best friend, huh?
John's OK.
You'd do well to end up
with a partner like him.
Well, this is what you wanted,
kid, official academy training.
I'm feeding you to Lebell
for real this time.
You're on your own this time.
Come on, take it like a man.
Right, like a man.
[grunting]
Two, step forward.
Three, pop to the groin.
Fourth, knee the groin.
Step back.
Draw your weapon.
Hands up!
Get down on your knees!
[grunting]
ACADEMY TEACHER: Remember
the cycle of violence
is remorseful stage
into the tension stage
into the acute
battering stage and then
back into the remorseful stage.
You've got the cycle and
it's a continuous cycle,
going on and on and on.
OK, any other questions?
ACADEMY STUDENT: Yeah.
Why would a woman
stay in a relationship
where she's battered?
[grunting]
Oh, there you go.
Beat yourself up.
Let's do it again.
Nah, give it a rest.
I want to do it
again, Lebell, please.
OK.
[grunting]
Ow, Jesus.
God, I can't believe
how out of shape I'm in.
I'm starting to make
me feel guilty again.
You ready for chapter
two Wonder Woman?
Yeah, let's do it.
OK.
Arrest procedures, auto.
Call in location
or stop and check
license plate before
leaving police unit.
Instruct driver to place his
hands on the steering wheel.
Approach driver side
window with caution,
leaving firearm
free at all times.
Check back seat for other
passengers or suspicious items.
Note driver's features,
eyes, hair, weight.
Request driver's license
and registration.
Excuse me, Sergeant.
- Go ahead.
Hypothetically
asking, if a woman was
in a domestic relationship
and she had been beaten
several times, and
what really drew
the line was her being
completely battered
and in the hospital.
Her husband threatened her--
threatened to kill her.
Would he actually-- actually do
it and proceed in his threat?
Absolutely.
Remember the lethality
checklist we talked about.
Remember one of them was the
threats to the victim, threats
to the children, the family
members, even to the pet,
also the fantasies
of the threats.
Absolutely.
If this person is in
jail, I guarantee you
that if this person
gets out, he's going
to try to complete the threat.
It's the same if he's
running around loose right
now, I guarantee you he will
try to complete that threat
and kill her.
[gun shots]
That's pretty good, kid.
Where have been shooting?
I haven't shot before, sir.
Just thought about it a lot.
Hey, well, you're a natural.
You keep that up and you'll
have no problems at all.
Let's try it again.
[screaming]
[grunting]
Hey.
Great day for a run.
What are you doing here?
Well, I like to keep
up with my exercise.
You know, I get a little
soft riding around in a unit
all the time.
I can imagine.
You're looking pretty tough.
I hear you're doing well.
Just doing the best I can.
Ah, but is it good enough?
Want to race?
First one to the
end buys dinner.
You'll never do it, kiddo.
OK.
Try me, tough guy.
Come on, Blackwell.
Oh, Blackwell, you look
like you're breathing hard.
Come on, girl.
[heavy breathing]
[laughter]
I told you.
I don't believe it.
Well, I guess that
means I owe you dinner.
It's OK.
I've got to watch my figure.
But you can eat your words.
Bon appetit, tough guy.
91, 92.
I think you're crazy.
Crazy?
5.
When are you done dealing
with Officer Hunk?
In no time.
Stand on your bologna.
You're scared.
99.
100.
When did you become a shrink?
Don't need to be a doctor
to see an open wound.
Listen, Jackie, I've
got to take things slow.
I just had forgotten
how to be with--
Men.
No, anyone.
Do you understand?
Dear God, I'm hugging a cop.
I need dinner.
Beaudet and Blackwell,
you're up next.
John, wait a minute,
wait a minute.
Go back there.
John.
Yes, sir.
What are you doing?
Sir?
Who told you to come out
here dressed like that?
Where'd you get
those yellow socks?
Sir.
If we wanted a clown, we'd go
to the circus to get a clown.
We don't want those socks.
You wear the regulation
socks, you understand me?
Yes, sir.
Well, you get your
butt out of the academy.
This is not a college campus.
- Yes, sir.
Now, get out of here.
Beaudet, Blackwell, you're up.
All right, Blackwell,
any time you're ready.
Yes, sir.
Put your hands up
in the air slowly.
Get down on your knees.
Get down on your stomach.
Bury your forehead.
Spread your arms out to the
side with your palms up.
[grunting]
[gun shots]
Hey.
- How you doing?
Pretty good.
If you keep hanging
out with us rookies,
people are going to start
wondering about you.
[chuckles]
So, how are those tired,
sore muscles of yours?
I mean, you're starting to
get pretty cocky, young lady.
If I remember right, I
still owe you a dinner.
Yeah.
Well, it's night time.
You busy?
You know, I'm still thinking
you lead a double life.
And as a matter of fact, I never
have seen you with that man
together.
[laughter]
Oh, you're a funny guy.
No, it's just that I really
have to stay focused.
I really need this.
I want it really bad.
OK, I understand.
Well, I'm not going
to quit trying.
Neither will I.
Graduates, these
past seven months
have been the toughest
in your lives,
but I would hasten
to add, the proudest.
Your training has been
the best in the world.
And as the newest members of the
Los Angeles Police Department,
you're about to become
members of the finest law
enforcement team in the world.
Your mission is to
protect and to serve,
and we're all very proud of you.
Class of 195, please come
forward for your diplomas.
[applause]
Congratulations.
It is now my great honor to
present the outstanding recruit
award to Ms. Bonnie Blackwell.
Ms. Blackwell,
please come forward.
[applause]
This award represents
the highest achievement
in recruit training.
Congratulations,
Officer Blackwell.
Thank you, sir.
[applause]
Class of 1995, you
represent the finest
that this city has to offer.
And we know that you will
conduct yourself professionally
with respect and a
dedication to service,
and a pride in
what you've become.
Welcome to the LAPD.
[applause]
Class of 195, dismissed.
To Officer Bonnie
Blackwell, a great cop,
an outstanding woman,
and my new partner.
What's that?
You mean he didn't tell you?
No, he didn't.
Well, I figured the
first in her class
really ought to
learn from the best.
I'm just doing my civic duty.
Mmm mm mm, girl,
after tonight, blue
is my favorite color.
Woo, sure glad Dwayne
has to work late tonight.
You be a good girl now.
Oh, come on, you
know I'm all talk.
I'll let you go celebrate.
She is so crazy.
Oh, before I forget.
I got you a little
something for graduation.
Oh, you shouldn't have.
You know, I still have
that little tiger you
gave me back in the hospital.
Oh my God, that's so beautiful.
Oh, wow, this is really--
thank you so much.
Here's a little
something to go with it.
You did good, for a girl.
You are such a tough guy.
[telephone ringing]
Allow me to introduce you
to the real police work.
Go get them.
You know, it's been
a week now, John,
and all I seem to do
is fill out reports,
is that because I'm new?
It's because you're a cop.
They haven't even
busted any bad guys.
I mean, real bad guys.
[police radio chatter]
How does anything
get done around here?
Well, you just
grin and bear it.
Let's get it.
Fuck, man.
Let's get out of here.
Come on.
Get a 2151 in pursuit
of the 503, a black Buick.
License plate number 1ML760.
[police sirens]
Headed East down 6 towards Mill.
Any backup units stand by.
[tires screeching]
[crashing]
[gun fire]
[explosion]
I got him.
Stop all your actions now!
Put your hands up in the air.
I said, put your hands
up in the air, now!
[gasping]
What the fuck am I
running from you for?
Bitch.
[screams]
Fucking bitch.
Fuck you.
I'm sorry.
You all right?
Radio in that one got away,
heading north on Hewitt.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Bonnie, do you have
the Jackson file?
Blackwell, in my office.
Yes, sir.
Doctor says you're OK.
I'm fine.
What the hell
happened out there?
I don't know, sir.
I can't explain it.
You better be
able to explain it,
cause you got a partner out
there who's worried about you.
I'm sorry, sir.
It won't happen again.
He's not worried
about how you feel.
He's worried about
how reliable you are.
He's afraid for himself, even
though he won't admit it.
And I'm worried too,
because I can't have
you choking out there again.
It won't happen again, sir.
I'm putting you on
desk duty for a while.
John will get another partner.
Just temporarily.
OK, sir.
[background music playing]
Hey, Blackwell, heard
about what happened today.
Rough day.
Yeah, rough day.
Look, I know why
you choked out there.
Even if the rest of these
bozos don't understand,
I know where you've been.
So I can't totally blame
you for what happened.
But understand something, to
these guys, women on the force
is some kind of charity program.
They jump all over stuff like
that, especially when it's
one of the best that screws up.
Is that supposed to
take the pressure off?
No, it's supposed to put it
on, whether you like it or not,
whether it's fair or not.
You are something here, and
if you fail we all fail.
And I have worked
too hard for that.
Everybody's got a past,
something that gets in the way.
So what do you suggest?
Get over it.
I took the
liberty of ordering.
I got this sneaking
suspicion that you're
walking around with the idea
that that guy in the alley
somehow beat you.
He got away.
He could have killed me.
But he didn't defeat you.
You saw him come at
you and you turned
back into that fright lady I
first met a year and a half
ago.
You're dredged up, right out
of the old storage closet,
and put around like an old suit.
That's not you anymore.
You're another person.
I'm not so sure about that.
Bill, it was like
Zach all over again.
I was paralyzed.
Then you have to
take control and not
simply respond to what they do.
You call the shots.
I'll tell you the truth,
that bloody nose did
you more good than you know.
No rookie is worth
his salt unless he's
tasted a little pain.
But he realizes that life goes
on and the job is still there.
Bill, I've tasted
plenty of pain.
As a victim, not as a cop.
You don't just take it
anymore, you use it.
Let it make you mad.
They should stick
it out, I mean,
that I didn't make a
mistake doing this.
You quit on me now
and I'll personally
take you over my knee, and don't
think I couldn't, young lady.
I don't know what
I'd do without you.
You're a real touchstone for me.
Oh, don't let it get out.
Pretty soon everyone will
expect me to buy them a drink.
[chuckles]
Can't do that.
Hey, baby.
Oh, Bonnie, I've missed you.
So glad you decided
to come see me.
Honey.
I need to talk to you.
It's a funny thing, Zach.
I need to talk to you too.
Wait a minute.
Baby, let me say something.
I forgive you.
I forgive you for
putting me in here.
All right.
No, no.
I'm a different man.
I'm a changed man.
I've had time to
think about how wrong
I was to treat you that way.
And I've had a lot
of time to think too.
Zach, I-- I--
Go on.
I filed for a divorce.
A what?
You filed a what?
I hear you correctly?
A divorce?
What are you going to do?
Huh?
How are you going to live?
You, you could never
take care of yourself.
You-- Honey, I'm sorry.
Wait.
I didn't mean that.
No no no wait,
wait, wait a minute.
I guess, I'm just a little
upset, you know, with the news.
Just forget everything
I just said, OK?
Baby.
I'm looking at you here.
I see you.
You're looking so fine.
You're so pretty.
I want you, baby.
I want to be with you.
I was thinking later
maybe we could, you know--
Look, I just can't
take the pain anymore.
My life has been shattered
and I'm just beginning
to pick up the pieces.
I'm living a different
life now, Zach.
And I feel good
about myself now.
What is this new life?
What do you mean,
lead a new life?
Well, that's fine.
You didn't think
you had a good life?
Huh?
The clothes?
The food?
A roof over your head?
Huh?
And a man.
Yeah, me.
I provided well for you, Bonnie.
I'm not good enough
for you now, huh?
Is that it?
You think you can run from me?
Huh, Bonnie?
Zach.
God, you haven't changed a bit.
I thought I loved
you, but how could
anybody love a person like you.
Goodbye, Zach.
Wait a minute, I'm not
finished talking to you.
Hey!
You think you can run from me?
Huh, Bonnie?
You think you can run--
all right, all right.
OK.
[grunting]
Come on.
You're dead.
You're finished.
You'll shove off to
Buffalo, and you know why?
Because your heart ain't in it.
You think you're going
to beat those guys just
using technique?
Those guys are fighting
for their lives.
Is that what you want?
You got to fight for your life.
Get my drift?
I think I got the hint.
You sure you want to do this.
It's going to take
a lot of extra work.
Yeah, the regular
training just isn't enough.
I mean, I really need
to go way beyond that.
I want to be able to kick
any butt on the force.
Oh, you want to be respected.
No.
I want to be feared.
You want to be feared.
Yeah.
I don't think so.
You just might be
wasting your time.
[grunting]
What do you say now, Lebell?
Wednesday, my time?
Huh?
OK OK OK.
OK OK.
We could do it.
You got it.
Besides, I think I
like you better on top.
[grunting]
[telephone ringing]
Hey, partner.
This desk ain't big
enough for the both of us.
What you say we ride
the range and head
off a few bad guys at the pass?
You mean, I'm
back on the streets?
That's what the captain says.
What do you say?
Well, I say that everybody
deserves a second chance,
especially the best.
Besides, this new rookie
they stuck with me
is a goddamn nightmare.
He packs limburger
cheese sandwiches,
he bites his fingernails,
and all he can do
is talk about reruns
of the Honeymooners.
You know what his
life's dream is?
What?
To own the first
oceanfront trailer court.
[laughter]
You've got to save
me from this guy.
OK, I'll come to your rescue.
I owe you that at least.
Well, you also owe me dinner.
How about after we knock off?
Deal.
But this time,
dinner's on me, OK.
OK.
OFFICER [ON RADIO]:
Come in 825, code 6.
105 North Avenue 52.
[screaming]
I'll take the runner.
[thud]
[gun shot]
[grunting]
[gun shots]
Give me your left hand now!
Hands behind your back.
So your 10 partner
wants a trailer court.
Yeah.
What's your dream?
My dream--
I want to be Andy of Mayberry.
- Excuse me.
Yeah, I want to be the
Sheriff of a small town.
You know, big fish in a small
pond, master of all I survey,
even if it is a two meal town.
So does that mean you want
a bunch of little Opies?
Well, it depends.
I have to find someone
other than Aunt Bee.
How about you?
Oh, I don't know.
I kind of like animals.
Maybe I'd like to raise some
dogs and cats and bunny rabbits
somewhere.
So what are we doing
in the Big Bad City?
Fighting for truth,
justice, and the American way.
Yeah, I'll drink to that.
See that W up there?
Yeah.
That's Cassiopeia,
the mother of Andromeda.
Wow.
And what's that zig
zag one over there?
That zig zag,
that's Aetna, she's
the goddess of life insurance.
Boy, those Romans
thought of everything.
Did they have cops back then?
Well, they had gladiators.
You know, leather sandals
and light mini skirts.
Oh, yeah.
They had the right idea.
Yeah, yeah.
They sure couldn't
dance like this though.
I'm going to dip you.
OK.
Want to come in for a minute?
Yeah.
Let me just lock up.
I'll be right in.
Great.
That's perfect.
Bye.
- Hi.
- Come on in.
- Thanks.
It's really starting
to come down out there.
Yeah.
It's nice and warm in here.
Would you like some wine?
I would love some wine.
Should I pour it?
OK.
All right.
That was a great dinner.
Here you go.
Thank you.
So what are you thinking?
Just trying to think of
some clever original way
of saying the most obvious
thing in the world.
What's that?
That you're beautiful.
I like hanging out with you.
And I know falling
for your partner
is against every common
sense idea I ever had,
and I don't care.
I wonder why I don't care.
[telephone ringing]
Hello.
Hi, Jackie.
No, that's not
actually the case.
Thanks, Jackie.
Thanks for your advice.
Bye.
Jackie, good friend with
the best intentions.
Well, that makes two of us.
What is it?
Is it me?
Is it that bust we
had the other day?
No, it's nothing like that.
I-- Sorry.
I just thought--
I don't know what I thought--
I'll tell you what, I
had a great time tonight.
Why don't we just
call it a night.
Leave it at that.
Go to sleep happy, OK?
OK.
All right.
It's too bad though, I found
this really great parking
space.
Bye.
[police sirens]
MAN: You say nothing!
Nothing!
[beating]
[woman crying]
BONNIE BLACKWELL: Open up.
It's the police.
JOHN BEAUDET: Open the
door, it's the police.
What is this?
You tell me.
What's the problem here?
No problem here, except
you're in my house.
Nobody called you.
Oh my God.
What's he been
doing to you, ma'am?
You shut up!
You don't say nothing.
You shut up.
You should take it easy.
Folks, clear out.
Thank you very much.
It's nothing, officer.
It was my fault.
John, let me talk
to her for a second.
Bonnie.
Look, just a second
in the other room.
She don't got to say nothing!
[yelling]
I don't want to
cause no trouble.
It's OK, ma'am.
He has no right to hit you.
Do you work?
Part time at the
job care center.
And what about him?
No.
He hasn't worked in two
years, except for poker money.
He don't even try anymore.
It's just-- he's so
stressed out about--
That means you're
not depending
on him to live, right?
So you can file a
complaint and completely
put a stop to all of this.
No, I couldn't.
That would make him mad.
He's already mad.
You see this?
My husband did that to
me with the steering
wheel of my own car.
And if I didn't put a stop
to it I would have had a hell
of a lot more than these.
And I would have been
in the same situation
that you're in now, or dead.
Listen, I can't
tell you what to do,
but as scary as it is
to put a stop to it,
it's not half as scary
as it is living with it.
With the steering
wheel of your own car?
We ain't married.
We're just living together.
You should show me what to do.
Yes, I can.
John, she's going
to file a complaint.
And you are under arrest.
I ain't arrested for shit!
You just shut up!
John, your turn to
take out the trash.
It's a pleasure.
Don't worry about
anything, ma'am.
I'll show you all the
necessary arrangements.
So what do you
want to do tonight?
Oh, am I tired.
Yeah, well, yeah.
Would you like to do something?
- How about seeing a movie?
- You want to see a movie?
Yeah.
Let's get a paper
and see what's playing,
so we can go to movies.
- Well, why do we do that?
- You want to do that, OK?
[laughter]
Come on, hurry.
Give me the money.
Come on, let's go.
John, got a
robbery in progress.
Call for back up.
Come on with the money, bitch.
Put the gun down now!
[screaming]
Drop the gun!
I said, drop it!
Leave the gun!
WOMAN 3: Help me!
That would be
your shot, Beaudet!
Cover me.
[gun fire]
[scream]
CAPTAIN: Blackwell, on
behalf of the department,
we'd like to give you
this metal of commendation
for a job well done.
Congratulations.
Thank you, sir.
[applause]
You just keep
outdoing yourself.
I really owe it
all to you, Bill.
Thank you.
No, thank you.
This is it.
Wow, great place.
Can I take your coat?
Yeah.
Let's hang it up.
That's what I always do, too.
It feels good.
To the blue.
Another bad guy bites the dust
at the hands of the karate cop.
You were magnificent.
Thank you.
Bonnie.
I'm sorry.
I guess I still tend to flinch
when anybody touches me.
I just need to learn
to trust again.
I hate it as much
as you do, John.
You think I can hurt you?
I know it doesn't make sense.
What are you doing?
Creating an
atmosphere of trust.
Here, cuff me.
Cuff me.
Now, there's nothing
to be afraid of.
I'd like a sip of
champagne, please.
Oh.
Now, look at the
mess you've made.
I'm so glad you invited me here.
I'm so glad you came.
Nice day.
Darn near perfect, I'd say.
My wrists hurt.
Oh, I thought you
were a tough guy.
Nah, that's just
good public relations.
Can't have too much
of that these days.
Remind me to complement
your agent, huh?
MAN 2: Please don't take
her-- don't take her back.
You've got to leave her here.
Please, don't--
don't take her back.
I need her.
I really-- please,
please don't take her.
I have the money.
I just have to sell some--
[gun shot]
Oh, please, help!
OFFICER [ON RADIO]: We
have a 209 in progress.
Units in Montgomery,
officer down.
Approach the premises.
All the units, respond.
This is 2151 responding,
ETA, 4 minutes.
2151 out.
[police sirens]
My God!
You're alive.
The guy had a gun.
He wanted money.
When the cop came he just
shot him and then he ran.
I thought he was
going to kill my--
my daughter and me.
I didn't know what
he was going to do.
[whimpering]
According to this Hummel
guy, it was a simple break-in.
We haven't found any
signs of forced entry.
Hummel says he was having lunch
with his Korean stepdaughter
when this guy broke,
demanded money, almost as he
didn't have any,
but the guy claimed
he was loaded, which he is.
So he calls his broker
to cash out some stocks,
bring the money over.
Actually, he called the police.
Starr and Riley
responded, but they
didn't know it was an armed
robbery, because Hummel
didn't tell them.
Riley got knocked out the second
she came through the door.
Starr was on his own
when he drew his gun,
but it was too late.
Want me to come in
and fix you dinner?
No, I--
I really need some time alone.
That's fair enough.
I'll see you in the morning.
[engine starts]
Oh, Bill, thank you for coming
into my life when you did.
God, please, rest his soul.
Hummel says he can't remember
much about the shooter.
He was kind of drunk at the
time and the killer wore a mask.
Can you believe that?
A mask.
So what are we
going to do about it.
No fingerprints, Hummel
has a bullshit story,
and his lawyer is
being a son of a bitch
when it comes to cooperating.
I think he's hiding something.
But there's nothing we can
do but keep a sharp eye.
It's going to take time.
I'm sorry to hear that, sir.
Do you mind if I
take an early lunch.
You OK?
I'm fine.
OK.
Open up.
Police department.
Oh, Jesus.
Quick, put that on.
Hurry up.
God damn it.
What do you want?
I answered questions for
you guys the other day.
I need to ask you some
questions about the guy that
just broken in.
The hell is going on here?
It's nothing--
it's nothing, ma'am.
Nothing, officer.
Nothing.
Nothing?
This girl was your
adopted daughter.
No.
No, it's what-- it's not
that really-- it's not that--
It's not what, sir?
Talk.
She's-- she's not my daughter.
She's my wife.
I got her through
the service overseas.
They fix up girls who
want to come to the states
with guys like me.
I got money.
I'm not much of a hit
with women, and so I--
Is that true?
What's your name?
Quanjiet.
I thought you said she was
Korean, this sounds Vietnamese.
Does it make any difference?
Is she legal?
No, please.
Couldn't we keep this quiet?
If it got out, I could
never face anybody.
Does she have anything
to do with the person
who tried to break in?
He's not a thief.
He's the guy that brought her.
He runs the service.
I paid him.
Everything was fine for
about a year and a half.
And then, all of a
sudden, he shows up
and he wants more money, he said
he'd turn us into immigration.
I don't have any money
around the house.
He said he'd turn us in, so
I said I'd call my broker
and sell some stock, and
instead I called the cops.
Please, I want to stay.
Listen, you tell me everything
you know about this guy.
And I mean, the truth.
and I'll do what I can to
see you guys stay together.
And that's all I can promise.
[telephone ringing]
Well, where'd
you take the unit?
Just a little
independent research.
I'll tell you later.
OK.
You look tired.
You want me to take you home?
Yeah, if you would.
Yeah, let's go.
[telephone ringing]
Hello.
Oh, hi, Jackie.
Yeah, pretty good.
I guess.
Just a little tired.
I don't seem to get
over Bill's death.
Well, it just seems to go
around and around in my head.
Thank you.
I appreciate it.
You're the best.
All right.
Bye.
[gun shot]
[grunting]
I'll kill you.
I'll kill you, you bitch.
I should of been
there for you.
It's OK.
It's not much you
could have done.
What the hell is he
doing out anyway?
He had another six months to go.
Well, I checked
with the prisons.
He was with parole
two weeks ago.
Out on good behavior.
We checked the room
we was digging around
and I found this in the
safe behind the bookshelf.
You sure you had no idea
he had a safe in the house?
No.
Not at all.
I knew it was just
a storage closet.
I never cleaned it out.
What is this?
Best that I can tell,
your husband was creating
fake IDs for these girls.
These are immigration documents.
They're probably fake like
the rest of this stuff.
So this was sitting around
the whole time he was in jail.
Probably just wanted to steal
it back before you found it.
But what was he going
to do with all of it.
That's what we
have to find out.
We've had an opportunity
to review all your records.
You have been an
exemplary person.
We are very happy with your
growth and development.
The psychologist feel very
confident about your evolution,
but you must appreciate that
we have a legitimate concern
regarding the general public.
We want it to be
a comfortable fit
for them, and yet for you also.
Do you feel that
your incarceration
has had any impact
on your thinking
about your role in
society, about respect
for law and order?
How dare you.
How dare you not tell
me he was released.
He had another six months
to go, and you didn't even
call me to the hearing.
Ma'am, what are
you talking about?
I'm talking about
Zachary Blackwell.
My husband.
He was sentenced for two years,
and you released him early.
And you didn't even think it
was important enough to call me?
Who the hell's rights
are you protecting here?
Maybe I should
leave you folks alone.
Annie, you stay put.
Officer, we complied with
all the relevant regulations.
We felt that it was--
- Bullshit.
You felt nothing.
And you acted like
God damn robots
who know nothing about
him or me or the women
out there who have to face
this scum when you let him go.
God damn you!
Yeah, go on, girl.
You tell them like it is.
Yeah, you're a real man.
[telephone ringing]
Hey, how was your lunch?
Wonderful.
What do you got?
Well, they ran a check
on those passports.
As expected, they're homemade.
The girls are not citizens,
they're Vietnamese.
Mail order brides.
We tracked them down to the
home of some wealthy bachelors.
The INS has been after
this guy for years.
Mail order brides?
Zach was into mail order brides?
Yeah, apparently.
But we got a special problem.
Right?
We don't have trade
relations with Vietnam,
so anything coming
through them is illegal.
Bingo.
[keys clacking]
Where you going?
I've got some papers
to sign for the course.
You lost?
[grunting]
You kill a cop and
it's all over for you.
Who's going to ID me?
You think they'd
find witnesses here?
I own these streets.
What do you want?
I'm looking for these girls.
Do you know any of them?
Maybe.
What do you want with them?
They're here illegally.
And who isn't?
What do you care?
You're not immigration.
I'm not looking for them.
I want the guy who
brought them here.
So do we.
You?
Why?
Because he a slave trader.
What?
He pays Thai boatmen
to kidnap runaways
in Saigon, Di Linh, Cao Lanh.
Smuggle them here.
Sell my people to
rich white bastards.
We know him.
Been in jail.
Safest place for him.
His name is Blackwell.
Who the fuck are you?
I'm his wife.
And I put him in jail once
and I'm going to do it again.
The wife wants
to put him in jail.
This man sure knows
how to make friends.
You know how to fight.
I respect that I don't
know where he is,
but the Manta Ray
is in that picture.
Comes in the first of
the month, Dock 51.
You find him.
We cut his dick off
like a good wife.
Officer Beaudet, please.
Hi, John.
It's Bonnie.
Listen, call the
Coast Guard registry
and look up the Manta Ray.
Zach tried to break in
to still the blank IDs
because he's bringing
another shipment of girls.
Yeah.
Listen, we have to nail him.
We have to find that boat.
If the gang leader
was right, they'll
be heading in sometime tonight.
OK.
Bye.
So how do you want to do it?
Well, back-up's on the way.
We've got to move in on them.
Catch them in the act.
Listen, this time, you take the
front and I'll take the back.
But promise me one
thing, show up this time.
Promise.
[rattling]
MAN: Just be patient
ZACH BLACKWELL: Come on, smile.
Girls, you're in America now.
Come on, be happy.
[laughter]
Say, will you take
those girls upstairs?
Hold them upstairs until the--
come on, girls, smile.
What's the matter
with these girls?
They need to relax.
We're happy!
Can you say sensation
mister, sensation mister?
You're in America now.
Come on.
God, you're so nervous.
I don't know what's
the matter with you.
Relax.
Can I get you another girl?
I don't know why it's late.
[thud]
[gun fire]
Get out!
Stop her.
Why do you think I paid you?
[gun fire]
Zach.
[thud]
[grunting]
Goodnight, lover boy.
Go get her!
[helicopter flying]
[grunting]
[gun shots]
Put the gun down, Zach.
I said put the gun down!
Sweetheart, didn't I tell you?
Never bother me at the office!
Anyway, so nice to see you.
What is this?
What is this new wardrobe?
Ah?
Tell me, Bonnie, does it make
you feel more like a man?
Huh?
What is this new career?
I think I like the old Bonnie.
You see, every man needs an
outlet for his anxieties.
Why?
Because you took it--
You took it so well.
[laughter]
Wife.
[grunting]
Don't shoot.
Take the money!
You can have the money!
[screaming]
Congratulations, Zach.
You turned out to be
the worst piece of shit
than I ever expected.
But I forgive you now, husband.
[music playing]