(police radio
transmits indistinctly)
- All right, Jimenes,
Would you rather wake up
every morning - - Already?
You wanna start
with that already?
- It's just a way
to get to know you.
See what type of man you are.
So would you rather
wake up with cabbage,
two big things of cabbage
on your hands every morning
and you have to eat 'em all
before you can even
start your day?
Or would you rather
have a little midget
that follows you around
but fucks with you,
like turns out the lights
when you're taking a shower
or mismatches your socks,
locks your keys in your car
when you're not
paying attention.
Which one?
- I will say I
fucking hate cabbage.
I don't like cabbage.
It's gross.
Little Midget,
I feel like I already
had that shit,
'cause that shit always
happens to me, man.
So think I'll do the midget.
- All right.
- Yeah, I'll settle with that.
- That was an easy one,
that was an easy one.
All right, all right.
Would you rather
be at San Quentin
with the craziest serial raper
of all time?
- But what's San Quentin?
- San Quentin?
- What is that?
- Really?
Like one of the worst fricking
jail or prisons on earth.
- Oh, okay, I was testing you,
I was testing you to see
if you knew what that was.
- Boy.
Oh boy.
Okay, would you
rather be in there
with like this
craziest rapist guy
and like once a month he's
gonna have his way with you
and there's nothing you
can do at all, like -
but it's only once a month.
- Okay, what's the other option?
- Or would you rather
go viral on TikTok,
everybody in the
world's gonna see it,
there's gonna be
memes after this,
you walk outside and
somebody pranks you
by throwing shit at your door
and it's filled with dildos
and while you're trying
to smash the shit out,
dildos are just
falling from the sky
and hitting you in
the face everywhere.
(Jimenes laughs)
And it goes viral.
Everybody's gonna see it.
- Where do you get this shit?
Is this what you're
always thinking about?
- Yeah.
- This is what you're
always thinking
about, wow, okay.
- Well, do you see
a lot going on?
- I'll go with the -
Fuck, man, I don't know,
go with dildos.
- Viral, dildos and shit
- Viral, I'll be known
- just smacking you.
- For the dildo guy.
- Okay.
- Yeah. Why not? Fuck it.
Fuck it.
So, being on the force
for two weeks now,
what do you guys normally do?
- This is it, drive around,
parking tickets,
pulling people over.
I mean, it's not
a glamorous job.
It's not like what
you see on Cops.
There's not a bunch
of shit going on.
Nobody's really chasing us.
We're not really
chasing anybody.
I mean.
We'll probably pull
somebody over tonight
for something boring.
Who knows what that is.
I hope we don't
pull anybody over
'cause I don't feel
like doing paperwork.
(Jimenes laughs)
I'm just saying.
- I, I agree.
But I'm kind of excited
though, you know?
First, well, first stop.
Tired of all the
fucking office work.
All that desk work,
it's just, killer man.
Have you ever fallen asleep?
- Oh yeah, I take
naps all the time.
I mean, if you weren't
here, I'd probably pull
down one of these streets
and take a nap right now.
No big deal.
Now that you're here I
can take a nap all day
and you can just drive around.
(static ping)
- That's kinda strange,
don't you think?
- Text the wife.
You married?
Kids, anything?
- No.
No, no kids, no kids.
Married once though,
yeah, married once.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- How did that go?
- Huh? Not married anymore.
(both chuckle)
- Yeah, I've been married
for about five years now.
- Kids?
- Yeah, I got two kids, but I
mean, it's a bunch of babies.
- I bet that's awesome,
though, man, to have kids?
- It's cool, I mean, the
wife hates me being a cop.
She wants me to do a
safer job, I'm like,
(Jimenes chuckles)
This seems pretty safe, right?
- Pretty safe, yeah.
She's just asking like,
"How's your partner?"
(Jimenes chuckles)
- So have you had a
partner before or?
- Yeah, I mean, they
usually choose me
to do on-the-job training.
- Got you.
- Apparently I have a knack
for walking the
new guys through.
Not too bad.
- So this is it, huh?
- Nobody's speeding, you
can't make 'em speed.
You hungry?
- I am hungry, actually.
- All right, where are we?
No speedsters today.
Lunchtime.
Even though we've only
been on duty for two hours.
(Jimenes chuckles)
But I am hungry.
- [Server] Jimmy's, how
can I get you started?
- Can, let me ask you, does the
number one come with onions?
- [Server] You said a number
one combo with medium fries?
- No, I said does the
number one come with onions?
- [Server] Oh, a number
one with a slushie?
- No, does it come with onions?
- [Server] Oh, number one with
no onions, I'm so sorry sir.
- Oh my god.
- Hold on one second.
- I'm sorry, can you hear me?
- [Server] Kinda, can you
speak up a little bit louder?
I'm so sorry.
- Does the number, sorry,
does the number one
come with onions?
- [Server] Does the number
one come with onions?
- Yes.
- [Server] Yeah, do you
want me to take it off?
- Yeah, let's take
off the onions.
- [Server] Okay.
- Does it come with lettuce?
- What, are you kidding me?
What are you talking about?
- I don't know, I -
- Hey man, just give us two
number ones with Sprites.
With everything on, just two
Did you lose your mind?
I don't like onions, so.
You want them to
spit in our food?
(Jimenes chuckles)
Did you catch that, boss?
Except for these pictures,
go slide.
- Fucking hate
these things, man.
You, you comfortable
with these things on?
- No, 'cause they can
see everything I'm doing.
The only cool thing is if I
prop my head up like this,
you don't know if
I'm awake or asleep.
- Oh, that's true, yeah.
- They're just gonna
look at me. (chuckles)
Don't look at me, puppet.
(Jimenes chuckles)
- So, what, it's live
feed going directly
to like Headquarters or what?
- That's what I've heard.
I've never actually seen
where the footage goes.
- Oh.
- I don't actually care,
because I don't
really do anything.
- I mean, our - - I guess
if you're doing something
wrong, then worry about it.
- Yeah, I mean, our job is
to control the situation.
Don't lose your head.
When I was in the Marines,
that's all it is, muscle memory.
Everything is muscle memory.
You're still new, but
you'll pick it up.
You'll learn when and
when not to draw your gun,
when to use your taser.
Have you used a taser before?
- I have, yeah, yeah,
I did at the Academy.
I had to get my ass tased
before I could grab it. (laughs)
So yeah.
- That shit hurts, huh?
- Yeah.
I think I pissed myself.
(police radio transmitting)
- Okay.
Would you rather have the
worst explosive diarrhea
any time anybody
sneezes around you?
- Like the sneeze triggers
- Yeah. You hear, - Diarrhea?
- you hear somebody sneezing,
you're just like (mimicked
explosive sound).
- You know what I, okay, or?
- Or would you
rather get attacked
by a hundred hornets
once a month?
- Oh, fuck no.
Diarrhea.
- You like the diarrhea?
- Yeah.
I wasn't gonna -
I'm all over the ass play, man.
(both laugh)
From dildos to this.
(police radio
transmitting indistinctly)
- (grunts) Let's
light this dude up.
(police siren wailing)
Where's he going?
- I don't know.
Not sketchy at all.
- Just keep your head
on a swivel, all right?
Just follow my lead.
- I don't like this.
- Oh, great.
(car doors unlocking)
- (sighs) All right.
- Hold on.
(Radio beeps) Dispatch.
Dispatch, this is 1389.
Car stopped, Williams
and Third, red light,
Nevada plates 3 1
4, Ida, Nora, David.
- [Dispatcher] Ten four.
- You good?
- Yeah.
(seat belts unbuckling)
(door thuds)
(traffic droning)
- [Harrison] Good
evening, sir, you know
why I pulled you over?
- No.
- No?
- See that red light
over there?
- No.
- On Williams? You ran it.
- Really?
- Yes.
- Wow, I thought it was green.
- Hey man, you put
the camera down.
You don't have to be filming us.
- No, no, no, I got it.
If I cough, you might shoot me.
(Jimenes chuckles)
So.
- [Harrison] No,
we're not gonna
shoot you, but yeah,
we did catch you on the camera.
- I could have
sworn it was green.
- Oh shit, hold on.
You know, the funny thing is
your opinion doesn't matter.
Can I see your driver's license
and registration, please.
- See, my opinion does matter.
Just because of color
doesn't mean it doesn't.
- [Jimenes] Hey, hey!
Hey, buddy, just
listen to him, man.
All right, just listen
to him, all right?
- License and
registration, please.
(Glove compartment clacks)
Thank you, sir.
Happy birthday.
- [Jimenes] Is it your birthday?
When's your birthday?
- Is this driver's
license gonna be clean
or is there anything
on your record
that you want to tell me about
right now, before I run this?
Yeah, I think I should say
that there's a party coming up
at my house, so.
- Listen, hey,
I think what my partner's
trying to tell you
is that we're gonna give
you a warning right now.
All right?
All right.
Here you go, sir.
- I mean,
I didn't do anything,
- You're good.
- But thank you.
- Have a good night, man.
Have a good one.
- [Harrison] A warning?
He's got a warrant for -
You know somebody you
freaking (indistinct).
- Man, I don't wanna
deal with the paperwork.
You taught me that, so.
- I don't have the
fucking ticket machine.
(doors thud)
- I don't wanna
deal with it either.
Fucking flashlights dying, man.
- Jesus.
- Forgot to charge it.
- Well, there's no
fucking charger in here,
so you're shit out of luck.
- Shit.
(static ping)
(police radio beeping)
- [Dispatcher] (breaking
up) 1389 we have a body
inside cart.
- Dispatch, what was that?
- [Dispatcher] 1389 we
have a PR who found a body
inside a shelter on
Fifth and Carter.
- Ten four.
So much for a quiet night.
- All right.
- I'll let you do the
paperwork on this first one,
just so you get the
hang of it, okay?
(police siren wailing)
We're gonna come out here
(indistinct) and were we -
I didn't really catch
everything you said,
I wasn't paying attention.
- Fifth and Carter.
We're right here,
actually, aren't we?
- Up here?
- Yeah, it's just right here.
Look at this.
- All right, let's take
this nice and easy, okay?
(Jimenes mumbles indistinctly)
Hmm.
(seat belts unbuckling)
Let's see what this is.
How you doing, sir?
You the one that called it in?
- Yeah, I'm the
one that found him.
- [Harrison] What
have you got for us?
- So I was doing my
rounds like I normally do.
- Okay.
- I heard a scream.
And there's a lot of
drama around here usually,
so, pretty much my intui- -
Just breathe for me, okay,
just breathe.
- Okay.
- Keep going, just relax.
- So I went in the building
and about 10, 15 feet in,
I saw a body laying there.
I yelled, tried to
get their attention.
Didn't get any response at all.
- Okay, can you show
me where that's at?
- Yeah, it's right
around over here.
- You'll walk us over there?
Okay, great.
So have you worked
here for a long time?
- Yeah, I've been here
for a couple years.
- Yeah?
You seen anything
like this before?
- Never, nothing like this.
It's a pretty creepy
fucking place, but.
- Yeah, this is, -
Never dealt with this.
- Place is not ideal.
Hopefully they pay you well?
- Yeah, not enough
for this shit.
- [Harrison] Is there anything
out here we should
be worried about?
- Nothing that I know of.
Just what I found in here.
- Okay.
- It's right around this way.
- Around here?
All right, why don't
you do me a favor,
Why don't you wait
here for me, okay?
- Yeah, I can do that, man.
I seen some people a few
minutes ago running out
of the other side
of the building.
I was gonna go check that out.
You're cool with that?
Or stay here?
- No, stay here for me,
so we know where to find you,
just in case anything happens.
We want to know where
you're at, okay?
- That's fine with me, you
guys can deal with this shit.
- [Harrison] Okay.
Ready?
What do you think?
- [Jimenes] So much
for quiet night, huh?
- Yeah.
(Jimenes chuckles)
- Hey, your first night
where you get to do
actual paperwork.
Exciting, huh?
Okay.
You wanna get the
entrance over there?
(footsteps crunching)
- [Jimenes] Watch
your step, man.
- Yeah.
- It's fucking dark in
here man, can't see shit.
- [Harrison] I can definitely
say it's dark in here.
- [Jimenes] Oh man.
- [Harrison] What do you think?
Age before beauty?
- [Jimenes] Let's do it.
- Metro PD, anybody in here?
- [Jimenes] Metro
PD, we're coming in.
- Metro PD, hello hello?
- [Jimenes] Metro
PD, anybody in here?
- Metro PD.
(lock clangs)
- [Jimenes] What do
you think's in there?
- I don't know,
that's fucking weird.
- [Jimenes] Metro PD!
- What kind of building is this?
- [Jimenes] It's supposed to be
a fucking homeless shelter.
- Whew.
Smells like shit.
Definitely smells like
a homeless shelter.
Metro PD, anybody in here?
- [Jimenes] Dude, it feels
fucking weird in here, man.
There's shit everywhere.
- Hey, man, just keep
your head on a swivel.
Just keep moving
forward, all right?
- [Jimenes] This
doesn't feel right, man.
- You see all these
cameras everywhere?
- [Jimenes] Yeah,
that's fucking weird.
- [Harrison] Where
do these even go to?
Hey, sir!
Hey, Metro PD!
Hey, you wanna come over here
and talk to us for a second?
Sir, can you come talk to
us for a second, please?
Hey, hey, man, let's call
this in, call this in.
- [Jimenes] Dispatch, we
came across a Caucasian male.
- [Dispatcher] Ten four.
- [Harrison] Metro PD, sir,
can you come and talk to us
for a second?
- [Jimenes] Dude, I
can't even see him.
Where'd he go?
Did we lose him?
- Hello, sir?
- [Jimenes] Oh, this
doesn't look creepy at all.
- Oh, that's (laughs nervously)
Oh, that's my shadow.
- [Jimenes] (chuckles
nervously) Okay. Okay.
And this room isn't
creepy at all, huh?
Now what is this place? Is it -
No lights whatsoever.
- [Harrison] Well, we got
creepy door number one,
number two, or number three.
Which one do you wanna take?
- [Jimenes] Oh, man.
Dude, I don't even
know how to get back
to where we came from, man.
- I don't know
where that guy went.
- [Jimenes] Oh shit.
- Hey, hey ma'am.
Hey, we're with Metro PD.
We're here to help you, okay?
Ma'am, are you hurt?
Ma'am? (woman screams)
Hey, calm -
Ma'am! Hey, calm down.
Hey, wait.
- [Jimenes] What was that, man?
The fuck was that?
- [Harrison] Okay, okay, okay.
Okay, wait, okay, you know what?
Let's -
- [Dispatcher] 1389,
what's going on?
- [Jimenes] Dispatch,
we lost the man,
we came across a woman.
Caucasian female,
looked like she was, -
she had some blood on her face.
- Fuck, what in
the hell was that?
Oh, I don't like this, man.
I don't like this at all.
- [Jimenes] Dude, what
the fuck was that?
Fuck, fuck fuck fuck fuck fuck.
(indistinct whispering)
Oh fuck.
- [Harrison] What?
- [Jimenes] What the fuck?
- We've got the body
in the next room.
- [Harrison] What? No no no.
Where? Fuck.
Fuck. Okay.
Okay, okay, okay, okay,
come on, let's go.
Come on, come on.
- [Jimenes] Sir, sir?
Hey, can you hear me?
Hey, hey, who did this to you?
- Dispatch, come in, over.
- Who did this to you?
Can you tell me who
did this to you?
- [Harrison] Dispatch,
come in, over.
We're gonna need
ambulance, EMS, paramedics,
all that good stuff.
Dispatch?
Dispatch, come in, over.
Dispatch, we need paramedics.
- [Jimenes] Oh shit.
- What?
- Dude, he has like -
Something's on a skin.
- What the fuck?
- Did this woman do this
to you?
- [Harrison] Dispatch, come in.
- [Jimenes] What
the fuck do we do?
- [Harrison] We have to, we -
(Loud bang)
- [Jimenes] We're
gonna have to -
- [Harrison] We're have to move.
We're gonna have to move.
Get him up, get him up.
- We're gonna get you out,
okay, you have to work
with me though, okay?
Come on.
- You got him? You good?
- Yeah.
- [Harrison] Okay, okay.
Come on, come on, come on!
Come on.
You coming? You got it?
- You good? You good?
- [Harrison] You good?
You good? Okay.
- [Jimenes] Yeah.
- Let's keep moving,
let's keep moving.
- [Jimenes] The
was fuck was that?
- Did you hear that?
(door creaking, low groaning)
- [Jimenes] Okay, fuck this.
- [Harrison] We need to
get outta here, fuck this.
- [Jimenes] Dispatch,
we need backup now.
- Metro PD! Is
anybody out there?
- [Jimenes] Dude, I
don't fucking know
where you're going, man.
- I, look, there's that camera.
Okay, let's go -
(loud bang)
Okay, let's get the
fuck outta here.
Dispatch, come in, over.
Okay, Dispatch, we need EMS.
- [Jimenes] Wait,
wait, wait, wait.
- [Harrison] What?
You okay? You good?
Come on, man, we
gotta keep moving.
Dispatch, come
in, over, anybody.
(person screams)
- What the fuck is going on?
- What the fuck was that?
- [Victim] Go back.
You guys, the door,
the door right here.
Right here!
- It's right there!
- What the fuck?
(Door thudding)
- [Jimenes] What the fuck?
(door thuds)
- [Victim] Just go back.
- What the fuck
is going on, man?
- [Harrison] Put him down
here, put him down right here.
- [Jimenes] You
good right there.
(door thuds)
- Who locked these
fucking doors?
God damn it, who locked
these fucking doors?
Yeah?
- [Harrison] Dispatch.
Come in, over.
- [Jimenes] Hey, can you
tell me what happened?
Who did this to you?
- Dispatch. Anybody copy?
We need EMS, we need backup.
Anybody, come in, over.
Paramedics, we need ambulance.
We need backup now.
- You're gonna die in here.
- [Harrison] Cell phones,
cell phones, cell phones.
Fuck.
What the fuck?
How in the heaven do we have
no fucking services in here?
Fuck!
- Wait wait wait wait what?
- You're gonna die in here.
- [Harrison] What'd he say?
- We need to get the
fuck outta here, man.
- We gotta keep moving.
We're gonna have to fucking -
Hey, man, you know a
fucking way outta here?
All right, are you sure?
- [Jimenes] What do you think?
- Well it's better
than just sitting here.
Hold on, come on, man.
You're good, right?
You okay?
Come on, you're all right.
You good?
- [Victim] Yeah.
- Hey, you got him?
All right.
Okay, so this way?
- It's right around the corner.
- [Harrison] Corner?
- [Jimenes] Okay.
- Are we going the right
way? (person screams)
- [Jimenes] Fuck, is that a -
(door bangs loudly) Oh!
The fuck was that?
(distant banging)
- [Harrison] All right,
let's just keep moving.
Keep your head up.
Come on, you guys good?
- Yeah.
- [Harrison] Keep moving, okay?
Let's bring him back here.
- [Jimenes] You okay, you okay?
- Let's sit him over here.
Sit him down here, let me just
check this out real quick.
- [Jimenes] You'll be all
right here, I'm gonna go look
for something.
He said the exit was near here.
- [Harrison] Okay.
Look around.
- [Jimenes] What the
fuck was this building
before it turned
into a shit hole?
(victim coughing)
What the fuck is
this place, man?
(victim continues coughing)
- [Harrison] Dude, that smell
is not getting any better.
It's getting fucking stronger.
Shit hole.
- [Jimenes] You okay?
Oh, fuck.
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, wait, wait.
Okay, what the fuck?
- What's going on, hey man!
- [Jimenes] He's having
an seizure or something.
- [Harrison] Wait.
- [Jimenes] Oh, shit.
- [Harrison] Wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait.
Sir, you need to calm down.
Take it easy, take it easy!
Sir, you good?
- [Jimenes] Fuck.
Fuck.
Oh, shit.
Sir?
- [Harrison] Check his
pulse, check his pulse.
- [Jimenes] Oh, shit.
- What?
- He's fucking dead.
- What do you mean
he's fucking dead?
- He's fucking dead.
- What the fuck?
God, damn it.
Okay, Harrison, think,
fucking Harrison, think, okay.
Okay, fuck.
We gotta keep fucking moving,
we gotta keep fucking moving.
Okay think.
- Oh, shit.
- [Harrison] What
do we need to do?
We need to get the fuck outta
here, is what we need to do.
- [Jimenes] Oh, shit.
- [Harrison] Dispatch,
anybody come in, over.
Please.
- [Jimenes] Oh, fuck.
Dude, there's blood
on my fucking vest.
- [Harrison] There has to
be another fucking way out.
You know, maybe if we follow
some of these camera cables,
we can find a way out.
Maybe it still leads to a
security room or something.
You good?
Pete.
Pete!
- [Jimenes] What? What?
- Pete.
- [Jimenes] What?
(eater growling)
- [Jimenes] What the fuck?
- [Harrison] Hey, get off!
Get off! (Jimenes screaming)
(high-pitched beeping)
(heart beating rapidly)
(eater growling)
(Jimenes screaming)
(flashlight thudding)
(Jimenes breathing loudly)
Where'd you learn how
to take a fucking pulse?
- [Jimenes] No, shit.
- Hey, look at me, look at me.
Relax, relax.
Pete!
Just relax, okay?
- Yeah.
- [Harrison] Okay.
We gotta think smart.
We gotta get outta here.
- We need to just fucking go.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait my, my,
I dropped my pistol, man.
I dropped my fucking pistol.
- [Harrison] What the fuck?
- I must have
dropped it when I was
in the other room walking
- Pete! Hey, come here,
- through here.
- Here, stop stop stop.
- We have to go
back, - Relax, relax.
- [Harrison] All
right, okay, you got -
What do you, what do you have?
You got a baton?
- I have a baton, yeah.
- You have your taser?
- Yeah.
- We're good, we're good,
we're good, we can't fucking
go back for that shit.
Somebody probably
already picked it up.
You don't want to get
shot with your own gun.
That'd be embarrassing, right?
- Yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah.
- [Harrison] Just
keep breathing.
- We gotta go back for
my - - Let's just keep,
Let's just keep moving.
- Oh, fuck.
- Let's just keep moving.
Okay?
- Yeah.
- I got my gun.
I'll take the lead, let's
just keep moving, okay?
Just relax, okay?
Let's just go home.
- [Jimenes] Oh, shit.
What the fuck was that?
(electronic static)
(static ping)
- Oh, man.
You almost have
to laugh about it
'cause it's so fucked up, right?
Right, Pete?
- Yeah.
- It's pretty, man, you're good.
We're good, we're good.
We're gonna get outta
here, we're gonna go home.
All right, Pete, would
you rather have sex
with that diseased tranny
that we picked up last week?
That nasty prostitute,
you remember?
Or have sex with that dead guy?
And you have to choose one.
You can't kill yourself
either, you gotta choose one.
- Oh man, I don't know.
- I don't know, man.
- [Harrison] Come on,
man, just, let's play.
We play this all the time.
- Dude, what the fuck
was wrong with that guy?
- I don't know.
- Was a fucking animal, man.
He was trying to bite me.
I honestly, I've never
seen that shit before
in my entire life.
It doesn't make sense.
- Wait, Wait, Wait, Wait.
(low groaning)
What the fuck is that?
Wishful thinking, right?
- [Jimenes] What
the fuck is that?
- All right. (indistinct)
All right, cover me, okay?
I'm gonna go in.
- No, man, just
stay back here, man.
- [Harrison] Just
cover me, okay?
Just, just - - [Jimenes] Fuck.
- Just calm down for a second.
Just stare at your
friend over here.
Fucking camera.
- Man, just stay back.
- [Harrison] Relax, relax.
Chillax, okay?
We're good, we're good.
Okay?
- [Jimenes] Jensen?
(distant noise)
- [Harrison] Oh fuck.
Oh, just breathe.
Just, breathe Harrison.
- [Jimenes] Jensen.
Jensen!
- [Harrison] What?
- [Jimenes] Jensen!
What?
- What are you doing in there?
- [Harrison] Nothing, nothing.
(heavy breathing)
- [Jimenes] Oh, shit.
- [Harrison] Ma'am, Ma'am.
(woman groans)
- Hey, calm down, ma'am!
(woman continues groaning)
- [Jimenes] What the fuck?
- [Harrison] Okay,
what's happening?
- [Jimenes] This is fucking
number two, fucking number two!
What the fuck, what the f-
- [Harrison] Ma'am!
- [Jimenes] Fuck.
(low groaning) Oh, shit.
What the fuck is that?
- Sir, sir, put your hands up.
Let me see 'em.
Sir?
- [Jimenes] Wait, Jensen.
Jensen.
- [Harrison] Did you see his -
- Jensen, Jensen, man, there's
something up with that man.
- [Harrison] Dude, he's
just fucking scared.
Dude was just fucking
- - No, come on.
- He's just fucking scared.
- Something's up with him.
- It's good, come
on, just relax.
- Watch out, watch out,
watch out, watch out!
(eater growling)
(gunshots banging)
Dude, fuck.
- Oh, fuck.
Fuck.
Did you see that (indistinct)?
Dude, he just came
fucking at me!
Dude, he came at me, right?
- [Jimenes] Yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
He did, he did, he did.
- Okay.
(Harrison breathing heavily)
Oh, fuck.
That was not my fault.
I had to shoot, I
had no other choice.
- You're good, you're good.
- Fuck, fuck, fuck!
Okay, what do we do?
- She's gone.
- Fuck, what?
- [Jimenes] She's gone!
- [Harrison] Where
the fuck is the girl?
What the fuck is going on?
What the fuck?
All right, all right,
Harrison, just relax.
Just think, think, think, think.
We gotta get a fucking
way outta here.
(floorboards creaking)
- What the fuck?
- What is that, man?
Should we just go
back the way we came?
- [Jimenes] How the fuck do
you know where to go back, man?
(indistinct whispering)
- [Harrison]
Dispatch, do you copy?
Dispatch!
You think he's actually dead?
- [Jimenes] Oh man,
I don't know what the
fuck is going on, man.
- Must have put three
rounds in that guy.
(distant rattling)
(static ping)
Hey, Jimenes, you smell that?
- Yeah.
Yeah, what is that?
Smells like shit.
- [Harrison] Jimenes, hey.
- [Jimenes] Oh, shit.
- [Harrison] Hey, we got a body.
Ma'am?
- Ma'am?
Oh shit she looks fucking
sick or something.
What's wrong with her?
- [Harrison] She's
not breathing.
I don't think there's anything
else we can do for her now.
- [Jimenes] Fuck.
Jesus.
- [Harrison] Jimenes!
Hey, come on.
Hey, we gotta stick
together, man.
I don't go home, you
don't go home, all right?
Let's go.
Get the fuck outta here.
(zipper whirring)
- [Jimenes] Wait, wait wait.
- [Harrison] You hear something?
- [Jimenes] I thought
I heard something.
- Come on, let's keep going.
- [Jimenes] Ah, fuck.
Oh, fuck.
- Dispatch, dispatch,
come in, over.
Dispatch, you there?
- Fuck.
- Dispatch?
Hey, dispatch, hey.
- [Jimenes] Fuck.
- Dispatch, it's critical
now, we need backup now, over.
- [Jimenes] Fuck.
- Dispatch, we're trapped
inside this building.
Where is our freaking backup?
- [Sergeant] Harrison,
Jimenes, are you guys there?
- Sarge? Hey!
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Hey, Sarge,
Sarge, we are at the
old homeless shelter
on Fifth and Carter.
We need backup right away.
Where are you guys at?
- [Jimenes] I think we're
in the northeast side
of the building.
- We're in the northeast
side of the building.
- [Sergeant] Backup
is five minutes out.
- Backup is five minutes out?
Hey, Sarge, we ain't
got five minutes.
We need backup now.
There's some weird
shit going on here.
We need you now.
- [Sergeant] We're on our way.
Just hold on.
- [Harrison] Hold on to what?
- So we're supposed
to sit here and wait?
Oh, no, no, no,
no, I don't know.
No.
Think.
- Man, this makes
no fucking sense.
How do we not have
signal in here?
We're in the middle of the city
and we have no fucking signal.
- [Harrison] Yeah,
something's cutting off
our fucking signal in here.
- [Jimenes] Wait, wait wait.
Don't think it's kind of weird
that there's no fucking
windows in here, man?
There's no windows
on the outside,
there's nothing that
can connect anyone
from in here out there,
It's almost like - (sighs)
it's almost like they're trying
to keep something in here,
something to control
whatever's in here.
It's fucking weird, man.
We can't just sit here, man.
We can't just be sitting here.
There has to -
We have to do something.
God knows how far out they are.
Five minutes is long time.
- You know, let's
just keep moving.
Sarge will get back
to us sooner or later.
Your guess is as
good as mine, man.
I mean, this whole
place looks like it's -
We're in a fucking maze,
we're going in the same
circle over and over.
(electronic static)
- [Jimenes] Man, this is fucked.
- [Harrison] This is
a fucked up place.
This is a shelter home?
- This is not a shelter, man.
There's supposed to be beds.
There's supposed to be
things to help the people.
- All right, Pete, would
you rather have sex
with a zombie or would
with a 102-year-old woman
who's on her deathbed?
- We're doing this again?
- (chuckles) Until you pick one.
And you can't kill yourself.
Pick one.
- [Jimenes] The the
woman man, the woman.
The old lady, fuck.
- Disgusting.
- You fucking asked.
- Gross.
You have a thing for old ladies.
You usually do that
for money, right?
I think I might take the zombie,
because you know
it's already dead,
she's not gonna say no.
(distant growling)
- [Jimenes] Dude, is
there three of them?
(distant banging)
- Wait, wait, wait.
- You hear something?
- [Jimenes] Dude, what is that?
- Is that coming from in here?
Or is that ups-
Hello?
Jimenes! Jimenes!
- [Jimenes] What?
- Hey.
Hey, how are you guys doing?
We're Metro PD, we're
here to help you, okay?
Are you guys hurt?
Any pain?
Can you guys walk?
- [Jimenes] Hey.
Hey!
- [Harrison] Hold on, give
me just one second, okay?
- What, dude, this is my spot.
- [Jimenes] Whoa, whoa.
- What the fuck is going on?
- [Harrison] Relax,
it's the police, okay.
- Oh God.
- [Jimenes] You okay? It-
Whoa, shit, what happened
to your arm, man?
- Well, I was coming
home last night,
if you could call this home.
- [Jimenes] God.
- And a dude jumped
out from behind a wall
and started like
rambling something at me
and, I don't know.
He just fucking bit me.
- [Jimenes] Well,
we'll get someone
to take a look at that for you.
Do you guys know of an exit?
Another exit from here?
- Well, there should be
one up front, nearby.
- [Harrison] No, we tried
that one, it was locked.
Do you guys know of another one?
- There's one in the
back on the lower level.
- Okay.
- What do we have to lose?
Let's go.
- Let's do it.
- All right guys.
- Cool.
- You guys ready, you guys good?
You wanna get outta here?
We have EMS and paramedics
waiting for us on the outside
to look at you guys, so.
Okay?
- [Jimenes] Come with us, buddy.
We'll get some
help for you, okay?
- I'm not going to jail, am I?
- [Jimenes] No, no, no, no, no.
We're just gonna get
you guys outta here.
Doesn't look safe in here.
(person moaning)
You good? You okay?
- Yes.
Gonna have some
breakfast, might as well.
Pulled it out of
the dumpster myself.
- [Harrison] Stay close,
you guys, stay close.
- [Harrison] Stay
nice and close.
Jimenes, bringing up the rear?
- Yeah.
- You good?
- [Jimenes] Yeah.
- [Harrison] Hey, check
it out, check it out.
Some cameras probably has
to be a control around here,
we could contact
someone from here.
- No, not a chance.
They're monitored off-site.
- [Harrison] You sure?
- Mm hmm, positive.
I volunteer here.
It's my job to
know those things.
- [Harrison] Shit.
Jimenes, we got a
tent in here, man.
I think this is where
the smell is coming from.
(tent panels rustling)
(flies buzzing)
- We're good, keep
on moving, guys.
Just watch your step.
Okay.
- [Jimenes] So what kind of
homeless shelter is this?
I mean, this place is empty.
Do you usually have more people?
- Yeah, people come in
and out all the time.
- There's never an exact
amount of people here.
- [Harrison] What?
What do you mean, what kind
of homeless shelter is this?
(person coughs)
Oh, fuck, are you okay?
Oh shit!
(person groans)
You okay?
- (groans) Yep.
I need a second.
- [Harrison] Come on, man, we
don't have time for this shit.
We gotta keep moving, okay?
(woman screams)
- [Jimenes] We've got
movement back here.
- [Harrison] What the fuck?
- Have you guys
seen anything crazy
or anything outta
the ordinary lately?
- Just a few sick people and
just some fights and that's it.
- Why are you guys here?
- [Jimenes] Fights?
- [Harrison] We got
called for an assault.
You know, the
security guard said
there might be an injury
here, or a possible body.
We found one guy and
then he attacked us.
We kept moving and
found another guy.
He attacked us and he had
this fucking crazy rage
in his eyes.
- Wait.
We noticed there
were some people
who get sick and they
just go to the hospital.
- Yeah, we realize
everyone that left sick,
they never came back.
- [Harrison] Thank you guys.
- We thought it was another
strain of COVID or something.
- COVID?
Oh, no, no, no.
This is something different.
- [Jimenes] Oh, shit.
Where'd he go?
- Fuck.
- [Harrison] Hey!
- Jimenes, hey, we
gotta keep going.
We gotta get these
people to safety.
- [Jimenes] Dude, what
about the sick man, though?
- We get outside,
we'll have more people
to search this building, okay?
- [Jimenes] Fuck.
- Come on, hey, stay with me.
Jimenes.
- Okay.
- Pete!
- [Jimenes] Gotcha man, yeah.
- Just keep moving, okay?
We gotta get these
people outta here.
Okay, which way is this exit?
- [Speaker 2] That way.
Jimenes, you still with me?
- [Jimenes] Yeah,
yeah, you're good.
(static ping)
(footsteps thudding)
(man groaning)
- [Jimenes] What
the fuck is that?
- We got a body.
[Jimenes] A what?
- [Harrison] Hey! My
god, what the fuck?
Hey!
(eaters screeching, growling)
- [Jimenes] Go, go, go, go.
Go, go, go! (woman screaming)
(gunshots banging)
(woman screaming hysterically)
- Help me!
- [Jimenes] Jensen!
(eaters groaning)
Oh, shit.
What the fuck?
Oh shit.
(gunshots banging)
Jensen!
Down, down, down,
down, get down!
(screaming) (eaters groaning)
Oh, shit!
He's got his gun!
Move, move, move, move!
Oh, shit.
- [Speaker] In here, in here!
Get the door, get the door!
- [Jimenes] Get the door.
(person coughing)
- [Harrison] You okay?
- What the fuck was that?
They're eating that man alive!
We're safe here.
They can't come in here.
Wait, if we stay here,
will they come and find us?
- [Harrison] I don't know.
I don't know.
- What do you mean
you don't know?
- It means we don't know, okay?
The Sergeant told us to wait
here and hold for an update.
- Look, hey, look, we
can't stay here, okay?
We gotta fucking move, okay?
You guys with me?
- Up and move.
- [Speaker 2] We're
gonna be okay.
It's gonna be all right.
- [Speaker] Okay, yeah.
- [Speaker 2] It's
gonna be fine.
- [Harrison] Hey, guys,
you're good right?
Still with me?
- Yeah.
- [Harrison] What you got there?
- Okay.
- You good?
- [Jimenes] Yeah.
(furniture shuffling)
(eater growling)
(woman screaming
hysterically) (eater growling)
(high-pitched beep)
(muffled eater growls)
(Jimenes grunting)
- [Harrison] Fuck! Fuck!
(eater growling)
(static)
Fuck!
(Jimenes breathing heavily)
Jimenes, you good?
(Jimenes breathes
loudly, grunts)
- [Jimenes] Fuck.
- [Harrison] You good?
- [Jimenes] Yeah, all good.
- [Speaker 2] Fuck!
- You guys good,
you guys okay?
- [Speaker 3] Yeah.
- What the fuck,
what the fuck?
- [Jimenes] What the f-(grunts)
- [Speaker 2] We're
fucking out man, we out.
Yeah.
- [Harrison] You guys good?
Just breathe.
- [Jimenes] Okay.
(Breathes heavily)
- [Harrison] Jesus Chr-
What the fuck?
Guys, you're still
with me, right?
We're still good?
Everybody's good?
Just breathe.
Where are we, where are we,
where are we, where are we?
- [Speaker 2] This is the
facility manager's office.
(papers rustling)
What are you doing?
- Well you said this is the
manager facility office, right?
So there has to be a blueprint,
freaking diagram or something
of this place, right?
Right?
- Yeah.
- Well fucking help
me look, come on!
Jesus.
You wanna get the fuck
outta here, right?
(papers rustling)
What you got, Jimenes, anything?
- Mm mm, there's nothing.
(papers rustling)
- [Speaker] Here!
- [Speaker 2] Where's that?
Oh!
- [Speaker] It's right here!
I think this is it.
Does it look right?
- Yeah I think so.
- [Harrison] All right,
there's an exit right here.
- [Speaker 2] Yeah.
- [Harrison] All right,
can you get us there?
- I think so.
- You think so?
You didn't sound too
confident, can you get us here?
- Yeah.
- All right, we gotta
find a distraction
or something for all
these guys out there.
- Wait, I have an
idea, I have an idea.
- [Harrison] You have an idea?
- We can use this, cellphone.
- It's okay.
Okay, let me take this map.
You guys, stay close.
We need to get outta here okay?
(heavy breathing)
- [Speaker] All right.
- [Harrison] You guys
ready, you guys good?
- [Jimenes] Let's go.
- [Harrison] All right.
(door handle disengages)
(music playing on cellphone)
(eaters squealing,
growling in the distance)
Show me that fucking map.
Where are we?
Is that the way?
(indistinct talking)
- We're right here.
- We're right here?
- All right, you guys ready?
You got it?
- [Harrison] Yeah.
Let's go.
(eaters screaming
in the distance)
- [Jimenes] Fuck.
(static ping)
- [Speaker 2] Right
here, right here!
(Velcro tearing)
- Let's check out this map.
(paper rustling)
Where we at, where we at?
- Oh here, right here.
- We just need to get through
here, there's the exit.
- [Speaker] Oh, it's just
- - [Speaker 2] Yeah,
it's just right over there.
- All right, let's fucking roll.
Go.
- [Jimenes] Wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
- [Harrison] What, what?
- Hey!
What's his name,
what's his name?
- Zach.
- Zach, hey, buddy.
- [Speaker] Zach, hey.
- [Harrison] Bring him
back, guys, bring him back.
- Zach?
(eater growls) Hey, buddy,
we found a way out, okay?
Come on, we can get-
Buddy?
Hey, hey, hey!
Oh, shit! (eater growls)
- [Harrison] Zack!
- [Jimenes] Oh, shit!
- [Harrison] Hit him,
hit him, hit him, back!
Hit him, hit him!
(loud thump)
- [Jimenes] Oh, shit, oh,
shit. (breathes heavily.)
- [Harrison] Fuck! Fuck!
- [Jimenes] Oh, shit.
- You okay?
(eaters growling) Look,
look, what the fuck?
- [Jimenes] Go, go, go.
Oh, shit.
Oh, shit! (woman screams)
(eaters screaming)
- [Harrison] You go,
guys, go go go go!
Move move move move!
(chaotic screaming)
Come on, let's move.
What the fuck?
Come on, come on, come on!
(chaotic screaming continues)
Jimenes, Jimenes!
- [Jimenes] Oh, shit.
- Jimenes!
(taser buzzes)
Fuck! Fuck! Fuck!
- [Jimenes] Fuck, oh shit.
Oh, shit!
- [Speaker] Go, go, go!
Go go go go!
(eaters growling) Run!
- [Harrison] Move, move, move,
Jimenes, come on, let's go!
(chaotic screaming continues)
You good?
- Oh shit, oh shit.
- Look.
You guys okay?
(eaters screaming,
growling in the distance)
All right, they're fucking gone.
You see that shit?
See all those fucking wounds,
fucking blood everywhere?
Fucking bite marks,
what the fuck is that?
- Dude, I can't believe
I'm saying this.
Did you see all the wounds?
- [Harrison] You don't need
to say it, don't be stupid.
- What if it's an infection?
They all were injured somehow.
What if this is being spread
by bites or something?
They all had wounds
on them, man.
I don't know, I don't know.
It's all I could
think of, is bites.
- Wait, am I bit? Am I bit?
- [Jimenes] Shhh!
- No, you're not, you're not.
Calm her down!
(Velcro tearing)
(paper rustling)
We calm? We good? We relaxed?
Okay, all right, where are we?
Where are we?
Okay?
- Jensen! Jensen! Jensen!
(eater growls)
(spine cracking)
- [Harrison] What the f-
(eater moaning)
- [Jimenes] Watch your
back, watch your back!
- Geez!
(eater gurgling)
- [Jimenes] They can't see us.
Jensen!
- [Harrison] What?
- They can't see, we
can walk around it.
- What?
- We can walk around it,
it can't see us.
- You fucking out of your -
(eater continues
gurgling, grunting)
- Right, where's the map?
Where's the map?
Right, come on,
everyone, let's go.
Go go go go.
(eater gurgles)
- [Harrison] Right,
where the fuck are we?
Dude, we're all
fucking turned around.
Where are we?
Which way?
- Right here, we're right here.
Almost there.
- [Harrison] We're almost there.
- [Jimenes] We gotta
move, we gotta move,
we gotta move!
- All right.
(static ping)
Come on, let's go.
Come on, over here, over here.
All right.
All right, let's look at this.
What the fuck?
What room?
- I'm not sure.
- You're not sure, huh?
(eaters groaning)
- [Jimenes] Oh, shit.
- Megan?
- Shhh, wait.
- No no no no, it's not.
- [Harrison] Stay
here, stay here.
- We can't just leave
or we gotta go find her.
- No!
If you guys go, we have
to leave without you guys.
- Fuck.
- [Harrison] Wait!
No, no, fuck fuck!
(chaotic screaming)
Jimenes!
(chaotic screaming continues)
- Shit, fuck.
- [Harrison] No, no, Jimenes,
We gotta get outta here first,
then we come back for them.
Come on!
- [Jimenes] Fuck!
- Jimenes!
Get the fuck outta here, man.
- [Jimenes] Yeah, okay.
- Get the fuck outta here.
Jimenes.
- Where the fuck are we going?
- Let's go this way.
(shrill screaming)
What the fuck is that sound?
You hearing this?
- Yeah.
Fuck, I don't know.
- Fuck, all right, come on.
Let's keep going.
I think we're right here.
Let's go around
this fucking corner.
- [Jimenes] Oh shit, oh
shit! (eaters growling)
(static ping)
- [Harrison] Jimenes,
pick up your feet!
- (breathing heavily) Oh, shit!
Oh shit! Oh shit!
- Jimenes, follow me,
follow me, follow me!
Jensen, Jensen, Jensen!
- [Harrison] Jimenes!
Come on!
- [Jimenes] Oh shit.
Oh shit!
- Jimenes, Jimenes!
- Oh shit!
(chaotic eater growling)
- Where are we going?
- Jimenes, I'm here, I'm here!
Right, right, right!
- [Jimenes] Shit, oh, oh shit.
- [Harrison] Where's that map?
- [Jimenes] What the fuck?
- [Harrison] All right, look
at the map, look at the map!
Right, right, right!
(chaotic screaming, growling)
- [Jimenes] Where'd you go?
- [Harrison] Jimenes!
Jimenes, over here!
- [Jimenes] Wait,
wait, where are we?
- [Harrison] I don't fucking
know where we are now.
(indistinct shouting)
- [Jimenes] Jensen!
(muffled growling)
- Jimenes, go, go, come on!
Don't stop, don't stop!
- [Jimenes] Right there!
- [Harrison] Fuck!
(door banging) Ah, shit.
This has to be it,
this has to be it!
(door slams) Fuck!
(both breathing heavily)
- [Jimenes] Where
the fuck are we?
- [Harrison] Fuck.
I don't know.
(Velcro tearing)
- [Jimenes] Fuck.
(Paper rustling)
This is supposed
to be an exit, man.
- Yeah, well this is
where the fucking -
This is where the
fucking map points.
- [Jimenes] Where
the fuck is the exit?
- [Harrison] God damn
it, dropped my torch.
(indistinct frustrated talking)
- [Jimenes] Fuck.
- [Harrison] Fuck are
we? (siren wails briefly)
(metallic rumbling)
God damn, we're in
a fucking elevator.
- [Jimenes] Fuck.
(metallic rumbling continues)
(doors rumbling)
(heavy breathing)
- What the fuck?
(doors creaking)
- [Jimenes] What the
hell is this place?
- I don't know, what the fuck?
Look.
- [Jimenes] What the fuck?
- [Harrison] This is
some kinda facility
for the fucking CDC?
- But why would it be
under a homeless shelter?
- [Harrison] How the
fuck should I know?
(paper rustling)
- [Jimenes] They're doing
some sort of experiments
down here.
- Oh my god.
They're using this place as
some kind of testing facility.
All these fucking
poor bastards are
just fucking experiments.
God damn guinea pigs.
- What? Fuck. (paper rustling)
What the fuck is this?
- [Harrison] I don't
think it's good, man.
I don't think -
- [Jimenes] We gotta
get outta here like now.
(metallic ping)
(water dripping)
(Radio beeps)
- [Sergeant] Harrison,
are you guys there?
- About God damn time,
fuck, fuck.
Yeah, sarge, yeah, we're here.
- [Sergeant] Look,
we're all here now.
We're working
close with the CDC.
There's some sort
of case of scabies,
a skin parasite, like rabies.
They're working on
getting quart set up
before they can get you out.
The health department is
preparing to enter the building.
Where are you guys, exactly?
- No, no no, no.
- [Jimenes] Dude.
- No.
- We've been exposed.
If they find out that we
know what they've been doing
down here, they're not
gonna let us out, man.
We're a fucking liability.
- Think, God damn it, think.
Sarge.
Yeah, Sarge, hey, we
know of another exit.
We're gonna head
there right now.
(radio beeps)
- [Sergeant] No, stay put.
They want to -
(loud screaming over radio)
- Oh, shit.
- Sarge?
Sarge, come in, over?
Dispatch? Try yours.
Dispatch?
- [Jimenes] Sarge?
Dispatch, are you guys there?
- [Harrison] What the fuck?
- Let's just keep moving.
Let's keep pushing forward.
- Jesus Christ.
- I guess the CDC doesn't
believe in the housekeeping, huh?
- [Jimenes] Dude, what
the fuck is this place?
- Fuck, I have no idea.
(strained groaning)
Oh shit!
- Oh shit!
What, where the fuck do we go?
(strained groaning continues)
(radio static)
(agitated grunting)
(Jimenes grunting)
(spine cracking)
(heavy breathing)
(multiple groans, grunts)
- [Harrison] Shh, shh.
(strained groaning)
(strained groaning continues)
(light bulb clinking)
- Fuck.
- [Harrison] What do
you think was in there?
(door creaking)
(screen rattling)
We need to find our way
back to the surface.
(metal banging)
(indistinct talking)
Motherfucker!
- Stop, wait!
I'm not affected, I'm
not one of those things.
- No?
Yeah, but I bet you're
the motherfucker
who started this shit,
I just ran into your
friends upstairs.
- I was just doing my job!
- Your job?
What's that, playing God?
You better start
fucking talking.
- You know I can't
fucking say anything.
- Bullshit!
Fucking bullshit!
You think it's
good cop, bad cop?
You better start talking
or I'll fucking
kill you right here.
Do understand me?
- We were just trying to help.
We're finding
cures for diseases.
- Fuck you.
You're a fucking liar.
- First, first,
it was just small.
Small hosts.
- Do you believe this shit?
What?
- Rabbits, rats.
- But?
- The higher ups
wanted us to experiment
with larger animals,
larger hosts,
cats, dogs.
- Humans?
- Answer him.
Answer the question!
- They were terminally ill.
- Bullshit.
- They were dying.
It wasn't gonna go
further than that.
- Bullshit!
You knew exactly what you
were fucking doing down here.
- [Jimenes] What happened
to everyone down here?
- What happened?
- Specimen got loose.
Affected the lead researcher.
- And he didn't report it?
- It affected
everyone down here.
- [Jimenes] Not only down here.
- It reached the surface, too?
We gotta get outta here.
- Yeah, no shit!
And you're gonna
fucking show us how.
- They'll never let us out of
here, we're all fucking dead!
- Man, you might be.
(metallic rumbling)
- If the virus got out,
we're all fucking dead.
- Just keep walking.
- They're never
gonna let us leave.
- [Jimenes] No loose
ends, no liabilities.
- No.
We're getting outta here, okay?
Stop.
Wait right there.
(objects clanging)
(metal sliding)
(clanging continues)
- What is it?
- An exit.
It's right around that door.
- And?
(eater growling)
- What the fuck is that?
What the fuck are you
guys working on here?
(eater grunting)
- Fucking lead us
out, lead us out!
Right, stay close.
Quiet, stay close, okay?
(Researching screaming)
- [Jimenes] Oh shit.
- Run, run!
- Oh shit.
- [Harrison]
Jimenes, pick it up!
Move your feet, man, come on!
- Oh fuck, oh shit!
- Pick it up, pick it up!
Fuck you, fuck you!
- [Jimenes] What
the fuck was that?
- We gotta fucking go.
We gotta fucking go, come on.
Come on, Jimenes!
- [Jimenes] Fuck.
(metallic ping)
What the fuck was that?
We need to get the
fuck outta here.
Shit.
What the fuck?
Fuck are we now?
(Velcro tearing)
(paper rustling)
- Is this map even worth
anything anymore?
Is it that way?
- Yeah - Okay.
Let's go.
- [Harrison] Wait wait wait.
05 13 85.
- [Jimenes] 09 13 89.
Zero five two four.
Hold on.
(paper rustling)
- Okay, okay.
All right.
So.
05 13 89, that's
where the exit's at.
So we just gotta keep
following this, right?
So, all right.
Go here, go - You
know where it's at?
- Yeah, we need to go here.
We need to go -
All right, 05 13,
89, right there.
We're gonna go left up
here, down the hallway,
on the right, that
corridor there.
Exit should be there, okay?
- [Jimenes] Okay, let's
go, let's go, let's just -
- Where's the exit?
- [Jimenes] 05 13
89 (indistinct)
- Yeah, we're fine.
- [Jimenes] We get the fuck
outta here, Jensen, come on.
- Shh, shh, shh, shh.
Fuck.
- [Jimenes] Go, go go go go.
It's right over here.
- [Harrison] Come on.
Come on.
- [Jimenes] Wait,
wait wait wait wait.
- [Harrison] What?
- Wait wait wait wait.
- What?
- Wait wait wait.
- [Harrison] What?
Hey!
- [Jimenes] Hey, hey,
you need to come with us.
You need to come
with us, come on.
What?
- [Harrison] Pete?
Pete?
Pete, come on man, let's go.
Quit digging around
this fucking ground, come on.
- You need to come with us,
right now.
We've found a way out.
Right now, we gotta go.
- I can't leave her.
(crying) I can't leave her.
I can't leave her.
- [Jimenes] You can't
do anything for her,
we need to leave right now.
- (crying) No.
Get up!
- [Speaker 2] No, no no.
- [Harrison] Pete.
Pete, Pete.
Come on!
You fucking doing?
Come on.
- [Jimenes] Get up right now!
We gotta go.
- No, I can't
- [Harrison] Pete, Pete!
Hey, look out, come on.
(indistinct whisper)
Back up towards me.
(Speaker 2 screaming)
(eaters screaming chaotically)
Go, Pete!
- [Jimenes] Oh, shit.
- [Harrison] Pete!
(muffled screaming)
- [Jimenes] Dude, what the fuck?
- [Jimenes] We gotta move up.
- Pete, let's go, come on.
Shit, Pete!
(eater screaming)
- [Jimenes] Oh shit.
- [Harrison] Pete! Pete!
- [Jimenes] Oh, shit.
Oh shit.
Oh shit!
- Come on, come on!
Pete! Move away from -
(eaters growling, screaming)
The corner, the corner, shit!
Push it back, push it back!
Push through!
Pete! Pete!
Push it back, push it back!
(muffled screams)
(chaotic screaming, growling)
Pete!
Wait wait wait, Pete!
Door door door door!
Pete, get the door!
(eaters screaming)
(Jimenes grunting)
(door clicks) (Jimenes
breathes heavily)
- Oh shit.
Fuck.
- Pete!
Get up!
Hey, get up, come on!
Jimenes, hey.
All good?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
- [Harrison] Fuck, fuck,
fuck, you bleeding?
- No, I think I
just ran into something.
- [Harrison] You bit?
- I just ran into something.
Fuck.
- Fuck, you're gonna
be all right, right?
Can you walk?
- Yeah, I'm good, I'm good.
(explosion pounding)
(chopper droning)
(eaters screaming)
Oh, shit.
Shit!
(Jimenes screaming)
(continuous ominous low droning)
(static ping)