[MUSIC PLAYING]
[THUMP]
-Karen.
Karen.
OK, fine.
You don't want to talk?
Tell me I'm an idiot.
Say, Wes, do this, do that.
Vacuum the carpet.
Wash the dishes.
-Enough.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
-I love you, Karen.
I wish you'd just
try to understand.
Just try.
There's no point in having any.
What for?
There's nothing left.
There's nothing.
-Mom, hi.
I'm fine.
I'm OK.
It's awful.
So many years now.
He's afraid to make me pregnant.
You know how stubborn he is.
I can't take it anymore.
OK.
I love you, too.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
-I told you, dear.
With a fast one.
You're the one who is
rushing to the alter
as if he's the only
fish in the pond.
Look at Jim Sadler and the
way he treats his wife.
Bought her a peach
color convertible
which matches her hair.
She looks gorgeous in it.
Children are adorable.
He was so much in love with you.
Why?
No.
He's too tall for you.
You like his voice, remember?
Well, now you're paying for it.
Make the same
mistake that I did.
And then she'll think carefully
before she commits herself.
Uh.
Your father nearly
killed me before he died.
I'm a different woman now--
so relieved, so happy.
It's hard to be alone, I know.
It's lucky to take
care of yourself
when feeding, nursing,
and protecting a monster.
I didn't deserve it,
and I'm not going
to let the same
thing happen to you.
A man should be a man
and respect his woman.
You can't live without respect.
And, dear, it's about time.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
-Karen!
-I'm sorry!
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Huh.
-(ON TV) 200 Americans die
during a murder/suicide.
Item 1984, 88 followers of the
controversial Faith Assembly
have died from diseases
left untreated.
Their leader, Reverend
Hobart Friedman
relied on prayer
to heal the sick.
Item 1989, Fundamentalist
Mormon Jeffrey Lundgren brutally
kills five members of his church
in a sacrificial ritual which
he believed would
lead his congregation
to the promised land.
-(ON TV) shall
put to death those
who lead you to false gods.
-(ON TV) Will you start
this from the beginning?
-(ON TV)Where's our
marriage license?
I want to see it.
-(ON TV) Don't you
remember, Gracie,
our marraige license
was in a trunk,
and the trunk was
burnt in Vancouver?
But I'll be glad to
get you a duplicate.
-(ON TV)I don't want a trunk.
That won't prove we're married.
[LAUGHTER]
-(ON TV) Look--Gracie.
-(ON TV) That's right.
Call me Gracie.
Everybody calls me Gracie.
[LAUGHTER]
-(ON TV)What's wrong with that?
-(ON TV) If we were
really married,
they'd call me Mrs. Burns.
[LAUGHTER]
-(ON TV) Harry, will
you talk to her?
I'm going out.
-Hi.
-How you doing, Dad?
-I'm fine.
How are you?
-I'm OK.
-Where's Karen?
-She stepped out.
-Shopping?
-Yeah, something like that.
You hungry?
-No, I just had a sandwich.
-(ON TV) No, he wants it legal.
Mother. mother, stop laughing.
-My favorite show.
You like it?
-No.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
-Jeez, Dad, what's this?
New insurance?
-This one's really great.
Costs nothing.
Pays the whole world.
-I don't need it.
-Wes, you can't live
without insurance forever.
-I don't need it.
Your my father,
when are you going
to stop trying to
sell me insurance?
-Is a sandstorm coming?
WES: I don't think so.
Why?
-I can always feel
it in my bones.
WES: Do the gloves help?
-A little.
Nothing really helps.
-Quit drinking, it might help.
FATHER: I did quit.
-Hmm.
FATHER: This is
my cough medicine.
You know how much
I miss your mom.
Have you been to her grave?
WES: No, I've been pretty busy.
I'll go tomorrow.
OK?
-Hi, Wes.
-Hey, Gary, so how's work?
-Slow.
-It takes hours to get the
damn sand out of the engine.
-Yeah, and then you've
got to clean the oil.
Such a mess.
-Hey, what's going on over here.
You're not watching the game?
-No, my father showed up.
-You must be kidding.
Turn it on.
I thought you'd
tell us the score.
-(ON TV) And we're at
the bottom of the fourth.
-All right, bottom
of the fourth, guys.
-(ON TV) You can see
the action here is
really heating up
in the ballpark.
Pitcher's coming in.
He's checking over his
shoulder, looking at second.
The throw, it's a line
drive, and no, it's
gone foul down the
third base line.
-He needs a big fly to the left.
-Nah, to the right.
-Right.
-Karoom.
-(ON TV) Than any other
player on the team this year.
He's going to take the
pitch again and-- ooh.
Gosh, looks like he
got him on the hip.
I'm not sure.
-Hey, Wes, you got any beer?
-Yeah.
-That's all right.
I'll get it.
It's self-service, right
-Help yourself.
-Hey, Wes, you
ain't got no beer.
-No?
I thought I did.
Sorry.
-Hey, we need a homer now, man.
-You don't even have a coke.
-What's this?
No salt added, cultured,
low-fat buttermilk.
Hey guys, look what
he's got in his ice box.
-What?
What?
-Nothing.
-What do you mean, nothing?
-Dannon Low- Fat Yogurt,
Schaefer Cheese, sand.
-I can't believe this!
-And some no calories
lemon/lime sparkling slime.
-He's gone nuts!
-It's her!
-Well, I have to get going, Son.
-What's the rush?
-Time for me.
Give my regards to Karen.
-Hey, Dad I will.
Thanks for coming.
-Good.
-You know, you're
such a swell guy,
I don't know why you have
to get married anyway.
-Goodbye.
-Wrapped him around
her little pinkie,
made a noodle out of
him, put him in her soup,
and ate him alive.
[SLURP]
No fat soup, looks like it.
-How come you got married?
-Well, I guess I
was young, you know.
-Guys, what's up?
-Well, we were just
discussing your diet.
-Yeah, your diet.
Is that what she makes you eat?
-You guys got something
better to talk about?
-You allow that, man?
-You guys want to
watch the game or what?
-The game sucks.
Your ice box is better.
[LAUGHTER]
-I don't need your company.
-I told you.
-You didn't have to tell me.
-OK Buddy, we're leaving, and
you won't so us in your rotten
place again.
-Good.
-Unless you get some beer.
-Why don't you
bring your own beer
next time, you little prick?
-Did you hear that?
-Yup.
-He offended me, right?
-He damn sure did.
-You're the witness, right?
-Right.
-Oh come on.
-I'll kill him in a fight.
-Get out of here man.
It's nothing worth a shit.
Let's go.
-(SINGING) I've got the sand.
I've got the sand
all in my head.
I've got the sand.
I've got the sand all in my bed.
I've got so much
trouble in my life, sand
coming through my heart,
in black of night.
I've got sand in my tee, it's
about two [INAUDIBLE] wide,
but I've got no place to run,
and I've got no place to hide.
I've got no place.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
-I can't take it anymore.
[INAUDIBLE]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
-Hi.
-I'll make you breakfast.
-I'm not hungry.
-OK.
I'll eat alone.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
-I missed you.
-I missed you, too.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
-It felt like you
were gone forever.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
-Gently, Wes.
-Damn.
-Gently.
The sand really hurts.
[HEAVY BREATHING]
-Huh.
I can't live without you.
Not so hard.
Not so hard!
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[SCREAMS]
-I want to go We're
going to be killed!
-I don't care.
Just hold me.
-Who is that, Wes?
Bernie?
-No, it's Jameson and Tully of
Jameson, Tully and Bambridge.
-Tully came back?
-I guess so.
-He wasn't supposed to be back.
-Well, he is.
-That's strange.
-Yup.
-Look, Wes, they're fighting.
Look!
-They always fight.
-You should stop them.
-Why?
-Because you should.
-Do you think they're fighting
because of the stock market?
-Could be.
-OK.
You wash up.
I'll exercise.
Got to burn the calories.
-Making love burns the calories.
-Not really.
None of the muscles get used.
-Yeah, I noticed.
-(ON TV) Give me two more.
I want you to roll over
onto your elbows and knees.
Let's concentrate
more on the buttocks
and the back of the thigh.
Place your elbows directly
underneath your shoulders,
hold abs in tight,
lifting and lowering.
Press through that heel.
Press up to the ceiling,
making sure you're
working it down also.
Work the movement down and up.
Relax the shoulders, keeping
the head straight and relaxed.
Up, down, you've got great
legs, great strong legs.
Abdominals are tight, head's
relaxed, working that move.
OK, how about a little
smaller range of motion?
Press it up, up, up.
[DISHES CLANGING]
-Hi.
What are you doing?
-Taking care of some business.
Nothing much.
And you?
-I was just exercising.
-[LAUGHING]
I see.
How are you?
-Ah, I'm fine.
-I'm fine as well.
-But he isn't fine.
-Oh, you think so?
-Yeah, he doesn't look so good.
JAMESON: It depends.
KAREN: On what?
JAMESON: The circumstances.
-What do you have in mind?
-The weather, for example.
Do you think it's going to rain?
-I don't think so.
It hasn't rained for years.
-It's not good for the greenery.
-There's no greenery.
There's only sand.
-I know, but still,
it's not good.
It's going to be a beautiful
day, don't you think?
-I have to go.
-I see.
OK.
-Bye.
-Keep well.
-Argh.
-Give my regards to Wes.
KAREN: I will.
-Wes?
-Yes, Love?
-That was so weird.
-What's that?
-I went out to see Jameson.
He was so weird.
By the way, he
sends his regards.
-Make a pass at you?
-No, no, no.no.
No.
Nothing like that.
it was different.
He was so weird.
He acted as if nothing happened.
-Did anything happen?
-Of course.
-He just killed Tully.
-So what?
I don't care if he killed him.
I don't care if they
all kill themselves!
What I care about is you.
-[CRYING]
You don't believe me.
You never believe me.
I was telling the truth.
-I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I lost my head.
Please.
Don't cry.
It's me.
I'm sorry.
[INAUDIBLE] I love you so much.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
-It's amazing.
Liz Taylor lost 20
pounds in just a month.
She looks beautiful.
I
-Gorgeous.
-It's so important to
keep the right diet.
-My girlfriend is
doing carbohydrates.
-Oh yeah?
-Yeah.
The Dr. Zimmer Diet.
-I don't know that one.
-You only eat vegetables, bread,
macaroni, and nothing else.
-The macaroni's kind of heavy.
I like beans and rice, and mix
those, make a complete protein.
-I think it's best to choose
one diet and stick with it.
-I agree.
How much did your friend lose?
-She didn't lose anything yet.
I think she cheats.
-That's awful.
-I know!
Horrible!
She sneaks out and
has a huge piece
of cream cake or something.
I think she gained.
-How much?
Five pounds at least.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
-Good morning.
Harry White, IRS.
Do you mind if I ask
you some questions?
-No, go ahead.
-Is this your tax
return from last year?
-Looks like it.
-Are you sure?
-Can I see?
-Of course, be my guest.
-Yeah, it looks like it.
-Could you--?
You sure?
-Yeah, mine.
-You sure you didn't
make any mistakes?
-I don't think so.
You think so.
-What I think is what I think.
Would you please kneel,
and kiss my briefcase?
Do you swear to tell the
truth, the whole truth,
and nothing but the truth?
-So help me God.
-OK.
-Were there any changes
determining quality
to these costs,
valuations between opening
and closing inventory?
-Yeah, Section
GH, I checked yes.
-I know that.
What about depreciation, Section
179, deductions from Form 4562?
-That's not included
in Section Three.
-That's correct.
-Did you enter line
31 end of line five?
-I don't know.
Did I?
-Are you asking me?
-Can I-- let me see.
-Absolutely not!
-I got so fed up with him.
Uh.
Really tired.
He never understood me,
never even tried to.
Right after the wedding, I
wanted to go to Disneyland,
have some fun, see Mickey
Mouse, be like a kid, you know?
-Mm-hmm.
I love Minnie Mouse.
-Minnie's just great.
-Oh, so he says, no.
We've got to be alone,
walk on the beach,
so we went to this
motel near San Diego,
and it was so horrible.
Horrible!
It was the year when
the Pacific dried up.
Do you remember?
-How could I forget?
-And the mosquitoes had a feast.
Sam only wanted to see me
naked, and make love to me.
I wanted it, too.
Don't get me wrong.
I was attracted to him,
but not all the time.
It was so boring after a while.
Since I met Jeff, mm, my whole
life became a dream, fantastic.
Oh God, I'm so much in love now.
It's so good to have a lover.
When I get close to him, my
skin is like electrified.
It lights up.
-How do you manage?
Do you still sleep
with your husband?
-I have to.
I'm his wife.
-Doesn't your body
feel repulsed?
I mean, doesn't
it just refuse to?
-I close my eyes
and think of Jeff,
and how wonderfully
better he is,
and I begin to
love him even more.
-Hello.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
On the way here, when I was
looking into the distance,
I saw all these
people, good citizens,
laboring and resting, struggling
and enjoying themselves
under the ruins of houses and
offices, homes and factories,
I saw them all, and I had one
thought, just one thought.
Let's bring us together.
Let's labor and rest.
-Get out of here.
-No, I want to finish my speech.
Let's labor and rest,
struggle and enjoy
ourselves, in
gentler, kinder way.
Let's create, yes, let's unite
and create a better nation.
Let's forget the past,
and heal our wounds.
Let's just look into the future.
There's a light, a tender ray,
a beam of hope for better days,
for the satisfying
future of all of us.
To illustrate my point, I
want to show your something,
something very dear to my heart,
an example of what I just said.
-Now with the sand, when it
gets inside, what do you do?
-I am trying not
to think about it.
-I try, too, but it hurts.
It hurts so bad.
-Not so much with a new lover.
-This is my boot.
I just took it from my foot.
It's good leather.
It's good made.
It fits me perfectly.
Do you think it's
an American make?
No, you're wrong.
This boot is made in China.
It was give to me while I was
there, and it proves we all,
we, the people of this
planet, can make and have
the same things, the same goals.
Thank you.
-You know why they call
a manila envelope manila?
-No, Harry, I'm afraid I don't.
-Don't be afraid,
Wes, either do I.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[CHURCH BELLS RINGING]
-How's the olive?
-Mm.
Great.
Where'd you get them?
-I don't know.
Karen loads up on
them once a week.
-Karen?
Did I tell you you have
a very beautiful wife?
-No, you didn't.
Thank you.
-Is that all regulation?
-Yes, sir.
Would you mind?
-Oh, no, no, no.
Please, be my guest.
-Please excuse the fingers.
Mm.
-Do you think they
need a victim?
-Victim?
A hero.
What was I saying?
I don't like eating here because
the sand gets in my teeth.
-(LAUGHING) I don't agree.
It helps to keep them clean.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
-How does it feel?
Why'd you attack the president?
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Can't you talk?
It's OK.
I can.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
The other day I was reading
a book, a really good book,
and I didn't feel anything.
What happened?
What happened to me?
[THUNDER]
I mean, can you tell
me what went wrong?
[THUNDER]
Do you know what she wants?
You know what I want?
What am I asking you for?
[HEAVY WINDS BLOWING]
-Hi.
-Do you need any help?
-No.
-Oh, I insist.
-If you wish.
-You have beautiful hands.
-Me?
-Yes, you.
-They were beautiful
a long time ago.
-It couldn't be that long ago.
You look 18.
-Do you think so?
-Yes.
[CLEARS THROAT]
-Hiya, Wes.
-Hi, Harry.
-Did I ever tell you
I was a good dowser?
-Dowser?
-Dowser, worked the twig.
-Oh yeah?
-Yeah.
-This is my favorite.
-I have to wash them.
-The sink is full of sand.
-Oh, is it?
-It is.
-Well, I should um clean it.
-(WHISPERS) Why don't
we do it together?
[MUSIC PLAYING]
-You want me to check
your ground out?
Hah?
-Well, my sink works pretty
good most of the time.
-No, I mean with water.
-Water?
-I'll come back.
I'll check the ground.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
-Hey, Wes, you lucky
son of a bitch!
Wes!
You're sitting on-- you've
got water-- you've got water!
-Good.
-Walk with me.
Walk with me, Wes.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
-You fucking--
-Wes-- don't!
[MUSIC PLAYING]
-[SCREAMS]
[MOANS]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
-Wes, hey Wes, you
lucky son of a bitch,
you've got water
all over this place.
Wes.
You've got water--
what's the matter?
What's the matter?
Wes, what happened?
Wes!
Somebody help!
Will somebody help?
-Hi.
-You have beautiful hands.
-Thank you.
-Yes.
It happened just
a few minutes ago.
I don't know.
Yes.
12/10/1950.
650-36-4756.
His father.
Yeah.
Yes.
Generally good.
Policy number 37985423172.
-Listen, I must
go now, but I will
be back next week sometime.
Definitely.
-Not to my knowledge.
He never complained.
Normal.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
-Can I do something for you?
-For me?
-Yeah, Can I bring you
something to eat maybe?
-No, no.
Thank you.
-Are you sure?
It's no trouble.
-Thank you.
-What are you thinking about?
-What?
-I know.
It's awful, isn't it?
-Yes.
-You could leave
us alone, please.
Thank you.
-I want to be with my husband.
-That looks quite horrible,
and you might faint.
-I don't care.
-Yeah, but I do.
-Yes.
-Do you want me to hug you?
Why?
-Leave me alone.
-Multiple fuel
injection, and this back
had a bumper-to-bumper
warranty, good for three years
or 50,000 miles.
-So what?
So what?
-You can't beat that.
-Yeah, well what about the
Subaru 2.3LEFI 1.4 engine?
Huh?
You seen that baby?
Whoa, that's a baby.
And you've got a five
speed manual overdrive.
-Scalpel.
That's it.
It's there, there.
-You've got a five speed
manual overdrive transmission,
rear wheel anti lock
brakes, deluxe wheel trim.
You get a stereo--
just here-- swab.
A stereo and clutch
just for home.
-Got it.
Got it.
-That's it.
That's it.
Stereo and clutch just
for home comforts.
It's got power steering,
interval wipers.
There we go, Swab.
Tachometer, headliner, sliding
rear window, trip odometer.
It's got beautiful
chrome body work, looks
like Jayne Mansfield
lying on the beach.
-Ha.
Forceps.
-It's the car you want to take
your chick out for a ride,
I'm telling you.
It's got easy cruise,
layout there back to back,
it's the car.
Oh, that's the baby.
There we go.
Ah, look at this.
It looks like a chicken factory.
Jesus!
-Hi, guys.
-Hi, Jerry.
-Hi.
-Hello.
Can I introduce myself?
My name is Masur, Jerry Masur.
I'm the head of the
Holy Cross Hospital
Debt Collection Department.
-What do you want?
-What number of the
insurance policy
did you quote to the operator?
-I didn't quote any numbers.
-Yes, you did.
Number 379854231-72.
-Yes?
-Yes, and we checked it.
-I didn't give you any numbers.
-Yes, you did, and this
number doesn't exist.
-I couldn't possibly have
given you any numbers.
-Maybe you just made a mistake.
-No, I didn't.
-I understand you are
under a lot of pressure.
I'm sorry about sneaking
on you like that,
but you must
understand I'm sure,
the operation will cost a
certain amount, rather a lot,
and the hospital cannot
take any chances.
-How much?
-$87,463.29 plus tax.
Fuck!
-What did you do to her?
-Nothing, Ma'am,
she just fainted.
-While she was talking to you.
Who are you?
Oh, I'm sorry, Ma'am.
I should have introduced
myself in the first place.
My name is Masur, Jerry
Masur, head of the Holy Cross
Hospital Debt
Collection Department.
-Oh my God!
Oh my God!
He doesn't have insurance!
-He doesn't?
-He does not.
-Hmm.
I might faint myself.
-So what?
-Yeah, but look, the
decline in the mutual funds,
over 15% in the last 10 days.
It's unbelievable.
[WHISTLES]
-Yeah.
-How can you protect
yourself these days?
Inflation's going crazy, and the
last stock I bought, I think,
went down 20% within two days.
-No, you're kidding.
-Within two days, and
now it's completely
off the,off the board.
-20%?
-It's off the board.
Even more than that.
Look, there's no way you
can protect yourself.
You've got to stick
it to somebody else.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
-Bingo.
Lotto.
-15%.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
-No, nothing, I swear.
Maybe the furniture.
I don't see anything else.
Yeah, of course, I'll wait.
Send them over.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
-What happened to the body?
-Nurse!
-Yes, Dr.
-What does she want?
-I don't know.
I didn't hear.
-Go and see what
the hell she wants.
-Yes, sir.
-Nurse.
-Yes, Dr.?
-Maybe she needs a sedative.
-Yes, sir.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
-What did you say?
-The body!
It vanished!
-Who vanished?
-It was a man, a black man.
He was here.
-There?
Are you sure?
-Positive.
He was dead.
-Dead?
Mm.
Maybe coyotes got him.
They clean a lot.
Would you like a tranquilizer?
-No, I'm OK.
Thank you, Nurse.
-Not at all.
-What did you find out?
-Nothing much.
She saw a man.
-Where?
-On the cross.
-Was he OK?
-Supposedly he was dead.
-Maybe he just needed
a good operation.
-Gentlemen,
gentlemen, don't even
dare to contemplate an
operation without me making
sure the money aspect
is in place, understand?
Enough is enough!
-Look!
[MUSIC PLAYING]
-I can't believe it.
It's Liz.
-Good God, it is her!
[MUSIC PLAYING]
-Faster.
-Hey, guys, it's Liz!
Nobody's going to go and look?
-Forget it.
We've got work to do.
-I saw her last week.
She's walking the whole desert.
-I know.
-You're right.
We're going to have
to make two trips.
It won't fit into one.
What goes first?
-All right.
Let's do it the easy way.
Let's get this half.
This goes first.
Hey,
-He doesn't look too good.
-What a mess!
[MUSIC PLAYING]
-Excuse me.
Excuse me.
-Step aside, please.
-What's the name of the movie?
I want to look out for
it when it comes out.
-Three, four, go.
-Ah, Dr., Harry White.
Ah, listen, how's the
organ market today?
Oh.
Not even kidneys.
OK, sorry.
Yeah.
All right.
Thank you.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
-No [INAUDIBLE] silver.
Flower holder.
OK,OK.
Be careful with that.
Glass tabletop and stand.
Two chairs.
-Excuse me.
-All right.
OK.
Four chairs.
-This is it.
We're going to make another run.
-OK, but make it snappy, huh?
I'd like to finish up here
before the day is out.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
-Hey, Harry, how are you?
Did you see Liz?
Is she something?
-Something.
How are you?
-Big guy.
-Good to see you.
-Big guy, hah?
Big guy.
What do you think about Liz?
-Very good.
She's nice.
-Hah?
[INAUDIBLE] What a view, hah?
[LAUGHTER]
-All right.
All right.
-Good to see you.
-You, too.
-You like that Liz though, hah?
Listen, do you want me to
take all the furniture?
-Yeah.
-What's wrong with Wes?
-It's not, you kn ow, it's not
going to cover the bill at all.
-Yes, how is he?
-He's dead.
-Yeah, I'm very sorry.
-What shall you do?
-Nothing, I'm afraid we
did the best we could.
Not much is for us, is there?
-Argh!
-I'm very sorry.
-That's OK, guys.
They wouldn't pay anyhow.
-Harry.
-Why didn't you take
all the furniture?
-Oh, they could only
take a half a load.
It's a union regulation.
-Oh, I see.
The rules are the rules.
-The rules are the rules.
-Well, [INAUDIBLE].
I want to thank you very much.
Please go home, and
have a good rest.
You, too, Nurse.
-Bye, Harry.
-Don't be offended.
It's time for me.
I'd love to have some
breakfast with you.
Maybe, maybe other time, hmm?
-We'll do lunch.
-Big lunch, huh?
-I'll call you.
I'll call you.
-Yes, I call you, too.
-You call me, huh?
-On the desert, the best thing
is to put it into the fridge
until the undertaker comes.
Goodbye.
Goodbye, Harry.
-Safe trip.
Take care of yourself.
-Goodbye.
I'll have this furniture
packed by night.
-Can I help you?
-Yes, please, my
hands are no good.
-Yes, I noticed.
Did you burn them?
-No, no.
It's arthritis.
It, it helps to keep them warm.
-May I make a suggestion?
-Sure, what?
-If these gloves help
to ease the pain,
you can use them
as a tax deduction.
-Yeah, but they're so cheap.
-Every penny counts.
I was just trying to be helpful.
All right.
-Oh.
Damn.
Christ.
Oh.
-Where is the body?
-It's in the fridge.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
-You're a wreck.
You're shaking all over.
We'll take care of the funeral.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
-No, wait, wait.
I want to say goodbye.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Goodbye, my boy.
Keep well.
Give my regards to your mother.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
-You know, I could make you
want a warmer pair of gloves.
-Yeah?
WOMAN SINGING: I'll
tell you one more thing,
and it's plain for you to see.
No matter what I get--
[MUSIC PLAYING]
This land takes it away from me.
I've got the sand,
got the sand over me.
Please, sand, get
out of my life.
Leave me alone, and let me be.
Please, sand, get
out of my life.
Leave me alone and let me be.
-Not that one.
That one.
Faster.
Pull.
-Well, where the hell were you?
-We got hungry.
We had to make a break
at Burger King, OK?
I mean, we've been
working all day,
can't go around on
an empty stomach.
-Yeah, all right.
OK,OK.
-We're moving.
We're moving.
-Can we roll the carpet?
-Absolutely, everything goes.
-Give it back!
It's the only thing
I can't live without.
-Sorry, Miss, Mr.
White's orders.
-Please, I beg you.
I'm a widow.
I have no husband, no money,
no insurance, nothing.
Please, I beg you.
-It's OK, JC.
-Good choice. [INAUDIBLE].
-We can make an
exception in this case.
Your husband was
a really nice man.
-I'll never forget it.
-Goodbye.
-Bye.
-And God bless you, Mr. White.
-God bless you, too.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[LAUGHING]
-God.
I'm pregnant.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[THUNDER]
[RAINING]