♪♪
Do not forget
to subscribe down below,
like this video,
and follow me on Instagram
for more beauty related
things...
photos, outfit pictures.
[Cameras shutters clicking]
Woman: All right, can I get
my makeup influencers
on this side, please?
♪♪
Hey, girl.
Hey.
Killer shoes.[Laughs] Thanks.
Hey, everyone.
I'm here with Genelle,
last year's
Beauty Influencer of the Year
and current Beauty Ambassador
for Sekani Cosmetics.
I am personally a fan.
My winged eyeliner is solely
thanks to your channel.
So good. [Laughs]
How are you
feeling tonight?
We are so blessed
to be here.
I'm beyond grateful for
the support of all my followers
and to be a part of
an amazing beauty community.
Namaste, bitches.
I mean, it is so
amazing talking to you.
Oh, my God.
Thank you.
Hey, guys.
I'm here for
the super exclusive,
invite-only red carpet
for Sekani Cosmetics.
[Indistinct talking]
Next week, I'll be doing
a new tutorial
on their new line
of matte shadows.
- Oh! My God!
- Oh, my gosh.
- Oh, my...
- Uh...
Oh, my God.
♪♪
Be a good girl.
[Growling]
[Clamoring,
camera shutters popping]
[Air dryer whirring]
[Barking]
[Whirring stops]
Ew, don't!
Hey!
Hey, give me my dog.
Ah!
Don't!
♪♪
♪ I come home
in the morning light ♪
♪ My mother says, "When you
gonna live your life right?" ♪
♪ Oh, mother dear, we're
not the fortunate ones ♪
♪ And girls,
they wanna have fun ♪
♪ Oh, girls just
want to have fun ♪
Reporter: NVS News
is reporting it looks
like the Southland Dog Killer
has struck again,
but this time,
the pooch got away.
His owner, not so lucky.
♪ The phone rings
in the middle of the night ♪
♪ My father yells, "What you
gonna do with your life?" ♪
♪ Oh, daddy dear, you know
you're still number one ♪
♪ But girls,
they wanna have fun ♪
♪ Oh, girls
just want to have fun ♪
Hi, guys.
I'm shook.
Seriously.
Genelle was a makeup legend.
So because of what happened,
I've made a decision.
I'm not going to do the live
stream with my friends tomorrow.
Instead, I'm going to go
to my sister Nicole's house
to baby sit
her amazing dog Chico.
I just really feel like
it's necessary
to be selfless
during this time.
Jade:
Psycho dog killer, whatever.
Chico does not need
a baby sitter.
You got to go to
the live stream tomorrow.
You have the most followers!
There will be tequila!
♪ Hide her away from
the rest of the world ♪
Santi: So, what you're telling
me is that you love a dog
more than me,
your smoking hot boyfriend.
Not cool.
No one's going to watch
if you're not there.
You know you have
the most followers.
♪ That's all I really want ♪
♪ Some fun ♪
Lani: Mia, I can buy Nicole
a new dog.
You've got to come.
Although, that said,
kudos on the selfless thing.
It's very on brand.
♪ Oh, girls just
want to have fun ♪
♪♪
♪ Just wanna ♪
Mia! Mia, where are you?!
♪ Just wanna,
they just wanna ♪
♪ They just wanna ♪
Nicole doesn't need you.
We need you.
♪ Just wanna ♪
[Dog bark]
[Dog food rattling]
Mia: Come get
your food, buddy.
[Sighs]
Alexa.
Diana, turn on
the lights in Mia's room.
♪♪
[Camera shutter clicks]
[Cellphone buzzes]
Nicole:
I just want to say hi.
Um, first, thank you
for watching Chico.
Granted, you said no,
you wouldn't watch Chico
like 10 times,
and then that chick died
and you realized it could make
you look better or whatever.
I don't know, but I'm glad
you're there, really.
Um...
feel free to help
with the packing.
The realtor is coming
to take pictures next week.
And second, I know I've been
kind of hard lately.
Diana, turn on the lights
in mom's room.
Um, I just think when I was
taking care of mom
and all of her medications,
all these different ones
had to be different times
on a schedule, and it just...
Not that I'm trying to make
you feel bad or anything.
Really, I totally signed up
to take care of her,
and I was happy to.
I really was.
And, um, you're
not off the hook.
It'll be your turn to
take care of me soon.
So there's that. Um...
Love you.
[Cellphone buzzes]
[Chimes]
Chico, come here, buddy.
There you are. Hi!
[Barking]Hi, Chico.
[Snoring]
Diana, play
Chill Vibes play list.
[Music plays]
And turn on the A.C.
[Chimes]
Ew.
[Speaking indistinctly]
Are you guys there?
Are you guys there?!
I think they're there.
Happy. Welcome.
It's ancient game,
it's called Quarters.
I haven't actually
played it before.
Ready?
Ah.Ah, that's okay.
That's not how you play.
It ishow you play.Nuh-unh. [Laughs]
Do better, come on. Do better.
Do better. Do better.
[Indistinct talking]
[Clanging]
[Gasps]
Oh, that was so close!
Mia, we miss you. We miss you.
We wish you were here. I miss you, Mia.
Oh, my God.
Where are you right now?
We're touching knees.[Laughs]
Love you, Mia.
I'm just saying, when the cat's
away, the Santi will play.
Oh, my goodness.
He wouldn't do that.
I quit.
No, don't.
[Chimes]
What the hell?
Diana, lock all the doors.
[Locks click]
And turn on the lights
in the living room.
You see this?
She's on my phone.
He has crazy bitches
on his phone.
If you could see
his battery right now.
It is so bad.
[Laughs]
Oh, my gosh.
Should I turn the phone around?
Shall I turn
the phone around? Shall I?
Shall I show
our wonderful audience?
[Screams]
Leave me alone!
[Laughs]
Oh, my goodness!
I think I have to.
Oh, my gosh.
What about this one?
That's crazy.
[Gasps] Oh, no, I can't.
Shut up!
Leave me alone.
Oh, my goodness.
You called me a lot
of shit right now.
He is crazy.
This is so crazy.
No, no, no.
Ow! You tickle me.
[Chimes]
Come on.
That was then.
This is now.
Bullshit.
Chico loves car rides.
Chico, come here, buddy.
Chico?
Diana, turn on the lights
in the foyer.
Chico?
Chico, come here, buddy.
[Line ringing]
Jade: Hey, babes. It's Jade.
Leave a message.
[Indistinct talking]
Chico?
Diana, turn on the lights
in the kitchen.
Chico?
[Cellphone buzzes]
[Cellphone chimes]
[Sighs]
Diana, turn on the lights
in Mia's room.
[Static, indistinct talking]
[Sighs]
[Line ringing]
Jade: Hey, babes. It's Jade.
Leave a message.
[Cellphone buzzes]
[Chimes]
Chico?
Got your food.
[Cellphone buzzes]
Hello?
Man: Mia?
Who is this?
Oh, sorry.
This is Kellan.
I live across
the street.
How did you get my number?
Your sister gave it to me.
For emergencies, you know?
Did you just leave me
a voicemail?
Yeah. Sorry.
I wanted to know
if you'd seen my dog, Rascal.
I can't find him.
No. Sorry.
Shit.
I mean, uh, shoot.
Okay.
Well, I'm going to go.
You haven't been around
in a while.
Huh?
You haven't been around.
I haven't seen you.
Oh. Yeah. You know,
I don't live here anymore.
I'm going to school.
I mean, I get it.
I know things were
pretty bad with your mom.
No, I've just, you know,
been busy.
Last time I saw her,
she thought I was your uncle
and told me to vote
for Jimmy Carter.
Oh, well, you know, at least
she's not a pedophile, so...
I just meant
you used to come around more,
with your friends.
Yeah. Like I said,
I've been busy.
How's Jade?
What?
I can't believe she got
that tattoo.
What are you
talking about?
You know they call it
a tramp stamp, right?
How do you know about
Jade's tattoo?
We're friends now. What?
Online.
[Chimes]
That girl takes more
selfies than even you.
You know, I...
I really should go.
Oh, okay.
Yeah. Sorry.
Let me know
if you see Rascal.
[Sighs] Sure. Sure thing.
[Light switch clicks]
Chico?
[Rustling]
[Sighs]
[Clattering]
Chico?
[Cellphone buzzes]
Hello?
Kellan: Hey, Mia.
It's Kellan again.
Yeah. What do you want?
I just heard you calling
for Chico a bit ago.
Is he lost, too?
I don't know.
[Chimes]
Get your ass over here.
Kellan: Probably
hiding under the bed.
What did you just say?
Nicole says he hides
under the bed when he's scared.
I didn't realize you
and my sister talked so much.
Oh, you know,
just in passing.
He's a cute dog.
Okay.
Well, thanks for the tip.
Yeah. I'd hate to see
anything bad happen to Chico.
Aren't you worried
about Rascal?
Yes, absolutely.
Then why aren't you out
looking for him?
I did. I just, uh,
couldn't find him.
I don't think he's
in Nicole's room.
Why not? The door is closed.
[Cellphone buzzes]
Oh, Lani
is such a slut.
What?
Is he there
under the bed?
No. What did you
just say before that?
Uh, hold on a sec.
Diana, turn on the lights
in Nicole's room.
Diana, turn on the lights.
Chico!
Here, buddy!
[Gasps]
[Barking]
What was that?
What?
I heard a dog.
You said yours was missing.
Oh, I just found him,
a few seconds ago.
Why did you tell me
to look under Nicole's bed?
I told you.
Stop lying.
What's going on?
What's going on is...
I've got your
fucking dog, bitch.
Operator:
Please stay on the line.
You have reached
the 911 call center.
Your call will be answered
as soon as possible.
Please stay on the line.
You have reached
the 911 call center.
Your call will be answered
as soon as possible.
Please stay on the line.
You have reached
the 911 call center.
[Cellphone chimes]
Your call will be answered
as soon as possible.
Please stay on the line.
You have reached
the 911 call center.
Your call will be answered
as soon as possible.
Please stay on the line.
You have reached
the 911 call center.
Your call will be answered
as soon as possible.
[Gasps]
Please stay on the line.
You have reached
the 911 call center.
Your call will be answered
as soon as possible.
Man: This is 911.
What's your emergency?
Hello?
Oh, my God.
What is your
emergency?
Sorry.
Oh! Oh!
Is everything
all right?
I made a mistake.
I'm sorry.
Diana, turn on the lights
in the living room.
[Cellphone buzzes]
Jade. Oh, my God.
Are you okay?
Jade, are you there?
Jade: [Crying]
He says if you leave,
scream for the neighbors.
if you call anyone...
Jade... he'll kill me.
[Gasps]
[Cellphone chimes]
Kellan: The time
has come for us
to establish
some ground rules.
[Cellphone buzzes]Rule number one,
when I call,
you answer.
[Cellphone buzzing]
Jade covered the rest.
No leaving, no screaming
to get attention from neighbors,
no speaking to anyone
other than me.
If you do, then...
I kill everyone.
[Barks]
Chico!
Oh, don't do that.
It's just taunting
the poor fella.
Why are you doing this?
What were you supposed
to do tonight?
What do you mean?
What was the one thing
your sister asked you to do?
Take care of the dog.
It's an important thing,
you know, to be a caretaker.
What are you talking about?
I'm saying you were supposed
to take care
of a dog,
and look what's happened.
I tried.
You tried?
You mean by spending
all of your time
texting your
worthless friends?
No, he was with me
on the couch.
For how long?
I don't know.
He was there.
You don't even know.
Terrible.
I'm sorry!
That's not
good enough, Mia.
[Chico whimpers]
[Gasps]
What are you doing to him?
It's not me, Mia.
It's you.
Why are you doing this? You'll see.
But first,
I need you to make a choice.
[Cellphone chimes]
Mia!
He says you have
to choose!
You have to choose
between Lani and Chico!
[Gasps]
Mia!
Wait! Don't hurt her.
This is crazy. Can't argue with that.
Why are you doing this?
I promise to tell you.
Pinky promise.
But right now, you have
to make a choice.
Who do you care about more?
Chico or Lani?
Are you kidding? It's a simple question.
Your sick sister's dog
or the girl
trying to sleep
with your boyfriend?
You don't have to do this.
You don't have to hurt anyone.
Time's up.
Wait!
[Shouts indistinctly]
Mia, he says you're out of time.
You're out of time!
You have to pick!
He's got a knife!
[Screams]
Lani!
I pick Lani.
Hello?
Are you there?
I pick Lani.
[Whimpers]
[Sobs]
[Sobbing]
All right, back inside.
The sooner
you go inside,
the sooner this will
all be over.
Oh, I see.
You're scared.
It looks like you need
some extra encouragement.
[Cellphone chimes]
No!
[Sobbing]
That's not possible!
She's on a plane right now.
Kellan:
No, I don't think so.
How are you doing this?
Round two.
Come inside, Mia.
I think you know
what will happen if you don't.
[Gasps]
[Sobs]
[Barking in distance]
[Cellphone buzzes]
So, here we go.
You ready?
I guess.
You don't sound like your usual
buoyant self, Mia.
Anything wrong?
Fuck you!
What the fuck
is the matter with you?!
And she's back.
Okay, much better.
What if I just hang up?
What if I just stop
talking to you?
[Chuckles]
That's not an option.
But how about this?
I'll meet you halfway.
"Yes, Kellan.
Tell me more."
Okay, well,
since you asked,
we both know you have another
big choice coming up,
but what if there was
a way for you
to not have to
make that choice?
Might that be
appealing to you?
Yes.
That's what
I thought.
So?
So, all you have to do
is answer three questions.
That's it.
If you get them right,
then I'll stop this whole thing
and let everyone go.
But if you get
one wrong,
then you have to make a choice
between Nicole...
and Santi.
Okay.
Here we go.
First question.
When administering CPR,
maintaining proper rhythm
is crucial.
What song is recommended
for achieving
the correct tempo. Huh?
You have one minute.
No, wait, what?
Can you repeat that?
57, 56, 55.
Damn it.
[Cellphone chimes]
[Gasping]
Mia! Help!
Help me, Mia!
Mia, babe.
CPR might come in handy.
Asshole!
I don't know. I don't know.
I don't see a song!
Here you are cheating
and complaining about it.
Tsk-tsk.
Didn't say...
You didn't say I couldn't.
16, 15, 14...
10 Mississippi,
9 Mississippi.
"Staying Alive",
by the Bee Gees.
Ding, ding, ding,
ding, ding!
Get that girl a toaster!
Next question.
And this time, no cheating.
Wait.
What is...
Wait!
Yes?
Is Santi okay?
For now.
Next question.
At what temperature is someone
considered to have a fever?
No. No interwebs.
59, 58, 57...
[Chimes]
[Screaming]
Aaah! No!
...42, 41, 40...
...28, 27, 26...
...5, 4...
100.4.
...3...
Hello? Was I right?
[Sighs]
Yes, that is correct.
Is Jade okay?
So far.
Okay, what's next?
Oh, now you're into it
now that you're winning.
Come on, let's finish this.
Okay. Final question.
What were your mother's
last words?
How would you know what
my mother's last words were?
59, 58, 57...
[Cellphone chimes]
[Crying, screaming]
[Gasps]
[Screaming]
...42, 41, 40...
Why are you asking
about my mother?
Why not?
What does she have to do
with this?
I liked your mom.
I don't remember her
ever speaking about you.
Well, she didn't speak
of you much either.
Go to hell.
She probably forgot
you even existed.
I mean, how often did you
come by to visit
when she was
getting sick?
I mean, when she
was really sick.
Fuck you!
And I don't mean how often
you promised to visit
because that's not obviously
a much different answer.
Who told you what my mother's
last words were?
How do you know
I wasn't there?
You weren't.How do you know?
Nicole would have told me.
Did she tell you what
your mother's last words were?
No?
Why weren't you
there, Mia?
I had school.
Didn't Nicole tell you that
she had only a few hours left?
Yes, but...
14, 13, 12...
You're running out
of time.
This isn't fair!
...6, 5...
No!
...2...
Please, please,
don't hurt her!
One.
Don't hurt who?
Lani or Nicole?
That's right.
Looks like we went
through all of that,
and we're right back
where we started.
Time to make a choice.
This isn't fair.
You don't know the answer.
I do know the answer.
And you do, too.
What do you mean?
Your mom had a breathing tube
for the last two weeks
of her life.
She couldn't
say anything.
I...
You forgot.
Well, that's behind us now.
We have more pressing
matters to deal with.
I can't do this.
Sure you can. In fact,
you've done it once before.
But that was a dog!
A beloved dog.
Just leave us alone.
Who's it going to be, Mia?
You've got one minute.
59, 58...
...57, 56...
[Screams]
...55. 54...
[Sobbing]
[Sobs]
[Cellphone chimes]
[Sobbing]
[Gasps]
This is crazy! Fuck you!
You know what happens
if you don't choose, right?
They both die.
I can't choose. I can't.
You must want something.
There must be a reason
why you're doing all of this.
You must want something.
22 Mississippi,
21 Mississippi...
What do you want?...20 Mississippi.
Tell me what it is!
...15 Mississippi...Stop!
...14 Mississippi,
13 Mississippi.
Just stop this!
5 Mississippi,
4 Mississippi...
Stop! 3 Mississippi.
I don't know!
Nicole's sick!
Lani! I pick Lani!
[Cellphone chimes]
[Panting]
[Sobs]
[Screams]
[Sighs]
[Sobs]
[Cellphone buzzes]
[Cellphone buzzing]
[Laughs] Dude, you just
killed your sister.
What? I love you too, bitch.
[Smooching]
I don't understand.
I know. [Laughs]
Fucking cut it out, Lani!
Tell me what's happening!
It's okay. It's okay.
Everyone's okay.
How? It was all fake.
Well, here we are
just fucking with you.
I am in your attic
right now.
[Pounding on ceiling]
Lani, where's Nicole?
Oh, um, probably
in San Francisco by now.
I don't know. I don't understand.
Okay, so the videos were from
after your mom's funeral.
You know,
back at the house.
What? Okay, so I wasn't sure
if it was going to work.
I was going to ask Nicole
to help us out,
but then Jade and Santi
was like,
"No, there's no way
she'd do this."
And well, you know,
she hates us.
So I thought
I'd improvise.
What about Kellan?
What about him?
I don't know, he's probably
jacking off over there.
Ew.He was on the phone.
No, it wasn't him.
It was a voice changer app
and a fake phone number.
Oh, wait. Wait, wait, wait.
Hold on.
[Male voice] Hey, babe.
Jade: Hey. Where are you?
We're in the house next door,
the one that's for sale.
We've been going back
and forth all night.
- How?
- The balconies are
so close together in the 'burbs,
so we can just jump
from the balcony of
the master bedroom
over there
to the one over here.
We recorded all
the live video last night.
Did you know
there's an app
that lets you upload
pre-recorded stuff?
[Chimes]
Why are you doing this?
You know, you have
a lot of followers.
So?
So we've live-streamed
everything.
Okay, well, not everything,
but most of it.
And you two just
went along with it?
Okay, let me explain. I'm sorry.
Awesome. I thought it would be fun.
Fun?
What the fuck is wrong
with you guys?!
Fucking followers?!
Ugh!
[Crying]
♪♪
[Breathing deeply]
Fucking assholes!
Ohh!
♪♪
[Cellphone vibrates]
[Sighs]
[Sniffles]
♪♪
[Squeals]
[Whispering]
Shh, shh, shh.
She has no idea
what's going on right now.
This is amazing.
[Gasps]
And we're bringing her flowers.
How cute.
♪♪
[Scoffs]
[Chuckles]
Look what I've got.
I pinched them from her room.
Shh! [Giggles]
This is so much fun. Shh.
[Scoffs]
♪♪
Okay, guys,
this stuff is the shit.
It is so good.
And it tastes amazing.
But it's really gory. Oooh.
No, I'm going to drink it.
Aah!
♪♪
[Sobbing]
[Banging]
[Sobbing continues]
[Sobbing stops]
[Sniffles]
Nicole:
Please leave a message. Thanks.
[Ringing]
Man: Barrington Hotel.
Hi. I was wondering
if you could connect me
with someone staying there...
uh, Nicole Larson.
One moment.
Thank you.
Nicole: Hello?
Hi! It's me!
Mia. Everything okay?
Um, did you make it
to San Fran okay?
Yes. [Chuckles]
Good.
Um...
are you sure
everything's okay?
♪♪
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
For what?
I'm sorry
I haven't been here.
Oh.
Yeah, I just wanted to call
and... tell you that I was sorry.
Do you mean that?
Yeah.
I wish
I could believe you.
I know
I've apologized before.
You have.
And nothing's changed.
Exactly.
But... this is different.
How's Chico?
He's fine.
Really?
Yeah.
What's he doing? He's sleeping.
Where?
Uh, with me, on the couch.
Send me a picture?
Yeah, sure,
as soon as we hang up.
Thanks.
It'll help me fall asleep.
Oh, um, N-Nicole,
your phone is off,
by the way.
Nicole?
I was getting a lot of texts,
so I put it on silent.
Oh, from who?
From the camera
in Mom's room.
[Sighs]
Now, is it just Jade,
Santi, and Lani,
or are there more people?
It's not what you think.
I got to get to sleep.
I have to be at the hospital
early tomorrow.
Yeah. Okay.
♪♪
Lani, where is Chico?!
[Vibrating]
♪♪
Where's the dog?
Mia.
Mia, get out the house.
Just cut it out already!
Stop it!
[Whispering]
Mia, you have to leave.
Stop it! Just stop it! Get out of here.
Where's the dog? Where's Chico?
[Crying] Get out.
Or I swear to God...
Listen to me. I mean it.
[Gasps]
Assholes!
[Vibrating]
[Sighs]
Where's the dog?
Santi: Mia, wait. No, fuck you.
Mia, just listen. No, youlisten.
It wasn't my idea,
I swear, but...
Do you want me to start counting
down, you sadistic fuck?
But... What is wrong with you guys?
[Beeping]You don't understand!
No, you're right.
I don't understand.
I don't know what the hell
happened here tonight,
but I know that I hate you.
I know that.
I mean, that shit about my mom?
What did I ever do to you?
It was Lani. It was all Lani.
You guys are supposed
to be my friends.
Why don't any of you
come down here yet?
You know that I can hear you
walking around up there.
The game is over. It's not, Mia.
We had to do what they said
or they were going to hurt you.
Oh, give me a break.
They told me to go
into your room and wait,
and then it was locked. You know what?
Just give me my keys back
and I'll leave.
I don't have your keys!
You aren't listening!
[Sighs]
I'm getting out of here!
♪♪
Oh, fucking suburbs.
[Vibrating]
♪♪
[Water splashes]
It's not funny anymore!
Okay, enough.
It's not funny anymore, Lani!
♪♪
Aaaaaaaaaaaah!
What?
[Vibrating]
♪♪
What the fuck?!
[Breathing heavily]
I'm ready.
Put down the knife.
♪♪
Put it down.
Go into the living room.
♪♪
[Whimpers]
[Breathing heavily]
♪♪
[Gasps]
[Whimpers]
[Cellphone vibrates]
♪♪
What's in them?
[Whimpers]
[Cellphone vibrates]
♪♪
Santi:
I'm in your bedroom right now.
But I can hear someone.
♪♪
They're coming.
[Thudding]
♪♪
[Cellphone vibrates]
[Whimpers]
♪♪
[Gasps]
[Whimpering]
♪♪
Aah.
[Gasps]
[Whimpers]
[Crying]
♪♪
[Whimpers]
[Breathing heavily]
Mm.
[Whimpers]
[Crying]
♪♪
[Groaning]
[Breathing heavily]
♪♪
[Crying]
[Groans]
[Breathing heavily]
♪♪
[Whimpering]
[Crying]
[Gasping]
Aaah!
[Breathing heavily]
♪♪
Ahhhh!
[Grunts]
[Whimpers]
[Groans]
[Breathing heavily]
♪♪
[Groans, whimpers]
[Crying]
Aaaaah!
[Breathing heavily]
No.
[Whimpers]
Santi!
[Breathing heavily]
Santi! Santi!
Santi!
♪♪
Aaaaah!
[Grunting]
♪♪
Aaah! [Grunts]
[Breathing heavily]
♪♪
[Whimpers]
[Crying]
No!
♪♪
[Crying]
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah!
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah!
[Breathing heavily]
I don't understand!
♪♪
[Cellphone vibrating]
Jade?
Jade: Mia, is he okay? No, he's not.
[Crying] Fuck, fuck,
fuck, fuck, fuck.
Where are you?
Jade, where are you?
I'm so sorry.
I'm so, so sorry.
Shut up.
Just... try and stay calm.
It's just [Sniffles]
it was a lot of money.
That's why you did this?
Lani paid you?
It was just... so much money.
And Santi and I thought, well,
we'd split it with you after.
This was about money?!
We were going to
split it with you!
[Cellphone vibrates]
♪♪
Did you just get that?
Yes.
♪♪
[Indistinct conversations]
[Man laughs]
[Conversations continue]
Man: Excuse me. Could you help me
find the ice cream?
Ice cream? Uh, you turn right,
right again. Aisle 7.
Okay, thank you.
Sure.
What do you want me to say?
Okay.
I'm... broke.
I pretend that I have
a lot of money, but I don't.
♪♪
[Crying] What?
Yeah, okay.
I work at Whole Foods.
I lied. I just...
I say that shit online because
no one would be interested
in following a cashier.
Okay?
But Mia... she had the money,
we thought.
[Cellphone beeps]
[Crying]
♪♪
[Breathing heavily]
Uhh.
[Grunts]
♪♪
[Gasps]
Aaaaaah![Thud]
Mom?
[Crying]
God.
[Cellphone chimes]
♪♪
Nicole:
I guess you found Mom.
I know you're in my closet.
I get texts that
there's movement, remember?
♪♪
[Ringing]
Hello.
♪♪
What did you do?
I feel so much better
now that you know.
We buried Mom!
Well, no.
Obviously, we didn't.
How?
People will do anything
for money.
Do you really want
to know the details?
♪♪
[Whispering] Oh, fuck.
N-No.
♪♪
You were in San Francisco.
I called you.
You called San Francisco.
The hotel patched you
through to my cell.
What?
I found the front-desk clerk
on Venmo last week
and, uh, made him an offer
he couldn't refuse.
Sensing a theme?
What about Kellan?
I don't know. He probably
is jacking off over there.
Jesus, Nicki!
♪♪
Oh, my God!
[Crying]
♪♪
I had to.
I don't understand!
[Voice breaking]
She wasn't her anymore.
She was becoming
less her every day.
But Nicole!
And now...
Now she's still her.
♪♪
I know.
I know it's crazy.
If you know it's crazy, then why
are you doing any of this? Why?!
How can you pick Lani over me?
Nicole.
[Crying]
I'm your sister, Mia.
Yes, but...
you're sick.
♪♪
Nicole, i...
I-I didn't...
I didn't plan on this part.
I only planned the first part,
the fake part.
But then...
then, after all of this,
you still went ahead
and you lied to me
about Chico.
♪♪
You still...
couldn't tell me the truth.
♪♪
Still [Sniffles] covering up
for your friends.
♪♪
I just couldn't take it.
This is just Livingston's.
This isn't you.
Most of the time it isn't.
♪♪
But sometimes... it is.
Nicole, where's Jade?
Oh. Ready to play again
already?
Sheesh. I would have thought
you'd want a break.
No, stop!
I don't know
if you've noticed,
but there's been
a bit of a theme
to all of this tonight. I've noticed.
You could have been the one
to take care of Mom. I know.
You could have been
the sick one. I know.
I have to have injections
every day.
I have the personality changes,
the mood swings,
fever, trouble breathing,
walking!
You know, it's funny,
but that's the one
that really pisses me off...
walking.
It's such a simple thing.
I saw you earlier.
You walked fine.
Yes, earlier.
Now, not so much.
Tomorrow, fine.
Next week, not at all!
So, here's the thing.
I'll give you five minutes
on this one
because it's a doozy.
Break your leg
in five minutes
or Jade dies.
What?! I don't care how you do it,
but you have to do it
in five minutes.
Stop, Nicole!
Sorry. Can't.
How do I know you aren't just
going to kill her anyway?
I promise you, Mia.
♪♪
I give you my word.
If you do this...
I'll stop.
How can I believe you?!
Because I'm your sister.
♪♪
I know when Mom was sick,
we agreed
I'd be the one
to take care of her.
I know that.
But once you moved out...
you were gone.
It's like we didn't even
matter to you anymore.
That's not true.
♪♪
You know, sometimes
it feels like...
It's... It's like these...[Crying]
sharp, shooting pains,
like, all over my body.
[Whimpering]
Like... Like little knives.
[Screaming]No! Oh, my God!
4 minutes, 59 seconds.[Sobbing]
58... 57...
[Screaming]
Aah!
56.
♪♪
[Grunting]
[Whimpers]
♪♪
[Breathing heavily]
That might work.
Going to take some commitment
on your part, though,
and let's admit it...
you haven't always been
the best
at following through.
How are you going to know
if it's broken?
What if it's
a hairline fracture?
If I can't tell,
then it's not broken enough.
Fuck.
Whoa. You only got
three minutes left.
Better get cracking.
[Breathing heavily]
[Cellphone vibrates][Gasps]
Who was that? No one!
If you call the police or let
anyone know what's going on,
I'll kill Jade now.
I didn't! I swear!
Why is there
a car outside?
I don't know why he's here.
It's not me.
You're running out of time!
Aaaaaah!
Ohh!
[Breathing heavily]
I can't tell!
Then it's not enough.
Fuck. Okay.
Ohh.
[Grunting]
♪♪
[Grunting continues]
[Screaming]
Go away!
[Grunting]30 seconds!
[Grunting continues]
[Gasps]
[Sobbing]
[Breathing heavily]
Aaaaaaaah!
[Gasps, whimpers]
Ohh. I did it!
I said, "Legs,"
not "Leg."
[Breathing heavily]
[Whimpering]
♪♪
Ugh!
Aaaah!
[Crying]
[Sobbing]
Well, that was
quite a jump,
but it still looks
like you only got one.
Ohh! Ohhhhhhhh!
You went for both, though.
I applaud the effort.
You really love
your friends.
Is she okay?!
Is she okay, Nicki?
I can't believe you broke
your leg for Jade.
I guess part of you
really is a good person.
Please tell me she's okay.
Jade?
Yeah.
No.
[Crying]
[Scoffs]
I got to say...
[Whimpering]
...you surprised me.
I did not think
you could be this selfless.
[Crying] Nicki, no.
If only you would have
done it for me.
[Crying]
So, you paid them?
Are they pieces of shit
or what?
Nicole.
Put Mom's pension
to good use, at least.
Nicole!
Do you know how many dogs
I killed to set this thing up?
What?
It was way worse than Lani.
She slept with Santi
last night, by the way,
after we were finished
recording everything.
That's not true.
How do you know?
Santi was a virgin.
Super Catholic, so...
I don't know. I doubt it.
[Scoffs]
People are so different
online.
Lani's rich. Santi's a player.
You're sweet as an angel.
That's your brand, right? I guess.
"Makeup by Mia."
I don't know why you
couldn't use your real name.
Mia ismy real name.
Middle name.
It sounded nicer.
I really...
I really thought you were going
to pick me in the end.
[Crying]
But you didn't.
And if you didn't
pick me now,
you're not going
to pick me later...
not when I can't walk
or feed myself
or go to the bathroom
by myself.
I promised I would
take care of you.
Yeah, you did.
You promised.
But that's just words.
It's not real...
just like so much of tonight
wasn't real.
Nothing about you is real.
It's all just carefully curated
for online consumption.
I'm not like that.
[Crying]
You can't handle me
or... or sickness
or complicated feelings,
so you just bail and live
in your fantasy world,
putting on makeup
for your legions of fans.
But I did it!
I did all of your tests!
But for them.
Well, I guess this is it.
What are you talking about?
We might as well
check out, too.
I've got a gun.
♪♪
I can do you, do me,
and then we're done.
Where did you get a gun?
Mom had it.
I guess she didn't think
my baseball bat was gonna cut it
if we were overtaken
by suburban rapists.
♪♪
I can vouch for the bat.
[Chuckles softly]
You sure can.
[Dog barking in distance]
♪♪
Chico?
I-I left him outside
and his crate.
[Knock on door]
[Gasps, sniffles]
[Sniffles]
If you move or do anything,
I'll kill them.
♪♪
Hey, Nicole.
Sorry to bother you.
I found Chico wandering around
in my yard.
Oh, my gosh.
He must have snuck outside.
Thank you so, so much.[Chico whines]
[Smooches]
Yeah.
You got to be careful
with that, uh, maniac
running around
killing dogs.
You're right.
Thank you so much.
Yeah, no problem.[Chico barks]
Uh...
Oh.
[Laughing] Oh! Oh!
That wasn't
what it looked like.
Wha... [Chuckles]
What was it, then?
I'm painting,
and I spilled it everywhere.
And now I have
to give Chico a bath.
[Chuckles]
I hate when that happens.
[Chuckles][Chuckles] Red, huh?
I wanted something
with a little drama.
That'll do it.
Okeydokey.
Well, thanks again
for bringing Chico back.
Sure.
Uh, how's your sister doing?
What?
Mia.
I saw her come by earlier.
Yeah. I just wanted her to watch
the dog while I was out.
It doesn't seem like she did
a very good job.
Yeah. [Chuckles]
Well, that's Mia.
Anyway, I should go.
C...
Could I talk to her
for a second?
What?
I just...
I mean, I've never, uh...
I've never actually met her.
She went home.
No, she didn't.
Why do you say that?
Her car's still here.
She got a ride.
She wasn't feeling well.
Oh.
Hmm.
That's too bad.
Yeah.
Phew. Um...
Ah, for fuck's sake.
[Gunshot]
Diana, turn the lights on.
[Singsong voice] Mia.
Mia?!
[Cellphone vibrating][Gasps]
[Grunts]
[Vibrating continues]
[Cellphone chimes]
Not funny, Mia.
Man: Who says this is Mia?
Mm. You found
the voice-changer app.
It's a little steep,
for $5.99,
but, hey,
I think you'll like it.
Glad you think
this is funny.
This is stupid.
Your leg is broken.
You're not getting away. We'll see.
[Cellphone beeps]
[Cellphone chimes]
Hmm.
[Crying softly]
Hi, guys. My sister, Nicole,
just killed my friends
Jade, Lani, and Santi,
and I think she's going
to try to kill me next.
But, first, I think
I'll kill her dog.
[Chico whimpering]
[Crying continues]
Ugh!
Aaaah!
Aaaaah!
[Both grunting]
Aah! No!
[Grunting]
Ugh!
Aah!
[Both grunting]
♪♪
Ahh!
Yaaaaah!
[Both grunting]
♪♪
[Whimpers]
[Choking]
♪♪
[Gasps]
Aaah!
[Crying]
♪♪
[Groaning]
[Groaning continues]
[Crying]
[Breathing heavily]
♪♪
Chico!
Hi, buddy.
Hi. Come here.
Good boy.
[Breathing heavily]
♪♪
[Groaning]
[Crying]
[Vehicle approaches]
You Mia?
No.
[Breathing heavily]
[Grunts]
[Off With Their Heads'
"Theme Song" plays]
♪ Well, I don't give a fuck
about anything ♪
♪ When I think about the future,
all I see is it bringing me ♪
♪ Pain, misery, and poverty ♪
♪ Well, I've been trying
for 15 years ♪
♪ To smile and take shit,
but now it's so clear ♪
♪ That it's all downhill, yeah,
it's all downhill from here ♪
♪ Well, I wish I could turn back
the clock eight years ♪
♪ Think twice about the person
staring back at me ♪
♪ In the mirror ♪
[Instrumental break]
♪ Well, I don't give a fuck
about anything ♪
♪ When I think about the future,
all I see is it bringing me ♪
♪ Pain, misery, and poverty ♪
♪ Well, I've been trying
for 15 years ♪
♪ To smile and take shit,
but now it's so clear ♪
♪ That it's all downhill, yeah,
it's all downhill from here ♪
♪ Well, I wish I could turn back
the clock five years ♪
♪ Well, I never would have
thought that you'd be standing ♪
♪ Right here ♪
♪ Life's got the best of me ♪
♪ And I just want
to drop to my knees ♪
♪ Scream and punch the concrete
until my hands bleed ♪
♪ It's all a fucking joke
to me ♪
♪ I wake up and work
and get fucked up and sleep ♪
♪ And then wake up and work and
get fucked up all over again ♪
[Instrumental break]
[Guitar solo]
♪ Life's got the best of me ♪
♪ And I just want to drop
to my knees ♪
♪ Scream and punch the concrete
until my hands bleed ♪
♪ It's all a fucking joke
to me ♪
♪ I wake up and work
and get fucked up and sleep ♪
♪ And then wake up and work and
get fucked up all over again ♪
♪ Again ♪
♪ Agaaaaaaaaaaaain ♪
[Song ends]