(Eerie music)
(Gears winding)
♪
(Eerie music)
(Hannah)
Mom?
♪
Mom!
Mom, where are you?
Mom?
(Coughing)
Mom? Mom!
Where are you? Mom?
♪
Help me, please help me.
Help me.
Help! Please!
♪
I can... they can help you.
(Soft, tense music)
♪
Knock, knock.
You scared me.
(Keys jingle)
I got the place.
Really?
Mom, oh, congratulations!
(Melanie)
Thank you.
(Hannah)
Yes, finally.
- I am so excited.
- Yes, it's amazing.
- Can I see it?
- Yes!
♪
- Okay.
- Wow.
(Melanie)
So, imagine.
(Hannah)
It's awesome.
(Melanie)
All of the rooms out the back
are already divided up,
so I won't have to do
much renovating.
I'm just gonna set
a few things up,
fresh paint job.
Oh, and check out the best part.
(Laughs)
- Hm?
- Awesome.
(Melanie)
Yeah, the law offices left it,
but I think it will fit in
nicely here.
So I can stop by
and get a massage
whenever I want
from a cute Swedish guy?
Mm-hm, sure.
Whenever you want.
For only 89 bucks.
(Laughs)
This is perfect.
Have you decided on a logo yet?
(Melanie)
Actually, I was hoping
that you could design
the logo and the sign.
Seriously?
You're an amazing artist,
Hannah.
Thanks, mom.
It's about time
you had a big success.
- You deserve it.
- Yeah.
(Chatter)
(Hannah)
Excuse me, hey, uh,
where's hall 7c?
(Amber)
Anyway, the roster
already looks really good
and I'm not worried
about the JV team.
(Muttering)
- Oh.
- Oh!
- Sorry.
- Hi, no, are you okay?
(Hannah)
Yeah, I, um, do you know
where hall 7c is?
- Uh, Tanner.
- What?
- Check this out.
- Okay.
(Zoey)
It's the piano room, right?
Yeah.
Uh, just to the left.
Thank you.
(Zoey)
You're playing for Kurtz?
Oh, boy.
Good luck.
What does that mean?
(Zoey)
You'll see.
Okay.
Thank you.
(Playing piano)
♪
(Clapping)
(Sighs)
So your fond hope
is to go to Juilliard?
There's no way
I could afford Juilliard.
Actually, I'd have
to be good enough
to get on scholarship.
Do you have any idea
how much work
it would take to get you there?
Honestly, no.
But I'm willing to do
whatever it takes.
Okay, to start with,
you're gonna have to take
choir music theory.
And then begin your one-on-one
tutoring after school.
(Hannah)
Does that mean
you'll accept me
into the intensive program?
I've heard worse.
Thank you.
(Mr. Kurtz)
All right, go, sit down.
Next!
(Birdsong)
Hey, guys.
Hey, can I sit here?
(Emily)
Sorry, my friend's
gonna sit there.
Okay.
- Hey, guys.
- Uh, sorry,
that seat's taken.
- Sorry.
- Okay.
(Soft music)
♪
(Nervous laugh)
Hi.
(Garrett)
Why are you eating over here?
(Hannah)
I'm sorry, I'm new,
I don't really know anyone
and I couldn't find
anywhere to sit.
- But I'm finishing up...
- No, no, no, it's okay.
I wasn't trying
to give you a hard time.
You played beautifully,
by the way.
Earlier at the piano.
(Hannah)
Oh.
(Garrett)
I'm no musical expert,
but I thought
it sounded phenomenal.
(Hannah)
Thanks.
(Garrett)
It's Hannah, right?
I'm Garrett, Mr. Williams,
the guidance counselor.
(Hannah)
Oh, hey, it's nice to meet you.
(Garrett)
Hey, look, I know the first day
can be kind of tough
and some of the kids here
can be pretty intimidating,
but there's a place
for you here.
You'll figure it out.
And my door's always open
if you ever wanna talk.
(Hannah)
I appreciate that.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
(Clears throat)
Oh, Hannah, don't forget this.
And good luck
with Mr. Kurtz, huh?
(Hannah)
What?
(Chatter)
(Soft music)
♪
Anybody here?
Hello?
♪
(Playing piano)
(Zapping sound)
(Eerie music, zapping)
What... okay.
Hello?
♪
Anybody here?
Hello?
♪
(Screaming, zapping)
(Dramatic music)
(Tense music)
♪
(Melanie)
Green for the front
and turquoise for the back.
And I really want to try
and get the painters in
sooner rather than later.
We really don't want a lot of
paint fumes for the grand...
Okay, great work.
I'll talk to you later.
Bye.
(Phone beeps)
Huh.
Your day was that great, huh?
(Hannah)
It was whatever.
This school's got
a really good piano.
(Melanie)
Anything you want
to talk about?
(Hannah)
Sounds like opening a spa
is much more fun
than finishing high school.
(Laughs)
(Melanie)
Well, graduating high school
was step one.
Okay.
New plan.
(Hannah)
What?
(Melanie)
How 'bout some Mac and cheese?
(Hannah)
Right now?
(Melanie)
There's no time
like the present.
(Hannah)
Okay.
(Melanie)
So, what do you got so far?
(Hannah)
Mm.
All right, so, it should be, uh,
happy and relaxing.
(Melanie)
Mm-hm.
(Hannah)
But also clear and memorable.
- Mm-hm.
- I'm not sure
if you want, like,
a tropical theme.
(Melanie)
Oh, wow.
(Hannah)
Or like an undersea theme
or what.
But this is just some of the
stuff I've been working on.
(Melanie)
Oh, I love the lotus flower.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
I've been working on, like,
a lotus flower-sunset
combination.
This one's my favorite.
(Melanie)
Oh, Hannah, that is beautiful.
I love that.
What about the sign?
(Hannah)
I'm still working on it.
(Melanie)
Okay.
(Hannah)
Is it gonna light up?
(Melanie)
Hm.
Light up, flashing neon,
whatever you want.
Flashing neon.
(Melanie)
Oh, well, I want it
to be noticeable
from anywhere in the Plaza.
I have a feeling
that sign is going to be
one of our biggest money makers.
Oh, well, I am going to go
and settle up the bill.
(Hannah)
Wait, wait.
Definitely a moment
worth celebrating.
(Phone camera clicks)
(Phone vibrates)
(Typing)
(Phone alerts)
(Clears throat)
(Melanie)
Well, I have been hogging
all of the conversation.
(Hannah laughs)
I wanna hear all about
your first day.
Did you make any new friends
at school?
(Hannah)
Yeah, I think I met
some pretty cool people.
(Melanie)
Oh. Oh, I am so happy
to hear that.
(Energetic music)
♪
(Door opens)
(Stepfather)
One of my sisters try to wear
something like that
out of the house,
my father would have
called her a tramp.
- Get out of my room.
- What do you call yourself, huh?
You know,
we've talked about this
and you are way too young
to be spending the night out
with some boy, I forbid it.
(Amber)
You're not my real dad
and I don't care what you think.
(Stepfather)
Is it an older guy, huh?
Some creep pervin' on you?
Mind your own damn business.
You're grounded, Amber.
You're on lockdown
until I say otherwise.
And if this boy thinks
that he can spend the night
out with you, let's see how he
likes dealing with the cops.
(Bangs on door)
You know,
when your mother's at work,
I make the rules
around here, Amber.
(Window slides open)
If you wanna start being
treated like a grownup,
you need to start
acting like one.
(Bangs on door)
Amber.
(Rattles doorknob)
Amber, open up.
I mean it.
(Bangs on door)
(Crickets chirring)
(Dog barks)
(TV character)
Shane, dammit, Shane,
I keep finding you girls
and you keep losing them?
(TV character)
I thought she was the one.
I thought I could trust her.
(Eerie music)
Is that you, Amber?
♪
Might as well come in here.
You know you're gonna get
a talking to.
♪
(Dog barking)
Hey, shut up already.
♪
(Zapping)
(Duct tape ripping, tearing)
♪
(Zoey)
Glad to see you
survived the day.
(Hannah)
Yeah.
(Zoey)
Kurtz really tried
to grind us
into the floor
at choir practice.
I wonder if he got into teaching
just to be a sadist.
Kurtz isn't that bad.
What? He just acts tough
to whip us into shape I think.
(Laughs)
(Zoey sighs)
(Zoey)
I just wish I didn't have
to protect my voice.
I'm dying for a smoke,
you know what I mean?
(Hannah)
I don't really smoke.
(Zoey)
Oh.
So what do you like to do
to cut loose?
(Hannah)
Still trying to figure that out.
Actually, there's kind of a lot
of things I haven't done yet.
(Zoey)
Like what?
(Hannah)
Like, I don't know,
go to a real party
with like booze
and dancing and bonfires.
Or like make out with someone
who makes me desperately hungry.
Or drive a really fast car.
(Giggling)
I know it's stupid.
(Zoey)
Nah, it's not stupid.
I've done all that stuff
and I'm still restless.
- Yeah?
- Yeah. Oh yeah.
♪
(Hannah)
I keep feeling
like I'm coming out
of an awful dream.
We moved here
after my parents divorced.
(Zoey)
Mm.
(Hannah)
My mom's cool now,
but it was messy.
Actually, that's when I got
really good at piano.
(Zoey)
Yeah, I remember
my mom's first divorce.
Totally sucked.
(Hannah)
Right?
- Can mess you up.
- Oh yeah.
(Hannah)
I'm afraid of taking up
too much space,
but I'm also afraid of
disappearing from the world.
(Zoey)
You're not, you know?
- What?
- Taking up too much space.
And you're not
disappearing either.
Come on, everyone notices you.
- No.
- That's why Amber is so vicious.
She's jealous and scared
and you're way more fun
to pay attention to.
And she dies
without attention, so...
(Laughs)
(Energetic music)
(Phone alert)
♪
(Typing)
(Phone camera clicks)
♪
What? What?
(Phone camera clicks)
♪
Oh, come on, that isn't fair.
(Typing)
♪
(Phone camera clicking)
How do people do this?
♪
(Phone camera clicking)
All right, there has to be
a good one in there somewhere.
♪
(Phone camera clicks)
(Sighs)
♪
This is the best homework ever.
(Giggles)
(Playing piano)
♪
(Sigh)
(Mr. Kurtz)
Josh, measure 64, you were flat.
Everyone else,
thank you so much.
Have a good day,
see you tomorrow.
(Hannah)
So, I think I might try out
for the cheer squad.
(Zoey laughs)
(Zoey)
A rah-rah, sis boom bah!
(Zoey laughs)
Oh my god, you're serious?
(Hannah)
Yeah.
What's the big deal?
(Zoey)
You wanna be a cheerleader?
Kinda, yeah.
I mean, I don't know,
I wanna dance
and make more friends
and, I don't know,
do something different.
Brain-dead definitely counts
as different.
(Hannah)
Come on, the only reason
people like Amber
don't get along
with people like us
is because we don't
understand each other.
Oh, she's so misunderstood.
- Stop.
- Amber and her friends
are the girls
that grew up rooting for
the mean, rich,
popular girls in movies.
They're not misunderstood,
they're toxic.
(Hannah)
I'm just tired of being nothing
but the music nerd, okay?
You don't have to go
with me or anything.
Seriously?
Careful.
(Hannah)
Okay.
(Amber)
All right, you guys,
Jillian's gonna
show you some moves.
Try to incorporate them
into your tryouts.
And remember, smiles.
(Beep)
♪
(Melanie)
I didn't know you were
still interested in dance.
It's not only the dancing.
I wanna get out
of my comfort zone,
explore something new.
(Melanie)
Well, if it makes you happy,
then I think that's great.
Break a leg.
(Amber)
Six, seven, eight.
Come on, let me see smiles.
You're here to get the crowd
pumped, right?
All right.
Do you want to show 'em
one more time?
(Jillian)
Yeah, I'll show 'em again,
but you guys have to stretch.
(Amber)
Okay, last but not least,
we wanna see your moves.
Um, start behind the line,
and when the music stops,
land in front of the line
and give it a big finish, okay?
Um, let's see.
Emily.
Go ahead.
I... I can't do this.
(Amber)
No guts, no glory.
Who's next?
Uh, you, Anna.
(Hannah)
Uh, it's Hannah, actually.
(Amber)
Okay, Hannah actually.
Let's see what you've got.
And big finish!
(Laughter)
- Did you get it?
- Perfect, I got it all
- in super slow motion.
- Send it to me.
Oh, I'm sorry.
We actually don't have any spots
on the cheer squad right now.
We just needed a new fail video
for our social media.
All right.
(Giggling)
#cheerleaderfail.
#pigslop.
#sad.
(Jillian)
Oh.
(Soft music)
♪
(Eerie music)
(Tense music)
♪
(Keys jingling)
(Unlocks door)
(Dramatic music)
(Tense music)
(Locks door)
♪
(Door rattling)
(Lock clicking)
♪
(Melanie)
Hello, hello.
Hi, mom.
So, how were tryouts?
♪
Fine, I guess.
I'm not really sure
if I wanna be on the squad.
I think I should
just focus on piano.
(Melanie)
Hm, well, that is
the Hannah I know.
Oh, hey, could you please
help me unload those.
(Hannah)
Yeah.
(Playing piano)
♪
I... I know I can get it right.
I'm sorry.
(Mr. Kurtz)
Hey, that's... yeah,
that's enough practice
for today.
(Hannah)
No, I...
No, I... it doesn't really hurt.
We can keep going.
(Mr. Kurtz)
No, if we stop now, you'll be
fresh tomorrow. It's okay.
(Hannah)
I want to keep going.
I want to get it right.
(Soft, tense music)
(Mr. Kurtz)
Okay.
♪
(Hannah sighs)
(Playing piano)
♪
(Birdsong)
(Eerie music)
♪
(Garrett)
You waiting on somebody?
(Hannah)
I think someone's following me.
(Garrett)
Okay, well, here,
we can come and wait
in my office if you want.
You wanna call your mom,
maybe get you a ride?
(Hannah)
Okay, yeah.
♪
(Garrett)
Yes, ma'am.
She's right here.
Yeah, she's fine.
Your mother is on the way.
You wanna talk,
tell me about anything?
(Hannah)
I don't feel like talking.
It's just...
(Garrett)
It's what?
(Hannah)
I... I didn't even want
to be a cheerleader,
I just wanted to try
something different.
(Garrett)
You're talking about Amber,
the girls on the cheer squad.
Yeah, I mean, it's crazy
how much they hate me.
I mean, I don't hate them.
Why do they love torturing me?
I heard about their prank.
(Hannah)
And then what about Tanner?
I mean, is he really a nice guy
or is he just another trick?
I mean, everybody loved my dad,
but that didn't stop him
from dumping my mom
so he could run off to Florida.
And is it supposed to count
as good parenting
if he just writes you
a check every month?
And I know my mom,
she puts on a good front,
like, but it's like she thinks
she always has to be happy
in order to protect me
from reality.
And... and then now I think
I have a stalker.
And I have too much piano
practice to do and I...
I can't even take a breath.
Wow.
Sounds like you got
a lot on your plate.
(Sniffles)
- I'm sorry.
- For what?
Hannah, you have nothing
to apologize for.
(Sobs)
I know it sounds corny,
but it's okay
to feel your feelings.
(Hannah)
Are you just gonna tell me
everything's gonna be okay?
'Cause it's not.
Everything's messed up.
No, I'm not gonna do that.
I'm just gonna try to listen.
But I feel like you
probably hate the idea
of counseling anyway, don't you?
(Hannah)
Yeah.
Kind of.
I just feel like I need
to figure it out for myself,
you know?
Feels weird talking about it.
I mean, no offense.
(Garrett)
I get it.
None taken.
How 'bout this?
Instead of thinking of me
as Mr. Williams,
the guidance counselor,
what if you think of me
as a dad that wants
to hire you to tutor
his daughter in piano?
(Hannah)
Tutor, like...
Like a part-time job?
(Garrett)
Yeah, just twice a week.
Katie is eight years old,
she loves music,
and she is endlessly curious.
Plus, I know you'd make
a great teacher.
You pay attention,
you're compassionate.
(Hannah)
I don't know.
I mean, that sounds...
Come on, ask your mom.
I'd pay you something fair,
so it'd be good pocket money.
Plus, you know,
give you a chance
to take your mind
off things for a bit.
Yeah.
Maybe.
(Garrett)
I'm gonna give you
my personal cell, okay?
We can work out the details
of this whenever,
but I want you to feel free
to reach out.
Call me or text me
if any of this
starts to feel overwhelming.
(Soft music)
♪
(Hannah)
Thanks, Mr. Williams.
(Garrett)
Yeah.
(Birdsong)
(Zoey)
Hey, you got a sec?
(Hannah)
Not if you're just gonna say,
"I told you so."
(Zoey)
No, nothing like that.
I...
I wanted to say I'm sorry.
What happened
was really screwed up
and you deserve better.
Thanks.
It was pretty embarrassing.
(Zoey)
So do you think she was, like,
born evil or does she
have to work so hard
to make everyone so miserable?
- Born.
- Yeah.
(Eerie music)
(Hannah)
Hey, hey, watch out!
(Grunting)
(Loud clattering)
- Are you good?
- Yeah.
(Hannah)
Hey, are you okay?
(Panting)
(Amber)
You just saved my life.
♪
I gotta be honest,
I don't know why you did that.
(Hannah)
What... you think I did that?
I didn't make the unit
fall on you.
(Amber)
No, no, I mean, I don't know
why you pushed me
out of the way.
You saved me, and I've been
treating you like...
(Soft music)
♪
I bet nobody in the entire
school would blame you
if you just stood there
and watched me die.
(Hannah)
No one deserves that.
♪
(Amber)
Seriously, thanks.
♪
Everything's been, uh,
really messed up
since my stepdad,
he killed himself,
and I...
♪
I don't know, maybe I just heard
the wrong things about you.
♪
(Hannah)
Apology accepted.
Doesn't make much sense for us
to hate each other, you know?
(Amber)
I never hated you.
♪
It's not like that.
Sometimes winning what you want
means somebody else has to lose.
It's not fair,
but I'd rather win than lose.
(Hannah)
Amber, look at
what just happened.
I mean, we're better off
if we look out for each other.
♪
(Amber)
I wish you were right.
♪
But, hey, um, I'm having
a house party this weekend.
Bonfire on the lakeshore
and plenty of dancing,
no parents.
It's gonna be epic.
You should come.
♪
(Hannah)
Thanks.
But, nah, I don't know.
(Amber)
Tanner's gonna be there.
Relax, he's not into me.
He's too much
of a goody two-shoes.
Plus, I've got my own hot guy.
Um, Jillian,
text Hannah about the party.
See you Saturday night?
(Hannah)
Yeah.
Cool, thanks.
♪
Oh, where'd Zoey go?
(Amber)
Who's Zoey?
(Hannah)
Never mind.
(Amber)
Um, thanks again.
Yeah.
♪
(Melanie)
Hi there, uh, Mr. Williams?
(Garrett)
Oh, hey.
Please, just call me Garrett.
Nice to meet you.
- Oh, you too.
- Thanks for...
(Melanie)
Oh, uh, before I forget.
- Oh, this is your spa.
- Yes.
(Garrett)
This explains
why you look so young.
Oh.
Oh, you're too kind.
(Garrett)
Well, Hannah mentioned
you were hard at work on, uh,
starting up a new business.
Mm-hm, the grand opening
is next week.
You should stop by,
treat yourself to a massage.
(Garrett)
I'm sure my wife
is gonna love that.
Anyways, thanks for meeting me.
Oh, no problem.
So, Hannah mentioned
that you have asked her
to tutor your daughter, Katie.
For the record,
I think it's a great idea.
She could use
a healthy distraction.
I agree.
So, uh, you see her at school.
How is she doing?
How is she really doing?
She's studious.
And I know it can be hard
to fit in at a new school,
but she's making friends.
Oh, I am so glad to hear that.
(Garrett)
Still, though, I think things
have been really tough.
You know, all the teen drama,
plus the pressure
she puts on herself
to be perfect at piano.
Not to mention the divorce.
Yes, uh,
it hasn't been easy on her.
Who likes being discarded?
You know, I hired Hannah
to teach Katie the piano,
but, truth is,
it'll be an opportunity
for me to counsel her
and let her vent.
I think she'll feel
a little better.
Oh, uh, I think that could help.
You seem uncertain.
(Melanie)
No, no.
I think it's a good idea.
I'm just...
(Sighs)
(Soft music)
Hannah doesn't talk to me
like she used to.
She used to tell me everything.
You know, I think she just
needs space to grow.
When she first came
into my office,
she didn't need my advice
or problem solving.
She just wanted to talk
and let it out,
have somebody listen.
Well, I think we could all use
a little bit more of that.
(Garrett)
Yeah.
♪
(Hannah)
Bye, mom, love you.
(Melanie)
Love you too.
Okay, I'll see you
in a few hours.
(Hannah)
Okay.
Oh, Hannah?
Don't forget your raincoat.
It might rain later.
(Hannah)
Thank you.
(Melanie)
Bye.
(Birdsong)
(Hannah)
Your house is lovely.
(Eleanor)
Thank you.
You look so familiar.
(Hannah)
I don't think we've met.
(Eleanor)
No, I know,
it's just that you
remind me of younger days.
Are you... you're not
a cheerleader, are you?
(Hannah)
No, actually,
I tried out for the team,
but I didn't make it.
Oh.
I guess there is no point
in dreaming about the past.
I better go get my husband,
I can take that.
- Thanks.
- Yeah.
It was nice meeting you.
You too.
Hannah, I'm so glad
you could make it.
I've told Katie all about you.
We even watched some videos
of your recitals.
Oh, gosh.
(Katie)
Piano lady.
I'm happy to meet you.
(Hannah)
Nice to meet you, lovely Katie.
You can call me Hannah.
(Giggles)
(Garrett)
I'll leave you to it.
Okay.
So, what kind of music
do you like?
(Katie)
Um... I can already play
"chopsticks" and "twinkle,
twinkle, little star."
(Hannah)
Oh, you can?
That's pretty impressive.
(Katie)
No, it's not.
There are girls my age
who can play Beethoven
and Mozart and anything.
(Hannah)
But is that the kind
of music you like?
Mm-mm.
Hm.
You want to learn something
from frozen?
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
All right, let me teach you.
Here we are.
First we're going to learn
the chord of C major.
We're gonna look here
and we're gonna start
with one finger on C,
the thumb right here.
That's right, yes.
And the next on E.
(Playing piano)
Mm-hm, and then the pinkie's
gonna go on G.
♪
Now try it all together, ready?
(Hannah)
Isn't that pretty?
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
Wow, you're already a pro.
It's like you already know
what you're doing.
(Phone vibrates)
(Eerie music)
♪
(Man)
Hey, nice rack.
♪
(Phone alert)
(Zoey)
Of course it's the cheerleaders.
They're usually the worst,
but this is...
This is way too far.
I mean, hacking you?
Sharing your private pictures?
It's totally illegal.
I promise I'll help you
get revenge.
Bloody, painful,
delicious revenge.
(Stall door opens)
(Hannah)
No, I don't want revenge.
I just... I just want
my life back.
Gosh, my mom's gonna kill me.
Your mom's nuts if she gets
mad at you over this.
You're the victim, Hannah.
I don't wanna be the victim.
I just meant
it's not your fault.
The invasion of privacy sucks,
but it's over with.
What's the worst
that can happen now, right?
Tanner.
What?
Oh, gosh,
I gotta talk to Tanner.
(Chatter)
(Tanner)
Bro.
Hey, can I talk to you
for a second?
(Tanner)
Yeah, yeah, sure.
Please tell me
you deleted those pictures.
(Tanner)
Yeah, yeah, I deleted them.
I promise.
It was kind of weird
you sent them
in the first place.
You know, my parents
are always looking
through my phone for stuff.
No, I didn't send them,
I mean, never to anyone.
They were stored in my cloud,
my phone auto-saves everything.
I didn't realize...
I gotta get to class, so...
(Hannah)
Wait.
You're not gonna laugh at me
with all your locker room
buddies, are you?
No way.
Okay.
I'll see you at the party
this weekend.
Yeah, about the party.
(Sighs)
You probably shouldn't go.
I mean, those girls,
they can be vicious
to some girl who...
Some girl who what?
(Tanner)
Well, look,
I'm sure you're
a nice person and all,
you're just not the girl
I thought you were.
What the hell
is that supposed to mean?
(Tanner)
Look, I know it sounds
corny or whatever,
but I've been saving myself
for a good girl,
you know, a nice girl.
Somebody who shares my thoughts
and shares my values.
And now that everybody's seen
those pictures of you,
it's kind of ruined all that.
Oh, so now I'm cheap
and dirty to you?
- Look, I just want...
- No, get out! Go! Go.
(Tanner)
Geez.
(Somber music)
(Hannah)
God.
♪
(Melanie)
I am sorry that it's been
such a rough day.
Oh god, I can only imagine
what you were going through.
This is not your fault,
baby girl.
Everyone keeps saying that.
♪
I know what'll make you
feel better.
How 'bout some Mac and cheese?
♪
(Hannah)
No thanks.
♪
Hannah.
(Ringing)
♪
(Muffled voicemail)
(Sobs)
♪
(Weeping)
(Chatter)
♪
(Amber)
Looks like you get to be
the center of attention
for one more day.
(Hannah)
Just leave me alone.
(Amber)
Oh, you are definitely
gonna be alone.
You know what I think?
I think you leaked
your own photos
as some sort of pathetic attempt
to get people to notice you.
Oh, and in case
you want to go blaming me,
I was at cheer practice
this morning
with a dozen witnesses.
Alibis are important.
(Dark music)
Who did this?
(Bangs on locker)
(Melanie)
So, how was school today?
(Hannah)
Fine.
(Melanie)
Well, the new sign
looks great.
I love your design.
I think it helped bring in
our first few customers.
So do you want to hear
about the grand opening?
I've got to go do homework.
(Melancholy music)
♪
(Door opening and closing)
You had nine months!
Nine months,
and you said nothing,
so, no, you listen to me.
This is not
what I signed up for.
You have a husband and a kid.
Yeah, and I don't want
to mess with that, okay?
So, no, this is done
completely, it's over.
So no more texting,
no more showing up at my house,
no more calling me at wo...
♪
Hey, uh, I, um...
I'm really sorry,
but this is just...
It's not working,
so I wish you the best of luck,
and I just can't
get in the middle of it.
I got to go.
♪
(Clears throat)
Sorry about that.
♪
I just feel like ignoring
everything in the world
except this piano.
How about you?
That sounds perfect.
♪
(Bell jingling)
Hello!
Hi, Garrett.
It's nice to see you again.
Wow, it looks great in here.
- Thank you.
- Hannah said
you've been building up
the business from scratch.
(Melanie)
Yeah, well, it turns out
getting started
is the easy part.
The hard part
is drumming up business.
That's actually why I'm here.
Look, I know I should wait
and do a romantic getaway
with Eleanor,
but things have just been
so stressful lately.
Plus, I couldn't stop staring
at this coupon.
(Melanie)
Well, treat yourself, huh?
(Garrett)
Yeah.
What are you in the mood for?
Well, I've got a couple hours
before Eleanor's dinner
comes out of the oven,
so what do you recommend?
(Melanie)
Uh, a facial, manicure,
pedicure, massage?
Ooh, how about the works?
Great choice.
Oh, Jenny, could you get
Garrett started, please?
- Of course.
- Thank you.
- Hello, Jenny.
- Hello.
What are we getting done today?
- Everything.
(Knocking)
(Birds chirping)
(Suspenseful music)
♪
(Hannah)
Hello?
♪
Garrett?
Mrs. Williams?
Katie?
♪
(Beeping)
Anybody home?
♪
(Dark music)
Oh, no.
♪
No.
Oh! Oh, no!
♪
(Unintelligible)
(Beeping)
Yes, I... I need the police.
I need an ambulance.
Someone is hurt really bad.
I think they're dead.
No, no, no,
I don't... I don't think
it was an accident.
Yes, poplar Avenue,
please hurry.
♪
Oh, no.
Katie.
♪
(Unintelligible)
Katie, Katie, psst.
Psst, Katie cat.
(Katie)
Hey, Hannah?
Uh, Hannah?
Come on, we got to get you
out of here, okay?
What's going on?
(Hannah)
I need you to breath deep.
(Katie)
Why?
And I need you to close
your eyes real tight
and count to a hundred.
♪
Thirteen, fourteen, fifteen,
sixteen, seventeen,
keep your eyes shut, eighteen,
nineteen, twenty, twenty-one,
twenty-two, twenty-three,
uh-huh.
Thirty-seven, uh-huh,
39, 40, 41.
Oh, good job, 43, 44.
Uh-huh, good job, you're good.
Good job, you're good,
you're good.
- Inside the house.
- Okay.
- What's happening?
- It's okay.
- What's going on?
- Okay.
Come here, come here.
It's okay.
Hey, you're gonna be okay.
I've got a 1-8-7 on-site.
I repeat, I've got a 1-8-7
on-site.
I think it may be a robbery.
What's going on?
Hannah, what's going on here?
- Sir, I'm sorry.
- You're sorry for what?
- Sir.
- No, no,
I want to see my wife!
- Sir, hold on!
- Eleanor!
(Officer)
Sir, hold on.
- Sir.
- I've got to see her.
(Officer)
Hold on.
(Sobbing)
♪
(News anchor)
I'm here at the scene
of last night's
gruesome tragedy.
Police are now searching
for a murder suspect
in what appears to be
a robbery gone wrong.
Mr. Williams, I know
this must be heartbreaking.
What do you want us to know
about your wife?
(Garrett)
Eleanor was the light
of my life.
I never could've imagined
anything like this.
Please, I beg you,
we need justice for Eleanor.
(Sighing)
(Bell ringing)
(Zoey)
So are you just never
gonna talk to me again?
What happened?
I mean, I've been trying
to follow it all,
but everyone is so full
of lies and bs.
I don't want to talk
about it, okay?
(Zoey)
Fine, I guess if you don't care,
I don't care.
I didn't say I don't care.
I said I don't want
to talk about it.
Everything is too much.
(Zoey)
Friendship is supposed to work
both ways.
Zoey, I'm sorry.
(Zoey)
You know what?
Save it. Forget it.
I'm the stupid one.
(Somber music)
♪
Right here.
Right, now go like this.
("Fur Elise" by Beethoven)
♪
Okay, now you try.
Mm-hm.
♪
It's okay to be sad, you know?
Music is good for that.
Everything's changed.
I don't want to play anymore.
Okay. Give me a hug.
Go on, you don't have to play.
Before I forget...
The money I owe you
for tutoring.
Don't worry about it,
Mr. Garrett.
It's not important.
(Garrett)
No, it's extremely important.
You're the only stability
in Katie's life.
She needs that right now.
(Hannah)
I can only imagine
what she's been going through.
(Garrett)
She's a trooper.
She's actually been
my motivation to keep going.
But it's tough around here.
There's so much
Eleanor used to do.
Do you need help with the dishes
or, uh, making dinner
or anything?
You kn...
Actually, no.
You've been
such a big help already.
I feel bad asking you
for anything else.
(Hannah)
We've been through
a lot together.
You can ask me for anything.
(Somber music)
(Garrett)
I'll go crazy
if this house becomes a shrine
to Eleanor.
I need to pack up her things
sooner rather than later.
♪
I don't really want
to do it alone.
Do you think you could
swing by on Sunday,
help me sort through her stuff?
Of course.
You helped me through
some hopeless moments.
We can get through this
together.
♪
(Sighing)
Is that everything?
(Garrett)
Yeah.
Wow.
(Hannah)
Wait a second.
Is that...
Hey, Mr. Kurtz!
(Dramatic music)
(Garrett)
Was that Kurtz?
That guy gives me the creeps.
(Hannah)
Why would he be watching
the house?
(Garrett)
I don't know,
I'll call the detectives.
Keep an eye on Kurtz
for your sake.
(Hannah)
Thanks.
(Garrett)
Hannah, you have to be careful.
We don't know
who we can trust, okay?
(Soft music)
♪
(Beep)
(Garrett)
I don't know what I'd do
without you, Hannah.
(Hannah)
I'm glad we have each other.
You're like the one
really good thing in my life.
(Garrett)
Well, whatever happens
with all of this,
we've shared something together.
I really learned from your trust
and compassion.
(Hannah)
I just want to make you
happy again.
(Garrett)
Would you do me a favor?
(Hannah)
Anything.
(Garrett)
I bought this for Eleanor
ages ago,
and she barely wore it,
but I know that Ruby
is your birthstone,
and I just figured
it made more sense
to give it to you
than to lock it away
or sell it to some stranger.
(Hannah)
I don't... I don't know
what to say.
I mean, it's too much.
(Garrett)
No, come on,
just hold on to it.
You deserve a real thank you.
See how it looks.
(Hannah)
Wow, I've never had a piece
of jewelry like this before.
It's gorgeous.
♪
(Garrett)
I'm sorry.
That was definitely
inappropriate.
I apologize, I'm just...
I've been so raw and vulnerable
since Eleanor's death.
I haven't been myself.
You've been a real hero
for dealing with me.
(Hannah)
It's okay.
Actually, I can't think of
anyone else I'd rather kiss.
♪
(Garrett)
Hannah...
You're a sweet,
wonderful person.
Why don't you get some sleep?
We can talk about this later
after our minds have cleared.
I don't want to rush things.
(Hannah)
Okay.
♪
Don't be so tough on yourself.
Like you say, we all need
a little support
from time to time.
♪
- Hannah...
- Yeah?
(Garrett)
Please don't tell anybody
about this, okay?
Some things are better left
as secrets.
(Hannah)
Of course.
I like sharing secrets with you.
♪
Bye.
(Clanking)
(Indistinct chatter)
♪
(Zoey)
Not a ton, but I do know
how to make spaghetti,
which is probably pretty good.
(Laughs)
♪
(Melanie)
Oh, yes, this looks great.
Oh, Hannah,
I didn't hear you come in.
Look who dropped by.
- Hey.
(Melanie)
How was Katie?
(Hannah)
Good.
Sad, but good.
Poor kid.
Well, uh, dinner will be ready
in about ten minutes.
I already ate. I've got
a lot of homework to do,
so you guys go ahead without me.
(Melanie)
Is she doing okay?
That's a stupid question.
I just mean are things
getting any better at least?
I don't know, she hasn't said
anything to me.
(Melanie)
Could you do me a favor?
Could you keep an eye on her?
- Like, spy on her?
- No! No, no, no.
You don't have to betray
her confidence.
Just...
Look after her.
Double-check that she's okay.
- What's wrong?
- Nothing.
I'm glad
that she's spending time
with Katie and Garrett...
(Zoey)
But...
It's a lot of emotions
to handle.
Just help make sure
that she's not doing
anything unwise.
(Zoey)
Yeah, I'll do my best.
(Melanie)
Thank you, Zoey.
(Water trickling)
(Indistinct chatter)
(Student)
Afternoon.
(Laughing)
No tutoring today?
Yeah, I'm sorry.
I know it's short notice,
but I'm moving on.
I took a job teaching
at a school in new England.
It's effective immediately.
Wait, you're leaving town?
(Mr. Kurtz)
Mr. Franks is gonna take over
as your tutor.
Hey, you've made a lot
of great progress.
All right, so I know
you're gonna be great
at your audition for Juilliard,
so don't worry about it.
No, so that's it?
(Mr. Kurtz)
What do you want, hm?
You want roses? A gold watch?
A formal handwritten letter?
What do you want?
I want to know why
you were snooping on me
and Mr. Williams.
It doesn't matter, okay?
Believe me, Hannah.
(Somber music)
I was looking for an...
I was looking for answers,
but I don't have
any of the answers
that you want.
But you know something?
No, that is the point.
I don't know anything.
♪
Good luck at your audition.
(Dark music)
♪
(Ominous music)
(Sighing)
♪
- What's going on?
- Hannah.
- Sweetie...
- What?
- Zoey's been attacked.
(Melanie)
She's okay,
she's in the hospital.
She's in stable condition,
but it was pretty bad.
(Hannah)
That's terrible,
we should go visit her.
What?
(Melanie)
They had a warrant.
Hannah, would you like
to tell me where you got this?
(Hannah)
Uh, Garrett... Mr. Williams
gave it to me.
(Detective)
I see. Please have a seat.
(Dark music)
♪
The problem, Hannah,
is we spoke to Mr. Garrett
and he says that the necklace
went missing.
"Stolen" is the word he used.
(Hannah)
I don't understand.
It was a gift.
He gave it to me.
(Detective)
He says that you've been
clinging to him,
and ever since Eleanor's death
you've been acting bizarre
and obsessive.
(Hannah)
What?
He never said that.
He was worried
that you may have stolen
his wife's prized possession,
and sure enough, we find it
hidden in your closet.
(Hannah)
He gave it to me,
it was a gift.
No, I don't understand.
Why would... why would he lie
about that?
Oh my god.
Oh my god, what if he did it?
What if he murdered
his own wife?
(Tense music)
Hm, great performance, Hannah.
Right on cue.
Garrett was actually getting
a massage at your mother's spa
during the time of the murder,
so he couldn't
possibly have done it.
(Hannah)
But it wasn't me.
(Detective)
Your fingerprints
are on the murder weapon.
(Hannah)
Wait, no, we went over this.
I helped him cook dinner
one night.
I used the knife
to cut vegetables.
Ah, well, when we checked
your phone,
we noticed certain
text messages were missing,
but Garrett still had a record
of those messages.
What messages?
(Detective)
"I love you more
than anything ever.
You can't say 'no' to me.
If I can't have your love,
I'll kill myself."
(Hannah)
What?
(Detective)
That was right after the murder,
a couple days before
you sent this one.
"We're supposed to be together.
It's destiny.
Hannah and Garrett
is written in the stars.
I know you say I'm too young,
but I'll never let anybody
come between us."
No, this is insane,
I never wrote
any of those messages.
I promise, it wasn't me!
What about the pictures?
If you're not in love with him,
why send him these pictures?
♪
(Hannah)
I... I didn't send them to him.
I mean, they got sent
to everyone,
but it wasn't me.
My phone got hacked.
Hm. The pictures, the necklace,
the murder weapon,
your obsession
with the one man who showed you
real kindness.
(Hannah)
That's not how it was.
(Detective)
What type of person
goes through everything
in his house and throws away
his wife's clothing?
Frankly, I had a bad feeling
about you from the get-go,
but everyone seemed
to tell me the same thing,
"how could she have stabbed
someone to death
and been perfectly clean
a few minutes later?"
I... I didn't stab her.
♪
That's your raincoat,
confirmed by pictures
from your own social media.
Mr. Williams' neighbor
found it yesterday
shoved in the bottom
of his garbage
covered in Eleanor's blood.
(Melanie)
This is ridiculous.
Detective, my daughter has been
through far too much already.
I'm gonna have to ask you
to leave.
(Detective)
Hannah Baxter,
you're under arrest
for the murder
of Eleanor Williams
and the attempted murder
of Zoey Jones.
(Melanie)
No, this is ridiculous.
- Turn around, please.
- Do not touch her!
(Detective)
You have the right
to remain silent.
Anything you say or do
will be used against you
in a court of law.
(Hannah)
Mom, I didn't do this,
it wasn't me.
You know that, right?
(Melanie)
It's okay, I'm going
to get a lawyer.
(Hannah)
Please, no, I didn't do it,
though, it's not me.
I'm being set up!
Mom, please!
- Let her go.
- I promise, please!
(Melanie)
Get your hands off her!
This is not okay.
♪
(Tanner)
Hey, Amber, uh, check this out.
(Indistinct chatter)
Like...
(Amber)
I knew there was something
wrong with her.
What a freak.
(Tanner)
Yeah.
I'll see you around.
(Somber music)
♪
- Hannah.
- I didn't do it.
(Melanie)
I know.
Oh, honey, I know.
I don't believe you would
ever do something like this,
not for a single second.
I love you.
I am going to support you
through this.
The truth will come out.
Oh, come here.
♪
Oh my god.
I can't believe this.
♪
Well, I guess I will deal
with the police tomorrow.
(Bell jingling)
I don't even think there's
any security cameras nearby.
Who would do
something like this?
Who cares?
Everything we try to create
ends up broken anyways.
Every friend ends up
betraying us.
Nothing ever works out.
I'm not trying.
We are not going to give up.
We are not going
to stop fighting.
I am not going to let you quit
just because things seem unfair
right now.
(Hannah)
I'm going to prison, mom.
My life is already over.
(Melanie)
No, it's not.
We are going to focus
on proving the truth.
The police believe his story.
And you saw them,
they don't care
that I'm innocent.
(Melanie)
I know things seem difficult
right now,
but this whole story
about a love affair,
come on, it's... it's absurd!
You have the truth on your side.
- Mom, he did kiss me.
- What?
I mean, I kissed him, we kissed.
I thought I wanted to do more.
It seemed so right, I'm sorry.
♪
Men like him know how
to manipulate people.
This is not your fault.
(Hannah)
But that's the thing.
I wanted to be with him.
There's no way
they're gonna care
that I'm innocent.
(Melanie)
Yes, they will,
if we can find evidence
that he is the one
that killed her.
(Hannah)
How? You're his alibi, mom.
You said he was right here
at the time of the murder.
(Melanie)
Then he must have had
an accomplice or he...
(Sighing)
I don't know, he...
There has to be a loose end
somewhere.
♪
Mr. Kurtz.
(Melanie)
Your piano teacher?
What does he have to do
with any of this?
I don't know, but he might
know something.
I think he knew Eleanor.
He had her picture
like he loved her or something.
And on the same day
of the murder,
I overheard a phone call
with him,
and I think he was breaking
things off with someone.
What if...
What if he was having
an affair with her?
That's the kind of thing
that makes people kill, right?
♪
(Beep)
Hi.
Yeah, I'm watching him now.
♪
I don't know.
It definitely looks like
he's getting ready to leave.
♪
Okay, I'm gonna go in
for a closer look.
♪
Don't worry, I will be careful.
(Beep)
♪
Ah!
(Mr. Kurtz)
Hi.
Here you go.
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
♪
Um...
I, uh...
I saw Eleanor on and off
for about a year.
She called herself Ellie.
She never told me anything
about her personal life.
You know, part of me wondered
if there was someone else,
but she always had
the free time,
so I just didn't ask.
She was, um...
She was really lonely.
Really grateful.
How did you find out
that she was married?
She told me.
She said that she was living
with a monster,
said that she had to escape.
And I, I thought
she was exaggerating.
(Dark music)
It just sounded really messy,
you know, just too messy.
And I didn't sign up
to be involved
with a married mom,
so I just broke up with her.
♪
I told her to think
about her kid.
♪
Less than a week later,
she was dead.
♪
You have to go to the police.
No, I...
♪
I can't.
Don't you understand that?
Like, I... I don't have
any evidence
that Garrett actually did
anything wrong,
and if he did, if he actually...
♪
If he killed his own wife,
I don't think he would
hesitate to kill me,
or you, or Hannah.
(Melanie)
Please, if you think
there's a chance
that he did this,
go to the police.
Are you sure?
Are you sure that he did this?
What makes you so sure
that he killed her?
Because it is the only reason
that he would've lied to Hannah.
- He manipulated her.
- No.
(Melanie)
He planned all of this.
(Mr. Kurtz)
No, no. Hannah is actually
involved in this.
(Melanie)
No. She is not.
♪
- You're sure?
- Yes.
♪
Okay, um...
Garrett, he still has
that airtight alibi.
I mean, he was with you.
(Melanie)
I know.
I don't know.
Theoretically, it is possible
that he stopped by
to kill Eleanor
before he went to the spa.
I don't think
it would've taken long.
Doesn't really sound
like you're sure about anything.
♪
No, I, uh...
I can't be listening
to any of this.
I'm getting out of here.
I'm just gonna go
as far as I can.
I'm not supposed
to be involved in this,
I'm just not, I'm sorry.
(Melanie)
John, please, help me.
I just need information.
(Mr. Kurtz)
I don't have it.
I don't have anything.
All right, I barely know
Garrett from school.
Frankly, he seems
like a nice guy.
♪
I do know that she has a sister.
Emma.
She lives in the city,
in a loft.
It's downtown.
I think I have her number.
♪
(Emma)
He's a terrifying man.
♪
(Melanie)
Please, I need your help.
I need to prove
that he did this.
♪
Eleanor was my little sister.
She was 17 years old
when she started dating Garrett.
♪
He was 31.
- What?
- Yeah.
He was her guidance counselor
when she was
a varsity cheerleader.
She thought the other students
were bullying her,
but it was all him.
Gaslighting, mind games,
grooming.
He knew exactly how to play her.
Oh my god.
(Emma)
They officially started dating
when she was 18.
They got married and had Katie.
Everyone decided
it was all okay.
♪
He was controlling, abusive.
He enjoyed being cruel to her
and then being the nicest guy
in the world
to everyone else.
He would tie her up,
torment her, beat her.
Anything to break her
and control her.
♪
But he never broke her,
not really.
Not until he killed her.
♪
She was looking for a way out.
She was terrified
of what might happen to Katie.
♪
Here.
She wrote it all down.
♪
It's all there, take it.
Thank you.
I don't know what to say,
this is...
This is a huge help.
(Emma)
Melanie, no matter how much
you want to protect
your daughter, he won't stop.
He will kill you.
He will kill Hannah
just to protect his secrets.
You're in grave danger.
♪
(Melanie)
This is Hannah's only chance.
♪
Hi, Katie.
What are you doing here?
(Hannah)
I just came to say "hi"
and talk to you for a second.
Daddy says you took away mommy.
Hey, no.
You don't believe that, do you?
I would never.
Do you remember anything?
Anything that happened
the night before?
Daddy stayed up late with me.
We watched movies
until midnight.
That's why I had a nap
after school.
If I was awake, maybe
this wouldn't have happened.
Hey, no, don't think like that.
None of this
is your fault, okay?
I miss mommy, but I'm glad
daddy is happier now.
What do you mean?
(Katie)
He used to argue and cry
with mommy.
Now everything is quieter
and daddy smiles a lot more.
He says he'll marry
a beautiful cheerleader.
(Soft music)
Bye, Katie, I'll talk to you
later, okay?
- Okay.
- Okay, bye.
♪
(Dark music)
(Gasping)
♪
(Hannah)
That's why he did it.
He killed Eleanor
because he was replacing her
with Amber.
(Melanie)
It's the same pattern.
Replace her
with the young cheerleader.
But was she involved
in the murder?
(Hannah)
Amber?
I don't think so.
She's just a messed up kid.
I know what it's like
to be under his spell.
♪
Wait a second.
Amber thinks her stepdad
killed himself,
but what if Garrett
actually got rid of him?
Mom, I think he arranged
everything.
But he set me up
because he was getting rid
of every obstacle
between him and Amber.
(Melanie)
And Zoey must have been
too close
to discovering the truth.
♪
There is still the problem
with Eleanor's time of death.
(Hannah)
I was looking into that.
When I got to the house,
the heat was on full blast
which means the body
wasn't cooling down
at a normal rate,
which could throw
the time of death off
by a couple of hours,
I mean, easy, right?
♪
(Melanie)
He left the school,
makes a quick stop past
his house to kill Eleanor,
and then he stops at the spa.
With Katie asleep upstairs
the entire time.
So he stabs Eleanor wearing
gloves and your raincoat,
and then he throws the raincoat
into the neighbor's trash
knowing that the cops
are going to find it.
And during Katie's lessons
and after Eleanor's death
when I was helping him out,
he had plenty of chances
to steal my phone.
He could've easily faked
those messages.
This is the light at the end
of the tunnel, Hannah.
I think we have enough
to nail him.
And if this isn't enough
for the cops,
we will take it to the press
and we will make him famous.
(Ominous music)
Do you smell smoke?
♪
Mom?
(Coughing)
♪
Mom?
Mom!
Mom, where are you?
Mom? Mom!
Where are you?
♪
Where is she?
(Garrett)
Hannah, I wish
you could understand,
I just want a happy family.
And now I can start
all over again.
(Hannah)
Katie will never forgive you.
(Garrett)
No! Katie will
never forgive you!
Don't you see?
I wanted to pin this on Kurtz,
but you, you were so easy
to manipulate.
It was like you were
begging me to use you.
Every time I had
Amber bully you,
you just came
running into my arms.
Oh, I had so much fun
killing your mother.
Watching you, stalking you.
(Indistinct) Shame,
complete humiliation.
(Hannah)
Please, no.
(Garrett)
But you were so fucking curious!
(Hannah)
Please, no!
You know your mother
would still be alive,
but the two of you couldn't
stop asking questions.
(Hannah)
Please! Please! No!
Help! Please, help!
Let me out, please!
(Garrett)
Come on, Hannah.
You know how this has to end.
(Hannah)
No, please.
I can... they can help you.
(Garrett)
Come on, Hannah!
(Melanie)
Hey!
(Grunting)
♪
(Screaming)
Stand back.
(Screaming, shattering)
(Coughing)
♪
(Fire crackling)
(Siren wailing)
(Somber music)
♪
("Clair de lune"
by Claude Debussy)
♪
(Applause)
(Melancholy music)
♪
(Mr. Kurtz)
I've seen some strong
performances in my time,
but nothing that fine.
They couldn't have given
a scholarship
to a more deserving artist.
(Hannah)
Since when did you start
saying nice things?
(Mr. Kurtz)
Well, your mother has a knack
of making the world
a lot more bearable.
♪
(Hannah)
She is the best.
♪
(Mr. Kurtz)
Hannah, I've said
congratulations,
but I don't think I ever said
a proper thank you.
- For what?
- For fighting
when the rest of us were scared.
(Hannah)
I was scared too.
Scared, but brave.
You certainly saved Amber
from a life of misery
and, someday, she will
thank you for that.
I appreciate that.
But there's only one thing
I really want right now.
- What's that?
- Mom knows.
♪
Mac and cheese?
(Laughing)
I'll teach you the recipe.
I'll learn the recipe.
(Laughing)
♪