- Are you sure you don't wanna
come to Vienna for the holidays?
- You know it's going to be
my first Christmas with Roy.
- Yeah, so bring him here.
Vienna is beautiful and
romantic during Christmastime.
Besides, everybody's
getting all set up
for the holiday ball season.
Maybe you guys could go to one.
- You should go to one.
You're always the better dancer.
- Yeah, it's only 'cause
you stopped practicing
ballet in high school.
- Well, I still go
to cardio barre classes.
- Yeah, that is not
the same thing.
- How's the search for
your dad's family coming?
- No family yet.
- I still can't believe
my big brother's gonna be
alone on Christmas.
- Don't worry about me.
I just want to make
sure that you and Roy
have a romantic first Christmas.
- Ooh, I gotta go!
He's taking me to
this really fancy restaurant.
And he says he wants
to talk about our future,
something important.
- Hm, like a proposal?
- I don't know. I hope.
You'll be the first one I call.
Hey.
- Hey, babe.
- So sorry I'm late.
Thank you.
I got caught up
talking to Daniel.
Brought you some
homemade Christmas cookies.
- Thanks.
You look gorgeous, by the way.
So, I'm really excited to know
what you wanted to talk about.
- Remember when you said
you wanted to give me
the best gift you could?
- Yeah.
- Nothing, really nothing,
would make me happier for you
to make my Christmas
fantasy come true.
- Yes.
- So I want you to meet
someone special.
- Am I finally
gonna meet your mom?
- No, not really. Hey...
- Hi. You must be Amy.
So nice to meet you.
- Who...who is that?
Who is she?
- Uh, this is Elaine.
Elaine? Amy?
Have a seat.
- Who is she?
- I'm his girlfriend.
- Yes.
- You said she
was okay with this.
- She is okay with this, right?
- Okay, but what am I...
Why would I be okay with this?
- Amy, what are you doing?
Okay.
I'll only be a second.
Amy!
- I can't believe I thought
I was gonna marry him!
- Yeah, I'm sorry, Ames.
I know how much you liked him.
I see you got
my Christmas present.
- Oh, yeah.
Thanks.
It's pretty.
- And handmade.
- Tell me more about Vienna.
I need a distraction.
- Okay.
It's magical.
There's Christmas lights
on all the shops.
Everything smells
like gingerbread.
And everybody's
getting extra hyped
for all the extravagant
Balls happening.
- Oh, yeah, with
the big gowns and the dancing.
I can't believe that
they still do those.
- And everyone is extra
hyped right now
because the biggest Ball of
the season, the Christmas Ball,
is like it's right
around the corner.
- Sounds amazing.
- Hey, you should
come to Vienna.
- Oh, no, I can't.
- Why not?
Look, we're family.
We shouldn't both
be alone on Christmas.
- I can't. It's crazy.
I...
- Okay, look.
Let's make a deal.
Come out to Vienna and
stay with me through Christmas.
Try some new food!
See some new sights!
Maybe even go to a Ball.
I think getting outside
of your comfort zone
is exactly what
you need right now.
- I don't know.
- Vienna, it's so full of all
this magical old world charm.
- Does sound nice.
- Plus, it's
5,000 miles from Roy.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, as in
you're coming
'cause I'm not taking
"nein" for an answer!
- I'm coming to Vienna.
- You're coming to Vienna?
- I'm coming to Vienna!
- Wow!
I did not think that
was gonna work!
- I'm coming to Vienna.
I'm gonna come see you.
- Hey, and who knows?
You might even meet
a prince and get married.
- That's not funny.
- Hey.
- Hey!
Nice to see you too!
- Sorry. Didn't get
any sleep on the plane.
- Hi.
- How's it all going,
by the way?
- It's good.
Taking me forever to track
down my dad's family,
but I think I found my uncle.
- Daniel, that's great!
- Yeah.
I'm just... I'm hoping
he can tell me
a little bit more about
my biological father.
He died when I was so young
that I'm trying to
get a better sense of
where I come from, you know.
- You will.
I know it.
And when you do,
maybe Mom, Dad and I
will finally know
why you're so weird.
- Hm. And then you'll also
maybe know why
I don't invite you to the palace
when I discover I'm royalty.
- Oh, you're so funny.
- Let's go drop your bags
and go see the town.
- Sound of Vienna concerts.
- Welcome to Vienna's best café.
- Thank you.
- I'm so sorry.
I've got to take this.
It could be about my uncle.
- Okay.
- Hello? This is Daniel.
- May I be of some assistance?
- Um...you know, we'll just have
a couple of large cappuccinos.
- Two Café Mélange.
Right away.
- Great.
So that was my researcher.
Ames, I'm a nephew.
I've got an uncle.
He's here.
His name is Markus.
They could call me at any time.
- Oh my God.
- I can meet him...I...
- That's amazing!
- You sure?
- Hey, the coffee was amazing,
but you know I don't
eat anything with eggs.
- So much for trying new things.
- I am working
my way up to that.
- Sure.
- Hey, who's that?
Think they're hosting a Ball?
- Probably.
Sorry.
Hello?
Okay, sure. Right now?
I'll see you soon. Great.
That was my researcher.
My Uncle Markus,
he wants to meet me.
- Right now?
- Yeah.
- That's incredible!
- I'm sorry I can't
sightsee with you.
Are you gonna be
okay on your own?
- Sure, yeah.
I've been here about a day
and practically an expert now.
- Okay. You know, go check
out the Danube Tower.
It's great.
It's beautiful.
The view is incredible,
especially this time of year.
- Okay, I will.
- Okay. You're not
gonna regret it.
- Okay.
- Thank you!
I love you!
- Love you!
- Bye!
- Okay.
- Ich bien...
...lost.
- I'm afraid you screwed
that one up, Lukas.
- Tommy, I'll take
the class by myself.
- Waltzing alone?
And I think you can clap
with one hand too, right?
You know, this is for
the Midnight competition.
And I'm afraid there's no sense
in continuing this class
without a partner.
- How am I going
to find a dancing partner
on such short notice?
- You have this little playbook.
Find someone.
- My apologies.
I'm just gonna ask one
of these gentlemen over here,
if you don't mind.
Hi.
Hopefully, you can
understand me.
I was just
curious if you guys
are practicing for a Ball and
if there are any tickets left.
I keep hearing
amazing things about it
and I'd really like
to go to one.
You can't understand
anything I'm saying.
- No...yes... I can.
We are practicing for the Ball,
the Christmas Eve Ball.
- That's the fancy one
that sells out tickets
a year and a half in advance?
- Yeah. Actually, it's more
like two years in advance,
but, yes, that one.
- Can you help me get tickets?
- No, not directly, but I do
have a proposition for you.
- I don't know what you've
heard about American girls...
- Do you have any
ballroom dance experience?
- No.
I mean, I did ballet
in high school.
We almost went
to Nationals junior year.
- I'm Lukas Hofbauer.
- Amy.
Listen, I know this is going
to sound completely strange,
but I'm looking
for a dancing partner.
And I must attend this class
to qualify for the competition
of the Midnight Show
for the Christmas Eve Ball.
It showcases the best dancers
in Vienna.
- Mm-hmm.
And you want me?
- Yes.
Yes, but once
you commit, that's it.
I mean, you would have to
be my dance partner
and commit your time
and energy to waltz.
If we get through
the competition,
we'll be able to attend
the Christmas Eve Ball.
And if you take the class,
I'll be your personal
tour guide in Vienna
to whatever you want to see
for the rest of
this beautiful holiday season?
- Well, I did...
- I know...
- Promise myself
I would try new things
and I do really want
to see the Ball.
Okay, yeah, I'll be
your dance partner!
- All right!
Wunderbar!
- Yeah. Wunderbar!
- Welcome to Christmas
in Vienna.
- Everybody? We have a
new dancer with us today.
Please welcome...
what was your name?
- Amy, Amy Michaels.
Hi.
- Hi.
- This was kind of a
spontaneous decision.
I flew in from Chicago
after catching my boyfriend
with another woman.
But...but I'm moving on
and I'm trying new things.
So I think it's working
'cause two days ago
I really didn't expect to
be dancing
ballroom in Vienna, right?
So, cest la vie...
Oh, that's French, not German,
but I ramble when I'm nervous.
- Okay, everyone,
come on, get up.
Break is over.
- Two bodies...
- One mind...
- Four feet.
- They don't mess around,
do they?
- No, they take the waltz
very seriously here.
Here we go.
Don't look at me.
- I... I feel like
I'm in over my head,
like you should find
somebody who actually
knows what they're doing.
- No, no, no.
A deal is a deal.
You can do this, okay?
- Guys, always maintain contact!
- Oh.
- All right?
And, remember, the judges will
be looking for the perfect form.
We try this with music.
Start with the basic
right turn
just to get a little bit
of a warmup, okay?
On my count.
- Go.
- Oh!
- I'm so sorry.
Are you okay?
- I'm fine.
- Everyone back to one!
Once again.
You live in Chicago, hm?
Take your head to the left.
Good.
Shoulders down and elbows up.
Nice.
Now keep your posture.
- Posture was never
really my forte as a ballerina.
- Go.
- Don't look at me.
- I wasn't.
God, get over yourself.
- No. It's just that if you
look at me, you'll get dizzy.
- Oh!
- I am so sorry.
- You really got to watch
your feet a little bit more.
I mean, take
this seriously, okay?
It's not that hard.
One, two, three,
two, two, three.
- Okay, I wanted to
try new things.
But I didn't come to Vienna
to be ordered around, okay?
I'm gonna find
my own way to the Ball.
You , uh...
Good luck in your competition.
- Well, nice meeting you!
And thanks for
confirming everything
I already knew about
stubborn Americans!
- Well, thank you for
confirming everything
I already knew about
snobby Europeans!
- What?
- Wait, the Lukas Hofbauer?
You've been here
less than 24 hours.
You already head-butt
the Prince Harry of Vienna.
Gonna see him again?
- He was kind of a jerk.
- Uh...
- I'm so done with jerks.
- Right.
That's fair, but
counter-argument.
I hear he's a heck of a dancer
and he might be your best way of
getting into the Christmas Ball.
Come on!
You said that you'd get
outside your comfort zone.
- Okay. Yeah, maybe I'll try
to find him and apologize.
Or something.
- Oh, wow!
That's gonna be painful.
- Get outside my comfort zone.
- Yeah, that's the spirit.
- Hi. I'm looking
for Lukas Hofbauer?
I took a dance
class with him today.
I wasn't very good.
I bought him a
Gugelhupf to apologize.
- Who is it?
- Lukas, it's Amy.
I brought you a Bundt cake!
- I got it from here.
Thank you.
- Amy?
How did you even find me?
- Have you ever Googled
Lukas Hofbauer's address?
- No.
- Good. Don't.
- Well, guess you know
who I am now.
- Yeah. Kind of.
I actually just
came to apologize.
Dancing seems really
important to you and I...
- That's so sweet of you.
I feel like I need
to apologize to you as well.
Thanks for the cake.
That's very kind.
Why don't you come inside?
It's freezing out here..
- Sure.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
I also tried to find
you some edelweiss.
I know how you
Austrians love it.
They have a whole song about it.
Unfortunately,
it's out of season.
- It's also written
by Americans, I think.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- Huh.
Well, speaking of,
where's the rest of
the Von Trapp family
and the Christmas decorations?
- Yeah, well, I haven't
been able to bring myself
to decorate in
the last couple of years.
- Really?
It's the best part.
I mean, your
place is so beautiful,
it makes up for it.
It looks like it has
so much history.
This chandelier is beautiful.
- My great-great-grandfather
actually made that one.
- He made it?
I'm so sorry!
I'm such a klutz!
- It's okay.
- I get you a gift
and I ruin it.
- You know, I just
realized I haven't lived up
to my end of the bargain.
I would love
to take you to town.
If that's okay with you?
- Yeah, of course,
- Okay.
- Wow, you Viennese really do
take Christmas seriously.
It's my kind of town.
- For me, Vienna is the most
beautiful city in the world.
And this is when it comes alive.
You know everybody's preparing
for the Holiday Ball season.
It's like a
Viennese requirement.
- You really do love it
here, don't you?
- I've traveled the world,
but for some reason
I always come back home.
35 years ago my parents
won the midnight show
and were crowned King and Queen
at the Christmas eve ball.
Shortly after, they got married
and they had me.
- So dancing really is
in your blood.
- Yeah.
- Of course, they always wanted
to see me win as well.
But they're gone now.
- Oh Lucas, I'm sorry.
- No, it's okay.
It's been a few years.
But now I feel like I have
to win it for them.
Listen, I just
want you to know
I was going to
compete with my ex.
We were pretty much
going to win this thing
until she decided
to find a new partner.
- That's why you need me.
- Exactly.
She said she didn't think
that she could win
with me as a partner.
So she found a new one,
in and out of the ballroom.
Some French guy, Philippe.
- That's awful.
I can relate.
My ex cheated on me too.
- You know what they say.
Misery loves company.
- I've had worse company.
- It's beautiful, huh?
Uh-huh.
Very nice.
- I haven't done that
in so many years.
- It's because Vienna
suits you, that's why.
- You think?
- Yeah.
You know, now all we
need to do is get you
to waltz the way you ballet.
- Yeah, you see, it's a
little bit different, though,
Because when I was a ballerina,
I was actually
more of a soloist.
So all I really had to do was
trust myself and my body.
But the waltz,
I gotta trust you.
- Oh, no.
See?
You can trust me.
- I'm hungry.
Are you hungry?
I know a really
great place around here.
- You do?
- Yeah, I do.
- You do.
Okay, well then, try to find it.
- Yes, um, I think
it's this way.
It's awful people can't
just leave you alone.
- It's a little odd
having all of Austria
cares about who you're dating.
- Well, if it makes
you feel any better,
I didn't know who you were
until 12 hours ago.
- Don't feel bad.
If it makes you feel any better,
I didn't know who you were
12 hours ago either.
- Two cups of the
best Heyse Schokolade.
- Danka Schoen.
- Thank you.
- You know,
other Viennese may argue,
but personally I think
there is nothing better
during the holidays
than a hot chocolate.
- The secret is the egg yolk.
That's what gives
the rich texture.
- I don't usually do eggs...
but here's to
trying new things.
- All right.
To new things.
- Mm.
- Mmm. Mmm.
I think I'm okay with eggs now.
This might be the best thing
I've ever tasted.
- Thank you.
I'll leave you to enjoy.
- I need to thank
you for tonight.
Nobody's really
ever done anything
that nice for me before.
- That's sweet.
I do enjoy making
you smile, Amy.
- You do?
- Very much so.
- Sorry to interrupt,
but that young lady wanted
me to hand you this.
- Well, uh...
This is awkward.
- You know, I don't know
what I'm doing.
I really...
I can't get strung along again.
- Amy...
- I don't know.
It seems like you have
a lot of girls around.
This hang out...whatever
it is is over, okay?
- Amy, please, just...
- And I can pay
my own bill, okay?
- Just wait, please?
- I got to go.
- Hey, Amy!
- Finished, sir?
- Thank you, Dominik.
- You got in late last night.
- Yes. Amy and I
went to Café Sluka
after we went
to the Christmas market.
- You really seem to like her.
- Yes, I do,
but I think I mucked it up.
- Does she have any
potential as a dance partner?
- She does have talent and that
American stubborn determination.
- Americans can be
quite annoying,
but very determined, too.
Maybe that's what you need.
You may not win this year,
but the connection you two share
could help you win for years.
You need to tell her that.
- Hm. And here I was thinking
you didn't even like her.
- It's nice to see
you smiling again.
With Lydia, you would
just go from
sulking about the mansion
to dancing to sulking again.
I don't want
that old Lukas back. Do you?
- She did leave
her wallet last night,
so I will have
to see her eventually.
- Maybe that was on purpose
so she could see you again.
- Maybe we should
try to find her.
- Hey, I think we
should go to Christmas mart
and get some Gluühwein.
- What's glue-wine?
- Gluühwein.
It's hot spiced wine.
- Yes. That's what I want.
- Oh, you're thinking about
Lukas, aren't you?
- No.
Yes!
- Come on, I thought you said
that you walked out on him.
- Well, I did.
I don't know what I'm doing.
The whole thing was a bad idea!
- Bad idea?
I mean, aren't you ever
gonna see him again?
- I really want
to see him again,
but he deserves to
have a partner
with some modicum
of waltz ability.
- Oh, will you stop
selling yourself so short?
Jeez!
Look, the deal we made
when you came here
is that you're gonna have some
fun and try some new things.
And not try and win at every
new thing that you do try!
I mean, think of everything that
you've done since you got here.
You learned to waltz,
you head-butt a rich guy,
and you tried stuff
with eggs in it.
That's huge!
- Okay, yeah, I know.
- Shall we get some Gluühwein?
A little liquid courage?
- Yes, let's do it.
- Ah!
Ja. Guten morgen, Uncle Markus.
Yeah, yeah.
That was Uncle Markus.
He's in town.
He wants to see if
we want to grab some lunch.
- You go see him
and have some bonding time.
I'm gonna go explore, okay?
- Okay.
- Let's go.
- Thank you.
- Oops!
- I'm so sorry!
- So sorry.
I'm such a klutz.
- Whoa, are you American?
- Yeah.
- Where are you from?
- Chicago.
- Really? Me too.
Hal Stenson.
- Amy Michaels.
- Nice to meet you.
- What brings you here?
- Oh, vacation...
getting away from...
I am spending
Christmas with my brother.
You don't happen to know
about these places
that have Glu or glow wine...
- Gluühwein, yes.
- Yes.
- They're amazing.
There's a place up here.
Wanna grab it?
- Yeah.
- Let's go grab some.
- So you're the
Chief Nursing Officer
for the Lakeshore
Pediatric Hospital?
- That's why I'm here.
It's the latest in medical tech,
huge conference.
- What made you decide
to become a nurse?
- When I was 10,
I got appendicitis
just before Christmas and
I was admitted to Lakeshore.
- You had to spend
Christmas in the hospital?
- Yeah, but it wasn't so bad.
The nurses... Oh, my goodness,
the nurses were amazing.
They decorated my room
and even gave me a stocking
with my name on it.
I knew one day I wanted
to return the favor.
- That's really nice, Hal.
- Amy...
You know, you really
have beautiful eyes.
- That's really sweet.
And I don't want to seem
presumptuous in any way,
but I don't really know
what I'm looking for right now.
- No, no.
- But I'm so happy that I got to
share some glow wine with you.
- Gluühwein, Gluühwein, yeah.
- Say no more.
I've got to get going.
- Okay.
- I actually promised some
people at the conference
I'd meet up with them.
Let me grab the check.
- No, no, no, no, I got it.
It's on me.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah.
You helped me find
the place, so...
- It's great meeting you, Amy.
Merry Christmas to you.
- Merry Christmas.
Bye.
I have to pay.
I can't find my wallet.
- Oh...
- I must have lost it.
I'm so sorry.
I promise I'll come back
and I'll pay you.
I promise.
- Okay.
I found it.
Hey, Lukas.
- Hey, Amy.
You, uh, left your
wallet yesterday.
You weren't trying
to trick your way
into seeing me again, were you?
- No.
But I do want to apologize
for how I behaved.
Thank you.
And I have to say I...
I know
I'm not the best dancer.
I really want you
to be able to win this.
- I feel like I
need to apologize
'cause it was
a misunderstanding.
I want you to be my partner.
I just feel like winning
will come in time.
- Okay.
You been waiting long?
- Amy, Lukas is on his fourth
hot chocolate waiting for you.
Can I get you one as well?
- Yes, please.
So what do we have
to do to get up to speed
with the competition
in two days?
- Practice, practice, practice.
- The waltz is simple.
All you have to do
is keep your center steady.
Don't forget to take
big sweeping steps.
Your turn.
- Oh, okay.
- Mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
Hey, Daniel.
Is everything okay?
Okay. Yeah.
Yeah, I'll be right there.
I gotta go.
- Everything okay?
- Yeah, yeah.
It's nothing serious.
I just... I have to go now.
So I'll see you tomorrow?
- Yeah.
Bye.
Thank you for returning
my wallet.
Hey, what's going on?
What's wrong with Uncle Markus?
- Wrong? No, nothing.
He's fine except I invited
him over for dinner.
- You said this
was an emergency.
- Yeah, it is.
Look, I have no idea how to cook
a traditional Austrian feast.
He's from one of the oldest
families in Vienna.
He's gonna disown me.
- Daniel, you're being silly.
- Am I? Am I?
I think I should go back
to Chicago...like now.
- Okay. Uncle Markus is
the reason that you're here.
- Right.
- He doesn't care about
what you cook for him.
He just wants to
spend time with you.
- Yeah.
- I've got Mom's Christmas
ham recipe, we'll make that.
Be nice to make it for somebody
who actually appreciates it.
- Ham?
Okay.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- Okay. We can do that.
That'd be great.
- Okay, can you
handle buying me a ham?
- Mm-hmm, yeah.
Totally.
- Can you handle that?
- Yeah, yeah.
- Awesome.
- The one with feathers, right?
- Go!
- This looks delicious.
- Who knew Amy could cook?
- Oh, that's funny.
Good thing I have my
brother's support at all times.
- Speaking of brothers, I want
to show you something, Daniel.
Daniel? Amy?
Meet your family.
Our family settled in Vienna
in the early 1800s.
This is your
cousin, Uli
and your great aunt,
Aunt Mavis, on the family farm.
- Wow, a cousin and an aunt.
- They took such great
pride in it.
It was one of my favorite places
to visit growing up.
It's why I moved there
after I retired from city life.
- It's beautiful.
- Oh, who's that?
- That's me and my wife, Greta.
This was taken
at the Christmas Eve Ball
years ago at the Kursalon.
Where we all danced
the famous...
This was such fun.
One of my fondest memories.
- Look at that dress.
That gown is amazing.
They don't make
them like that anymore.
She wears it well.
She's beautiful.
- Yes.
Yes, she was.
- Oh, I'm sorry.
- Oh, it's ok. We had
a very happy life together.
What a dancer!
- You know, Amy's
actually taken up ballroom.
- Well, I'm trying to
get in to the Midnight Show
so that I can go to
the Christmas Eve Ball.
- Christmas Eve Ball?
That's the biggest one in town!
- All right, guys.
You know I don't expect
anything less than perfection
from you tomorrow
at the competition.
No pain, no gain.
Let's get to work.
And always think while you're
dancing of this beautiful room.
You have to feel it, okay?
From the beginning,
starting position, please.
- Scary.
- This one is the must.
Like he said,
try to feel the room.
- I will.
- Good.
- I'm glad to see that you two
are more in the steps today.
Good job, good job, very good.
All right.
Okay, thank you!
- All right, how do you feel?
- Thanks, everybody.
Remember, the one who place
in the top four
get to dance at
the midnight show.
for a chance to get crowned
King and Queen
of this year's
Christmas Eve ball.
Thank you very much.
See you tomorrow.
- This could just be
our year, Vicky.
- Yes, especially
if Lukas dances with her.
- Don't listen to them.
Your dancing has
gotten much better.
- Yeah? Better enough
to get into the Ball?
- Well, your movement
and technique are there,
but it's a little sloppy.
- Sloppy?
That's blunt.
- Blunt is the Austrian in me.
I apologize for saying it,
but it's true.
Hey, I mean it in a funny way.
- Ha-ha. Funny.
- You know what they say about
Austrian humor.
- No. What?
- It's no laughing matter.
- What can I do?
I want my waltzing
to get better.
I want to do this right.
- Okay, listen.
The waltz is about emotion
and precision coming together,
and about practice,
practice, practice.
- Lukas? Are we going?
- Hey, Tommy.
Sorry. Is there any way we
can stay a little longer today?
- Sure.
I'll give you the keys,
but keep it between us
and lock up after.
- Thanks.
- And remember...
You break it, you buy it.
But's that not
a problem, right?
And, Amy, this was
much better today.
Good job.
See you tomorrow guys.
- Coming from the mean guy.
- Yes.
- Come on.
Stretch out a little bit.
And then we'll do it
without shoes this time, okay?
- Okay.
- Okay, so the Vienne Waltz
is one of the oldest forms
of ballroom dancing
in the world.
Steps are pretty easy, but
the details are complicated.
I'll lead.
When I go forward, you go back.
When I go right, you go left.
But we're going
to spend a little more time
on posture and feeling it.
So here we go.
Elbows up, shoulders down,
beautiful.
I'm gonna count.
Three, two, one, go.
That's it.
Nice, nice.
Nice.
- Oh, sorry.
- It's okay.
No worries.
Let's take it again.
- Okay.
- Everything up.
Perfect.
Feel it.
Feel the music.
Here you go.
One, two, three.
Nice.
That's it.
Right here.
There you go.
- Yeah.
- Oh, gosh. Amazing.
- The dip.
- Ooh, hi.
- Okay, we did
enough for today.
It was amazing.
- Do you think we got a
chance of winning or, you know,
at least getting fourth and
getting in the Midnight Show?
- We'll just keep practicing.
- Okay.
- I also would like
to ask you to dinner tonight
as a thank-you.
I just need to make
one quick call.
- What does the great Lukas
Hofbauer have planned now?
- Surprise.
- So, enjoy Vienna so far?
- It's more beautiful every day.
- Well, let me show you
my favorite view.
And it's not from
the Danube Tower.
- These are amazing.
- Not as amazing as you are.
- That was a little corny.
- Well, I'm a corny kind of guy.
What can I say?
I'm sure you've been
on one of those, right?
- Of course, yeah.
I try to go on the one
in Chicago
at least once every summer.
- But not during Christmas.
- No.
- See? I think
we should change that.
- All right.
- Huh?
- It's cool.
- I told you I wanted
to thank you.
- This is...
This is too much!
I mean, don't get me wrong.
It's beautiful.
Thank you, but it's too much.
- No, it isn't, not for you.
Come on, we worked
so hard all day.
Let's just enjoy the night
and enjoy the view.
Let me get you out
of your jacket. Come on.
- I bet you it's even more
beautiful in the summer.
- Oh, it sure is.
You know, the kids out there
picnicking on the shore,
boats in the water.
It's great.
You should really see it.
- I'm only here
for another week.
My real life is in Chicago.
- So this isn't real life now?
- I have had the best
time with you, Lukas.
And this has been incredible.
But I can't pretend
that this is what
my life's gonna be from now on.
- Okay.
Well, then let's just enjoy
your time here in Vienna.
You know what? Here.
Let's drink to that.
To Christmas in Vienna.
- Christmas in Vienna.
- Sorry I have to do that,
but I need one last dance.
- Oh, I thought
we were done practicing.
- Well, if we can dance in
a swinging Ferris Wheel car,
we'll be so much better
tomorrow on solid ground.
- All right.
Thank you so much for tonight,
for dinner and the dancing.
I'm never, ever going
to forget it.
It's so beautiful.
I'm bummed.
I'm not gonna be
able to decorate
for Christmas this year,
you know.
- Okay. You know what?
You've brought so much
Christmas spirit into my life.
Why don't
we just decorate my house?
It's gonna be fun.
Let me get your jacket.
- Oh, thank you.
- Here we go.
- Hello, sir.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I didn't realize
you had company.
- Oh, no. Hey, Dominik.
We need your help.
Get all the Christmas
decorations
out of the cellar, please.
- Christmas decorations?
- Yes! We're gonna decorate!
- Let's do this.
- Go!
He's all excited!
- Okay!
So, what do you think?
- I love it.
You know, this is
the first time
I decorated this house
without my parents.
- You okay?
- Yes. I'm super happy.
I'm glad you brought
some holiday spirit
back into this lonely house.
Thank you.
- Of course.
You're forgetting one
important thing, though.
- What?
- Christmas tree.
- Oh.
We'll save
that for tomorrow.
- Hey.
Where you been all day?
I thought you just had
your dance lesson.
- I did.
The day got away from us.
Do you know how to get to
the woods outside of Vienna?
- I don't, but I could
ask Uncle Markus. Why?
- Lukas doesn't
have a Christmas tree.
Thought I'd surprise him
with a real one.
What?
- You really like him.
Yeah, you do!
You like him!
- Nothing is going on, okay?
Stop!
I leave for Chicago in
a few days.
I just want to do
something nice for the guy.
- Sure.
- Now if you'll excuse me,
I have to go and iron
the only formal dress
that I brought
so that I can go to
the competition tomorrow.
- Hm.
- Mind your own business.
- Goodnight.
Wow, they all look
so professional.
- Don't worry about them.
You see the lady in the middle?
The other two are
sticklers for precision,
but she, she judges
on chemistry,
emotion and
overall performance.
- So you're saying
we actually do have a shot
at the Midnight Show and
the Christmas Eve Ball?
- I sure hope so,
or my parents
will come back from
their grave to haunt me.
- Well, looks like
we're about to be haunted
by a ghost of Christmas
past right now.
- Good luck.
You will need it.
Nice dress.
- Excuse me...
- Why don't you just
go sign us in?
I'll be with you
in a second, okay?
- Okay.
- Chicago, I hardly
recognized you.
You've certainly come a long way
and I wanted to wish
you good luck.
- Oh, thank you, but you
can't wish me good luck.
- Why not?
- Because in America,
when there's a performance,
it's bad luck to wish good luck.
- And what do you say instead?
- Break a leg.
- Right.
That makes sense.
- Wow!
- And now, welcome our next
couple, Lydia and Philippe.
- Oh...
- Ah, Lydia will definitely
not be happy with that.
- Thank you, Philippe.
Thank you, Lydia.
And now, please welcome our
next couple, Lukas and Amy.
- Oh my God.
- Oh my God!
- Do you want to do this?
- No, no.
I'm too nervous.
You go ahead.
I'll be right behind you, okay?
- Yes! Yes! We did it!
We're going to the Ball!
We did it!
- Oh!
- What happened?
Are you okay?
- I slipped on this champagne
and I think I sprained my ankle.
- No. I'm gonna go
get an ambulance.
- No, no, no, no.
It's fine.
It's just twisted.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah.
- Get a chair or
something, please!
That's it.
- Oh, okay.
I am so sorry.
- Don't be sorry.
It's not your fault.
I'm gonna go get you
some ice, okay?
- Too bad about
your dance partner.
- Lydia, not now!
Come on, please!
- You know, Philippe
is a great dance partner,
but we don't have
the same spark that we had.
- Lydia...
- You saw what he did
to me on that lift.
You would never
embarrass me that way.
And I know what
winning means to you.
You know that
there's a rule that allows you
to switch dance partner if one
gets physically unable to dance?
I'm just saying.
- I feel so stupid.
I can't believe I fell.
Lukas and I actually make
it into the Midnight Ball
and I screw it up
with my clumsiness!
- Well, at least
there's a bright side.
- Do tell?
- You get to stay here with me.
- You have a point.
- Sure.
- Oh, wow.
- Amy insisted you have
a real tree
sourced from the Vienna woods.
- It's beautiful.
Merry Christmas.
- Now we gotta keep ice on this.
- Ow! Ow! Ow!
- Look, I don't know.
I think that maybe you
should go to the doctor.
- It'll probably
be better in the morning.
- If it's still swollen,
you promise that you'll go?
- I promise.
- Who's that?
"Hi, Amy. I hope that
your ankle is feeling better.
"And, by the way, thank
you for the tree.
It was so thoughtful."
That's really sweet.
"Are you free
tomorrow morning?"
I like him.
- Give me my phone.
I'm glad.
It's good that you like him.
- Sir, you missed a call
from your lady friend.
- Thank you, Dominik.
It's amazing, isn't it?
- "Good morning, Lukas.
"Just wanted to let
you know I'm on my way
"to the hospital right now.
Nothing serious.
"My ankle's still
a little swollen.
"So I just want to make
sure it's healing properly.
"I'm sorry I can't
meet up this morning,
but I'll call you as soon
as I'm done. Bye."
- I think we should go
to the hospital.
- Mm-hmm.
I go prepare the car.
- Thank you, Dominik.
Thank you, Vienna.
Not gonna cost a thing.
- Thank you for making me
go to the doctor.
- No problem.
Hey, by the way,
Uncle Markus said
he's gonna stay with us through
the holidays to help out.
- That's really nice.
- Mm-hmm.
- The doc said
it's just a mild sprain.
It should heal pretty quick.
- Yeah, well, he insists.
Says it's gonna
be great to spend Christmas
with family again.
- That's great.
- Yeah, Wunderbar!
- All right, let's do this.
- Whoa, whoa!
What are you doing?
You got to stay off of it
for at least a couple of days.
- Goodbye, Christmas Ball.
- Whatever you need, okay?
- Thanks.
- Hello, Lukas, have
you given any more thought
to my proposition?
- Hey, Lukas, it's Amy.
I'm at home recuperating.
I'm sorry, again,
this has happened.
I would really, really
love to see you again soon.
I know that you are
preparing for the Midnight Show,
so I totally understand
if you're too busy.
But, yeah, I hope you're well.
Merry Christmas.
- Come on, sis.
What are you doing back there?
We gotta hang stockings.
Still nothing?
- No, not even a text.
- Perfect.
- Lukas Hofbauer,
nice to see you again!
We're about to close,
but I can still make
you two hot chocolates.
- Oh, that would be nice,
Sophia, but one only, please.
- What happened?
- I think I trusted
Amy a little too much.
She was with someone
else the whole time.
- I'm sorry.
She seemed to like you,
the you, you,
not the rich, stuffy you.
- Yes, I guess you're right.
She was...is...different,
but it doesn't matter now.
I'm back with my ex.
I will be dancing in
the Midnight Show with her.
- Where is she now?
- She doesn't like
hot chocolate.
- All I know is
hot chocolate isn't very much
fun to drink alone,
especially at Christmas.
- Hey, are you sure you're
gonna be okay at the market?
You really should
have let
Uncle Markus and
me come with you.
- Daniel, it's fine.
How else was I gonna be able
to get you both gifts?
And I have to get Mom
and Dad Christmas gifts.
- Okay, but I'm picking
you up in an hour.
Those crowds are no joke.
- I'll be fine.
I'll see you in an hour.
Bye.
- Oh, my gosh.
Hey, Amy?
- Hey!
How are you?
- What happened to your leg?
- I overdid it in
a waltzing competition.
- Eee.
- Yeah, it's a long story.
- Does it hurt?
- Yeah, it's still throbbing.
- Here.
You know I'm a nurse, right?
- Yeah.
- Here's a bench over here.
Let me take a look at it.
Let me grab your stuff.
- Thanks.
- Yeah.
Okie-dokie, that should do it.
- Wow. That actually
feels a lot better.
- It's just a minor
sprain anyway.
- Still, do you think
I could dance on it?
- It's totally up to you,
but it might hurt.
Just take a little Ibuprofen
and you'll be good
to go, though.
- I appreciate it,
but I don't think I'm gonna
be dancing any time soon.
Thank you, Hal.
- Happy to help.
Well, I need to be heading...
I actually put my
name in a raffle
and won tickets
to a party tonight.
- Cool.
- So when do you
head back to Chicago?
- After Christmas, after
my doctor clears me to fly.
- Get well soon, Amy.
Be well.
I'll see you soon.
- Have fun.
- Good job, guys!
Thank you.
We will do one last one
before our Christmas Eve Ball
at Kursalon.
Is this all right?
- Can I say something?
Just because I'm gonna
be crowned
as the Queen of
the Christmas Eve Ball
doesn't mean I can't return
to my humble beginnings.
I want to say that I appreciate
every single one of you.
I mean, you're all so wonderful.
You make us look so good.
- Lukas, have you
heard from Amy?
- Who?
- Chicago?
The charming American?
Quick learner?
Feisty spirit?
With her, I could have
sold classes the whole winter.
- You mean the crass, clumsy one
with the two left feet who fell?
I mean, I hope she's all right.
- She's fine.
She's well taken care of.
- Come on, guys.
One more time.
- I gotta get back to Chicago.
This trip has been such a mess.
- Ames, hey, look.
I haven't seen you
this happy in years.
- Do I look happy
to you right now?
I don't even get
to go to the Ball.
- Yeah, I know.
That wasn't really the point,
though, was it?
Look, all I'm saying
is that I see you happy.
You're doing stuff
because you want to do it,
not because
it's on some schedule,
not because you feel
like you have to.
That's a good thing, right?
- Why are you always
so annoyingly right?
- I think I get it
from my sister.
- My ankle's actually
feeling a lot better.
- Oh, this is wonderful news.
Seems like you've got a
late visit from St. Nicholas.
- Santa Claus came early.
- I would like to give
a toast to my new nephew,
Daniel, who may not have
hunted our Christmas goose
in the woods, but,
thank goodness,
it was still open season
at the butcher's!
We'll get 'em next year,
Daniel, and...
to Amy's recovery.
You'll be back to
waltzing in no time.
Prost.
- Prost.
- What's the matter?
- I can't help but
think the Ball is tonight
and it's setting in
that I won't be going.
- Hold on a second.
You know, I was
the head groundskeeper
of the palais where the ball
is held for over 40 years.
- Really?
- And for my lifetime
of service,
every year I'm given these.
Brought them along just in case.
- What's that?
- It's tickets...
to the Christmas Ball!
- They're yours.
Merry Christmas!
- Oh, my goodness,
Uncle Markus!
That's amazing!
Thank you so much!
- Nothing would give me greater
joy than for you to go.
- Thank you!
I wish I could.
I don't have a dress.
- Oh, yes, you do.
Your dress, my dear.
- Is that...
- It was Greta's
favorite gown.
I can think of no one
better to wear it.
- Oh, my goodness!
I would be honored.
Thank you, thank you!
- Now let's all go to the Ball!
- Amazing!
I feel like a princess!
- I think Greta
would be very happy.
- Thanks, again, Uncle Markus.
I'm so glad you're a
part of the family.
- Merry Christmas.
- You guys ready to do this?
- You look great in a tux.
- Oh, thank you.
Markus says it was my father's.
- You really look like him.
- Hopefully, I
don't disgrace the family
too much with my dancing.
- You could never.
- Shall we?
- We shall.
It's magnificent.
- Have you ever seen
anything so magical?
- Only in fairy tales.
- A waltz, my dear?
- Indeed, good sir.
- All right, let's see how
those dance lessons paid off.
- Hi.
My name is Vira.
- I'm Daniel.
- Nice to meet you.
- This is my sister, Amy.
- Nice to meet you, too.
- Nice to meet you.
- I'm gonna get some air.
Looks like you have to dance.
Good luck.
Sorry...
Lukas!
- Hi, Amy.
I didn't expect you here.
- Yeah, well, I might
have fallen down.
But I managed to get
myself back up again.
- I can certainly see that.
How did you manage
to get a ticket?
- Look, I just want to
know what happened.
Then you can go back to
pretending I never existed!
- Hi.
I want to say, "Ashley"?
You look very classy tonight,
A really, really
phenomenal dress.
But we'd better get going.
Let's get some practice
before the crown is ours.
- Don't let her get to you.
- It's not easy.
- You should be proud
of your dancing.
There are not a lot of people
who could learn
as much as you did
in such short time.
Thank you, Amy.
You helped me remember why I
teach waltz in the first place.
Excuse me a moment?
I have to set up
this competition.
- Amy!
- Hal, what are you doing here?
- That party I told you about?
This is it!
- Wow!
Well, you look great.
- My mom always told me to pack
at least one nice suit
because you never know
when you're gonna need it.
- Looks like she was right.
- True. She's been
wrong before, though.
Hey, this is Eva.
Tonight we're having
a great time.
- Great. Nice to meet you.
- Hey, how's your leg?
- It's much better, thank you.
- I'm very happy
you're here tonight.
- Thanks. I'm happy that
we met here in Vienna.
You're a great guy.
You guys have
a great night, okay?
Bye.
- Hey.
- Have you seen Lukas?
- What? Lukas Hofbauer?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, I...
I saw him on the balcony.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
- This is just like
in the old days.
- Yeah, just like the old days.
- Did you ever think
we'd be dancing
at the Christmas Ball together?
- Lydia, I think I need a break.
- No!
We need to keep practicing!
- I'm sorry.
Listen...
- We need to keep practicing!
- I need to get some fresh air!
- Lukas?
Please, why won't
you talk to me?
What's your problem?
- My problem?
- Ever since I got hurt, you've
completely blown me off!
- Excuse me?
- I mean, I get it.
You just wanted to be
crowned King of the Ball.
But you could have at least
said thank you and goodbye!
- Hey, listen!
I came to see you!
I just didn't know you
were with someone else.
- Someone else?
What are you talking about?
There is no one else!
- Yeah, right.
I know what I saw.
You know, with girls like Lydia,
I know what I'm getting.
She's not just pretending
to be nice,
to be clawing her way to the top
just like all the other ones!
- Is that what you think of me?
- Without further ado,
the moment we all have
been waiting for.
- Let's win this crown.
- Please welcome our
Midnight Show dancers.
- I knew you'd come around.
- Please welcome our
final waltzing couple.
- I'm glad you came
to your senses.
You would never won
that crown with her.
- Hey.
- Is everything okay?
- No. I'm sorry.
- What is he doing?
- What are you doing?
- Lydia, you deserve
to dance with somebody
who wants the crown
as badly as you do.
- But this has been your dream
for years!
- I need to do this
for myself.
I can't live my life
for everybody else.
This is it!
Amy, I am so sorry.
- Lukas, I...I...
- I never planned
on meeting you.
But now that I have, I can't
imagine my life any other way.
- I don't know.
I don't know, Lukas.
- I'm sorry for what
I said outside.
I didn't mean it.
It was out of hurt.
I just needed to let
you know how I truly feel.
Listen, take good
care of her, okay?
You're a lucky man.
- Wait. You think Daniel's
my boyfriend?
- Ah, no...
- Daniel's my brother.
- What? Daniel is your brother?
- Yeah.
- Amy is your sister?
- You guys are
brother and sister?
- Yeah!
- Yes.
- No!
That's amazing!
I mean, I'm such a fool!
- Yeah.
- I didn't want
to get hurt again.
Could you ever forgive me?
I am so sorry.
- You could start
by asking me to dance.
- May I have this dance?
- Yes.
- This is beautiful.
- I thought it was dangerous to
look your partner in the eyes.
- Not if she is as beautiful
as you are.
- Merry Christmas.
- Chicago!
- It's the best
Christmas Ball ever!
- Shall we dance?
- Love to.