Dan: I want you to quit
your post, Jake.
I want you to take
over Metro for me.
Superintendent rank.
Jake: What do I know
about Metro?
If I've been out of downtown
a half dozen times
the last five years,
it's a lot.
Metro overlaps Boston,
same police power.
Come on Dan,
there must be a dozen captains
begging for that spot.
Last time I checked
I wasn't one of them.
What's the problem?
There's a knot of corruption
in that department so thick
I need a knife to cut it with.
A clean, sharp knife.
We're talking about deep-seated
extensive corruption, Jake,
the kind that takes a
rookie and presses him
into believing if you
wanna be one of the guys,
this is the only way to go.
That's why I want
you on the inside.
Bust it up.
Any names in Metro I can use?
I'll need someone. A choirboy.
You're gonna have to
find him for yourself.
How about surveillance?
Wire taps? Backup?
Extremely low
profile, no budget.
No outside agencies.
Thanks a lot, Dan.
(drilling)
(crashing)
(hissing)
(drilling)
(humming)
Hey! Looking good, Barry!
Thanks.
So, where's George Washington
gonna put that ax, huh?
Over there? Huh?
(chuckles) Yeah.
- (laughs)
- Are you gonna take the car?
Oh, the car...
I'd like to bury that car.
Take the wagon honey.
I wanna check out a
couple more trade-ins
on my way to work.
Mary: Putting
that on the market?
If I can't get my
price I'll work it out.
Right.
(dogs barking)
(birds chirping)
Get rid of it for
me, will ya, Frankie?
Thanks a lot, babe.
Burn it, trash it, bury it,
I don't care what
you do just as long
as it looks good
on the insurance.
Wanna get rid
of your car, huh?
Yeah.
We'll take care of it tonight,
no sweat.
But you're better off leaving
these in the ignition.
Park the pig outside
in your usual space,
Doogie and I will swing by
and give it the deep six.
But you're gonna owe me one.
No problem, Frankie.
What are friends for?
Name it.
Well I, uh...
I already got something in mind.
There's this video depot
Doogie and I got cased out.
Medford video depot.
It's ripe for the slaughter.
Frankie, I'm one
of your biggest fans.
But I think you're way out
of your league on this depot.
They got a high
tech alarm system.
It's impossible.
Nah, I got an alarm man.
It's the real thing.
Benny Brown. The best in town.
Hey that rhymes!
Maybe we ought to make
an ad for this guy,
what do you think?
Doogie, would
you just shut up?
An alarm man?
Well...
that's a horse of
a different color.
But I gotta run it by Jimmy.
Anything this big in Medford,
I got run it by Jimmy first.
An alarm man?
You got an alarm man and
you're gonna waste him
heisting cameras? Come on!
What are you talking
about waste him, huh?
Hey Jimmy you just passed the
video store, stop the car.
That's small potatoes.
You really got an alarm man,
this could be hot!
What are you doin'?
Come on guys, what's goin' on?
Hey guys, huh?
What are you stoppin' here for?
That's my bank.
Frankie: The
Depositor's Trust?
Jimmy: If I'm
lyin', I'm dyin'!
Frankie: (laughs) I get it.
A bank job, right?
What are you talkin' about, huh?
It's nuts!
There's millions in the vault.
That place ought to be a piece
of cake for a real pro.
Tin can.
Hey guys, a video
store's one thing.
We been doing that
kinda heist for years.
But a bank?
What's the matter, Frankie?
Afraid of the cops?
(laughter)
(phone rings)
(chatter)
(police scanners)
Metro, Clemente, talk to me!
Third and Mason,
I can spring a
canine and a cruiser,
but I gotta have
'em back by 11:00,
DUI's up and down the parkway.
Metro, Clemente, talk to me!
Jimmy! How's my boy?
Hey Jerry. Just checking in.
I'm excited about
today's little talk.
Real excited.
That's a big 10-4 but
now's not exactly the time,
know what I mean, huh?
(knocking)
I gotta go. Quinn.
Spell me, will ya Frank?
Yeah, sure thing Captain.
- (knocking)
- Come in.
Come on, Gerry. Come on in.
Have a seat.
I've gotten word the
mob's running drugs
direct into Logan on
single engine prop planes.
You hear anything?
No, sir.
Narcotics is not
my chain though.
Yeah, I know, I know.
Well, if this running drugs
into the airport is true,
my bet is someone in the
division's on the take.
Nothing makes my skin crawl more
than the stink of a dirty cop.
Hmm, understandable.
Gerry, I'm the
new boy in town.
I'm gonna need all the
help I can get on this.
So, you hear anything about
the division being compromised,
I expect you to come
straight to me, okay?
Of course! Of course.
Well, I gotta be
getting back, sir,
I'm on watch.
Well, go! Go.
Thank you.
Forgive me, Captain Clemente,
for I have sinned.
Sir?
Here we are still
on our honeymoon,
and I'm asking you to
break Omertà for me.
That's the second
code of silence!
Is that an Italian joke, sir?
No Ger, it's a cop joke.
Huh.
Not a funny one.
I'll let you know
if I hear anything.
Good.
I expect you to.
Oh, no! No, not again!
Where's my car?
Where's my Caddy?
Did you guys see anybody?
Hey, Lieutenant!
Lieutenant!
Get Hawkins from theft.
- Get him up here right now!
- What's the problem?
The problem?
The problem is they stole my car
right out of the squad lot.
Oh, that's a real
shame, Captain.
Why don't you call
the motor pool?
Oh, you're a real comedian.
Everybody's a comedian.
What are you guys
laughing at, huh?
Clemente. What
a piece of work!
Dollars to donuts, he just had
that old rust bucket of his
pinched right off the lot.
(laughter)
What makes you say
that, Lieutenant?
Well, you know Gerry.
Do I?
(revving engine)
(splashing)
If I knew you guys had this
much fun on the job, Frankie,
I would have become
a cop myself.
- Get outta here!
- (laughter)
In this game, making
each shot is important.
Setting up for the next shot
is what it takes to win.
Your wife was very attractive.
Great pool player,
rest her soul.
Speaking of which,
I never knew you were enrolled
at the Jesuit
Seminary, Lieutenant.
That was a long time ago, sir.
Jake.
What do they say?
Give me the boy
until he's seven,
and I'll show you the man?
Something like that.
Yes.
Father killed in action.
Brother on the beat, in Quincy.
A regular second
generation Boston cop.
Third.
Third? Whew!
You got me beat by one!
So Paul...
what do you know about
Captain Clemente that I don't?
That depends on
what you know, sir.
What I know?
Omertà from a Jesuit?
Silence among thieves,
even if the thieves are cops?
Mea culpa, padre.
I think I can trust you, Paul.
So here's what I know.
I've been doing a
little nosing around.
Rumor has it that Clemente
is a legend in his own time.
Pulling patrol heists, TVs,
refrigerators, washer-dryers.
Presents for his wife, his kid.
Probably some other
officers involved.
But who's gonna talk
about that, huh?
Omertà?
You know a lot
about him then, sir.
I know I hate everything
that he stands for,
ever since I put on a badge.
Why don't you
take him down then?
I can't take him down because
I haven't got anything
hard against him.
Except what?
Beating his electric meter?
I heard that one.
But when it was tipped
he busted up his box
and said burglars broke into it.
So the choirboy can sing,
if he hears the right tune.
Gerry's dirty as sin.
He's the highest ranking
man in my department.
And it burns me I haven't got
anything hard against him.
This whole part of
town is compromised,
not just by OC,
but by cops pulling
their own scams
with or without the mob.
He's the worst
part of that breed.
If I can bring him down,
it's gonna make an example.
Are you with me?
Or does being a cop
mean nothing to you?
That's what it comes down to,
nothing less than that.
People trust cops.
They ought to trust cops.
Anything gets in the
way of that trust,
I'm gonna smash.
Now once again, are you with me,
Lieutenant?
I'm with you, sir, yes.
Good.
Now.
What do you know about
Gerry that I don't?
There's this girl.
What girl?
Kelly Sherwood.
Gerry's mistress, going
on at least three years.
She works bails in Revere.
I've seen his car parked outside
her house plenty of times.
- On duty?
- Most of the time.
And what's so important that
it can't wait another hour?
Call of duty, baby.
Well just as long as it's
not the call of the wild.
Better not be going out on me,
or home to Mary.
(Gerry sighs)
Know what the
problem with you is?
Hmm?
You have no
respect for the law.
(Kelly laughs)
Oh, and you do?
You bet. Gotta go.
Oh come on baby, stay!
- Baby...
- Kelly: Come on!
(screeching tires)
Busting into a bank with cops,
I mean that'd be history,
it'd be a first.
So what's the problem, Benny?
You're the problem, Captain.
You and the two sergeants here.
I mean how do I know
that this isn't a setup?
That wouldn't fly,
Benny me boy!
It's entrapment.
Entrapment nothin', I'm
talkin' about gettin' whacked.
No.
Cops or no cops,
an alarm man is always
lookin' over his shoulder
after the job.
Lone outsider brought in to
help the tight local boys.
And the local boys being cops,
well I figure the odds of me
being hit are about even money.
Not that we'd do that, Benny.
Yeah. Besides,
any bank job it's risky enough.
Risky?
This place is a tin can!
There's millions just waiting.
I've been prayin' for years
for someone like
you to come along.
Let me tell ya
how a guy like me
lives long enough
to be a guy like me.
You stay as far away
as possible from cops.
Sounds like you gotta
learn to trust cops, Benny.
Cops like us could
be your best friends.
Why should I trust you?
Because, Benny, there
are two kinds of cops.
There are honest cops,
and there are smart cops,
and even the honest
cops don't talk.
It's a perfect little
world out there, Benny.
Okay. Let's just say
that I do trust ya.
(laughs) I mean I'm not
so sure that I can still
take this bank down.
Here's my proposal.
Just check the joint out,
and then you make your decision.
If it ain't
everything Jimmy says,
you can jump off the wagon,
no harm no foul.
Ah, you're a smart guy, Gerry,
just like they say.
(sighs) Okay, Captain,
so when can I see
this here tin can?
Jimmy: Tonight.
It's popcorn, a piece of cake.
Absolutely unbelievable!
Benny's in, even splits.
- It's an old box.
- All right.
Hell of a lot of telephone
wires in there with alarm
but nothin' electrical!
How soon before
you can make it?
Can you get me
in an hour a shot,
say three times a week?
- Yeah.
- A month.
Two at the most
to beat the alarm.
Another week to
build a bypass box
so we can control it.
But, I need an inside man.
I need a blaster.
Come on, Benny!
Another guy to split the take?
Yeah, well I need
someone to blow that vault.
We don't beat the
vault, we get nothin'.
Look, I'm tight with a demo man,
Vince Brogan. He's a pro.
A pro that'll watch your back
against us cops, huh Benny?
You're reading my mind.
Sure okay, maybe one of my own
will make me feel a
little more comfortable.
But I do need a
blaster, that's no lie.
No Brogan, no Benny.
Welcome aboard, Benny.
(laughs)
If I'm lyin' I'm dyin'!
We're going scuba fishing
off the boat tomorrow.
You and Quinn?
He says he's never
done it before,
and he wants to build up
his retirement skills.
(laughs) You and Quinn!
That's something
I never figured.
Especially now.
You think he's on to the bank?
Ah, come on!
Don't even fool,
don't even go in that area.
Quinn in a scuba
suit! (laughs)
Like a beached whale!
That's a picture!
I'm about to wet my pants!
I gotta hit the head.
Hey Scarzi, what do you say?
Hey, Ger!
Hey, Mr. Scarzi!
Got the same show this week.
What happened, Nick?
Sinatra cancelled again?
Sinatra? Very funny.
(Gerry laughs)
Look, I need some help.
You got a second?
For an old friend
and choirboy?
Yeah. Sit down.
Thank you.
What's up?
Well I got some
trouble, you know?
There's these two guys,
dealers, pals of mine.
They got pinched by
Metro over at Wellington.
They're connected, you know?
Yeah.
Well, Ferrano
wants 'em cut loose.
(laughs) Nick!
I mean listen, this is his turf,
we're tight and all that
happy horse manure over there,
but even he knows
I can't erase a drug bust!
I just want you to talk
to the arresting officer.
He's an undercover guy.
Bobby Kellogg, you know,
just get him to stretch things
so that these two
guys can get off.
Say that the bust was illegal.
Just talk to him, okay?
(distant sirens)
Hey Kellogg, you got a second?
Captain? What's the occasion?
Ah, you gotta help me out
on something here, Bobby.
Yeah, sure, what?
That bust you made down
on Wellington yesterday.
Oldham and Willette?
Did you get 'em clean?
Yeah. Clean as a cat's tongue.
Big haul, too.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
So who wants to know? Lawyers?
Eh, a friend of a friend.
Owns a nightclub
down on Route 1.
Real connected.
Anyway, he wanted me
to pass it on to you,
that there's a lot of real
money to be made here.
With the right kind of truth.
I spoke to Kellogg, like I said.
Wasn't too subtle,
but he got the hint.
No.
What do you want from me?
This is no good.
I got guys to account to
if those two guys go down.
Gerry: If they go down,
they go down.
It happens, okay?
They're small fry,
don't worry about it.
Kellogg's a square,
he won't bite.
Scarzi: Can't you talk
to him again?
No way!
What the hell's the
matter with you man?
Come on!
Stop giving me this grief!
Leave me alone,
I'm gonna go fishing.
Jake: Ah, last time
I was on a boat,
I don't even remember.
I ought to enjoy life more.
(laughs) That's right.
That's what it's for!
Hmm, right, right.
Maybe I'll get me a boat.
There you go.
How much does
this run you, Gerry?
(Gerry whistles)
Well, you know what
they say about a boat.
I don't know, Jake,
what do they say about a boat?
It's a hole in the water
you throw money into.
(Gerry chuckles)
What's the sense of having money
if you don't spend it, right?
Except if you don't have it!
And that's a horse
of a different color.
Yeah, I tell ya,
this baby keeps me skimpin'
all the way around.
Boston cops.
To Boston cops.
We always get our man.
Oh, those are the
Mounties, Jake.
My mistake!
What do Boston cops get, Gerry?
Twenty-two thousand
dollars a year (laughs).
Good one!
To Boston cops.
The best cops in the world.
Best in the world.
And the outside lock to
the optical shop is easy.
I picked it last night
when I was on patrol.
Gerry: Went in, looked around.
It was beautiful.
The loft's got a dual
set of heavy-duty sockets
for grinding lenses,
which is right near
the wall to the bank.
Now, that's perfect because
there's plenty enough juice
to handle the drills to
get us through the wall
into the crawl space,
over the vault.
The vault.
I don't know.
Vince?
It's an old baby
with metal rods
crisscrossing the top,
should make it easier on us,
but nothing's a cinch.
We'll drill a couple of holes,
smash through with
sledgehammers.
That doesn't work,
we use dynamite.
(laughs) Dynamite, huh?
- Yeah.
- What are you, nuts?
No.
Somebody's gonna hear us.
We'll use a couple of
sandbags to muffle the sound.
Yeah, sure.
Listen, I'd like
three nights in there
over a long weekend.
You know?
Short hits in and out,
it's worth it to
clean all the boxes.
Like some satin sheets
while you're at it?
Three nights.
Shouldn't be difficult.
Memorial Day weekend.
(suspense music)
Got the name of a
pal Gerry hangs with.
Hunting, fishing,
families go out together.
Everybody knows they're friends,
but it could go deeper.
The guy's a sergeant
over in Medford.
Jimmy Donnelly?
You know the name?
Why don't you give it to me?
I just heard rumors, Jake!
I'm not gonna trash
a cop on a rumor,
not to you or anybody!
It's probably a
dead end anyway.
Clemente and Donnelly
are pulling penny ante
stuff together,
fat chance of proving it.
Omertà.
Right. Cops don't rat on cops.
Even Jesuit cops!
Sorry, sorry.
(ticking)
(beep)
Gentlemen,
Memorial Day weekend,
that tin can's ours.
Ha-ha! Party time!
Hey Doogie. Doogie, please.
We're outta here.
Now Vince and I'll sneak back
from Florida on the 23rd.
An out of state alibi
ain't gonna hurt.
I mean the Feds,
they know my rep.
I'm gonna be taking a
lot of heat for sure.
So remember, business as usual
the whole Memorial
Day weekend, all right?
Okay.
Gerry, I'm gonna
be with your wife.
Yeah, I'm workin'.
The more people
you see the better.
Set things up. Work and play.
I'll go bowling.
And you better
call Kelly, Gerry.
Before this gets out of hand...
Now, remember,
five years from now,
when the statute of
limitations runs out
this isn't gonna mean anything.
But for now, this is the circle.
Nobody gets caught,
unless somebody talks.
That won't happen.
No way, boss.
Don't look at us,
we're not gonna cross
a bunch of cops!
(laughs) And live
to talk about it!
Get out!
Whoa, whoa.
We stick together
or we fall apart.
(snapping/clapping)
Understood?
I'm gonna meet some
of the guys, okay?
Nothing important.
I don't like being
left alone, Gerry.
Oh baby, come on. Come on.
Give me a kiss, come on.
There you go, see.
(Kelly laughs)
(kissing)
Man: (over radio)
Two to one clear.
Check.
Three to one, set.
Like buttah, like buttah!
(car door slamming)
(lock turns)
Bring it home, bring it home.
(whispering)
Two to one,
two to one, all clear.
Go, go, go, go, go, go!
Come on!
Let's go!
(drilling)
(crashing)
One to two, one to two.
Go ahead.
Popcorn.
Yeah!
(swooshing)
Ready!
(drilling)
(smashing)
Benny: Forget about it!
This ain't working Benny!
Okay, I'm gonna
have to blow it.
Vinny.
This is gonna do it,
right, Vin?
Gerry, relax.
Move, move!
(explosion)
(rumbling)
One to two, one to two,
come in.
Two to one, all clear.
Popcorn!
(sizzling)
(cheering)
(crashing)
(rumbling)
(shouting)
Let's go boys, let's do this!
(hissing)
Talk to me, Frankie,
how's it going?
Come on down.
Whoa! Hello there, lass!
Come on, baby!
Give it to me now!
(banging)
Come on!
Let me do the lock.
(clunk)
Yo! Whoa!
Oh, no! No!
(screams in frustration)
What? What?
Look at it!
Jimmy's off, there's nothin',
next to nothin' in here!
Let me see, shut up!
Read 'em and weep.
60 bundles, 1000 on a band,
numbers don't lie, pal!
Lousy $10,000 each!
Oh, yeah. Jimmy says
there's gonna be millions.
Sure, yeah. Cops!
You're supposed
to know something!
I thought you were smart, Gerry!
Hey!
- Man 1: No, no.
- Man 2: Gerry. Gerry!
Come on! Come on!
Okay, all right.
(yelling)
Now listen, there's
still plenty of boxes here.
We'll just dump 'em!
Let's just keep going!
Yeah?
You're wastin' your time!
Shut up!
(arguing)
Quiet! Quiet! Jimmy!
Jimmy: Two to one,
come in.
Let's move.
It's gettin' light.
Jimmy: We'll come
back tonight.
No way.
- Benny!
- Yeah, sure.
I should have--
(slamming)
(sigh) We going back for the
rest of the boxes, Benny?
You guys can do what you want.
You think there's anything
there, that's fine.
I'm not taking the risk.
Let's just divvy up,
each stash his own,
and we'll call it quits,
all right?
Vince: Hey, look at this!
There's over $100,000 here.
Yeah!
And this.
Whoa!
- Whoa!
- The boxes!
I knew it was in the boxes!
Wait a second, wait a second!
This is real good stuff!
Vince!
Nice!
Vince: Look at this, look!
How many boxes are left?
Eight, 900 more!
We're going back.
(clanging)
Come on, how much?
Close to a million cash!
- Yes!
- Jimmy!
(laughter)
But it's nothing
compared to this.
These pink diamonds here
alone are worth $2 million.
Get outta here!
Pop the gems out,
melt down the gold,
another million, two easy, huh?
Rest of the boxes,
eight million, $10 million.
Vince, I've never seen such
big stuff in one place, huh?
With what, maybe 300
more boxes to go?
Who knows?
Where the hell did
all this come from?
Who cares?
It's ours now, huh?
If it's the mob's,
they'll care.
Yeah, right.
Enough of them
live in this town,
Winters, Ferraro...
This could be theirs
laundered into gems.
I'll check it out
with Ferraro.
Either way, a hit
this big in his turf,
he's gonna want a cut.
I figure at least
$1 million easy.
A million, what are you nuts?
I hate cuttin'
those bastards in!
Well, it's either that
or we get our legs cut off.
Benny, if anything's
fenced you make tribute
right off the top.
Yeah, I'll take care of it.
But I gotta get down to Florida
tonight and salt my alibi.
So you give my share
of the cash part to Vince.
Everybody's responsible
for his own cash splits.
You burn it, you bury it
in the basement, whatever.
Yeah, I got it, I got it.
What are we gonna do
with all this jewelry
in the meantime, huh?
I mean this here,
this is the haul, huh?
So? What's it gonna be?
I'll look after it!
Oh, Doogie, just forget it.
Forget about it.
(laughter)
What's it gonna be, Ger?
You take care of
the stones, Benny.
After all, you're
gonna be the one
who's gonna be
fencin' 'em, right?
After all, if you can't
trust the alarm man,
who can you trust?
(laughs) This is a switch, huh?
(laughter)
Sure.
Okay, I'll hold all the gems.
Vince, you get
tomorrow's beauties
down to me in Miami.
Look, as I sell them off,
I'll keep in touch with Frank.
Everybody get's
their share. Okay?
When we get the cash,
we'll mix it in
with the rest of the haul.
And remember, no spending,
no flashing
until the heat's off.
Even if we have to wait the
whole five years of the statute,
we lay low.
And then, bingo.
(crashing)
(laughter)
With what we got last night,
I bet we got 20,
maybe $25 million!
Twenty-five!
Oh, my God!
(laughs) Oh, mother of pearl!
Shut up, Doogie.
Shut up.
Twenty-five million dollars!
This is bigger than Brink's!
Brink's, that was
a lousy 1.2 me boy.
Twenty-five mil!
that's twice as much as
the great train robbery!
And that, gentlemen,
makes it the biggest
job of all time!
All: Yeah!
(screaming in celebration)
Thank you, Benny!
(police sirens)
(reporters' chatter)
All right, let me through!
Let me through!
No comment!
Let him through!
Back away now!
Everything's okay! Back off!
- Jake: Ted!
- Mother of God!
Jake: You got that right!
Manager said
that they wiped the vault
and the boxes clean.
Could be millions.
Local yokel time.
Gosh, Ted!
I wonder what happened here?
The roof fall in, you think?
Hall Phillips, Federal Bureau.
Jack Burton.
I'm Captain Davis,
Medford Police.
Oh, Jake Quinn.
Superintendent Metro
District Commission.
We overlap Medford on this.
So what do we got?
Well what we have so far,
are no clues and big problems.
The gang spent
the whole weekend here
and they wiped it clean.
All three nights?
That took guts.
They must have figured
they couldn't get hit.
Any noise on patrol?
Nah. No alarm, nothin'.
Who was the walking man?
We'll get to that.
First we want a soup
to nuts forensic in this vault.
Every loose piece gets bagged.
What about the bill
wrappers and serial numbers?
Get 'em. Put 'em
over the wire ASAP.
(phone ringing)
Who was on patrol, Teddy?
Last night?
Jimmy Donnelly.
Look, somebody drops
a dime that the cops
did the Depositor's Trust.
We don't go off half-cocked.
Who knows how deep it runs?
Meaning you
checked me out first.
Meaning I followed procedure
and ran an official
profile on you.
Sit down.
Who said it was cops?
Nick Scarzi, local OC.
He's just testing the
waters with this tidbit
and wants us to
pony up $500 grand
before he'll tell us
what else he knows.
Scarzi? First off,
he's not mob.
He's an errand boy.
A nightclub owner.
Strictly small time.
You'd actually pay
him 500 large ones?
Money's not an issue
if Scarzi's gonna give us
the Depositor's Trust.
Did Scarzi tell you
that Jimmy Donnelly,
the walking man in
Medford that night,
is pals
with a certain somebody?
Like I told ya, Scarzi's
not gonna play ball with us
until we do a deal with him.
That certain somebody
I followed up elsewhere.
Gerry Clemente.
(phone rings)
- Yeah?
- Gerry. Nick Scarzi.
They're after me.
- Who?
- The mob! That's who!
What are you talkin' about?
Scarzi: 'Cause I know
about you and Jimmy.
Come on, Jimmy's been talkin'
for years about his bank,
doin' the bank.
They want their dough!
You know it's theirs!
I don't know anything
about any bank.
Come on, man.
They know!
You know something?
They got photographs,
they got folders,
they got stuff on your life.
They got a whole profile.
A profile.
Scarzi: They put a hood
over my head,
they took me for a ride.
I thought I was finished.
I thought I was gonzo!
They got an ice pick.
They cut me real bad.
(sigh)
I wasn't involved, Nick.
Scarzi: They just call me
tomorrow at noon, at my place.
I'll call you.
- (sighs)
- (knocking)
Captain Gerald Clemente?
Yeah, that's right.
Hal Phillips, Federal
Bureau of Investigation.
This is my partner, Jack Burton.
We're here in connection
with the burglary
of the Depositor's Trust
in Medford
over the Memorial Day weekend.
Like to ask you a couple
of questions about it,
if that's all right.
Yeah, sure, sure.
Come on in, guys.
(children giggling)
(door squeaking)
Can I get you guys some coffee?
Something to drink?
Some soda?
No, thanks.
Captain Clemente,
the law requires that we tell
you that you're a suspect
in the burglary.
On what grounds?
We're not at liberty to say.
Oh, should I be
talking to a lawyer?
(laughs)
We can't advise you on that.
That's strictly
your own decision.
I didn't have anything
to do with this, guys.
You're not under arrest,
and no arrest is anticipated.
We'd just like to ask
you a couple questions.
Sure, shoot.
Can you account
for your whereabouts
Memorial Day weekend?
(sighs) MDC Friday night
shift into Saturday morning...
slept back here and
worked on my boat
down at the marina. That's it.
We'd like it in a
little more detail.
Okay. Well, look.
Can I keep this between us?
You know, off the record?
Go ahead.
But don't waltz us around.
That weekend,
like most weekends,
I spent with a friend,
you know what I mean?
The FBI? Maybe a grand jury?
Gerry, what do you
expect me to say?
I don't know the exact times
that you were here those nights!
How do I know you
didn't do that bank job?
'Cause I'm
tellin' ya I didn't,
that's why.
Now listen.
Just tell them
that I was here.
And that I stayed
until the morning.
Okay?
You think I'm looking
forward to having this
out in the open, huh?
I had to tell the FBI the truth.
As nasty as it is.
Well, thanks a lot!
Baby, come on.
You're my legit alibi!
Anything else
would be suspicious.
By the way,
Mary's gonna love
hearing about this.
Oh, now it's poor Mary, huh?
Gerry, how's the divorce
coming along?
Baby, this is not the time!
It's never the right time.
Hey, come on now.
Come on.
Do this for me, okay?
Okay, baby?
- Say yes.
- Yes.
Give me a kiss. Big kiss.
Big kiss.
Want a beer?
No.
Confidential sources
believe the vault
may have contained millions
of dollars in mob money,
which would make it the largest
bank robbery in history.
Gerry! Get in here, quick!
According to
authorized sources...
- What's up, babe?
- ...the immediate suspicion
has focused on a police officer.
Look! It's your house!
A captain on the
Metropolitan Police Force
with reputed connections
to underworld figures...
That's my house, creep!
Who the hell needs a name?
Find out who did this
I'm gonna kill him!
I didn't see who ran
me off the road, Dad!
Yeah.
They came up from behind!
I don't know,
maybe it was an accident!
That was no damn accident!
Look, whoever is leaking
these lies about me
has got the mob convinced
that I took their cash.
Or didn't make tribute!
Well, what's tribute?
Forget about that, okay?
- Here, keep this on.
- Ow!
Tight!
- Tell me, Gerry.
- What?
Don't give me "What?".
Everybody in this
town knows "what"!
- The bank!
- Mary!
Don't lie to me, Gerry.
Tell me!
What's it gonna take?
What is it gonna take
to get the truth?
One of us getting killed?
Mary, Mary, Mary, Mary.
Come here baby, come here.
Come here, come here.
That's it. That's it.
I swear to God I didn't
have anything to do
with that bank job.
I'm a cop.
And the mob's after
my kid for no reason.
(glass breaking)
(Mary screams)
Get down!
Hey! Hey!
(gun cock click)
Come on! Hey! Hey!
Hey! Hey!
Come on, come on.
- Hey! Hey!
- Mary: Gerry, no!
- Come on I'll take one of you--
- No, stop! Please!
Get inside!
- Get inside!
- Mary: Stop!
Please, please!
(sirens)
(honking)
I wanna go
after the Feds, Jake.
Uh-huh, that's right.
They come to my neighborhood,
they come to my house,
they bother my family.
I'm a police captain,
for crying out loud
and they do this!
Oh, yeah, my wife,
she can't even go out
in the neighborhood anymore,
Jake!
The mob tried to kill my kid!
Yeah, and they're buying
into this setup real good.
What can I do to help, Gerry?
Anything. Name it!
(sighs) Well, naturally,
I came to you first,
to see if I could
straighten things out.
Jake, I swear to God,
I'm completely innocent
on this thing.
You gotta help me.
Okay.
Look, you got 40 days
vacation coming.
I want you to take it,
for your sake.
You need the break.
As far as the department goes,
I think it better if the Feds
just think I'm standin' still.
Don't stand still.
Get into it.
Go after them for harassment.
There's nothin' to
go after them with!
You need proof
to press harassment,
not just leak some rumors!
Take a 40 day fast, Gerry.
It's for the best!
Look, I'm on your side here.
Right now, it looks
like I'm the only one.
Trust me!
(spraying)
Oh. Mastermind
of Depositor's Trust
finally pays me a visit.
I didn't mastermind
anything, Mr. Ferrara.
Mr. Ferrara.
Don't go too far with the
dog and pony show, Gerry.
Doesn't suit you.
I tell you it wasn't my idea.
That's what you'd
like everybody to think,
even your partners.
I work like that.
It's a good thing to
keep in the background,
still pull the strings.
That's a smart thing.
What's not so smart,
is you not paying me tribute.
Excuse me?
Not for nothin',
but my alarm man
paid off from Florida.
I haven't seen a dime, Gerry.
Why?
I don't know, I...
I have to get in touch
with my man.
I'm not in contact with him.
That's not so smart.
Should keep a tighter
rein on your people.
Somebody could get hurt.
I'm givin' it to you straight.
I know what's bothering you.
You got a lot more out of
the bank than you expected
and had your boys worried.
You've been thinkin' maybe
some of it belonged to me.
Did cross my mind, yes.
(clears throat)
Relax.
It was a clean score.
None of it was mine.
Just want my cut,
you'll have nothing
to worry about.
What about Nick Scarzi, huh?
He tells me that you're
threatening to put an ice pick
in his head
unless I pay him off.
Scarzi's nothing.
My boys tell me the only
ones giving him a hard time
are the Feds.
Scarzi's disappeared?
I thought he was supposed
to be under your wing?
We never did a deal with him.
Scarzi's a loose cannon.
If he's squeezing Clemente,
he's doin' it
on his own. Dammit.
Listen.
(phone ringing)
I'm as frustrated by this
case as you are, Phillips.
Believe me. Let me clue you.
Washington's not gonna
wanna be at the table
if the grand jury
comes up craps.
Once this case goes south,
you'll be packing up
this show in a week!
Tell me something
I don't know.
Look, I don't
know about you guys,
But I've been takin'
some serious heat.
I'm still on parole.
Feds are watching every move.
The way things are now,
I can't even get to the jewels!
Did you pay
tribute to Ferrara?
Oh, yeah, a lot of laughs.
It's suicide to try to
move anything right now.
It's just too hot!
Yeah?
Well it's gonna get a
hell of a lot hotter
if we don't see ours soon.
All it takes, Frank,
is just one little thing,
a ring, a watch, to
fall in the wrong hands.
And bang!
We're nailed.
Look, you can't be
too careful moving it.
Now look, just as soon as
the Feds are off my back,
I'll get down to some business.
I promise.
You promise, huh?
Benny, I got somethin'
I wanna show you.
(sniffing)
This is an interesting
piece, isn't it?
It's just somethin' I picked up.
(clicking)
What do you think, Benny?
Come on Gerry, come on!
I don't deserve this!
I think he gets the point,
Frankie.
(snap)
That's it?
That's all the FBI has
on the good Captain?
It's not much.
What have you got on him?
Departmental misconduct
with an on duty affair.
That's it.
Jake: I'm looking for
bigger things.
Payoffs, kickbacks, bribery.
But no other cops
have come forward yet
to corroborate the
kind of stuff I need.
What you need for what, Jake?
To bust Clemente
down and take his bars.
That's the only way
I'm gonna put him
and the rest of his gang in jail
for the Depositor's Trust.
How does that follow?
I've got Gerry thinking I'm
the only one he can trust.
On that score, I wanna
keep him spinning so fast
he doesn't know where
I'm coming from.
Here's the tactic.
I sucker him in close, get some
cops to break omertà.
then put pressure on
Gerry until he cracks.
According to the Feds, there
had to be four to five guys
including Clemente,
inside the bank.
Smart guys,
and moreover, tight.
Gerry's the pin, the glue
that holds them together.
I wanna keep the heat on him.
I bust him down,
I loosen the glue,
I get the gang.
Gerry, I hate to
keep harping on this,
but Commissioner Kirkland
still wants you in
for a polygraph on
the Depositor's Trust.
Kirkland? That suit?
You're on the line, you should
be able to hold him off.
Gerry, the man's all over me!
All right Jake... I'll do it.
But it's a no-win deal.
I don't trust those things.
I'm going in there
involuntarily,
so they can't
hold it against me.
You have to sign this.
You can get an attorney,
if you want one.
Attorney?
You sound like the Feds!
Gimme a break!
Give me a break.
You want an attorney?
You can have one.
That's all.
I'm just trying
to help you out!
(police sirens in the distance)
This is on for tomorrow!
How am I gonna get an attorney?
What's that gonna look like?
This is nuts.
If they've got enough evidence,
why not the hell
just indict me?
Answer me that, huh?
I can't.
Look, look, look!
Take the test.
It'll clear the air!
What's the problem?
The problem is,
that I expected a lot more
support from the department.
The problem, Jake,
is that I expected a
lot more from you, okay?
I do what I can, Gerry.
Here.
(heavy breathing)
Gerry, I'm telling you that
somebody is watching my house!
Will you stop it Kelly,
this is ridiculous.
I'm a cop, this is
what I do for a living.
I would know all this.
Here, see? Nothin'.
- Gerry, I'm scared!
- Gerry: No need.
Gerry, I'm not lying!
Why would I lie?
Maybe because
you miss me, baby.
Did you ever think of that?
- (Kelly sighs)
- There's my baby.
Well, maybe just a little.
That's my girl.
That's my baby.
You know, maybe I haven't
seen as much of you
as I've wanted to
since this leave.
Well, that's easily remedied.
Oh, baby! Oh!
Gerry! Look!
Cops!
Hey! Hey, come here!
(squealing tires)
Come on! Come here!
Come here, ya dirt bag!
(dog barking in the distance)
(car door open)
(engine revving)
(tires screeching)
Come on, come on!
Come on!
That's it!
(tires screeching)
(honking)
Here we go!
(tires screeching)
Dammit! I'm off duty, man!
I don't need you guys
comin' around here!
- Hey! What's the problem?
- Gerry: What's the problem?
You know what the problem is!
I was just
investigating an accident!
Well, stay off my back
or I'll give you something
to investigate!
Get outta here.
- Okay.
- Get the hell outta here!
(engine revving)
(tires screeching)
You got nothin' on me!
Nothin'!
What do you got?
You know Bobby Kellogg?
Sure, I pensioned
him out of narcotics
a couple of months ago. Why?
I'm on to something hot.
Rumor is Gerry tried to
bribe him off a drug bust
just before that.
Kellogg didn't go for it.
Jake: Rumor according
to who?
A narcotics cop.
No way he'll come forward.
I got Kellogg tracked,
he doesn't wanna come in.
He's up and down, Jake.
I don't know what kinda
witness he's gonna make.
Our only witness.
He won't talk to
me about anything.
I danced around what
we wanted to know,
he wouldn't bite.
Said he'd only talk to you.
In secret, and off the record.
Set it up.
Any place, anywhere.
You got the word,
Gerry could get the word.
I wanna move on this now.
Move how?
Whatever Kellogg gives us,
I'll slip into the polygraph.
That ought to get Gerry hoppin'.
Gerry: That wasn't
a lie detector test,
that was an inquisition!
Something's wrong here, Jake!
What do you mean?
Gerry: I mean that wasn't the
regular polygraph guy.
That was a fed, I could feel it,
I could hear it the
way he was talking.
I mean it's probably all
taped and that's illegal.
Jake: It would be.
Gerry: Yeah. Yeah.
Well, listen,
I don't like this whole thing.
You should be behind me,
instead of draggin'
me over here.
I am behind you,
but you gotta remember,
Commissioner Kirkland's
behind me with a cattle prod.
Cops are under investigation
and he wants the truth!
The truth?
The truth is that I'm
being set up with a bogus
lie detector test.
The truth is that I'm being
spied on in my own house
at four o'clock in the morning,
from guys from my
own department.
Your department, Jake.
What do you mean by that?
(sighs) I mean, whose
side are you on, huh?
I'm on your side, Gerry,
but I've got pressure on me.
Lots of it.
I'll bet.
Let's get outta here.
(tires squealing)
Bobby Kellogg,
how ya doin'?
Cut to the chase, Quinn,
what do you want?
I want you to
give me Clemente.
Clemente's not mine to give.
What do I know?
You know about the
Wellington Circle bust.
Clemente tried to
bribe you, didn't he?
He offered you money,
you refused.
Dealers went down.
Clemente told Scarzi--
Well you know so damn much,
what do you need me for?
I wanna bring
him up on charges.
I wanna take away his bars.
And I need your
testimony to do that.
Without you,
I've got nothing on him.
Then you got nothin'.
Gerry's dirty, Bobby.
He stinks to hell.
And that makes guys
like you and me stink too.
Good cops.
Even good cops
don't rat on cops, man.
He shouldn't be
on the streets.
wearing a badge.
It's not right,
you know it's not right!
Right?
What's right anymore, man?
He's a cop!
No he's not.
Nothing like you were.
He's nothing like you ever were.
Help me bring him down.
Let's bring him down together.
I need you!
If you don't do this--
(squealing tires)
Bobby?
Gerry: One year down,
four to go.
You know something', Gerry?
Between your boat
and this cabin
you're leasing up here,
it's good to see you
cut loose a little man.
You got a little uptight,
you know?
Move your foot, pal.
Well, if push comes
to shove there stretch,
I could trace all of this legit.
Not like those jewels.
(laughs)
Might as well wear
signs around your neck
that says "buy drugs here".
What are you looking at?
Especially you.
Do wonders for a cheap suit,
you know that?
(laughs) Dress
for success, Cap'n.
Just part of doing business!
Hey, you know something?
Jimmy's in the real estate
business right now,
that's right.
Starting next month, I'm
gonna move into a play pad
right next door to him.
You know,
we shouldn't be scrambling
for any kind of money.
I can't believe that
ferret faced Benny,
still nickel and diming
us on the fenced jewels.
(snorting)
(heavy breathing)
Oh no, Jimmy. No, man!
Come on! Not in here,
not in my house!
Not where I live!
Come on,
it's just a little hit!
Let me tell you somethin',
smart guys don't use this crap!
Frankie uses,
it's not a big deal.
Frank's your new idol now,
is he, huh?
It's not like that.
I can handle it.
Come on Jimmy, man.
Nobody can handle it!
You either quit, or you die.
Kellogg's hiding out.
I can't find him
to set up another meeting.
Probably couldn't
turn him if you did.
More time passes,
the harder it's gonna get for us
to nail Gerry on anything except
seeing his mistress on duty.
He's probably gonna blow cover.
It's time we made our play.
Gerry: A hearing
of my fitness for duty?
Violation of departmental
rules and reg--
What is this?
Just what it says.
I haven't heard
anything for months
from the Depositor's Trust job.
This has nothing
to do with the bank job.
Well, I can see that!
Dereliction of duty,
my competence
to serve as an officer?
We have a unique
situation here.
We don't quite know
how to handle it.
Full hearing
scheduled for September.
You seem to be handling
it pretty well.
Jake: I'm sorry.
(sigh) Sorry doesn't wash.
Not anymore.
It's out in the open now.
What?
It's you against me, isn't it?
That's what it's been
all along.
(sneers)
(door closes)
Lieutenant Brill,
in your deposition,
you've affirmed seeing
Captain Clemente's
watch commander's car
parked outside
Miss Sherwood's home
on several different occasions
while he was on duty.
During the course of one
single week in April,
five separate times.
- Is that correct?
- Yes, that's correct.
In response to our question
concerning Captain
Clemente's whereabouts during
Memorial Day weekend 1980
both on and off duty,
his response was,
and I have an indication
that this was a
"Just between me and
you" type admission,
that he spent 90% of his time
meaning both on and off duty,
with a friend.
Kelly Sherwood.
So, Miss Sherwood,
you would have this
hearing believe,
that at no time during
your four-year acquaintance
with Captain Clemente,
did he ever visit you at home,
except on official business,
while he was on duty?
That's right.
I mean when he was there,
it was only business.
(low volume chatter)
You got nothin', Quinn.
This is a joke!
This is a 30-day
slap on the wrist,
And I'm gonna
look good walkin'.
Walkin' straight to hell.
Huh-uh, walking right
into your job pa--
Hey!
Gerry, come on, come on.
(cheers)
(whistles)
I'm sweatin' out
a hearing while everybody's
getting nice, chummy.
So you guys playin' it
fast and loose, are ya?
Out here all alone, huh?
Spending too much money,
are ya?
Me and Benny we got what,
25 G's a piece into this place?
That's chicken feed
to what's comin',
when I start moving the stones.
I got that song and dance
comin' out of my ears, Benny.
Come on, I'm dishin' out!
Gerry: I thought it was
supposed to be $20 million
divided by six G's comin'.
I sure as hell ain't
got anywhere near
my end comin'.
I wonder if everybody's getting
a fair shake. That's all.
I wonder that a lot.
I'm doing the best
I can, I swear it!
If I'm lyin' I'm dyin'.
(laughs)
That's for sure,
Benny me boy.
That's for sure.
What's so funny?
Hey. Lighten up pal.
Oh, I get it.
Hey, to me that's not funny!
Cops!
Whatever was I thinkin'
to go into business with cops!
Money, pal. Money.
Hey! Hey!
I'm gonna tell you somethin',
you guys stink!
- Hey!
(crowd cheering)
Bobby. I hope
this isn't just social.
I'm comin' in clean.
Good!
What changed your mind?
I thought long and hard
about what you said.
Clemente's not a cop, man.
He's rotten.
And if I don't turn him in,
that makes everything
that I stood for as a cop,
everything that I went through,
mean nothin'!
And I can't live with that.
Let's bring him down.
Two days after the arrest
of all the men
who led... on possession,
Captain Clemente
here approached me
in the rear parking
lot of the station.
He said that he had this
guy who wanted to know
about the arrest.
He said that...
Captain Clemente stated that
there was a lot of
money to be made here.
A lot of money to be made?
Yeah.
Now would you please
relate the remainder
of your conversation
with Captain Clemente?
Huh...
Captain Clemente said that
all this guy wanted me to do
was tell the truth
about the bust,
you know, that...
Meaning that I
should come up with
some kind of illegality
to get him off.
No further questions.
Mr. Kellogg, is it not true,
that when you were
separated from Metro Police
in May of this year,
it was for Delayed
Stress Syndrome?
Kellogg: Yeah. Yes.
Gerry's Lawyer: And based on
your understanding,
what does Delayed
Stress Syndrome mean,
in lay terms?
It means that uh...
It means that I've been
under stress lately.
It means that, you know, that
I'm kinda depressed sometimes.
Nervous and paranoid.
As a result of my
undercover activities.
And during this time
when you were a member
of the Metro Police during
your undercover activities,
did this condition ever
affect your judgment?
Leave that man alone!
- Jake: Leave him alone!
- Superintendent! Sir!
Bobby Kellogg was a good cop!
A damn good cop!
Like most cops!
You are out of order!
That piece of garbage!
Guard!
Take him outta here!
(yelling)
(chatter)
You may resume your testimony.
Yeah. Uh, you know,
I'd just like to
say somethin' here
that my personal
condition at that time
had nothin' to do
with what I remember
about Captain Clemente
making an approach on me.
I mean I remember that
day absolutely clearly.
Dan: Captain Clemente,
based on the findings
and recommendations
of the hearing officer,
it has been determined
that you are guilty
of misconduct
and abuse of office,
as charged.
As a result, it is my
decision that you be demoted.
Two ranks, to sergeant.
Two ranks?
That's extreme, sir.
No one's ever
been dropped two.
I'm gonna appeal.
That's your right.
Dismissed, Sergeant.
Gerry: You've fallen,
Jimmy boy.
Look at you, you're
going off the deep end!
Jimmy: Hey!
I've been hearing things,
Jimmy boy.
Using on duty?
Dealing drugs?
What? What?
Gotta spend money
to make money.
You're gonna get hit, man.
Who? Who's gonna hit me?
Just don't give up the bank!
Jimmy: The bank.
The bank!
First, I'm not gettin' near it.
And second, I don't care
anymore about the bank!
I got my own bank!
I got a snow bank.
A snow bank!
Yeah, I like that.
That's funny, huh?
A snow bank!
You can ski see up that sucker.
You see? Woo!
Ski right up that sucker!
It's a snow bank!
You're fried, man.
God, I don't know what's worse,
you flashin' coin
or dealin' drugs!
What do you want me to do, huh?
What do you expect?
We haven't seen a dime.
Not a dime
worth a penny! Nothin'!
Nothin' but excuses!
That's it!
(yells in frustration)
Hey, hey!
What? Why?
- How's business, Benny? Huh?
- Gerry!
- Shut up!
- (gun cock click)
You hear that, huh?
I want my cut Benny,
and I want it now!
- Now!
- Put the gun down, please!
Anything, anything you want!
Shut up!
I can't get you
your whole share,
you know
I can't get that much!
I'll take the jewels.
I'll take them.
I'll take the gold
straight up, uncut.
Benny: Looks it's still gonna
take time to get it, huh?
You know, I don't carry
that much with me!
(shouting) Come on!
Put the gun down.
Put the gun down. I'll get
you whatever you want.
(gun cock click)
(plastic rustling)
I don't know
what you said to Benny,
but it did the trick.
Just a taste, pal.
I'm outta here.
- Carl: It's junk, Gerry.
- What?
I'm sorry to tell you,
but it's pure junk!
Hey! Don't give me that, Carl!
I know that piece!
You may think
you recognize it.
That's 'cause it used to
be good at some point.
I can't get you a cent for this.
What are you--
I'm tellin' ya, a real expert's
picked this clean.
(sighs) I know
just the expert.
(sirens)
(crowd chatters)
Commissioner Kirkland
called me, what do you got?
Follow up on a
missing person, sir.
Benny Brown.
His wife called it in.
We found this blasting
equipment in the trunk.
FBI's on their way and they're
gonna wanna look it over.
This have something to do
with the Depositor's Trust?
Is that case still open?
Damn right it's open.
Charlie, run everything
you've got on a Benny Brown.
That stuff that Benny
laid on me was garbage, okay?
Gerry, that's what I'm
tryin' to tell you man!
Benny's gone!
- What?
- Jimmy: Disappeared!
He got out on bail
for this grass bust.
He had a court date,
but he didn't show.
He's vanished!
He's got a lot of enemies,
not just us.
Think somebody hit him? Huh?
Who? Frank?
I don't know, man.
But let's put it this way.
I think we can
forget about getting
any more shares off
of Benny, you know?
(slams phone)
Damn! Damn!
(office chatter)
(phone ringing)
(crash)
(screaming)
You all right, Sergeant?
(groaning) I don't think so.
I think I busted a rib.
Well, you can go to the
hospital if you want.
(coughs)
Freak accident?
I half figured him
pulling a number like that.
Ten to one sick
leave and pension.
At least it'll be
at a sergeant's rate.
You must be happy.
I'll only feel
really happy, Captain,
when I nail him on the bank job.
Sick leave agrees with ya.
You're looking good.
Doogie: Hey Ger!
You hear my theory
on Benny Brown?
He's layin' out flat
on the beach in Tahiti,
And next year,
when the statute's up,
it's the resurrection
of Benny Brown.
(sigh) Benny better stay dead
if he knows what's good for him.
Doing business with the IRA,
are we Jimmy, huh?
Just branchin' out a little.
Yeah.
(gun cock click)
I don't believe this.
We spent over four years
layin' low on that bank job.
We've got less
than 9 months to go
and you guys wanna deal
guns on top of drugs.
You wanna go and blow it all!
Well damn you, Jimmy Boy!
What are you, my mother?
(phone rings)
Yeah? Lay it on me.
What? That's the deal, man.
Listen to me, that's the deal!
You don't back out!
You blow this Jimmy,
I swear to God!
If I have to, I'll come down
there myself, you understand?
Yeah. Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, I'll move south.
You know what's going south?
Do you know what's going south?
I'll tell you
what's going south.
My money is what's going south!
You get it?
Now you tell me!
Jimmy: All I gotta do is
I gotta go down there
and I gotta find
out what's goin' on!
Man: Yeah?
I'll tell you what's going on.
They're trying to screw us!
They found another
source for their drugs.
And you blew it Jimmy!
You blew it!
You're an idiot!
Jake: Yeah?
You're gonna love this!
Mississippi State
Police just nailed
Jimmy Donnelly for drugs!
Medford Sergeant Donnelly?
- One and the same!
- Oh, boy. Oh, boy.
Just gets better!
Feds are onto him
for crossing state lines
with illegal firearms.
Gift from God.
With the right squeeze,
he could
cough up Gerry and the bank.
Keep me on top of this.
And one more thing.
Benny Brown.
That alarm man
who disappeared?
Yeah.
Turns out he was owners
in that bar of his
with a retired Metro
sergeant, Frank Moran.
Hypertension discharge.
Guy's really on the edge.
Check him out.
If we can link Frank to Gerry,
that could get us the bank.
Just a minute.
Gerry?
Yeah.
It's Frank Morran, he's
going crazy over something.
When's this gonna be over?
You said you'd quit!
Yeah? Tell me.
Damn! I knew this
was gonna happen!
Frank: I'm out Gerry!
See?
I'm outta pile.
Jimmy nailed me
good on this one.
That's my money that got burned
on that Mississippi deal.
That's mine!
And he owed me big!
Gerry: Well listen Frank,
Jimmy's out on bail.
He'll be back and
we'll work it out.
Oh yeah, right.
Sure, we're gonna
work it out, huh?
He's your friend, isn't he?
How come you're always
takin' up with him, huh?
You know somethin'?
I should never have moved
in across the street here.
What an idiot I am!
I'm payin' him rent,
and he owes me money!
Should never,
never have had anything
to do with that idiot!
Hey!
Sweetheart, I want
you to get upstairs.
Go. Upstairs.
Outta here.
We're talkin' business,
do you understand me?
Do you understand me?
Sherry: Yeah.
Look Frankie, I'm tellin' you
what I'm gonna tell Jimmy.
Now whichever way
this case works out
for either one of you guys,
don't give up the bank.
You understand what
I'm saying to you?
We've got less than eight
months and we're home free.
Oh, right, the bank.
Let me tell you somethin'.
The Feds get their
hooks into Jimmy,
he's gonna take us all down.
We gotta take him out.
Nobody takes anybody out.
He deals us, he's dead.
We stick together
or we fall apart.
Okay.
- (office noises)
- (chatter)
Well, Jimmy Donnelly's
a real hard case.
The good sergeant's not
talking about the bank.
We got a local snitch
that connects him
and the drugs to an
ex-cop here in town.
Used to be one of your men.
- Who?
- Frank Moran.
Jimmy: Said I'd get you
your money, Frank.
Jimmy. It's already
been two months, huh?
Make nice, Frankie!
You promised Gerry
you'd make nice!
- You want me to make nice, huh?
- Yeah.
(slap)
Hey, hey!
Don't you talk when
I'm doin' business,
- you understand me?
- Jimmy: Hey!
You understand me?
(Sherry laughs)
Back off.
Hey, you two wanna fight,
take it next door, huh?
And what's this Gerry business?
Gerry says you're gonna
give the Feds the bank.
He says you're gonna deal us.
Jimmy: Gerry says.
Gerry's a loser.
He's still got his bank pile
buried out in his backyard
like it's gonna
grow a money tree.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Well let's just
forget him, huh?
Now, I want my dough.
I mean it.
Do not push me.
You'll get your money.
Sherry: You'll get it, Frankie!
- Okay.
- Sherry: You're so smart.
You wanna play games,
don't ya sweetie?
Yeah.
Huh? You wanna play games?
Okay, we're gonna
play some games.
(gun cock click)
(Sherry gasps)
Frank! Back off.
Knock it off!
Frank.
Hey, what's this huh?
Come on.
I said you'd get
your money, huh?
Just need some time.
Just some time. Okay?
Okay, Jimmy.
Come on, sweet cheeks.
Get outta here.
(- giggles)
You got two days, Jimmy.
(ticking clock)
Jimmy: Hey Gerry, Frank's going
off the deep end and fast.
He's got some people
real mad at him, you know ?
Drug people.
Word's out something's
gonna be done about it.
Well people say
that all the time.
It don't mean anything, Jimmy.
Yeah, well.
I just thought you
ought to know.
Fair enough,
listen I gotta go.
I gotta get outta here.
Hey, Gerry.
We haven't seen
each other like pals,
you know, in a long time.
What do you say you
come by tonight, huh?
- Tonight?
- Yeah.
I don't think so.
Come on, what? Is it Mary?
Yeah. She's got me on
a short leash, you know.
Well, come by
after she's asleep.
Say, midnight.
Midnight?
It's a little late for a
civilian to be leavin' his wife.
Asleep or not.
Come on, we can talk.
We can go out and have
a couple of beers.
It'd be like old times, huh?
What do you say?
Gerry, listen.
Listen to me.
Just huh... call me first.
Around 11:30. Okay?
Yeah, Jimmy.
I'll call you.
I'll call you, all right?
Yeah.
Yeah, Jimmy.
Well, you sure as hell
better have it, pal.
(snorting)
Right. I said I'm
comin and I'm comin!
I'll see you in a minute, pal.
(snorting)
Jimmy said he's gonna get
me all bread tonight, huh?
(snorting)
He better not be lyin'.
Yeah.
(clock ticking)
(dog barking in the distance)
Hey Jimmy, I'm com in' up!
It's payout time!
Come on, pal (laughs).
Yes, sir, it's payoff ti--
(gasps)
- (gunshot)
- (groans)
(gun cock click)
(gunshot)
(groans)
(dog barks in the distance)
(Frank groans)
(sparks)
(drilling)
(explosion)
- (sparks)
- (crash)
- (crashing)
- (groaning)
Frank?
(Frank groans)
Oh, my God! Frank!
Gimme my gun!
Sherry: Please!
Someone's been shot!
- Operator: How bad?
- He's dying!
Operator: Address?
17 Pleasant Street.
Hurry please!
- Frank!
- Frank: Huh?
Frank, it's all right!
It's gonna be all right,
I called the police.
Huh?
- Yeah, I called the police!
- Frank: What?
- It's gonna be all right!
- Frank: You called the cops?
Yeah.
What are you,
are you outta your mind?
Called the cops.
Eight more months.
Eight more
months.
Cop: Police!
Come on! Don't get crazy!
Cop: Comin' up!
Go, go, go!
Let's go, let's go.
(police radio chatter)
(phone keyboard tapping)
(phone rings)
Quiet!
Jimmy!
Jimmy, is that you?
(dial tone)
(ticking)
(phone rings)
Hello? Hello?
Mr. Clemente?
This is Nurse Hankins
at Surgeon's Hospital.
We have a patient
here who's made
an urgent request to see you.
I'm here to see a patient,
Frank Moran.
Mr. Clemente?
Mm-hmm.
I spoke with you.
I'm sorry, but you can only
see him for 10 minutes.
Room 142.
(groaning)
Frank, Frank!
What happened here?
Gerry, you scared
the hell outta me.
What the hell happened to--
Oh, man, they told me
it was gunshot wounds.
Gunshot wounds nothin'.
Come on, sit, come on.
I got shot through
in two loads.
- What?
- Frank: Yeah.
Easy, easy, there you go.
If I wouldn't have
been so loaded myself,
I'd be dead right now.
They had to pinch
an artery right here.
Oh, man.
Damn Jimmy.
- Jimmy did this?
- Frank: Yeah!
Yeah. Jimmy tried to stroke me!
He tried to
take me out last night!
Why?
Frank: Drugs. Money.
Million reasons in that
fried out brain of his,
none of which makes any sense!
(coughs) Sherry...
Sherry called the cops, Gerry.
Oh, this is bad, man.
- This is bad.
- Frank: You're telling me?
You know, they got Jimmy
on that Mississippi deal.
And Quinn's got him
for attempted murder,
dead their rights.
Quinn, Quinn, Quinn.
Yeah, Quinn.
Quinn was right on it,
like he knew somethin'
was gonna pop.
Jimmy's gonna give up
the Depositor's Trust.
He's gonna bargain
the shooting and the drug bust
and we're both
gonna go down, man!
You're damn right.
Soon as I can get up
I'm outta here like,
(coughs) like a shot!
Jimmy's gonna sell
us down the tubes!
- Hey, easy!
- (Frank coughs violently)
Take it easy,
it'll be all right.
No, no it's okay!
There, there.
Hey man, what's this?
A wire?
You're wearing a wire?
(groans)
You gave the bank to Quinn.
Jimmy tried to kill me, man.
He's your pal.
He was your pal!
You set me up, man!
I'm not gonna let
you guys sandbag me.
No way!
I'm not goin' down!
I'm not goin' down for you!
I'm not goin' down for nobody!
I'm gettin' off for everything.
(gun cock click)
Go ahead.
Let the cards fall
where they may.
(gun cock click)
(Frank coughs)
(spits) You go to hell!
Yeah? See you there!
Freeze!
Okay, all right.
Easy, easy. Easy!
You're under arrest, Gerry,
For the burglary of the
Depositor's Trust Bank.
What are you kiddin' me?
You got no proof.
Frank's a co-conspirator!
It ain't gonna stick, Jake.
You have the right
to remain silent,
you have the right
to an attorney--
Let it rest, will ya?
I know it by heart.
I'm a cop remember?
You wore a badge, Gerry.
You were never a cop.
(jail doors clanging shut)
Jake: His fate
remains unknown.