[*****]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[KIDS LAUGHING]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[CLATTERING]
GEORGIA: The supplies
for the shelter
will be picked up next Saturday
between the hours
of 9:00 and 12:00.
Make sure someone's home.
And Ellie,
I know from experience
that sometimes
you don't hear the doorbell
when you're working
in your garden.
Well, my garden is my sanctuary.
Fiddlesticks.
You stay in next Saturday
and needlepoint.
Well, yes, ma'am.
Last order of business,
the Peach Gala Dinner.
The RSVPs are pouring in,
and I think we are going to have
a bigger turn-out
than last year.
ELLEN: Last year
we didn't have the governor
of Georgia in attendance.
Oh, last year
we didn't have a lot of things
we're going to have this year,
thanks
to my gracious sister-in-law,
Miss Madeleine Porter,
and her generous donation
of her lovely home
for the evening.
Well, it's the least I could do
for such a worthy cause.
Ellen, put that foul thing out.
You told Jack you'd quit.
-I did quit. Just now.
-[GEORGIA CHUCKLING]
Georgia, please tell me
you are considering
taking a date to the gala.
I am going to be working
that room for donations.
I just won't have any time
for entertaining a date.
My God, Georgia,
it's been a year.
It's time you get back
in the game.
MADELEINE:
Loosen your belts, girls.
Here comes Georgia's apple pie.
Betty, be careful
with that dish.
It belonged
to Georgia's great-grandmother.
Yes, ma'am.
She maintains that a pie
in that dish
was made superior
by its age and experience.
-There goes my diet.
-What diet?
The one I fully intend to start
as soon as you quit
your smoking.
[CHUCKLES]
ANSWERING MACHINE:
You have one message.
Message one.
Wednesday, 11:13 a.m.
JANE: Mrs. Porter,
this is Jane Cramer.
I'm a patient representative
at San Diego General Hospital.
I found your number
in your daughter's purse.
She's been in an accident.
Please call me as soon
as you get this message.
JANE: It's a matter
of some urgency.
I can be reached
at extension 216.
[*****]
WOMAN ON PA: ...to Atlanta
and connecting to...
GEORGIA: I love you, Lily-Joe.
LILY-JOE: I love you
to the stars and back.
GEORGIA: I love you
to the stars and back
-and around the moon. [LAUGHING]
-[LILY-JOE LAUGHING]
Well, I love you
to the stars, back,
and around the moon
and to the last corner
of the universe.
GEORGIA: Me too, babe.
[CHUCKLING]
Night, mama.
Roses on your pillow.
GEORGIA: Roses on your pillow.
Ma'am, you're boarding.
-All right.
-[INDISTINCT CHATTER ON PA]
WOMAN: Ma'am,
you're boarding pass, please?
[SIREN WAILING]
JANE: Mrs. Porter?
-I'm Jane Cramer. I called you.
-GEORGIA: How is she?
Dr. Peterson would like
to talk to you.
Well, I'd like to see
my daughter first.
He should be here any minute.
It just took forever
getting here,
but I was very lucky to--
to be able to get
a plane right away.
Mrs. Porter, it would really
be better if you waited.
Why?
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
[GEORGIA GASPING]
How bad is she?
The nurse wouldn't tell me.
I'm sorry.
-Oh.
-Massive internal injuries.
GEORGIA: Oh, no.
[CRYING]
No.
No, I don't believe it.
-That's a lie. No, no.
-[DR. PETERSON SHUSHING]
-DR. PETERSON: It's okay.
-Oh, oh, God!
GEORGIA: No, no, please...
No, not my baby. [SOBBING]
DR. PETERSON: We thought
it would be best
-if you told the child.
-[SOBS]
The child?
DR. PETERSON: Don't worry,
she's fine.
The fact that she was belted in
probably saved her.
Except for a few cuts
and bruises
we expect her to fully recover.
What do you say? Uh...
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
DR. PETERSON:
She's just down here.
NURSE: Doctor,
can you take a look at this?
I'll be right in.
Hi.
That's a nice elephant
you got there.
Mrs. Porter...
we're over here.
Excuse me.
DR. PETERSON: Jacey.
I brought you a visitor.
[TELEPHONE RINGING]
Don't worry about her arm.
She has a few stitches,
but I don't expect
they'll leave a scar.
I'll leave you two to talk.
Doctor?
I don't understand.
DR. PETERSON: What?
Who is this child?
I-- isn't she
your granddaughter?
Well, I haven't talked
to my daughter
in over nine years.
We had a falling out.
She's a black child.
DR. PETERSON: Well, her--
her father was African-American.
Your daughter's husband.
He died at the scene.
I'm sorry.
I thought you knew that.
[PAGER BEEPING]
We pulled the child's records.
You were the only relative
we were able to contact.
You can take her home tomorrow.
Take her?
DR. PETERSON: Well, yes.
If you don't,
she'll be put in foster care.
She needs to be close
to someone right now.
She doesn't remember anything
about the accident.
But at some point she will,
and she'll need to have--
-[BEEPER BEEPING]
-I'm sorry.
I have to go.
I'll be back as soon as I can.
Hi.
I'm thirsty.
GEORGIA: Here you are.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
[*****]
Your name is Jacey.
It's a pretty name.
Very southern.
Howard Binkman
calls me J.C. Penny.
A boy teases you
it means he likes you.
Your mother...
what's her name?
Lily-Joe.
[*****]
And your father?
Marcus P. Hastings.
Oh, my God.
What time is it when an elephant
sits on a fence?
Time to get a new fence.
I was a nurse once
for Halloween
when I was little.
Oh, I'm not a nurse, honey.
Then what are you?
Your mother, Lily-Joe...
Your mother is my daughter.
Uh-huh. That's not true.
I would know you already.
You would be my grandma.
Well, I live in Georgia.
That's pretty far from here.
Did your mother
ever say anything
about growing up in Georgia?
A farm?
-School?
-I want my mom.
-Can you get my mom?
-GEORGIA: Honey.
Your mama...
and your daddy, uh...
There was a...
There was a terrible accident.
No.
-No.
-Uh, honey,
it's going to be okay.
-Mommy. Daddy.
-It's going to be okay.
-JACEY: Go away. Mommy.
-Honey...
-Daddy. Come back, Mommy.
-Honey... Please, Mommy, Daddy.
-[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
-I'm so sorry.
-JACEY: Please come back.
[JACEY CRYING]
I'm sorry.
[*****]
[CAR APPROACHING]
JOE: You stay right here.
Let-- go of me.
GEORGIA: Joe.
No, no, come on home, Joe.
Come on.
-JOE: Stay in the car, Georgia.
-Come on.
JOE: Get back.
Just stay put, Georgia.
[DOG BARKING]
-GEORGIA: Joe.
-[GUN COCKS]
[GUNSHOTS]
[*****]
JACEY: Mama.
WOMAN ON PA: May I have
your attention, please?
This is the final boarding call
for flight 710 to Atlanta.
-Passengers...
-GEORGIA: Honey,
won't you take a little sip
of this?
You haven't had anything
all day.
How about a little chocolate?
I never hear a child
who didn't like chocolate.
I'm allergic to chocolate.
I'll throw up.
Really? I'm sorry.
WOMAN ON PA: Can I have
your attention, please?
-This the final warning call...
-That's not heaven.
GEORGIA: Oh, no, you're right.
That isn't heaven.
Heaven is hidden from us.
It's-- in the last corner
of the universe.
Why?
Well, um,
maybe it's just so beautiful
that we'd want to go live there
before our time.
[*****]
[KIDS LAUGHING]
GEORGIA: This is it.
This is Sweet Creek.
This is where your mother
grew up.
You've come at a good time
when the hydrangeas
are still blooming.
-DRIVER: Here you go, ma'am.
-GEORGIA: Thank you.
All right, here we are.
I'mma arrange to have
all your things sent here.
JACEY: Why is it so hot?
GEORGIA: Well, honey,
this is the south.
We just have more sun here.
Pretty soon it'll seem
just like home.
[KIDS TALKING INDISTINCTLY]
-ALL: Surprise.
-[GEORGIA CHUCKLING]
-Welcome home.
-GEORGIA: My word.
MADELEINE: Now where
is that grand-niece of mine?
[CHUCKLES]
-GEORGIA: Jacey.
-[LAUGHS]
Oh.
GEORGIA: I told my friends
about you
so they planned
a little welcome home surprise.
These are my friends.
These are the Georgia Peaches.
[CHUCKLES] Welcome
to Sweet Creek, honey.
JACEY: Thank you.
MADELEINE: Hello, Jacey.
It's nice to meet you.
You know you look
just like your mother except...
Except your eyes are brown
and your mother's were blue.
Why, you have
your grandma's eyes.
-[ELLEN CHUCKLING]
-GEORGIA: Come on, honey,
I'll show you to your room
right up the stairs from me.
GEORGIA: You know, this room
used to be your mama's room.
She helped me make
this very quilt.
Uh, oh, look at this.
Wow!
Well, I think the Peaches
must have just--
Just bought out every store,
just for you.
Is your arm hurting you, honey?
Is...
Well, don't-- don't you worry.
We'll go down Monday
and have the doctor
take a look
at those old stitches.
You must be worn out.
You know... [EXHALES DEEPLY]
...I never was able to--
to put your mama's clothes
away.
But it's time now.
I'm going to clean out
this closet,
and it's going to be
just for you.
Oh, my God.
Georgia,
why didn't you tell us?
[SIGHS] I...
I just didn't know what to say.
I still can't believe
this whole thing has happened.
They were going to put her
in foster care.
Are you sure she's Lily's?
Well, of course she's Lily's.
She's the spitting image of her.
Well, there must be someone
who can take her.
Take her where?
She's Georgia's grandchild.
A child is always a blessing.
[*****]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
GEORGIA: Honey?
Honey, are you in here?
Oh, come on, sweetheart.
[GRUNTING]
Come on. Let's go to beddy.
There, there.
Upsie-daisy.
Here.
Roses on your pillow.
[*****]
JOE: I'm only giving you
one more minute
and then I am coming in there
after you.
[GUN COCKING]
LOU: Joe, what the hell
you doing?
JOE: I'm going to give
that boy of yours what for.
LOU: Marcus, get back
in the house.
-MARCUS: Dad.
-LOU: Get back in the house.
Take that gun off my boy, Joe.
Look at you... [LAUGHS]
...drunk as a skunk.
-Put the gun down.
-Just get out of my face, Lou.
-Get out--- get out
of the way, Lou.
-LOU: Put the gun down.
-JOE: You-- Maybe you need
a whooping too.
-GEORGIA: Joe...
[GROANS]
-GEORGIA: Oh!
-MARCUS: Stop it.
LILY-JOE: What do you want, Dad?
You want me, Dad?
-Fine.
-Joe, this is crazy. Come on.
Fine. You kill us both.
-She is coming home
with us tonight.
-No, you're not--
-I promise you that.
-[GEORGIA GROANS]
-MARCUS: Mrs. Porter.
-I won't ever come home
while you're still alive.
-[GUN COCKS]
-GEORGIA: No.
No. Go, go in the house.
JOE: Georgia, get
in the car now.
Mama, don't go with him.
-Don't go with him.
-JOE: Georgia, get
in this car now.
-MARCUS: Stay here.
Stay here with us.
-[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
-JOE: In this car.
-[GEORGIA GRUNTING]
You just better pray
she comes home.
-[GEORGIA GROANING]
-LILY-JOE: Mother, mother.
GEORGIA: No, I'm all right.
I'm all right.
-Mother.
-[CAR DOOR CLOSING]
LILY-JOE: Mom. Mother.
JACEY: Mommy. [CRYING]
Mommy.
Mommy. Daddy.
Daddy. [CRYING]
-Honey, honey, no.
-[CRIES]
Oh, it's all right.
It's all right.
I'm here. I'm here.
* My baby buys me... *
* Daddy's gonna love it *
No, she's still sleeping.
She must be exhausted,
poor thing.
I'm making all
of her mother's favorite dishes.
-[DOORBELL RINGING]
-Shoot, there's the doorbell.
It must be the man
from the shelter.
Madeleine, I'll call you
right back.
Good morning.
Uh, the box is right at the side
of the house.
You want to be real careful
with it
because there are some
good dishes.
You know, don't let them slide.
Is there a problem?
Where's your truck?
JACEY: Grandpa.
GEORGIA: Oh.
It's okay, little bear,
I'm here now.
Everything's going
to be just fine.
-Mommy and Daddy are gone.
-I know. I know.
[*****]
[JACEY SOBBING]
LOU: I was away
or I would have been here
much sooner.
-You don't remember me, do you?
-GEORGIA: No.
I mean, yes, of course.
You're Marcus's father.
I'm-- I'm sorry.
I thought you were
from the homeless shelter.
Of course you did.
Are you ready?
-JACEY: Mm-hmm.
-Okay.
Ready for what?
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
I'm taking Jacey home...
where she belongs.
[*****]
GEORGIA: Well, you do realize
she just got here.
We haven't had a chance to get
to know each other at all.
Grandpa, I want to go home.
I know you do.
Hey, if you go over there
on the porch
there's a pre-birthday present
there for you.
-It's right over there.
-Okay.
[LOU EXHALING DEEPLY]
Oh. Yes, please.
I bet you didn't know
she existed, did you?
-No.
-LOU: Yeah.
Lily and Marcus didn't want you
or your husband
to have anything to do
with that child.
My husband died over a year ago.
Oh, sorry, for the loss.
He's perfect, Grandpa.
I love him so much.
-So, what's his name?
-[MEOWS]
-Mm, Smoky.
-Smoky? Another Smoky?
-Smoky Number Two.
-Hey, Smoky Number Two.
Well, she's just cute as a bug.
You like cats?
Uh, Jacey was a cat
in her last life.
I see.
-I guess I have a lot to learn.
-LOU: Yeah
What happened
to Smoky Number One?
-Grandpa, I'm hungry.
-GEORGIA: I-- I cooked.
I, uh, I cooked chicken and rice
-and some--
-I want your food, Grandpa.
LOU: Okay.
No, you take Smoky Number Two
out and play,
and I'll make you something
very, very special.
-Okay.
-All right.
[CAT MEOWING]
May I?
Of course.
-This is it.
-[SIZZLING]
Ah.
Milk?
-Here you are.
-Hmm.
[SIGHS] Just
because I'm curious,
how did you ever expect
to raise a black child
here in Sweet Creek?
-Well, she's only half black.
-Well...
and this is the south.
One drop of black blood
makes you black for life.
You ought to know that better
than I do.
-You know things are changing.
-[GRUNTS]
This town is as progressive as--
When was the last time
you had a black man here
in your kitchen?
I hardly think that's pertinent.
I mean, you've probably
never had a black man
in your house at all,
unless he was
in here fixing something.
Why don't you pack up
her things.
I'll take her away
this afternoon.
I am sorry, but...
you can't take her.
I won't allow it.
You don't have a choice.
I have been appointed
her legal guardian
in their will.
Lily and Marcus left Jacey
to me.
Jacey will never be raised here
in Sweet Creek.
Jacey, the rice pudding
is almost ready.
-[CAT MEOWS]
-Mm.
[LAUGHS]
I would like to take her
to the doctor Monday morning.
I told her I would be with her
when the stitches came out.
I want to do this one thing
with her.
If I may.
All right. I got some business
to attend to here
in Sweet Creek.
We'll leave Monday afternoon
for San Diego.
Thank you for that.
I'll be at that motel
on Cherry Street.
Little bear,
-I will see you tomorrow.
-JACEY: No.
-GEORGIA: I'll make supper.
-That'll be fine.
-Give me a hug. Give me a hug.
-No.
-[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
-JACEY: No.
LOU: Okay. Go ahead.
Jacey, come on.
Let's us girls go shopping.
Bye, Grandpa.
-Come on, honey.
-[CAT MEOWING]
I know a place we can get
a beautiful new dress
for church tomorrow.
Why do I have to take a bath
in the day?
GEORGIA: Because it's Sunday,
and because you're a girl,
and girls should smell sweet
at church.
Oh, I love this shampoo.
It smells just like coconuts
from Hawaii.
I got it out
of a Hawaiian catalog
called Aloha Shopper.
[GRUNTING]
See. [GRUNTING]
[GROANS] Coconut hurts my eyes.
-That's not how Mommy does it.
-Oh, here. I'm sorry.
Just a little more water.
-I want mommy
-I know.
So do I.
[CHURCH BELL TOLLING]
[*****]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
-Gotcha.
-[GROANS]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
All right, honey, um,
bow your head.
Dear Lord, we thank you
for your blessings.
Help us to be worthy
of your love.
We pray for Lily-Joe
and Marcus,
and we know they're with you.
They're part of your flock,
but they will be in our hearts
forever.
And thank you
for sending me Jacey.
-Amen.
[*****]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
LOU: Put your head there,
right up against this post now.
Well, let's see
what we got here.
I think this is going
to be a world record.
My goodness, look at that.
You have gained
three and a half inches
since the last time
we measured.
Boy, what have you been eating?
Huh?
[CAR DOOR CLOSING]
-Morning.
-Stop, you're hurting me.
-GEORGIA: Well, I'm sorry.
I just can't get through
this comb to work. Never mind.
-Hi, Betty.
-BETTY: Hello, Mrs. Porter.
And who's this sweet thing?
This is Jacey. My...
-Jacey, you want to shake hands.
-BETTY: Well, hello, Jacey.
Aren't you a pretty girl?
And how old are you?
-Six and three quarters.
-BETTY: Really?
Betty, I need to talk to
Mr. and Mrs. Porter for a bit.
Could you just keep an eye
on her for me?
Oh, yes, ma'am.
I could use the company.
Come on with me.
I was just thinking of having
an ice cold lemonade.
-Would you like some?
-Yes, please.
Larry, thanks so much
for talking to me on Sunday.
I know this is your golf day.
Georgia, please, you're family.
Now this here document
gives him full legal custody.
This kind of thing
is hard to fight.
But I am her grandmother.
Well, maybe
it's the best thing for her,
for the child.
She does know him.
They do have a bond.
I mean, maybe she'll do better
being raised by her own.
She's Lily-Joe's daughter.
See, we just think
it may be easier.
Georgia, honey,
we want what's best for you.
Now this may be the way
out of this whole mess.
You know how my brother
would have felt.
I'm not interested
in how Joe would have felt.
Thank you very much.
Oh, that looks darling.
-Thank you, Betty.
-Yes, ma'am.
Now come on.
We better get going.
You know, I could teach you
to do her hair.
Oh, I appreciate that, Betty.
-JACEY: It's just hair.
-Well, I know.
You know she favors you.
-You think so?
-BETTY: She's got your eyes.
Well, her grandfather's
taking her back to California.
Hmm.
Sweet Creek's
an old-fashioned town
with old-fashioned ideas.
That sure would be easier
if easier is what you're after.
-I guess.
-BOTH: Bye-bye.
-GEORGIA: Thanks again.
-Bye, Jacey.
Have a great day.
GEORGIA: How would you like
to go to the park?
They've got
a real nice swing there.
You know,
I haven't been swinging
for one, two, three, four--
a hundred years.
-JACEY: Uh-huh.
-Uh-huh.
Pump your legs in and out,
in and out.
I know how to swing.
I'm almost seven.
You surely do.
[*****]
GEORGIA: You know,
your mama used to like to swing
right up to the stars
-and try to touch the moon.
-JACEY: That stuff's for babies.
Swings don't really go
that high.
GEORGIA: Well,
maybe not in California.
But you don't have
the bilateral gravitational pull
we have down here in the south.
-Really?
-Uh-huh, sure.
Okay, now lean back.
Take a deep breath.
-Count to ten
as fast as you can.
-One, two, three, four, five,
-six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
-Close your eyes, and take off.
You're right.
I can see the moon.
GEORGIA: Of course I am.
Grandmothers know everything.
JACEY: Higher.
[LAUGHS]
JACEY: I can see the moon.
You know, having you here
in the summers
is not such a new idea.
Your mother used to spend
summers with her grandmother.
Maybe next summer you
and I could some time--
On the farm with the chickens
and the cows?
GEORGIA: Yeah.
You know about the farm?
-JACEY: And the fountain's
outside.
-Huh.
And you have to get up
real early to milk the cows.
[CHUCKLES] Goodness.
Now, you know more
about this family
than I realized.
Were you very sick?
No, I'm healthy as a horse, why?
Well, mommy said...
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
Why don't we get us
some ice cream?
Mommy doesn't let me
have ice cream before lunch.
GEORGIA: Oh,
she's absolutely right.
You shouldn't have ice cream
before lunch.
No, uh,
that was a terrible idea.
But I have something here.
I have something right here.
Did you know
that saltine crackers
are filled up with most
of the food groups
that the FDA requires
for a healthy lunch?
Good lunch.
-Very good.
-[CHUCKLES]
Let's go get some ice cream.
Of course,
we'll finish our lunch
before we get the ice cream.
-[*****]
-[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[WATER LAPPING]
-GEORGIA: Thank you.
-And three boys rub the bottle,
and the genie pops out.
And the genie says
he'll give each boy one wish.
The first boy wished
to be smart,
and the genie says, "Poof,
you're smart."
The second boy wished to be
smarter than the first boy,
and the genie says, "Poof,
you're smarter
than the first boy."
And the third boy wished
to be smarter
than the other two.
And the genie says, "Poof,
you're a girl."
[LAUGHS]
You're pretty funny.
I'm going to have write
that one down.
Daddy says ice cream
has too much sugar.
Your daddy was a smart man.
He knows about all the foods.
You have to know which foods
to keep from getting sick.
That's right.
Did he work in the market?
No, he's a pharmacist.
He gives you medicine
when you get too sick.
A pharmacist.
Well, how about your mama?
Did she work there, too?
[CLICKS TONGUE] No.
She goes to school like me.
To school.
What did she study?
Sad people.
-GEORGIA: Hi, baby.
-Hi.
Grandpa won't eat pie.
More for you and me.
* Tick tack
Right in the dough *
* Mama bakes a pie
For Lily-Joe *
Your mother taught you that?
Yeah.
-[DOORBELL RINGING]
-Grandpa's here.
[SIGHS]
JACEY: Can I please have some
more milk?
Well, that depends.
Are you able?
May I please have
some more milk?
You certainly may.
There you go.
-Thank you.
-LOU: You're welcome.
[INHALES DEEPLY]
Jacey tells me your son
was a pharmacist.
Yeah, uh, he got his degree
at UCLA.
GEORGIA: And Lily
was a student?
Jacey said that she
was studying sad people.
Oh, she was just finishing
her studies in psychology.
GEORGIA: Really?
I always hoped she'd go
to the University of Georgia
when she graduated
from high school.
Hmm.
Uh, this is a fine dinner.
We-- we baked a pie, but Jacey
says you won't eat it.
No, I'm not much on deserts.
GEORGIA: Oh, honey,
Dr. Diamond called,
and he's going to take
those old stitches out
-tomorrow morning at 11:00 a.m.
-LOU: Dr. Diamond.
Is he still practicing
medicine?
One would think he'd be
retired by now.
No, he's still going strong.
You know Dr. Diamond?
[LAUGHS]
Baby, he saved
your father's life
the day he was born.
-Really?
-LOU: Yeah, yeah.
No other doctors would come
and visit us.
And hospital said
it wouldn't admit patients
who, uh, weren't pre-registered.
We didn't have time
to go to County General.
So your father was born
in the parking lot
-of Mercy Hospital.
-Why?
LOU: Because Black people
were not allowed
in the white hospital.
GEORGIA: That is absolutely
not true.
And I don't think
that it is fair
for you to fill
this child's head
with-- with negative hateful
stories about the south.
[SCOFFS] You're right.
Don't need to at all.
Especially since we're leaving
tomorrow afternoon.
Why don't we have coffee
in the living room?
Are you ready, mademoiselle?
[WATER RUNNING]
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
LOU: Hi.
I put her to bed.
I hope you don't mind.
-No.
-She loves books.
You know,
when she was a baby,
I started her off
on fairy tales,
now we're moving on up
to classics. [CHUCKLES]
You remember your first
fairy tale?
Oh, yes, Cinderella.
My mother must have read
it to me a hundred times.
I remember my first
fairy tale,
I was about Jacey's age,
about six.
Kindergarten teacher
read it to us
on the first day of school.
Little Black Sambo.
[SCOFFS] Is this how you intend
to raise her?
Just filling her up
with hate and fear?
That's part of history.
A part you don't want
to look at.
Now, look, I don't have time
for this.
We're leaving tomorrow,
we only have time for the truth.
GEORGIA: Well, the truth is,
I would be the better choice
to raise her.
Why, because you're white
or because you're a woman?
-I am simply more appropriate.
-[GRUNTS]
[GEORGIA GROANING]
I know you hated my husband.
He was unspeakable
to you and to your son.
But I am not my husband,
and I would appreciate it
if you would not treat me
as if I were.
He held a gun
to my son's head that night,
and you could have stopped him.
-You think that?
-I will take Jacey out of here
and away from people like you,
and there's nothing
you can do about it.
-You know what Jacey's
handicap is?
-LOU: What?
It's you,
and that hostile wall
that you hide behind
to cover your own inadequacies.
I may be inadequate,
but I didn't chase my only child
out of my life.
[*****]
[DOOR OPENING, CLOSING]
GEORGIA: Jacey, breakfast.
Honey? Breakfast.
-What are you doing, baby?
-I'm trying to look like Mommy.
Oh.
Well, honey,
you do look like Mommy.
But mostly you look
just like you.
I'm sorry I don't have
the same skin
as you and Mommy.
Why would you say
something like that?
Because we're going so far away.
And Grandpa said
it would be easier for you
to remember me
if I had white skin.
[SNIFFLES, SIGHS]
Well, your grandpa is wrong.
I would never forget you.
Never in a million years.
You're my grandbaby,
you hear me?
Mommy told me her mom
was too sick
to be a grandma.
[INHALES DEEPLY]
Well, maybe I was.
But I'm getting better.
It sure was nice
getting to know you,
even if just for a little bit.
Maybe you'll come see me
sometime.
JACEY: Maybe.
GEORGIA: Let's see now,
seven, six, here we are.
Mr. Hastings, are you in there?
[CHUCKLES]
Maybe he went to breakfast
or something.
Let's go see.
Oh, my God. Help!
Help! We need some help here!
-WOMAN: Yes, ma'am.
-GEORGIA: Can you unlock
this door, please?
WOMAN: Yes, ma'am.
-Oh. Come on.
-WOMAN: I'll get
the manager, ma'am.
OPERATOR: 911,
what is your emergency?
-This is an emergency.
-OPERATOR: Yes.
Please send an ambulance
to the motel on Cherry Street.
Is Grandpa sick again?
Again?
Honey, he's been sick before?
OPERATOR: Ma'am?
Ma'am, this is 911.
How can I help you, ma'am?
DR. ROSE: Hi, I'm Dr. Rose.
Are you here with Mr. Hastings?
-Yes.
-DR. ROSE: He's going
to be fine.
He took too much insulin,
and his blood sugar got too low.
But we managed to revive
him rather quickly.
-He's a diabetic?
-Yes. I thought you knew that.
Well, then,
he isn't a drug addict.
No. We can't release him alone.
He's not very
well-controlled right now.
And he has a severe foot ulcer.
And he told us he was
in a California hospital
for treatment,
but he checked out
a few days ago.
-Mm. To come here.
-Yeah.
Well, his kidneys and heart
are doing fine right now.
But we've got to get
his sugars under control.
The important thing
is keeping his wound clean
and medicated
or he could lose his foot.
GEORGIA: My word.
-Does your foot hurt?
-No, I don't feel a thing.
-How are you?
-Oh, I'm fine.
Now, this never happens,
you know, except for the travel
and the stress and me
not being careful,
it'll never happen again.
And I still plan
to take little Jacey
back to San Diego.
I called over
to the resident care center.
I'm going to have you moved
over there tomorrow.
Thank you. Two weeks.
That's all I need.
Then I'll get home get back
on my schedule and everything's
going to be better.
[INHALES SHARPLY]
Come here, little bear.
You are gonna have to stay
with your grandma for a while
until I get better, okay?
-No, you can stay with us
in my room.
-Oh, no, no, no.
-I'll take care of you.
-I can't do that.
-Why not?
-No, I just can't.
I want to be with you.
Please don't leave me with her.
No, no. Listen to me now.
Listen to me.
Time is going to fly by so fast.
[CHUCKLES]
You'll stay with us.
Until you're on your feet.
Jacey wants you nearby,
and I want what Jacey wants.
I don't think
that that would be possible.
Why? Because I'm a woman
or because I'm white?
You're kidding me, right?
You're going to have
that man living with you
in your home?
Are you crazy?
Madeleine, she lost both
her mother and her father.
She can't lose him too.
Oh, my God, Georgia.
Send him a card.
Make him a pie.
You don't invite a man
like that into your home.
A man like what?
Don't you play games
with me.
You are a single woman
living alone
in a town that has
-formalities and traditions.
-Well, the hell with the town.
I-- I got to do what's right
for her.
It's one thing to have
a beautiful Black baby
living in your house.
It's another to have
a fully-grown Black man
sleeping under your roof.
And you have a choice here.
No, I don't have a choice.
I need to do what's best
for Jacey.
[FLIES BUZZING]
-LOU: Now, this is your room.
-Yes, it is.
This is not right.
I need to find another room.
All the rest of the bedrooms
are upstairs.
This room is perfect.
The bathroom is right
across the hall.
-It'll be easier for you.
-I won't take your room.
It's already done.
I moved all my things upstairs
so that I can be closer
to Jacey.
You will stay in here,
and there's nothing
you can do about it.
I think she's mad at you.
[*****]
[CHUCKLES]
-MIDGE: Hey, Mrs. Porter.
-[BARKS]
-GEORGIA: Hi, Max.
-MIDGE: Oh. oops, I better go.
I don't think that Max
likes Smoky Number Two
very much.
He just needs to get
to know her.
Mommy said that animals
think they hate
different animals,
but they're just afraid to love
what they don't know.
[MEOWS]
Your mama was a smart cookie.
-[DOOR KNOCKING]
-Come in.
Supper is served.
It's early,
but we Southern ladies
supper early in the south.
-[LAUGHS]
-Absolutely right.
Now you remember you was born
and raised in California.
-I made the rice and the salad.
-Mm.
Don't eat the slimy stuff.
GEORGIA: Oh, your grandpa
was raised down here.
I bet he just loves okra.
[SCOFFS] I may have
grown up here,
but you're right,
that okra is a vile substitute
for a vegetable.
-[LAUGHS]
-GEORGIA: Honey,
why don't you run
and get the salt and pepper?
I forgot 'em.
Look, if this little charade
is an attempt to coerce me
into letting Jacey stay here
in Sweet Creek,
you're wrong.
I'm going to fight you
all the way.
I know. You have told me
several times.
You know, I am trying
to be civil
in a very
uncomfortable situation.
I would appreciate it
if you would extend me
-the same courtesy.
-Look, you and I,
we may have grown up here,
but we come
from different worlds.
GEORGIA: Mr. Hastings,
you just lost your son,
and I just lost my daughter.
We live in the same world
whether we like it or not.
LOU: Mrs. Porter...
tomorrow's Jacey's birthday.
Now, Lily used to make
her a cake.
Now, will you get her
one tomorrow, please?
-No chocolate.
-Makes her throw up. I know.
-Thank you.
-GEORGIA: You're welcome.
You roll on over there.
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
Why do you have stars up there?
Those are your mother's stars.
You know, there's one there
for every year of her life.
Your mama just loved stars.
Do you think Mommy and Daddy
miss me as much as I miss them?
No, ma'am, I do not.
I think your mother and father
are right here watching
over you.
They're making sure
you're happy,
and they're making sure
you're not eating
too much ice cream.
So, you just better go to sleep
and give them some rest.
[*****]
Roses on your pillow.
Roses on your pillow, honey.
[CHUCKLES]
LOU: Feminine Mystique.
The Woman's Struggle
Against Man.
Alone and Happy.
No, no, no, no.
A Woman's Guide.
Hmm.
"There is a warrior
in every one of us.
A woman will call
on her warrior
or let her sleep."
[*****]
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
What am I doing here?
GEORGIA: Meet your approval?
It's just fine.
Yeah, it's not bad.
I called Madeleine
this morning,
and I asked her to invite
her grandchildren over
to the Georgia Peach meeting.
That way Jacey will meet
some friends,
and then I'll invite them
back here for cake
-and ice cream later.
-Just what is a Georgia Peach?
They're, uh, a group
of women volunteers.
Currently we're putting
on a dinner to raise money
-for the homeless shelter.
-LOU: Hmm.
Well, Lily volunteered
for the battered woman shelter
-in San Diego.
-Did she?
LOU: Mm.
Thank you for telling me.
-Thank you for the cake.
-[INHALES] I did it for Jacey.
-BETTY: Hello, Jacey.
Hello, Mrs. Porter.
-GEORGIA: Hi.
-How are you, Betty?
-Hello, Jacey. Happy birthday.
JACEY: Thank you.
Oh, she's so excited
to be meeting
your grandchildren.
I'm so sorry,
but the girls couldn't come.
-They have the sniffles.
-Aw.
All three of them?
That's too bad.
Well, Jacey,
you're just going to have to be
a Georgia Peach today.
You sit right beside me
and all my good friends.
MADELEINE: Well, I think
we should move
right to the first order
of business.
I spoke to the caterer,
and she said
that the three main orders
would be more than enough
so that we should cancel
the caviar and toast.
Now right there
we'll save 800 dollars.
GEORGIA: Wonderful.
Oh, my word,
Betty made her shortcake.
Half the reason people
come to the gala
is to try some
of Betty's great deserts.
And to see what racy
thing I might wear.
MADELEINE: Better start
baking now, Betty.
Looks like we're going
to have a big turnout.
-Yes, ma'am.
-GEORGIA: Betty, you've been
as much a part
of the Georgia Peaches
as any one of us.
We should make you
an honorary Peach.
Well, that's true enough.
-My Betty's a special girl.
-Thank you, ma'am.
-Thank you, Miss Porter.
-My goodness, Betty.
We've known each other 15 years.
Please call me Georgia.
Thank you, ma'am.
Georgia.
Betty, I think I'll take
an itsy-bitsy piece
of that cake now.
Such a shame the gardens
aren't as nice as last year.
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
What is with you?
GEORGIA: Me?
What's with you?
[SCOFFS] All
of your grandchildren
are suddenly unavailable.
That is just-- that's bull.
That's what it is.
You have a Black man
living in your home.
Now isn't that just a slap
in the face?
Why? He's not living
in your home.
Don't you dare.
I treat Betty like a member
of my family.
I always have.
But there are rules.
I know where the line is
and you have crossed it.
Maybe it's time
we moved the line.
As a matter of fact,
I'm thinking of asking
Lou Hastings to be my escort
to the Georgia Peach dinner.
Are you trying to provoke me?
This is not about you.
This is about Jacey.
She's part
of your family now, too.
And it's time you started
treating her like that.
You self-righteous--
I love you like a sister,
and I am sorry about Lily,
but don't you preach to me.
You were me a week ago.
Then shame on me.
-Hi, Grandpa.
-LOU: Hey, little bear.
-The kids weren't there.
-Aw.
This town has changed, huh?
I should have known better.
They were sick.
It didn't have anything
to do with anything.
Don't you worry
about those kids, little bear.
I've got a very special
birthday gift just for you.
-Look at that.
-JACEY
It looks just like Mommy's.
Well, it is Mommy's.
She wanted you to have it.
JACEY: I'm going to go show
Smoky Number Two.
All right.
I gave that cross to Lily
for her confirmation
when she was 12 years old.
[*****]
Yeah.
Oh.
Here, we got you
some books.
Did you know
that two of the authors
on the best-selling list
are Black--
-I mean African-American?
-Does that surprise you?
Yeah, it does.
Maybe I'm growing.
I wouldn't worry about it.
You've got a lot to overcome.
Try it.
-There.
-Well, thank you.
-That's been broken a long time.
-Well, you're welcome.
It's the least I could do.
I know how hard it was for you
to take me in.
Why you got so many catalogs?
Oh, I just like to shop at home.
I like to be able to think
without a salesperson
standing over me.
You probably wouldn't
understand that.
You're so good with people.
Oh.
What?
Oh, I didn't even know
it was July.
-What is it?
-Oh.
Once a year, the Star Registry
sells ownership of the stars.
You get to name them
and keep them forever.
I bought one every year
since Lily...
you know, went away.
They publish her name
and mine
in every important newspaper
all over the country.
And I-- I just always hoped
that wherever she was,
she might-- she might see
our names
and-- and know
how much I love her.
She could call the registry too,
and they'd send her, her stars.
You know, they
were just little charms
for bracelets.
Oh, I guess this is stupid.
[*****]
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
-GEORGIA: Hi, Betty.
-BETTY: Hi.
I brought my grandchildren over
for Jacey's birthday party.
Um, I'm sorry,
maybe I should have called.
Oh, no, that's wonderful.
Jacey.
No, come on in.
I'm so happy to see you.
-BETTY: Thank you.
-Hi, I'm Jacey. I'm seven.
-GIRL: Hello.
-BOY: Hi.
Are those for me?
-GIRL: Happy birthday.
-JACEY: Thank you.
-[CHUCKLES]
-BOY: Happy birthday, Jacey.
JACEY: You wanna come see
my room?
-GIRL: That'll be great.
-BOY: Sure.
-Oh, thank you.
-You're welcome.
I'll pick them up
in a couple of hours.
GEORGIA: Oh, come on in
and stay for dinner.
-Are you sure?
-GEORGIA: Hey.
-We got birthday cake here.
-Oh, in that case.
[BOTH LAUGH]
-Hello.
-This is Lou Hastings.
Hi.
Lou, this is Betty Greenlee,
my friend.
-Pleasure to meet you.
-The pleasure is all mine.
Come on.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
-GEORGIA: Ellen.
-Is this where the party is?
It sure is.
How are you, girls?
The other kids are upstairs.
Why don't you all go up?
-[KID LAUGHING]
-Come on in.
-ELLEN: Hi.
-Hello.
-Just an illusion, huh?
-[SCOFFS] Smoke and mirrors.
-[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
-[LOU LAUGHING]
All right, here we go
with the birthday cake.
Oh, here it comes.
-LOU: Birthday cake coming
right now.
-It's getting closer.
-Here it comes.
-[ALL CHEER]
GEORGIA: Okay,
blow them all out.
-One, two--
-Don't forget to make a wish.
GEORGIA: Three.
LOU: Oh, yeah.
-[ALL CHEER AND APPLAUSE]
-What did you wish?
I can't say it
or it won't come true.
They're here, little bear.
They are right here.
-Happy birthday, honey.
-[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
-I want a big piece.
-LOU: You want a big piece?
[ALL LAUGH]
LOU: I'm going to have
a big piece, okay?
I'm eating the whole
cake right now.
[ALL LAUGH]
LOU: Bye-bye, girls.
Goodbye, girls. Y'all come back.
-Nice meeting you.
-All right.
-Thank you for coming, Ellen.
-Oh, my pleasure.
That is one handsome man.
I'd have the vapors knowing
he was sleeping right there
-under my roof.
-What are you talking about?
ELLEN: Oh, please, Georgia.
Grow up.
This may be the south,
but you'd have to be
dead not to notice him.
Well, I assure you I don't.
Bye.
LOU: Oh, that was
a great party.
JACEY: Yeah.
LOU: Don't you worry,
little bear.
Soon we'll be home
and everything will be back
to normal.
Hey, maybe...
we'll have one of those
end-of-the-summer parties,
the way we had last year.
-Okay?
-When we ran in the sprinkler
-and ate popsicles?
-Absolutely. Sure.
JACEY: Remember what Daddy did
on my birthday when I was three?
LOU: Oh, yeah, he--
he woke you up
in the middle of the night
and drove you to the beach
and built a bonfire
in the sand, right?
And we chased fireflies
and roasted marshmallows.
[LAUGHS] Yeah.
You were such a baby.
How can you remember that?
It's my best day with Daddy.
Yeah.
LOU: Well, anyway,
you, uh, close your eyes
and dream about being home.
-What about Grandma?
-LOU: What about Grandma?
JACEY: Is she coming with us?
[*****]
Well, see...
y-- your grandma,
she has a whole life here.
This is her home.
She wouldn't enjoy California
the way we do.
Besides where would
she find all those catalogs?
Hmm? [LAUGHS]
All right, close your eyes
and get some sleep.
-Butterfly kiss.
-Butterfly kiss? Okay.
-Eskimo kiss?
-Eskimo kiss, too.
-Night, Grandpa.
-Night, little bear.
[*****]
[CAT MEOWS]
LOU: Oh.
Sorry, I didn't know
you were in here.
I just, uh, come
to get some water.
Smoky Number One was with her
in that car that day,
wasn't she?
Yes.
[INHALES SHARPLY]
That's just about enough
to break your heart.
Yes, it is.
Good night.
[CHURCH BELL TOLLING]
GEORGIA: Hmm.
-Banana pancakes.
-They're my favorite.
-Very impressive.
-Where are you off to?
Well, it is Sunday, and we
are good Christian women,
we're going to church.
I was gonna go
to my own church,
and I was hoping to bring
Jacey with me.
Well, maybe she could go
with me just this once.
Well, Jacey and I, we
were invited to this barbecue.
Some friends I haven't seen
in years.
Perhaps, you could pick her up
after the services.
Well, maybe you could
drop her off.
-Fine.
-All right.
-Uh-huh.
-CHOIR: * Early in the morning *
* Our song shall rise to Thee *
Thank you.
* Merciful and mighty *
-* God in three persons *
-GEORGIA: Excuse us.
-Just slide in there, honey.
-[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
Why is everybody looking at us?
GEORGIA: They're looking
at our new dresses.
-PRIEST: Let us pray.
-You look like an angel morning.
Lord, we ask that you
guide us and defend us
in these turbulent times.
The world is not a simple place
and we are not perfect.
-Help us, Father, to be tolerant
of our brothers and sisters
-[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
who were, like all of us,
created in your divine image.
-Amen.
-ALL: Amen.
* A mighty fortress is our God *
* A bulwark never failing *
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
-[SHUSHES]
-Quiet.
Why do we have to be quiet?
That's just the way
they do things in this church.
Maybe you'll get in trouble
if you make noise.
JACEY: Not in my church.
I should have gone with Grandpa.
CHOIR: * His craft and power
Are great... *
[*****]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
-Grandpa.
-Hey, little bear.
-Thanks for bringing her.
-Oh, you're welcome.
Well, I'll-- I'll see you
in a little while then, honey.
Stay with us, Grandma.
-I don't think your grandma--
-Well, I'd love to stay.
Suit yourself.
-Come on, baby.
-[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
If you boys don't stop
chasing each other,
I'm going to separate you
for an hour.
-Do you hear me?
-[KIDS LAUGHING]
Go-- Would you go
get those boys?
-Mm-hmm.
-[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
-Hello.
GEORGIA: Oh,
this looks delicious.
Well, it's an old family
recipe from way back.
GEORGIA: Really?
-Would you like some?
-Oh, yeah, sure.
Just one.
-There you go.
-Thank you.
-Enjoy.
-[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[LAUGHS]
-I wish I could dance like that.
-LOU: I'm sure you can.
You know...
we come from a family
of very, very talented people.
As a matter of fact
when I was young,
I could dance as good as that.
Do you want to see?
-What about your foot?
-Don't worry about the foot.
Let's go. Come on.
[*****]
[WOMAN CHEERING]
-Yes.
-[WOMAN LAUGHS]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
-Yes.
-[LAUGHS]
What is she doing here?
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
-GEORGIA: May I join you?
-Yes, you may.
[CHUCKLES]
JACEY: Grandma, did you see me?
Oh, yes, you look wonderful
out there.
I just used to love to dance
when I was your age.
Then come on.
GEORGIA: Oh, I don't know
that one, honey.
I'll teach you.
Okay.
One, two, three.
-Then step back.
-[LAUGHS]
-Then you turn.
-[BOTH LAUGH]
Hey, I'm getting better.
[JACEY LAUGHING]
[GROANS]
[LOU GROANING]
[DOOR OPENING]
GEORGIA: My God.
-What happened?
-[BREATHES HEAVILY]
I'm fine. Go-- go on back
to bed.
-No. Come on. Come on.
-I'm fine.
-Just get on up there.
-[CLICKS TONGUE]
[GRUNTS]
-[GRUNTS]
-Okay.
-Slide back there.
-You-- you know, you go--
Put your--
Oh, my sweet Jesus.
-Oh, it's nothing. It's nothing.
-That is not nothing?
That is horrible.
Have you been doing everything
the doctor said?
LOU: Oh, it's--
it's hard for me to change
the bandage
-as often as I need to.
Oh, I didn't realize that.
I'm sorry. Oh.
Look, I-- I can take it
from here.
GEORGIA: Oh, I've got it.
-There.
-[GROANS]
-Am I hurting you?
-LOU: No, no, no.
-All right.
-[EXHALES]
[CHUCKLES]
Well, at least
you won't have to lock
your bedroom door anymore.
Clearly it's hard
for a Black man
to climb those steps
without his foot.
I am an old-fashioned,
-moral, southern woman.
-LOU: Uh-huh.
I wouldn't care if you were pink
with purple polka dots.
-[LAUGHS]
-You're still a man,
and I still would lock my door.
-I see.
-No, you don't.
All right.
Let's get back in bed.
Come on, now. Come on.
[LOU EXHALES DEEPLY]
You know I'm-- I'm sorry
about this afternoon.
I'm sure it was uncomfortable
being with my people.
No, not at all.
I was just happy
to crash the party.
Yeah, right. [GRUNTS]
I'm sure you would have
felt much more at home
with your Georgia Peaches
at the fancy dinner.
-When is that dinner?
-That was tonight.
Oh, I'm sorry.
For what?
It seems impossible for Lily
to have been raised
by you and your husband
and still come out so special.
-Really?
-[GRUNTS]
I take that thought back.
-[CLICKS TONGUE] Good night.
-Good night.
-[*****]
-[LAUGHS]
[SIGHS] It's hot.
-GEORGIA: That's true.
-[WOMAN SIGHING]
This park has gone
to hell in a hand basket.
Time was you could come here
and have pleasant afternoon.
[CHUCKLES]
The handsome devil
over there is my grandson.
The boy's got two speeds,
red hot fire and coma.
I can hardly keep up with him.
That's my granddaughter
over there.
-Where?
-GEORGIA: On the swing.
That's Jacey. That's my baby.
I see. Well, isn't she adorable?
I think so.
I'm going to start
wrapping things up, okay?
-GEORGIA: Sure.
-LOU: Yeah.
-So, is this your husband?
-LOU: Oh, no, ma'am.
We just live together.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[WOMAN CHUCKLING]
Well, really.
[CHUCKLES]
I do believe
that global warming
is concentrating on Georgia.
-[LOU SCOFFING] Impossible.
-Grandma told me
they have more sun here
in the south.
Oh, it's true.
You, uh, say it's a little
too hot here in Georgia?
Yeah.
Maybe you need
a nice cold shower.
Yes, ma'am,
that would be perfect.
[MOUTHS] One...
two...
-three!
-[BOTH LAUGH]
Oh. Oh, you.
-All right, all right.
-LOU: Let's go get her.
-[BOTH LAUGH]
-[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
-[*****]
-This is it, this is it. Okay.
All right. This is it.
Okay. There you go.
LOU: Oh, yeah? I'mma get you.
Watch this, watch this.
[GRUNTS, LAUGHS]
[ALL LAUGH]
It's getting late.
We should be thinking
about dinner.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
-[SIREN WAILING]
-[*****]
[JACEY TALKING INDISTINCTLY]
Are you all right, honey?
-No, no.
-LOU: Little bear.
No. No. No. No.
No.
[CRYING] Come back.
Please come back.
-Mom.
-[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
JACEY: Come back!
Mommy, come back!
Mommy, don't leave me!
-LOU: Little bear, it's okay.
-Mommy! Let me go!
-LOU: No, no, it's okay.
-Let me go!
I know, I know.
-I want Mommy and Daddy!
-LOU: I know, I know.
JACEY: Let me go! [CRYING]
GEORGIA: It's all right,
it's okay.
Your Grandpa and I, uh,
we'll always be here
forever and ever.
-It'll be all right.
-[JACEY CRYING]
[*****]
Is she asleep?
She's starting to remember
everything about the accident.
I can't even imagine
what she must be feeling.
Well, school starts
in a couple of weeks.
Maybe, uh, when she's around
her-- her teachers
and her friends
and everything's on schedule...
everything might go back
to normal.
[SIGHS]
Our children are gone.
And that little child upstairs
is suffering God knows what.
Every bit of it is my fault.
-What?
-I was weak.
I was so weak. I was--
I don't understand it.
I should have just--
I should have done
what you said.
I should have stopped him.
I shouldn't have let him
go out there that night.
And I should have stayed
with Lily
when she asked me,
and I didn't.
-And I don't know why.
-You left with him
because you knew
that if he was home
beating on you,
he wouldn't be able
to hurt them.
It's not your fault.
I should have taken her away
years ago when she was a baby.
I should have just gotten
her out of the house.
What was I so scared of?
[SNIFFLES] I just want
another chance.
I just want to go back. I...
I want to fight for her.
-That's what you're doing.
-[CRYING]
That's what you're doing now...
you're fighting for that child.
[SHUSHING]
Everything's going to be
just fine.
-Hey.
-[SNIFFLES]
Hey.
He can't hurt you anymore.
-[GEORGIA CHUCKLING]
-Hmm.
I must go to Jacey.
[*****]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
-LOU: Did you take a bite?
-[JACEY TALKING INDISTINCTLY]
LOU: We're toasting marshmallows
out here in the sand.
Oh, this gonna be-- Quick,
quick, quick, quick, quick.
-It's on fire.
-Oh, it's on fire.
Blow, blow, blow.
Oh, okay.
This one's better than this one.
Blow it out.
Okay, now try it.
-How's it taste?
-Yummy.
Ooh, that's good, huh?
-Let me see.
-Mm-hmm.
[GROANS]
This is the third marshmallow,
do you think you stand it?
We're toasting marshmallows
out here in sand.
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
What are you doing?
I've imposed
on your hospitality too long.
You're taking her, aren't you?
I...
I need to tell you something.
Marcus and Lily...
they was going to move
back here.
What are you saying?
They wanted to come home.
They wanted to live
in my old house.
Why didn't you tell me?
Because I didn't want them
to move here.
I was against Jacey
being raised here.
And I thought
that if you knew,
uh, you'd try and keep her.
And I couldn't let that happen.
Um, I just didn't trust you
to raise her.
-So, why are you telling me now?
-Because now, I know I'm wrong.
She belongs with you.
You're a good mother...
good woman.
She needs you.
[SNIFFLES]
She's lucky to have you.
GEORGIA: She needs you, too.
This is crazy.
What are you doing?
Is this because of last night?
I pulled away from you,
but it wasn't because
you're Black.
It's because you're a man.
[BAG ZIPS]
I think I better go.
[*****]
Morning, honey.
What's that?
-Grandpa went away for a while.
-I know.
He told me to give you this.
Oh?
See, now what we have to do,
we have to get you
over to that school
and get you registered,
because first grade is going
to start in a couple of...
Oh.
[*****]
Lily-Joe's star bracelet.
She knew.
Honey, these are the stars
I gave your mama.
Aren't they beautiful?
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
-Grandpa.
-Hey, little bear.
-What are you doing here? What?
-JACEY: We found you.
Where are you running to?
I'm going home.
Jacey is your home.
Lily and Marcus,
they're trusting us
to raise this child.
I'm going to be in her life.
And I will see you soon,
little bear.
I'm not sure I can do this
by myself.
LOU: Georgia broke my heart
once before.
I'm not going to let
that happen again.
Stay with us, Grandpa, please.
Grandma wants you to stay.
Don't you, Grandma?
Yes.
Ah. Mm-mm.
WOMAN ON PA: Final call
for Flight 856 to Nashville
with continuing service
through San Diego,
this is your final call.
Flight 856 to Nashville
with continuing service
to San Diego.
Please proceed to gate seven.
[*****]