Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
Are we alone out here?
Yes, sir.
No Americans in the area, sir.
Run the program.
I said run
the program, Dr. Lee.
Yes, Captain.
[rumbling]
All of America's
personal communications
brought down through
a satellite in mere seconds.
There are no secrets anymore
thanks to our work, Dr. Lee.
Don't worry, Dr. Lee.
The American's won't
find us here.
[roars]
[crash]
Captain! Something hit us!
A ship? The Americans?
I... don't think so...
I think it's... alive.
[alarm blaring]
[crashing]
I'm sending a
distress signal, Captain.
No... no...
The technology on this
ship could... start a war.
[creaking]
[screaming]
[grunting]
[panting]
[screams]
No two ways about it.
You got a raw deal, Commander.
I screwed the pooch, Captain.
You stood behind your people.
And my sister and
I are forever grateful.
Commander Lynch did
what she had to do
to save as many lives as
possible from that thing.
Your sister deep-sixed
a destroyer to save lives
from "a thing that
doesn't exist."
Oh, it exists, Brian,
just like the Chinese
ship circling our waters.
So you'll be going out there
to see it, yes?
No. The Admiral is handling
it all from D.C.
According to him,
it's legal transit
of the U.S. territorial seas
conducted in accordance
with the Law of
the Sea Convention
and we're supposed
to stay out of it.
So they trust
a foreign government,
an enemy, but not
your sister, right?
Hmm, looks that way.
Doesn't look that way.
That's the way it is.
They said it's a "product of
fabrication,
exhaustion and confusion
and nothing else."
You know, your sister's
a lot of things,
but she's no liar.
If she said a
million-pound megalodon
ate her ship, well...
Hey, I'm gonna believe it.
Because just like you,
your sister is
a very good person.
So are you.
You stood behind her.
I don't know what else
you were supposed to do.
Let's hope the Admiral feels
the same way during my hearing.
Your sister shouldn't
have been court-martialed.
She shouldn't have.
And I'll be goddamned if
she'll be court-martialed alone.
You'll get your rank back,
Commander.
I'm sure of it.
Will they give me back
my submarine project, too?
I hate to see that
beautiful piece of machinery
mothballed at the final
testing stage.
You know, a deep-sea machine
like that
might even confirm
the existence of that megalodon
if they just let me finish,
if they just let me
back on the project
which I don't think they will.
Captain Lynch!
We're getting
an abnormal distress call.
Tuan located it and we're
nearly on top of the ship now.
We still haven't deciphered
the code on whose ship that is.
Seems to have been
intentionally masked, Captain.
Hmm.
Let's peel back that mask.
See if it has anything
to do with
those ships circling our waters.
- Let's get underway.
- Yes, ma'am.
Thank you, Commander.
Happy to do it.
Stay safe.
Ah, see, I'm not saying
she's not good at her job,
not at all.
I'm just saying...
Just saying... when are you not
just saying something, XO?
Yes, Tuan.
I'm just saying
she is not aggressive.
Is that a bad thing
or a good thing?
Is that a bad thing?
We are in the Navy, hmm?
Not some damn summer camp.
You know I'm right,
you know I'm right.
That's why I'm already
Lieutenant Commander, hmm?
I got that fight.
I'm old school.
I'm about kickin' ass
and takin' names,
not playing grab-ass
kumbaya with our enemies.
How about your friends, sir?
He doesn't have any.
[laughing]
Y'all funny.
Captain on the deck!
What's so funny in here, people?
Nothing, Captain.
We're still getting the
distress signals, Captain.
So I heard, Tuan.
Ahearn suggested
we reorient to the location.
I assumed that's
what you wanted to do.
You assumed right, Ahearn.
Thank you, Captain.
But you should stop assuming
while you're ahead.
Understand me?
Aye, ma'am.
How close are we, Tuan?
Nearly on top of it, ma'am.
We see anything?
Negative, ma'am,
but still receiving the signal.
Whatever it is, she's sunk.
Any signs of life, Tuan?
No S.O.L., ma'am.
I'm not seeing
any more signs, ma'am.
Uh, ma'am?
We have a confirmation
of an unknown object
in the water from
the deck crew.
Any idea what, Wilco?
Any idea what it is?
Debris?
Really?
What is the unknown
object, Wilco?
It's a survivor.
She's seen some pretty
intense exposure.
At least two or three
days worth,
additionally lacerations,
some bruising,
very likely a concussion.
She's a Chinese national.
Pretty close to
U.S. waters, Captain.
Nothing about them in
our files or schedules.
Keep an eye on her, Dr. Ray.
I have a few questions
for her when she wakes up.
Aye, ma'am.
Ma'am?
Do you think
she's Chinese Intelligence
and her ship was on some
kind of off-label mission?
I think this
is above my pay grade.
Hmm.
It's time we loop
the Admiral in.
And you know what
I'll do then, Ahearn?
What, ma'am?
Whatever they tell me,
grab-ass kumbaya or otherwise.
Yes, ma'am.
Captain!
Yes, Brand?
You just oughta see this, ma'am.
See what?
Is that a Chinese ship, ma'am?
Affirmative, Brand.
What are they doing here?
They're not supposed to be
in these waters.
That's why
we need answers, Brand.
Captain on the bridge!
Affirmative.
I will send that message.
Was that Commander Moore?
Admiral Green?
No, ma'am.
That was the captain
of the Tsai.
He's spoken with our
superiors in San Diego,
and says he has full legal
permission to travel our waters.
He is claiming innocent passage.
They're requesting that
we and all the U.S. ships
evacuate the area
so they can search for a ship
that went off-course
during bad weather.
Bad weather?
Bad weather, ma'am.
Their ship is assumed lost and
they are looking for survivors.
Was there additional
wreckage, radar, sonar?
I am picking up
something below us, Captain.
Below us?
Yes, ma'am.
From what I can surmise,
there is a tall shelf below us,
nearly 20 fathoms.
It appears there's
something there,
most likely the survivor's ship.
I find this all highly suspect.
- Do you agree, Ahearn?
- Yes, ma'am.
It's not every day
a Chinese destroyer
rolls into our town
without prior authorization.
Agreed, ma'am.
Very fishy.
- Wilco?
- Yes, ma'am?
Tell them we found a survivor.
Something wrong, Ahearn?
No, ma'am.
Tell them
she's still unconscious
and their ship seems
to have sunk.
Don't tell them precisely
where if they're not asking.
Yes, ma'am.
Fewer moving parts,
the better, people.
Let's keep that all in mind.
- Yes, ma'am.
Actually, hold that, Wilco.
Tuan, you speak Mandarin,
don't you?
Yes, ma'am...
well, around the house.
I'm a little bit rusty.
Rusty like you mix up ducks
and geese
or rusty like the bed that fell
out of my father's truck?
First one, I think, ma'am.
Look at
Lieutenant Commander Ahearn.
Tell me what he's thinking...
in Mandarin.
I wish I didn't have
such small hands.
That'll work fine.
Wilco, put her on the comms
with the Chinese.
Aye, ma'am.
Already on it.
Attention, CNS Tsai,
this is the USS King.
Do you read me?
Don't look so worried, Ahearn.
I'm sure she
said something nice.
Your survivor is unconscious
and you ship seems to have sunk.
Ma'am?
Yes, Tuan?
They're saying by
international agreement,
we must hand over
the survivor and depart.
Hand over and depart?
Well, that's not just arrogant.
It's wrong.
I can put them on
your comms if you want.
No. Let's keep it impersonal.
Tell them I need
to pass it up the flagpole.
We have received your request
and must pass it on to
our commanding officers.
All right.
Yes, I will tell her.
What did they say, Tuan?
They said that
it's an act of war.
An act of... an act of war?
Not handing back a survivor
is said it will be
seen as an act of war
between the two countries.
What should I tell them?
End all communications!
Put the big guns on the horn!
Aye, ma'am.
Ahearn?
Do you have the
copy of the UNCLOS?
Yes, in my berth, ma'am.
I want to check
the Innocent Passage.
Brand, go and fetch
Ahearn's book from his berth.
Right away, ma'am!
Ma'am, permission to exit the
bridge to find the book myself.
I'm not a hundred
that I know where it is.
Permission granted.
Thank you, Captain.
What do you think?
She'll live.
Can you wake her up?
I don't think I should, sir.
Is something the matter?
World War III.
What?
Never mind.
Just let me know
the minute she wakes up.
I'll let the Captain
know the minute it happens.
Let me know.
I'll keep the Captain apprised.
She is dealing directly
with the Chinese Navy.
She has not the time
nor the inclination
to be checking in
on Sleeping Beauty.
Let me know.
Yes, sir.
I understand, sir.
Thank you, Admiral Green.
Should we ready the survivor
for transport, ma'am?
No. We're staying here.
Admiral Green wants
to keep her here?
He wants us to do nothing,
not engage with the Chinese
in any way to hurt or to help.
We don't make a move
until they sort things out
with the Chinese directly,
which will take the day.
Yes, ma'am.
We're holding
our position, people.
Stay on your toes.
Ma'am?
Yes, Wilco?
The watch crew says that
they're aiming at us...
They're what, Wilco?
And readying their
munitions, ma'am.
Indeed they are.
All right! Battle stations!
We cannot let them get past us
and get to the San Diego shore!
Yes, ma'am.
[alarm blares]
[bell rings]
Are they reacting, Tan?
They're moving into battle
readiness, I believe, Captain.
Good.
They are distracted.
If they fire,
we send back two, people!
Let 'em know they messed
with the wrong ship!
- Yes, ma'am!
We await your order
to fire, Captain.
I await my orders, as well, Tan.
And the imminent arrival
of the armada.
Yes, Captain.
[crash]
What was that?
Was that us?
Was that us!?
Who fired without my command?
It wasn't us, ma'am.
I know what's happening.
What, ma'am?
Megalodons!
Keep your sights
on those things!
Yes, ma'am.
It's the meg...
I'm positive.
And, uh...
What? What?
There's more than one!
What?
I see three fins,
Brian, three fins!
Get outta there, Emily!
Get out of there now!
Your sister barely survived one.
You won't be able
to stop three.
Are they coming for you yet?
No.
The Chinese ship
is firing on 'em.
I think it's got them agitated.
It's like shooting
a tank with a pistol!
Just get out of there!
If they come anywhere near us,
you blow those things to hell!
Ma'am, yes, ma'am!
Emily? You must leave!
I can't.
I can't just leave.
Look, you cannot make a move.
You cannot make a
move towards that ship, Emily,
- or Admiral Green...
- I know!
And you can't say
word one about the megs.
I know!
Well, you know what
he'll do if the Admiral
hears any more talk about
megalodons or even sharks...
I know! It's just sitting
here like this...
Full ahead!
Yes, sir.
Full ahead! Full ahead!
Look, they're
not our responsibility
and I'm living proof
of his thoughts on megalodons
and stepping out when it's your
authority not to step out.
And you definitely cannot fire
at them
while
they're surrounding the ship.
If you miss...
I get it!
World War III.
Look, I wish I wasn't
trapped here
with my sub tarped
like a naked statue.
And I could come and help you,
but your objective is clear.
Please listen.
Get the footage you need to
prove your sister's case
that these things are real,
that that beast
destroyed her ship
and a Russian sub and put us
on the brink of conflict
with the Russian Army,
and then get out of there.
We can't just leave
'em to die, Brian!
Look, I'll contact Admiral Green
and tell him what's happening.
He won't believe me,
but I'm already in it and how
much worse could it get, right?
Oh, it can get a lot worse.
Ma'am, we're ready
to fire on those things
when you give us the command.
With all due respect, Captain,
I think we should be
departing immediately.
Those sharks could turn
on us at any moment.
And the Chinese
are way too distracted
to start anything with us now.
Now's our chance.
We're staying here.
- But Captain...
- We're staying right here!
Captain, if those things
turn on us...
If those things come at us,
do you think that
we can outpace them?
You see how fast they are?
We're staying here.
Killian, tell Engineering
to kill the engines.
Nothing noisy that will attract
those things before we have to.
Aye, ma'am.
Samperio, the moment
those things move away
from the Chinese,
we fire on 'em!
Yes, Ma'am!
I can't imagine they still think
we're responsible for this mess.
Ma'am?
Yes, Tuan.
They stopped attacking
the Chinese ship.
Looks like they
sustained some damage,
but they aren't totally sunk.
I'm not sure, ma'am.
The sharks dropped fast
like something hurt them or...
Or they're regrouping and
looking for a better target.
Confirming the sharks
are in sight
and out of the danger zone
for the Chinese, ma'am.
Samperio, let 'em
get a little closer
and hit 'em all at once
nice and fast.
Turn that tide!
Yes, ma'am!
Hold your fire until my mark.
They're just a
few hundred feet out, Captain!
Wilco?
Put Tuan on the comms
to the Chinese!
Yes, ma'am.
Tuan, inform the Chinese
that we will be firing,
but not on them.
Yes, ma'am.
Here they come!
Hold.
Hold!
- Now!
- Open fire!
Fire! Fire! Fire!
They're gone again, Captain.
Hold fire, Samperio!
Hold fire! Hold fire!
Hold your fire!
What's the status
of the megs, Tuan?
It appears they've gone deep,
Captain, maybe under the shelf.
They're tough, but they
don't like being shot at.
Readings are unclear,
but they appear
to still be in the area.
So they're hiding.
It would seem so, ma'am.
If they're hiding and
not just running away,
that means they're coming back
the moment they recover
from that first shelling.
They're toying
with us like cats.
Killian, what's the status
of the Chinese ship?
Definitely taking
water, Captain.
Tuan and Wilco,
radio them
and see if they're ready
to receive assistance.
Yes, ma'am.
We don't need to make friends,
but I'd like to get
outta here without starting
a world war if possible.
Yes, ma'am.
CNS Tsai, this is SS King.
Do you copy? Over.
If we don't hear anything
from them in two minutes,
- we're heading out.
- All right, ma'am.
Any status on the survivor?
Still unconscious.
Are you sure?
Positive, Captain.
I'm getting
nothing back, Captain.
That's long enough.
[beeps]
Captain, we have
a response text.
Only ELF.
What is it?
He wants a parlay.
You and a comms man
and no one else.
We are under no obligation to
accede to any terms, Captain.
I'm not acceding anything.
I'm saving lives on two ships,
300 souls at least.
That is my obligation
and my code.
What is yours?
Yes, ma'am.
Clear the bridge!
We have a secure line, Captain.
Hello, Captain.
I don't believe
I know your name.
Captain Ping is my name.
Good to meet you.
I'm Captain Lynch.
I hope you and
your crew are doing well.
We're not, Captain.
We have been attacked.
Yes, we saw.
We tried to assist,
but were afraid
of further mistakenly
damaging your ship.
Your lack of action
is tantamount to an attack
on us and our mission, Captain.
We did not sic sharks
on your ship, Captain!
That is not
what the U.S. Navy does!
We have heard otherwise
from the Russians.
We have saved the Russians.
If you've heard anything
but that, you've heard wrong.
There's nothing that can stop
us from our missions, Captain.
Your mission?
Yes.
You should not underestimate
the situation
we are in here, Captain Ping.
We don't know when those
things will come back.
Now I can offer you safe harbor
and provide you transport
until such time as...
We must complete our mission.
I should hope
that your mission would be
to save your ship and
your crew, Captain Ping!
Now, like I said,
I can provide you
harbor and offer you transport.
Captain Lynch, I told you
we must complete our missions.
You have two hours
to return our survivor
and depart these waters.
Well, I don't take orders from
anyone but the U.S. government.
Added to that,
you are in our waters,
30 nautical miles off
the coast of San Diego.
So I'll be taking orders
from my Admiral.
But I will pass on
your request to him.
You have two hours.
Get him back, Wilco!
Yes, ma'am.
I didn't believe those
stories about the sharks.
I thought people were
just messing around.
If they keep coming
at us like that...
We're gonna kick their ass!
That's what we're gonna do.
- Back to your stations, people!
- Yes, ma'am!
We have to keep
those things away
from San Diego, no matter what!
Do you mean the sharks
or the Tsai, ma'am?
Both, Tuan.
Be ready for a show
of force, people!
- Yes, Captain!
Ahearn?
- Ahearn?
- Yes, ma'am?
What's the status
of our survivor?
Well, we...
She's awake, ma'am.
I was gonna say just that.
She's awake, Captain.
Hold the bridge, Ahearn.
Yes, Captain.
Those sharks
attacked your ship
and killed your crew,
didn't they?
What's your name?
Well, I don't know
if you speak English,
but if you do, you should know
we're getting ready to engage
with a Chinese destroyer
that's demanding
we turn you over to them.
What that means is,
we cannot move from this spot
without maybe starting a war.
We're sitting here waiting
to be lunch
for three giant sharks
that will return the moment
that they recover from
their last shelling.
So I hope you don't
speak English
and I hope you're not purposely
sitting on information
that will be the difference
between two ships
worth of people living
or dying here today!
I hope for
everyone's sake
that all I need to
do right now is go down
and get my translator!
My name's Dr. Lee
and their Armada
is coming for me.
They know about the megalodons
and have been
waiting on standby.
That's why the ships
have been circling.
I knew it wasn't for transit.
The first ship
is just a warning.
They've recovered!
Keep her here, Dr. Ray.
Brace yourselves.
[alarm blares]
Fire! Fire! Fire!
Hell, yeah!
Good shot, boys!
One hell of a shot!
The The Americans are
firing into the water.
I don't think they're lying,
about the sharks, sir.
They're fighting them
just like we are...
Should we depart, sir?
Or should we wait for
the armada, sir?
[sighs]
We wait.
Yes, sir.
We have a message
already prepared for you,
Captain, both in English
and Mandarin.
Read it back to me.
Communication from Captain Lynch
to Captain Ping.
"At this time after
the near destruction
"of your ship and the imminent
destruction of mine,
"we are in preparations
to return
"to San Diego Naval Base
where the survivor
"will be taken care of.
"And we will work
through diplomatic channels
"to get her back home.
"We cannot take the time
to transfer personnel
"or otherwise engage
without further endangering
"lives in the face
of the megalodons.
"And while what
is clearly damaged
"and appears to be being
devoured as we speak,
"this present calm
will not last.
"Our offer is not
an act of hostility
"and should not be
taken as such.
"It is an offer of assistance
and safe harbor.
"If you accompany
us to the harbor,
"we guarantee the safe return
of personnel.
Regards, Captain Lynch."
Send it.
Give me the P.A., Wilco.
Yes, ma'am.
On your comms now.
Crew, this is
your captain speaking.
I have been informed
that a Chinese Armada
will be approaching us.
Report any and all
new sightings of new ships
on the horizon
to myself and your XO.
Thank you.
Is that really happening,
Captain?
A Chinese Armada?
Yes, and we have to be prepared.
And even more prepared
when those things
finish eating their friend.
And I have a sense that
it's not gonna satiate them.
On the move, people!
- ASAP! Now!
- You heard the Captain!
ASAP! Let's go!
That was close, Captain.
A warning shot from the Chinese?
We have incoming comms, Captain.
Putting Tuan on now.
They're saying if we move,
it will be perceived
as an act of war.
They're firing on us!
Stop the ship.
They're damaged, ma'am.
We can take them!
Should we engage, ma'am?
Be ready to, Samperio!
We may not have a choice
if they keep firing on us.
We're all set, Captain!
Wilco? Raise Admiral Green.
Yes, ma'am.
He may not want
to hear about this,
but he'll damn sure want to hear
about the Chinese firing on us.
Ahearn, go talk to Dr. Lee.
Captain, I'm sorry,
but who is Dr. Lee?
Our survivor. Find out what she
was really doing here, Ahearn.
If we know that, we'll have
an idea how to stop this war.
Yes, ma'am.
Wilco?
Do you have Admiral Green?
Not yet, ma'am.
Admiral Green is still
in talks with the Chinese.
He's on his jets and...
Everyone with a pay grade
has their asses covered.
Understood.
I think it's time
I phone a friend.
We don't know
where these things are.
We could use some eyes
in the sky.
We're sitting ducks
and the other ducks
are taking pot shots at us!
I'm already on my way.
What? What does that mean?
I thought you were grounded?
Oh, I am,
but my underwater drone isn't.
[chuckles]
I put it in the water
the second our call ended.
It's already 29 miles out
from shore,
which means we should be in
your neck of the woods in about,
I don't know, 20 seconds.
You know if the Admiral
hears about this...
It'll be a bloodbath,
figuratively.
But I'm concerned about
the literal bloodbath
that will occur
if I don't do this.
I can take the consequences,
but all the same,
keep this under wraps with
your crew, if you will, Captain.
Loose lips...
well, you know the rest.
Your secret's safe with me,
Commander.
Good...
Because here we are.
Look at the size of this thing.
We'll have to get around it
and get a picture of
the bigger one, too.
Salles!
What's the status
of the megs, Tuan?
Looks like they're just
getting on the move again,
not coming on strong.
Maybe we put them on notice
again with the last volley.
That's almost good news.
Or they're finishing their
last meal and biding their time.
That's more what I'm used to.
Uh, Captain, one
of the megs is...
What?
Distracted.
Good. Wilco?
Any news on the Admiral yet?
Getting word now, ma'am.
We're being told
to hold our ground.
Hold our ground?
Wilco, do you have the Admiral?
No, ma'am.
Support staff only.
Admiral's in negotiations.
What would you like
us to do, ma'am?
If they move any closer,
hit 'em with all we got.
Hard, fast, all at once,
just like the last time.
We will not move,
but we will not be sitting here
like wounded deer either.
We have a duty to protect
ourselves and the other ship!
Yes, ma'am.
Come on, boys! Let's go!
Let's go! Come on!
Sorry, Commander.
Every time I get close
to the big one,
the small one
blocks off my path.
Yeah.
That mini meg is trying
to protect that big beast,
running interference
for it like a yappy dog.
You know what that means?
No, sir.
It means the beast is in charge.
Punch through, Salles.
I'm trying to, sir,
but that small one's fast.
Move over. I'm driving.
Yes, sir.
You know, I wanted to catch
you before Captain did,
but I missed my opportunity.
Here's what you should know.
She's a good woman, she is,
a fair woman, the Captain.
She believes that...
everyone is important,
even you,
a Chinese spy...
floating
around American waters.
But see, I'm not like
my Captain, though.
I'm not, hmm?
I'm what you call
a natural born warrior
and I for one hate my enemy.
And make no mistake about it.
You are my enemy, hmm?
See, I'm supposed
to come down here,
try to get you to offer up
your precious spy information.
But, you know, I'm glad
you're not cooperating.
I am, I really am.
Because I'm going to enjoy
throwing you in those waters.
And watching those sharks
tear you limb from limb,
giving us just
enough time to escape.
See, make no mistake about it.
No matter what deal
you get offered,
that's how this ends for you.
You hear me?
Any luck, Ahearn?
Not so far, ma'am.
I don't think her
English is so good.
Hmm.
Why don't you take the bridge,
see how we're
doing with those sharks.
Dr. Ray, if you don't
mind stepping out?
Yes, ma'am.
Lee and I need to
do a one-on-one.
I know you can understand me.
But maybe you're afraid
you said too much
the first time we spoke.
But the megs
are coming at us now.
We would be happy to take
you to the other ship.
I will do it myself
in a dinghy if I have to.
But I must know what you
were doing in these waters!
I already know it
must be a spy mission.
But I need to
know more than that.
So here it is.
You either tell me
what I need to know
or we all die with
our secrets here today.
More power, Salles!
We're almost
there, we're almost...
[groans]
Dr. Ray, take Lee to the brig.
Aye, ma'am.
All right.
The moment that big one
comes anywhere near the surface,
drop a bomb on its ass!
Where are they?
They're on the move
again, Captain.
Back to the Tsai?
No, ma'am, away from it,
moving fast.
What?
Where are they going?
[phone vibrates]
Moore! It worked!
It worked too well.
What? What do you mean?
My drone got 'em nice and mad
and dragged them away from you.
But they seemed to have realized
there's nothing to eat in it...
What do you mean, eat, sir?
They're close enough
to smell the cotton candy,
so they're heading
for San Diego.
They're heading for us.
Isn't that great?
We've got to do something.
You can't go out there,
Commander Moore!
Hell if I won't.
If you go out there, you'll
end up in the stockade, sir.
If we don't stop those things
from destroying our ships,
we can't stop the Armada
from storming our shores.
We'll be sitting ducks for
whatever comes for us!
And I will not stay in here
and do nothing.
That's why you won't.
We need your eyes here
helping guide us.
You keep in contact with me,
you'll see what I see.
You'll be with us.
Look, I don't consider
it an upside,
but if those
things do attack the beach,
no one can deny that they exist.
And I'll get footage of it all.
You're a good man, Salles,
you're a good man.
There you go.
And you're my commander, sir,
no matter what they say.
There's no way I can stop them,
but I'll get all
the evidence we need.
Just in case...
Let's blow up some fish.
Salles, PACCOM says our
carriers are tied up
with the Chinese Navy, so air
support is not available.
First platoon one me!
Second platoon, clear that pier!
Destroy those things before
they hit the beaches, Salles!
Let's go!
I got eyes on!
We're clear.
Coast guard is still enroute.
You gotta hold 'em off!
Fire!
[gunfire]
Fall back, Salles!
Fall back!
Gah! Go!
First platoon, fall back,
fall back!
Let's go!
Ma'am, the megalodons have
decimated the San Diego Base
and are approaching the beaches.
I'm going to see Dr. Lee.
[clears throat]
Captain?
Should I have Wilco and
Tuan contact the Tsai?
For what reason, Ahearn?
Captain, she is a spy.
Are you suggesting
we throw her overboard?
Make her walk the plank?
Is that what you want us to do?
No, ma'am, not at all.
Good.
Because that's not how
the U.S. Navy operates.
And that's not
how my ship operates.
And it is indeed my ship,
Lieutenant Commander!
We do not throw
inconvenient people
into shark-infested waters!
If we were to defy
orders and cut Dr. Lee
before knowing what she knows,
we would be defying orders.
And that's not the captain I am
nor is it the captain I will be,
no matter what
the circumstances are
or what arguments
have been made!
I follow orders
and so should you!
Yes, Captain.
Understood.
Now let's go break
this woman down
and find out what she knows
so we can get outta here.
[knocking]
Thank you, Ahearn.
You don't need my help, Captain?
You've done exactly what I need.
Return to the bridge.
Take the con.
Yes, Captain.
What are you doing?
He wants to throw you
in the water.
He hasn't said it to me,
but he's ready to do it.
I think a lot of people on this
ship are ready to do it as well,
but I'm in charge.
And I want to send you home,
but we're running
out of options.
I'm not afraid to die
for my country, Captain Lynch.
I am.
Please.
That doesn't mean
I won't do it, but I am.
I'm willing to kill
for my country, too.
But I'm not willing
to sacrifice my honor for it.
Are you willing
to sacrifice your honor
for your country, Dr. Lee?
Because the way
I see it, without honor,
we don't have a country
or a society.
We only have ourselves.
I would die to protect
my country's secrets.
But I will not die
to protect its lies.
A country's lies are a weapon
to be used against its country.
If we make them our lies,
we become weapons
against our own country.
Now something happened here
and it brought those sharks
in like a revenge of sin.
Do you believe
in luck, Dr. Lee?
I do.
Do you believe in bad luck?
Well, bad luck doesn't
usually follow bad action.
But when it does,
it's the worst kind,
the kind that erases
all the good we ever did.
[static]
Salles, I need a status report.
Talk to me.
Moore, sir,
we were firing, but we lost 'em!
They tore apart both docks
and hulled the Vitus
and both battleships!
The Naval base is
completely destroyed.
Get to the beaches, Salles.
Please get to the beaches now.
Oh, my God!
I understand
what you're saying, Captain,
but I'm not going
to betray my country.
There is nothing to betray.
We know your team was spying.
There is no other reason you
were here in the U.S. waters.
You're a scientist,
so you must have developed
a technology to do that spying.
And, well, we know
something exists.
And it's really only
a matter of time
until we realize what it is.
And every second
we waste here in this room,
it's another life on the line.
A child, a parent,
a soldier in San Diego?
Help me save those lives
you put into harm's way!
And I'll do whatever I have
to do to make this go away!
But there
are people dying, Dr. Lee!
Get your officers
to clear the beach!
Get your officers to clear
that beach and do it now!
You saw the video we sent,
you need to act now!
This is the United States
Coast Guard!
All citizens must evacuated
the beaches immediately
Get everyone off the beach!
[gunfire]
Help me save
those people, Dr. Lee.
All right.
We were acquiring information.
You were hacking.
Satellites.
Our technology.
It drew
the megalodons to us.
It's the sound, I believe.
And can we retrieve it?
Is it still on the ship?
No need to retrieve it.
What do you mean?
We could...
We could save those people...
if you let me help you.
[clamoring]
[gunfire]
The beam is deadly
to most sea creatures.
The sound-wave, in fact,
dis-equilibrates their swim
bladders and even burst them.
But not the sharks?
Not with this power level.
It is possible that it
can damage their inner ears
enough to confuse them with
enough of a pulse, enough time.
Sharks hear much
lower than we do.
This, we believe, is why
they respond to the beamformer.
When you say respond,
you mean it calls them?
And makes them angry.
Wilco?
Can we hook this up to
the P.A. and radio system?
I think I can figure
something out, Captain.
But I have no idea
how this works.
Oh. Lee will help you.
Won't you, Dr. Lee?
I will.
Captain, a word, please?
You're worried, Ahearn.
I do not trust this woman.
Nor should you, but she's
who we need right now.
Without her, a lot
more people in San Diego die.
We gotta call those sharks
back from the San Diego line.
Understood.
Ahearn, you are the most
intelligent, capable officer
I've ever worked with.
I need you to be exactly
who you are
while still doing
what needs to get done.
Understand?
Understood, Captain.
Good man.
Keep an eye on the Tsai for me.
I'll be on this.
Understood, ma'am.
Are we ready?
Uh, we're having
to cross-strap a lot of stuff.
Will we be ready soon?
We will.
Samperio?
If what Lee says is correct,
those things will be
coming in hot and confused.
Ready your team to blow
the last two out of the water.
I want teeth for the hood
of my car.
[gunfire]
Of the beach!
Yeah, I think...
I think we're ready, Captain.
All right.
[beeps]
I don't understand
what I'm looking at here.
I do.
Captain, should I let
her use the terminal?
Explain everything, Dr. Lee,
or it's back to the brig.
We are probing for data packets.
It's the only way the system
is designed to work.
We have to hack.
We do.
Shall I tell it
to access, Captain?
That's the only way it
can reach enough capacity
to bring the megalodons back.
Yes, do it.
Did it work?
Something wrong?
It's not connecting!
I think it's out of synch.
One of these connections
isn't working properly.
We can patch it.
No. If you patch one unit,
then we have to resynch
the whole system!
Whatever we need to do,
do it fast and do it now!
- Let's go!
- Yes, ma'am.
Salles?
Salles!
The Tsai looks
pretty bad, Captain.
How long will this take?
Five minutes at least!
We don't have five minutes!
People are dying, Captain!
Step off the bridge, Mr. Ahearn.
We are screwing around!
We should be saving lives,
not trusting our enemies!
Step off the bridge!
That is an order!
Aye, Captain!
The only enemies are
the megalodons and ourselves!
That is it!
[gunfire]
No...
Status?
Almost there!
It looks good, looks good.
We're ready.
Press the button, Dr. Lee.
[beeping]
Do we need to resynch it again?
It should work!
It's connected everywhere!
Let me try something...
I thought that would work.
You're doing so good.
You're like a super genius
or something, you know.
Salles?
Salles!
Damn it, Salles!
[static]
Is it supposed to do this?
Yes! The vibrations are low!
We can still do damage!
What is the status?
I believe the connections
worked, ma'am.
Tuan, do you see
anything on the radar?
The radar is
unresponsive, Captain.
Try rebooting it.
Wilco, how's your terminal?
Completely unresponsive
as well, ma'am.
I need eyes on windows!
I need eyes everywhere!
Salles?
[sighs]
Okay.
Captain, enemy ships
are approaching!
Not now!
Not now, damn it!
Wilco!
Ready the P.A. system!
Yes, ma'am.
Attention, all crew!
Three destroyers on approach!
Ready battle stations!
[alarm blares]
Okay.
Battle stations!
All crew to battle stations!
Battle stations now!
Look alive!
Come on.
Come on, don't do it.
Do not come here now!
Oh, we need more help!
Ma'am, we're getting a text-only
readout from Commander Moore.
It's still working.
What does it say?
"The Naval Base's fleet,
is completely destroyed,
but they're sending
reinforcements now."
He better send them fast.
Any word from Admiral Green?
He's still talking to the
Chinese, but our orders stand.
Our do-nothing orders?
Are they sending anyone to us?
Status quo, ma'am.
The jets, they're
ready to deploy.
But we don't have an update yet.
Wire the Admiral again.
We need help.
Yes, ma'am.
Ma'am...
This is my father's knife.
He carried it with him all
the way through Vietnam.
But I've dishonored him and
his memory by thinking of myself
instead of my crew
and my captain.
If you would have me, Captain,
I would like to retake my post.
Permission granted, Ahearn,
and not a moment too soon.
We're getting ready
to join this fight.
The other ships need us.
Thank you, Captain.
Killian, get us going.
Yes, ma'am.
[clamoring]
We hit the small one!
One hell of a shot, boys!
Lay him up! Yeah!
We're hit, men! We're hit!
Shoot that thing!
Shoot that shark down now!
He's going down!
The Tsai put a bullet in him!
Hell, yeah!
Ma'am, the lower deck
tells me that
they're sustaining
a lot of damage!
How bad?
Manageable, ma'am...
they think.
They're working on it now.
Captain Lynch! Ahead!
It's coming right at us!
Fire!
I'm not seeing any
lone survivors, ma'am.
Well, keep an eye out, Tuan.
Yes, ma'am.
It's time to move outta here
before the other one comes back.
Wilco, what's our comm
situation?
No comms,
but ELF only, ma'am.
Tell Ping we're ready
to give back Dr. Lee.
Yes, ma'am.
And our previous
offer still stands.
The beast is still out there
and these waters are not safe.
Yes, ma'am.
Are you ready
to go home, Dr. Lee?
Yes, I think I will.
It's safer for you that I do.
Think about what's best to
help your country, Dr. Lee.
That's the idea, Captain.
All right! All right!
Let's go, people!
These waters aren't safe and
the shark's still out there!
Let's go!
The ships are going down!
Change of plans!
We have to destroy that thing!
- Fire!
Full steam ahead!
Let's catch that thing!
Yes, ma'am.
Fire, fire, fire!
Survivors! Survivors!
Let's bring 'em up!
Let's go! Let's go!
Come on, come on!
Let's go, let's go!
Come on!
Ahearn, Ensign Brand,
Get them inside and
make them comfortable.
We need to get to
shore, ASAP.
Yes, ma'am.
Full steam ahead,
that thing is coming back,
and we need to get to port
before it catches us.
Samperio, keep your gunners
on their toes.
We are our most vulnerable.
We need to take that shark out.
Ma'am, we're out of ammo.
We've got nothing left.
I need eyes on that shark, Tuan!
Sonar's still a little...
Got it! Circling, moving
out fast!
We don't have long!
Let's go!
Engineering says the ship
doesn't have long either, ma'am.
We took an eye out, Captain.
Look, we got handguns
and rifles.
We can still take
this thing down.
That was a lucky shot, Samperio!
I don't expect we'll
get another one,
but let's ready
the weapons just in case.
Yes, ma'am.
Killian, can we make it
before those things come back?
I'm not hopeful
with that, Captain.
These things are fast
and we're injured badly.
- Ahearn?
- Yes, ma'am.
Take the con!
Killian, keep moving
for land as fast as we can go!
Yes, ma'am.
Samperio, the moment
we see that thing...
We'll go after it hand to
hand if we have to, Captain!
Follow me, Dr. Lee.
I have nothing to say
to you, Captain.
Then just listen.
Our ship is badly damaged,
possibly sunk.
I'm just trying to
save everybody's lives,
including yours.
Now my government won't
step in because your government
will consider it an act of war.
I need your help.
What kind of help?
Well, that's just the thing.
I'm a captain and so are you.
I think the reason
that we lost to it
is because we were fighting
alone and not together.
What would you do if
you were me, Captain Ping?
I don't understand
your question.
I'm saying if someone
on your team
must have worked
on this project.
And someone must have faced
off with this thing before.
Those things have
a real vendetta
against your ships
and now ours, too.
Now the beamformer.
It must disorient them,
distract them.
I know it draws
them to the tech,
but I don't think they like it.
I don't know what
you mean... beamformer.
Where is your ship, Dr. Lee?
If you can take us to
the ship, I can help you.
Follow me to the bridge,
Captain Ping.
What the hell did they just say?
I had no idea what the hell
did they just said.
This is our sense.
It kills aquatic life
in its path...
I see.
And yet the megalodons
appears to be...
Attracted to it...
Although the
ship might be sunk,
but it appears that the SAT
tech might still be alive.
It might help us... perhaps.
Crew, this is Captain Ping.
He's going to help us...
not die.
Tuan, are we still receiving the
signal from their sunken ship?
Yes, ma'am.
Captain Ping, what do we do?
We must go to it.
We must use its
beamform technology
to destroy them.
Killian?
Set a course
for the sunken ship.
That's the opposite direction
off the coast, Captain.
Yes, it is, Killian.
Let's go.
Yes, ma'am.
Ma'am! The engine crew
is saying that
we're taking on a lot of water.
They are not sure
how long we can make it.
We got about a one in a million
shot to survive this, people.
But it's the only one we got,
so we're gonna take it.
Killian, turn us around.
Now you think
Lee's device will be able to...
Connect to the device
on the sunken ship.
And this whole ship will become
some kind of transponder.
I don't know what will
happen to us nor its ship.
Captain Ping...
If we do this, it will destroy
all the information
that we gathered.
[speaking Mandarin]
You've got to
be kidding me.
Is there something wrong,
Killian?
They're speaking in code, sir.
It's Mandarin, Killian.
It's a language spoken by
billions all over the world.
Just because
you don't understand it
doesn't mean it's code.
They could be leading
us into a trap,
trying to protect whatever's on
that ship from being discovered.
I trust the Captain
and the Captain trusts them,
so I trust them.
You got a problem
with that, sailor?
No, sir.
Good.
Ahearn?
What's the update on
Engineering?
Been better, ma'am.
Are we sinking?
Not yet, ma'am.
I'll call that a win for now.
Wilco, do you and
Lee have that thing set up?
I do, ma'am.
But when we turn
this thing on...
Yes?
We're gonna lose al our comms,
probably much more than that.
Understood, Wilco.
Target has been spotted, ma'am.
The beast is in sight.
Fire a warning shot, Samperio!
Keep those things distracted!
Yes, ma'am.
Again, Samperio!
It's my last shot, ma'am.
You want me to take it?
No.
We don't know if this will work
and we'll need everything
we got left.
Yes, ma'am.
Ma'am, we're just
over the top of it.
While we're here, we cannot move
our positions, no matter what.
It will disrupt the connection.
Well, screw it.
Turn on the device.
Yes, ma'am.
[beeps]
Are you okay?
I'm good.
Any sign of it?
No sign of it.
Must be way down there.
Or dead...
We need to be sure.
Ma'am, it's...
It didn't work!
That shark's still alive.
We're dead!
We're all dead!
No, no, we're not.
Not yet.
Battle stations!
Let's go!
[alarm blares]
Arm yourselves!
We have to be ready!
Let's go! Let's go!
Battle stations!
Come on!
Let's go! Battle stations!
Let's do this!
Battle stations!
Come on!
Let's go, people!
Let's get 'em!
Come on!
Eyes to the sea!
Eyes to the sea! Let's go!
Get ready, y'all.
[gunfire]
Let's go, boys!
[grunting, shouting]
- Wilco!
- No!
No!
[screams]
Where is it?
Anybody see it?
Does anybody see it?
Disappeared.
It must be underneath us!
It's gonna hull us,
drag us down!
It stopped.
It knows we're dead.
It's waiting for us
to climb out.
We're gonna be lunch.
I'll stay aboard
and distract it.
Everybody go!
Like I'm leaving you,
Captain... or anyone else.
Head to engineering!
Have them rev the engines!
Bring that thing back to us!
Here it comes!
Wait for it to come close!
Whites of the eyes, people!
2:00!
[shouting]
What happened, Captain?
Something hit it.
It's Commander Moore's sub!
He's heading for the megalodon!
Okay, you big giant...
The ship's going down, Captain!
Are there any more
lifeboats, Ahearn?
No, ma'am.
Do you think Commander Moore
killed it... or it killed him?
I think we're gonna
find out very soon!
Give it everything you got!
Get ready for it!
[laughing]
I'd have brought a bigger boat
if I'd known
there'd been any left!
We won, baby! We won!
Yes!
Thank you!
That's what
I'm talking about, baby!
I love this thing.
Hoo-rah. Okay, fishes,
it's a watery grave.
We're goin' in.
Abandon ship!
Let's go, people!
We lost a lot of
good people today.
If it weren't for the bravery
from both my crew
and the many men
and women of San Diego,
as well as members
of the Chinese Navy,
far more destruction would have
been wrought by these creatures.
Excuse me, Captain Lynch.
Were you aware of the existence
of more of these creatures?
We've officially
seen no evidence
that there are any
more of these megalodons.
Officially seen?
That is correct.
But you weren't
officially aware of these three
before they
demolished the base.
So how do we know
there aren't more out there?
We don't.
There are rumors that
you're tagging and tracking
undersea objects and there
may be more megalodons.
I don't comment on rumors.
Captain Lynch, care to
comment on your sister's case?
What were Chinese ships
doing in U.S. waters?
Are we going to war?
Thank you.
That is all I have to say
about this at the present time.
- Captain Lynch...
- Captain Lynch... please!
- Captain Lynch?
Captain Lynch...
Hey, what is that?
That's the thing.
I don't know.
- I can't make out...
- Can't tell what it is...
How'd I do?
- Terrible.
I'm ready to get
back in the water.
How's the tagging
and tracking going?
Hard to say.
Do you think they're mates?
- Not till we go looking.
- Not until we go looking.
- Well...
- We won't know.
Let's go looking, gentlemen.
Is that your thing? Like
repeating everything I say?
- Oh, my goodness...
- I'm not trying...
Let's go!
It just that it seems like I am.
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull