♪♪
GEORGE, I'M SURE MR. MacDONALD WILL SERVE
THE ULYSSES WITH THE SAME PRECISION THAT EARNED HIM TOP
HONORS THROUGHOUT HIS CAREER.
WE'RE HAPPY TO HAVE HIM.
MR. MURPHY, YOU'LL SEE TO IT OUR NEW X.O. WILL HAVE
EVERYTHING HE NEEDS BEFORE WE GET UNDERWAY.
AYE-AYE, CAPTAIN.
GENTLEMEN, GIVE THE COMMANDER AND I A MOMENT.
THIS IS YOUR FIRST REAL TOUR--MUST BE EXCITING FOR YOU.
YOU'LL BE WORKING WITH A GREAT CREW.
SO I WAS TOLD.
I'M LOOKING FORWARD TO IT.
YOU'RE THE YOUNGEST X.O.
ON RECORD, AM I RIGHT?
I WOULDN'T KNOW THAT.
I JUST KNOW I EARNED MY JOB.
OF COURSE YOU DID.
YOU GENTLEMEN GETTING ACQUAINTED OKAY?
GETTING ALONG JUST FINE.
HAPPY TO HAVE HIM ABOARD.
FINE, I'LL EXPECT YOU TO SHOW COMMANDER LANGE
SOME EXCELLENT TEAMWORK.
YOU'LL SHIP OUT TOMORROW.
OH, NO, THEY WON'T.
EXCUSE ME, DO YOU KNOW WHO YOU'RE TALKING TO?
HE'S ALL RIGHT.
THAT'S JAMES CARTER.
HE DESIGNED THE SUBMARINE.
HE'S EX-NAVY, USED TO BE A SEAL, AND ONE OF THE BEST.
THAT'S RIGHT. MR. MacDONALD, MR. MURPHY, SEE YOU ON BOARD.
YOU'RE DISMISSED.
Both: AYE, CAPTAIN.
CARTER, IT'S A HELL OF A TIME FOR A MALFUNCTION.
DON'T TELL ME IT'S THE REACTOR.
NO.
THE ELECTRICAL SYSTEM?
NO, NOT THAT, EITHER.
THEN WHAT IS IT?
I NEED A NEW DEEP FRYER.
HELLO, GEORGE, JOHNNY.
THIS IS TOMMY, MY SON.
HELLO, TOMMY.
YOU THINK YOUR DAD'S PRETTY FUNNY, DON'T YOU?
YES I DO, SIR, VERY FUNNY.
ADMIRAL. I'VE REVIEWED YOUR AGENDA FOR THE JOINT CHIEFS
MEETING.
I'VE ALSO INCLUDED S.O.P.
ON NUCLEAR PROTOCOL.
THE CAR'S READY, SIR.
SWELL. GOOD SAILING, GEORGE.
SEE YOU AT HOMECOMING.
SIR.
SEE YOU, JAMES.
WOW, DAD, YOU SHOULD'VE GOT HER PHONE NUMBER.
( laughs )  ANYWAY, WHO IS SHE?
AH, LIEUTENANT COMMANDER LISA STARK, SPECIAL
COMMUNICATIONS OFFICER-- ADMIRAL PENDELTON'S RIGHT HAND.
SMART AS A WHIP.
JIM, I GOTTA GET ON BOARD.
I WANT TO THANK YOU FOR TAKING A LOOK FOR ME.
SOUNDS GOOD.
YOU HAVE A GOOD ONE. TAKE CARE.
SEE YOU WHEN WE GET BACK.
WILL DO.
BE WELL.
HER NAME'S LISA.
YOU SHOULD'VE GOT HER PHONE NUMBER.
♪♪  SO, IT TURNS OUT THIS
MacDONALD IS ONE OF THE MacDONALDS, FROM THE
CONNECTICUT MacDONALDS!
USED TO STEER HIS DADDY'S YACHT ON WEEKENDS.
( laughter )  MURPHY...
YOU HAVE A PROBLEM WITH ME?
NO PROBLEM AT ALL, SIR.
I EXPECT YOU GENTLEMEN TO SHOW SOME RESPECT TO THE NEW X.O.
CAPTAIN'S IN CONTROL.
HOW WE DOIN', MURPH?
SAILING SMOOTH, SIR.
VERY WELL. MR. MacDONALD, RUN A STATION CHECK FOR US.
YES, SIR.
SONAR, CONN, SYSTEM CHECK.
SONAR REPORTING.
WELCOME ABOARD, SIR.
( imitating Bill Clinton ) AND MAY I SAY THAT MY
INVOLVEMENT IN WHITEWATER WAS ENTIRELY HILLARY'S FAULT--
NAVIGATION.
STEADY AT 808 DEGREES AND READY TO ROLL, SIR.
WEAPONS.
FIRE CONTROL 1, SWEET AND FINE-LOOKING AS A WOMAN AT
THE END OF TOUR, SIR.
HOW'S OUR PILOT DOING?
A-OKAY, SIR, ALL READY.
( laughter )  MR. COLLINS, WHAT THE HELL
WAS THAT?
IT MEANS CRASH DIVE, SIR.
CRASH DIVE.
AND UNDER WHAT CIRCUMSTANCES DOES A 688-ATTACK CLASS
SUBMARINE WITH TOMAHAWK MISSILES EVER DO A CRASH DIVE?
NEVER, SIR.
I TRUST YOU HAVE ENOUGH INTELLIGENCE TO REMEMBER THAT.
ALL SET, MR. MacDONALD?
YES, SIR.
SUBMERGE THE SHIP.
SUBMERGE THE SHIP, AYE, SIR.
ALL HANDS, PREPARE TO DIVE.
♪♪ MR. COLLINS, THREE DEGREES
DOWN BUBBLE.
MAKE YOUR DEPTH 150 FEET.
THREE DEGREES DOWN BUBBLE.
MAKING MY DEPTH 150 FEET.
( guitar playing ) ( rhythmic clapping )
♪ I NEED A WOMAN ♪ TO LOVE AND TREAT ME RIGHT
♪ YEAH, YEAH ♪ I NEED A WOMAN
♪ FOR EACH AND EVERY NIGHT ♪ NIGHT
♪ OH, OH ♪ YOU NEED A WOMAN
♪ HE NEEDS A WOMAN  I NEED A WOMAN!
♪ YEAH, WE ALL NEED ♪ A WOMAN, NEED A WOMAN
♪ YEAH, YEAH, YEAH  ♪ WE NEED A WOMAN
♪ YEAH, YEAH, YEAH  ♪ OH, A LITTLE WOMAN
♪ YEAH, YEAH, YEAH  ♪ ONE MORE, NOW, WOMAN
♪ YEAH, YEAH, YEAH  ♪ BREAK IT OFF ONE TIME
♪ MAMA, I WANT TO BE A SAILOR ♪ YES, I GOTTA LEAVE MY
♪ NEIGHBORHOOD, IT'S SO GOOD ♪ IF YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN
♪ TO GO AWAY ON A SUBMARINE ♪ ME AND MY BOYS ARE ON A
♪ MISSION TO PROTECT AGAINST ♪ THE EVIL OPPOSITION
♪ AND WE'RE ARMED WITH ♪ A NUCLEAR BOMB, FUCK WITH
♪ THE U.S., AND IT'S ON  ( laughter and cheers )
Tommy: EMPTY BALLASTS!
AYE-AYE, SIR!
AHH!
YOU SCARED ME.
I SCARED YOU, HUH?
COME ON, IT'S TIME FOR DINNER.
HAVE YOU SCOPED UP LISA YET?
NO, I HAVEN'T SCOPED OUT LISA YET.
YOU'RE DOING A GOOD JOB HERE, BUDDY, REAL GOOD.
SHE'S JUST WHAT THE DOCTOR ORDERED.
OH, YOU THINK SO, DO YOU?
SHE'S JUST WHAT THE DOCTOR ORDERED?
WELL, YOU KNOW WHAT I THINK?
WHAT?
THE DOCTOR ORDERED DINNER.
CONN TO RADIO.
RADIO, CONN, GO AHEAD.
CAPTAIN, I'VE GOT A DISTRESS CALL COMING IN FROM TOPSIDE.
IT'S PRETTY WEAK, SIR.
PATCH IT THROUGH.
Man: ( Russian accent ) MAYDAY, MAYDAY, OUR SHIP
IS DESTROYED BY STORM!
ONLY FIVE OF US ARE ALIVE.
WE ARE IN A SMALL RAFT.
BY THE LOVE OF GOD, HELP US!
HELP US!
PETTY OFFICER WAGER, WHAT'S THE WEATHER TOPSIDE?
15-FOOT SWELLS, AND I GIVE YOU 10 TO 1 ODDS THERE'S
A HURRICANE COMING.
THE NEAREST SHIP?
NOTHING FOR OVER 100 KLICKS.
WE SHOULD PICK THEM UP, SIR.
ORDERS ARE SILENT PATROL.
NOTHING SILENT ABOUT SURFACING.
IT PUTS US AT RISK FOR DETECTION.
THE STORM WILL SWALLOW THOSE PEOPLE UNLESS WE HELP THEM.
MR. MURPHY!
GENTLEMEN...
MR. MURPHY, TAKE US TO THE SURFACE.
TO THE SURFACE, AYE.
MR. MacDONALD.
THREE DEGREES UP BUBBLE, SMARTLY.
THREE DEGREES UP BUBBLE, SMARTLY. AYE, SIR.
MR. MacDONALD, YOU ARE HERE TO LEARN AS WELL AS SERVE.
BOOKS AND RILLS ARE ONE THING, BUT AS THE EXECUTIVE OFFICER
OF ONE OF THE DEADLIEST WEAPONS EVER KNOWN TO MANKIND, IT WOULD
BE A GOOD IDEA FOR YOU TO LEARN A LITTLE BIT ABOUT HUMANITY.
IS THAT UNDERSTOOD?
YES, SIR.
NOW, MR. MacDONALD, YOU ARE NOW PERSONALLY RESPONSIBLE FOR
EACH AND EVERY ONE OF THOSE SURVIVORS.
SEE TO IT EACH OF THEM MAKE IT ON BOARD SAFELY AND THAT THEY
HAVE A COMFORTABLE STAY WHILE THEY'RE WITH US. CLEAR?
YES, SIR.
VERY WELL.
MR. MURPHY, SEE TO IT THE MEDICS ARE STANDING BY.
AYE, CAPTAIN.
PREPARE TO SURFACE.
WE'RE GONNA PICK UP SURVIVORS TOPSIDE.
ATTENTION MEDICS, RESCUE TEAM, REPORT TO THE TOWER
IMMEDIATELY.
♪♪ ( beeping )
( screaming ) ( indistinct chatter )
GIVE ME YOUR HAND!
( shouting )  COME ON, GET 'EM ON!
LET'S MOVE!
( shouting )  GET 'EM BELOW AS QUICKLY
AS POSSIBLE!
WELL, THEY DID IT.
( alarm buzzing ) TAKE US DOWN, MR. MURPHY.
AYE, CAPTAIN.
MR. COLLINS, TAKE US DOWN.
AYE, SIR.
DO THEY HAVE ANY WEAPONS?
NO, SIR.
TAKE THEM TO THE WARDROOM SO THEY CAN DRY OFF, SEE TO IT
THEIR CLOTHES ARE DRIED.
THANK YOU, SIR.
THANK YOU VERY, VERY MUCH.
WE ARE GRATEFUL. SPASIBA.
TAKE THEM TO THEIR QUARTERS.
YES, SIR.
FOUR MEN, ONE WOMAN, SIR.
IF THERE'S A WOMAN, SHE SHOULD HAVE SECURE QUARTERS.
I'LL SEE TO IT.
THE X.O. HAS RESPONSIBILITY FOR THE SURVIVORS.
HE'LL SEE TO IT.
YES, SIR.
IS SHE PRETTY, SIR?
I DIDN'T NOTICE.
MR. MURPHY, YOU HAVE THE CONN.
HE DIDN'T NOTICE.
CHRIST, HIS ASS IS SO TIGHT, A DIME COULDN'T DROP OUT OF
THE CRACK.
( laughter )  UH, I DRIED CLOTHES
FOR YOU, MA'AM.
COULD YOU PLEASE TURN YOUR BACK?
YEAH.
HEY, WHAT'S THE MATTER?
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
YOU'RE OKAY.
YOU'RE ON THE BEST BOAT IN THE FLEET.
IT'S OKAY, NOTHING'S GONNA HAPPEN TO YOU.
( speaks Russian ) ( crack )
( moaning )  ( choking )
( choking ) ( exhales )
EXCUSE ME.
CAN I ASK YOU SOMETHING?
YES, MA'AM, ANYTHING.
WHAT ROOM IS IT?
OH, THIS IS WHERE WE KEEP THE WEAPONS AND--
GO.
Wager: SIR, WE HAVE A COMMUNICATIONS ERROR.
FIND IT, MR. WAGER.
LIEUTENANT, I THINK YOU SHOULD SEE THIS.
THAT'S THE ULYSSES.
RADIO COMMUNICATIONS ARE BLOCKED.
GET ME ADMIRAL PENDELTON.
AND THERE'S NO RESPONSE TO RADIO CALLS?
NONE AT ALL, SIR.
WHAT ASSETS DO WE HAVE IN THE VICINITY?
WE HAVE SEVERAL TARGETS COMBING THE AREA, BUT WE CAN'T
GET A BEARING ON IT.
IT'S POSSIBLE THE HIGH-RANGE DROP BUOY SONAR--
WILL PICK UP EVERY WHALE AND SHARK IN A TEN-MILE RADIUS.
THE SUB PROBABLY HAS A MOVING SIGNATURE.
GET ME JAMES CARTER.
AND GET ME THE PRESIDENT!
RIGHT AWAY, SIR.
WE TAKE ONLY WHAT WE CAN CARRY NOW. WE CAN ALWAYS
COME BACK FOR MORE.
LET'S GO.
JAMES ALLEN CARTER?
YEAH.
I'M LIEUTENANT COMMANDER LISA STARK, SPECIAL
COMMUNICATIONS OFFICER FOR THE NORTH ATLANTIC.
OH, YEAH, YEAH.
WE MET BEFORE.
I DON'T RECALL.
HEH, I THOUGHT YOU'D NEVER FORGET.
WE HAVE A SERIOUS SITUATION ON OUR HANDS.
I WAS HOPING YOU'D SAY THAT.
A SERIOUS MILITARY SITUATION.
ADMIRAL PENDELTON SENT ME.
TOMMY!
THE ULYSSES IS MISSING.
MISSING?
DAD! IS THAT LISA FROM THE BASE?
YEAH, THIS IS SPECIAL OFFICER STARK.
YOU CAN CALL ME LISA.
HI, SPECIAL STARK.
I'M TOMMY.
TOMMY, GO GET US SOME JACKETS, OKAY?
WE'RE GONNA GO FIND US A SUB.
OKAY.
LET'S GO.
( indistinct chatter )  EXCUSE ME, THIS IS
A RESTRICTED AREA.
ARE YOU CAPTAIN LANGE?
YES, I AM.
I WANT TO THANK YOU IN PERSON.
( overlapping shouts )  DON'T MOVE!
GET YOUR HANDS UP!
( guns cocking )  ( imitating Clint Eastwood )
WELL, THIS NEW MacDONALD KID'S REALLY A PUNK.
SOMEONE NEEDS TO TAKE HIM OUT AND SLAP HIM AROUND A LITTLE.
HELLO.
HEY.
YOU MAKE FUNNY VOICES?
( imitating Jack Nicholson ) WELL, I'LL DO ANY VOICE
THAT YOU WANT ME TO DO.
MAKE THE QUIET ONE.
MY NAME IS RICHTER.
I KNOW CONTROL THIS SUBMARINE.
IF YOU DON'T COOPERATE--  HEY!
( gunshots ) OH!
I THINK THAT SAYS IT ALL.
SAPRICH, TAKE A LOOK AROUND.
IT'S ALL FAMILIAR TO YOU, NO?
YES, JUST LIKE THE PLANS I STUDIED.
WE WILL HAVE NO PROBLEMS HERE.
WE WILL NOT TAKE ORDERS FROM YOU.
YOUR FORMER CAPTAIN HAS BEEN RELIEVED OF HIS DUTIES, SO I AM
YOUR CAPTAIN NOW.
IF THERE ARE ANY PROBLEMS, MR. SAPRICH CAN RELIEVE YOU
OF YOUR DUTIES AS WELL.
BOLANNE?
YES?
GO TO THE MACHINE ROOM AND THE AIR CONDITIONING SYSTEM.
BYPASS THE DUCTS FOR THE RADIO ROOM, THE SONAR ROOM,
AND THIS ROOM, AND FLOOD THE REST WITH GAS.
WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU DOING?
THE REST OF THE CREW WILL SLEEP FOR A WHILE, MR. LANGE.
YOU WON'T BE NEEDING YOUR KEY ANYMORE.
OR YOU, MR. MacDONALD.
MOVE!
DOWN, DOWN, DOWN, DOWN!
FIND HIM AND GET THAT KEY BEFORE THE GAS FILLS THE HALLS!
AND GET A MASK!
GET THE FORMER CAPTAIN'S BODY OUT OF MY SIGHT.
YOU! YOU!
MR. NEWTON, GO WITH HIM.
IF THEY TRY ANYTHING, SHOOT THEM.
( gas hisses ) ( gas hissing )
( coughing ) WHAT IS THAT?
( coughing )  Man: MR. CARTER, THIS WAY.
GOOD MORNING.
WHAT'S THE MATTER, ADMIRAL?
LOSE A SUB?
YOU BELIEVE IT?
YOU GOT ANY IDEAS?
LAST KNOWN POSITION WAS 700 MILES OFF THE COAST,
NEAR THE MID-ATLANTIC RIDGE.
WE THOUGHT YOU COULD IDENTIFY THE UNIQUE MOTION SIGNATURE
ON THE DROP BUOY RADAR.
WHOSE IDEA WAS THAT?
MINE.
NOT BAD, BUT IT WON'T WORK.
I'LL NEED THE HEAT REGISTRATION VIEW FROM THE SEASAC SATELLITE.
HEAT REGISTRATION?
HOW CAN YOU POSSIBLY PINPOINT A DEEPLY SUBMERGED VESSEL?
THE WATER AT THE SURFACE WILL--  TRUST ME. BRING IT UP.
I'LL PUT HIM IN MY OFFICE.
ENLARGE.
ENLARGE TWO MORE TIMES.
ONE MORE TIME.
THAT'S IT.
THAT'S THE ULYSSES.
BUT HOW CAN YOU SAY THAT FOR SURE?
HERE'S THE HEAT RADIATING RADIATING FROM THE REACTOR,
AND HERE'S THE COOLEST PART OF THE SUB.
BUT THEY HAVEN'T BUDGED.
ANY RADIO CONTACT?
NONE. I DON'T GET IT.
WELL, LISTEN, I'M SORRY TO BRING YOU DOWN HERE LIKE THIS.
IT'S OKAY. I'LL GRAB MY KID, AND I'M OUT OF HERE.
SIR, THERE'S AN EMERGENCY CALL FROM THE ULYSSES.
THIS IS ADMIRAL PENDELTON, U.S. NAVY.
Richter: AND THIS IS THE NEW CAPTAIN OF THE ULYSSES.
THE CHIEF OF BOAT WILL NOW BRIEF YOU/
DON'T MAKE A MISTAKE, OR YOU'LL DIE.
THIS IS CHIEF OF THE BOAT MURPHY.
ULYSSES HAS BEEN TAKEN OVER BY TERRORISTS.
THE CREW HAS BEEN GASSED.
CAPTAIN LANGE IS DEAD.
JESUS.
AND?
AND THEY HAVE THE LAUNCH KEYS.
TO GET ULYSSES BACK WILL COST YOU $100 MILLION IN GOLD.
IF YOU DON'T COMPLY, I'LL USE THE NUCLEAR MISSILES ON BOARD
AND DESTROY WASHINGTON, D.C.
LISTEN UP, WHOEVER YOU ARE-- YOU HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT WE ARE PREPARED TO DO.
( laughs ) YOU MEAN SINK US?
I DON'T THINK SO.
IF WE EVEN SUSPECT THERE ARE ANY SUBS NEAR US
WE'LL LAUNCH THE MISSILES.
YOU HAVE 24 HOURS TO DELIVER THE GOLD.
I'LL CALL BACK WITH THE COORDINATES FOR THE DROP.
SAPRICH, I THINK THE CREW SHOULD BE SUFFICIENTLY
INTOXICATED BY NOW.
HAVE THEM DRAGGED INTO THE MESS HALL AND LOCK THE DOOR.
WE'VE GOT TWO SCENARIOS.
WE CAN PAY THEM THE MONEY AND PRAY THEY GIVE THE SUB BACK
AND DON'T JUST POINT THE MISSILES AT SOME OTHER COUNTRY,
OR...WE BRING OUT OUR FORCES AND SINK THE ULYSSES.
SIR, THAT'S 100 MEN AND A BILLION-DOLLAR SUBMARINE.
IS THE PRESIDENT PREPARED TO MAKE THAT DECISION?
HE'LL HAVE TO!
THOSE NUKES CANNOT BE LAUNCHED!
IT WOULDN'T ONLY BE THE END OF D.C.
THE FALLOUT WOULD POISON THE ATLANTIC, AND THE AIRBORNE
WILL HIT EUROPE-- UNLESS THE WIND'S BLOWING
THE OTHER WAY.
IN THAT CASE, THE CONTINENTAL U.S. BECOMES A VAST WASTELAND.
WE COULD USE ANOTHER PLAN.
THE S.S.N. DAVIES IS HEADING IN THEIR DIRECTION
FROM THE AZORES PLATEAU.
WHAT IF WE GET SOMEONE ONTO THE DAVIES?
MAYBE THEY COULD USE A SUBMERSIBLE TO GET ONTO
THE ULYSSES AND DISARM THE MISSILES MANUALLY.
SOMEONE WHO'S INTIMATELY FAMILIAR WITH THE INTERNAL
WIRINGS OF THE COMPUTER SYSTEM THROUGHOUT THE SUB.
NO.
JAMES--  WITH ALL DUE RESPECT, SIR,
I'M RETIRED.
BUT YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE WHO KNOWS THAT SUB WELL ENOUGH
TO PULL IT OFF.
LOOK, IF I HAD ONLY MY LIFE TO WORRY ABOUT, I WOULDN'T
HESITATE--YOU KNOW THAT.
BUT I'VE GOT A SON WHO LOST HIS MOTHER, AND I'M NOT GONNA
LET HIM LOSE HIS FATHER, TOO.
DAD, THEY NEED YOU TO HELP THEM.
YOU CAN'T SAY NO.
HEY, PAL.
I THOUGHT YOU WERE SLEEPING.
I UNDERSTAND.
BUT, CARTER, IF YOU DON'T GO, 100 SAILORS LOSE THEIR LIVES,
THEIR FAMILIES LOSE THEIR HUSBANDS AND SONS,
AND MILLIONS OF PEOPLE LOSE EVERYTHING.
WE NEED YOU, JAMES.
YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE THAT KNOWS THAT SUB INSIDE AND OUT.
DAD?
HOW FAST CAN YOU GET ME THERE?
HI, AUNT JANE!
TOMMY!
JIM, IS EVERYTHING ALL RIGHT?
WE'VE GOT A SITUATION ON OUR HANDS.
CAN YOU WATCH TOMMY FOR ME?
WELL, OF COURSE I WILL.
I WAS PLANNING ON GOING UP TO NEW YORK THIS WEEKEND.
CAN I TAKE HIM WITH ME?
I THINK THAT'S GREAT.
HE'S BEEN BUGGING ME FOREVER TO SEE THE EMPIRE STATE BUILDING.
YEAH!
YEAH. COME HERE.
I DON'T WANT YOU TO WORRY ABOUT ANYTHING, OKAY?
I'LL BE BACK SOON.
DAD, I KNOW YOU'LL TAKE CARE OF EVERYTHING AND YOU'LL
BE BACK.
THAT'S RIGHT, I'LL BE BACK.
GIVE ME A HUG.
YEAH. PERFECT.
UH, CARTER...WE HAVE TO GO.
CHOPPER'S WAITING AT THE AIRSTRIP.
YOU TAKE CARE OF YOURSELF, OKAY?
YEAH.
HERE'S THE CONTACT NUMBER.
OKAY.
BYE.
♪♪
SO, WHAT'S YOUR PLAN?
BY TAPPING INTO THE BSY-1 WEAPONS COMPUTER, I CAN SWAP
THE CODES OF THE TOMAHAWK NUKES WITH THE HARPOON MISSILES,
WHICH ARE ONLY T.N.T.
WASHINGTON WILL STILL TAKE A BAD HIT, BUT AT LEAST
IT WON'T BE NUKED.
YEAH, BUT IF I CAN'T RESET THE GUIDANCE SYSTEM, WHO CAN
GIVE ME COORDINATES ON A SAFE TARGET ZONE?
THE PLOTTER-- NICKNAMED WAGER--SUPPOSEDLY
HE CAN DO LATITUDES AND LONGITUDES IN HIS HEAD.
THESE TWO ARE YOUR FIGHTING EXPERTS.
COLLINS-- NAVY WRESTLING CHAMP.
MURPHY--MOST EXPERIENCED ON THE SHIP EXCEPT FOR THE CAPTAIN.
DENT IN SONAR.
ROBINSON AND DALEY IN WEAPONS.
I'LL MEMORIZE THEIR FACES.
LET'S HOPE THESE GUYS ARE STILL ALIVE.
THE CHOPPER'S READY FOR YOU UP ON DECK, SIR.
TELL THEM I'LL BE RIGHT THERE.
YOU GOT EVERYTHING YOU NEED IN THAT BAG.
THIS IS A SHORT-BURST RADIO.
YOUR MESSAGES ARE RECORDED ON THE MICROCHIP, COMPRESSED--
I'VE USED ONE BEFORE.
I'LL BE BACK IN WASHINGTON WITH THE ADMIRAL BY THE TIME
YOU GET ON THE ULYSSES, SO WE'LL WAIT FOR YOUR
FIRST TRANSMISSION.
IF WE NEED TO CONTACT YOU, THE RADIO WILL VIBRATE
AND YOU'LL READ OUR MESSAGE ON THE DISPLAY.
LOOKS LIKE I'LL BE KEEPING YOU UP AT NIGHT, HUH?
ON THE RADIO.
♪♪  ( coughing )
VERY GOOD.
NOW, MR. ROBINSON, OPEN THE SAFE TO THE LAUNCH TRIGGER.
DON'T DO IT, MAN.
MR. ROBINSON?
DON'T DO IT, TONY!
DON'T DO IT!
( gasps )  TAKE HIM OUT.
WE CAN DO THIS ALL DAY.
OKAY. DON'T SHOOT.
( beeping ) ( beeping )
MOUNTAINOUS TERRAIN AHEAD.
APPROACHING FAST.
WE'RE TOO DEEP.
YOU'RE GONNA KILL US ALL.
SHUT UP.
I KNOW WHAT I'M DOING.
PROCEED WITH YOUR COURSE.
IMPACT, DEAD AHEAD.
( all shouting )  NOW!
DON'T MOVE.
EVERYBODY HOLD IT RIGHT THERE OR YOUR BOSS GETS IT!
BOLANNE.
AAH!
STAY PUT.
NOW ARE WE ALL SETTLED DOWN?
THERE'S AN AVALANCHE OUTSIDE, BRACE FOR IMPACT!
( all shouting ) ( grunting )
( shouting )  I DON'T KNOW, BUT THERE'S
WATER RUSHING IN FROM THE WALLS!
GET TO THE DOOR!
OH, MY HEAD.
WHAT THE HELL HAPPENED?
NEWTON?
SIR.
GET THIS CLOWN INTO THE SONAR ROOM.
AND TIE THEM TO THEIR POSTS.
I WANT TO SEE MORE COMMITMENT TO THEIR JOBS.
OPEN THE DOOR!
IT'S LOCKED FROM THE OTHER SIDE!
LET US OUT!
( all shouting at once )  WE GOTTA STOP THIS LEAK!
ANY SIGN OF THEM?
NOT YET.
KEEP LOOKING.
COMMANDER CRICHTON, WE'RE APPROACHING THE RENDEZVOUS
POINT, WE'LL HAVE RADAR CONTACT IN 30 SECONDS.
MR. BURKE, TAKE US TO PERISCOPE DEPTH.
AYE-AYE, SIR.
( beeping )  THERE! CARTER, YOU'D
BETTER GET READY.
GOOD LUCK, SIR.
THE WINDS ARE HIGH, BUT I'LL TRY TO HOLD HER STEADY.
TAKE US DOWN TO 80 FEET AND HOVER.
THEY'RE IN POSITION, SIR.
SIR, MR. CARTER IS AT THE AFT ESCAPE HATCH.
RELEASE THE HATCH.
( whirring )  MR. CARTER'S IN THE CONN.
WATCH COUNTDOWN 13 HOURS, 5 MINUTES.
MR. CARTER, WELCOME ABOARD.
I FIGURE WE CAN GET WITHIN A MILE OF ULYSSES.
GET YOUR GEAR TOGETHER, AND I'LL BRIEF YOU.
THE SHIP'S STABLE.
TAKE US BACK UP 200 FEET AT A REASONABLE RATE OF SPEED.
MR. WAGER, PLOT A COURSE TO TAKE US WITHIN WEAPONS RANGE
OF THE EASTERN SEABOARD.
MR. COLLINS, DON'T RAISE THE SUB.
DO WHAT RICHTER SAYS.
DON'T COUNTERMAND ME!
ARE YOU ABLE TO FULLY GRASP OUR SITUATION HERE, SIR?
HE'S RIGHT, MR. MacDONALD.
COLLINS, I'LL KILL YOUR FRIEND.
SORRY, SIR.
THREE DEGREES UP BUBBLE.
MAKING OUR DEPTH 200 FEET.
WE'RE HERE, 1/4 MILE AHEAD OF THE ULYSSES HERE.
YOU'LL HAVE ONE CHANCE TO GRAB ON ONCE IT COMES BY.
IF YOU MISS IT, WE'LL SWING BACK BY AFTER THEY PASS.
WE'LL BE IN TOTAL SILENCE.
GOOD LUCK.
THANK YOU.
MR. JOHNSON, PREPARE TO RUN SILENT ON MY MARK.
PREPARE TO RUN SILENT, AYE, SIR.
EVERYTHING YOU NEED IS IN THE BAG, SIR--
SHORT BURST COMMUNICATOR, SPEAR GUN, SURVIVAL KIT, ETC.
GOOD LUCK, SIR.
AND...
NOW.
( whirring ) ♪♪
HERE SHE COMES.
MR. COLLINS, LEVEL THE SHIP, PROCEED AT NORMAL SPEED.
( whirring )  WHAT IS IT?
I DON'T KNOW.
WHAT IS IT?!
IT'S PROBABLY A BIOLOGICAL.
IF YOU'LL TAKE THE GUN OUT OF MY EAR, I'LL PUT ON THE
HEADPHONES AND TELL YOU WHAT IT IS.
( rhythmic tapping ) ( whirring )
IT'S A DOLPHIN SWIMMING NEAR THE HULL.
WHAT?
UM, DOLPHIN.
UH...FLIPPER.
( imitates dolphin )  SEE?
DON'T KILL ME.
SHH, SHH.
I'M ON YOUR SIDE, OKAY?
THE NAME'S CARTER.
JAMES CARTER.
YOU GOT ON THIS SUB?
ARE YOU CRAZY?
I'VE BEEN TRYING TO FIGURE OUT A WAY TO GET OFF.
I'M ON BOARD.
CARTER'S IN.
HELP? WAIT, HOW AM I GONNA HELP?
YOU LISTEN.
I'LL INFORM THE PRESIDENT.
THERE'S A LITTLE BOY ON THE PHONE, SAYS HE'S LOOKING
FOR "SPECIAL STARK".
HEH.
HELLO, LISA?
WE'RE GETTING READY TO GO TO NEW YORK.
HOW'S EVERYTHING GOING?
VERY WELL. YOUR FATHER GOT ONTO THE SUBMARINE.
COOL!
WHY DON'T YOU CALL ME AGAIN WHEN YOU GET TO NEW YORK?
YOU GOT IT!
OKAY.
LOOKS LIKE THEY'RE PRETTY HEAVILY ARMED.
A LITTLE.
LET'S GO.
OKAY, WE'RE GONNA SET UP A COUPLE OF TRAPS TO TRY
TO LURE THEM IN.
WHAT I NEED YOU TO DO IS TO CREATE A DIVERSION LONG ENOUGH
TO GET ME INTO THE SONAR ROOM.
YOU GOT IT?
LET'S DO IT.
HEY.
NAME'S CARTER.
HOW MANY WE GOT?
FOUR, AND THE LEADER.
HOW MANY DOWN?
SIX.
SIX. OKAY.
WAIT, WAIT, WAIT!
AREN'T YOU GONNA UNTIE ME?
NO. YOU'RE GONNA KEEP PRETENDING TO BE A PRISONER.
( clang )  YOU HEAR ANYTHING?
YEAH!
YEAH? WHAT?
I HEAR EVERYTHING.
I AM THE SONAR GUY, REMEMBER?
UHH!
( speaks Russian ) ♪♪
Richter: DOING JUST FINE, GENTLEMEN.
GUM?
2 TO 1 ODDS IT HELPS YOUR EARS POP.
I DON'T HAVE ANY TROUBLE WITH MY EARS.
TAKE THE GUM.
GIVE ME!
SURE.
IT'S MY LAST PIECE, THOUGH.
87.016 DEGREES LONGITUDE, 24.862 DEGREES LATITUDE.
THESE COORDINATES ARE ABSURD.
WHAT ARE THEY FOR?
JUST WANTED TO SEE IF YOU COULD READ A MAP, ASSHOLE.
SO, WHAT ARE YOU DOING NOW?
I NEED TO ACCESS THE BSY-1 CABLES IN ORDER TO PATCH
MY LAPTOP INTO THE MISSILE LAUNCH SYSTEM.
HOLD THIS.
HOW DID YOU KNOW WHERE TO LOOK?
I DESIGNED THIS SUB.
LET'S GO.
1337, APPRISED CREWMEN OF SITUATION.
( vibrates )  Block: WHO'S SENDING THESE?
A CHICK?
A SPECIAL ADVISOR TO THE PENTAGON.
COME ON!
( indistinct shouting ) THERE'S NOTHING I CAN DO!
YOU GOTTA FIX IT!
FIND A WAY TO FIX IT!
GET DOWN THERE!
EVEN WHEN THEY'RE DYING, AMERICANS CAN BE SO--
SO UNDIGNIFIED.
YOU WOULDN'T KNOW COURAGE IF IT WAS LOOKING YOU IN THE FACE.
DON'T YOU SPEAK TO ME ABOUT COURAGE.
YOU HAVE NEVER LIVED THROUGH YOUR HOMELAND BEING DESTROYED
BY...PEACEKEEPERS.
THEY'RE HUNTING US NOW.
WHEN THEY FIND THIS SUB, THEY'LL BLOW IT TO HELL.
WILL YOU STOP BAITING HIM?
YOU WANT TO GET SOMEONE ELSE KILLED, YOU SELFISH
SON OF A BITCH?
YOUR GOVERNMENT WILL TRY TO FIND A WAY TO KEEP THE GOLD
AND GET THE SUB BACK.
AMERICANS LOVE GETTING SOMETHING FOR NOTHING. HEH.
NO COMPREHENSION OF SACRIFICE.
THEY WILL LEARN ABOUT SACRIFICE VERY SOON.
( typing )  Carter: I'M IN.
EIGHT HOURS TO GO.
GOTTA CHANGE THE POLARITY ON A BUNCH OF CIRCUITS
OR WE'LL FRY THE MAINFRAME.
( grunting )  FUCK YOU, AMERICAN!
( cocks gun ) ( grunts )
( choking )  Block: SHIT.
OKAY?
YEAH.
GOOD.
AHH.
I HAD TO KILL ONE OF THEM.
NAME--GUNTHER NEWTON.
28, SLAVIC, BORN IN DUBROVNIK.
GET FILE FROM INTERPOL.
SUSAN, HAVE INTERPOL CHECK THIS GUY OUT ASAP.
HE'S PART OF A TERRORIST NETWORK, AND I WANT TO KNOW
WHO ELSE IS IN IT.
RIGHT AWAY.
WE'RE RUNNING OUT OF TIME.
WHAT I NEED YOU TO DO--  NEWTON, ARE YOU THERE?
OH, NO.
MR. NEWTON?
( Slavic accent ) I AM HERE.
MR. NEWTON, I WAS WAITING FOR YOU TO REPORT BACK.
YOU WENT ON PATROL.
I FOUND NOTHING.
VERY GOOD.
MAINTAIN YOUR POST.
AVALLONE?
CHECK ON MR. NEWTON.
MICHAEL, COME BACK HERE!
WE CAN GET IT TOGETHER!
READY?
JUST TEN MORE CODES, AND THEIR CONTROLS WILL BE SWITCHED
OVER TO HARPOON MISSILES.
YEAH, BUT EVEN THAT AMOUNT OF T.N.T. IS STILL GONNA MAKE
A MESS OF WASHINGTON.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
WAGER GAVE ME SAFE TARGET COORDINATES ON A WASTELAND.
ALL I HAVE TO DO IS REDIRECT THE MISSILES.
RICHTER.
THIS IS RICHTER. GO AHEAD.
WE HAVE A PROBLEM.
Richter: I DON'T KNOW WHO YOU ARE, BUT YOU KILLED
ONE OF MY MEN WITH A SPEAR.
THAT'S A STRANGE WEAPON FOR A CREW MEMBER.
REGARDLESS OF YOUR WEAPONS, WE WILL FIND YOU AND KILL YOU,
BLOOD FOR BLOOD, AS MY PEOPLE SAY.
BOLANNE?
YES?
HELP AVALLONE SEARCH THE BOAT.
WATCH YOUR BACK.
( choking )  OH!
OH!
( grunting )  Richter: ADMIRAL
PENDELTON?
NO, THIS IS LIEUTENANT COMMANDER STARK.
OH. TELL ME, HOW DOES IT LOOK?
HOW DOES WHAT LOOK?
ALL THAT GOLD YOU'VE MANAGED TO GATHER--
APPROXIMATELY 2 1/2 METRIC TONS.
YOU HAVEN'T GIVEN US ENOUGH TIME.
YOU HAD TIME TO GET A MAN ON BOARD, BUT YOU CAN'T GET
A HOLD OF A LITTLE GOLD?
YOU'RE NOT SPEAKING THE TRUTH.
WHAT MAN?
LADY, YOU'RE SO MANY MOVES BEHIND ME, IT'S ALMOST
NOT FUN TO PLAY.
HAVE MY GOLD READY IN 2 HOURS.
THERE'S STILL SEVEN HOURS LEFT ON THE CLOCK.
( hangs up ) WE'D BETTER SEND A MESSAGE
TO CARTER.
TELL HIM THE TIME'S BEEN MOVED UP.
♪♪  WE LOST HIM.
SEARCH THE HALL AGAIN, ROOM BY ROOM.
I THINK RICHTER WILL BE INTERESTED IN THAT.
RICHTER, WE JUST FOUND THIS.
HMM. GO BACK TO YOUR POST.
Richter: YOU'VE LOST YOUR SHORT BURST RADIO--HOW SAD.
I KNOW HOW TERRIBLE IT FEELS TO BE CUT OFF FROM EVERYONE,
DEMORALIZED, OUTNUMBERED, ABOUT TO DIE.
CARTER SHOULD BE RESPONDING BY NOW.
SIR, THERE'S A CALL FROM THE ULYSSES.
THIS IS ADMIRAL PENDELTON.
HERE ARE THE COORDINATES FOR THE DROP SITE--
55.076 DEGREES LONGITUDE, 32.495 DEGREES LATITUDE.
COPY THAT.
IF IT'S NOT DELIVERED IN ONE HOUR, WASHINGTON, D.C.,
WILL BE GROUND ZERO.
AND YOU NEEDN'T BOTHER SENDING YOUR MAN ANY MORE MESSAGES
ON THE SHORT BURST RADIO.
HE IS DEAD.
( sighing )  MAYBE HE'S LYING.
MAYBE THEY FOUND THE RADIO.
WHAT HAVE YOU GOT FROM INTERPOL ON THESE PEOPLE?
UH...THEY'RE ALL PART OF A MOVEMENT THAT'S TIED TO
A RADICAL MIDDLE-EASTERN TERRORIST GROUP--
A WELL-FUNDED, ORGANIZED OP.
THEIR M.O. ISN'T MONEY, IT'S THE DOMINATION OF THE FREE
WORLD BY ANY MEANS NECESSARY.
THEY'D USE A NUCLEAR BOMB WITHOUT A SECOND THOUGHT.
SO, THEY PLAN TO NUKE US WHETHER WE PAY THEM OR NOT.
I'M AFRAID THAT'S WHAT WE MUST ASSUME.
GET ME CRICHTON ON THE DAVIES.
OUR INFORMATION LEADS US TO BELIEVE THE PRESIDENT WILL
UPGRADE THE SITUATION TO DEFCON 3.
YOU MAY BE OUR LAST LINE OF DEFENSE.
I COPY THAT, SIR.
WE NOW HAVE LONG-RANGE SONAR REGISTRATION ON THE ULYSSES.
STAND BY...
TO SINK THE ULYSSES.
Carter: WELL, YOUR MAN'S DEAD--GUNTHER NEWTON.
I BELIEVE YOU AND MR. NEWTON SHARE A COMMON ORIGIN.
YOU WOULDN'T HAPPEN TO BE FROM THE SAME PLACE, NOW, WOULD YOU?
YES, WE ARE.
WE ARE FROM A WORLD YOU COULD NEVER COMPREHEND.
A WORLD FILLED WITH DEATH.
NOT OF OUR OWN MAKING, BUT DEATH HANDED TO US
BY OUR ENEMIES.
WE LEARNED TO KILL AS CHILDREN SO THAT SOME WILL SURVIVE.
WELL, I'M SORRY YOU HAD A TOUGH CHILDHOOD, BUT THAT
DOESN'T MEAN YOU HAVE TO KILL FIVE MILLION PEOPLE.
YOU HAVE NO COMPREHENSION OF THE NATURE OF MY WORLD.
YEAH, WELL, COMPREHEND THIS, ASSHOLE--YOU CAN'T FIND ME,
BUT I KNOW EXACTLY WHERE YOU ARE, AND YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'M ON MY WAY.
MAKE SURE ALL THE HATCHES ARE CLOSED AND LOCKED FROM
THE INSIDE.
OUR OWN LITTLE FORTRESS.
LET'S SEE HIM TRY TO GET PAST A STEEL DOOR.
HOW'S THAT LEAK, GOING?
( overlapping shouts )  IF YOU WANT YOUR GOLD,
YOU'RE OFF-COURSE.
WE'LL PICK IT UP ON THE WAY BACK.
BACK FROM WHERE?
FROM LAUNCHING OUR NUCLEAR MISSILES.
SAPRICH, ARE YOU READY FOR THE TARGET COORDINATES?
COORDINATES ARE ALREADY ENTERED FOR WASHINGTON, D.C.
WELL, WE ARE RESETTING THEM, 41 DEGREES LATITUDE,
74 DEGREES LONGITUDE.
THAT'S NEW YORK CITY.
WE'LL FIRE ONE MISSILE AND WAIT.
THE UNITED NATIONS WILL FINALLY FIND OUT THAT IT'S BETTER TO
GIVE THAN TO RECEIVE.
Woman: PENTAGON.
Tommy: CAN I SPEAK WITH SPECIAL OFFICER STARK, PLEASE?
JUST A MOMENT, PLEASE.
LIEUTENANT STARK.
HELLO, LISA? THIS IS TOMMY.
HAVE YOU HEARD FROM MY DAD YET?
YOUR FATHER'S DOING A TERRIFIC JOB, TOMMY.
I KNEW IT.
SO, DO YOU LIKE HIM?
YEAH, TOMMY, VERY MUCH.
I KNEW YOU WOULD.
HE'S THE GREATEST.
YEAH, HE SURE IS.
WELL, GOTTA GO.
WE'RE GOING TO SEE THE EMPIRE STATE BUILDING.
OKAY, HAVE FUN.
BYE.
HOW SOON, AUNT JANE?
ARE YOU READY TO GO?
UH-HUH.
THE COORDINATES ARE ENTERED.
I'M ENCRYPTING THE SYSTEM.
ENCRYPTION COMPLETED.
WHAT THE HELL?
WELL DONE, MR. SAPRICH.
WE'RE NOW WITHIN FIRING RANGE, MR. ROBINSON.
( sonar beeping )  SHIT, WE GOT US A U.S.L.A.
CLASS SUB ON OUR TAIL.
FLOOD TORPEDO TUBES ONE THROUGH FOUR.
ONE THROUGH FOUR FLOODED.
TORPEDO DOORS OPEN, SIR.
FIRE TWO, THREE AND FOUR.
TWO TORPEDOES, SIR!
RANGE, 600 YARDS, BEARING 048050, 50 KNOTS, SIR.
WHAT DO WE DO?
IF YOU DON'T TELL ME, WE ALL DIE.
CHRIST. ROBINSON, RELEASE COUNTERMEASURE NOW.
COUNTERMEASURES AWAY, AYE.
CLOSING FAST, SIR!
SHIT, WE ONLY GOT 15 SECONDS TO IMPACT!
COLLINS, TAKE BALLASTS TO EMERGENCY SEQUENCE. DIVE! DIVE!
OH!
FIRST TIER BALLAST TANKS FULL!
SECOND TIER BALLAST TANKS FULL!
TORPEDOES GOING AFTER COUNTERMEASURES.
BRACE FOR IMPACT!
( screaming )  ( screaming )
FIRE EXTINGUISHER!
WE GOT IT!
I GOT HIM, I GOT HIM!
AH! HURRY!
( screaming )  HELP! HELP!
SHIP'S STABILIZING, SIR.
WHAT DO YOU WANT ME TO DO?
( whispers ) LIEUTENANT.
HOLD IT STEADY, MR. COLLINS.
YES.
GOT IT.
BRING US AROUND TO FIRE.
I'M NOT FIRING ON MY OWN BOAT.
I'LL KILL COLLINS.
WAIT, WE CAN EVADE THEM.
WAGER, WHAT'S THE IMMEDIATE TERRAIN?
THERE'S A TRENCH BENEATH US.
WE CAN OUTRUN THEM, WE CAN LOSE THEM IN THE CANYON.
WE CAN'T DO ANY OF THAT IF YOU SHOOT THE DRIVER.
GET DENT ON THE LINE, HE CAN CALL THE TURNS WITH SONAR.
DENT, GIVE ME A HAND HERE.
WE GOT SOME TIGHT MANEUVERING.
CONN, SONAR.
THEY'RE ENTERING THE CANYON, BEARING 750 DEGREES,
35 KNOTS, SIR.
KEEP A TAB ON THEM.
PULL THE CHARTS.
WE'RE GOING AFTER THEM.
DOWN FIVE DEGREES BUBBLE, SMARTLY.
Carter: COME ON, DAMN IT.
ACCEPT THE COORDINATES.
( grunting )  ( shouting )
( groaning )  CONN, SONAR.
THEY ARE RIGHT BEHIND US.
THEY'RE FLOODING THE TUBES.
TALK TO ME, DENT.
THEY'VE ACQUIRED US AGAIN.
GET READY FOR A HARD RIGHT.
HARD RIGHT ON MY MARK.
90 DEGREES STARBOARD, COMING UP, SIR.
WEAPS, PREPARE TO FIRE TWO, THREE AND FOUR.
TWO, THREE AND FOUR, AYE.
FIRE!
TORPEDOES AWAY!
ACQUIRING THE TARGET, SIR.
HOLD.
HOLDING.
WE'RE GONNA CRASH INTO THE WALL, SIR.
NOW, COLLINS, NOW!
OH, SHIT.
AVALANCHE DEAD AHEAD, SIR!
SHIT! FULL REVERSE!
SOUND THE COLLISION ALARM!
FULL REVERSE, AYE-AYE, SIR.
( grunting )  THEY'RE GETTING AWAY, SIR.
INCREASE SPEED.
WE CAN'T LOSE 'EM. FULL AHEAD!
NO.
WE'VE LOST SONAR CONTACT.
IT'S THESE TRENCHES.
ACKNOWLEDGED.
BUT THEY'RE OUT THERE.
JUST KEEP YOUR EARS ON.
MAINTAIN SPEED AND COURSE.
CONN, SONAR, THEY'RE STILL IN THE CANYON, RIGHT BEHIND US.
BRING US AROUND TO FIRE.
FLOODING TUBES.
SONAR, DETERMINE RANGE TO TARGET.
( sonar beeping )  SHIT. FULL REVERSE ENGINES!
PORT AND STARBOARD!
FULL REVERSE, AYE, SIR!
FULL STOP.
HOVER AND PREPARE TO FIRE.
THEY'RE FLOODING TORPEDO TUBES.
OPEN TORPEDO DOORS.
FIRE TUBES TWO AND FOUR.
TORPEDOES AWAY.
TORPEDOES INCOMING!
CLOSING FAST, SIR!
NO RETREAT!
TAKE THEM DOWN WITH US.
RELEASE STARBOARD COUNTERMEASURES NOW!
PREPARE TO FIRE TUBES THREE AND FOUR.
THREE AND FOUR, AYE, SIR.
FIRE!
TORPEDOES AWAY.
CLOSING.
1,000 YARDS.
ROBINSON, RELEASE COUNTERMEASURE NOW!
700 YARDS.
TORPEDOES ARMED.
BRING US HARD APORT!
TORPEDOES GOING AFTER THE COUNTERMEASURES, SIR!
SECOND TORPEDO STILL ACTIVE!
FULL REVERSE!
IT'S TOO LATE, SIR!
THEY'VE GOT A LOCK ON US!
MR. PRESIDENT, IT DOESN'T LOOK GOOD.
THEY SUNK THE S.S.N. DAVIES.
TORPEDOES STILL CLOSING, 300 YARDS.
RIGHT FULL RUDDER, MR. COLLINS.
TORPEDOES LOCKED ON ON COUNTERMEASURES!
( grunting )  ( shouting )
SEAL SECTIONS A-5, B-7, D-9.
WE'RE TAKING IN WATER.
ROBINSON, HIT THOSE EMERGENCY BATTERIES.
AYE-AYE, SIR.
NOW, THAT WAS STIMULATING.
COLLINS, TAKE US UP TO PERISCOPE DEPTH...
SLOW AND SILENT.
DO IT.
DO IT, COLLINS.
IT'S NOT WORTH DYING OVER.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
DON'T YOU GET IT YET, COLLEGE BOY?
THIS IS ABOUT SURVIVAL.
DO IT, COLLINS.
HOW POETIC.
SURFACE NOW, OR YOUR HEAD GETS BLOWN OFF.
PREPARE TO SURFACE.
85 FEET.
80 FEET.
75 FEET.
65 FEET. COMMENCE HOVERING AT ZERO BUBBLE.
ZERO BUBBLE, AYE, SIR.
( knock on hatch )  AVALLONE.
SPASIBA.
AVALLONE, SAPRICH-- THE LAUNCH KEYS.
NOW DO THE MATH FOR ME, MR. MacDONALD.
HOW MUCH DAMAGE CAN A SINGLE NUCLEAR WARHEAD DO TO A CITY
THE SIZE OF NEW YORK?
WELL, WE ALL FIND OUT IN EXACTLY FIVE MINUTES...
STARTING NOW.
THE LIGHTS OF BROADWAY ARE ABOUT TO GO DOWN, AND I
NEVER EVEN SAW DAMN YANKEES.
WE SWING BACK, PICK UP THE GOLD, IF THERE IS ANY,
AND RENDEZVOUS WITH OUR SHIP.
ATTENTION, ALL HANDS.
THE FIRST NUCLEAR WEAPON TO BE FIRED UPON THE BEAUTIFUL
UNITED STATES OF AMERICA WILL IMPACT IN FOUR MINUTES.
SORRY WE CAN'T PROVIDE A VIEW.
( beeping )  AAAH!
( gunfire ) ( shouting )
GIVE ME YOUR WEAPON!
GO! HERE!
UHH!
I'M GETTIN' OUT OF HERE.
NO!
SOMEONE THROW ME A HANDGUN, DAMN IT!
MURPHY! GUN!
HOLD YOUR FIRE!
STAND UP OR I'LL KILL YOU!
WELL, THAT WAS LIKE IN THE GOOD OLD DAYS.
YOU TRAITOR BASTARD.
YOU WERE IN ON THIS THE WHOLE TIME, HUH, MURPHY?
YOU'RE GODDAMN RIGHT.
THE ONLY THING MY LOYALTY EVER GOT ME--
BULLSHIT, LOYALTY.
HOW DO YOU CALL THIS LOYALTY?
YOU CONTINUE TO BE INVALUABLE, MURPHY.
HOW DO YOU FEEL? WE'RE ONLY MOMENTS AWAY FROM LAUNCH.
DAMN GOOD RIGHT NOW.
40 SECONDS TILL LAUNCH.
THE MISSILES TAKE A LITTLE OVER FOUR MINUTES TO GET
TO NEW YORK.
MURPHY, GO AFTER HIM!
THE REST OF YOU, STAY DOWN.
YOU ARE DEAD.
STABILIZE THE SHIP, MR. COLLINS.
DO IT.
WHERE TO?
THE EMPIRE STATE BUILDING.
( beeping )  OPEN MISSILE BAY DOORS,
MR. ROBINSON.
DOORS OPEN.
WE'RE LOSING MAIN ENGINE POWER!
WE CAN'T FIRE, DAMN IT.
WE'RE TAKING ON TOO MUCH WATER.
YOU'LL KILL US ALL!
UHH!
( beeping )  WE HAVE MAIN ENGINE FAILURE!
CARTER!
YOU'RE MINE NOW!
I USED TO BE JUST LIKE YOU, CARTER.
MADE LIFE HARD FOR MYSELF OUT OF SOME WARPED SENSE
OF DUTY.
BUT I GOT SMART.
STARTED LOOKING OUT FOR NUMBER ONE.
I SURE HOPE YOU LIKE THE PINE BOX THEY PICK UP FOR YOU, PAL.
Carter: WHY DON'T YOU COME IN AND GET ME?
YOU AFRAID?
I CAN'T HOLD IT STEADY.
WE'RE GOIN' DOWN!
( grunting )  AAAAH!
( groans ) ( beeping )
Man: 1:30 TO IMPACT.
GET ME THE PRESIDENT.
THERE IT IS!
THE EMPIRE STATE BUILDING!
OKAY, TOMMY, CALM DOWN.
WE'RE ALMOST THERE.
( beeping )  GIVE UP.
THE MISSILES ALREADY LAUNCHED.
IT'S OVER.
( grunting ) UHH! OHH!
Cab driver: GET DOWN!
( sighs ) YES.
UH-HUH. GREAT.
SOMEONE MANAGED TO ABORT THE MISSILE, AND IT WAS
A HARPOON, NOT A NUKE.
( all cheer )  THE EMPIRE STATE BUILDING
TOOK A HIT FROM THE BLAST.
( grunting )  SHE'S NOT RESPONDING.
RICHTER!
I WILL SEE YOU DEAD.
♪♪ ( beeping )
SHIT.
( grunting ) ( grunting )
( screaming ) AAAH!
( gurgling screams )  WE'RE TOO DEEP, THE SHIP
CAN'T TAKE ANY MORE PRESSURE!
WE NEED AUXILIARY POWER NOW!
NOW!
COME ON.
COME ON, BABY.
( powering on )  AND WE ARE RISING.
( mutters )  HELP!
AAH! HELP!
( shouting ) ( shouting )
Carter: STAND BACK!
I'M BLOWING THE DOOR!
( coughing )  OKAY, ENOUGH R&R.
I NEED YOU UP TOP. LET'S MOVE.
COME ON.
COME ON, MAN.
HEY, COLLINS.
GOOD TO SEE YOU, BRO.
EVERYBODY OKAY?
LET'S DO SOME DAMAGE.
STUART!
WOULD YOU GET ME OUT OF HERE?
SORRY, DUDE.
COME ON, LET'S GO.
THIS IS JAMES CARTER ABOARD THE S.S.N. ULYSSES.
Pendelton: JAMES...
YOU'RE ALIVE!
( all cheering )  YES, SIR, I'M A LITTLE
SURPRISED MYSELF.
WE'RE GONNA NEED SOME ASSISTANCE ON THE SURFACE--
RESCUE TEAMS AND A TOW HOME.
THE SHIP'S OURS AGAIN.
( cheering )  SIR, IS LISA STARK THERE?
I WAS WONDERING IF SHE HEARD FROM TOMMY YET.
I--NO, I HAVEN'T.
YOU'LL LET ME KNOW AS SOON AS YOU FIND OUT?
YES, I WILL.
JAMES, I'LL DEBRIEF YOU PERSONALLY AS SOON AS
YOU HIT PORT.
OVER AND OUT.
( all cheering ) ♪♪
( cow moos )  DADDY! DADDY!
I MISSED YOU SO MUCH, DAD!
HEY, BUDDY.
HOW YOU DOIN'?
HOW WAS NEW YORK?
IT WAS AWESOME.
THIS BIG, HUGE BUILDING BLEW UP ON THE TAXI.
YEAH, WAS THAT THE EMPIRE STATE BUILDING?
YEAH!
YEAH? YOU LIKED IT, HUH?
YEAH, IT WAS AWESOME.
LOVE YOU.
I WAS REALLY WORRIED ABOUT YOU, PAL.
I MISSED YOU.
HI.
I JUST WANTED TO SEE IF YOU WERE OKAY.
AREN'T YOU GONNA KISS?
WE KISSED.
( laughs ) ♪♪
♪♪