(MultiCom Jingle)
(gentle piano music)
(soft music)
(baby crying)
- [Man] Get out in front of it.
Just get some milk and warm it up.
Every day here is the same thing.
This place is in utter chaos.
I am so tired I'm having a
hard time keeping my eyes open.
I have told you 100 times
how particular the boss is.
He wants me to look clean and neat.
What a joke!
Clean and neat does not
exist in this house.
Look at this shirt, it stinks.
I cannot wear this to the garage.
- [Cathy] Wear this one.
- [Steve] It's a uniform, Cathy,
you have to wear the damn shirt.
You don't get it.
There's nothing in the refrigerator.
Oh, dammit.
There's no food, there's
crap all over the counter.
- [Cathy] I'm sorry,
okay, I'll make it better.
- That'd be a nice change.
What's the matter with you?
What, am I supposed to do
everything around here?
Huh, is that it?
I'm supposed to earn the money
and take care of this place?
Look at me, dammit, look at me!
I'm doing my part, geez, I'm working
my butt off all day long.
I am home from the
restaurant at three a.m.
so I can be up at six o'clock
to be to the garage on time.
I'm working three jobs here, Cathy.
I do not think it is to much to ask
for you to clean up the floor
and do the damn dishes every now and then.
(baby crying)
(soft music)
(baby screaming)
- Andrea!
I'm not cleaning up this mess.
You made it, you clean it!
Clean it up now, go on!
(baby screaming)
(crying)
(hard breathing)
(baby crying)
- Mom.
Mom, Mom, Mom, Mom.
Mama.
(chattering)
(soft music)
(dog barking)
(somber music)
- Brad?
Oh, Brad, honey.
Sweetheart.
Come here, honey.
- I want my daddy.
- I know, I know.
(soft music)
(sniffling)
(dog barking)
(dog crying)
(hard breathing)
(dog barking)
(dog panting)
- Okay, Hammer, race you home.
(dog barking)
(rock music)
- Where's Andrea?
Brad.
- Mom.
- Sorry, where's your sister?
- Coach Beebe called again.
He's gonna stop calling, you know.
- Oh.
You are not going to
school dressed like that.
Andrea, do we have to go
through this every morning?
- It's my body.
- No, it's not.
I mean, of course it is.
But I am your mother,
and I'm not gonna let you
walk outta here dressed
like some hooker, some.
Where did you get that anyway?
- Tandy, her mother bought it for her.
Her mother knows fashion.
- Oh well good for her mother.
Now go upstairs and put
some real clothes on.
- And what if I won't.
- What did you say?
- He's asked you out three times already.
- Just wait a minute.
- If you keep saying no,
he's gonna stop asking.
- Forget it.
Oh.
(sighing)
Andrea, I'm not gonna say it again.
Go upstairs and change your clothes.
- [Andrea] Mother, you are so unfair.
- [Laura] Now, Andrea.
- No, we've pushed the
print date back three times
already, and if it doesn't get out now,
we'll miss Easter, and
we can't afford to miss.
- [Jerome] Miss Eagerton
can see you now, ma'am.
- Look, I've gotta go.
Just get me the galleys by the 15th.
- Oh, hi.
- Mrs. Tennyson, how nice to see you.
- Thank you, and how is
my little empire faring?
- Well, we'll finish the
photos for the fajitas book
today, and I just finalized
the Sarah Beck deal
for the celebrities
cookbook, and I'm proofing
the galleys of Cooking in the Catskills.
- I feel it's time for
us to expand our list.
- Oh, Mrs. Tennyson, I am so glad.
I have just found this
great science writer.
- [Mrs. Tennyson] Erotic poetry.
His name is Appaloosa.
(door knocking)
- Not now, Jerome.
- It's the school nurse,
something to do with Andrea.
- Mrs. Eagerton, thank God
you're here, I'm so worried.
- [Laura] That's okay, Tandy, is she in?
- On the cot, yes.
And she says the pain
is just excruciating.
My second stepmother has the same thing,
and she's incapacitated
for three days every month.
She's doubled over in pain,
violent chills, vomiting.
- Tandy, would you please
go get Andrea's things
out of her locker for me?
- Andrea, I'll be right back.
- Sweetheart?
- Mom, it hurts.
I can't believe this happened in school,
especially in health class, God.
I'm so mortified.
- Don't be, it's just your.
Do you feel all right, did the nurse
give you an aspirin, or?
I feel like I should say something.
- Yeah.
- Well, congratulations, this
is an important moment in um.
- Guess I'm no longer a child.
- I guess not.
(soft music)
Oh, honey.
It's just nature's first step.
It doesn't mean you
have to be all grown up.
You're only 13.
You're still my little girl.
- It hurts.
- Yeah, I know.
- Why did I have to come?
- Because school was almost out,
and I didn't know how long we'd be.
- Did you call Coach Beebe?
- Nope.
- He's gonna stop calling.
- Laura.
- So?
- She's got her period.
- [Laura] Well I know that,
but what about the cramps?
- They're cramps.
- So what am I doing here?
- You're indulging her.
She's a very sensitive young girl.
Caught up in the drama of
her reproductive system.
Problem?
- No, just work.
Kids, Dad, mortgage.
- All the incurable stuff, huh?
- I'm thinking about moving.
- What about your friends, your dad?
- My friends?
Well between Andrea's
drama and Brad's track,
and Dad's gone completely gaga over Annie,
which I just can't.
And work has become suddenly surreal,
and Brad is trying to set
me up with his track coach.
- So, what's wrong with this coach?
- I don't know, it's just,
it's only been two and a half years.
- Yeah, I know.
It's only been 14 for me, but.
- Look, I know Steve wasn't perfect,
but he was a good man, and a good dad,
and I'm just not ready to--
- Settle.
(laughing)
- I just had a depressing thought.
The closest thing to a
man in my life is my kids'
pediatrician, and he's
42.50 every time I walk
through the door.
(laughing)
- The things you come up with, Brad.
Out of the mouths of babes.
- I'm not a babe.
- Would anyone like dessert?
- Oh no, Laura, you just sit.
You let me do the dishes.
- No, Annie.
- Oh now, come on, catch
me while you can, sweetie,
because once I get on that love boat
for our Christmas cruise, the only dish
I'm gonna be carrying is myself.
(laughing)
- Isn't she a pip?
- She's a pip, Dad.
- What's a pip?
- Same thing as a babe, just older.
- So how do you know Doreen Hinkle?
- Well, I don't really,
Andrea would you pass--
- Well her number's on the fridge.
- Would you pass me the sugar?
- Doreen who?
- [Annie] Doreen Hinkle, honey, you know,
the one with the dark hair, talks a lot.
- The real estate lady?
- Yeah, the one who--
Oh my God, you're not thinking
about selling, are you?
- We are not selling this house.
- Can we move to California?
- Are you serious, Laura?
- No, no, Dad.
- We are not leaving this house.
- But Disneyland, Knotts
Berry Farm, Universal Studios.
- Honey, this is not the time
to sell, can't you stick?
- Of course I can stick.
I just got this thing in the mail
about a free appraisal, and I thought--
- I am never leaving this house.
- She's got cramps.
(dog barking)
(crickets chirping)
(woodwind music)
(soft music)
(swing creaking)
(dogs barking)
(car starting)
(dramatic music)
(tires squealing)
- Hi.
- Hi, I love your hat, is it new?
- You wanna borrow it?
- Oh, yeah, like my mom would ever let me
wear something like that.
(clock chiming)
(door squeaking)
- Oh, Mrs. Hinkle, you scared me.
- I'm sorry, I--
- No, no, no, I'm glad you're early.
I really appreciate you
coming by this morning.
I need to get into work, and I didn't want
my daughter to be here.
She's not exactly crazy
about me selling this place.
Let me get rid of his, oh, and these.
Shall we start in the living room?
Like I said on the phone,
the house is 80 years old, and it's been
in my late husband's family forever.
Excuse me one minute.
I'll be right back.
Now we rewired everything,
I'd say about six years ago.
The roof is new.
Now we did have some dry
rot a few years back,
but that's all gone now
and the ceiling, well,
there is some water damage
from before we fixed the roof.
See, it's right there.
But that's it.
And the carpet's only five years old.
Oh my God, what a mess.
Oh, I should tell you that I repainted
the master bedroom and
both of the kids' bedrooms
and the upstairs bathroom
just last summer.
I didn't do the hallway,
because it's looking
pretty good still, I think.
And, uh, oh, what else?
The bathroom's in here.
Now the, uh,
the plumbing is really really old.
The tub's original, but the tile's new.
And the linen closet's out
here, it's a little small, but,
there's plenty of storage in the attic,
which is a good thing,
because I can never seem
to throw anything away.
Mrs. Hinkle, I'm in here.
(soft music)
You know, this is really is a lovely room.
Should be a little more closet space,
but you can always use more closet space.
So you can see the
Methodist steeple from here.
Oh boy, it's getting late.
The kids' rooms are this way.
Now what else do I need to tell you?
Oh, we have forced heat.
Oh, teenagers never close a drawer.
Now underneath all this
carpet is a hardwood floor.
And it's really held up pretty well.
There's no mold or dry rot.
Although they always
inspect for termites, right?
(soft music)
- Mrs. Hinkle?
(soft piano music)
- I'm sorry.
(dramatic music)
(car starting)
- Mrs. Eagerton, Doreen
Hinkle, Van Adams Realty.
You know, this neighborhood is so sweet,
a little gem in the rough.
And folks are going gaga right now
for these cute old fixers.
Tell me, have you considered
carrying any paper?
Mrs. Eagerton?
(school bell ringing)
(kids chattering)
- [Laura] Brad?
Brad?
Honey, hop in the car.
- I got practice.
- Just, please, just get in the car.
- I gotta go to practice.
- Hey, Lorelei, stick around for practice,
I'll take you out for nachos after.
- I'm sorry, Mike, we
really have to get home.
- Just tell her I gotta go to practice.
- He's gotta go to practice.
- Dammit, Brad, just get in the car.
- What about my bike?
- Get it, and I'll put it in the trunk.
I'm sorry, I've gotta go find Andrea.
(kids chattering)
(locker doors slamming)
(car starting)
(horn honking)
(dramatic music)
- Brad?
Do you know who I am?
- No.
- I'm your mother.
(dramatic music)
Brad!
- Brad, what are you doing?
- Andrea, my God, I can't believe it.
Look how beautiful you are.
- Go away.
- Andrea, please.
- Go away!
- Andrea, Andrea.
- You stay away from them.
If you ever, ever try this
again, I'll call the police.
- I just.
- I will have you arrested for, for.
Andrea?
- [Tandy] Andrea, what is it?
Who is it?
(hard breathing)
- She's back, Tandy, she came back.
Oh my God.
- It's your mom.
- [Andrea] What is she
doing here, oh my God.
- [Tandy] Your mom you live with.
- You knew?
You knew, why didn't you say anything?
- Please, honey, let's
talk about this at home.
Andrea, please get in the car.
Honey, you don't have to
stop being angry with me,
just please get in.
Please?
(dramatic music)
This is the way he usually comes home.
He couldn't have gotten too far.
(dramatic music)
- Brad?
Oh, honey, I,
I wanted to tell you at home, I wanted to.
(birds chirping)
Do you wanna talk?
- No.
- I think we should talk about it.
- Why?
- Because this is a big
deal, and must feel very.
I mean, she is your mother, and--
- She's not my mother.
What's for dinner?
- I'll look.
(dramatic music)
(dog barking)
(car starting)
(dramatic music)
- Mom, Mommy.
Mom.
(dramatic music)
Mommy, Mama, Mom, Mommy!
- It's okay, honey, it's okay, I'm here.
I'm here, Andrea.
It's okay, honey, it's okay.
It's all right.
It's all right, okay?
(dramatic music)
(kids chattering)
- She looked very young
and thin, tragic kind of.
She looked like Audrey
Hepburn in that nun movie.
- She's not a nun.
- But she could be, you don't know.
That's one of those things
that makes it so romantic.
- Please, Tandy.
- Oh come on, you gotta
admit it's romantic.
Just showing up like this
looking all thin and everything.
- It's not romantic, it's insulting.
Like, why does she just
assume that I wanna see her?
I don't even think about her anymore.
- Bull, you think about her.
- No I don't.
- You talk about her a lot.
- Not a lot.
- A lot.
At times.
You know what, Andrea?
You're lucky.
I haven't seen my mom more than five times
in the last three years.
I mean, I talk to her
once a week on the phone,
and she sends me a bunch of stuff.
Somehow, she thinks we're still together.
Please, like she knows
anything about my life.
But, Cathy, it was like this
really big thing, her leaving.
Definite.
So it's a really big
thing when she comes back.
I mean, don't you wanna know?
Don't you just wanna ask her?
(sighing)
(laughing)
- [Instructor] And, forward.
(dogs barking)
(laughing)
- [Instructor] And stop, and forward.
- Down, down, down, Duke.
- [Ed] You don't like her.
- [Laura] I don't count.
- Lord, I loved your mom.
With all my heart.
But I've,
I've never in my life had so much fun.
(dog barking)
So I'll talk to Price.
He doesn't practice family law,
but he'll know somebody good who does.
- Thanks, Dad.
- Until then, you can't get
some kind of restraining order?
- Laura, honey, forget all
about that legal thing.
- Annie, please.
Dad, I've talked to the
police, they said there had
to be cause or something,
and that I should
get a lawyer, so I--
- Honey, listen to me.
You get the law, the whole
legal system involved,
it's in, okay, I mean, lawyers and writs
and court orders and all that stuff.
I mean, maybe Brad and Andrea
don't wanna see her now,
but what about five years from now?
Kiddo, I'm telling you, you are better off
dealing with this woman one on one.
- I don't want to deal with her.
I don't want anything to do with her.
I just wanna keep her away from my kids.
Dad, I'll talk to you later.
- Oh, whew, she sure doesn't like me.
(soft music)
(sighing)
(bird calling)
- May I help you?
Ma'am?
Excuse me.
(bell ringing)
- Jerome, have you ever heard of this, um?
Get out.
- I wanna talk to them.
- I think you saw how much
they wanna talk to you.
- [Cathy] I did it all wrong.
- Damn right you did, now go.
- I'm getting married, I have a good job,
it's been a long time.
- It's been 10 years.
- It's taken me a long time.
I'm ashamed of what I did, but I'm not
ashamed of me now, I'm a good person.
I have this new life, and
I want my kids to know it,
to know me, and if they
don't want to, fine,
but I just have to try to say I'm sorry.
If there's anything they want from me.
- They don't want anything from you.
- Ask them.
- They love me.
I've taken care of them.
For eight years, I've taken care of them.
I've been through their
father's death with them.
They are my kids.
- I don't wanna take them away from you.
I just wanna talk to them.
Please.
Ask them.
- I don't see why Tandy couldn't come.
- Andrea.
- [Andrea] I don't understand.
- [Laura] You see her all day.
You talk to her every night
on the phone for hours.
- [Andrea] Not hours.
- Sometimes it's nice
to be with just family.
Cathy came by my office today.
And she asked me to ask you
if you would like to talk to her.
I said I thought you'd
made it pretty clear
the other day, but just to be sure, I--
- No.
- Okay.
I'll call her and tell that--
- Mom.
(dramatic music)
(birds chirping)
(dogs barking)
(shower running)
(sighing)
- Honey, you want me
to come with you today?
- Do you wanna come?
- I will if you want me to.
- Do you want me to want you to?
- What do you want?
- No.
But, Mom?
Could you be close?
- Mmm-hmm.
(soft music)
(birds chirping)
- Honey, she's just late.
- She's not coming.
- Andrea.
- Wait, wait.
I was early, and I thought.
(hard breathing)
Doughnut?
Brad?
What time should I bring her home?
- We'll just wait here.
- Oh, okay.
So.
(soft piano music)
- Brad, that tree doesn't
look very strong, honey.
Be careful.
(dogs barking)
- [Cathy] It's a long time
since I been in this park.
- [Andrea] Why, where do you live?
- [Cathy] I live in Chicago.
- [Andrea] Oh, is it really that windy.
- Oh yeah, yeah.
What?
- Nothing, you, you just don't look like
your old pictures.
- You have pictures of me?
- Yeah, up in the attic, just a couple.
- Can I see your thumb?
You used to suck it so hard
you'd get these big blisters.
I was afraid they'd scar up and stay.
- No.
- We have the same hands.
- Long fingers.
- I'm really, really sorry
about the orange juice.
(soft piano music)
(crying)
(kids yelling)
- Ahhh, Mom, Mom, please!
Mom, Mom, Mom, please, get my mom.
- Brad, honey, I'm here.
Excuse me, honey, don't move, don't move.
Okay, where does it hurt?
- My ankle.
- Okay, which ankle?
- Left.
- Okay, don't move.
How in God's name did you do this?
We need to get you to the hospital.
- Do you want me to call an ambulance?
- Yes, please.
Wait a minute, where's Andrea?
Can you stay with him for a minute?
- Sure, sure.
- Don't move, honey.
- Man, how did you do this anyway?
- Andrea.
Andrea.
We can't wait.
Honey, don't put any weight on it.
- [Man] Let me get it.
- Great, thank you.
It's okay, it's okay.
- I got you, I got you.
- What happened?
- I think Brad broke his leg.
We're going to the hospital.
- We'll follow you.
- No.
- Come on, Andrea.
- Mom.
Do you really need me?
- Why don't I take Andrea home?
That way, you can concentrate on Brad.
- Go straight home.
- Now your left ear.
No, this is nothing.
People come in here all the time,
bones speared through the skin,
limbs hanging by tendons.
- Gross.
- Let me look in your eye.
- Ah, a casualty.
- Hi, Joe.
- So what happened to you?
- I jumped off a statue.
- Sure, why not?
- Hairline fracture in the tibia.
Some pulled ligaments, no hemorrhage.
- Yep.
So, you want plaster or one of those
fancy athletic braces?
- Athletic brace.
- You got it, cowboy.
- [P.A.] Dr. Cottrell, Dr. Janet Cottrell.
Emergency admitting.
- How did you meet Anthony?
- He hired me for the counter.
It paid well, and I always liked jewelry.
It's not like one of those
junky little mall chains.
It's a nice old family business.
His dad was a pearl man.
- So you're a salesgirl?
- Started that way.
But then I got into the
gems and wanted to move up.
Anthony was very supportive.
Even paid for me to go to
the Gemological Institute.
So now I have my certificate.
- What's this?
- Amethyst, Brazilian.
Pretty.
Semi-precious.
- Tandy gave it to me.
- Did your dad ever tell you about me?
Did you ever ask?
- Not after a while.
- I left home when I was 13.
(phone ringing)
- [P.A.] IV nurse, call the
fourth-floor nurses station.
- I shoulda kept an eye on him.
He was antsy, and when he
gets antsy he gets so--
- Laura, he's fine.
- No, he's not.
Their mother's back.
- What?
- Cathy, their mother,
she's in town.
(phone ringing)
- Have they seen her?
- Andrea's with her now.
What will this do to them?
- What do you mean?
- Emotionally.
Look, I know you're not a shrink,
but you are their doctor,
and you've known them
almost as long as I have,
and everything they've
been through, and this
can't be good for them.
This could do permanent damage, right?
- Look, Laura, I think we're all
permanently damaged by our parents.
- [P.A] Dr. Cohen to radiology,
Dr. Cohen to radiology.
- You are a terrific
mom, and they love you.
But this is somebody too.
- Brad says she's not his mother.
- [Joe] Okay, so he's not
ready to deal with it yet.
- And Andrea's at such
an impressionable age.
- She's a bright girl.
- She's just a child.
- What are you afraid of?
- What do you think I'm afraid of?
This woman is going to
take away my children.
- Laura, come on.
What is she to them?
A ghost, a mystery, a question
that needs to be answered.
But not a mother.
That's you.
And they know it.
- How'd you meet Daddy?
- At a car wash.
He brought his church group or something.
He drove up in this red Camaro.
He was older, cute.
- And you got pregnant?
- Not right away, but--
- And you got married.
And you had me.
- Yes, I did.
- Then you had Brad, and then you left.
- Yeah.
I did.
- Because you didn't love us.
- No.
- Then why, did Daddy do something?
- No, no.
It wasn't his fault.
He did the best he could.
I wasn't much older
than you when I had you.
I was too immature.
I, I couldn't.
(dog barking)
I never wanted to hurt you, Andrea.
That's why I left.
But I never stopped loving you.
I thought about you and Brad
every minute of every day.
- Then why didn't you come back?
- Because I felt I didn't
have anything to give you.
Up to now.
- She was supposed to be here hours ago.
I don't know.
Hold it.
Oh no, it's okay, she's here now.
- Where are my birthday cards?
(rock music)
- What?
- And Christmas, every year from Cathy.
10 years' worth of cards,
and I never even knew about them?
(rock music)
(clocking chiming)
- I was going to tell you.
I just.
Andrea, it was your dad.
At first, when you were
little, he thought,
he thought it would hurt and confuse you
getting cards from her, and then,
after he died, I felt you'd
had enough to deal with it.
And I thought maybe when
you were 16, I could--
- You opened them?
You had no right.
- I'm sorry, honey.
I was only doing what I
thought was best for you.
- Stealing the only thing
she ever sent me was best?
- What the hell does she know
about your seventh birthday?
You had the measles.
And I stayed up with you all night
putting on calamine lotion.
For my daughter on her seventh birthday.
- They were mine.
- When are you leaving?
- Friday.
- Good.
If I let you see Andrea
again, you will bring her home
when I tell you to bring her home,
or you will not be
allowed to see her at all.
- Why didn't you adopt them?
- Did she tell you that?
- I checked the records at county.
- God, you've got nerve.
- When Steve and I got married,
you wouldn't let me adopt them, remember?
- You coulda gone to court.
You coulda proved I abandoned them.
- I didn't wanna put them through that.
- Ah.
- [Laura] Why?
- Just curious.
- Well if you're curious
about anything else,
don't ask around at county.
Don't ask her.
Ask me, okay?
- You're so easy to talk to.
- What the hell do you want from me?
You walk in, you disrupt my life, you--
- This is my life you got, okay?
My kids, my house, my life.
- You were the one that walked out.
- And you're the one who
benefited from it, okay?
So maybe you can treat me
with a little courtesy.
- What, you want me to say thank you?
- Can I take Andrea out to dinner tonight?
- No, it's a school night.
- She has to eat.
- I'll feed her.
- Laura, I'm leaving Friday.
- Just have her home by seven.
- Thank you.
(instructor speaking French)
(class speaking French)
- A Christmas wedding at
Anthony's country club.
He's really rich, his dad was a pearl man.
- Wow.
(clearing throat)
(instructor speaking French)
(class speaking French)
- She says he's really nice,
really supportive of her and all.
She says I'm really gonna like him.
- Wow, weird, huh?
- Yeah.
What?
- Just that she was the screw-up,
and your mom was the good one.
Now it's Cathy who's got
a great job in a big,
beautiful city getting
married to a rich man
who's crazy about her.
And then your mom lives here, God.
Has this little cookbook job and
and like no men interested in her.
It's just weird, huh?
Karma.
- I guess.
- [Laura] It's too late for a lawyer.
- It's never too late.
- Andrea wants to see her.
If I bring a lawyer in
now, I'm the bad guy.
- Is that what you're worried
about, being the bad guy?
- I am worried about losing my daughter.
(car starting)
- Then let the courts help you
set some reasonable limits.
- Dad, if I can't set
reasonable limits on my kids
without legal action then
I'm not much of a parent.
Dad.
- You asked me what I think,
I give you my best advice,
you throw it back in my face.
- That's how we always do it.
- Dammit, Laura, sometimes
you drive me so crazy, I.
- Come to dinner?
- I'm gonna go shopping
with Annie for the cruise.
She needs something formal.
- And here I thought
Spandex fit every occasion.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I.
(dog barking)
Tell me why the stars do shine
Tell me
- I used to sing that to you.
I guess you were too young to remember.
Brad, I know you're mad at
me, and I don't blame you.
Brad, I just wanna say that
no matter what, I love you.
- Bull, you can't love me.
You don't even know me.
I don't know you, I don't
wanna know you, ever!
- I realize that, and
I have thought about.
Brad.
- Are you stupid, what
the hell are you doing?
- Honey.
- [Cathy] Hello.
- Hi.
Come on in.
- Yes, Mrs. Hinkle, I'm still here.
- Nice outfit, love your hair.
- Thanks, hold on a second.
- I changed my mind.
- Bye, Mom.
- Seven o'clock.
- Promise.
- And, um, wait a minute, what restaurant?
No, I love this house, I could never sell.
Andrea.
No, it was a mood, okay, it passed.
(dog barking)
(soft piano music)
(sighing)
(dramatic music)
- Brad, what are you doing?
Drop it, drop it.
Just drop it.
- They're mine, I can do
anything I want with them.
- That's true.
That's true, and I understand
why you wanna do this, but--
- Then give me the matches.
- Look, you may not believe this now,
but I think that someday,
you'll probably want these.
- Are you gonna give me the matches?
- No.
(dramatic music)
- [Andrea] It was Brad's birthday.
We went on a picnic.
I was, I don't know, six maybe, seven.
You had been gone for a while.
It was her hair, mostly,
and the way she walked.
I thought it was you.
I kept thinking, what should I say?
Should I say hello?
Or where have you been?
- Andrea.
Andrea.
- I went to a counselor
for a while after that.
I didn't want to, but Mom made me.
- She was right.
(sighing)
When I first left,
I couldn't look at little
kids without crying.
And then, after a year or two,
I started going outta
my way to be near them.
I'd stand outside a preschool,
or sit by a sandbox in a park.
And I'd pick out two kids
I could pretend were you and your brother.
I'd just watch.
And think to myself, no, Brad,
don't eat the sand, sweetie.
Or, Andrea baby, don't climb too high.
- There were no return addresses
on the cards you sent me.
- I wanted you to know
that I still loved you.
- But you didn't wanna hear from me?
- Your dad had remarried.
I thought you were better off.
- But you didn't know.
You didn't know if we were happy,
or if Mom was beating us or--
- Does she beat--
- No.
But why did you just assume?
- I won't anymore, okay?
From now on, I'll always ask,
and you'll always tell me, okay?
Oh.
I have something for you.
I have something for Brad, too.
I wanted to wait to be
sure it was all right.
- Thank you.
It's beautiful.
- They used to say, if you put an emerald
under your tongue, you
could predict the future.
- How about this?
- Let's see.
Amethyst.
Amethyst will protect you from betrayal.
You're well armed.
- We better go.
- I know.
I could stay here all night.
The wedding sounds great.
And Anthony, and Chicago and everything.
- You'd love it.
(clock chiming)
(car engine running)
(door opening)
- Hi, honey.
Have a nice time?
- Yeah, good night, Mom.
- Where'd you go?
- City Lights at Centerpoint.
- Oh, was it good?
I've been thinking about
taking all of us there
for New Year's Eve.
What'd you have?
- Night, Mom.
(door closing)
(soft dramatic music)
(birds chirping)
- [P.A.] Resident on call to ER.
Resident on call to ER.
- I got a call.
- Mrs. Eagerton, haven't
seen you in a few days.
- What happened?
- Don't worry, he's gonna
live, right over here.
Apparently, he convinced his coach
he could jump with the brace on.
- Oh.
Brad, what were you thinking, honey?
Your leg is broken, you could have--
- Laura, he's in enough pain.
- But, Joe, he could have hurt himself.
- He's gonna be okay, why
don't you go get some coffee?
- I don't want coffee.
- Laura.
- [P.A.] Dr. Rosen, please dial 884.
Dr. Rosen, please dial 884.
- This was not a brilliant move.
That hurt?
There?
- Ah.
Yeah.
- I hear things have
been pretty interesting
around your house lately.
Do you remember much about her, Brad?
Your mother?
- My mother is getting coffee.
(machines beeping)
- Remember when you fell off the roof?
You were six years old.
You broke your arm, you split your lip
and you were making jokes.
Tough little guy.
But your dad,
he stood in my office and he sobbed.
He was so scared, so angry at himself.
Just sobbed, did you know that?
You know, it's okay to cry, Brad.
It's okay to be angry.
It's okay to hate her.
It's even okay to like her.
To be curious.
- Can I go now?
- Yeah.
- If this ever happens again, Brad,
no more track, I mean it.
I have half a mind to
have your coach fired.
- You just don't like him.
- No, I don't.
And this little episode
certainly hasn't helped.
- [Andrea] I can't believe
it, it's so beautiful.
- [Laura] Andrea?
- Isn't it gorgeous.
- Yes, but.
- I'm gonna wear it in the wedding.
I'm gonna be the maid of honor.
- I know I should have
asked you first, Laura,
but we were shopping and saw the dress,
and everything just--
- No, absolutely not.
- Mom, please, I'm gonna
go on the honeymoon, too.
We're gonna go to St. Thomas scuba diving.
- Andrea, it's Christmas.
You're supposed to spend Christmas
with your family, remember?
- But Grandpa Ed and
Annie are leaving anyway.
- Go take that thing off
and get ready for dinner.
- [Andrea] No.
- Andrea.
- I wanna go, I wanna
be the maid of honor.
We already have my ticket
set and everything.
- You are some piece of work.
- Andrea, do what she says.
- Don't help me out here, okay.
Feel free to see yourself out.
I'm sure you remember where the door is.
- It's only for a couple weeks.
Winter vacation starts Friday,
so she won't miss any school.
- You have really set me up here.
Whatever I do, I'm the bad guy.
- Believe me, Laura, in this equation
you can never be the bad guy.
- Oh, so now I'm supposed
to feel sorry for you?
Because you screwed up,
and now you wanna make it
all better, and I'm supposed to be patient
and understanding and nice.
Forget it.
(train whistle blowing)
(kids yelling)
Huh, for someone so good at leaving,
you're sure hell to get rid of.
(birds chirping)
- You wanna hear the
whole wedding fantasy?
My daughter is maid of honor.
My son is best man.
- You can't blame him.
- I don't blame him.
He's just like Steve.
Looks right through you
like you don't exist.
- Well I don't remember Steve doing that.
What you said about me having your life.
I've thought a lot about that, I guess.
I guess every second wife does.
Thinks about the first wife.
Wonders what she left
you and why she left it.
Steve was a good man.
- I never said he wasn't.
- You know, it took us
years before we could fight.
Just,
fight like married people without him
making me promise I wouldn't leave.
How could you do it?
I mean,
what gave you permission to just walk out?
To just.
- You never felt like you were drowning?
- Overwhelmed, daily.
But I could never leave my kids.
- I didn't know what to do.
I had no one to go to, I was terrified.
- They were babies, they were terrified.
- What did you want me to do?
Would you rather have me
stay and beat my kids?
(sniffling)
I'll never forgive myself
for not being stronger.
But I wasn't.
Then.
- I knew it.
- They're my kids.
- No.
- I've talked to a lawyer,
I could get custody.
- No, you planned this all along.
- No, honestly, when I came,
I just wanted to see them.
But I've already missed so much.
- And who's fault is that?
- Mine, and I'm not
gonna screw it up again.
I'm getting married to a wonderful man.
They'd have a mother and a father and.
(dramatic music)
- You can't go.
- You little twerp, get outta my room.
- I won't let you.
- I have to, she's my
mother, she's your mother.
- No.
- She is.
Whether you like it or
not, she's our mother.
And I care about her, I wanna know her.
I wanna know who she is.
- Then you're not my sister.
(door knocking)
(dog barking)
- Laura.
- Dad, your phone's been off the hook.
I need that number.
- [Ed] What number?
- I've been trying to call you for hours,
the lawyer's number.
Cathy wants the kids.
She's seeing somebody, and
she can get custody, and so,
if you could please
just get me that number.
- Oh, honey, I'm so sorry.
Look, can I get you
some coffee or anything.
- No, thank you.
- Well, did she get an injunction or?
- No, Annie, Annie,
it's complicated, okay?
- Well does Andrea wanna go with her?
- Of course she wants to go with her.
She thinks it's all
about being in a wedding.
She doesn't realize that
Cathy wants her to stay.
- She doesn't?
- Shut up, Annie, just for once.
- You know, honey, you can
go get a judge that's gonna
give you a piece of paper
that keeps Cathy outta town.
But that's not gonna keep
Andrea from thinking about
or caring about her mother.
- I am her mother.
- You know, I was born
to one hell of a bitch.
Ooh, she was tight-fisted
and she was mean.
But she clothed and she fed me.
But the lady next door, my Aunt Jo,
that was who I went to
when I needed somebody
to cry on or take care of me.
I always did right by
the woman who raised me,
but I did for Aunt Jo because I loved her.
Everybody chooses their own mother.
(soft piano music)
- I can't let her go.
- Sounds to me like she's halfway gone.
- But she's too young, she's too.
- Honey, you can hold
this door open for her,
or you can bolt it shut and
force her to knock it down.
But either way, sooner or later,
she's gonna come through this door.
(soft music)
- Have you done anything?
Legally?
About custody.
- No.
- I could fight you.
I'd probably win.
- In a year, Andrea'll be 14.
Legally, she can decide
who she wants to live with.
I don't wanna go to court.
I want us to work this out ourselves.
Just you and me.
- And then?
- I know you love them.
And I know they love you.
They're great kids because of you.
I'm envious of what you've been to them,
and I'm also thankful.
- Don't, just.
I want her to come home after the wedding.
- What about St. Thomas?
- She doesn't know how to scuba dive.
- I'll teach her.
- Of course you will.
Okay, but,
I want her home in time for school.
No matter what happens,
I want her to finish
the school year, here.
- Okay.
I thought,
if Brad wanted to, they might both come.
- Please, let's just get through this.
(sighing)
- Mom, Mommy, Mom.
Mommy.
(dramatic music)
Mom, Mommy.
Mom.
- I'm here, Andrea.
Wake up, honey, wake up.
You know she wants you
to come live with her.
That's what this wedding
trip is all about.
Showing you just how nice it would be.
- I really wanna go.
- Okay.
(soft music)
(sniffling)
Okay.
- I thought you might need these.
It's her prescription
stuff for her cramps.
And an iron supplement, plus some cream
for around her toenails, she
has a problem with ingrowns.
And if she should break out in a rash,
use this ointment, and
make sure that there's
no lavender in her soap
or cologne or whatever,
because she's allergic to lavender.
- I know.
Andrea, we better go.
- I almost forget.
- No keep it, to remember me.
- I'll bring you back something okay?
- Sure.
- Sweetie.
(soft music)
- Have fun, okay?
- Bye, Mom.
- Bye.
You have a safe trip.
Call me when you get there, okay?
- Why did you say yes?
She's the only person in the whole world
I really care about.
At least you still have Brad,
but I don't have anybody.
- Tandy, she's coming back, she's coming
back.
(soft music)
- I can't believe you're actually here.
- Wow, look at the skyscrapers.
- You should see the view
from the top of that one.
I'll take you up there later, if you like.
- When do I meet Anthony?
- Lunch.
- Oh.
- Do you like this room?
- I love it.
- It's yours.
- This is just amazing.
- This is just the beginning.
- Can I use the phone?
- Sure.
Then get dressed and I'll
take you to breakfast.
(busy signal)
- Tandy, hi, oh my God,
there's these incredibly high skyscrapers
right outside my window.
(dog barking)
- Hey hey hey now, Duke, you cut that out.
- You gonna be okay?
I feel like I'm abandoning you.
- I'm a grown woman,
Dad, I'm not abandonable.
(chuckling)
- Where's that grandson of mine?
- Oh, he's out back
shoveling snow off the porch.
- Okay, I'll take him, come on.
- He likes the yellow one for water.
Don't ask me why.
I really appreciate you doing this, a lot.
- I'm glad Dad has you.
- Oh, no you aren't.
- Well, I'm coming around.
- Oh, good, I'm glad to hear it.
Now, listen, while
we're gone, can you just
do something nice for yourself?
I mean, do something to relax,
take your mind off everything.
- Sure.
- What do you do for fun?
- Fight with my daughter.
- Oh, honey.
(diners chattering)
- Old people, young people, kids,
lovers, everyone comes
out, and there's music.
And the voices ring across the ice.
You'll see.
Right after lunch, I'll
get you some skates.
- Are you gonna come, Anthony?
- Oh no, as an athlete,
I'm a wonderful jeweler.
- We'll hold you up.
- But you will come scuba diving, right,
on the honeymoon?
- Scuba diving in Vail?
- I changed the tickets.
I thought St. Thomas
would be more romantic
and fun for all of us.
- Oh.
Oh, well, I'm sure you're right.
- Listen, I don't want
you guys to change if--
- Not at all, I love the beach.
- I'll be back in a minute.
- Never seen her so happy.
You know, I was very surprised
when she told me about
you and your brother.
- Yes, well, she's very
good at surprising people.
- Yes, she is.
We wanna have our own family.
I mean, you're welcome to stay with us,
and I'm sure as I get to know
you I'll come to love you,
but, we wanna have our own children.
You can understand that.
- Sure.
- So this business with your brother,
you think that'll blow over soon?
- Well, I don't--
- Because there's a very good prep school
right outside of town,
be a nice way to segue
to being a family, having him close enough
to visit on the weekends.
He'd probably get a much better education
than what he's getting know,
and there are also excellent
schools for girls here too.
My nieces attended St. Meredith's.
You can ask them about it
later at the rehearsal dinner.
- Excuse me.
- [Daughter] I do not.
- [Mother] Yes you do, two or three hours
every night on the phone.
- [Daughter] Mother.
- [Mother] And all day long at school.
- She's my best friend, don't
you want me to have friends?
- Why can't we spend
some time alone together
for once without Rebecca?
Is that too much to ask?
- Hi.
(water running)
- You okay?
- Yeah, it's just hot in there.
- Let me show you a trick.
Let Earth receive her king
Let every heart
Prepare him room
And heaven and nature sing
And heaven and heaven
And nature sing
He rules the world
With truth and grace
And makes the nations prove
The glories of
- It's okay.
His righteousness
And wonders of His love
- We were in the front
yard waiting for Daddy.
And I'm barefoot.
And the flagstones are
so warm against my feet.
And we're so close.
And I know Daddy's coming.
I just feel so,
safe.
You know what I mean?
Just completely like nothing can hurt me.
I haven't felt that way since.
It's my favorite memory of you.
(soft piano music)
- When I lived in that house,
there was no flagstone walk.
Your dad must have added it later.
(soft piano music)
- Mom.
Mommy.
Mom.
(dramatic piano music)
- Up up up, rise and shine.
Good, we have tons to do today.
What do you wanna do first?
Bikinis and sarongs?
Or dress pumps?
- You're gonna be so mad at me.
- What happened?
- You should always
tell you, you said that
no matter what happened,
I should always tell you.
- Sweetie, what is it?
- I wanna go home.
- What happened?
Did Anthony say something?
- No.
- Did I do something?
I just wanna go home.
(soft music)
- Okay.
Well, after the wedding, we'll--
- No.
I really really wanna go home now.
- Tell me what I did.
Tell me what I can do.
- Nothing.
I just, I miss Tandy and
the rest of my friends.
You know, and my house.
And I really miss my mom.
(soft music)
- Andrea?
Honey, I'm so glad to--
What are you doing here?
- Supposed to spend Christmas
with your family, remember?
- Oh.
Wait a minute, where are you going?
- [Andrea] Tandy's.
- But you just got back, Andrea.
Andrea, come back here.
(laughing)
(rock music)
- I brought your sister home.
- I tore up your cards.
(crying)
I can't even remember you.
No.
(soft music)
- Wait a minute.
What happened?
- You were right.
You're their mother.
- Cathy.
It took you a long time to come back.
It's gonna take them time to accept you.
- I wanted to say goodbye to Andrea.
- She's at Tandy's.
(church bells ringing)
- I used to hate this place.
You've done a lot with it.
With.
- Thank you.
(soft music)
(crying)
(soft piano music)
(soft music)
(MultiCom Jingle)