[THUNDER RUMBLING]
[OVER RADIO] Command,
this is Captain Irons.
I got a visual on a UAP
in close, bearing 310.
WOMAN: Roger, Irons.
We don't see anything
on the scope.
CAPTAIN IRONS:
I've never seen anything
maneuver like that.
Turning inland
towards the park.
WOMAN:
Our scope is still clear.
Does IFF show us blocked?
CAPTAIN IRONS: Negative,
that's moving too fast.
Permission to engage now.
WOMAN: Disengage
and back off, Irons.
Repeat, do not engage.
Acknowledge.
CAPTAIN IRONS:
No can do.
I need a closer look.
[WHOOSHES]
[GROANS]
[LAUGHING]
Too much mustard.
I thought we were friends.
CHARLIE:
We are friends.[LILY CHUCKLES]
What are you doing?
I hit him with a little
too much mustard.
Yeah, you think?
I wish I could make him
laugh like that.
What can I say?
Daddy's boy.
Key to his heart
is fake pain.
[LOUD RUMBLING]
[DISTANT EXPLOSION]
Come here, Charlie.
Come on.
It's okay, honey.
It's okay. It's okay.
Here, stay with Charlie
and call 911.
Jack, come on, stop.
What are you doing?[SOFTLY] The nearest
town's an hour away.
If I don't try to help,
who will?
It's okay,
I'll be right back.Okay. Okay, go, go.
Yeah, it's probably
just fireworks.
[ENGINE ACCELERATING]
[GASPS]
[EXHALES]
God. I'm sorry.
You okay? Sorry,
I didn't see you. Hey.
You all right?
Hey. What's
your name, buddy?
Irons.
What?
Captain Sean Irons.
U.S. Air Force.
Are you alone?
What happened?
No, we had a collision.
Collision?
With what?
JACK: Are you sure
you're okay?
[IRONS BREATHING HEAVILY]
[EXHALES]
Is that a...UAP.
What?Unidentified
Aerial Phenomenon.
UFO wasn't working
for you guys?
I've been waiting
a long time to see
one of these up close.
This technology's gonna
change everything.
Hey, there's something moving.
FEMALE VOICE:
Analyzing planet.
FEMALE AUTOMATED VOICE:
Guardian denied.
Guardian accepted.
Pairing.
Self-destruct initiated.
Watch it!
[GASPS]
Come here.
FEMALE AUTOMATED VOICE:
Analyzing planet.
FEMALE NEWSCASTER:
No one has claimed
responsibility
for tonight's daring rescue
of 15 kidnapped schoolgirls.
But eyewitnesses report
yet another sighting
of the hero dubbed The Guard.
MALE NEWSCASTER:
Crime rate is
actually going down.
Overall crime has dropped
four percent.
CHARLIE: Hey, Daddy!
Come play catch with me.
JACK: Look, I'm sorry.
How about next week?
LILY:
I can't do this anymore, Jack.
JACK: Charlie,
we're still a family.
In breaking news, another
possible Guard sighting.
The Guard is using
alien technology.
The laws of thermodynamics
and physics just
don't even apply.
And I can find
the power source,
but I need resources.
Looking at you, Ansel Argon,
CEO of Argon Industries.
CHARLIE: [SOFTLY] You messed
with the wrong superhero.
Bad guy, you better
say your prayers.
TEACHER: Charlie?Guard's gonna kick your butt.
TEACHER: Charlie![STUDENTS GIGGLING]
You're up.
[IN NORMAL VOICE]
The nuc... No.
Well, my presentation
isn't about any of these
energy sources,
it's actually
about a new one,
which happens to be
the world's greatest hero,
The Guard.
[MOUTHING] No.Charlie, how is this relevant?
Everybody's talking
about how The Guard
stopped that nuclear meltdown
in India, right?
Or how he saved
those kids in Taiwan,
or stopped that jet from
crashing in Brazil.
But nobody's talking
about how he did it.
He's got some kind of
new energy source,
and it's not any of these...
Uh...
Hey. Am I
at the right place?
TEACHER:
You must be Maya Monroe?
Class, this is our new
transfer student
from Turkey,
so please do not mock any
strange customs that she...
She used to go here.
[BURPS]
[STUDENTS TITTERING]
Whatever.
Miss Monroe, take a seat.
Charlie, you can continue,
and please
bring this back
to the subject at hand.
[WHISPERS] What?[WHISPERS] I don't know.
[SCHOOL BELL RINGING]
BOY1: Finally.You know what?
BOY 2:
That's the stupidest thing
I've ever heard.
TEACHER: Test tomorrow.
[STUDENTS GROANING]
BOTH: Berger!
Berger! Berger!
My parents are
so embarrassing.[CONTINUES] Berger! Berger!
At least your dad
shows up.
Mine's at a never-ending
IT conference.
Look.BERGER: Hey.
Lizzie with Maya.
Nine o'clock.[BURPS]
So my elementary
school BFF
just showed back up
after, like, years of
traveling the world.
So jealous.
What's your at?I'm not on social media.
What?
Okay. Well, what
are your interests?
Um, lock picking,
Norwegian Death Metal
and I can field-strip
an M4 blindfolded.
Okay.
You ask Lizzie
to the dance yet?
Not yet.
Women like it
when you leave things
till the last minute.
Where'd you
hear that?Yo! Berger...
Mom wanted me
to bring you your fan,
so, here.
Take it.
You ever think about how
you call him Berger,
but that's your
last name, too?
That's why I go as
Big Mac, because, uh,
I'm the tastiest Berger.Okay.
GIRL: Wow,
this is a real blowout.
COACH HAMMER:
Let's go, Forrest.
Charlie Kincaid.
Uh, Coach?
I think you, um,
accidentally said
my first and last name?
You're in.
We need a lefty.
BOY: Man, that's a big kid.
Who is that?
That's Forrest Deal.
They call him "The Sequoia."
BOY: Now pitching
is Charlie Kincaid.
COACH:
Crafty Kincaid, look alive.
Come on, Forrest! Let's go!
I heard he bullies
his own parents.
[CHUCKLES]
BOY: Good luck, Charlie.
I heard that
his stare is so deadly
he can't even look
himself in the mirror.
LIZZIE: Let's go, Charlie!
You got this.
Didn't know this was
the Peewee Leagues.
Didn't know they allowed
steroids in middle school.
BOY: Come on, Charlie.BERGER: Please
don't kill my friend.
All right, let's go, Forrest.
[GRINNING] Crush it.
[CROWD CHANTING]
Charlie! Charlie! Charlie!
[GROANS]Ooh.
BOY:
That's gonna leave a mark.
Charlie.His mama gonna be mad.
[SONG PLAYING]
This song again?
Can we just change...
No. No, we can't.
Plus we all know
this song's a classic.
BERGER: No one knows that.CHARLIE: Oh, God.
BIG MAC: No, okay, well,
my car, my music.
All right?[SOFTLY] My life is over.
Uh, that's 24.
That's right on the fence.
You wanna go for it?
Nah. They're just kids.
Let 'em go.
I hate kids.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER
ON POLICE RADIO]
Even my own.
BERGER: Bye, Charlie.
FEMALE NEWSCASTER:
But eyewitnesses report
yet another sighting of...
What? ...the hero dubbed
The Guard.
Once again authorities
have found no fingerprints
and no other evidence
with the exception of strange
patterns left on the scene.
Now a trademark...
Hey. How was the game? ...of Guard's sightings.
Another Guard sighting?Yeah.
...what is The Guard exactly?
Is it a lone vigilante or...[CELL PHONE RINGING]
Hey. Did you pack a bag
for your dad's yet?
We both know
he's gonna cancel.
Hey! Hey, Jack. Hey.
Joining us tonight
is Ansel Argon,
CEO of Argon Tactical.
His business has been
uniquely impacted
by the so-called Guard,
who has ushered
a new era of peace
leaving many countries to...
Yeah, I saw.
NEWSCASTER:
Your company, Argon Tactical,
recently reported
operating losses
for the first time
in 13 years, so...
That's not true.
I think it is. No, that's definitely
not true.
JACK: Just push it to next
week, the celebration.[SIGHS]
Jack, come on, I'm...
I'm sorry.Don't do this to me today.
I am so sick of
all these excuses.
JACK: I'm sorry.
It's my job.All right, well...
I'm dropping him off at 6:00,
so you better be there.
Okay.Okay. Yeah, bye.
Let me guess.
Another "IT conference"?
Rescheduling for next month?
No! He's really excited
to see you tonight.
I bet he doesn't even
remember my birthday.
Of course, he does.
Come on, go, go get
your bag packed
and maybe take a shower.
If The Guard continues
to erode the need
for a defense industry
will there be panic
at companies like yours?
I'll... I'll give you
a better question
that you could have asked.
With zero oversight...
what happens if The Guard
has a bad day?
LILY: Look, he's there
waiting for you.
CHARLIE:
Why are we doing this?
LILY: Hey.All right!
Hi.LILY: Hey.
He looks a little older,
I can tell.
He's really happy
about it.Very happy to be here!
Okay, you wanna just
put that stuff inside
and I'll meet you
in there?
I feel like
I'm in trouble.
No, no, no,
he had a rough day.
Um, candles
are in the bottom.
My favorite!Try not to eat 'em
all tonight.
We'll do our best,
no promises.
This isn't gonna
last forever, Jack,
you know that, right?
Before we know it,
he's gonna be
grown up and...
you're gonna be
begging him
to return your calls.
You don't have to
convince me. Okay?
I want to spend
more time with him,
I really do.
I've just been busy.
There are some things
that are more important
than work, Jack.
Okay?I know.
Talk to him.Yeah.
Tonight.
Been a while.Yes.
I like what
you've not done
with the place.
I'm going for that kinda
single-dad short-term
rental feel.
Where's that funny mug
I got you?
Uh, it's around
here somewhere.
Listen, Charlie,
sorry about the game.
Missed my connecting
flight in Denver
and in-flight Wi-Fi
was screwed up.
But I got you something.
It's okay, you don't
have to bribe me.
Yes, I do have to
bribe you.
And I'm gonna be...
I'm gonna bribe you.
Wait right here!
Okay, Charlie.
My old mitt.
Now, I have been
saving this for you,
and I think now
is the time.
I'm a lefty, Dad.
Oh, yeah.
That's right.
Sorry about that, I...
Well, if you could
have anything,
what else would you want?
I just want to go
camping again.
Like we used to?
That's a great idea.
Well, as soon as things
slow down at work,
we're gonna do that.
In the meantime...
I got this Nintendo Switch.
I know you don't
like bribes.I accept bribes.
JACK: Keep it going,
keep it going,
keep it going.
Three, two, one...go!
Home run! Dinger!
Boom, boom, boom, boom...
And now pizza!
We got to do it
in three, two, one.Two, one.
Ah, come on.
Does this game
not have HBT?
What's an HBT?You know,
Hidden Ball Trick?
You know that one, right?
Where the first baseman
pretends to throw it
to the pitcher,
and then when the base runner
takes a little lead off first
and he's right there,
then he grabs it with a...What?
Hey. Cheater.And they get
him right there...
No, no, hold on.
That's cheating.
You're wasting all my...
Give it back.
You're making me lose.
Look what you did.
Ah.[CHUCKLES]
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
Sorry. Let me
just get this.
Okay.
Hurry up.
JACK: Hey.
Sorry that took so long.
Let me guess.
Something at work.
Yeah, that was my boss.
I gotta...
I guess there's an emergency,
so I'm gonna have to...
There's always
an emergency.
Why can't you just cancel,
like you always do?
Charlie, listen,
I know this sucks.
I wanna stay here
and celebrate with you.
But, I gotta go.
You have to believe me
when I say it's important.
Yeah, I know.
More important than me.
No, that's not
what I'm saying.
You only had me over
because Mom forced you to.
Just be honest!
You want me
to be honest?
Yeah. That's all I want.
Listen. I'm gonna be
back in a couple days,
tops. Okay?
And we're gonna sit down,
and I'm gonna explain things
in a way that I hope that
you're gonna understand
what's been happening.
Oh, I understand fine.
You're just a crappy dad.
Charlie...
Well, you can't be
here by yourself.
Let me call Mom
and she'll come pick you up.
CHARLIE:
Nah, I got it. I got it.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
Hey, Mom.
Uh, hold on to your hat.
Dad has a work emergency,
so can you come pick me up?
Yeah, I know,
it's a bummer.
Okay.
She'll be here
in ten minutes.
You don't have to wait.Listen. I know.
I'm not a baby
anymore, Dad.
Okay, I'll see you later.
Fanny pack.
Can't forget that.
I love you.
I'll see you
in a couple days.
[DOOR CLOSES]
You still there?
I love it when you
call me "Mom".
Now, let's throw a rager.
Yeah, let's throw a rager.
Wait, what is a rager?
[MOUTHING SONG]
[DOORBELL RINGS]
[IN FEMALE VOICE]
Hey, Berger.
Hi.
Oh, crap.
[MOUTHING]What are you doing here?
Berger said I could
borrow your notes for that
stupid test tomorrow.
Also, he said your dad
abandoned you
and you're listening
to Anne Murray alone.
All right, let's get this
rager started.
[MUSIC SWITCHES]
LIZZIE: Much better.
[WHISPERS]
Dude, what the hell?
Uh, chicks dig
sob stories.
Why did you bring 'em
here at all?
I'm sorry, I didn't know
you wanted to have
a one-on-one rager.
Maya does not like me.
She left the country
because of me.
BERGER: If that were true,
she wouldn't
be here right now.
Take a deep breath in.
And now breathe
into your hands
and tell me how
your breath smells.
[SNIFFS] It's good.Okay.
Now, use some of that
sweet, sweet breath
and ask Maya
to the dance.
No.
Do you ladies want
a sugary beverage?
LIZZIE: Lead the way.
Wait. It's your birthday
tomorrow?
You remember my birthday?
No, it's on the photo.
Cool. Cool.
I don't like
to make a big deal.
I always find
birthdays disappointing.
Birthdays with
divorced parents suck.
Tell me about it.
My dad is the king
of thoughtless
airport gifts.
Do you know how many butt
pillows I have at home?
I think those are
neck pillows.
There's only two forks?
What is this guy,
a serial killer?
I want to, um...
...address the...
I don't know
if you remember
fifth grade?
Yeah, what happened
in fifth grade?
I feel really bad
about what I did.
and I don't, um, know...
...how to say this.
But...What's happening?
What's happening
is I'm trying
to open up.
No, like, behind you.That's what
I'm trying to say.
Berger?Lizzie?
I hit the balls
and it opened up
and I can't...
It's okay, I understand.
Your dad's a freak.
Whoa.
Wait. Careful, careful.
BERGER: How do we open it?We need a code.
This is just like
an escape room.
Scan the room for clues.
It's numerical.
So that rules out
childhood pets, birthplace.
When's your parents'
anniversary?
They're divorced.
LIZZIE: How about
your dad's birthday?
November 18th.
[BEEPS]
LIZZIE: Or...
Better yet, the birthday
of a loved one.Nothing.
Hey, Happy Almost Birthday.
0-4-0-7-0-8.
[UNLOCKING BEEP]
[WHIRRING]
BERGER: Hello.LIZZIE: Whoa.
Looks like
an elevator.
What, to go
upstairs?
That's kinda lazy,
isn't it?
Why is there
only one button?
Please don't touch...
[ALL SCREAMING]
My guts are floating.
[GROANING]
MAYA: How far down
did we go?Far.
Yeah... I'm okay.
MAYA: Whoa,
this place is big.
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Headquarters activating.
Come on.
BERGER:
How far down are we?
This is so tight.
This is beyond tight.
This is the tightest.
Look at that.
CHARLIE:
Come on, guys, over here.
BERGER:
Whoa, what's this?
MAYA: Okay, how could
he have built this?
We're, like, a hundred miles
underground.
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Welcome.
[BEEPING]
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Mission in progress.
"Current location:
New Zealand."
LIZZIE: That's far away.
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Mission archive.
Plane crash in Brazil.
Nuclear meltdown in India.
That was all over the news!
Tsunami in Japan.
The thing in
the Empire State Building.
These are all
The Guard's missions.
We're in The Guard's
secret headquarters.
Which is under
your dad's house.
Do you realize
what this means?
It means my dad
works for The Guard.
No.Dude.
It means your dad
is The Guard.
What?
No.
My dad is not The Guard.
The Guard is like
the greatest hero ever.
BERGER: Okay.My dad can't
handle hot wings.
Yeah.I've seen him without
his shirt on.
He can barely swim.
Okay.My dad is not The Guard.
MAYA:
Somebody's in denial.
Hey, guys.
Does The Guard wear
a fanny pack?
IRONS: Lost it again.
Signal blocker's too strong.
Run it again.
Simulate its origin.
On it.
So, Irons, where do we stand
on finding The Guard's source?
We'll find it, all right?
Relax. We just need more time.
Time?
You've had time.
You've had years.
Sooner or later,
it becomes binary, okay?
You either found it
or you haven't.
And you haven't.
And that's why
I'm pulling the plug.
You're firing me?
Oh, I'm not just firing you.
No, no,
I'm firing everybody.
I'm firing that guy,
firing him, her.
She's all right,
he's cool.
I know what happened
that night.
And I know I've lost
everything trying to
prove that it's real.
My credibility,
my career.My money.
My own government
tried to destroy me
for asking questions.
Why do you think that is?
Listen,
I love that story.
The uniform, the woods,
the bad man
who stole the orb,
how you got
your little boo-boo.
I get it. Tell it
to someone else.
As soon as The Guard
makes a mistake,
we'll find the Source.
If there's one thing
I learned
about The Guard
it's he doesn't
make mistakes.
All right, you got
till the end of the week
to shut this down.
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Printing in progress.
Wow. Cool lasers.
Escape hatch
panel number 13 complete.
BERGER:
Look, it's building itself.
LIZZIE: Some kind of
3D printer from space.
Ooh, tell it
to print a fake ID.
BERGER: Can it print
Britney Spears?
Hasn't she been
through enough?
Can't print people.
Looks like only a few things
to choose from.
Uh, Maya, I think you
pressed the wrong button.
Yeah.
Emergency shutoff.
CHARLIE: This is a bad idea.LIZZIE: Uh, here,
try this button.
[CLASSICAL MUSIC PLAYING]
AUTOMATED VOICE: Transferring
to charging station.
Nice material.
Oh, what's this?
BERGER:
Looks like a magic wand.
Whoa.
[GASPS]
Looking good, Hermione.
It's not a magic wand,
it's a magnet wand.
What?
[SCOFFS]
It's a HUD.
A what?A heads-up display.
I wonder
what this button does?
[LIZZIE SCREAMING]
Help me! Berger!
Berger! It's not a backpack!
CHARLIE: Hold on,
I'm coming!Turn it off!
Pull me down, Maya!Okay, hang on,
hang on, I got...
Whoa!BERGER: Lizzie, careful!
[LIZZIE SCREAMING]
You okay?That was awesome.
That was crazy.You guys okay?
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Target applying.
Oh, shh...
[MAYA GRUNTS]
LIZZIE:
Oh, my God, Maya!
I killed Maya.You killed Maya.
I killed Maya.You killed Maya!
She's okay. You're okay.
That was awesome.
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Shrink to fit.
Stylish and functional.BERGER: Guys, check this out!
[ALL SCREAMING]
LIZZIE: Where's his head?
It's DJ Berger,
the headless assassin
comin' at you live!
Berger?
Guys! Guys!
Look over here.
BERGER:
Ooh, I look good today.
How?
It's amazing!
You put your head through
one magic portal thingy
and it comes out
the other.
Oh, my gosh.
Ooh, what's that?
[ALARM CHIRPS]
[ALL SCREAMING]
AUTOMATED VOICE:
G-mobile summoned.
Ready for mission.
This is sick.
LIZZIE: You still
think your dad's
The Guard's butler?
Uh...
You okay?
What? Yeah, I, um...
I'm just ready
to get outta here.
Right, 'cause
it kinda looks like
you broke something.
Yeah, I guess
I don't know
my own strength.
[FLAMINGOPLAYING]
Hey. Now that
we're alone,
I just wanted you to know
that I've been picking up
on your signal...
And...What?
Yes. I would love to go
to the dance with you.
Aww.
Thank you for
the completely random
and utterly
last-minute offer, Berger.
Truly.
But, I already have a date.
Who?An older guy,
more my speed.
You're a little young
for me.
But we're the same age.
CHARLIE: Guys, we gotta
put everything back
where we found it.
Nobody can know
we were in here.[MOUTHING INDISTINCTLY]
You know we have
that test tomorrow,
anyway.
That class was so easy.
I wish I could
take it for you.
About that...
I kind of have
a crazy idea.
[BURPS]
A covert mission.
But, we're gonna need to
borrow a few gadgets.
TEACHER:
You have five minutes
to complete this test.
No phones.
Cheaters will be prosecuted.
LIZZIE: "Maya."
No problem.
You ready to chop down
the Sequoia?
[MOUTHING]
What the hell?
VIRGINIA: We got a hit.
It's strong.
Hawaii, Irons,
you seeing this?
That was awesome.She didn't
even notice.
TEACHER:
Excuse me, Mister Berger.
Uh...
What was that thing
you put in your locker?
It was a sculpture
I made for art class.
I got my eyes
on you, Berger.
Very challenging test,
thank you.Anytime.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
Hey, Coach?Yeah.
Put me in.
You sure about that?
[SCATTERED APPLAUSE]
PLATE UMPIRE:
Strike one!
That was pretty fast.
This is the lifeline.
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Power increased.
Charlie.
We got a strong
flash signal.
Like single-mom
strong.
IRONS:
This could be it.
This is the
prosperity line.
Strike two!
And this is the, uh,
line that tells me
that you don't
have a date
to the dance.
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Maximum strength.
Do you wanna
go with me?
I guess.Yeah, cool.
[CROWD CLAPPING]
Now that's fast.
Strike three. You're out.
[BOTH CHEER]
Shotgun!BERGER: You owe me
a new glove!
LIZZIE: What's next?
[ALL SCREAMING]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[SHOUTING] You're
an excellent driver!Thanks!
HAWAII: Is The Guard
doing donuts?
IRONS: Stay on him.
NEWSCASTER: And in
breaking news, another
possible Guard sighting.
Local officials...
[BEEPING]OFFICER GRANT: 108!
Oh! We got
a live one!
Light 'em up!
[SIREN WAILING]
Dispatch, we got
a 10-80 in progress.
Looks like a hippie van
on steroids.
Are those police sirens?
Charlie? Charlie,
I need you to gas it
right now!
I can't get arrested!
I need to go
to medical school!
Time for some
evasive driving.
YOLO!
Hey! Hippie Monster Truck!
Pull over!
Let's dance!
Get outta the road,
you idiots.
LIZZIE: Charlie, drive faster!
They're still there!
This is a tactical vehicle.
It must have
diversionary features.
All of them, guys,
try all of them!
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Automatic machine gun.
Missiles.
Discombobulator on.
Discombobulator off.
HAWAII:
It's a full-blown surge.
Lockin' on.
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Engaging smoke screen.
Is that smoke?It's smoke bombs.
I can't be near smoke,
I have asthma.
[SCREAMING]
Roll up the window!
What is that, anthrax?
Let me have some.
MAYA: What else
do we have here?
LIZZIE: Come on try something.
Figure something out.
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Magnetic pulse activated.MAYA: Magnet activated.
Whoa.
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Connection established.CHARLIE: Woo-hoo!
Magnets bonded.Stop!
Nice driving, Kincaid!
Yeah, I play Mario Kart
at a very high level!
It's unblocked.Yep, there he is. Got him!
All right,
pull up the map.
VIRGINIA: He must've
made a mistake.
Hell yeah, he did.
Tell the team
we're mission go.
We got him.
CHARLIE:
Driving's not that hard.
[CELL PHONE VIBRATING]
You guys go down.
I'll be there in a sec.
BERGER:
Okay. Don't be too long.
Hey, Charlie,
uh, I'm sorry,
things are more
complicated
than we thought.
So, I'm gonna have to
extend this trip
for a few more days
but I will see you
the following week
and happy birthday.
I really...
BERGER:
Hey, Maya, go long.
I got it!LIZZIE: Oh, no!
Guys, I think it's dead!
CHARLIE: Lizzie!
Okay.
MAYA: Ow.
That was amazing.
I'm gonna go upstairs
and make a phone call.
[BURPS]
[GRUNTS]
I can't believe...So I was thinking...
Sorry, you go first.
I was just gonna say it.
It must be weird, huh?
Knowing your dad has,
like, a sci-fi man cave.
Yeah, it is weird.
Thanks for asking.
It's like we don't even
know each other.
I thought he worked
at a Genius Bar.
And he thought
I was a righty.
Well, I didn't forget.
Happy birthday.
You fixed it?
Thanks.
[WHISPERS] Formation.
HAWAII:
What do they call you?
Wisconsin.I'm Hawaii.
Aloha.
Shh.
Oh.
Everyone on alert
here, okay?
Yeah, careful, this could be
Freddy Krueger's house.
You seeing
any security?
No, I see defenses.
They just seem
to be disarmed
at the moment.
Signal's comin'
from inside.
Move.
[HUMMING TUNE]
Clear.Clear.
Smells good.
Feels like we're breaking
into a Pottery Barn.
What are we stealing, Irons?You'll know when you see it.
Oh. I have this lamp.
I get why he couldn't
tell the world about
his secret identity.
But...
Why couldn't he tell me?
Am I that untrustable?
Certainly weren't
in the fifth grade.
So you do remember.
How could I forget?
Robbie Fernandez's
birthday party.
You and I almost kiss.
You chicken out.
And you tell everyone
I have bad breath.
It wasn't true.
There's nothing wrong
with your breath.
I know, 'cause I have
amazing breath,
but you do know
the nickname
Moldy Mouth Maya
followed me
around, right?
And that's why
you left the country.
What? No, my mom got
transferred, you dingus.
[BEEPING]
I'm getting
an electromagnetic pulse
from below the house.
WOMAN: We checked.
There's no basement.
Hey, you guys
are gonna wanna
check out his office.
It has a great feng shui
and a secret elevator.
Sick, right?
We are in the right place.
What's up, guys?
Welcome toMTV Cribs
with your boy,
Barry Berger.
And right now
I'm in my secret HQ,
which kinda rocks,
pun intended.
[ELEVATOR DINGS]
Must be Lizzie?
When did Lizzie
get a flashlight?
[WHISPERS]
Something's wrong.
We gotta move, come on.
[KEYPAD BEEPS]
[DIGITAL BEEPING]
And, uh, yeah, this is where
the magic happens.
I don't really know
what this room...
[MUFFLED SCREAMING]
Shh.
Okay, we gotta hide.
There are people
here with guns.
[NERVOUSLY] The Mafia?Shh!
No. They look
paramilitary to me.
How could you tell?
Equipment.
I saw a Sig Sauer MDX,
Zev Dragonfly Glock 17,
Plate Carriers,
and grenades.Wow.
We gotta get Lizzie
and... [GASPS]
Oh, my God, Lizzie.
MAN: [ON PHONE]
I'm wearing a vest now,
I'm really looking forward...Mmhmm.
All right. Well, remember
not to make a big deal
when you get here, okay?
IRONS: The Guard's on
a mission in Japan. So...
It looks like we just
missed him then.
Let's get this object
and get the heck
outta here.
Um...
Looks like
we got company.
IRONS: Well, whoever it is,
it's not him.
They might be after
the same thing we are,
though, so...
Let's make sure
they don't
beat us to it.
CHARLIE:
What are we gonna do?
[WHISPERS] I have an idea.
We hide until Charlie's dad
gets back and saves us.
How long is he
gone for again?
He said he could be
a couple of days.
[IN NORMAL VOICE]
A couple as in two
or a couple as in ten?
'Cause the human body
can survive three days...A couple
literally means two.
Guys, come on,
Lizzie's up there
and we gotta help her.
How? The only way
out is the elevator.
The garage. That's where
the camper van came out of.
There must be
an exit, right?
Let's go.
Whoever's down here,
we're gonna smoke 'em out.
You and Wisconsin
sweep the perimeter.Yeah.
Jersey, you and Hawaii
set the signal jammer
upstairs.
Make sure no one's
hidin' out up there
and no one takes
as much as a piss
without talkin' to me
first, you got that?
WISCONSIN: Copy that.
Starting now.
He's got one of those
little fancy Japanese toilet
motion-sensor things
that spray the...
Yeah. Get upstairs.
Copy that.WISCONSIN: Move. Let's go!
JERSEY: You heard him.
Let's move.
Just text me when you're here
and I'll come outside.
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Lockdown initiated.
Hurry up!
In five, four, three...BERGER: Go, go, go.
...two, one.
WISCONSIN:
Did you hear that?Yeah.
On me.
[WHISPERS]
Go back.
Argon, we found
the place.
ARGON: And what?But we got a problem.
Yeah, what is it?
You'll wanna
get over here ASAP. I'm on my way.
[GASPS]
[PANTING]
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Power source removed.
Where are you hiding?
[LIZZIE WHIMPERING]
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Generating predictions.
BERGER:
Charlie. Charlie.
Charlie.Huh?
MAYA: Come on!
IRONS: Whoever is here,
I know you can hear me.
We have this place locked down
so there is no escape.
We've come
to retrieve an object,
and we followed
the energy trail
to this exact spot.
So we know it's in here.The van.
We came for the object,
not you,
so you have a choice.
You can just give it to us
and no harm will come to you.
Or you can get in our way
and you will be sorry.
Oh, no.
[INTENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Where are these intruders?
JERSEY: They're downstairs
and there's someone
up here. A girl.
What if she called the cops?
Not possible.
I set up blockers
around the house.
Did you block
every frequency?
Does SpongeBob live
in a pineapple?
Looks like we might have to
get our hands dirty tonight.
Hey, killing kids is not
a part of my contract.
Hey, hey, hey, whoa.
Who said anything
about killing kids?
All right, we're gonna
find her and we're gonna
scare her, right?
Uh-huh.Good. 'Cause
I don't kill kids.
No, totally,
totally, totally.
But, uh,
what about adults?
Adults are fine, right?Adults are fine.
I kill adults
all the time.Yeah, exactly.
One less adult.
[FLOOR CREAKS]
Freeze![GASPS]
Who are you?
I'm Lizzie McGonagle.
Elizabeth.
And I'm 14 years old.
And I look really mature,
but I'm just starting
to feel comfortable
in my own skin.
And I'm too pretty
to die, okay?
I'm way too pretty
to die
and I don't know why
you guys wanna kill me.
Because I'm so pretty
and I have so much more
of life to live right now.
You guys don't have
as much life
to live as I do,
and I really just don't want
you guys to kill me.
Please don't kill me.
Shh.
Please.[DOORBELL RINGS]
Who is that?
I don't know.ARGON: Did you call the cops?
No! I swear.
Did you order food?No, no, it's not food.
There's pizza over there
It's DiGiorno, not delivery.
Who is DiGiorno?
Is that DiGiorno at the door?
No! No.Who is DiGiorno?
I don't know why
you guys are here.
Get her down here.
"We came to
retrieve an object."
BERGER: I think
he means that thing.
Yes, obviously
Okay, where did you go?I don't know.
It showed me things.
Like a vision.
Whatever it is,
it's powerful.
Well, whatever it is,
let's give it to them
and get the hell
out of here.
What? No!
It's not ours to give,
it belongs to my dad.
Who cares? If we don't
give 'em that thing,
they're gonna kill us.
Well, they still might
kill us even if we do.
I don't trust militias.
BERGER: Then there's
nothing we can do.
Wrong. There is
something we can do.
Defend ourselves!
That's what
I'm talking about.
Okay, I lied
to you guys.
Listen. It's just my date.[KNOCK ON DOOR]
Please let me get rid of him.
He's not part of this.
No one has to get hurt.
Wait, wait. His parents
are both lawyers.
I mean, one is just
a personal injury lawyer,
but still, they'll come
looking for him
and they'll call
the police.
You don't wanna deal
with an ambulance chaser,
trust me.
BOY: Lizzie!Cover the door.
Wait, wait, wait.You have 60 seconds
to get rid of him.
BOY: It's scary out here!Be cool.
Hi.
[SPEAKING FRENCH]
Bonsoir, ma cherie.
You look ravishing,
as always.
Uh, thanks,
Big Mac. Um, so...
[WHISPERING GIBBERISH]
What is that?
Get help!
Call the cops.Get her inside.
JERSEY: That's enough.
Get in here.[BIG MAC YELPS]
Looks like Eugene
just got his license.
Um, can you not
call me Eugene?
He likes to be
called Big Mac.
Gun.What are you doing here?
Well, what happened was,
um, I came here
to pick up my date...
Right.That's my date.
And, it just so...
It happens that
she has been hangin'
out with my brother
and his friend,
[STAMMERING] Charlie.
That's why I'm here.
So what happened was
you [MIMICS STAMMERING]
came here to hang out
with your girl who's also
hangin' out with your...
Brother.
Who then is
hanging out with...
Charlie....Charlie,
and his friends.
You don't gotta
make fun of me,
but yes.
Perfect.
Just kids, huh?
Irons! When were
you gonna tell me
you found The Guard's
secret headquarters?
I wanted to wait
till we actually had
the energy source.
You were waiting.
So where is it?
Missing.
There's someone down here.
Could be security, militia...
Militia?
I mean, whoever it is,
they're highly evasive.
Romeo and Juliet over here
are the teenage militia?
Hi, guys.
Defend ourselves?
How do you expect us
to do that?
I have an idea.
Have you guys heard
of guerilla warfare?
Xbox or PS5?
No, actual
guerilla warfare.
Using your weaknesses
as strengths?
We're smaller than them,
but we're mobile.
We have home field advantage
and a giant 3D printer.
I say we get
the gadgets,
get scrappy,
and fight our way out.
ARGON:
Is this thing on? Yeah.
Hi, I'm looking for
a Charlie Kincaid.
I got someone here
who'd like to say hi to you.
LIZZIE: Charlie, these
old guys have guns!
Do whatever they say.
They got Lizzie.
BIG MAC: Berger, hey,
hey, man. Look, if I die,
I'm gonna kill you!
ARGON: Dude, shut up.
Give me the Source,
Charlie Kincaid,
or I'll kill your friends.
You got it?
BERGER: My brother's here.
They're gonna kill
my brother. Give me that.
Berger, I know you're
scared. I am, too.
But we have a plan.
We can fight back.Shh.
Come on, Charlie,
you're not exactly
the action hero type.
What am I then,
since you seem to know?
You're a scaredy-cat.
And you know what?
Scaredy-cat is good.
Guys.But this is not the time
to play hero cat, okay?
Stick to scaredy-cat.MAYA: Shh!
This coming from
a guy who's scared
to leave the house
without a backup inhaler?
With all the asthma,
the celiacs,
the tubs of Flonase?
Guys, come on.
You guys are friends.
We're risking our lives
for that rock
so you can prove
to your dad
how brave you are.
But guess what?
He doesn't care.
He cares more
about his job
than he cares
about his own son.
[GRUNTS]
MAYA: Guys, stop fighting.
Hey, stop it. You idiots.
This isn't the time for
airing of grievances!
Now let's work together.
No way. I'd rather go
Han Solo than be
teamed up with you.
[MUFFLED] His parents
are lawyers.
IRONS: Where is Hawaii?
Busy. Just focus on
finding the Source.
You heard him,
guys. Move out.
You, too. Jersey's
gonna babysit.
WISCONSIN: We're clear.
VIRGINIA:
Let's check the next room.
AUTOMATED VOICE: Low power.
[WHISPERING]
This one's dead, too.They're all dead.
IRONS: Virginia,
what's your status?
Have you found anything?
Damn.
Nothin'. And the power
source isn't here.
Find it, please.
Time for phase two?Yep.
ARGON:
I can't wait to blow
this place up.
Seriously, I hate
this place.
Watch the kiddies.Yeah.
A fanny pack?
[SCOFFS]
What can he say?
He looks like a baby.
Sweet. Quarter.He hasn't even hit
his growth spurt...
[SQUEALS]
[GROANING]
I just killed someone.
AUTOMATED VOICE: Charging.
This is it.
This is The Guard's
energy source.
You literally gave
a presentation
about this yesterday.
Ms. Squint owes me
an apology.
Do you think I could win
a Nobel Prize from this?
I don't think so.BERGER: Hey!
Who's the hero-cat now,
buttmunchers?
Sorry about what
I said back there.
Your ailments aren't
what make you weak,
they're actually what
makes you strong.
And I'm sorry
I punched you.[SIGHS]
BERGER: That was
a really good apology.
I wasn't ready
to forgive you.
I planned on throwing
way more shade.
But, I'm sorry, too.
[GRUNTS]
Hey, I think
I saw this guy
on TV yesterday.
Mm-mm.
[MUFFLED]
Wait, wait, no, no.
[GROANS]
[PANTING]
Hey, how old
are you guys?
Eighteen.Fourteen.
ARGON: It's just
you guys down here?We'll ask the questions.
I say we torture him
to get info.
[LAUGHING]
And how do you plan
on torturin' me?
Are you gonna
tickle torture me?
Like what are you
gonna do?
Dude, that was too long!
Does that feel
like tickle torture?
That thing's amazing.
Ya wanna sell it?
You wanna see it again?No, no!
No, no, no.
You know, okay.
What do you guys
wanna know?Everything.
Okay, that thing?
That glowing thing?
That thing's highly
advanced technology.
It's like otherworldly
technology.
"Otherworldly"
as in aliens?
Yeah.
That's what "otherworldly"
means, it's not
from this world.
No way. That thing
is clearly designed
for humans.
No, that's because
it adapts
to its environment.
It's a world builder.
It created
this entire place!
I mean, do you think
The Guard built this?
Not without that.
Why do you want it?
Because I think that
The Guard has only unlocked
a fraction
of its potential.
And you wanna
make weapons out of it.
Ya know what
I want it for?
I wanna use it
so I can solve
the world's problems.
So why not tell that
to my dad, huh?
You know how many times
I've been on TV
asking for his help?
And you know what?
I got ghosted.
I'm familiar
with the feeling.
And your dad's being, like,
so selfish right now.
He just wants
that technology
all to himself!
I want to share it.
Huh?
Who's the bad guy here?
You are.You guys look
like smart kids.
Just give me the orb
and I'll let you guys go.
I don't trust him.No way.
I'm giving you my word.
Hey, Charlie. Come here.
Hey, man.
Now's your chance
to be a hero.
You know? Dude,
don't do it for me.
Do it for her.
I mean, there's definitely
a vibe there.
Do you think?There's no vibe, Charlie.
It's hot. It's too hot.
It's gotten...
It's uncomfortable.
Don't listen to him.
JACK: Hey, Lily,
how you doin'?
LILY: Hey, I was just
callin' to see
how it's goin'.
Did you talk?
Yeah, I had a talk.
I didn't have the talk.
To be honest, I just
don't think he's ready.
Jack, I'm so sick
of this superhero shtick.
Listen, if you wanna
be close to him,
then you have to
let him in, okay?
Yeah, you gotta let him in.
Just put Charlie on.
Okay. Put him on where?
What do you mean?
Put him on the phone.
He hasn't picked up
any of my calls.
Right, 'cause
he's not with you.
Oh, shoot.
What?
Because you haven't
seen him
since you dropped him off
at my house.
Dang it!
Okay, wait,
where is Charlie?
He's right
where you left him.
Okay, but...
CHARLIE:
We have your boss.
We're a super tough gang
of mercenaries,
way tougher than you.
Meet us downstairs
for an exchange, losers.
Get up.
LIZZIE: Hey, stop!JERSEY: God, you're strong.
LIZZIE: Take it easy.
We give you the Source,
and you let us go, right?
All of us.Abso... Yes.
You sure?
[SIGHS]
All right, now release
our friends.
BERGER: Come on,
just let 'em go.
What are you doin' here?I'm picking up my date.
Really, Lizzie?
This is the older guy?
My brother?
How could you?Oh, I have no autonomy
in my own decisions?
You know what?
You both betrayed me.
Betrayed?
I didn't know
you liked her.
Charlie, give me
the Source.
Oh, come on.
I'm gonna keep it safe,
I promise.
Hey. Be a hero.
Come on.
Thanks, buddy.
It's beautiful.
Lock 'em up.
Put your hands up!What?
You lied to us?
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Business, man.
Hey.
Let's keep it under wraps
till we get it to the lab.
You mean after
we show the public.
Ansel, we're not
hiding this anymore.
Well, no, no, of course.
We're gonna share it
with the world.
Of course we are.
But we don't want it
to fall into the wrong hands.
We can't just turn this over
without proper analysis.
Can you imagine that?
Who would we want to
turn it over to?
Right? Wait.
Wait, what? It's fake.
It's a fake!
Charlie!
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Emergency shutoff.
CHARLIE: Just business!ARGON: Get back here!
Now!WISCONSIN: What the hell?
CHARLIE: Go, go, go!WISCONSIN: Who's got
eyes on the kid?
There's only one exit.
CHARLIE: Let's get to
the elevator, come on.
BERGER: Don't tell 'em
where we're going.
MAYA: Watch out!
Grenade!
[GASPS]
No!
[EXHALES] Gotcha.
Charlie, we're free!
Let's go!
Not without the Source.
ARGON:
Jersey, toss it to me.
CHARLIE: Hey, Argon!
Playtime's over, kids!
We're not kids!We're young adults.
And playtime
has just begun.
Hear!
Go get 'em.
JERSEY: Catch.ARGON: Toss it.
[BOTH YELLING]
ARGON: Get it, get it!
Shoot 'em!
Nonlethal!
Well, they were
shooting at us!
Nobody touches the 'fro.
Go!
Lizzie! The Source!
VIRGINIA: Come here!
[GROANS]
Bon voyage!
Charlie!
Hurry up!
Charlie, run!
Come on out.
I said, come out!
Nailed it.
Gimme that ball,
little boy.
AUTOMATED VOICE: Malfunction.
Get outta the way,
whopper.
Over my dead body.
No!
I said
gimme that ball.
What are you doin'?
Getting out of the way.
For what?
[MAYA GRUNTS]
Her.Okay. Let's get
to the elevator.
You shot at a kid!
Young adult.
[GROANS]
Hole in one.
Berger! Berger! Let's go!
Let's... Now. Right now.
Let's get...
Hey! Eugene?
What did you call me?
No.
[IN SING-SONG VOICE]
Yoo-hoo. Eugene.
Eugene.
[GASPS]
I told you don't
call me Eugene.
Attack!
Yeah. Take that. Take that.
Do not mess with
the Berger brothers.
Are you ready?
Big Mac Attack
on the scene!
I just did that.
My hand kinda...
I'm a superhero now, right?You're great.
CHARLIE: Let's get
to the elevator.
[CHARLIE YELLS]
BERGER: No, no!
Let go of me! No!
Come here!Let go of me.
Charlie...Let's go.
Charlie.We'll press charges!
IRONS: You fought well, kid.
Now hand it over.
I'm not gonna let you
steal from my dad.
Whatever he's told you
is a lie.
Charlie, I don't know
if you've noticed,
that's kinda
your dad's thing.
Lying.
Isn't it?
He ever tell you
anything about
what happened that night
when we found
the Source?
Hmm?
He mention that
I was right there
with him?
That's me, I'm the guy
who got his face blown off
so your dad can
run around pretendin'
he's some damn hero.
Where are you goin'?
Stop running.No!
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
You're a liar!
That didn't happen!
He found it.
Humanity was given a gift
from the stars that night
and your father
stole it for himself.
No.
You don't really know
your dad, do you?
And you think
your dad's a hero?
Not if you saw
what I saw, kid.
No! No.AUTOMATED VOICE:
Generating vision.
ARGON: Bravo!
Bravo!
I never doubted
you for a second.
[LAUGHS]
All right,
now bring it down here.
And the kid.
Let's go.
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Power low.
Dang it!
I never doubted you
for a second,
not one second.
That's why you tried
to fire me yesterday,
right?
What do we do
with the rugrats?
Get rid of 'em.
What?
Murder wasn't part
of the plan, Ansel.
Give it to me.
Don't move, Irons.
Nice, huh?
Whoa, my watch!
Go!
LIZZIE: Blast it! Blast it!BERGER: Big Mac!
Gross!BERGER: Blast it!
LIZZIE: Blast it!BERGER: Big Mac!
Blast it!
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Portal connection broken.
Put your hands up!
Yeah, put your hands up!
Where's the other portal?
[ELEVATOR BELL DINGS]
Who the heck are you?
Whoa, whoa, don't shoot!
Don't shoot.
I'm just the IT guy.
I was alerted to
a security breach?
I didn't know it was
Zero Dark Thirtyin here.
Hey, what are you doing?
Stay right there!
Let me come down
'cause there's a weird echo.
So we're not shouting
at each other.
What?It's all these echoes,
it's a big space.
Okay, yeah,
there is an echo.
I've been tellin' the guy,
he's gotta work on
the acoustics.
Is that him?
Is that The Guard?
And the cell phone service
is terrible.
Well, I shouldn't say
terrible. It's not
where I want it to be.
I'm gonna work on that.Is that The Guard?
As of right now, you're not
getting the push notifications
and some of the alerts,
although sometimes people
like getting rid of 'em.
Can you hurry up?
Let's turn down
the temperature.
JACK: You guys
are freakin' me out
with these guns.
Okay, are you The Guard?
No. I'm definitely
not The Guard.
I just work for him.
I'm more of a Luigi
than a Mario.
But you need firmware
or cyber security and
I'm your Huckleberry.
Okay, then how would you
deal with DDoS malware?
Ya probably wanna hit it with
a little anti-DDoS malware.
[BLOWS RASPBERRY]
Check his purse.
What's in the fanny pack?
Can anybody say front butt?
Nothing, just
fanny pack stuff.
I mean, I got some,
you know, lip balm,
sunglasses,
hand sanitizer...
Open it.
Slowly.
Yeah, it's a fanny pack.
I mean, see?
Oh, and some gum.
He's got a gun![YELPS]
You okay? You okay?Yeah. Yes.
Stay back, stay back!Dad, we...
Listen, Charlie,
I got somethin' to tell you.
Yeah, Dad, Dad...This may come
as a shock...
Charlie, please!
I am The Guard.
Oh, my God, really?
Okay, we'll talk more
about it later.
VIRGINIA: What is that?
Get the other fanny pack!
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Power level critical.
Dang it!
The suit's outta power.
You coulda chosen anything
and you chose a fanny pack?
It's practical.
Hey, guys, we're clear.
One, two!
Go!
Okay, here's the plan.
We're gonna get
you guys to the elevator,
then I'm gonna
grab the Source,
recharge the suit.Dad...
What?A little thing
about the Source...
No, wait, Charlie,
please! Look at me.
Charlie, please tell me
they don't have the Source.
He doesn't. Yeah,
we made sure of that.
Great.Yeah.
Charlie employed
a classic diversionary
tactic.
He printed a decoy
Source and fooled
all the mercenaries.
Really?It was pretty cool.
That does sound cool.
Mr. Kincaid,
sorry to interrupt,
and I actually think
fanny packs are having
a moment right now...
Thank you.Why just the glove?
Why not the whole suit?'Cause I ran outta power.
Ya can't get the whole suit
without the power,
that's why
I just got the glove.
Okay, so who's got the Source?
I threw it in a portal.
And I kinda zapped it
and it's gone.
Portal? What do you mean,
"zapped it"?
[GROANS]
CHARLIE: No!
MAYA: Mr. Kincaid!BERGER: Mr. Kincaid!
Dad!LIZZIE: No.
[KUNGFU SOUNDS]
ARGON: Hidin' the suit
in a fanny pack, huh?[JACK GROANS]
CHARLIE: God. Dad!
Clever.
You think that it
only works for you?
You're not special.
You're not the chosen one.
The truth is,
you're the recipient
of dumb luck.
Yeah, you got the suit,
but you don't have
the swagger.
You don't think
I got swagger?
[FARTS]
Where's the Source?
I'll never tell you.
[LIZZIE SCREAMING]
It's at school
in my locker!
Berger!Grab the kid.
Let's get outta here.
I'm changin'
the access codes.
Come on!
LIZZIE: No, leave him alone!MAYA: Berger!
Dad?
[GROANING]
Dad!
[EXHALES]
Swagger, damn.
What does he know
about swagger?
Ya know what,
set the nano bombs.
And give us enough time
to clear the blast area.
Uh-huh.
Did you just graze me?
Yeah.Don't graze me, bro.
[ELEVATOR DINGS]
Can I get the phone?Uh-huh.
Set one up
in the elevator.
I'll set up the timer.
Sorry, buddy.
Argon, no!
JERSEY: Argon, you're like
a father to me!No witnesses.
[EXPLOSION]Charlie!
What's goin' on?
What's happening?Thank God you're okay.
Charlie, what's happening?Dad, Dad...
Here's the deal,
here's the deal.
This whole frickin' place is
rigged with bombs, all right?
We got five minutes
to get outta here,
save Berger,
and get the Source.
I can't believe
you took the Source
to school.
No time for parenting, Dad!
How do we get outta here?
There's an escape hatch
above the gym.
Not an option.
System's locked down.JACK: What?
IRONS: Argon changed
all these access codes.
Everything is encrypted now.
Dad, Dad, Dad,
you stay here.No.
Dad, you stay here.
Blue Eyes, fix him up.
The name's
Captain Sean Irons.Shh. Zip it.
Lizzie, you crack the code
so we can get access
to the system.
Maya and I will print
enough jetpacks for all
of us, all right?
We will?I trust you.
Do you trust me?
I do now.
Here you go.
[BEEPING]
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
What did Captain Blue Eyes
back there just say?AUTOMATED VOICE:
All systems locked.
He said Argon locked
the whole system.
The escape hatch,
the printer,
everything.
If we don't crack this code
we're all gonna die.
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Access denied.Speakin' of Argon...
You know, for the record,
I don't have
a stuttering problem.
Ya know, I was
just nervous and see,
see, what happened...
What are you?
Hey. Hey.
What are you doin'?
Need to cauterize
this wound.
For a second there,
I thought you were
gonna kill me.
Yeah, I still might.
[GROANS]
It's a four-digit password,
only 10,000 combinations.
Only 10,000?
Look, Lizzie, I understand
you're really good at
the escape room stuff
but I don't see any clues.
We don't need a clue, Big Mac.
We're gonna brute-force
this password.
You're gonna
brute-force 10,000
different combinations.
Yes, I have a plan.We're gonna die.
I need to borrow this.
CHARLIE: Hurry up! We don't
have that much time.
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Error printing.
[BOTH GRUNTING]
So why are you
helpin' me now?
Let's just say I know
what the stakes are now.
You had a vision, didn't you?
Not everyone gets one.
What'd you see?
It's more powerful
than I realized.
I got this.
Code denied.
Now you understand
why it needed
to be protected.
I don't see
why you assume
you're the only one
worthy of
protecting it, though.
Wanna know what
my last ten years
have been?
Marriage: Over.
Kid: Hates me.
But I didn't
have a choice.You did.
You chose to
keep it for yourself.
MAYA: Charlie, move!
Lizzie!
Wait! That was
not part of the plan!
Lizzie!Lizzie, get us
out of here!
Speakin' of plans, do you
think we like maybe
need to reevaluate our...
No! We're all gonna go
to the dance and we're all
gonna have a great time!
MAYA: Lizzie, come on![SCREAMS]
Oh, no.No.
We're getting crushed!
Oh, my God,
they're getting crushed!
Help! Lizzie!
Maya, I gotta
tell you somethin'.
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Platform has reached
maximum capacity.
Wait. Wait,
what does that mean?
Commencing vaporization
procedure.
Only 100 more combos, Lizzie.
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Denied. Denied. Denied.
I really like you.
Like "like-like" you.
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Reducing volume in 15 seconds.
Like... Like a lot! Fifteen, 14, 13,
12, 11,
ten, nine, eight...You got this.
...seven, six, five...And I'm...
...four, three, two, one.
Code accepted.So sorry.
I got it!
Yes! Yes!Yes! Yes!
Sorry.
MAYA: What?
I'm sorry.
Boys pick the weirdest times
to be vulnerable.
Let's go print
those jetpacks.
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Jet pack printing three
of six complete.
[BEEPING]
Big Mac, listen to me.
We gotta go now.
Come here.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.Hold on.
[BIG MAC YELLING]
We gotta double up.
Wait, what about my dad?Go, go, go! I'm fine.
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Destruction imminent.
Well, I guess you gotta
learn to share now.
Bring it in.
Get in here.
[JACK YELLING]
JACK: Whoa, whoa.
Watch out for the tree! No.
[IMPACT GRUNTS]
LIZZIE: Oh, my God!
Oh, my God!
That was crazy!We just flew.
Thank you.Nice job, Angry Guy.
But we've gotta
get to school.
You should leave
the kids with me,
they'll slow you down.
No!No!
Berger's my best friend.He's my little brother.
We're going with you,
Mr. Kincaid.
[HELICOPTER HOVERING]
I'm not the only one
lookin' for ya.
You guys go.
I'll slow 'em down.
Yeah, the world
needs The Guard, Jack.
And you're the least
bad option.
Thanks.You're not gonna...
I know you're not,
I don't have to say this,
but you're not gonna
tell 'em who The Guard is
or anything...
We'll see.Gotcha, man, okay.
All right, you guys get
the heck outta here.
Stop that maniac,
all right?
CHARLIE: Let's go!MAYA: Let's go get Berger!
Sorry about
your man cave, Dad.
Yeah. Adios.Ten years
down the drain.
Well, it's not my fault
a militia showed up to...
There's two schools
of thought on that....steal your magic ball.
Well, whose is it?
Hey, if you would've
just told me the truth
about who you are,
I would have never
figured it out!
So actually,
it's your fault.
JACK: Really?CHARLIE: Yeah.
Well, we'll have plenty
o' time to discuss
whose fault it is.
ARGON: Let's go!BERGER: Okay, okay,
take it easy, man!
Dude, you are so slow.
Mom's right.
You're always deflecting,
putting up walls.
What? She says that?Yeah.
I disagree.
I don't put up walls
and I don't deflect.
See? Deflection.
What are you
talking about?It's deflecting.
That's not deflecting,
that's disagreeing.That's...
No, that's deflecting.
No, that's not.Why can't you just
be honest with me?
If you wanna know anything,
go ahead, ask me.
I'll tell you the truth.
Why does this thing
not have cup holders?Have you ever been to space?
Where do superheroes pee?
Like, in the suit?
That's for Charlie, okay?
Enough from
the peanut gallery.
Okay, uh...
Why'd you and Mom
split up?
That's your first question?
[SIGHS]
Not something
about the jetpacks
or something?
No. Uh-uh.No chance?
Look, Charlie,
that's a... It's...
That's a big question
and it's...
I think it's hard
to understand.
I didn't wanna
have to choose
between saving the world
and my family.
But I didn't have
a choice.
ARGON: Dude, pick up the pace,
for crying out loud!Settle down.
ANSEL: Is this your locker?BERGER: This is my locker.
Plus, how am I supposed
to say to my son,
"Oh, by the way,
some alien power source
"chose me to be
the guardian of
the planet"? Right?
I mean, would your
parents tell you that?No.
JACK: No, because
it makes you
sound crazy, right?
Yes.
I get it. You have this
super-powerful thing,
and you didn't know
who you could trust.
I just thought
you could trust me.
So who's excited
for the Moon Dance?
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
Where is it?I don't know.
TEACHER: Mr. Berger.Oh, hey.
Hmm. And who might you be?
I'm, uh...
I'm Berger's uncle.
Huh.
ARGON: Yeah.Nice costume.
Yeah, thank you.
I love The Guard
and this is, uh...
This is his costume.
Ooh, yeah, it's makeup.
It's kinda sensitive.
Hey, something is missing
from Berger's locker.
Would you happen to
know where it is?
I'm assuming
it's the art project?Yes.
Yes! Yeah, it's mine.Yes! His art project
BERGER: Uh-huh.Well, Jerry, the janitor,
found it glowing
in your locker.
You're lucky I didn't
call the bomb squad.
Oh, I'm glad you didn't.
And, uh, would you know
where it is,
by any chance?
I'll go get it.Cool.
Stay right here.I'm gonna stay right here.
Right here. Okay.Okay.
[BRAKES SCREECH]
JACK:
You kids stay in the car.
Where do I go?
Wait, you've never been
to your kid's school?
No, I've...
It's been a while.
All right, how 'bout
we crash through
the skylights?
Yeah, just like the time
you saved those diplomats
in Caracas...
I know, but I had
a fully charged suit then,
and how do you
know about that?
I'm The Guard's
number-one fan, dude!
I even defended you
on Reddit.
That was you?That was me.
Well, thank you.
That was pretty good.
Okay, so where do I go?
Mr. Kincaid, take these.
And, Charlie, you're gonna
call him on the phone
and tell him
where to go, okay?
All right.Okay, stay in the car.
CHARLIE: That's good.Goin' right past
the French class.
No, take a left,
take a left, not right.
You see a trophy case?
I see the trophy case.
Just keep walking by it,
all right?
You're almost there.
Past the trophy case
and you're gonna look
on your right
and it should be
glowing, I think.
Here's you with
the rest of the Bluejays.
Eagles, Dad.
Are Eagles blue?
I guess. Just keep going,
all right? Next question.
Are you even listening to me?
"Best Effort." Dad, hello?
That's great.
If she doesn't find it...
I'm gonna kill you.
Fudge my life.I am so serious
right now.
TEACHER: Just a second.
[GRUNTS]
Assuming this is it?
Yeah, that's my favorite
sculpture of his.
Uh-huh.
Well...
I really don't like
modern art.
It's hard to tell
the authentics
from the fakes!
Run, Berger, run!
No.
I don't like you!I don't like you!
I don't like you!
[WHISTLE BLOWS][BERGER SCREAMING]
I see 'em!What's happening?
I just heard Berger scream.
I think they're goin'
to the gym.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Excuse me! Oh, sorry.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
Hot potato. Hot potato.
[HIP-HOP MUSIC PLAYING]
Hey.Get outta my face!
[GRUNTS]
Sick costume, bro.
You remind me of a fart.
How do you
turn this thing on?
[EXCLAIMING]
[SCREAMS]
Give it to me!
[GROANS]
[ALL EXCLAIMING]
JACK: Argon!
Ugh!
Just wanted to
let you know
we're alive!
ARGON:
Not like I care!
You wanna dance?
Daddy wants to dance!
Let's dance.
[GROANS][ALL EXCLAIMING]
ARGON: Come on!
Hey, buddy!
[GRUNTS]
Whoo!
Dad? Dad, are you there? Dad?
Dad? Dad?
Wash your mouth out!
Berger! Throw me the Source!
Berger!Sweep!
Throw it! Throw it!
We gotta help him.
We gotta go!
No, he said
stay in the car.Yeah.
He definitely said
stay in the car.
Then we'll stay in the car.
Shotgun!
What are you doing?
Why are you
in the driver's seat?
Okay.You can't drive, Charlie.
[GROANS]
Man. That suit
sure does work.
Wait, wait.
Why don't you
take it off?
Let's fight mano-a-mano.
What, are ya stupid?
I'd rather fight
like a superhero.
Bein' a hero's
about more than
wearin' a suit.
Nah, it's all
about the suit.
Maya, do something!
What do you mean,
do something?Maya!
LIZZIE:
Press all the buttons!
Try all of them, Maya!
Now.
You're gonna
hit the wall, Charlie!
[GASPS]
[ALL SCREAMING]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[MAYA CHUCKLES EXCITEDLY]
Holy crap!
Not bad for an IT guy.
Thanks for
not listening to me.
Keep this safe.
Charlie. I trust you.
He went that way.
Dad!
Show him some swagger.
Berger!BERGER: Guys!
I'm so happy
to see you guys.MAYA: You're okay.
You know somethin', Argon?Yeah, what's that?
You might have a point
about the suit.
Hey, no!
[GRUNTS]
Bet you didn't know
how to finger blast!
I invented finger blasting.
You wanna dance with
the King of Pop?
I can dance!
I can dance...
Hold on!
Hold it! Hold it!
Hold it. I said
hold it, man!
I said...
[WHEEZING]
How do you do this?
How do you do it?
How do you take...
[EXHALES]
These things are warm.Yeah.
So hot.
They're so hot.
You got the winter suit.
[PANTING]
[WHEEZING]
I have this
trained on you.
Stand back!
I feel like a dog,
you know?Come on, let's go.
Come on. Yeah.You know, how dogs
do that? Like...
Argon, come on.Sorry.
We gotta finish this.
You ready?Yeah.
Wait, wait, I just
dropped something.
[GRUNTS]
Have another sip!
ARGON: My ear! Not my ear.
You hit me
right in the lobe!
[ARGON GROANS]
I hate you!
[SCREAMING]
Swagger!
Argon to the
principal's office!
Yes!
You just broke
my kid's trophy.
What? That's not
a real trophy.
Steal the suit,
blow up my man cave,
but don't ever
insult my son.
You're right, you're right.
I went too far.
[JACK GROANS]
Charlie! Charlie...
I lost him.
Throw me the Source.
Here.
Okay, get in the G-mobile.
Gettin' you guys outta here.Okay.
[YELLS] Dad!
Charlie! No, no!
ARGON: Get back!
Do not move!
Jack, don't be a hero!
No! Gimme the Source
or I'll kill your kid!
Okay.
ARGON: Give it to me!Okay, it's yours.
CHARLIE: What?
No, Dad, Dad. Dad...It's yours, you win.
Don't do it,
I'm only one person!
Shut up!
CHARLIE:
I'm only one person!
You're saving the world!
All right?Okay. Charlie,
Charlie, don't worry.
HBT. HBT.
HBT?
Give it to me!
CHARLIE: HBT. HBT.Okay. Please. Please.
[YELLS]
[BEEPING]
Strike three...
Charlie!
Charlie! Come on, buddy.
Come on, buddy.
Charlie!
Please? Please? Charlie.
Come on. Come on.
Charlie!
It's okay. It's gonna
be all right.
Charlie?Yeah?
Charlie?
Yeah. Can you see me?
Did Maya see that throw?
Are you kidding me?
How could she miss it?
It's one of the greatest
throws ever!
My son's a hero.
That's it.
I love you so much.
I'm so sorry
I wasted all that time.
The truth is
I did have a choice.
And I made the wrong one.
Dad?Yeah?
You're suffocating me.
Nice throw, Charlie.
Thanks.
Oh, my God
I gotta call Mom.
Jack, I know where
I'm going. I've been
to the school before.
Okay, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, I got lost earlier,
so I was just tryin' to
save you time.
It can get really confusing.[GASPS]
Charlie? Charlie,
my sweet boy!
Oh, my God, are you okay?
Are you...
What happened?
Well, we had the talk,
and it went, I think,
pretty well. It...
I mean, there was
a few bumps, but...
Wait, you knew?
And you didn't
tell me?
We wanted to wait
till you were older,
Charlie.
No, that Dad
wears a fanny pack?
JACK: He's been hammerin'
this fanny pack.
Actually, the fanny pack
was my design.
Now what are you gonna say?
We can talk about this
at home. Come on.
Uh, wait, wait. Um...
I, uh...
Hold on a second.
There's somethin'
I gotta do first.
I know that, technically,
you, um, have a date already,
but since Robbie Fernandez ran
away like a whiny little baby,
I was wondering...
Do you wanna dance?
Okay, Kincaid,
I'll try not to
breathe on you.
[BLUES MUSIC PLAYING]
You have great taste.Whoa! Thanks.
What are you
still doing here?
A DJ never
abandons her booth.
Might I have
this dance, mon cheri?
Yeah.
Should we maybe dance?
For old times' sake?
I mean, we don't wanna
just watch and make them
uncomfortable.
Okay.
Oh.
JK.
[SQUEALS]
[JAZZ MUSIC PLAYING]
They grow up fast,
don't they?
Maybe a little too fast?Yeah.
Remember our first kiss?
No.
It's 'cause we
haven't kissed yet.
Yes.Not until we're married.
Okay.How's my breath?
Amazing.
JACK: Okay, I think
we're gettin' close here!
You know how I like it?Oh, yeah.
Burnt to a crisp
and loaded up with spicy
mustard and lots of onions.
Does your girlfriend
like onions, by the way?
Okay, what? No. Dad.
[BEEPING]
We're needed.
What?Let's go.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
We gotta pack up,
and what do you
say we, uh...
[CAR UNLOCKING BEEP]...take the new one?
AUTOMATED VOICE: Uncloaking.
Wow.
Let's call it
an early birthday present.
Thanks. Can I drive?
It's a very early
birthday present.
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Welcome, Guardians.
Oh, my God!
This is the new
G-mobile, isn't it?
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Wait, wait, wait.
Now it's the new
G-mobile. Come on!
This is sick!
Watch this, watch this,
watch this.Yeah?
Hey, guys. Captain Irons,
Mission Control.
You ready for
your next mission?
Okay, Captain,
accept new mission.
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Propulsion drive activated.
Mind blown!
[HEYBB!PLAYING]
ARGON: Hello?
What is this place?
Anybody?
I'm really,
really warm.
I got swamp butt,
you know what that means?
That means the sweat
from my back's
goin' to my butt.
And it's not
a good feeling.
Oh, this sucks.
I'm sorry I tried
to take over the world.
I just need
a little help.
[RACY MUSIC PLAYING]
Guys, I can hear you.
Sounds like you guys
are leaving!
Guys, don't leave!
I really need to use
the restroom, guys!
I've been needing
to for a long time!
Help me out!
Come on, guys.