[music playing]
[ominous music]
[movie reel whirring]
(SHOUTING) Police!
Stop!
[grunts]
Drop it, or die.
OK, OK, I got you.
I got you.
Get your hands on your head.
You good, Jeremy?
Yeah, I'm good.
Lucky for him, you
came when you did.
He's all yours, so
is the paperwork.
Next time, I'll just
let you have the collar.
Life's all about choices.
Hey, you use my
words against me.
Hey, yo, would you
really have shot me?
Always ready.
Always there.
What does that even mean?
[grunts]
Use your imagination.
Hey, yo, would she
really have shot me?
Not my sister's keeper.
You got the right
to shut the hell up.
Now let's get to step up.
[music playing]
Hi, chief.
Hi.
Nice collar on that
carjacker last week, Forest.
Thank you, sir.
You're welcome.
You should have let
me have that collar.
Choices.
Ooh.
[chuckles] So are
you going to the bar?
First round's on me.
I think I'm going to
head home, grab a six.
Mm.
Drop it, or die--
[laughs] what was that?
[laughs] You like that?
I did.
I liked it.
It's all yours.
OK.
Ooh.
I think I'm going
to play the number.
Sucker.
[chuckles] Say that when
I'm sipping drinks in Maui.
Hope you take better deodorant.
Ha, she's kidding.
Whatever you say.
Hey, what isle is the deodorant?
First isle.
Mm.
[chuckles] I'm a police officer.
How nice for you.
And what do you do?
I work at the DA's office.
Oh, that kind of makes us,
like, colleagues, right,
co-workers a little bit.
Yeah.
OK.
Give me a pack of lamb skins.
Extra large.
It isn't Christmas.
Check your research.
Jesus was born in August.
We're closed.
I just need to get--
Closed.
OK, wrong store.
Yeah.
Hurry up!
Buckle up!
Hurry the fuck up.
OK.
It isn't my money.
You got that right.
Don't forget the lamb skins.
Want a receipt, too?
Do you want to keep both eyes?
Police!
Drop it, or die.
[music playing]
[gunshots]
Oh.
Come on, mother fucker.
[gunshots]
[grunting, screaming]
[groaning]
Megan?
I'm good.
I'm OK, too.
Drop your weapon now!
Hey!
Just wait.
We're cops!
[gunshot]
Oh, my god.
Oh, god.
[grunts]
Oh, oh.
Call 911.
Oh, my god.
Stay there.
You're not going to die.
Stay with me.
Come on.
Oh, god.
I thought he was going to shoot.
[sniffing] Come on.
Come on.
Stay with me.
Stay with me!
Come on.
Push.
You're OK.
I'm so sorry.
[crying] Oh, my god.
Oh, my God.
[gunshots]
I'm Olivia Dahlly, and I'm
running for re-election
as your representative
in Congress.
You know where I
stand on the issues.
Together, we can
make a difference.
[gunfire]
Welcome back to the
Justice Jenny Show.
Crime is on the rise
in America, but it
is our Second Amendment rights
that are under assault. I am--
Turn this off, will you?
You don't like what
she has to say?
--and stand--
I come here for booze, not news.
I like what she has to say.
I keep a cannon under my bar.
It's kind of early, isn't it?
What did you do, put out an APB?
No.
Found you all by myself.
You should be a detective.
You should check your messages.
I'm busy.
So I see.
It's a nice place.
At least no cops come here.
So Russet says you can come
back to work whenever you want.
She turned your resignation
into a leave of absence.
You're killing my buzz.
I seriously doubt that.
OK, have you-- have you spoken
to anyone, a priest or--
A shrink.
I was going to say, your father?
(WHISPERING) my father-- no,
I've not spoken to my father.
Why not?
Because he's a cop, like you.
I'm your partner.
Not any more, you're not.
Then I'm your friend.
Look, either way, I'm
worried about you.
Don't be.
I'm old enough to
take care of myself.
right, Billy?
Yeah, I [inaudible] myself.
Look, I'm going camping this
weekend with a few friends.
You should tag along.
It'll do you some good to
get you out of the city.
Friends with badges?
Civilians.
He teaches high school,
and she's a social worker.
Kumbaya.
They're good people.
You'd like them if you
just give them a chance.
Call me if you want to go, or
even if you just want to talk.
Hey, I'm still your rabbi.
Don't drink too much.
[gunshot]
Hey.
Good morning.
Megan, Blake and Gabriella.
It's nice to finally meet you.
Same here.
Jeremy talks about you all
the time
I bet.
Couldn't have left the
work clothes at home?
Come on.
Hey, once a cop, always a cop.
That's what you think.
[grunts] All right, say
goodbye to all the bad guys.
I already have.
[fast-paced music]
They've been in there
all night, doing
the devil's work, no doubt.
All right, gather around.
Everyone stay alert.
These are bad hombres.
Barry, you stay here.
If we get in over our
heads, sound the horn.
No smokies.
Right, Preach.
Bow your heads.
Dear Lord, protect us
from evil and give us
strength in our war against
your earthly enemies.
Amen.
Everybody comes home, got it?
Got it.
Let's roll.
[suspenseful music]
On you, long night.
Well, you going to be
bitching we unload this shit.
I ain't bitching, just tired.
We'll get some sleep when
we're done because we're
going to Philly tonight.
I ain't driving.
Hector can drive.
I like to drive.
All this hard work
is about to pay off.
[garage door opening]
Baby, are you
coming to bed soon?
How many times I got
to tell you to knock?
We almost smoked your ass.
Are you coming to bed?
Can't you see I'm working here?
You're always working.
Well, that's because
I'm a businessman.
Go back to your
horse, or something.
I'll be in when I'm ready.
[scoffs]
That bitch can't get
enough of my stuff.
[laughs]
What are you laughing at?
You're supposed to be standing
guard outside, eagle eye.
[man speaks spanish]
[music playing]
Beautiful, isn't it?
I love the mountains.
Those are hills, city girl.
[chuckles] Like you'd know.
Tell her, Blake.
They're mountains.
You teach history,
not geography.
Well, the study of
mountains is orology.
Whatever.
You just made that up.
Hills, mountains--
it's all God's country.
[suspenseful music]
Don't move, chico.
Throw your gun on the ground.
Get down.
Drop it, pigs.
[gunshots]
Gun!
[rapid gunfire]
Shit!
[grunting]
Eduardo Sanchez?
Sure, why not.
You came to the
wrong county, ese.
Smell that?
Smell that fresh air?
[laughs]
This isn't exactly a
designated campsite.
Oh, you don't get
the full experience
at those designated campsites.
We're going to rough it
out in the wilderness.
What if the wilderness
is private property?
It's Gods country, remember?
Yeah.
Do you think it's safe to leave
your wheels here like this?
I think so.
Cooked right under our noses.
This is worth a
fortune on the streets.
We're not the animals.
We found $80,000 in the house.
You know where to put that.
Wait, where's your warrant?
I don't like warrants.
They leave a paper trail.
Well, now I want a lawyer, man.
That's not how we
do things here.
I know my rights.
See if I care about your rights.
What about this evidence?
Burn it.
[fire crackling]
Ah.
That was good, Blake.
Gabby, now I see
why you married him.
[laughter]
Thanks.
When are you joining the team?
Me?
Oh, no time soon.
I'm still in my prime.
Who's going to want
you when you aren't?
That's a long way off from now.
What about you, Megan?
My only plan is
to go for a hike.
Want company?
No, thanks.
I'm going to try to
find some of that peace
and solitude I keep
hearing so much about.
Enjoy.
Hey, don't get lost.
Are you sure she's OK?
Got to take the social
worker out of the city.
Yeah, she's good, just
needs a moment to unwind.
I'll talk to her in a few.
[music playing]
[birds squawking, chirping]
Hey, wait up.
Are you tailing me?
No.
Blake and Gabriella
wanted some alone time.
Mm.
I guess I'm some stuck with you.
Ooh, I'm feeling the love.
Thanks for inviting me.
You were right.
I needed to get out.
The job was getting to
me before the shooting,
and the city was
getting to me all along.
Yeah.
They both can do that.
Maybe I should move out here,
get a cabin, or like a teepee.
[chuckling]
Somehow, I don't think
that that's a good idea.
I need to do something.
I wish you'd
reconsider resigning.
I miss you in the streets.
And the truth comes out.
[chuckles]
Chief.
[spade digging in the ground]
Just let me go.
[spade digging]
Come on, just let me go.
[ominous music]
Where are you from, Eduardo?
Colombia, Mexico?
Try the Bronx.
I'm as American as you.
I guess that depends
on your point of view.
This ain't right, man.
Keep digging.
What the hell?
You know, I can't be the only
one cooking meth around here.
Are you working for someone?
Maybe we can do some business.
We don't work for
drug traffickers.
They attract too much
federal attention.
Did you bring your
off-duty weapon?
It's back in the car.
Listen, if you want
me gone, I'm gone.
Just let me go.
Sorry.
Too much went down
this morning, amigo.
What, do you mean them?
Listen, I didn't see anything,
so I can't be a witness.
So just let me go.
Sorry, I can't do
that, Sancho Panza.
All right.
Then dig your own damn grave.
This man just threatened
my life with that shovel?
[ominous music]
This is bull--
[gunshots]
Hey.
Where the hell did
you two come from?
[grunts]
Barnes!
Double time.
[tense music]
Barnes?
Get those fuckers.
Barry, you help me get
him to the vehicle.
Rest of you know what to do.
[grunting, heavy breathing]
This way.
No, no, no.
I don't want to lead
them to the camp.
Come on.
Oh, whoa.
What's going on?
Guys, we need to get the
hell out of here right now.
Were those gunshots?
Leave everything behind.
What are you doing with that?
Go.
Hey, come on!
We can't explain--
Here, you lead the way.
I got the rear.
[grunting]
What do you want
me to tell the ER?
Nothing.
Leave that to me.
[vomiting]
I bet he's got a concussion.
We lost them.
There's only one
road out of here.
Down.
[car engine roaring]
What's going on?
Everybody in.
What the hell is going on?
We just witnessed the homicide.
Why did you flag
down those cops?
Because they're the killers.
They're after us because
we saw what they did.
What did they kill?
An unarmed man, with
three other bodies.
Jeremy, Jeremy, Jeremy-- dammit.
[gunshots]
They're coming your way.
My gun's underneath the seat.
I don't see any extra ammo.
This was supposed to
be a quiet weekend.
Shit, shit, shit!
[gunshots]
Come on.
Everybody out!
Let's go!
Come on!
This way!
Damn them to hell.
They're using the
trees for cover.
Do you want to us
to go after them?
They have Barnes's gun.
It's too easy to
ambush us going uphill.
We don't catch them
before nightfall,
we'll never get them.
Call up the reserves.
Tell Barry we need food
and water for an army.
On it.
Hey, Preach, you better come
back here and look at this.
Just what we need.
[grunting, heavy breathing]
Did we lose them?
They know I have this gun.
By now, they know I'm a cop.
That's good, right?
It doesn't make a difference.
Look, I know I said, no phones.
But did anybody break the rules?
Really, guys?
What the fuck?
No service.
We just got to talk to
them, make them understand.
Understand what?
We just witnessed
them commit a murder.
They're never going to
let us out of here alive.
You don't know that.
You don't know what
those people did.
They were drug dealers, OK?
It doesn't matter.
They were executed.
[siren wailing]
What's that?
Fire horn.
Oh.
It's a call to arms.
They're bringing
in reinforcements.
Oh, no.
Look, when there's
enough of them,
they're going to surround us.
We got to try to make
it difficult for them.
Why couldn't you two just
have minded your own business?
Look what you've gotten us into?
We didn't do anything, just
wrong place at the wrong time.
OK, so what can we do?
We're going to split up.
What?
She's right.
We have to split
up into two teams
and head in
different directions.
Then we can double our
chances of getting away.
Wait, wait.
Why two teams?
By your reasoning, we'd
do better splitting up
as four individuals.
Two guns, two teams.
Blake, you go with Meg.
Gabby, you go with me?
No.
You can't expect us
to leave each other.
Have you ever fired a
weapon in your life?
I don't suppose
video games count.
How about you?
There's nothing to debate.
Try to stay parallel to the
road so you don't get lost.
I'm not leaving without you.
Honey, they're right.
This is our best chance, OK?
Look-- Look at me.
We need to go right now.
Like I said, thanks for
the invite, partner.
When we get back home,
first round's on me.
You're on.
Hey, be all you can be.
He's been with [? nicole ?]
City PD for 10 years.
A month ago, his partner shot
and killed a fellow officer.
She's on leave.
Maybe she's the one
that was with him.
Maybe all four of them are cops.
That took longer than
a New York minute.
Not by much, it didn't.
You could be damn sure
we were locked and loaded
inside 60 seconds.
I don't know which
is twat out here.
What's the big emergency?
I'll give you the rundown
when everybody's here.
[fast-paced music]
The Latinos running this farm
were using it as a meth lab.
They opened fire
on me and my men,
and we did what any one
of you would have done.
We don't need the
feds or the media
sticking their noses
in our business.
Unfortunately, we were seen.
Seen by who?
Outsiders, two
men and two women.
One of them is Black.
They're hiding in the
green, and they're armed.
Look what they did
to poor Barnes.
We didn't know if he was
going to pull through.
I don't have to tell you what
will happen if they make it out
of here.
It's not just me and my men
whose necks are on the line
here.
It's our whole way of life.
Either we handle this now, or
we start the damn revolution
when the feds move in.
Revolution sounds good to me.
We're not ready for
that yet, Vernon.
Were supposed to be
preparing the next generation
for a war they can
win.
Do you expect us to kill
these people for free?
The council is offering ten
grand in cash for each target.
Shit.
You don't have to pay me.
I'll hunt these
motherfuckers for free.
Shut up, Darcy.
We ain't doing
this shit for free.
Cocksucker.
Blue team will run
this command post.
Block the main road, and
coordinate all activity.
Our Minutemen will be red team.
We're the only team you need.
Yeah, we are.
Our militia will be green team.
We'll get those four for you.
You got that shit right.
Not if we bag them we'll you're
all having a pissing contest.
Our Betsies will
be the orange team.
At least you didn't
make us pink.
I'd never make that
mistake, Annie.
At least I don't
piss standing up.
No, you do it on all fours.
You want to go a few rounds?
I bet you'd like that.
You're playing for
the wrong team.
Save it for the enemy, ladies.
We know these woods
better than any of you.
Oh, I didn't see
you arrive, Cletus.
Because we didn't want
you to know we were here.
Sister fuckers.
What did you say?
Oh, we're just admiring
your outfit, Claudette.
It better be I you're admiring.
Oh, relax.
We know you're
with your brother.
Come again?
Sorry, Cletus.
I meant to say, cousin.
You girls watch yourself.
We want to be shadow team.
That's fine, Wade.
The Wagners will be shadow team.
Our targets are
outnumbered and outgunned.
We have to find
them before dark,
promised my wife I'd
be home for dinner.
Yeah, I told mine
the same thing.
[laughter]
Leave your beer behind.
I don't want you shooting
each other by mistake.
Bring them back warm if you can,
but cold suits me just fine.
Good luck, and good hunting.
Make no mistake, this is war,
maybe not the one we wanted,
but the one that
landed in our backyard.
How do you plan on
explaining all this away?
We won't have to.
These people were never here.
We just have to
cover our tracks.
Sounds like bullshit to me!
Dead or alive!
[ominous music]
They have all the fun.
You forgot to mention one
of our targets is a cop.
I didn't forget anything.
Remember, the Firearms League
is honoring you on Tuesday.
I'm so sick of those
Rust Belt luncheons.
Are you sick of the
press they generate?
Dust off my usual speech.
You got it.
[cell phone buzzing]
I told you, never
call me on this line
unless it's an emergency.
We have a situation.
Pull over.
Get out.
Excuse me?
You heard me.
Wait on the curb.
Lay it on me.
[helicopter whirring]
Down!
We should be out there
waiving our arms.
No one good is looking for us.
Keep it together, Gabby!
[sobbing]
You good?
I think so.
Let's go.
Green team to blue command.
Go ahead, green team.
Found their campsite
and a couple of IDs.
We got a high school
teacher and a social worker.
Bunch of damn do-gooders.
Good work.
Torch everything.
One cop, two civilians.
One question mark.
[heavy breathing]
Oh, no.
[ominous music]
Keep moving.
What do you see, Caleb?
Two of them up ahead.
That's $20.
5K each.
What am I, your squire?
There's five of us.
That's 4K apiece.
Whatever you say, Mr.
high school graduate.
[grunting]
Come on.
We've got to keep going.
[heavy breathing]
I need rest.
Look, they're gaining on us!
You go on without me.
No deal.
I can't keep this up.
Here, take this.
Take it.
[grunts]
Keep both hands on the gun.
Squeeze the trigger.
Don't pull it.
You only got six shots,
so don't waste any.
Now go.
I told you I can't run anymore.
Then walk fast, but go.
What about you?
I'm going to lead
them away from you.
No.
Look, I'll circle back and catch
up as soon as I can, all right?
Now get going.
Come on.
Go.
Now these two have split up.
Then we'll split up, too.
[tense music]
[helicopter whirring]
[gunfire]
[grunting, heavy breathing]
[suspenseful music]
Stay back!
[sobbing]
Put the gun down, miss.
You don't want to hurt anyone.
You surely don't
want to kill us.
It's all a big misunderstanding.
Stay back, you redneck
sons of bitches.
I'll shoot if I have to.
No you won't.
That a girl.
Easy.
Easy now.
Don't you ever point
a gun at someone
unless you intend on using it!
[sobbing]
[heavy breathing]
[grunting]
[groaning, grunting]
[screaming]
[neck cracking]
[ominous music]
[gunshot]
[gun cocking]
[ominous music]
I call dibs on any women.
There's no calling dibs, Darcy.
I fucking call dibs anyway.
Jesus, would you stop
being a pain in my ass?
I'm sick of you given
Darcy a hard time, Coyle.
She's arguing with me.
That isn't how I see it.
Hey!
I thought we're all supposed
to be on the same fucking team!
Yeah, we ain't out here
hunting each other.
It's OK, Mojo.
We're just messing
around, right, Coyle?
Yeah, fine.
Can we please just
go make some money?
Just don't piss me off.
Fine.
Come on!
[gunshots]
Martin, Wilcox.
Don't make me shoot
you in the back.
You fucking--
[gunshots]
You-- you killed them
like they were nothing.
You better be ready
to do the same if you
want to see your wife again.
Ranger, it's Vernon.
Go for me.
Darky killed Bowen,
so Caleb killed him.
We captured a Latina.
Bitch was packing a 38.
Good job.
Bring her in.
Roger that.
We have to go back.
If we do, we'll be
killed, just like Jeremy.
How could you be so cold?
He was your friend, too.
He was more than a friend.
He was my partner, and he
would want us to keep going.
I can't leave Gabriella.
Her only chance is if
we make it out of here
and bring back help.
That could take hours, days.
Do you really believe
she'll still be alive then?
No.
Then I'm going back,
with or without you.
You don't even know
where they are.
I'll find them.
If they don't find you first.
Either way--
Nothing you do is
going to change what's
going to happen to Gabriella.
She wouldn't want you
to die for nothing.
Good luck.
You too.
[helicopter whirring]
Dragonfly, it's [? wolf ?] man.
[? go for blue, ?] wolf man.
I see you finished your blow.
They're all dead.
What?
Your survivors didn't
survive so well.
That makes six
casualties on our side.
We have to get this
bird back to base.
We only promise you one pass.
Affirmative.
Thanks for the assist.
Let God sort them out.
Amen, brother.
[distorted sighing]
[heavy breathing, grunting]
[ominous music]
[gunfire]
On the boulder!
Ma, Cletus!
Leave them be.
Can't do anything for them now.
Blood for blood.
[fast-paced music]
There she goes!
You two, after her.
Come on.
Come on, [inaudible].
[rapid gunfire]
There she goes!
Hey!
[gunshots]
[gun clicking]
[rapid gunfire]
Hey, Grizzly Adams!
[heavy breathing]
[ominous music]
What is it, Annie?
Nothing.
Let's get that bounty.
Hell, yeah.
Let's do it.
Caleb's still in the wild.
Wait outside.
When do we get our money?
When this is over.
Welcome to Eden, Gabriella.
We found your idea at your camp.
You killed Jeremy, didn't you?
Only after he killed
one of our men.
Is my husband alive?
For now.
But you can help us
bring him in safely.
I'm not helping you do shit.
You weren't even
there, were you?
There was another woman that
ran away, but it wasn't you.
The people we shot were
criminals, not embezzlers, not
tax dodgers, real bad guys.
That's none of our business.
Let us go, and I swear we'll
never say a word to anyone.
We both know better.
That's a beautiful cross.
Are you a believer?
Jesus Christ is my Savior.
That makes this more difficult.
We're a Christian community.
Christians don't commit murder.
Who's the other woman?
Tell me her name, and I'll make
this as easy for you as I can.
What difference
does her name make?
I like to know who I'm hunting.
You're police.
You're supposed
to protect people.
We protect our own people.
You're the one that
needs protection now.
[ominous music]
Oof.
[grunts]
[sobbing]
I've known you most
of your life, Barry.
I brought you into
this department
because you believe
in our cause.
Are you ready to take the next
step into a larger community?
Yes, sir.
Then send this bitch
to a better place.
[crying]
Preach?
I understand your
hesitation, son.
But it has to be done.
Shoot her in the head.
[crying]
What are you waiting for?
I'm sorry.
I just never shot anyone before.
That's what our
movement is all about,
shouldering responsibility
others are too weak to bear.
Don't listen to him, Barry.
This has nothing to
do with strength.
He's nothing without you.
She's trying to confuse you.
I'm trying to save you.
Shoot her now.
Make him do his own dirty work.
[crying]
God forgive me.
[gunshot]
Where are you?
[ominous music]
[groans]
Incoming!
Gabriella!
Blake!
Yes!
[gunshot]
Let go of me!
[screaming]
[rapid gunfire]
No!
[crying] Oh, God.
Do it.
I can't.
[gunshot]
I hope you get a chance
to redeem yourself.
Grab a shovel.
[ominous music]
You just drop that gun.
And the side arms.
Rise and shine.
[tense music]
Now turn around.
I don't know you.
I'm not from around here.
All you need to
know is that there
are people trying to kill me.
But that doesn't tell me
a whole lot now, does it?
What are you doing here?
I witnessed an execution.
Hmm.
That explains the
shooting that I
heard today, thought
it sounded livelier
than the usual tomfoolery.
Get inside.
I would feel safer
with my weapons.
Well, I'd be safer
with them out here.
Their camp was here.
She took out green team here
and is moving in this direction.
Frances is out there.
Frances won't help her.
She'll shoot anyone that
sets foot on our property.
Crazy bitches stick together.
Says the man who was drummed
out of the army on a Section 8.
Oh, you're looking
for a beat down.
Squash this.
I have enough problems
to deal with while you
two nitwits going at it.
Orange team to blue command.
Go for blue command.
Wagners are dead.
She took him out a close range.
I like her style.
So John Preacher killed
some folks today.
My god.
The fools have
finally gone too far.
I need a phone.
The radio I took won't reach
far enough to do me any good.
Yeah, well, you came
to the wrong place.
What about a car?
Oh, I just got a daughter
in town with a car.
But she only checks in
on me every few days.
It's a lovely little
town you got here.
Yeah, well, I live here
because I always have,
not for the company.
Why is everybody
following this Sheriff?
Well, I'll tell you.
You know the Revolutionary War?
Well, there was a battle that
was fought in these hills.
A handful of
farmers, Minutemen--
they held off the red coats
until the militia arrived.
Now the folks that
live around here--
well, they're descendants
of those brave souls.
So you see, tradition--
it's important to us.
It's in our blood.
That tradition include murder?
Oh, those Billy Bobs--
they're prepping for a
war against the government
that they can't possibly win.
I mean, mostly it's
just a show so they
can play with their damn guns.
They got a bunker not
very far from here,
some kind of a training camp.
I wonder if there might not be
some kind of a radio set there
that you could use
to call for help.
[car approaching]
Stay still if you
want to stay alive.
[suspenseful music]
What are you boys
doing on my property?
Now, hold on, Frances.
We don't want any trouble.
Well, get in your vehicle,
and there won't be any.
We're looking for a woman.
Try a whorehouse.
This one's dangerous.
And I'm not?
She's armed.
You don't say.
We have to look inside.
You do, and I'll shoot you.
Nobody comes inside
without an invitation.
And I'm not feeling very
hospitable right now.
This is a matter
of law, Frances.
Who's law, yours or mine?
There's only one law.
On my land, that's me.
Is she here or not?
You missed her by
20, maybe 30 minutes.
She asked for directions to the
highway, so I gave them to her.
Did she give you her name?
No, she didn't mention that.
She did say that you idiots
killed some folks today.
She killed some herself--
good men.
[laughs] There hasn't
been a good man
around here since my husband
died, God rest his soul.
Have a blessed day, Frances.
Keep your door locked
until this is over.
Hey, you go looking for judgment
day, you may just find it.
[car engine starting]
Go uphill for about a mile
till you come to a side road.
That'll take you to the
bunker that I told you about.
If I had had my
weapons just now,
I could have finished this.
Well, first of all, I
just saved your life.
And second, you're welcome.
Now get the hell out of
here before somebody else
gets killed, namely me.
Thank you.
Hey, if they pin you
down, give them hell.
Why aren't you back
at the station?
Walter said that you needed
this force woman's jacket right
away, so I ran it over myself.
That's her.
Her father was Buffalo
PD Brass, and her brother
carried a gold shield.
She's only been on
the job for two years.
A bitch and a rookie.
Nice language.
You can go now, Kayleigh.
Guess I'll go file my nails.
She served in the
National Guard,
and spent two years
in Alibaba land.
Combat?
Motor pool.
She trained for a war
she never got to fight.
So did we.
[suspenseful music]
Hello?
Fuck.
[suspenseful music]
Whatever you're
thinking, forget it.
Drop your hardware,
and raise your hands.
Nice and slow, darling.
Step forward so you're not
tempted to do anything stupid.
We can take you back with
your face or without it.
Thought most of you yahoos
around here were men.
Freedom fighters.
Domestic terrorists.
Annie, I'm tired of her mouth.
I like her mouth.
[laughs]
It isn't smart to antagonize us.
Cuff her, Jo.
With pleasure.
You don't have to do this.
You could walk away or help me.
In the name of sisterhood,
we've got 10,000 reasons
not to roll over for you.
A bounty.
3,300 apiece, not bad
for an afternoon's work.
We didn't even have
to fire a shot.
Fire!
[rapid fire]
[gunshots]
[suspenseful music]
Hey, good looking.
Why did you 86 them?
You're on the same team.
You capped those broads, not me.
Now I kill you, collect $10,000.
I've already got 10 coming to me
for killing your Black friend.
What about my other friends?
You're the last of the Mohicans.
It was boring around
here until you showed up.
Pick it up if you want to dance.
Ooh, fight back.
I like rough.
[grunting]
Ah.
[growls]
[grunting]
Body shots, huh?
[grunting, groaning]
[thudding]
[grunting]
[grunting, groaning]
[screaming]
You fucking bitch!
[gunfire]
[screaming]
[gunshots]
[breathing heavily]
Orange team, come in.
Preacher for orange team.
Come in.
Go for orange.
What's your 20?
I'm at some old training camp.
Annie?
Annie's dead, so are
the rest of them.
Some asshole with long hair
got them before I got him.
Caleb.
Turn yourself in, Megan.
There's no escaping.
[laughs]
I don't want to
escape, Preacher.
You started this.
I'm going to finish it.
I'm going to finish you.
You triggered the
wrong bitch today.
Out.
Hello?
Son of a whore.
Vernon, don't go to that camp.
It's a trap.
There's a debt to be paid
for Caleb, and I [inaudible]..
I'm in charge of this operation!
I order you to stay put!
And I thought you was
about personal freedom.
Come on, boys.
Let's go break out the big gun.
What now, Preach?
Circle the wagons.
Pull all of our other
people off the roadblocks.
Mom, Dad, I got myself
into a real jam.
And I couldn't save my friends.
I wish I could.
I'm going to take a
record of everything that
goes down today.
Before that, I want you to
know how much I love you
and how much I wish I
could see you again.
I--
[crying]
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I couldn't save them.
I just wanted to
be good for you.
I just wanted to make you proud.
But I'm going to
make things right.
If it's the last
thing I would do,
I'm going to make things right.
[car aproaching]
Padlocks off the door.
She broke in there.
[rapid gunfire]
Take over.
Keep your finger
off the trigger.
I don't want you
perforating me prematurely.
I ain't no idiot.
[ominous music]
[gunfire]
[tense music]
[screaming, gunfire]
[ominous music]
Let's go!
Hurry up!
Come on!
Let's go!
No screwing around.
We take this bitch out.
We go home.
Everyone goes home.
Let's do it.
[ominous music]
[suspenseful music]
[gasps]
[knife stabbing]
[gunfire]
[metal clanging, squelching]
[screaming]
[gunfire]
Get the hell out of here!
Do you want to get
shot in the back?
[gun clicking]
She's out of ammo.
I wouldn't count on that.
[whizzing, squelching]
[groaning]
[metal thudding]
[military music]
Oh, good god.
Here comes the crazy train.
Well, who's that?
She who must not be named.
[chuckles]
Park it somewhere safe.
Congresswoman Dahlly.
Get out.
Welcome home.
Mm.
There is no way I was
going to miss this.
Only the female cop is left.
We lost a lot of people today.
You just tell me where
to find the bitch.
[music playing]
Red team, come in.
Vernon, are you out there?
How about my strike team?
Damn it.
I think it's time
we packed it in.
Have you lost your mind?
I think we all have.
Are you going to spend
the rest of your life
in prison over one woman?
Beats being dead.
What will the council say?
Think about your family.
I am thinking about them.
Pick up, Preacher.
Are you going to
get that, or am I?
Go for me.
I handled red team and
the other deputies.
The rest of you are under
arrest for murder and accessory.
You've got 30 seconds
to lay down your arms.
You're out of your jurisdiction.
You're not even on active duty.
Call it a citizen's arrest.
How many people
did you kill today?
Ask me again when I see you.
I'm done.
Screw my pension.
You want to leave, be my guest.
Time's up.
[ominous music]
We're in the shit now.
I didn't sign up for this.
Well, man the fuck up.
Yes, ma'am.
[gunfire]
Shit.
Ah.
[gunfire]
We're going to
need a bigger gun.
[gunfire]
Walter!
Hey!
[explosion]
Hallelujah.
[gunfire]
[gunshot]
Preacher!
Drop your weapons now!
[gunshots]
[music playing]
Recognize this?
Please, I have a wife, a son.
My friends had families, too.
Jesus.
I don't even know if Blake
and Gabriella had kids.
I had a brother and
a brother-in-law
until about two minutes ago.
You have a knack
for killing lawmen.
What do you know about the law?
I know how little
a street cop makes.
I have $80,000 from
those traffickers.
It's yours if you let me go.
Give it to those
families if you want to.
Get on your feet.
Up.
Where is it?
Do we have a deal?
Show me the money first.
You have me at a disadvantage.
You got that right.
Speak now or forever
hold your peace.
It's in the glove compartment.
Keys.
You are a disgrace
to that uniform.
Take it off now!
Take it all off.
Eighty grand.
Was it worth it?
Takes money to build an army.
Did Gabriella beg for her life?
How about Blake, hmm?
Mistakes were made.
I'll give you that.
But if you pull that trigger
and shoot me in cold blood--
I'll be no better than you?
You already pushed
me over that line.
-You wanted to be pushed.
-You think you know me?
You only became a cop
because of your daddy,
but you couldn't
handle the shit.
Now you're trying to prove
you have what it takes.
You murdered my friends.
If you were going
to kill me,
you would have pulled
that trigger already.
[ominous music]
No, no, no, no, no, no.
[gunshot]
No!
I don't want to put you down.
I want to put you away.
Get your hands on your head.
I'm taking you in.
You have no idea what you're
getting yourself into.
I think I do.
You guys aren't all
that hard to figure out.
We just might surprise you.
FBI is going to love
your ass,
so is gen pop.
You don't want my
friends for enemies.
[scoffs]
They don't want me for an enemy.
You just assassinated
a Congresswoman.
I'm probably going to get
a book deal on a TV show.
You know what to do.
Tighter.
We have chapters all
over the country.
They'll find you, no
matter where you hide.
I'm not hiding.
That a girl.
Daddy would be proud.
[siren wailing]
What is that?
[laughs]
What the fuck is that?
[chuckles]
We were just the
first responders.
Do you realize how many men
there are in this county,
how many guns?
Well, it's a good thing
I have you with me.
Too bad you just killed
my hostage negotiator.
There won't be any negotiating.
You'll never get
out of here alive.
And neither will you.
We'll see.
Get moving.
[MUSIC - ARMAND JOHN
PETRI AND JOE ROZLER,
"WILL I EVER BE THE SAME?"]
(SINGING) The wind
is full of lies.
A flying bullet
cries and searches
for the mark to kill and
cool a burning flame.
Will I ever be the same?
A carnival of fools.
The master steals the jewels.
Hiding from the flame that
goes beyond another name.
The wind is blowing cold,
telling stories never told.
I'm screaming for
the final life.
Who will take the blame?
Will I ever be the same?
The wind is full of lies.
The final bullet flies,
searching for another life,
a sole, a prize to claim.
Will I ever be the same?
Searching for the truth to
tell, when will I decide?
I can never cry and hide.