Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
We're late.
Right.
Silly.
Sillier.
(Emily)
You're funny daddy.
Oohhhh (laughs).
Yes!
Thanks.
Thank you.
Em... milk.
(Blows bubbles)
Do you want cream?
It's how I take it.
Maybe you wanted to try
something different.
(Inaudible sounds from subway)
You need directions?
What?
Directions.
Um, yeah sure, where do you
need to go?
No, you just look like you need
Oh no, no... I'm good. I'm good
Thank you.
Okay!
Umm, just so you know,
Vanderbilt... Flatbush.
Thank you.
Hey Ethan, it's... me. I'm
just calling
to let you know that I'm stuck
at work,
and I'm uh, gonna be late
tonight.
So, talk to you later. Bye.
Are you following me?
Guess I am following you.
You must be Amber.
Oh... you're Logan...
...Pierce, yes
Realtor and local direction
giver
at your service.
Well, it's nice to meet you...
again.
You too. Right this way...
But if you are looking for
something
bigger, I have another place
that I think your husband
and you
would love.
Oh no... no it's, just gonna be
me... and... my daughter.
Sorry about that-
I just saw the wedding band...
You now what?
I love it... I'll take it.
Okay! Great.
Let's set up an appointment
get the paperwork done.
Perfect.
(Sound of rain falling)
Hi...
Hi.
Ethan...
I know... she's taking a nap.
I need to talk to you.
Okay...
It's important.
What?
(Typing sounds)
Ethan I'm leaving you.
(Exhales) What?
I'm sorry.
Stop.
Don't... uh..
...take another step towards me
We should talk about this.
The logistics...
...Emily.
Do not...
...do not take another step.
I'll be out by the end of
the month.
(Footsteps)
♪ Instrumental Music Plays
Dialogue inaudible ♪
(Amber and Emily chat
quietly in the background)
These things happen Gracie.
They happen all the time.
It'll be okay.
Okay?
For the better I think.
(Scoffs)
Well in time... yes.
You got all your boxes
mommy?
I got all my boxes
and I'm gonna take them
to my new house
which is going to be our
new house.
Like we talked about.
With daddy.
No... no, not with daddy.
Daddy's gonna stay in our
old house
You're gonna have
two homes now, you're
gonna have daddy's
home and mommy's home.
I don't want two homes.
I know...
I'm sad about it too.
It's okay to have sad feelings
about it.
I don't want you to go away.
I'm gonna miss you
so much babygirl.
But... when you're not with
daddy you're gonna be with me
four whole days a week.
Like a sleepover?
(laughs)
The best sleepover's ever.
I love you mommy.
I love you too.
(Footsteps approaching)
I'm gonna go now, okay?
Here we go Em-
See you in a few days.
What do you say you come
with grandpa
we'll go fix us up
some lunch. Hmm?
Um, I'll call you tomorrow.
Good morning Amber.
Hey Sol, good to see you.
How was your weekend?
Was...
...pretty uneventful.
...Right...
I was told I could find
Amber Evans here.
I'm Amber, yeah, how can
I help you?
I am presenting you with
a summons
with a notice of divorce.
That's very kind of you.
Please sign here.
(Exhales) That was quick.
Sorry.
Divorce?
Yeah (exhales).
Can we not talk about it
right now?
Of course.
Hey...
...come and find me when
you are ready.
Yeah.
♪ Music starts ♪
Can I get you anything else?
No thank you.
♪ Music continues ♪
♪ You were beautiful ♪
♪ I was beautiful ♪
♪ We made something so... ♪
♪ Your love shaped me ♪
♪ Even when my heart
was breaking ♪
♪ Now I ♪
♪ Will try ♪
♪ To become... ♪
♪ I will be... beautiful ♪
♪ You will be... beautiful ♪
♪ We will be... ♪
♪ If we walk away now ♪
♪♪♪ (instrumental music) ♪♪♪
Hey...
Hey! (laughs)
What are you doing here?
Aside from buying a stash
of wine?
No, no I mean in this
neighborhood.
Oh! I live up the street.
Really?
Well yeah for now.
So are you settling in okay?
Slowly... yeah.
Well it was really great
running into you.
Yeah.
Really great.
Is that everything?
Yes thank you.
I'd actually like to buy
you a housewarming gift.
Oh no no you don't have
to do that.
Oh, I just did.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
But it... wouldn't be much of a
housewarming without people.
I suppose not.
You think you can make it?
Sure.
And by that I mean tonight,
like now.
Oh...
Well I gotta check my schedule..
Great! Looks like I'm free.
(both laugh)
Great.
Hi.
She's asleep?
Yeah, she couldn't keep her
eyes open.
Okay, let me get this for you.
Thank you.
Alright bye.
Bye.
Umm, I'm just going to be
one second.
Okay.
Sorry that it's so dark,
my ceiling lights are
still out.
Oh, I can call the guy for you.
Oh no no... no. That's
not...
Are you sure?
Okay.
Well I love what you've
done with the place.
Thanks! Yeah, got some...
you know...
...you're messing with me.
No I love it, the boxes add
the boxes add this
'je ne sias quoi'
DIY chic
(both laugh)
Work in progress right?
Like me.
Like everyone.
So... what do you like to do?
...for fun.
(laughs)
Uhhh....
What do you love?
I... um...
I don't think that I've ever
really...
You know, I went to being a
kid to having a kid...
...and then I... out of my
parents house, into
Ethan's house. I'm a mom,
I work, you know I just...
I don't really...
feel like I know the answer
to that.
That's okay.
It's kind of exciting you know?
Cuz' now you get to figure it
out.
Here's to figuring it out.
Look you know, I don't
really know you.
And I don't know what
happened but -
It sounds like it's something
that you really needed to do.
And... not everybody does
that.
I think it's brave.
Brave.
So what about you? I mean
you're
you're a realtor, you live
temporarily in this neighborhood
Well, I uh
I don't have to just talk
about it
I can show you.
If you're free
on Thursday night.
you can meet me here.
I can do Thursday.
Cool.
♪ Faint sound of music playing
from inside ♪
♪ Music plays ♪
♪ I will be shatterproof ♪
♪ I'll stand up and spring
back like you ♪
Hi.
Do you have a reservation?
No, Logan told me to stop by.
Oh, are you Amber Evans?
Yeah, yeah.
She has a table set aside for
you right there.
Okay, thank you.
You're welcome!
♪ Live on in me ♪
♪ In me ♪
(cheering and applause)
Thank you guys.
Thanks for coming out tonight.
I'm taking requests.
Travellers!
Amazing Day!
Uh...
Umm, you know what? Nevermind...
I got it, I know what I
wanna do
uhh, it's an old song
but it'll be new to you
and it's one of my favorites
and it's called
Hold On.
♪ Guitar plays ♪
♪ I know you're coming ♪
♪ I can see down the road ♪
♪ I'm travelling but I'm
not alone ♪
♪ Love is calling ♪
♪ Over the rolling hills ♪
♪ and I'm running ♪
♪ to get to you ♪
♪ As we're standing ♪
♪ Face to face ♪
♪ I long to hear you say ♪
♪ Hold on ♪
♪ I got you ♪
♪ you don't have to ♪
♪ be so strong ♪
♪ Hold on ♪
♪ you don't have to ♪
♪ do this alone ♪
♪ I know you're coming ♪
♪ I can see down the road ♪
♪ I'm travelling ♪
♪ but I'm not alone ♪
♪ (guitar strums) ♪♪♪
(applause and cheering)
Thank you.
(laughs)
Looks like romance if I
ever saw it.
What?
No I am just chatting with
a friend.
Mm Hm
How many years have I
known you?
Hm...
A friend.
(laughs)
I told you.
So good.
I know right?
Can't come down here
and not try it.
What are you writing?
Not writing.
Sure looks like you're
writing though.
Not writing.
Can I use that actually?
Shut up.
This is so good.
You're an artist.
In a former life maybe.
Can I keep it?
It's all yours.
This gives me an idea.
♪ Music starts to play ♪
Walk with me?
Alright well, this is my ride.
Why don't you hop on in.
♪ She's filling my heart
with beauty ♪
I like to coordinate everything
with my hair.
Don't touch the car!!
♪ Making everything I do
shine ♪
♪ I can feel it pulsing
through me ♪
♪ Now I know ♪
Beautiful.
♪ I'm gonna be fine ♪
Yeah.
♪ Breathe deep ♪
♪ Don't forget to count
to five ♪
♪ This... bliss... ♪
♪ Is all I'm needing to
survive ♪
♪ My heart is like a
hummingbird ♪
♪ Everything else is turning
blurry ♪
♪ She's filling my heart
with beauty ♪
♪ Making everything I
do shine ♪
Such a good day.
Yeah.
You're awesome.
I like you.
Me too.
I should probably get going.
Okay.
This was fun.
Yeah.
I really...
...wanna kiss you
right now.
I'm sorry.
Right.
"I'm sorry"
(Phone buzzes)
"No I'm sorry, I was
out of line."
"But you weren't...
at all"
"Either way sorry"
"Logan, I do like you."
"Like, 'like you', like you."
"I 'like you' too."
(footsteps approach)
Hey Amber I was gonna...
I can come back
I'll come back
You-
No - I - e - be-
(sound of people talking)
So I ended up in this
hostile kitchen
(laughing)
No you didn't!
I did.
I love this song.
Oh yeah this is a good one.
You know this song?
Mm Hm
♪ I've been alone ♪
♪ Plenty of nights ♪
♪ Yeah it's alright ♪
♪ I can get by ♪
♪ Baby tonight ♪
Sing to me.
♪ Breaking me out ♪
♪ Making me melt ♪
Ooh I want to dance.
Just a little bit.
♪ Like I've never felt ♪
♪ Before ♪
♪ Sweet heat
set me on fire ♪
Oh my god, look at you go.
♪ Touch me
feel my desire ♪
♪ Everything you do ♪
♪ is making me higher ♪
Wait... what do you...
(laughs)
Wait I need to see this
robot dance.
(laughs)
I can't
♪ Feeling the sweat ♪
♪ Sliding down slow ♪
♪ There's nothing to hold ♪
We're dancing at a bar like
a bunch of hooligans.
♪ I won't let go ♪
There we go, there we go.
♪ Sweet heat, set me on fire ♪
♪ Touch me, feel my desire ♪
♪ Everything you do ♪
♪ Is making me higher ♪
♪ Sweet heat ♪
♪ Sweet heat, set me on fire ♪
Through the curtains.
Release me set me free.
(laughs)
♪ Touch me, feel my desire ♪
♪ Everything you do ♪
♪ Is making me higher ♪
♪ Sweet heat ♪
(both laugh)
♪ Instrumental music plays ♪
(Waves crashing)
♪♪♪ (music ends) ♪♪♪
When I was a little girl
my mom and I
used to come to the
beach
and take these long walks
to find
rocks or stones
and then we would assign
some sort of meaning to it.
An emotion or something.
anger, sadness...
...and then we would
throw it into the ocean
as this way of
releasing things we didn't want
I like that.
Did you ever do it for
things that you did want?
Yes, occasionally we would...
make a wish (laughs)
But it was really special
because my mom is just
so practical in so many ways
So whenever we did that
it was...
...it felt like something
magical might happen.
I didn't really have anything
magical like that growing up.
I did have this disappering
mom though
and this really cool key
I wore around my neck
If I used it...
...I could open my front
door.
Magic rocks sound a lot
nicer.
Yeah.
I coulda' used some of
those when I was a kid.
(laughs)
Mommy!
Hello
How you doing?
Good.
Yeah?
There was a guy on the
subway and he said 'shit'
and daddy told me never
to say that.
Great.
Well... daddy's right.
Hi.
So we're gonna go to
the park and then
I'm going to make you
your favorite.
Pizza?
Mm Hm
(laughs)
(footsteps approach)
Hi.
So this is my friend Logan
and she's gonna hang
out with us today.
Miss Emily it is my pleasure
to make your acquaintance.
(giggles)
I'm excited to go to the
park are you?
Do you like slides 'cuz
I love slides?
No.
You don't... nevermind I
don't love slides at all they're
they're terrible.
(laughs)
Uhh, who is this?
This is my friend Logan.
Logan this is Ethan.
Hey.
Logan...
...the pleasure's all mine.
Nice to meet you.
Shall we?
Swings?
Bye.
(laughs)
What's that?
Dessert.
Ooh.
Oh.
You're job is to taste.
Okay.
Close your eyes.
Mmm
Okay.
Open.
No. Don't cheat!
(laughs)
What, I'm not cheating
it's a reflect.
Open what? Eyes or
mouth?
Okay, shh. You're gonna
wake up Emily.
Sorry, god.
I forgive you.
Hang on.
What... is.. happening?
Cheat proof.
Uh huh.
Ready?
Mm hm.
Okay...
I see.
Okay.
Is that okay?
Mm hmm
Ready?
Okay... open.
Open wider
(laughs)
and bite
It's like a...
chocolate
brandy?
Do I win? Do I win a
prize? (laughs)
Maybe. Okay.
Ready for the next one?
Mmm can I say no?
Not really, no.
Alright hang on.
This is falling.
Ready?
Mm hmm.
I'm sorry.
We shouldn't do this.
Wait... what?
Why not?
(exhales)
It's just... this is so...
confusing.
because I have all these
feelings for you
I really value our friendship
and I'm like, kind of
attracted to you
like really attracted to you
and
I don't know what to
do with that
so maybe it's better
left untouched.
Okay
slow down.
What I'm hearing is
you like me
you want me
and there was this part about
not touching but...
I think we can just strike that
from the record.
I do like you
a lot.
I'm just
overwhelmed by this feeling
that I wanna get closer to you.
Closer
I like that.
Can we just...
take it slow?
Of course.
You know I'm really concerned
about this bill
if this contractor doesn't
come through we...
I got it.
You got it.
Okay while you got that
why don't you tell me
who's the mystery texter?
(laughs) What?
The flirtatious, smiley texts.
Oh the fliratious, smiley texts
Oh come on, who's the
lucky guy?
There is no guy.
Okay fine, if you insist.
See?
(laughs) Okay you got me,
but only slightly.
Aww come on, details?
Come on boss.
Oh how convenient
I'm your boss when you
don't want to spill.
I'm happy for you.
Who is it?
Not this time.
K? I have my reasons.
(phone buzzes)
Hey
I was just talking about you.
Ohh that's just selfish.
(Distinct laugh in background)
I'm telling you it's the G train
Mom?
Excuse me?
You're in New York?
I think you've mistaken me with
someone else.
Mistaken you for someone
else?
Wow, you're incredible.
I don't know what you're talking
about.
You... right.
You wouldn't.
You never did.
You're right
(train approaches)
This is us.
(giggling) I told you so.
Yeah
(both laughing happily)
I can't
get on the train
Okay.
I can't get on the train.
I was a fucking kid man.
Fuck.
How can she look at me
like I'm not even here
like I'm a fucking stranger?
(hits wall)
(cries quietly)
Fuck
Okay, alright alright.
Stop stop stop.
You're gonna hurt yourself.
Stop, stop.
(crying harder)
Look at me
Look at me.
You do exist.
Okay?
You matter.
And if she doesn't see that
then she doesn't deserve you.
She doesn't deserve you.
(sound of rain and thunder)
(distant thunder)
♪ (Instrumental music plays) ♪
Hey...
Oh, don't stop.
I wanna watch you work.
♪♪♪ (music ends) ♪♪♪
(sound of pencil to paper)
It's all about
the little unseen details.
But then
sometimes you just gotta
sit back so you can
see it all come together.
(sound of distant rain)
You're so beautiful.
I can't stop myself
from falling in love with you.
(thunder)
You okay?
I'm better than okay.
(laughs)
I don't know what I'm doing.
It's okay.
I think you got this.
(thunder rolls)
(laughs)
♪ (music plays) ♪
(shower sounds)
♪ Morning til noon with you ♪
♪ making the brew ♪
♪ I'll make the bed ♪
♪ We can be happy there ♪
♪ You could be happy anywhere ♪
♪ Tell you the truth all we
need ♪
♪ is a roof over our heads ♪
♪ And I could be happy there ♪
♪ I could be happy anywhere ♪
♪ Baby I'm happy there ♪
♪♪♪ (music fades out) ♪♪♪
Hey how we doin' ladies?
Come talk to me?
Just ignore him.
C'mon we could make
a baby huh?
Hey why don't you get rid
of the redhead - we could talk?
Alright dude that's enough.
Back off.
Oh oh I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Hey what you need is a dick.
Fucking dykes.
♪ (Piano plays) ♪
♪ (Piano playing ends) ♪
(applause)
Hey...
You were so good up there.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
High five.
(laughs)
Who's that?
Uh, that's my friend...
Logan.
Oh hey, nice to meet you.
Well a few of us are going
to dinner
would you like to join us?
Um, Ethan has Emily this weekend
so it would um, just
be me.
Perfect! Join us.
Okay... yeah.
Hi.
Hey... uh...
I'm gonna go.
Go?
Yeah, um... uh...
I'm not feeling so good.
Stay.
No, I... I want you to stay.
No that's okay, um...
I'm gonna go home.
Okay I'll, see you later or...
Yeah.
Okay.
Bye.
(knocking on door)
♪ (guitar plays) ♪
Logan.
♪♪♪ (guitar playing stops) ♪♪♪
Please let me in I
know you're in there.
(knocks on door)
Can I come in?
(exhales)
I'm an asshole.
I'm sorry.
Talk to me.
Ethan was there
there were parents there,
there...
teachers there...
...I... I..
I just I wasn't ready to -
- step into that kind of
role today
What role?
It's not a role
It's just us.
I know Logan but it...
It is kind of a role okay?
And it's not just us.
I wish it were that simple
but it's not.
I don't know, I just
sometimes I... I...
I wonder if I'm up for it.
For what?
For being with a woman.
I mean
bringing a new
guy around today
would have been hard enough
but to look at everybody and say
hey I'm a big fat lesbian now
I mean I just... I...
Wow.
I hadn't though it through okay?
I didn't expect you to do
any of that.
I just prefer to be treated
like I exist.
You don't even do that
to a friend.
I just...
How do you do it?
How do I do what?
Love people?
I don't let anyone's opinions
affect how I feel.
Look
I understand
this is a lot of change for you
it's not easy.
I get it, but...
But I hurt you.
And the last thing in the world
I wanna do is hurt you.
Forgive me.
I do.
No.
Really
forgive me.
♪ (Music plays) ♪
♪ Wrapping your head
around me ♪
♪ I want forever to be ♪
You know, I'm just gonna go now.
Are you sure?
I can go.
You stay with Emily.
Nah, she's sound asleep.
It'll only take a minute.
Okay.
You okay with that?
Yeah.
Okay.
I'll be right back.
♪ All of the earth feels
the same ♪
♪ Even the trees call
your name ♪
Hey.
You okay?
♪ I think I'm crying ♪
♪ but it's only the rain ♪
You couldn't sleep?
♪ All of the earth ♪
♪ feels the same ♪
(music ends)
(waves crashing,
bright music plays)
♪ I like the way you look ♪
♪ When no one's looking ♪
♪ I like the way your
hair falls in your face ♪
♪ Maybe we could get ♪
♪ something cookin' ♪
♪ Maybe we could just
try a taste ♪
I'm the king of the world.
♪ Everybody wants the same
thing baby ♪
♪ We're all lookin' for
a safe place ♪
♪ Hey ♪
♪ This could be our day ♪
♪ Baby won't you stay ♪
♪ Hey ♪
♪ I could be your
safe place ♪
♪ There's something in your
eyes ♪
♪ I just cant' fight it ♪
♪ When you pull me close
and draw me near ♪
♪ no need to hesitate ♪
♪ no need to hide it ♪
♪ when we can push
it into second gear ♪
♪ Everybody wants the
same things baby ♪
♪ We're all looking for a safe
place ♪
♪ Hey ♪
♪ This could be our day ♪
♪ Baby won't you stay ♪
♪ Hey ♪
♪ I could be your safe place ♪
Awe yeah do that again okay?
♪ Safe place ♪
Uh huh (laughs)
do it again.
♪ Safe place ♪
Oh so pretty.
♪ (song ends) ♪
I love watching you play.
Being away with you.
You know
you could come on tour with me
(laughs)
what?
Mm hmm
It could be fun.
Travel around the country
together.
Stay in these cute little
hotel roooms.
You could bring Emily.
Find time to paint.
Hm?
Sounds amazing.
Come on. Can you just like
pretend to
like the idea for a second?
I love the idea.
It's just not practical I just
can't quit my job.
Right.
Your job of course.
Yeah. My job, I love
my job.
And you know, I love structure
Yes I know
I have seen your color
coordinated sock drawer.
I love my sock drawer.
(laughs)
It does sound amazing though.
You know, I umm
I never asked anyone to come on
tour with me before.
I love you.
Can't believe I just said that
but...
I'm sorry, what'd you say?
I said I love you.
One more time.
(both laughing)
I love you too.
So much.
Okay everybody
find a partner
(mumbles)
I hate these things.
Maybe you should stop
organizing them.
Next we're gonna be asked to
throw ourselves at eachother.
Um, somebody your own
size is good.
You'll do.
Sugar bridges.
So just take a moment
be with your partner, take
them in.
Remember trust is a really
important part of every
workplace relationship.
So you gonna tell me
who's making you glow?
You have a way of saying
things Sol.
Well I know that sex glow when
I see it.
Sex glow?
Okay so, partner A
turn away from partner B
Take one big step away.
Talk.
(Exhales)
I don't know.
Try me.
You know Logan?
Yeah I know Logan.
(Exhales)
I'm fucking her.
(sound of Amber hitting
the ground hard)
You know catcing me was the
entire purpose
of that exercise.
I know.
But you gotta prepare an old
woman before you drop
something big off in her
lap.
You asked.
And you're not old.
Thank you.
This is why you've been
so secretive?
'Cuz I'm sleeping with a woman?
Yeah it's just not something I
ever saw myself doing.
It's just...
Just so much stuff that goes
along with that, you know?
Like now I, now I
suddenly have a label.
Black, white, straight, gay.
There's nothing wrong with
being gay.
I know that.
But you know, a lot of other
people don't.
Girl this is New York.
Yeah
Call my parents, they live
in Brooklyn.
Besides I'm not gay.
I still, I still like men I do.
I'm just... I don't know.
Once upon a time
what feels like a lifetime ago
I was in love
with a white man.
And he loved me.
I wanted to spend my every
waking hour with him
To spend my life with him.
But back then where
I was at
it would have taken courage
I didn't have
support from family,
friends, peers
to walk down the street
hand in hand without having
insults hurled at us
So what happened?
I closed my heart to him.
to that entire part of my life.
I don't regret where I'm at,
my family
my choices for any second,
but...
that is one regret
that still hangs over me
and living with regret
is
only my doing.
I feel like when I close my eyes
I keep thinking that
if the world didn't care
I wouldn't care.
If the world didn't care,
Life is a series of choices
Amber.
Every second we choose
our happiness or our
bitter remorse.
And we can only love who
we love
and stand by that choice
Times are changin' baby.
Times are changing.
So...
...step into your life
before it passes you by.
Oww.
(laughter and conversation)
Logan we are just so happy
that Amber
has found a friend like you
during such a difficult time
in her life.
And we really appreciate you
being there for her.
It's my absolute pleasure.
She's wonderful.
Nice to finally meet you.
Nice to put a pretty face
to someone we've heard so
much about.
Thank you. Great to meet
you both.
I actually have to get going,
I have a client to meet.
I'm sorry.
But please enjoy the rest of
your day
Um I have to go to the
restroom
so I'll just walk you out.
So
you met my parents
I like them.
Well that's because you don't
know them.
(laughs)
No...
I like them
and I love you.
What is this?
(exhales)
It's nothing.
You were leaving?
(exhales hard)
Yup, I'm leaving.
Logan.
Logan hey.
Logan stop.
I'm sorry.
You're always sorry Amber.
(exhales)
Hey look, I didn't expect you to
waltz into the cafe and
just announce your love for me.
But when are you gonna be able
to stand tall next to me?
I told you I just need time.
How much time Amber?
I have never leapt like this
before in my life
and I keep leaping into you
and I
keep falling on my fucking face.
I never asked you to do that.
You just did it on your own.
You jumped before I was ready
I don't know how this is my
fault
Fault?
Are you even listening?
Is everything alright?
(exhales) Oh god.
Mom everything is fine.
Yeah
everything's fine.
Fuck.
Amber.
Shut up mom.
What just happened?
Please don't let me
fuck this up.
What'd you say?
I said I love you.
I love you too.
(knocks on door)
Hey.
Hi.
Only got a couple of minutes so
what'd you want to talk
about?
Hi sweetie.
Hi.
What are you guys doing here?
Well Ethan called and uh...
thought it was best that we sit
down and
try to figure this thing out.
What's going on?
Well we thought it best to
convene.
Convene?
Yeah.
Why?
So...
...you and Logan.
Are you kidding me?
Okay, honey that's that's not
why we're here.
Wow.
They... they didn't say anything
You did
right now.
Really Amber?
What?
Just explains a lot.
Okay I am not having this
conversation.
Okay, hold on. Woah woah
woah hey.
C'mon, c'mon. Ethan...
Can we try to focus please?
Yes, yeah okay.
I'll... cut to the chase.
Sit down.
Great.
Don't sit down.
(exhales)
I got a job offer out of state.
I'm leaving in three weeks.
What?
You're leaving?
Yup.
It's a two year comittment
minimum.
What about Emily?
I took the job Amber.
I'm not asking for your fucking
permission.
Ethan relax.
Don't talk to her like that.
What?
Can you stay focused on Emily
here?
Hey, you have no idea
Enough! Enough!
Stop it!
Enough.
Mom, dad, I...
Can we just...
Alright c'mon.
You're right.
We'll be in the car honey.
(door closes)
I don't know what to say.
I think that went well.
(exhales)
You know I really did love
you Ethan.
Part of that never goes away.
I know that you think that I
pushed you away
a long time ago I - I -
pushed you away but
You didn't push me away
Amber
you burned my life to the
ground.
I know. Mine too.
And I'm sorry about that.
I'm...
(exhales hard)
It's just that
I still love you.
And I don't know how to do this.
I'm sorry that you're hurting.
Look, I - I know
I was an asshole to you
a lot.
I regret that.
No - look at me.
Amber.
Tell me what to do.
(crying whimper)
You tell me what to do
and I'll do it.
I was a kid Ethan.
We were just kids. I - I -
I - I... (exhales)
You need to be able to see that-
I mean -
Can you see that?
Yeah.
I didn't like the person I was
becoming around you.
I hated her
and I don't want to be her
anymore.
I think that we both failed us
and Emily.
But Emily can't live without you
You're an amazing mother.
Yeah
but you're her father.
And she's gonna miss you
so much.
Why do you have to...
(Ethan cries softly)
I have to.
He's leaving in three weeks.
Wow. Just like that.
Yup.
It's just a lot of changes
coming my way.
I can help
with Emily.
I can help you.
But I gotta figure out
everything with work and -
just everything is going
to be really different.
Amber... Amber...
I don't think that you're
listening to me.
Hey
I'm saying that I want to
be a part of your life
and Emily's life in a
bigger way.
I know and that's very
sweet
but...
you're leaving for tour and
Not forever. I'm here we can
figure it...
I know but it doesn't matter
because it's not the right time.
(exhales hard)
You're awfully quiet tonight.
(exhales)
Yeah I guess.
Anything you wanna talk about?
There's just a lot going on
right now.
You know? With you taking
Emily on and
a lot of (exhales)
a lot of things.
Yeah.
I know it's gonna be a lot
with work but
I'm actually really excited.
I miss her so much.
Hey.
What's going on?
I think we need to talk.
Okay.
The owners of the apartment I'm
taking care of
are coming back early.
And uh...
You know I'm going on tour
for a few months
And I'm not sure
where my home base is gonna be
when I come back to New York.
Okay.
Is... that's all?
I ju... (exhales)
What?
I think we need to break up.
I'm sorry.
I just don't think this
is working.
(exhales hard)
What?
We just can' keep doing this.
What? I...
I don't understand.
Look okay I know that I said
that this isn't the right time
but I think maybe once
Emily settles in a little,
you know
you can, you can
move in with us.
With me.
Move in?
Yes, I think that I'm ready
for that.
I'm...
I mean it Logan I am
ready for that.
That's what I...
You know if this is about
my parents, you know I don't-
I don't care what they think.
Emily loves you.
She loves you.
I love you.
I know that I keep letting
you down
but
I never loved anybody like
I love you.
So why are you doing this?
Because Amber
I can't
love you from such a
vulnerable place.
You say yes to me and my life
is amazing
you say no and I'm
crushed and
I can't
love you from this place.
I...
I really...
I need you okay?
I need you.
I don't, I don't want to do this
alone. I don't.
You have all these things
that you wanna do
you know?
And there's so much you
have to focus on
and it's not me.
You gotta figure out what
you want.
I know what I want.
I want you.
Please don't do this.
Don't do this okay?
Come here.
Please don't do this.
I'm sorry.
♪ (Music plays) ♪
So this is it then?
That's all?
I need you to go.
Can I walk you home...
at least?
No.
You should just go.
Can... I can still walk
you home...
Please go.
♪ Summer in the green ♪
I love you.
Go.
♪ Soft beneath my feet ♪
Please just go.
♪ Wishing for another kiss
before we end this dream ♪
Damnit.
♪ I was yours right from
the start ♪
♪ Nothing lasts forever like
a broken heart ♪
♪ No amount of time ♪
♪ Can get you off my mind ♪
♪ You changed the way I
see myself ♪
♪ There's no leaving you
behind ♪
♪ Deeply you have ♪
♪ Made your mark ♪
♪ Nothing lasts forever ♪
♪ Like a broken heart ♪
♪ I'm standing in the rain ♪
♪ Getting washed away ♪
♪ A friendly face,
a coffee shop ♪
♪ You look like you're
okay ♪
♪ Laughing as I ♪
♪ Fall apart ♪
♪ Nothing lasts forever ♪
♪ Like a broken heart ♪
♪ My broken heart ♪
♪ Summer in the green ♪
♪ Soft beneath my feet ♪
♪ Wishing for another kiss ♪
♪ Before we end the dream ♪
♪ I was yours ♪
♪ Right from the start ♪
♪ Nothing lasts forever ♪
♪ Like a broken heart ♪
♪ My broken ♪
♪ Heart ♪
♪♪♪ (Finishes song) ♪♪♪
Sounds good on my end.
I'm not sure what you want me to
do with this information Amber.
I don't think that lifestyle
suits you
or Emily.
It's for the best.
You don't think it suits
me mom?
It's not a dress that
we're talking about.
You asked my opinion.
No, I didn't mom.
You asked me how I was
doing
and I can't hide this
I'm sorry, I'm a mess.
Exactly why you need to
turn the page.
Nothing good can ever come
of this darling.
Why not.
Because it's not who
we are Amber.
I'm your daughter mom,
I'm not you.
Of course not but you're...
But what?
I love her.
Emily loves her.
And she left you.
It's for the best.
Yeah maybe it is for you mom
but it's not for me.
She made me happy.
She made me feel alive
for the first time.
And she loves me I know
she still loves me.
It's not love.
It'll pass.
It'll pass. It'll pass?
Mom this is heartache.
Okay?
This is good old fashioned
heartache.
And if you can't see that
if you can't see past
your shame
then I'm sorry but you don't
get to be a part of this.
You don't get to be a part
of my life.
You're gonna lose me.
You're gonna lose her.
You will lose us.
C'mon
We're going. C'mon.
Grace.
You just need to let her be.
Okay?
She'll ruin her reputation.
(exhales)
This isn't easy for me
either.
Not in the same way as
you but -
Mostly because it's not easy
for Amber.
I mean, I can see that.
She could just wait to meet
the right man.
She was
happy. I mean, had you stopped
to notice that?
Happy?
Put yourself in her shoes for
a second.
I would never be in her shoes
Michael.
Maybe being with Logan
surprised her
maybe it was there all along.
In any case
she's 30 years old
going throug a divorce
and coming out to the world
As gay.
I - I - just look -maybe
maybe she is
there's nothing we can do to
change that.
And I'm not sure I'd
want to.
Well you're on your own then.
Grace.
Don't do this.
She's still your daughter.
She's still the same Amber.
This is not something she'll
buckle under to please you.
Don't push her away.
♪ (Music starts to play) ♪
Well should we get some lunch?
You know what restaurant's
really close by?
Yeah.
You okay?
Mm Hm
Really cuz it seems like maybe
you're upset about something.
♪♪♪ (music ends) ♪♪♪
Hey there little girl
why so glum?
I don't know. Maybe we should
do some silly rock puns?
to make her laugh?
No, no, no, no, no, she hates
silly rock puns
Well
my sediments exactly.
I was magma before I was cool.
That's stupid
you're stupid.
Hey, hey, hey, hey
woah.
First of all that's not okay.
Okay?
What's going on?
I don't know.
What are you upset about?
You know what the feelings are
maybe?
I don't know. I said I don't
know.
Okay. Okay.
Look
I know it's been...
a big year
with a lot of changes.
A lot of feelings, big
feelings.
Confusing feelings
and I - I - I -
it's hard for a grown up you
know I'm, I'm feeling...
feeling confused too.
Really?
Yeah.
But you need to know that
when you're feeling this
when you're feeling confused
and angry
you can tell me
There's nothing you can say
that's gonna hurt my feelings.
Really?
Yeah, really.
I'm sorry.
No, I'm sorry.
I feel
so
angry!
Everything's messed up!
That was a good plop.
♪ (Music plays) ♪
Shall we get some pizza?
♪ Salt water cures ♪
♪ Everything ♪
♪ And candy is for travelling ♪
♪ You made me believe ♪
♪ You had done it all before ♪
♪ And never thought you
wanted more ♪
Oh it's mine but
honey I think it's time to put
it away.
Your mom will be here soon.
Do we have to?
I'm sorry love.
C'mon.
Can we play again
tomorrow?
Yes, sure.
How about next week?
Mm Hm
Next year?
Yeah.
What about when I'm big
like mommy?
Of course
I will always be there for you.
( sound of door opening )
Hey.
Hi mommy.
♪ (music plays on) ♪
I'm sorry.
♪ You always take the
small roads ♪
♪ Cuz it's prettier that way ♪
♪ And when somebody's
crying ♪
♪ You know the perfect
thing to say ♪
♪ You're the woman I rely on ♪
♪ I hear you every day ♪
Well thank you so much for
coming Phill.
Of course.
You're the best.
See you later.
Hey um, tell Sol I say hi.
♪♪♪ Music ends ♪♪♪
Are you familiar with her work?
Uhh, yeah.
What do you think?
Part of me loves it and the
other part of me is
terrified about what everybody
else is thinking.
You're the artist.
(laughs)
Well
now it would seem insincere of
me to say that
I think your work is
exquisite.
Maybe a little.
It is.
Thank you.
I won't take up any more
of your time.
Yeah okay. It's nice to meet
you.
Uh, Tim.
Tim, I'm Amber.
Amber... umm
Do you drink coffee?
Just cuz if you do, I
could sit next to you
while you do that.
Would it be okay if I called
you sometime?
Yeah.
Sure.
There's...
my contact information is at
the front desk.
Okay well then, I'm gonna go
to the front desk.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Enjoy your night.
Excuse me
hi
Amber?
Yes!
Regina Dey.
Yes... yes I know who you
are.
It's such a treat to meet you.
I'm just so honoured that
you would
come to my opening.
I wanna talk to you about
your work.
I do... I have a few ideas.
That would be great.
(laughs)
Thank you.
Yes.
Well you have guests to
entertain. (laughs)
Yes of course.
Do call me.
You can count on it.
Thank you.
(inaudible whispering)
Hi
♪ (radio music plays) ♪
(radio) We got Logan
Pierce here performing live at
The Caveat downtown Toronto
Could you turn that up
please?
(radio) Logan it is such a treat
to have you in the studio.
(radio) Thank you so much for
I'm so happy to be here.
(radio) Of course, your new
single 'Hold On'
is just climbing the charts.
Could you
tell us a little bit about
what inspired that song?
Gosh umm
I don't know where to start
(laughs) Come on girl you can
dig in there a little bit more.
You know, we're live.
So you want me to spill my
guts for the world?
(laughs)
Well...
...for you JoJo, I will.
Umm...
Well you know it's simple.
it's about
(radio) Love
you know, the kind of love
you dream about when
you're a kid. When you're
growing up and learning
about everything
and then you get older and
you stop believing in it
But... uh...
Turns out, it's real.
(radio) It's a thing.
Do tell.
It's ah, in the past.
Long story.
Aren't they all?
Okay...
Umm...
Well when I first wrote the song
it was kind of like
I wrote it
for someone I hadn't even
met yet.
But umm...
when I played it for an
audience for the first time
a friend of mine was in the room
(radio) and all of the sudden
it was really clear... that
somehow
I had written it for her.
And that's the story.
That's it.
(radio) You heard it here first.
Oh my god.
(radio) on JB Live Toronto.
Now what you have
all been waiting for
this is Logan Pierce
with Hold On.
♪ (guitar plays) ♪
♪ (music plays on radio) ♪
♪ I know that you're
comin' ♪
♪ I can see down ♪
♪ the road ♪
♪ I'm travelling ♪
♪ But I'm not alone ♪
♪♪♪ (music ends) ♪♪♪
So when do you leave?
Should I go?
I mean, what if she was
talking about somoene else?
I... okay fine. But what it
doesn't mean what I
think that it means?
Tell me this
when you're an old woman
will you be okay and look back
on your life not knowing?
Wondering what would have
happened?
Your time is now.
Step in.
Don't hang back by the sidelines
I love you.
Well wouldn't that be a
surprising turn of events.
Mm Hm yeah... shut up.
(both laugh)
♪ (music starts) ♪
Okay go.
Go get your woman!
Ahh...
Don't you have a flight
to catch?
Yes! Okay yes. Thank you.
Thank you.
I love you.
I love you!
♪ Pour another coffee in my
cup ♪
♪ Give me something pretty
to look at ♪
♪ I need every distraction I
can get ♪
♪ It would be so easy to
slip up ♪
♪ Oooh ♪
♪ I didn't want to walk away ♪
♪ But there was nothing left
to say ♪
♪ Gonna give it everything
I got ♪
♪ I'm gonna show the
fighters who's fighting ♪
♪ And I might be alone when
I'm on top ♪
♪ But I will be a hundred
percent in ♪
♪ Oooh ♪
♪ I didn't want to walk away ♪
♪ But there was nothing
left to say ♪
♪ Oooh ♪
♪ I'm making my own dreams
come true ♪
♪ Oooh ♪
♪ I'm a better me ♪
♪ becuase of you ♪
♪ Becuase of you ♪
♪ Because of you ♪
♪♪♪ (Music ends) ♪♪♪
(crowd cheers)
Thank you Toronto.
Have an amazing night.
♪ Music starts ♪
Oh hey
Hey
Great show tonight.
Thank you.
There's someone here to see you.
♪ Everything can wait ♪
♪ Just a little bit ♪
(exhales)
Hi.
Uh... how long have you
been here?
The entire show.
You were incredible.
You... um...
I... I... uh, don't know
what to say.
I feel like if I
speak too loud
or ahh
move too fast you might
just...
dissappear.
I'm not going anywhere.
Um...
I heard about your art
show.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
So, did you
just come for the music
or...?
(laughs)
I miss you.
(exhales)
You were right
you know I really needed
to
see myself
before I could see myself
in the world with you.
I was looking for approval
from everyone. But what I
really needed
was my own and I know
that now.
And I know that
My life
just isn't right without you.
(sniffles)
I want you.
(laughs)
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
♪ I will be the light ♪
♪ Here when you need me ♪
♪ Any day or night ♪
♪ I will love you completely ♪
♪ I can see your heart ♪
♪ It's bright and open ♪
♪ Even with the darkness ♪
♪ You're always holding ♪
♪ Hey ♪
♪ There's nothin' left to say ♪
♪ The words have flown away ♪
♪ And left us here ♪
♪ Just starin' ♪
♪ Hi ♪
♪ I'm lookin' in your eyes ♪
♪ And suddenly the skies ♪
♪ Are opening around me ♪
♪ You have found me ♪
♪ You will be the light ♪
♪ Here when I need you ♪
♪ Any day or night ♪
♪ I will always be near you ♪
♪ You can see my heart ♪
♪ It's bright and open ♪
♪ Even with the darkness ♪
♪ I'm always holdin' ♪
♪ Hey ♪
♪ There's nothin' left to say ♪
♪ The words have flown away ♪
♪ And left us here
just starin' ♪
♪ Hi ♪
♪ I'm lookin' in your eyes ♪
♪ And suddenly the skies ♪
♪ Are opening around me ♪
♪ You have found me ♪
♪ I will be the light ♪
♪ Here when you need me ♪
♪ Any day or night ♪
♪ I will love you completely ♪
♪♪♪ (music ends) ♪♪♪