My nephews, my nieces, my grandchildren...
I’m proud of all of them.
You make me look like the bad guy.
But this has been
a wonderful experience, no doubt.
There is no proof that you’re innocent.
What do you think?
That you’re wrong.
You are a free man.
You and your lawyer
asked for compensation
of 2 million euros,
which you should be receiving soon.
What will you do with this money?
I’d pay to make him
get a taste of his own medicine.
Mr Mauro, please,
give me a real answer.
What will you do with this money?
What happened?
He’s been throwing up all night.
-Do we have any medicine?
-No. Does he…?
-I’ve already asked, he doesn’t either.
-I’m going to the pharmacy.
-Can you…?
Thanks.
I even filmed the pharmacist.
I’m a pain in the ass, I know.
He didn’t want me to.
By the third time he wagged
his finger I was like: "What?"
"Don't film me."
Then I turned around
and I was like...
Emiliano, who’s right there
and is a jackass...
No, I think
he went out, there’s just Luca.
I can smell his stench, here he is.
Told you. I could
smell him a mile away.
Didn’t he say he would come?
He's not coming.
What do you mean he’s not coming?
I’m sensing some hostility.
From who?
Carlo, Frank...
-Matano?
-Sure.
We’ve only lost
an hour and a half of work.
It’s not that big of a deal
when you’re making a movie in five days.
-Am I right?
-No.
Good morning.
Were you sick?
I threw up.
-Have you taken any medication?
-Not yet.
What about the shots?
I’ve been in charge
of over-the-shoulder shots.
He took all medium shots.
We haven’t had any major issues,
just some beard noise.
I can’t shave it off
because my wife doesn’t want me to.
Rightfully so.
You should have told me
before shooting, not after.
Because these scenes
are improvised and no two takes are alike.
It’s fine.
Don’t tell me the other options
after we’ve already shot the scene
because it’s something we can’t repeat.
He will never do it
the same way. Understood?
Good job. Good job you too.
You didn't expect it, did you?
You actually got teary-eyed.
I was like: “It’s impossible,
my flesh and blood…”
It was completely unexpected.
"He was your grandchild".
Amazing.
-They told me to stop.
-You can go fuck yourself.
You can come with
if you want to.
It looks nice out of focus. I like it.
Turn it this way, just a little bit.
No, sorry, the other way.
That’s it, with this part out of focus.
Like this?
You cannot see the light, it’s fine.
What should I do with the light?
-Place it there.
-Alright.
-Roll camera…
-Rolling!
Action!
Nico, can you read his lines?
Sure.
“Reading” is a gerund, right?
What is this, primary school?
Roll camera.
Rolling.
Action!
A girl reported being approached
by a man in much the same way.
When her parents read
on the newspaper that a kid went missing
they immediately called us
to see if they could help us identify this man.
Take a look.
-Here?
-Yes.
Maybe you can move a bit...
-I think we should move into the shade.
-I have my doubts.
Let’s move into the shade.
Vittorio, you look different.
Where is Massimo?
There he is, let’s go.
We are looking for a man
in his thirties...
Say “in his forties”.
A man in his forties
who seems to enjoy scaring kids.
I'm moving it, ok?
-Is everyone ready?
-Let’s do this.
Daniele asked to do a sound check.
-Sure, do the sound check.
-Can you say your lines?
Good morning sir,
I’m Detective Ruggeri.
I’ve just met your daughter,
who was so kind
as to give me your phone number.
Try not to look down when you speak.
-Roll camera.
-Rolling!
Action!
I don’t know what you’re talking about.
I was home with the flu.
Gianni, from the town nearby,
came over to help.
He helped me in the fields.
I was so weak I couldn’t even get up.
Cut!
-Oh no, not you again!
-The pain in the ass is back.
We have a big nursery with many plants.
We are quite the experts.
These plants are gorgeous
but they need some care.
Action!
Cut! Let’s review this shot,
but it should be ok.
The lighter!
But you don’t go to jail for a lighter.
Wait, Nicolò. Here, take it
before I lose it.
I'm trusting you with this, don’t lose it.
I’m gonna lose it in no time.
This might take a while…
Let’s just watch it on there.
Do you see any shadows?
I don’t think so.
-Yes, maybe a little bit.
-I can see some shadows, but...
Keep going.
Keep going. Okay.
Action!
We’ll do another take.
Today we’re making you break a sweat, sorry.
Yes, go down the stairs.
What, did you want to change it up?
-Roll camera.
-Rolling...
Action!
-Roll camera, roll sound.
-Rolling.
-Mark it.
-Scene 10, roll 1, take 2.
-Roll camera.
-Rolling.
Scene 10, close-ups, roll 1, take 1.
Action!
Good morning,
what brings you here?
An ugly story I’m afraid,
a story of demons.
It seems like we have
a big bad wolf in the woods.
Roll camera, rolling, mark it.
Scene 24, close-ups, roll 1, take 3.
Action!
Rolling!
-Mark it.
- Scene ABC, roll 1, take 1.
Action!
Incoming!
And it hits you.
Tonight you’ll be coming to dinner
with a big bump on your head.
Roll camera.
-Rolling.
-Mark it.
-You’re always in the way.
-Can you read it?
ABC, roll 1, take 2.
Action!
Cut!
I said: “Sorry, we’re doing
a sound check, wait a second…”
She was like “ok”
then started making a lot of noise.
She said: "I just wanted
to annoy Daniele".
Roll camera!
-It wouldn’t go up.
-Cut!
-Now it works.
-It’s doing it on purpose,
just to spite you.
Let’s do another take.
-Are we ready to go?
-Okay. Roll camera.
Go Carlo, go.
Go with the left tyre.
Go, go!
You are young,
you have the equipment.
Just write a 5-minute scene and
shoot it in secret, without telling us.
We have no director,
no screenwriter, no nothing.
You don’t need much
when you have a theatre like this one.
You don’t even need actors.
Picture this: everything is dark,
with just a few lights
and the right music.
Two or three actors get up and down to the beat.
Completely at random.
And you have your horror movie.
A three-to-five-minute short film.
A Little Red Riding Hood horror story.
Lighter scene, roll 1, take 1.
Action!
Cut!
-Stay in that position.
-Alright.
-Rolling!
-Mark it.
Scene 133, VPA, roll 1, take 1.
Action!
Roll camera.
Rolling.
Sound rolling.
Scene Bah, roll 1, take 1.
Action!
Now we have a close-up
of you telling the fairytale.
-Are you happy with the shot?
-I am.
Now that you know where she lives
you can stay home. It’s fine.
Let’s do a close-up on him.
From the side?
No, from the front.
-The light is on him now, right?
-Exactly.
In this way.
Scene 7, CA, roll 1, take 1.
Action!
-Gargioni.
-Gargione.
Unfortunately we didn’t have a marker,
so it’s a little bit difficult to read.
Where should I put the lighter?
On the stairs...?
Yes, halfway.
Lights off on stage.
I like it.
Lights off on stage!
All of a sudden you turn the lights on
and "The Show Must Go On"
starts playing. Just perfect.
Roll camera!
Slowly.
-Mark it.
-Scene 14, roll 1, take 1.
Action!
Are you ready, Luca?
Ok.
Remember to look at him.
Don’t look at me. Look at him.
-Roll camera...
-Rolling.
-Sound rolling.
-Scene 14, close-ups, roll 1, take 3.
Action!
Listen, Franco. She’ll be sitting here
and you’ll be coming from there.
And then he says:
"Do you want me to go with you?"
To which you answer: "No, I live close by."
Scene 16, roll 1, take 2.
Action!
Cut!
Mr Vella, please don’t pay
any mind to these peasants.
Say your lines with the Swedish man.
-So you stop monologuing and say…
-”I’ll make something to eat!”
Good!
“I’ll make you something to eat.”
-Alright.
-Who wants a coffee?
Coffee sounds great.
-Rolling.
-Sound rolling.
Scene DE, roll 1, take 1.
Action!
She’s still here,
looking down on us from Heaven.
She’s never really left us.
Good job. Both of you.
This shot must be out of focus.
We’ll see a pair of legs
approaching her, but they won’t be in focus.
You go straight to the door.
You knock.
Great.
Then you knock again.
-What can we ask?
-What can we say?
-I’m Lisa.
-She is a third my age.
You can ask her
to call you by your first name.
But I already do that.
Of course.
You can say you
are the main character.
Because you are!
She doesn’t care.
It's not a big deal.
She’s just the most important character.
My classmates won’t believe me.
But then they’ll see the movie.
Don’t you have
some pictures you can show them?
No, it’s still a secret.
I’m telling them anyway.
We’ll invite your
classmates to the premiere, ok?
And you’ll be like:
“See? I told you so."
Be careful.
-Did we take the clapperboard?
-Yes.
-This doesn’t really look like Sicily.
-We’re in the hinterland.
In France.
Look, there’s a well!
Nice, there is a well over there.
It’s incredible what you can see
simply by driving around.
This camera is almost like my baby.
I even dreamt of it last night.
Do you also sleep with it, or…?
It’s on the night table, it keeps me company.
Action!
And lead us not into temptation,
but deliver us from evil. Amen.
-Carola, we can go.
-Okay, Dad.
Cut!
Roll camera!
-Rolling.
-FM, roll 1, take 1.
Action!
I knew you shouldn’t have come.
Now we shoot the scene.
Keep your eyes closed, pretend to be asleep.
-Roll camera!
-Rolling.
Sound rolling.
Scene SAD, roll 1, take 1. Action!
Mr Mauro, you were accused,
convicted and imprisoned,
for a heinous crime - pedophilia.
Five years later,
you were cleared of all charges
and now you’re free.
What do you think?
I think that five years are a long time.
I hope they catch the real culprit
who is still on the loose.
I’m one of eight siblings.
We had a good family -
wives, children, sisters-in-law...
Then I was thrown in jail for five years.
The first ten days were awful.
What I went through -
I wouldn’t wish it on anybody.
I went through a lot.
I couldn’t sleep at night.
I couldn’t eat.
I had nightmares.
I had done nothing wrong.
Sure, I got home but...
Everything had changed.
My wife, my children...
They seem different now.
I’ll tell you what happened.
That day I was
in those woods with my dog.
We used to go there every night.
My dog would hunt hedgehogs
and bring them to me alive.
So, I saw him come out
of this door that was usually locked,
and stop right at the entrance.
It was odd.
My dog is very smart, you see.
He wouldn’t come to me,
he stopped right there.
That got my attention,
so I decided to go inside.
And there it was.
What they accused me of.
It was your grandchild.
No, that’s impossible.
My grandchild would
always play with my dog.
They got along well, it’s impossible.
It was your grandchild.
That child was your grandchild.
Maybe he was too trusting,
he felt safe there?
Look...I...
I would have never,
he’s my flesh and blood.
But I will do anything
I can to find who did it.
I’d give anything to
find him and make him pay.
I want him to suffer.
I’ll take the law into my own hands.
Prisons have their own laws.
Women and children are off limits.
Outside, there are many other laws
that cause innocent men to be put in prison.
Finding this person would be easier,
if only you were given the compensation you deserve.
But we heard that this won’t happen.
Yes, whatever,
I have lost a grandchild.
I don’t care about the money.
I would use the money
to find this person,
and make him go through
whatever he made my grandchild go through.
I would pay ten people to do to him
what was done to me in prison.
The same thing,
but with ten people.
Hello?
Who?
Fuck, what a pain in the ass.
It’s a waste of time!
Send someone else.
Alright.
Fucking hell.
Here I am, go ahead.
Detective Ruggeri...
Don’t you feel any shame?
You sent an innocent man
to jail, for five years.
On a pedophilia charge.
That man was abused.
Now he’s out but he has no family, no life.
All because of your incompetence.
I was just doing my job,
put yourself in my shoes.
In your shoes?
I couldn’t even if I tried.
Accusing a man of such things,
taking the matter to Court,
having everyone believe you
for some inexplicable reason...
I’ve been doing this job for 30 years.
I solved over 500 cases.
You may have an excellent
track record, but maybe it’s time to quit.
Thirty years is a long time,
Maybe you’re just too old.
I don’t think so, I’m a long way from retirement.
Don’t you have an ounce of regret?
Don’t you feel responsible?
I’ve always done what I believed was right.
I’ve always been competent at my job.
If you think something isn’t right,
report it to the authorities.
Then request a formal investigation.
I don’t feel any guilt.
Who should he turn to though?
The authorities jailed him and tore his life apart.
Because of you.
Who should he turn to?
He had done nothing wrong.
Now he has lost everything,
He has no house, no family left.
Listen...
In life, there are winners
and there are losers.
Maybe that was his destiny.
I cannot be held responsible for that.
Not even for what happened to that man?
Don't you think you're morally responsible?
You made a mistake
that changed his life forever.
Do you know what?
He should take a vacation.
Maybe ask for compensation.
See?
-Is that all you have to say?
-If he’s as innocent as he says...
And lead us not into temptation,
but deliver us from evil. Amen.
-Let’s go, Carola.
-Okay, Dad.
I’m so happy you’re here.
Good girl.
You’re growing up so fast,
you’re going to be as beautiful as your mother.
I remember her.
I remember that she
would sit on the swing
and play just like
you do, in the same park.
She would spend
the whole day there, always happy and smiling.
We miss Mum.
We miss her.
But she’s never really left us.
She’s still here,
looking down on us from Heaven.
Do you go to school?
Good girl.
Wait, I’ll make something to eat.
Just a second.
This is bad, Mario.
We must look everywhere.
We must find him no matter what.
Everyone knows everyone around here.
If he lives here,
this cannot be his first time doing this.
Find out if there are
similar cases to this in the surrounding area.
Send me an email.
While we wait,
we must call the Social Services.
It’s a delicate matter.
If anything changes,
please let me know.
We can’t arrest all those
going for a walk in the woods.
We need more clues.
Who gave you this information?
Call the Forest Service, too.
Please find out if anything similar
has ever happened in this area.
Twenty years ago, for example.
I’ll go take a look in the woods.
Let’s start from there.
Where are you hiding,
you monster?
Dad, I went to the theatre
the other day. Can I go again?
Fine, but please be careful.
Okay, bye.
Have you noticed?
No, you haven’t noticed
the way they nod at me.
It’s almost like they’re afraid.
That’s because I’m a lawyer.
A lawyer!
It means the law.
And the word “law” has never
sounded good or friendly in this neighbourhood.
That has been true
since the days of ancient Greece and Carthage.
I only came here when I was twenty-five.
In those days, Al Capone,
the greatest Carthaginian of all
was learning his
trade on these pavements.
Frankie Yale himself was cut
precisely in half by a machine gun!
On the corner of Union Street.
Two blocks away!
Fuck!
Now listen carefully.
You too!
This is not Sicily.
It’s Red Hook.
This is the gullet of Brooklyn
swallowing the tonnage of the world.
My friends, especially my wife,
tell me the people
in this neighbourhood lack elegance,
they lack glamour.
After all, who have I
dealt with in my life?
Longshoremen and
the wives, fathers, children
of longshoremen!
However, believe me when I say that
every few years there is still a case.
And as the parties
tell me what the trouble is…
Do you know what happens?
The flat air in my office
suddenly washes in
with the green scent of the sea
and the dust in this air is blown away.
And the thought comes
that in some Caesar’s year
in Calabria perhaps
or on the cliff at Syracuse,
another lawyer, quite differently dressed
heard the same complaint
and sat there
as powerless as I
and watched it run its bloody course.
Now,
try to remember
at least 20% of what I’ve just said.
20% at the very least.
I’ll be back in one hour.
Let’s see what you make of it.
Get to work.
- Hello cutie pie.
- Hi.
- May I sit here?
-Yes.
What are you doing here all alone?
I’m waiting for my dad.
Your dad?
And where is he?
He’s at the doctor’s.
Did you like the show?
Yes.
Do you know I also do children’s shows?
With kids your age.
-How old are you?
-Eight.
Eight! You’re all grown up!
- And what’s your name?
-Carola.
That’s a beautiful name!
- Does he have a name?
-No.
What about we give him one?
Yes or no?
Nevermind then.
He’s nice, though. Very nice.
Such beautiful hands.
You’re very pretty.
Would you like to be in one of my shows?
-Is Dad fine with it?
-Yes.
We can meet every
other day, what do you think?
Kids usually work with me
for five hours, give or take.
That’s not a problem, is it?
Good.
Carola!
It’s time to go.
How are you?
I’m fine, everything’s fine.
Not yet, but she’ll be here any moment now.
You know how girls are.
They stop to chat, taking
their sweet time as we wait and wait.
I’m sure she’ll arrive soon.
Do you always come here to play?
Yes, because grandpa used to work here.
-What does he do?
- He chops wood.
Do you see this place here?
It’s very dangerous.
You must be careful.
I come here all the time,
so I know my way around.
A child fell in there once.
It was an accident.
Do you know what my job is?
I’m a woodsman.
I find wounded animals
and get them the care they need.
Then I patrol the woods
and whenever I see poachers
I catch them and arrest them.
Of course, I also do many other things.
Now I must go to work.
Are we clear? Never go out when it’s dark.
The woods are very
dangerous, do you understand?
If anyone tries to catch
a bunny, I’ll arrest them! Okay?
Have you seen a man
walking around in sports clothes,
someone you had
never seen around here before?
Maybe someone in town saw him?
The closer he was to the cabin
the louder the snoring got.
So the huntsman decided to get in.
And what did he find inside?
The wolf - snoring.
He thought: “I should kill the wolf now,
there won’t be a better time.
If he ate Little Red
Riding Hood and her grandma
I have to cut him open.”
So he did. He cut open the wolf’s belly
and saw a red hood.
Little Red Riding Hood lifted her head,
climbed up and jumped out of the belly.
Grandma jumped out right after her.
They were both safe and sound!
They thanked the
huntsman and went home.
So the huntsman filled
the wolf’s belly with some stones
then sewed it back together.
When the wolf woke up he tried to walk
but his belly was too heavy!
He collapsed and fell dead.
It’s a bit sad, but at least
Little Red Riding Hood was safe.
The wolf deserved it.
It’s a good story, isn’t it?
We could tell this story on stage.
Would you like
to be Little Red Riding Hood?
Yes.
Sounds good, right?
Would you tell me where you live?
I live in a house in the woods.
Can I come over sometime?
Your dad comes here every other day.
If I don’t see you, I’ll come to your house.
-Can I?
-Yes.
But you must promise me something.
Don’t tell your dad that I’m coming.
Ok.
Don’t tell your mum either.
-Deal?
-Deal.
-It will be our secret.
-Ok.
-Can I trust you?
-Yes.
There are no official reports yet,
just rumours about a man in his thirties
who seems to enjoy scaring kids.
-Hi.
-You really like coming here to play, don’t you?
-Yeah.
-In the woods?
I’m afraid I have bad news for you.
It’s time to go home.
There’s a big bad wolf in the woods.
Come on, I’ll take you home.
But I live close by.
I’ll come with you either way,
because that wolf is very naughty.
Come on, let’s go home.
It looks like our bad guy is gone.
But I want to make sure
for the kids’ sake.
We’re going to catch him soon.
-Hey there, cutie pie!
-Hi!
-How are you?
-I’m fine.
I’m very happy to see you.
-Has your dad gone out?
-Yes.
-Is that your house?
Has your mum gone out too?
Geppetto!
-Geppetto could have a small part
in our play, what do you think?
We’ll do Little Red Riding Hood.
Close your eyes, I have a surprise for you.
You can open them.
-Do you like it?
-Yes!
-Very much or just a little?
-Very much.
Very very much?
May I?
Remember to wear it under your jacket.
I want to show you
where we’ll play Little Red Riding Hood.
But promise me one thing.
Promise me you won’t tell mum and dad.
Okay.
Do you promise?
-Can I trust you?
-Yes.
Come on, let’s go.
No, I haven’t seen anyone.
I was home with the flu.
Gianni, from the town nearby,
came over to help.
I was so weak I couldn’t even get up.
I didn’t see anyone.
What happened?
How am I supposed not to worry?
My grandchild is wandering
the woods as we speak.
Tell me what’s happening, Mr Ruggeri.
What happened? Tell me what happened!
Wait, someone is knocking at the door!
It must be her, thank you for calling.
-Good morning.
What brings you here?
An ugly story, I’m afraid.
A story of demons.
It seems like there’s
a big bad wolf in the woods.
What are you talking about?
My partner should have
already informed the Forest Service.
You didn’t know?
No.
We’re looking for
a man in his early forties,
who has allegedly
been approaching children in this area.
Where were you last week?
I’ve always been here, sir.
Every morning I go to town early,
then I come back here.
I usually go home at around 7 pm.
Please show me your documents.
Here.
How long have you been
working as a woodsman?
Sixteen years.
Ever since I did my civil service.
Is there any problem?
Is there anyone who could testify
as to your working hours
here in these woods?
My coworker Andrea,
but he works the night shift.
Therefore no, there is no one.
You can only take my word for it.
Are you married? Do you have children?
No sir, I don’t even
have nephews or nieces.
Why do you ask?
-Do you live here?
-I live at my house.
I beg your pardon.
Hello?
We cannot arrest every single person
who goes mushroom hunting in the woods.
We need more clues.
Who gave you this information?
I’m coming.
We’re not done here.
-Have a nice day.
-You too.
If you ever see a man
around 40 hiking alone in the woods
call me immediately.
Thank you.
I’m sorry,
I need one.
Want one?
No, thank you,
I don’t take candy from strangers.
See you.
Goodbye.
Hello?
Do you like it here?
I do.
I’m starting an acting school.
Why do you ask?
An acting school?
Yes, an acting school.
Be careful.
Ay, that incestuous, that adulterate beast,
With witchcraft of his wits,
with traitorous gifts -
O wicked wit and gifts,
that have the power so to seduce!
—won to his shameful lust
the will of my most seeming-virtuous queen.
That it went hand in hand even with the vow!
No, it doesn’t work.
It doesn’t work.
It cannot possibly work.
No.
It won’t fucking work.
It has to work.
This is my kingdom.
What are you doing here?
I’m rehearsing for my upcoming show.
I knew it.
I knew you shouldn’t have come here.
You think you know what’s best for me.
You’ve always been like this.
You saw the girl.
You fucking saw her!
You saw her.
Don’t worry about it.
She’s mine.
I will fix everything.
She’s mine!
Come with me.
She’s mine.
Let’s go home.
Come on.
Mr Ruggeri, this is where you
stopped that monster once and for all.
How did you solve the case?
We had been looking for him
for a very long time.
I followed him to this abandoned warehouse
but he had a knife.
I had to defend myself.
Now the monster’s finally gone.
We would like to thank you
for everything you’ve done.
You truly saved us all.
Thank you, Mr Ruggeri.
And thank you for agreeing to this interview.
It was an honour to meet you, you’re a hero.
The honour was mine.
Turn the camera on!
You’re the monster!
You son of a bitch!
You’re the devil himself.
The girl has come out
of coma, I have proof!
Stay right where you are!
Or I'll kill you!