♪ No no no
♪ I don't have
that many wishes ♪
♪ I don't even need a tree
♪ Christmastime would be
much better ♪
♪ Having you right next to me
Hello, everyone, and welcome
to Six Degrees of Santa.
It's December first,
which means it's time
to kick off the third
year of our project.
Now, if you're new
to Six Degrees,
I'm here to give
you some instructions.
First, you want to get
one of our special boxes,
which has the directions
on the front.
You can order yours for free
using the link below,
or if you're
in the New York area,
you can pick one up at our shop,
McNevin Paper Company.
Next, you want to pick a gift
that's meaningful to you
and can be enjoyed
for a short period of time.
Some people choose books,
or a Christmas movie,
or a game.
For example, a puzzle.
Pack it all up in your special
Six Degrees box
and then begin your search
for Santa #2.
You can choose
a complete stranger,
or someone in your orbit.
Your neighborhood
crossing guard,
or the gentleman you always see
reading on the bench.
Pass it off.
Then Santa #2 gets to enjoy
the gift for a day or two,
then repacks it in this box
and gives it to Santa #3.
Then Santa #3 hands it off...
and so on until it reaches
Santa #6,
who gets to keep the gift.
Thanks, Santa! How'd you know?
I love puzzles!
The spirit of Six Degrees
is to connect to the world.
By Santa #6,
your gift will have made
its way to someone
you could never have imagined.
The process is anonymous.
It's more fun that way!
You're just sharing
a bit of yourself
and leaving the rest up
to Christmas magic.
Now, if you have any questions
or comments,
feel free to email me
at the address below.
Happy gifting
and Merry Christmas!
What do you think, Director?
I think it's our best yet!
Well, it's December first,
so Six Degrees is live!
Hmm!
Did you figure out
what you're doing
for your Six Degrees gift yet?
I'm still deciding.
Maybe my JingleMice
Christmas record?
You'll never guess
what I found for mine.
Whoa! You finally found
another copy!
Online from a used
book store in Wisconsin.
At least we'll always have
ours from Grandpa.
Mm-hmm.
Remind me, what's your
favourite part again?
I think it's when Elfie
is in New Mexico
and she learns about luminarias
and how luminaria
means "light."
Mm-hmm! Well, that's my
favourite part, too.
And you're my little luminaria.
- Oh!
Good morning, Harper. Dani.
I hope it's okay.
I love these for a background.
Very wholesome.
Christmas whimsical.
Ooh, that might be
a good hashtag.
I'm certainly trying
to snag more followers.
Especially with
my new crafty venture.
Oh, that's awesome!
Hey, you know I slipped
an invite to our small business
Christmas party
into your mailbox.
So, you know, you should come.
I'll try, if I'm not swamped.
So, wow was your date
the other night?
Dates.
Two different apps,
two different boroughs.
5 PM, then 8 PM.
They were both... okay.
I have to say, online dating
doesn't sound exactly magical.
It's the only way, Harper.
You just let me know when
you decide to get out there.
I'm happy to do a little
free consulting.
Good to know, but it's not
exactly a priority right now.
If you change your mind,
I'm here.
Take care. Bye, Zoey.
Alright, let's get you
to school, huh?
Good morning,
my darling daughter!
Oh! You just missed Harold.
He dropped off another bundle
of Six Degree boxes for you.
Ooh!
What do you think
of the pattern this year?
I think it's gorgeous. Oh.
And...
You were mentioned
on Ivy B. Holly,
one of my favourite
Christmas blogs.
"Here I go,
embarking on my second year
of Six Degrees of Santa,
a delightful, if mysterious,
gift chain I found online.
Check it out!"
Isn't that what
they call trending?
Huh? I know I've said it before,
but I really feel like you could
go big with this.
I don't think that counts
as trending, Mom.
You know what,
I've said it before,
small and personal,
you know? Almost renegade!
That's the whole point.
I don't mean big
like corporate partner.
I'm saying big, like,
get some momentum behind it.
Find a way to get paid for it.
Why? Are you firing me?
No, I like having
you around too much.
But your skills
are being underserved.
What? Working with my mom
in our family company
and getting to spend
more time with my daughter?
I'd say that counts
as fulfilling.
I suppose I'm also saying,
who knows how much longer
this will be around.
Do you mean that in
the philosophical sense or...
Mom, are you worried?
Your father was...
better at the business side
of things.
December just started.
It's our busiest time.
We just need a banner
sale season. We'll be okay.
Okay.
So, what do we need
for a big banner sale season?
A rush of Christmas spirit!
Luck.
Oh, before you settle in,
can you walk these packages
over to Gus?
Please!
- Sure, Mom.
- Thank you!
Mm-hmm!
Alright, let's hear it,
people, let's hear it.
Hi, everyone.
Thank you so much for coming.
Lovely to see you all.
Now, I am beyond thrilled
to bring my tech brand
into the real world
and into your living rooms
on Christmas morning with...
SparkLTree!
Partnering with farmers,
we have engineered
what we believe to be
the perfect Christmas tree.
From branch distribution,
shape, and needle retention,
right down to that magnificent
conifer scent.
Now, it comes in three sizes,
but most importantly,
it can be delivered
to your front door
with the very simple
click of a button.
Are you ready?
- Hey, Hal.
- Hey.
What's all this?
Oh, it's a Christmas tree
you order online.
Apparently it's perfect.
Ugh! Jason Sparks.
Of course he thinks he can
invade and commodify Christmas.
Oh, I'd suppose you've known him
from your Silicon Valley days.
Yeah, I worked for him.
Well, I mean,
for one of his companies.
I... I didn't know him.
He's more of a looming presence.
Now just think, no more
laborious trips to the farm,
having to strap your tree
to the roof of your car,
scratching the paint.
And if you live in the City,
imagine not having to haul
your cumbersome Christmas trees
seven city blocks,
only to have it poke you
and give you splinters,
sap all over your hands,
needles everywhere.
You gotta love how he pretends
like he's doing it
for our well-being.
Eh, he's always been nice to me.
You would buy one
of those things?
Yeah! I mean, look at it.
It's a good-looking tree!
But what about
your trip to Watson's Farm
with Jeanie and the kids, huh?
And hot cocoa in travel mugs?
Uh, maybe we could just stay in,
watch A Christmas Carol instead?
I don't believe it.
To be continued!
Alright. Have a good one.
Right to your front door.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
Are you going
to get a SparkLTree?
No.
Oh. You don't celebrate
Christmas. I'm so sorry,
I shouldn't assume.
Oh, no, no.
I celebrate Christmas.
I adore Christmas.
But I also adore
real Christmas trees.
SparkLTrees are real
Christmas trees.
Also, personally, you know,
I enjoy carrying my tree
back those seven blocks
from the tree lot.
You know,
a family-owned business,
something that is practically disappearing.
And if the tree wants
to poke me with its needles,
well, I welcome it!
Sorry, do I know you?
Have I done something
to offend you?
Why bother growing
living things at all, right?
Why not just skip ahead to,
I don't know,
a Christmas tree hologram
that you can decorate
from your tablet?
That's...
not a bad idea, actually.
That would be
really good for travel. Hmm...
Okay, why are you trying
to take the heart
and magic out of Christmas?
I think you're making a lot
of assumptions about this tree.
Tell you what, how about I send
you one, on the house?
You might change your mind.
I would send it back.
Merry Christmas.
Good morning, sir.
Quick question for you, Elliott.
Yeah, go ahead. Shoot, Boss.
Do you think the SparkLTree
brand fails
to exude magic and heart?
Uh, I'd say it piggybacks
off the inherent magic
and heart of the season?
We did have that focus group.
So... this is your
forwarded mail.
I checked for anything
time sensitive.
I also wasn't sure
whether to pass this one along.
It looks great.
Happy.
I suppose it was only
a matter of time.
Um, look up their registry
and send them something nice.
Sure.
Come in!
Hey, you!
Hey! Happy December, Harper.
Happy December to you too!
Dani, your dad's here!
And you guys better get moving.
Yeah.
Hey, I saw Six Degrees posted.
Yes! You know, look what
I found for my gift this year.
- Wow!
- Mm-hmm!
And... you're going
to give it away?
Well, yeah. I mean, it's the
perfect thing for Six Degrees.
You know, nobody knows it,
so it's new,
but it's also timeless.
And, you know, it's about
human connection.
It basically inspired
the whole thing.
What's up?
Speaking of human connection,
I've met somebody.
And I really feel like
it's going to go somewhere.
Her name's Sylvia.
And I wanted to introduce her
to Dani but I wanted
to talk to you first.
I trust your timing
and judgment.
I'm happy for you.
How about you?
Anything going on
in that department?
No. Nope, no.
I'm, uh...
I'm putting all of that
on the back burner...
Hey, Dad!
Hey, look at you!
Are we excited
for The Nutcracker?
So excited!
See, I wonder if he'll beat
the Mouse King this year.
Dad! He always does.
Come on, let's go.
Dear Santas,
this book holds a special
place in my heart.
I decided to go with
the Jingle Mice record.
Oh, that's perfect!
Do you know how many people
are going to be listening
to your favourite
Christmas music?
And, uh, do you have
a Santa #2 in mind?
There's this new girl
in my class.
She's really shy. How about you?
You know, this year,
I think I'm going
to be in the moment,
go where inspiration takes me!
Good morning, Leonard!
Good morning, you two!
Oh, it's the start
of your busy season, huh?
Yes, but I love it.
It probably sounds
kind of cheesy,
but this time of year,
it feels extra special
to be the person who connects
the people with the packages.
And cards.
It makes me feel
like a V.I.P.
- Mm-hmm!
- Very important postman!
Huh...
Hey, come on,
let's read the book.
Jump up.
Yeah.
What are these people doing?
Thank you.
And this is for you.
♪ Craving to hold your hand
♪ Six degrees of love
♪ Coming from different worlds
♪ Still would feel the same
♪ Six degrees from us
This is for Mr. Sparks.
He gets to keep it!
So, Christmas
is fast approaching,
but we are pretty much
wrapped on SparkLTree.
Um... We deployed the updates
to the companion app.
Music Department has added
a few extra playlists.
For example,
"Music to open presents to."
And, of course, there's tree
care, wrapping tips, et cetera.
So, uh, we should be all
good to go for your hiatus.
Hiatus...
Oh, there was this bake sale
sponsorship for a local high
school basketball team
coming this Saturday night.
It's really small scale.
I'm not even sure how
the request got through.
Do you just want
me to cancel on that...
No.
That would go against the sincere,
down-to-earth vibe we're going for.
No, put Fabian on it.
You can coordinate remotely.
Okay.
Are you sure I should be
heading to Vermont tomorrow?
Enjoy your time
with your family.
I mean, don't forget
to take notes on the authentic
family Christmas
for SparkLTree 2.0.
But you haven't spent Christmas
with your family in three years.
I feel like it's something
you should do, yeah.
Uh, is everything okay?
I think so.
Just that off feeling, you know?
Mmm. I'm sure
it's your open calendar.
You're not used to it.
I think it's a good thing.
I mean, everyone needs
to take time off at some point.
And Christmas is as good
a time as any to...
Reminds me, um, that box over
there is an actual present.
Yeah, Hal passed it along,
said some boy who's a fan
wanted to give it to you.
Thank you.
Dear Santas,
this book holds a special place
in my heart.
My father gave me a copy
when I was a child.
I miss him so much,
especially this time of year.
But the very book he gave me
always reminds me
that there is love and
connection to be had everywher.
Maybe even right
around the corner.
I wish all of this for you.
Yours, Ms. Santa #1.
This very book,
it was like a lifeline for me
when I was young.
My family, they moved constantly
and my uncle got this for me
to remind me that home didn't
necessarily need to be a place.
I lost my copy and I've been
looking for one ever since.
And then it just shows up!
And the note on the inside...
it feels like it was
written by me, or for me.
So... are we looking into
a publishing venture or...
The fact that this found me at a
time where I'm taking a break to...
process how I'm feeling
about my ex getting married.
So, are we looking
to get back into dating apps?
Cancelling your hiatus?
This isn't about the company.
All I know is...
when I read this note
in this book,
I felt something
I haven't felt in years.
With all those
coincidences lining up,
I feel like it would
be negligent not to follow
the data,
to see where this leads.
I have to find, to meet...
Ms. Santa #1.
I just have to say,
a few of us have really been
rooting for you to get back
out there, sir.
Okay, it looks like
this is the website.
It's like a chain letter,
but with gifting?
It is pretty clever,
if underdeveloped.
There's gotta be some kind
of social media component
for all these Santas
to meet each other.
Uh, I don't see anything.
Let's watch this video.
Hello, everyone, and welcome
to Six Degrees of Santa.
It's December first...
Wait a second.
I've met this woman!
Yeah, didn't she used
to work for us?
Wait, what?
I saw that you put
in for more boxes.
Are you still shipping
those out, free of charge?
Yeah! You know,
I actually mailed one off
to Skagway, Alaska
the other day. Yeah!
That's gotta start
adding up, sweetheart.
Well, you know,
sometimes people choose
to spend their money going
to Aspen for the holidays,
but this is how
I choose to spend mind.
Plus, you know,
it drives foot traffic
to the store, so I think
it's win-win.
Harper McNevin.
You used to work for me.
Hmm, yeah, have you popped by
for a forgotten
performance review?
Hi, I'm Jason Sparks.
Oh, I know! Hi.
I'm Pauline, Harper's mother.
This is Elliott,
my executive assistant.
I looked into it.
You were one of our most
promising programmers.
You designed Sugar Share,
charming neighborhood sharing app.
Yeah, which your VP
of Business Development squelched
because it didn't have enough
profit potential.
Yeah, that happens.
Why are you here?
Uh... and how did you find me?
Well, as a matter of fact,
I am a Santa #6 in
your Six Degrees of Santa chain.
Your video indicated
I might find you here,
and well, I was hoping you could
help me locate my original Santa.
This is the gift I received.
Would you look at that!
That's...
A book. Yeah, Mom.
It's a book that I've never
seen before in my life.
So why do you have to find
this original Santa?
Well, it's important to me.
This book was a childhood
favourite of mine.
That, along with the note
written on the inside the cover,
well, it made me think
that we might possibly
share a...
a connection.
You mean like romantically?
Possibly. Maybe.
Listen, I got a gut-feeling
and I simply can't ignore it.
Huh... I'm going to go inside.
I'm sure that I heard the phone.
Well, I can't help you.
The spirit of Six Degrees
is one of anonymity.
Well, speaking of that,
I actually have an enticing
thing to offer you in return.
See, I think Six Degrees
has a lot of potential.
Not interested.
I could help you make it
a household name,
along the lines
of "White Elephant."
We could loop in
investors, sponsors.
And we just got
that quick analysis back.
It would be an advantageous
follow up to SparkLTree.
Definitely not interested.
That's not what
the site's about.
Though, I don't recall
seeing a copyright.
Which means there's
nothing to stop us from
just taking off with it anyway.
Is that a threat?
No, I'm just thinking out loud.
There's gotta be some way
I can convince you to help me
find Ms. Santa #1.
Wait, which is it that you
want? Ms. Santa or Six Degrees?
Well, both.
I'm just hoping we could make a
deal, you know, help each other.
If you really want
to help people,
maybe help some
of the small businesses
that your industry
is destroying.
You mean like this one?
Sure! Easy-peasy.
I'll tell you what.
You help me find
Ms. Santa #1,
I'll help with your foot traffic
and marketing.
McNevin Paper Company
will see unprecedented sales.
Well, I mean, what if we can't
find Ms. Santa #1?
You know, or we do
and she's like 99 years old
or, you know, loathes
your very existence?
I mean, do our terms
still stand?
Sure. I don't think it'll
be any of those scenarios.
Okay, so to confirm,
you help boost McNevin Paper
Company sales,
and you leave Six Degrees alone.
No push for growth from you
or any of your companies.
This is the weirdest deal
I've ever made.
Oh, just promise!
I promise.
It's a deal.
Elliott.
So you made a deal
with him to find you.
Correct.
Look, I was this whirlwind
of confusion!
You know, at first, I wanted
to protect Six Degrees,
but then he mentioned helping
the shop,
and I was mad I didn't
think of it first.
Well, you have been known
to occasionally miss
the forest for the trees.
Mmm... For the SparkLTrees.
- Option one...
- Yeah.
You come clean
and you tell him that
the mystery match is you.
Just see where it goes!
No! Definitely not.
Everything about him goes against
everything that I care about.
And I feel it would
nullify the deal.
You know, why work up all of these
terms only to turn around and say,
"Hey, guess what? It's me!
Pay up now!"
No, that would never fly.
And you know I'm not
dating right now.
It's quite the pickle.
Mm-hmm.
No, except, maybe not!
You know, these tech guys are
always looking for a new project,
and then, within 48 hours,
they lose interest and move on.
So I'm counting on that.
No, I'm not interested
in buying more followers.
That's so cringe.
The only thing that concerns
me is finding something
for him to lose interest in.
You could just hire an actor
to play Ms. Santa #1.
Yeah, maybe someone
looking for a little publicity?
Ah...
You hang out with him once,
maybe twice,
you know, take some selfies,
create some hashtags.
It will boost your online
presence exponentially.
And it doesn't have to be
more than one day, maybe two.
Unless you want it to be more?
Nah, he's not my type.
I mean, he's objectively handsome in a "pulling
off a turtleneck" sort of way. But no.
I won't have to break up
with him, will I?
Um, no. No.
I guarantee that
he will lose interest.
Not because of you!
But because...
the tech lizard brain.
Look, I know that this lie
may be a little dicey.
Are you kidding me?
With all the hijinks that get
bandied about in the online
dating world, this is nothing!
Well, I prefer to see it as
an acceptable white lie
that helps multiple
small businesses.
All you have to do is pretend
to be Santa #1.
This is your roadmap.
You love this book.
And I will text you
what I wrote in the front cover.
Is there a chance that he can
discover that it's really you?
No, no!
Slim. Yeah.
But he'd basically have to track
back through all of the Santas,
and that's the beauty
of this plan,
because even if he does,
Santa #2 was Leonard,
our mailman! So, we're covered!
Sounds easy enough!
What's the next step?
Admiring your work?
Just thinking ahead
to SparkLTree 2.0.
Ooh! That sounds
Christmas magical.
It is magical.
Here, this is for you.
Is this part of our deal?
No, it's just
a nice thing to do.
Hmm.
This is peppermint.
I saw on your Swift-Gram
that you like the peppermint
coffee from the kiosk
downstairs. I'm thorough.
You seem to have
a certain idea of me.
But that's okay.
The lower your opinion is of me,
the more impressive it will be
when I become...
impressive.
Well, this impressive
journey will be brief.
Good news! I found
Ms. Santa #1!
Yeah, I was able to track
her back through the website
and, you know,
it's a crazy coincidence,
because I actually know her.
Yeah! She's my neighbour!
Well, maybe not that crazy
a coincidence,
since, you know,
most of the people that use
Six Degrees of Santa
are people that I know
because my website is so
underdeveloped, like you said.
Her name is Zoey.
I will send you her number.
And yeah, good luck with that.
I'll be in touch about
my side of the deal.
- Wait!
- What?
That can't be it.
I mean, especially since
you know her.
You gotta give me
some details here.
I mean, what does she like?
Well, she's public on all
her social media platforms,
so, you know, figure her out,
like you did
with the peppermint coffee.
Isn't that how we learn
about each other these days?
But that's not your philosophy.
That's okay. You do you.
Also, this doesn't seem
like a very good deal for me.
You just give me a phone number,
and then I help rescue
your family business?
Rise from the ashes?
Completely save it? No.
Why don't you come with me
and we'll scope out
the situation a little?
Maybe we can even organize
one of those quirky run-ins
that they do in the movies,
you know?
- A meet-cute?
- Sure.
How can you be one of
the most successful people
in the world and not know
what that is?
Can't your assistant help you?
I gave him time off
for the holiday.
Fine, yeah. Fine.
But you know what?
I need to call my mom first.
- Sure.
- Yeah.
- Tell her I say hello.
- Mmm, not likely.
Oh man...
Zoey, hey, okay,
bear with me here.
We're going to need
to add a little theatre.
She teaches workout classes,
she's some kind of influencer,
and she also sells
artwork on Craft-Zalea.
So she's really into
the gig economy,
so you'll have lots
to talk about.
She is quite pretty.
Well, that's a win-win!
And I also know from her feed
that she often comes here
for a snack after teaching
a Pilates class.
So, you know, we just have
to keep a lookout
and maybe we can stage one of
those so-called quirky run-ins.
Maybe you can bump into
each other,
or you both reach for the
last pastry at the same time.
Maybe the coffee spilling thing?
That's usually pretty cute, no?
No?
No. Definitely not.
Do you think I should tell
her the whole truth?
Like, that I sought her out?
Well, uh, it depends.
You know what? Maybe the fewer
the charades, the better.
See, this is what I don't
get about Six Degrees of Santa.
Here you have
an opportunity for a genuine,
charade-free connection,
and your system
literally prevents that.
It's not a matchmaking service.
You know, I actually
had a dream about
Six Degrees last night.
Sometimes I have these
creative problem-solving dreams.
Will you please stop dreaming
about my website?
But it has so much
untapped potential.
Mmm, not your problem!
Oh, no. I need
to get a napkin.
I will go. You stay here
and keep an eye out for Zoey.
And you know, please,
stop dreaming about my website.
Oh!
Harper? My neighbour?
Is that you?
Zoey!
- Here, here.
- What are you doing here?
Use this.
No, it's too nice.
It's fine, here.
Hi. I'm Jason.
I'm Zoey.
Hi, Zoey.
Um...
Smells good.
So, are you new to...
Yeah, just around the corner.
I teach dance fitness
and yoga. That's where I was.
O-M-G! Harper,
you will not believe
what we just discovered!
What did you just discover?
Jason and I here are part
of the same Six Degrees Chain...
that I started with a book
called Neighbourhood Elf.
Northbound Elf.
Right!
I'm just shaken up about
the bizarreness
of this coincidence!
We should commemorate
this moment.
- Yeah.
- Oh, sure, yeah. Okay.
So, I was thinking about
the different variations
of this Six Degrees
of Santa thing,
and so there were four other
people in our gift chain.
'I wonder who they were.
Well, I know one.
Our mailman,
Leonard, was Santa #2,
so that's something.
That is something.
That's a great scarf.
- Oh, you like it?
- Yeah.
It's one of mine.
I mean, I designed it.
I have a store on Craft-Zalea.
Oh, yes. Harper mentioned
that you were working
the gig economy.
The shop is called Zo-Brad,
'cause my name is Zoey Bradford
but no "E" or "Y".
In case you wanted to
check it out, or mention it,
or hashtag it.
Yeah, sure.
Yeah, I can get
my social media manager on it,
and get you a mention or two.
Yeah.
So... Northbound Elf.
It seems like it really
meant a lot to you.
Totally. Yes.
There's this part when
Elfie is in Machu Picchu,
and I was like...
I need to travel more!
That's, uh...
a worthwhile goal.
Cheers.
Look, this woman
had a great idea!
She said, "This year, I gifted
a set of cookie cutters
and my grandma's cookie recipe.
It felt like keeping her love
alive and spreading it around.
Thank you for making
this happen."
Do you want to read
the next one?
Where is Kolkata?
What?!
It's in India.
It's from a young man
named Arjun.
He's wondering how his gift...
a snow globe from St. Louis
made it all the way to him,
and he wants to start
his own chain.
Can you get him a box in time?
Oh, I don't think so, but...
Well, what do you think we
should do, business partner?
Could he make his own box?
Great idea. I'll let him know.
I finally fixed
the ordering page!
Oh, my hero!
Oh! You practising
for the party tonight?
I thought you were representing us in
the wrapping competition this year.
No, it's your turn.
One sec.
Oh! So, how did the date go?
I thought I did my job.
It was just bad enough,
kept it believable.
I really played up
the insincere influencer thing.
Zero chemistry.
Good. Good, good, good.
Yes. Except he scheduled
a second date, for tonight!
I don't know if he thought
it went well, or...?
Oh. Well, I mean, did you
at least get an online boost?
Such a boost!
Everything's gone nuts.
I have all these orders,
so now I'm, like, overbooked.
I don't know what to do about
this second date.
Do I go and act horribly?
Chew with my mouth open?
Let me...
see what I can do on my end.
Okay.
Um, wrapping paper malfunction.
Good morning, you two!
Here you go.
- Hi! Oh, thanks!
- You're welcome.
Please, feel free to browse.
We have a friends
and family discount.
So, how did the date go?
The date was... not great.
Oh! Well, I'm sorry
to hear that.
But I've already gone ahead
and scheduled a second date.
You know, at first I was
a little irked that it seemed
like she was just using me to
boost her social media presence.
But then I thought, why be offended
by her being a savvy business woman?
When I brought up
Northbound Elf, yeah,
her response was a little flip,
but why should I expect
her to open up right away?
On command, you know?
That's actually a very mature
way of looking at things.
But didn't you have
one of those popular Life-Talks?
You know, about sunken costs
and minimizing wasted time?
I mean, if the first date
did not work, why not move on?
That's what I used to do,
just move on to the next thing.
But if this connection
felt different, then shouldn't
I approach it differently?
I don't know, I...
I just don't want you
to get hurt.
Oh, no way!
Roller skates?
Do you sell these?
No, those are mine.
And no, we do not sell them.
Okay, quick Six Degrees
question for you.
Why stop at number six?
Well, that's the saying,
isn't it?
"Six degrees of separation."
You know, and the box
won't last forever.
And aren't you supposed to be one
of the busiest people in the world?
I mean, how do you have time to,
you know, hang out
and critique my hobby?
Oh, well, I am on hiatus.
Yeah, I'm taking a break
from work for the first
time in years.
Oh!
Now it all makes sense.
You're not looking for love.
You are looking
for a new project!
And maybe that's something
that I can help you with.
You know, we can spitball
some ideas, huh?
I mean, why don't we revisit
the Christmas tree hologram
that I pitched you
in the elevator?
Yeah? Or, um... I mean,
what is the SparkLTree
of Valentine's Day?
How about we discuss
the sales makeover
I had planned for this place?
Sure, yeah.
Talk to me. Where do we start?
Done. I just dropped you
the SparkLTree companion app.
There's a new feature
on the McNevin Paper Company.
I filed it under
gift wrapping ideas.
I thought that was
the perfect home for it.
I just, I thought we were
working on this together.
You know, I have to admit,
this is... it's not bad.
But this seems very generous.
Oh, it's Zoey. She just
cancelled our date tonight.
You know what?
Maybe the significance of all
of this is that your heart
is open.
You know? So why don't you
try online dating, huh?
That's a project!
Oh, can you believe
Haley just cancelled?
You're going to have to find
somebody else to compete against.
Well, unless Jason could do it.
Uh, I do have
the night free now.
Can we really invite
Jason Sparks to a small business
Christmas party
for local businesses?
Yeah, that is a pickle.
Oh, heck. Let's just
put him in a disguise!
Ho-ho-ho! Merry Christmas!
- Hey, Mom!
- Hey, honey! Ooh!
Who is this?
Oh! Why, I'm Santa, of course.
This is Jason, he is a...
a work colleague?
This is my daughter, Dani.
Hi, Dani. It's very
nice to meet you.
Now, tell me, how were
my Santa belly laughs?
And be honest,
on a scale of one to ten?
Uh, maybe five.
Geez, tough crowd.
Well, I appreciate your honesty.
Maybe I'll even hire you
on as a Santa consultant.
We could use somebody
like you around.
I hope everyone is enjoying
this celebration of Christmas
and local small business!
As many of you know,
we have our traditional
gift wrapping tournament,
sponsored by the McNevin
Paper Company!
The McNevin family
is being represented
by my daughter Harper this year,
who will compete against
a customary celebrity guest.
And this year,
our celebrity is Santa Claus!
Ho-ho-ho-ho-ho!
Thank you, young lady.
You've been a good girl
this year.
Oh! Well, competitors
will be judged on speed,
technique, and creativity!
Thank you.
You know, I hope you're ready
for defeat.
I grew up in this industry,
so, I was somewhat
of a wunderkind and I've
only improved from there.
You know, I'm not so bad myself.
It's all about making
shapes and forms,
and my visuospatial ability
is unparalleled.
And go!
♪ It's that time of year
♪ Santa comes
to bring that cheer ♪
Your side, please.
Oh, it's on.
♪ He's loaded down
with candy canes ♪
♪ I only hope he keeps
one open seat, oh yeah ♪
♪ Come on, Santa,
bring those toys ♪
And time!
Ooh!
Go!
♪ On Christmas Eve
♪ Let's hope
the weather's good ♪
♪ And his elf flight crew
finds my neighbourhood ♪
And time!
Winner.
♪ This year he's gonna
use the door ♪
♪ I'm begging please
keep an open seat, oh yeah ♪
Ha, ha!
♪ All the presents
for the girls and boys ♪
What?!
Ho-ho-ho, everybody wins
on Christmas!
There has been
a noticeable increase
in our online sales
for the last few hours.
Well, that must be from Jason
putting us up on his app.
Oh, tech mogul who's actually
good at what he does.
I didn't know that Zoey
was coming.
Yeah...
I forgot I invited her,
otherwise I would have
warned Jason.
She stood him up today.
Wasn't that basically your plan?
Uh, yea... yeah...
I mean... but it's awkward.
I'm beginning to feel guilty.
What do you think would happen
if I told him?
There's only one way
to find out.
That was really fun.
Yes.
- One Santa suit.
- Ah.
And one... sweater.
Thank you.
- I have to tell you something...
- So, I came clean... Oh.
- You go.
- I just wanted to tell you
that Zoey apologized for
cancelling our date earlier.
So, feeling inspired,
I came clean that I sought
her out as Miss Santa #1.
And I told her that you were
kind enough to help me out.
Wow. That's...
That's great news.
It must feel really good
to get that off your chest.
Yeah. Yeah.
She took it surprisingly well.
She wasn't even mad at all.
You know, like, yes,
I wish that we had connected
more on our date,
but it's just that gut-feeling
I got from the book
and... I just feel like
I have to see it through,
you know?
You gotta follow
that gut-feeling, I guess.
Yeah.
Uh, so sorry, what were
you gonna say earlier?
Oh, um, yeah, I wanted to say...
thank you.
You've been a lot of help today
and my mom says that online
sales are definitely up.
So...
Well, you're welcome.
You know, I really meant it when
I said you had beautiful store.
I love this place,
so, I'm happy to help.
If only we could find out
how the present
made it halfway
across the world.
You know how this works:
Anonymous Christmas magic.
I just wish Arjun in India
could talk to a Santa #1
about St. Louis.
Or that one dad could send
the thank you note
about the ukulele
that changed his son's life.
Finish getting ready, okay?
We gotta get you to school.
I think I may actually
like Jason.
Come on in.
I mean, I don't...
not like him in an epic way.
I felt bad about cancelling,
so I came to your party
to cheer myself up,
not knowing he'd be there.
Then... I saw him.
And then there
was something lively.
And maybe something
sweet about him?
Something I missed earlier?
I suppose he's had a few
surprising moments.
Right?!
Anyway, I don't know
if this is good or bad,
cause... you know?
The web of lies.
No, I think that this
is great news.
And if it does work out
with you two, then...
The book did bring you together,
just indirectly.
And this is a thing we review...
down the road?
We cannot deny,
Jason really helped us.
He did.
You didn't tell him, did you?
I couldn't.
I just saw how earnest
he is in his pursuit,
and... I chickened out.
Plus, you know, Zoey says
she may actually be into him.
So, if I told him the truth,
I could ruin things
for both of them.
So, is that it then?
The deal is all done?
Well, he helped us out.
He left Six Degrees alone and...
maybe I didn't connect him
to the real Miss Santa #1...
- You.
- Yes, but I did provide him
with a connection.
A better one, so...
He helped McNevin Paper Company.
Maybe when everything
slows down,
you bring him some of those
pastries you brought in.
A good old-fashioned
thank you, hmm?
Yeah.
Wow, you are bad
at being on hiatus.
Come in.
Yeah, I um...
I don't know where else to go.
Really?
With all your resources?
So, are things back up
and running with Zoey?
Yes, yes. We are getting
dinner tonight, actually.
Good.
The book that started it all.
Ah, Luminarias.
You know it means illumination?
Did you know the tradition
stems from small fires
used to guide scouts
and spirits home?
I did.
- Hmm.
- You should read it.
Borrow it and take it home
to Dani.
Uh, well, the reason
I texted you
is I wanted to bring you
these as a thank you.
Sales are definitely up.
Oh, that's great, thank you.
What are they?
They're kidyos.
It's an east Indian
Christmas dessert.
Dani and I, we have
this little project,
we read emails we get
from Six Degree Santas,
and when we get one
from somewhere new,
we look up their traditions
and we make something.
And Dani's in charge,
so it's usually sweets.
Oh, wow, these are really good.
Mm-hmm.
Okay, okay, fine.
Fine, let's take a stab
at improving
Six Degrees together.
What? Really?
Wait, are you making a joke?
No, it's...
Something Dani said
made me reconsider and...
Well, I suppose you had
a few good points...
- Mm, yes!
- here and there.
Are you fist pumping
because you're excited
about connecting people,
or because you think you won
an ongoing argument?
Can't it be both?
Dani, hurry up please!
I gotta go!
Wow, you put the tree up.
Ah, yeah.
Uh, thanks for doing this
so last minute,
I only need half a day,
so I can pick up Dani
on the way back.
Uh, no worries.
I think it's cool that
you're beefing up Six Degrees.
Oh, well, let's not get
ahead of ourselves,
but maybe.
Uh, quick question.
You wouldn't happen to be collaborating
with this fellow, would you?
I've seen that look.
I...
I can't believe you
even follow him.
Well, he has good
life hacking tips.
All I'm saying...
is that I'm sensing a new kind
of energy from you right now.
It's either this new project,
or Santa Claus here, or both.
Hey, either way,
you should let yourself have it.
Like I said the day,
I'm putting all of that
on the back-burner.
And either way,
it's a non-starter,
because he's dating
my neighbour.
Oh.
I think a wall would be
a good middle ground
for people to post publicly,
similarly that they would
a product review,
do you know what I mean?
Like, "Hey, loved
the reindeer sock puppet,
would Santa #1
like to come forward?"
You know?
Yeah, but that's where
the whole social media
element could go wrong,
you know? It could lead
to competing and outdoing...
Is that Zoey?
No, it's, um,
it's Fabian Lambert,
you know, the celebrity chef?
I hired him for a bake sale fundraiser
for this high school
basketball team,
no cause too small.
No, Zoey is away for the day,
she's doing some
Business Ladies Who Craft,
or something? I don't know.
I'm sorry, what were you saying?
Yeah, um, right. Um, okay...
So what if you're a young girl
who gets gifted,
um, you know, a hacky sack?
And then you look online
and then you start to see the...
I am so sorry.
Let me just finish this up
and we can focus, okay?
Sure.
Hey, what flavour
sounds better to you,
lavender or cardamom?
For a Christmas thing?
I'll just tell him to do both.
Ooh, how about this?
Maple gelatin caviar?
That seems kind of seasonal, right?
For a bake sale.
Why are you getting
molecular gastronomy
involved in this?
It's just what Fabian does.
It'll be very
high-profile stuff.
It's for a high school
bake sale.
I mean, what is it that
you've been going for
brand-wise lately?
Down to earth and sincere?
Uh-huh.
I've got a great idea.
Get your coat.
Trust me, this is going
to be great marketing.
For this bake sale,
Jason Sparks doesn't just
throw money at it, no, no,
he puts his back into it.
He's just like us.
Well, that's great,
but cooking isn't exactly
in my skill set.
Hmm. Well, I'm gonna teach you
how to make my dad's molasses
spice cookies.
They're world-famous.
And my world famous I mean that
they are Dani's favourite, so...
You have to wear this.
Okay.
Thank you.
Not bad, not bad. Okay.
So with this, you want to stir
it seven times clockwise
and three times
counter-clockwise
and repeat it four times.
Uh, okay...
Hey, wait a second! You guys
are pulling my leg, I knew it.
Okay, so then you're gonna
use spoons...
Yeah, put your back into it.
That's it.
And right next to it?
Actually, if you turn this
upside down, then right side up,
you get more cookies.
Oh, clever.
Alright. Sweetie,
it's time for you to go
get ready for your
grandma's sleepover.
And yes, you can take
some cookies with you.
Thanks, Mom.
Hey, you know what? I think
we made some darn good cookies
here tonight, let's have it,
up top, come on.
Alright. Oh yeah, yeah,
there we go.
It was really nice hanging out
with Dani today.
Isn't she the best?
She is.
Thank you.
As a matter of fact,
I'm thinking of recruiting her
as my decorative consultant
for SparkLTree 2.0.
Well, good luck with that,
you know,
because she's an artist,
so her approach is pure
and can't be commercialized.
We'll see about that.
So, um...
is Dani's father in the picture?
Yeah, Derrick.
Um, actually, he lives
in New York City
and he's one of the reasons
that we moved back here.
And you guys get along,
you're doing
the co-parenting thing?
Yeah, we do.
And you know, we were just
better off as friends and...
well, we respect each other,
and I...
I think that's important.
So...
what about you?
What's your story?
Um...
Well, uh,
I suppose I used to spend
a lot of time bouncing
from project to project,
and with my relationships,
I was always weighing
the risks versus reward.
And often it seemed easier
to just move on.
But then you begin to realize
that something's missing,
which is why I had such
a strong reaction
to Northbound Elf
showing up in my life again.
You know what's odd?
I still don't really feel
that Zoey matches the book
or the feeling in the note
and certainly not
the feeling I had
when the book showed up
on my doorstep. I mean...
Listen, I know how silly
this sounds, all this
over a children's book.
No, it's not.
It's not silly.
Actually, um...
I have to tell you something.
Um, I know Northbound Elf.
Yeah, it was an important part
of my childhood too.
It inspired Six Degrees
a little.
I guess what I'm trying
to say is,
when you talk about
how important it is to you,
I understand.
Why didn't you tell me this?
Well, I suppose I didn't see
you as an ally at first.
I mean, why would I share
that part of myself with you?
I can understand that.
But you know, for somebody
who has a lot to say
about human connection,
you sure do keep a lot
about yourself under lockdown.
Might be something
I have to work on, I guess.
So, Mr. Big Tech Entrepreneur
who, you know, occasionally
burns batches of cookies.
Um...
what do you say we have
a little fun?
So, roller-skating, huh?
Not ice skating?
Isn't that more seasonal?
Well, this is indoors,
therefore, anytime.
You know, I used to skate around
this store when I was younger,
but then I remembered this place
and that you have
nighttime access.
I see.
We can skate through a forest
of Christmas trees.
SparkLTrees.
Yeah, SparkLTrees.
We should play some music.
SparkLTree comes with a free app
featuring such things
as tree care instructions
and such playlists as
"Music to Open Presents to."
Ooh.
"Dancing around
the Christmas Tree."
Mm-hmm.
"Falling in Love
at Christmas."
You should save
that one for Zoey.
Okay.
So, I know this
is supposed to be
a stress-relieving activity,
so I promise not to make fun
of you if you wobble,
as long as you promise
not to make fun of my wobbles.
Yeah?
- Deal.
I can see why you would make
assumptions about me
given that I am
a techie-numbers guy.
- Mm-hmm.
- And by numbers guy I mean...
number one skater
in the entire lobby.
Whew.
What?!
You tricked me.
- You underestimated me.
- Seems I have.
Okay.
Okay, what you got then?
Yeah?
Come on, here we go.
There we go.
There you go, there you go.
Whew!
Go on, then.
I'll spin around ya.
- Yeah?
- Whew!
Oh!
Ah!
Are you happy?
Happy holidays!
We hope you enjoyed this music
along with your SparkLTree,
and that you sparkle
all the way.
I wanted your opinion
on something
as a potential
SparkLTree customer.
Okay, not even a potential
SparkLTree customer,
but how can I help?
I thought we'd do a little
quality control check
from this angle.
Well, this is how
the kids see it.
Exactly.
I used to love doing this
when I was a kid.
So, uh,
what made you move
towards agriculture?
What inspired SparkLTree?
My uncle.
Yeah, we were always very close.
In fact, he was the one that
gave me Northbound Elf
when I was a kid.
After my parents passed away
when I was in grad school,
he became the family that
I would spend Christmas with.
One year, I visited him
on Christmas Eve.
And I had been working
like crazy,
he had hurt his back
and he was living alone
and didn't have
a Christmas tree.
It broke my heart.
I started thinking, if we can
get everything else delivered,
then why not a Christmas tree?
And not just if you live
near a farm, you know?
So, I partnered
with some farmers
who were struggling
to stay in business
and invited them to participate.
Worked out well for everyone.
What... So, SparkLTrees
actually helps the farmers?
Yeah, of course.
I needed their skills
and they were helped by mine.
Wow.
Here I was, being such a...
brat...
about everything.
It's fine, I'm used
to people jumping
to the worst conclusions.
You know, the other beautiful
thing about SparkLTree?
It's extremely profitable
as an untapped part
of the Christmas market.
Oh... You-
It's Zoey.
Well, that's... that's good.
That's a good thing.
We should probably
call it a night.
Okay, regarding Six Degrees,
and I know I'm supposed
to be on hiatus here.
I don't know how to explain it,
this feels personal.
Fun, I mean...
It feels like a field trip.
I don't know.
Okay, do you want me
to have Leon start
printing you out the paperwork?
Yes, but not
the typical paperwork.
I'd like to get the copyright
process started,
fast-tracked out if possible.
So, we are looking
at a takeover?
No. No, no, no.
This is just protective.
And find a team of coders
looking to make
some holiday pay.
I'll also keep trying to track
down copies of Northbound Elf.
Is it okay for me
to use your handle
to really get it out there?
Yeah, of course.
Although...
may have a better angle.
Hmm.
I couldn't help but notice
that your dad's
molasses spiced cookies
are trending.
What?
Oh, yeah Jason had this
fundraiser emergency,
so I convinced him
to bake himself.
It was fun
watching him try to work
a rolling pin.
Oh, is this part of the deal
or a distraction tactic?
No, it just sort of happened.
I'm letting him help me
with Six Degrees.
You must really trust him.
I do.
I just wish he had a reason
to trust me back.
I wish I'd come clean earlier.
Now I'm in this... pickle,
as you like to say.
It turns out Jason Sparks
is a...
is a good guy.
Earnestly looking
for something real.
What if he has found it?
With the real Miss Santa #1?
What if you went ahead
and told him?
No. If I told him,
he'd be mad, and upset.
And it would ruin
things for everyone.
Him, me, and Zoey.
And I still have Dani
to think of.
You know, what if this journey
of his is...
is just a phase?
You know,
like I originally thought.
Looks like you have thought
of all the possible
bad outcomes.
Which is the sensible thing.
No, I think that this is best.
It means the least number
of people get hurt.
Either way, he'll fall so in
love with Zoey it won't matter.
Or...
He'll forget and move on
to the next thing.
What about your feelings?
I'll get past it.
I have a lot
that's good in life.
That your book,
Northbound Elf,
meant the world
to me when I was young,
and recently came back
into my life in a very...
auspicious and unexpected way.
I have searched high and low
and I am astounded at how hard
it is to find a copy,
and I recently discovered
it's been out of print
since the 90s?
It wasn't a big seller.
Well, let me tell you
from experience,
the world was missing out.
Now, I'm somebody
who's fortunate enough
to be in a position
to bring it back.
And it's actually
gaining momentum
since I posted about it online.
Here, have a look at this.
You're trending.
Do you believe that?
Is this something you might
consider bringing back to life?
This offer's come up before.
And from what I understand,
republishing isn't fiscally advantageous
unless a substantial
part of it is digital.
And that just
doesn't feel right.
I was thinking, print only,
hard back,
for that exact same reason.
- I'm trending, am I?
- Yes, you are.
Gosh, thanks for walking me
all this way.
You're like a real... gentleman.
This is me.
Yes, I know.
I was here the other night,
baking up a storm.
Harper helped you
with that bake sale?
Yeah.
And this whole time I thought
you came with cooking skills.
Guess I usually hire
people for that.
So, um,
I'll see you tomorrow?
Christmas Eve?
- I'd like that.
- Okay.
It's you.
- Yeah, hi.
- Ah.
Oh wait, are you Leonard?
- I certainly am.
- No way,
we were just talking about you.
That's so crazy.
You're like Cupid, you know?
You know, part of
the Six Degrees of Santa chain
that brought us together.
Guilty as charged.
You know, I figured
that out also.
You know, I follow you
on social media.
- Yeah? Oh.
- My son works in tech
so I gotta stay up on things,
you know?
I saw the pictures
of the two of you
and the post about
the Northbound Elf.
I put two and two together.
Santa #2.
I'm glad you found each other,
but you better treat her right,
because she's one
of the good ones.
And her daughter too. So sweet.
Wait, daughter?
- Yeah.
- Who are you talking about?
Uh, Harper
and her daughter Dani.
Oh, yeah, no. Wrong person.
So, uh, Harper started
Six Degrees of Santa,
but the original Santa
in our chain was Zoey.
Okay, I hate to quibble,
but I'm positive.
Yeah, Harper McNevin,
Santa #1 in 32A,
left Northbound Elf
in my car right here.
One sec.
Hello.
Hey.
Harper, it's Elliott,
Jason Spark's assistant.
Yeah, I know who you are.
Um, Merry Christmas Eve Eve.
Sorry, I'm just a little
out of sorts.
Uh... I'm calling because...
Have you by chance spoken
to Jason at all today?
To Jason?
No, no, we haven't spoken
since yesterday.
Maybe he's with Zoey.
Well, I haven't been able
to reach him all evening,
which is unusual, so,
I just started to worry.
Um, if you happen to see him,
can you just tell him
I have a few important updates
on the Six Degrees domain?
Also, he'll definitely be able
to fast-track securing
the copyright, so,
no need to worry about...
Wait, copyright?
From My Six Degrees?
That's the one.
Unless there's two?
No, I never agreed
to any of that.
I can't believe that Jason...
Harper...
So, I guess you're just
gonna do whatever you want
with Six Degrees?
What are you talking about?
Well, Elliott called me,
looking for you,
and I guess, well,
he let the cat out of the bag.
Something about
copyright and Six Degrees.
Wait, look, I know this
may look bad, but it's...
No, I just don't know
what's worse.
If this was part of your plan
all along
or if you just couldn't
help yourself.
I thought we made a deal.
Did we have a deal?
You mean the deal where
you help me find Miss Santa ♪1
and then I help you
with your shop
and leave your site alone?
Well, you didn't hold up
your end of the deal.
So it looks like
we're in a grey area.
Grey area?
No, I connected you to Zoey,
I did my part,
and I found your...
your person.
That's not who you found.
I know Zoey is not
Miss Santa #1.
Okay, yeah, um, you're right.
I'm sorry.
Is there anything else
you'd like to confess?
Yeah, it's just, the thing is...
Um, I thought that
you and Zoey...
I meant to tell you
that it wasn't her.
But then it seemed that you guys
might be good for each other
and... I didn't want
to interfere with that.
And...
you needed me to hold up
my end of the deal.
Yeah. Yeah.
I needed help
with the paper company
and I wanted you to leave
Six Degrees alone.
Well, mission accomplished.
You don't have to worry
about Six Degrees.
I think you should go.
You know, I know I may not
have been on all the up and up.
But Zoey's great.
And I think you deserve
someone great too.
Ooh.
Ah.
Another one for the books.
What are you so absorbed in?
I'm just getting more and more
of these emails
from Six Degrees people.
Like, look!
"Thank you for
the Christmas magic."
"Konichiwa
from Six Degrees Kyoto,
please tell my Santa ♪1
that their gift
changed my life."
I'm seeing now that
there's such a yearning
to connect to each other.
Am I limiting the joy
of this project?
Maybe Jason was right.
I thought he was helping you.
I wasn't really letting him.
We had a big fight.
And mostly because I was trying
to protect Six Degrees,
you know? And for what?
It just seems so silly now.
Now I've missed out
on two great things.
I tell you what
I won't miss out on...
That holiday casserole of yours.
Come on, let's get packed up.
Okay.
And that's how I found out
that you were not Santa #1.
It feels good to have
this weight off my chest.
Also, I'm so sorry about taking
advantage of your social media.
But I gotta say,
it's been life-changing.
It's no problem, really.
And I can keep that up,
it's easy.
You seem off.
Is everything okay?
I mean, the past week
of lies aside.
I know Harper is Miss Santa #1.
What?! No way!
I know.
Now all the weight's
off my chest.
To be fair, we were all
knotted up about it.
At some point,
we just found ourselves
at this point of no return.
Mm-hmm.
Elliott, what are you doing
here?
I am so sorry to interrupt.
I saw this reservation
in your calendar
and you haven't been answering
the phone so I started to worry
but I, uh...
suppose I can see why.
I wanted to make sure
you were alive,
and if you were alive,
which you are,
to tell you that I think
I messed things up with Harper.
I called her to see
if she'd heard from you
and I didn't know
I wasn't supposed to bring up
the copyright.
It's quite alright.
It doesn't matter anymore.
Zoey, this is my executive
assistant Elliott.
Elliott, this is Zoey.
Please, have a seat. Join us.
I thought it was the book that
was supposed to be a secret.
Oh, no, it was supposed to be
a secret from her, wasn't it?
No, no. Harper.
I'm having Northbound Elf
republished in hardback
for Harper.
Wait, it wasn't for Zoey?
Uh, no.
In the end, Harper deceived me,
but it led to you,
me and Zoey here
on this lovely date right now.
But, let's face it,
I'm not the person
you're supposed to be with.
No, no, you are.
You're falling in love
with her, aren't you?
You are falling
in love with Harper!
You and I meant well,
but we have terrible chemistry.
And Northbound Elf
did nothing for me.
Now all the weight's
off my chest.
I'm...
falling in love with Harper.
Oh! Harper's fantastic.
I've been trying to get her
to open herself up to dating
for so long.
You two would be adorbs.
And he's actually
double in love with her,
first as Miss Santa #1,
and now in real life.
Great point, Elliott.
So, what happens now?
Nothing.
She doesn't feel the same way.
She went to the end of the earth
to keep me from finding out...
she was the person
I was actually looking for.
Well, do you think she knows
how you feel about her?
What about the republication,
how did that go over?
It hasn't yet,
I haven't had ti...
I've gotta go.
Um, thank you both.
Elliott, you stay.
Yeah.
Dinner's on me.
- Uh...
- Okay you kids, gotta go.
Good luck! Merry Christmas!
- Cheers.
Hey.
Sylvia's wonderful, Derrick.
I'm partial to her myself.
How are things going
with Santa Claus?
It didn't work out.
And I think it's for the better.
So, uh, I'm to assume
that you headed it off.
And I guess it's safe to assume
that Dani's at least
part of your excuse?
Because the thing
about Dani is...
she's growing up.
She's getting wiser,
more perceptive.
Listen, at some point,
it will be less about
protecting her and more about
setting a good example.
Hey, remember that big fight
we got into in college?
And that big gesture
that I made,
singing to you from your window
of our biology class,
remember that?
Yes.
Right.
Well, I've been outdone.
Santa Claus posted something
that I think you might
be interested in.
Press play.
Yeah.
I'd say it's less
of a business venture
and more of a gift to someone
very important to me.
Because Northbound Elf
is very special to her too.
It's a book about finding home
where you least suspect it.
And I found home with her.
Oh...
I... I've gotta go.
Hi.
Hey.
Is this for Zoey?
No, actually,
it's for Miss Santa #1.
Thought it would remind her
of her favourite part
of her favourite book.
It is.
I'm sorry that
it's not fully wrapped,
I ran out of wrapping paper
and my favourite paper store
was closed early today.
I just saw your post.
It was...
I was inspired.
I need you to know that
I was not after Six Degrees.
I wanted to secure a copyright
but I wanted to do it for you,
to protect your idea.
And...
I also included a prototype.
You can think of it as
a type of scaffolding.
And you can go in there,
and play around,
and change things if you want.
Or nothing at all,
it's up to you.
But, um...
I was just hoping
that we could be partners.
I...
I think you were right
about opening up Six Degrees
and...
I want to do that with you.
I thought I was protecting it,
but I was actually
holding it back
from so much potential.
I think the same
might go for my heart.
I'm sorry I didn't tell you
that I was Santa #1.
At first I thought you were
the last person
in the world for me,
and then that became
less and less the case
until...
you were the only one for me.
I think this is another
great argument
for opening up Six Degrees.
I think you might be
right about that, partner.