[Shannon, narrating]
I've always been
a hopeless romantic.
Even as a kid, I had these
Barbie-inspired dreams
of the perfect wedding
I'd have someday.
This is how
I thought I'd look.
Love the hair? Ugh.
[chuckles]
And how many Irish housewives
went blind making lace
for that dress?
Hmm. My future husband.
Very Greg Brady.
Yes, yes, Greg was
way too old for me,
but even in reruns,
he was my first crush,
and I'm nothing
if not loyal.
[sighs] Could this be
any more embarrassing?
[birds singing]
[Shannon]
So, flip the calendar pages.
I grew up
and the big day came,
and this is what
my dreams looked like
a couple of decades later.
Mr. and Mrs. Jack Wicker.
Mom would have preferred
Bates-hyphen-Wicker,
but it was just
too early '90s for me.
That's me, of course,
the bride.
Almost as pretty
as the groom.
Perfect, isn't it?
I mean, right down to
the flower girl in horn-rims.
[Shannon]
But this is how it turned out.
[glass shatters]
[weeping]
Oh, honey,
I wanna be
supportive, but I...
I just don't know
what to say.
Don't say anything,
not a word, or I'll just...
Ugh! I'll scream!
[sniffles loudly]
I don't wanna scream.
I wanna sit here
and cry in peace.
Okay.
[groans, sobs]
I thought they never
locked churches.
There's a bar
down the street.
Oh, honey.
Drinking
isn't the answer.
I don't need a drink.
I need a bathroom.
Do you have a car?
No, I came with
Jack's family.
Didn't you...
You're not serious.
I haven't driven
in years.
In Los Angeles,
I pay people to
do that for me.
We'll have to walk it.
Really?
[Shannon, narrating]
Is this pitiful?
I mean...[chuckles]
this was so not the way
I saw this day going.
There must have been
signs I missed, but where?
Everything seemed fine
in L.A. the week before...
except for the fact
we were there
to visit my mother.
She can't be as bad
as all that.
This is the same woman
who missed my graduation
for a business lunch.
So, whatever you do,
please don’t start
taking her side today, okay?
I couldn't handle that.
Never. Your side
all the way.
How long since
you've seen her?
How long have
I lived in Boston?
Almost 2 years?
Yeah, almost 2 years.
The most peaceful
"almost 2 years" of my life.
You've got to relax.
We'll meet your
mother,
we'll go to dinner,
we'll tell her
the news...
and it'll be
just fine.
We have 3 issues left before
our 25th anniversary issue.
And it's got to be special.
Who was hot
when we started,
and where are
they now? Cheryl.
We're doing features on
the cast of Urban Cowboy,
and Who Shot J.R.?
J.R. who?
Remind me to fire you later.
Kurt. Photo layouts.
Mount St. Helens.
Reagan. John Lennon.
Fine.
For the cover, a face.
Someone the competition
hasn't touched.
That movie star
who's in seclusion.
Amy? What's-her-name?
Who slept with
you-know-who?
She's a nun in
the Italian Alps.
Vow of silence.
Interview unlikely.
Okay. Then get me...
an Elvis. A Janis Joplin.
Someone. I can't
do this alone, people.
I want access
to someone
we can't get access to.
Oh...was it today that
you were coming in?
Oh...it was today.
Right about now,
actually.
Oh...
I've been so looking
forward to this visit.
Aw...
Is that really how
you're wearing your
hair these days?
You didn't tell me
you were bringing
a guest.
Um...yes, I did, Mother.
You put me on hold.
This is Jack Wicker.
Jack? This is my mother.
Nice to finally meet you,
Mrs. Bates.
Oh, now now. You must
call me Marla.
And aren't you
the handsome one.
My daughter's taste
is definitely improving.
If you're smart,
you'll keep this one.
Well, um...actually...
That's...
why we're here.
Surprise.
I, uh...need
to excuse myself.
If...
if that's okay.
Hm. Help yourself.
I find out about him
the same day I discover
you're engaged?
How long have you
known this man?
Uh...we've been dating
for over a year.
If I haven't told you
about him, it's because...
you know how you are.
No. How am I?
No one is ever
good enough for me.
Well, if you're talking
about that electrician...
He was a computer
engineer, Mother.
His company is number two
in software today.
Okay. Right there.
Right there.
Number two.
We didn't come
for your blessing.
If it'd been up to me,
I might've just gone
ahead and done it.
But Jack insisted
on meeting you.
Well, I guess I should
thank my lucky stars
for Jack.
[sighs]
Ah, old friends
of my family.
[laughs]
Small world.
Oh, yeah.
So...uh...
what did I miss?
That was my
question, too.
Mom's feeling
insecure.
Umm...
I love your daughter,
Mrs. Bates.
Oh. Marla.
Mrs. Bates is fine
for now.
I've heard so much
about you from Shannon.
So you wanted to see
for yourself, did you?
He didn't mean it
that way.
I know.
He's much too polite.
[deep breath]
Well.
If you're serious
about this wedding,
why don't we plan it
for next winter?
Oh! Um, better yet...
the following spring?
We'll have it right here
in Beverly Hills.
And I'll handle
everything.
Mom.
The wedding
is next week.
[bangs on table]
Next week?
Since Jack's family
is all in Boston,
and...all I have
is you,
we're having
the service there.
Maybe just one more.
Of course,
Ma'am.
I'm assuming you would
like to attend?
Where else would I be?
How can you ask that?
And you...you don't
want any help?
It's all arranged.
Church, food, flowers.
My parents have taken
care of everything.
Oh.
I guess the only thing
left for me is to...
buy a gift for
the happy couple.
How 'bout a honeymoon?
Uh...Jack's made
the plans already.
Two weeks.
On a small island
in the Caribbean.
Sandals and seaweed?
When you could have Rio?
Vienna?
Rome?
It's privately owned,
and impossible to get into,
and the Wickers had
to pull a few strings.
They know people.
[stammers]
We know people
who know people.
Why am I not surprised?
[chuckling]
Ahh. Isn't it
lovely?
Like a garden.
Or the Rose Parade.
I understand Mr. Bates
is a no-show?
Oh, and has been for
a couple of decades.
I can't imagine today
will be any different.
How awful that
must have been.
A child needs
a father.
Thanks heavens Jack has
always had Randall, here.
He's a brick.
Yes. That was my
first impression.
Mom.
Can't get
this on.
Oh!
Help?
Of course,
darling.
Momma's here.
So, Dr. Wicker. Uh...
Are you a real doctor?
Or is that
an academic title?
I'm a
podiatrist.
Mm.
We've always joked that Jack
will one day follow
in his father's footsteps.
Podiatry. Feet.
You know.
No, no. I get it.
[laughs]
Oh. Thanks.
Ah...one hour.
Ah...[laughs]
My baby.
Hm. So...will he?
Will Jack become
a doctor as well?
He hasn't decided exactly
what he wants to do with
his life.
No sense rushing the boy
into something he hates.
Mm. Like gainful
employment.
[clearing throat]
[door opens]
And your daughter.
Well...
We just love her.
She has such
potential.
Yes. I've always
thought so.
♪♪ [church organ]
I wish you'd have let me
go shopping with you.
All the designers I know.
You could have had
something so special.
Mom. Please don't
ruin this for me.
Just this once.
I love this dress.
And I love Jack.
But is this really
what you want?
This life?
The Wickers make
Jerry Falwell look liberal.
You can't judge him
from his family.
We have so much in common.
We do everything together.
Tennis. Hiking.
Rafting...
And after you're married?
Not much money in rafting.
He certainly isn't
hurting for money.
He certainly isn't hurting
for his family's money.
When you get to know him,
you'll see what I mean.
He's wonderful.
Well...
if he's good enough for you,
that's good enough for me.
Really?
You mean that?
I have your blessing.
Of course you do.
Hmm.
If I only had a father
to give me away.
[sighs]
15 minutes, man.
My palms are sweating.
Throat's closing up.
[sighs heavily]
Is it "I do" or "I will"?
It's "I surrender."
[Marla]
I don't believe this.
I hoped to find you
on a plane or a bus.
Instead, I find you
still there?
Damn it, Larry.
This is the biggest day
in your daughter's life.
No, I will not!
You should've been here
to tell her yourself!
♪♪ [Pachelbel's canon]
For richer, for poorer,
in sickness and in health,
as long as you both
shall live?
I absolutely do.
[sighs]
And do you,
Jackson Thomas Wicker,
take this woman to be your
lawfully-married wife?
To love and to cherish,
from this day forward?
For richer, for poorer,
in sickness and in health,
as long as you both
shall live?
[deep sigh]
[clears throat]
Jack?
Umm...
Uh...
Can I, uh...
Can I talk to you?
[sighs]
Sorry. I... just give us
a minute, here?
[whispering] Yeah.
Come on.
[doors open, close]
What's wrong?
What is it?
[breathing hard]
I can't do it.
I'm sorry, but...
I can't get married!
I've been thinking
it over, and...
Thinking it over? When?
In the last 10 minutes?
[sighs]
What did she tell you?
Who?
My mother. What did
my mother say to you?
This has nothing to do
with your mother.
But she was right.
Back in L.A., she said
we were rushing through it.
And she was right!
I'm not ready! My mom
and dad are ready, but
I'm not ready...
I'm not marrying
your parents.
It's the whole...
freedom thing.
Not just for me,
you know?
You, too.
And I've been thinking about
going to Switzerland
for awhile.
Oh, the slopes are
supposed to be
amazing this year!
You're dumping me
for a ski slope?
You'd rather throw yourself
down a mountain than marry me?
It's not you.
It's me.
But I'm not
a bad person.
I'm just...
confused.
I'm really,
really sorry.
And if you could maybe
just explain to everybody?
[sighs]
[guests murmuring]
[silence]
Mom?
[Shannon] So...
that's how it started.
And that's how
I wound up here.
♪♪ [country-western]
Ugh. Look at me.
And I don't even drink.
I feel so deserted.
And stranded.
Ugh. Everyone I know here
is a...Wicker.
Or a son of a Wicker.
I know exactly
how you feel.
I remember when
your father...
Don't...this isn't
about you now, okay?
Today is about me.
My day.
[huge burst of thunder]
Oh.
Ah, perfect.
I'm a Greek tragedy.
And all I have to show
for it
is a honeymoon
I can't even use.
Hotel is owned by
Nick Tercel,
the astronaut?
That's why it's called
Blue Moon Bay.
He walked on the moon
a couple of decades ago.
25 years ago.
And he dropped out
of the space program
right after.
No one knew why.
Lots of rumors.
Sweetheart.
[clears throat]
Why don't we use
the tickets?
You and I.
Oh. That's just...
Mom.
[snorts]
That's just sad.
Well...maybe it's a sign.
Something good has to come
from this terrible day.
It's a chance for us to have
some quality time together.
To get to know
one another again.
We would kill each other
within a week.
Well, I don't know.
Maybe...no.
Yet...
I don't know.
[sighs, stomach gurgles]
I, um...
[clears throat]
I'll be right back.
Think about it,
sweetheart.
You and I, like...
like girlfriends.
And the sea air.
The swaying palm trees.
Pina coladas.
A honeymoon with Mom!
[forced laugh]
[beep]
Latrice? It's me.
I want you to cancel
every meeting I have
for the next two weeks.
I want you to go
into my schedule
and wipe it clean.
I think I have
the cover story.
Thanks.
[chuckles softly]
[Shannon] If this were
a courtroom, I'd plead
temporary insanity.
I mean, my mother and me,
on my honeymoon?
Ugh. What was I thinking?
Mom saw it as a chance
to hit every boutique
on Rodeo Drive,
and came back with a wardrobe
that would have made
Carmen Miranda blush.
You bought all this
just for the trip.
Oh, just a few things
I thought might come in handy.
Only if you're
opening for Don Ho.
An afternoon by the pool?
Yeah, with that blouse,
I think the darker,
the better.
Shannon, I promise
this will be the perfect trip.
I'll loosen up.
I'll be as laid back
as I possibly can be.
You.
Um...how should
I pack this, Miss Bates?
[deep breath]
Well, maybe I'll wear it.
I'll find something
to match.
What do you think? Is it me?
You're not serious.
This isn't Paris, Mom.
Well, it's not
Iraq, either.
If you're not up for this,
now's your chance to catch
a plane home.
Uh, no. No, no, no, no, no.
[stammering]
I...I want to. I do.
Thank you.
[Valet] Enjoy your stay.
There aren't
any windows.
We can zip them in later,
if it cools off.
Zip them?
Buckle up
and hold on.
Hold on to what?
[yelps]
[seagull cawing]
This is it?
[sighs]
This is it.
Well, this... this isn't
at all bad.
Ooo, Nice butt.
Mom...
Well, it is.
Mm-hm. Aloha.
Aloha.
Enjoy your stay.
Oh, we will.
[laughing]
[Shannon] Oh, Mom...
Um...so it's not
Mr. and Mrs. Wicker?
No. It's Miss
and Mrs. Bates.
That's Ms.
Ms. Bates.
Uh...we understood
this was going to be
a honeymoon trip.
Uh...no. He had
a...change of plans,
and is somewhere over
Switzerland right about now.
Is that a problem?
No. Not at all.
Right?
[keys rattle]
Follow me.
Hm. I'll be
right behind you.
Excuse me. I understand
Nick Tercel owns this hotel.
I suppose he wouldn't
be available to say hello?
Oh, you know him,
do you?
Oh, well...not really.
I'm just a huge fan.
Um...Mr. Tercel
values his privacy.
But, should I see him,
I'd be happy to tell him that
you've been asking about him.
No, no.
I'm sure I'll bump into him
sooner or later.
Okay.
[cell phone beeps]
Latrice. The eagle
has landed.
In absolutely nowhere.
[sighs] But, I'll be sending
the tapes just as soon as I
get the interview.
Over and out.
[chuckles]
Everything's inside
the bedroom, Ma'am.
Oh, I'm not a ma'am.
I'm a Marla!
[sighs]
[laughs]
Whatever you say, Ma'am.
Have you worked
here long?
Most of us just
work here summers.
I've been here a few.
I'll bet you
know people.
[laughs]
Like, say...
the owner?
Umm...
Nick something?
Mr. Tercel.
Yeah, sure.
Would you do me
a favor?
I would so like to meet him
while we're here.
I don't know. He's
a pretty private guy.
If he found out,
he'd...
Oh, no, no.
You don't even have
to tell him that
we talked.
Just point him out.
I'd be so appreciative.
[long sigh]
I make no promises,
but I'll see what
I can do.
That's all I ask.
[door closes]
Well. Things are looking
brighter already.
Don't you think?
What have you got there?
"Happy Honeymoon
from Blue Moon Bay."
Oh, sweetheart.
[sighs]
We could talk,
if you like.
[sniffs]
Yeah, um...
We've never been
very good at talking.
It tends to take us places
we don't wanna go.
[sighs]
But you haven't so much
as said his name
since that day.
That can't be healthy.
Don't you wanna...
yell, or scream,
or cry, or something?
[sighs] Maybe this wasn't
such a good idea after all.
[sniffs] No.
No, you know what?
[chuckles]
This is perfect.
After what I've been through,
I deserve this.
I intend to
enjoy myself,
starting right now.
Let's unpack.
That's my girl.
Hey.
[musically] Da-ta-da!
Da-ta-da-ta-da.
Da...
Sweetheart, don't put those
in a drawer. They'll wrinkle!
Hang them up!
Oh, my.
"Swim with the stingrays.
"Horseback by sunset.
Discover the bay!
Para-sailing."
I'm exhausted
just reading this thing.
You had your chance
to back out.
Uh-huh! Yep!
That's right.
I did. And this all
looks so...
wonderful.
But tonight, let's
ease our way into it.
Okay? Let's start
by dressing up.
We'll go to the very best
restaurant they have here.
Something really special.
Ah. Well. Looks like tonight
is your lucky night!
Ha ha ha!
♪♪ [steel drum]
Here you go.
Thank you.
Everything all right
with your room?
Yes, thank you.
Well, if you need anything,
my name is Adam.
I'm Shannon.
Are you here by yourself?
I mean, except for your mom.
Please tell me
that's your mom.
[chuckle]
Yeah, she's my mom.
No, uh, husband?
No boyfriend to spoil ya?
Just my mom.
Well...
I hope you have
a wonderful time.
Wow. [laughing]
That's too much.
Out here, that's
a child's portion.
Ah-hah.
This your, uh...first
time on the island?
First time.
Any advice?
Yeah. Watch out
for this guy.
[laughs]
[laughing]
He's mostly kidding.
Oh. Okay.
Good to know.
[Marla] Pssst. Hey.
Is that...?
[barely audible]
Oh. No...
Oh, thank you,
sweetheart.
You're welcome.
He, uh, he gave me
an extra portion
of wild boar.
What is that?
Some strange island
courting ritual?
3 hours ago, you thought
he had a cute butt.
3 days ago, you were
getting married,
and now you're flattered
when a man gives you
exotic meat?
Please stop. I know
what he's up to.
I hope so.
[crowd, whooping]
[Alex] C'mon, Shannon.
Let's see what you got.
[scattered applause]
You're a natural
at this.
Hey. Oh, well.
So... this isn't
home for you?
No. Just in the summers.
Home is in Sarasota,
and my parents have
a small business there,
so I help out.
Oh, wow! Parents
who stay together.
What a concept.
[chuckles]
My dad left when
I was a little girl.
I haven't heard
from him since.
Eh. It was what
he wanted.
But, um...
My-my mom is not
the easiest person
to deal with.
So, what? She, uh...
kick him out the door
and change the locks, or...?
[chuckles]
Ah. If he'd had
a choice.
Let's just say I am surprised
he stuck around as long
as he did.
I skipped out
to college as soon
as I could spell the word
"dysfunctional."
Like, I can't even spell
"dysfunctional," so...
[chuckles]
Well, she must have
done something right.
I mean, you turned out
pretty great.
Aw...[laughs]
Stop.
You...you're very good
at this, you know.
Good at what?
[soft laughter]
Ew, it's cold.
Ow! Hey...
♪ I watch the oceans... ♪
[Adam]
Ladies and gentlemen,
welcome to Stingray City.
Even though they may
look intimidating...
and yes, they are
related to sharks...
they're completely
harmless.
If you treat them with respect,
and are gentle,
you'll have a friend
for life.
Aren't they electric,
or something?
What am I thinking?
Thinking of
an electric eel.
And you'll be happy
to know we don't
have any of those here.
Who wants to get
in the water?
Come on in.
Yeah!
Oh, Shannon...
[laughs]
Ah ha ha!
Oh, wow.
You ever done
this before?
Uh...no!
I, um...
I petted a starfish
at Sea World once.
We have a pro, here,
ladies and gentlemen.
Let's give her
some support, huh?
[Crowd cheers]
[Shannon laughs]
Ohh...it's
so soft!
[laughs]
[squeals]
Slippery!
[moans displeasure]
Are you gonna try it?
Oh...when it's
the luncheon special.
[laughing]
[squeals]
That girl has
so much confidence.
[Marla] Shannon's never been
afraid to do anything.
She sees a challenge,
and she dives right in.
You wanna
feed him?
Umm...yeah.
Does he bite?
They're no more
dangerous than I am.
All right. Let's
get him in here.
I wanted her to be
independent.
Confident.
Everything I wasn't.
Lucky girl.
Here. Feed him this.
Uh-oh.
Ooo!
[laughs]
[laughing]
I'm fine.
Who else wants
to try?
[laughing]
[splashing]
Well, you're kinda handsome
for a horse.
I took a carriage ride
through Central Park
one summer.
Maybe one of
your relatives?
[Man, imitating Mr. Ed]
Could have been.
Talk to horses much,
do ya?
Not much. And they
certainly never talk back.
Maybe you're just not
listening hard enough.
[horse snorting]
Come on. Give him a pat.
Oh, no.
Come on!
Come on. Just give him
a pat.
Just stay calm.
Mm-hmm.
A horse
can sense fear.
[horse splutters]
[yelps]
Oh, that makes two of us.
Stay calm. Calm,
calm, calm.
[terrified moan]
They get nervous.
See? Look at that.
[moan tapers off]
Well, look at ya.
Oh, yes.
You're a natural.
Oh, yeah.
[laughing]
Tomorrow, the Kentucky Derby.
[horse snorts]
Well, maybe.
Just not in that outfit.
I mean, that's, uh...
that's quite a getup
you've got there.
Well, I'll take that
as a compliment,
no matter how
you meant it.
Look, if you ever want
to go for a ride...
[Marla]
Oh, no, I don't.
Why not?
Because, I...
Uh...
Well, there's no
trick to it.
Oh, yeah...
All you do is just
get on Thunder, here.
Uh-huh.
You tell him where to go.
Mm-hmm.
And he goes.
No, thank you. I'll pass.
[horse neighs]
So, um...I take it
you work here?
Oh, as little as possible.
But I...
wouldn't want you
to tell the boss that.
Oh, no. My-
my lips are sealed.
Say. Um...
You wouldn't happen to know
where I could get
a decent meal
that doesn't revolve around
wild boar, would you?
Actually, uh...
I know a great place.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah.
And if you'd be willin'
to meet me out by
the hotel at noon,
I'd be more than happy
to take ya.
Uh...uh...sure.
Sure. You, um...
You can-you can...
[grunts]
You can get the time off,
can you?
Oh, I think I could
arrange something.
You see, the boss and me,
we're just like this.
That's just great.
Then let's, um...
let's do it!
My name is Marla Bates.
Miss Bates.
Uh, no.
Marla. Please.
Marla.
Uh-huh.
And you are?
Uh, Nick.
You're...you're Nick.
Nick.
You...you're Nick.
Mm-hm.
See you at noon.
Noon.
Why didn't you tell me?
[horse snorts]
Testing, testing.
[clicks off recorder]
[rewinds, stops]
[Recorder]
Testing, testing.
[clicks off recorder]
[door opens]
[door closes]
What a morning.
Isn't this place incredible?
This place is...
incredible.
[laughing]
Are you going somewhere?
Mm. I have a lunch date.
With a man?
It could happen.
Okay. Who is this
Prince Charming?
None other than
Nick Tercel, himself.
We have a mutual
interest in horses.
Since when?
Since I got an up-close
and personal look at him.
Woof!
Woof?
Isn't that what the kids
are saying, these days?
Only if you're 12.
You may join us,
if you want.
Thank you. But, um...
I know an insincere offer
when I hear one.
Besides, I already
have plans.
I'm learning how
to fish today.
Adam again?
Shannon, I hope you're
not getting too serious.
Please don't start.
A mother worries.
20 years too late, Mom.
Ugh. Ugh!
Oh, Nick.
This is beautiful.
And it's a
restaurant?
Yeah.
Usually, I just
call it home.
Come on inside.
One martini up,
two olives,
and lunch'll be ready
in about 20 minutes.
Great.
So...if this is
where you live,
is it a safe bet
that you're the Nick
who owns the hotel,
as well?
And most of the island?
Most of the island.
Well...sounds impressive
when you put it that way.
It's not Tahiti, but...
you stick around long
enough, it'll grown on ya.
But you weren't always
in the...sand and surf
business.
No, I was raised on
a working ranch, just
outside Flagstaff.
Oh. That explains
the cowboy boots.
Ha ha. Well, my parents
used to bring me down
here when I was a kid
to these islands,
for a vacation.
Always seemed like
a safe place to come
back to.
What were you...
running from, Nick?
I- I hope that's not
too...personal
a question.
Life got complicated.
Here, it's simple.
You bought your own
paradise.
One way to look at it.
Now? I don't think
I could live
anywhere else.
[laughs] What a life
you've led.
I think I could...
listen to you talk
all day long.
[chuckling]
[laughing]
[engine stops]
You crazy. You crazy.
Oh, my goodness,
I had the best
time today.
Well, you were
a natural.
I don't know
about that.
I think that actually might
actually be a record catch.
What, smallest catch
by a guest?
That's what I'm thinkin'.
[chuckling]
So, um...
I guess I'll...
I'll see you in
the morning,
unless you wanna
grab a drink, or...
Well, the morning is great.
Great.
I will see you then.
Mom?
[Marla]
I'm just changing.
How was your day?
[laughs] Good.
Come see the catch.
[Nick] Always seemed like
a safe place to come back to,
if I ever wanted
to sort things out.
Turn that off,
please.
[Marla] I hope that's not
too...personal...
[clicks]
What is this?
[sighs] You can take
the girl out of
the magazine, but...
You know the cliche.
Is this Nick Tercel?
Mmm.
Why are you taping him?
He's an interesting
person.
Is this why you got
that sudden urge to do
a bonding session with me?
To get some story
for your magazine?
True confessions.
[sighs]
That was part of it.
But it was never
the only reason.
And it's not
some...story.
It happens to be
possibly the cover
of our 25th
anniversary issue.
Unbelievable.
You're using this
nice guy to get a jump
on the competition.
I don't like
what you're implying.
And I don't like
what you're doing.
Using me, and using him.
Everybody uses
everybody, Shannon.
The sooner you
realize that,
the less painful your life
is going to be.
[exhales softly]
No wonder Dad
walked out on you.
Shannon?
Ryan.
I need you to take
this package to
town tomorrow.
Overnight it
to my office.
This should more
than cover it.
Consider whatever's
left your tip.
[sighs] And make sure
no one sees this
before you send it.
It's not something illegal,
is it?
Only personal,
okay?
Very much appreciate
your discretion.
Okay?
Okay.
[Marla] Adam.
Adam?
Have you seen
my daughter today?
Yeah. You just missed her.
She just went out on a ride.
Would you put me on this,
and...point us in
the right direction?
You ride.
Well, of...
Well, of all
the silly questions.
Oh, horsey!
Oh, horsey, slow down...
[continued whimpering]
I'm gonna take
some more photos.
I'll catch up later.
All right.
Have fun.
[Marla] Shannon!
Oh, shoot!
Oh...!
Mother?
Whoa! Whoa. Whoa...
[groaning]
What are you doing
out here?
My foot's stuck.
[sighs]
[horse snorts]
Shouldn't you be
back at the hotel,
playing corporate spy
I...
I should have been
up-front with you.
But I meant
what I said before.
It's not the only reason
I came out here with you.
[stammering]
Who let you out
on your own?
Look at you.
You're not dressed
for this,
and you haven't
the slightest idea
what you're doing
on a horse.
Well, what's all the fuss?
There's no trick to it.
You say go, and it goes.
You say stop, and...
Whoa.
Whoa, and it whoas.
Oh. And when it runs away?
Ho! Hey! Thunder!
[horse whinnying]
No, no, no! Come back!
[stammers] Oh...
What do I do?
Well...no! Shannon!
Where are you going?
Don't leave me alone here!
Honey! Wait!
Take a little pity
on your old mom!
Wait! I'll go with you,
honey! Wait!
Here I come! Here I come!
Well, I hope you're happy.
There's not a sign
of them.
The riders, the hotel...
Oh, sweetheart.
Sweetheart.
I-all I wanted to do
was apologize to you.
To make you understand.
I understand, all right.
And this has nothing
to do with me.
It was never about me.
My entire life has been
devoted to you.
Your entire life was devoted
to sending me away.
To schools, and camps,
and activity groups,
so you wouldn't
have to be bothered.
Is that what you think?
It's what I know, Mother.
I gave you everything.
Things weren’t what I needed.
The right clothes,
and the most
exclusive academies
couldn't make up for the fact
that I needed a mother,
not a corporate executive.
Where is this coming from?
From years of taking
a back seat to your work.
The drivers who hauled
me around.
The nannies I ate meals with.
The generic birthday gifts
I know your assistants
picked out.
That's not true.
Mom, all I ever needed
was you!
And that's the one thing
you wouldn't give me.
[groans]
[sighs]
Well, it's gonna
be dark in about an hour.
We're gonna have
to camp out.
Camp out?
Okay. You're right.
We'll, um...
we'll make a tent,
or something.
Someone's bound to
notice we're gone.
Probably not till morning.
What are we gonna eat
while we're out here?
Here. Try this.
Dried fish?
The original islanders
practically lived on it.
So can you, princess.
[flies buzzing]
No.
[long sigh]
Hmm.
[chuckles]
Do you remember the time
you were...7 years old.
And...you built a fort
in the living room.
And you called it
Fort Shannon.
And we toasted marshmallows
over the 60-watt bulb
in the fake fireplace.
Remember?
Mmm.
Yeah?
Yeah. I remember.
I'm just surprised
that you do.
[whispers]
Oh, Shannon.
[long sigh]
You know, this isn't bad.
Your father always wanted
to bring me here.
To the Caribbean.
You know.
He loved the ocean.
And I had this dream
that I was gonna be
a famous artist
like Gauguin,
and run off to
my own Tahiti,
and paint the natives.
You...
Yeah.
...wanted to be
an artist.
I didn't
tell you this?
Oh, yeah.
I-I used to paint
watercolors
and your father was
my first customer.
Boy.
Larry was so handsome.
And he had his own car.
And it was love
at first sight.
At least for me.
[sighs]
Does it still
hurt that much?
Sometimes.
[howling]
What was that?
Mm. It's probably
a wild dog.
Is the wild dog
our friend?
Well, that depends.
On what?
On...how hungry he is.
Oh, that's so funny.
So terribly amusing.
Mm.
[moans and groans]
Is it morning already?
Yeah. How'd ya sleep?
Really well,
considering.
[vehicle approaching]
[Marla] Oh, yes!
Someone's coming!
Hey! Hello!
Over here!
Hello!
[both] Yay!
[laughing]
[shuts off engine]
Oh, we are
so happy to see you.
You have no idea.
You know, I had
half my staff
out lookin' for you
the whole night?
Now, now.
I know you're not happy
at having to come
and find us, but...
Thunder ran away.
And by the...
Yeah, well, you don't
have to explain to me.
Just get in.
We'll send someone back
for my horses.
Come on. Get in.
[door opens]
[shuts off engine]
Thanks, Nick.
Are we still on
for dinner?
No. Something's
come up.
And I think this
belongs to you.
This was supposed...
Ryan noticed the address.
He, uh...
He thought I should
see it.
You know, I can explain...
Yeah, well,
I'm sure you can.
Style In magazine.
Tape is labeled
"Nick, Part One."
What else do I need to know?
Do you want me to leave?
No, Ms. Bates.
You paid for the time,
you might as well
stay and enjoy it.
We'll just, uh...
stay out of one another's
way for the duration.
If you know what I mean.
Close the door, please?
[starts engine]
Well, I'm not
gonna tell ya
"I told you so."
Why not?
That's what
I'm thinking.
I haven't been honest
with anyone, and...
now I'm paying the price.
[sighs]
What would it take
to get your trust again?
Mom, I'm not sure
that's possible.
I love you.
Well...I kinda have to.
You're my mother.
Trust ya?
I know you too well.
That's your cover story!
I'll get another one.
It's only a magazine.
Here.
Join me.
[laughs]
Come on! Come on!
Get busy, here.
[both laughing]
What have you done
with my mother?
Ha ha ha!
[Shannon] I didn't buy it,
at first.
This...new attitude
of hers.
But she was determined
to prove me wrong.
And I had to
hand it to her.
She pitched right in,
literally,
like she was possessed
with the spirit of
John Wayne.
By way of Paris Hilton,
maybe. But...
she was trying,
and I had to give her credit.
You know that picture
about aliens
taking over human bodies?
It was like that.
I mean, this was
so not my mother.
[moaning]
Ew. Ew!
Ooh! ha ha!
[both laugh]
[Shannon] But whoever
she was... [laughs]
she was beginning
to grow on me.
Thank you.
Oh...[smooch]
Mm. Thank you.
I never knew
peace and quiet
could be so relaxing.
[chuckles]
It's been years
since I fell asleep
without phones ringing
and the television on.
Who knew I could?
[laughs]
Yeah, you've been
a pretty good sport
these past few days.
Oh, thank you,
sweetie.
[surf, gulls]
I love it when you
say things like that.
Well, you know.
It's-it's not
easy, letting go.
I never...really
got the hang of that.
Do you ever think
about Dad?
Wonder where he is?
Sweetheart, I know
you think that
I did something
to drive him away.
But that's not...
how it was.
We were too young.
And we realized it,
too late.
There's no one
to blame, sweetie.
I remember
the day he left.
I had a cold.
And, uh...
I came home early
from school.
And he was at the door.
With his bags packed.
[sniffles]
He seemed so sad
I had to see him going.
He said you thought
it was best for us all.
He said that?
That it was my idea?
I cried for weeks.
And you wouldn't even
let me comfort you.
You only wanted him.
I still miss him.
Every day.
Um...I'm sure he
misses you, too.
And I know he'd be
proud of you.
But that's in the past.
Can't we please
just leave it there?
Start fresh.
Yeah.
Yeah. As long as,
from now on,
it is total honesty
between us. Okay?
Okay.
So...
Honestly,
I think that you should
try to patch things up
with Nick.
Oh, ho ho ho.
There's no hope
of that.
I wouldn't know
where to start.
Well, you could start
with an apology.
And I know just
how to do that.
Mornin'.
Oh, Mr. Tercel.
This came for you.
Should I have it sent
to your office?
No, just put it
back there.
Knock, knock.
Come in.
This was at
the hotel front desk.
That's right where
I left it.
Everything that you
think about my mother
is true.
At least it was.
Actually, I-I don't
think about it, Shannon.
Now, if you'll, uh,
excuse me,
there's some things
to do.
And when you go, if you
can take that with you...
Ever since I can remember,
she has pushed and fought,
and done whatever it took
to get ahead in business.
I always thought
it was such a shame
that she robbed us
of all that time
we could have spent
together.
But...she's changing
out here.
At least she's
trying to.
Well, then, in that case,
I'm happy for you both.
She destroyed the tape.
Yeah.
It was a cover story
she was desperate for,
and she gave that up.
And that should
tell ya something.
Shannon, did your mom
send you out here
to tell me this?
Mm-mm. She has
no idea I'm here.
Huh.
I got your painting.
Thank you.
Mm-hmm.
Well, I know I'm no match
for the elephant
that shows her paintings
at the Guggenheim.
Oh, that elephant.
She's just a flash
in the pan.
Highly overrated.
Absolutely.
Mm-hm.
Heard you threw
that tape away.
Shannon told you?
Yes.
Oh...
[chuckles]
Well, she'll be telling
people my real age!
Would you rather
I didn't know?
Yes.
I mean about the tape.
Oh.
Well, I...
couldn't use it now,
after all that happened.
[exasperated sigh]
Not that I didn't want to.
I'm not a saint.
Really.
Just not...
quite as heartless
as you imagine.
Oh, that's good to know.
You're not dancin'.
No.
You don't wanna
see why.
I don't.
No.
Because when I was
good at it,
I wasn't good at it.
I'd just embarrass
myself.
Now, that's actually
something I'd like to see.
What, again?
Well, if you fall...
I'll catch ya.
Oh, there are those
who wouldn't blame you
if you didn't.
Gotta trust me,
don't ya?
Hm.
Put one hand here.
[laughs]
And now we step.
Oh, you're
a natural.
[Driver]
Here we go, sir.
Have a nice day.
Shannon?
Jack.
[stammers]
What the hell
are you doing here?
Well, nice to
see you, too.
Who's the surfer?
This is Adam.
Adam, Jack.
And you are?
Her fiance.
My former fiance.
The fiance that walked out.
The fiance that made
a big mistake,
and is here
to get you back.
I really need
to talk to you.
Whoa, whoa. I'm dancing.
You don't just pull
a lady off the dance
floor, all right?
Here's how it works.
You ask her nice.
And if she wants to go,
she'll go.
Okay. [sighs]
I'm sorry.
I really need to talk to you.
That's all I wanna do.
Please. I came
all this way.
Oh. From Switzerland?
It gave me time
to clear my head.
And-and-and-
figure things out.
I know what I want, now.
At least hear what
I have to say.
[Nick] Moon'll
be up, soon.
I hear it's gonna
be a full one.
[Marla] You know,
it's really hard
to imagine
that you walked
up there.
[Nick] Yeah, sometimes
it seems like a dream.
When I went up there,
my perspective changed.
Uh-huh.
And I didn't wanna
come back and just do
ads for running shoes,
and for orange juice.
Nah.
But you were a hero.
All the...parades,
and headlines.
Yeah, well.
Walkin' away
from that?
Nothing easy
about it.
You know, it just...
it seemed...
People wanted to know
what I was doing.
And the- the more
that I denied
the rumors,
the darker they got.
So I just had to
get away somewhere,
and find myself.
And you chose here.
Can you blame me?
No. I can't.
Well...
that's it.
Wouldn't have made
much of a story anyway,
I guess.
Oh...
I'm so sorry, Nick.
What are you
sorry about?
Hm?
I'm listening.
No matter how many lies
I told myself,
no matter how...
scared I got,
there was one fact
that never changed.
One argument
I couldn't get around.
I love you.
Where were those words
when I needed to hear them?
Do you have any idea
what you put me through?
Any idea at all?
[laughing]
I am on a honeymoon
with my mother.
I'm not leaving here
without you.
I mean it.
I'm gonna stay.
And I'm gonna fight for you,
as long as it takes.
Suit yourself.
I have to get back
to the dance.
Well...
[sighs]
Can I help you?
You have my bag.
And I'm gonna need
a room for a few nights.
Put it on this.
Sorry, but we're full.
[scoffs] Okay.
I get it.
Last minute and all.
Just charge whatever
you want.
Let me try this again.
We have a waiting list
8 months long
at the moment.
But if you'd like
to make a reservation...
Are you tellin' me
there's nothing?
No room? No bed?
No anything?
I see we don't have
a language barrier,
after all.
Here's your bag.
Now if you'll excuse me.
[sighs]
Say hello.
[horse grumbles]
[horse sniffs]
Oh...
[horse grunts]
Ho...!
Morning.
What...
What time is it?
Oh, I'd say
it's about time
for you to start
movin' on.
Excuse me?
Well, this here's
a private beach, son.
You can't sleep here.
[laughing nervously]
It's okay. I'm a guest
from the hotel.
I- I mean,
I have a room.
I paid for a room.
It's just occupied.
Well, why don't you try
to sort that out
by tonight, okay?
Have a good one.
Come on, Thunder.
[horse whinnies]
You look like hell.
Nice to see you, too,
Mrs. Bates.
Shannon told me
you were here.
What'd you do?
Sleep on the beach?
I had no choice.
I'm lost without
your daughter.
I can't eat.
I can't sleep.
I knew I didn't like you.
You're just like my ex.
Excuse me?
You don't care what
she's been through.
It's all about you.
What you want,
and how you feel.
Just because you can't
hold onto your husband,
don't blame me.
What?
I didn't mean that.
[sighs]
I'm tired.
I don't know what
I'm saying.
I don't blame you.
You are who you are.
Nothing can change that.
But I am not letting Shannon
make the same mistake I did.
Mrs. Bates, I know
you're upset at me.
And I'm sorry.
But I'm determined
to make things right.
Doesn't everybody
deserve a second chance?
I mean, come on.
Shannon isn't here.
What is it you want?
Right now, I would like
to use your shower,
if you don't mind.
I did pay for it,
after all.
I think your parents
did that.
Okay. [sighs]
Lock up when you leave.
Thanks.
Oh, thank you.
Thank you very much.
I needed that.
Missed you at
the island excursion,
this morning.
Yeah.
I needed some
time to think.
Hmm.
You and the, uh...
preppy a thing again?
Why? Would it bother you?
I'm just sayin' I don't
like to see people get
taken advantage of,
that's all.
And you think he's
taking advantage of me.
You got a good heart.
He knows that.
It wouldn't be hard.
I wanted him, yeah.
But I certainly didn't
need him.
What about now?
I don't know.
Maybe.
I'm just not sure
I could ever really
trust him again.
Kinda like your mom,
with your dad.
Hey.
Why don't you
get changed,
and we'll get in some
serious beach time
this afternoon.
How's that sound?
Come on. It'll be fun.
[laughs]
Okay.
And I'll see you
in about...20 minutes?
Sounds good.
Okay.
[laughs]
[Man] Hey,
watch it!
Sorry.
[shower running]
Mom, it's me!
You gonna be long?
[shower stops]
What are you doing here?
Takin' a shower.
You wanna join me?
I thought you left.
I tried to tell you
yesterday.
I'm here to win you back,
and I'm not taking no
for an answer.
Don't make me call someone.
Shannon.
I'll do whatever
you want. Name it.
I'll-I'll crawl.
I'll-I'll beg.
Stop it. [stammers]
There-there's nothing
that you can say.
[sighs]
What if I said I could
find your father for you?
No one knows where he is.
Hmm. Not even
your mother?
No. She knows I would do
anything to see him. If she
had any idea where he was...
But she does.
Your mother knows
exactly where he is.
She's known all along.
I-I think I-I twisted it
back there in the surf.
Okay.
Well...
you let me know
if this hurts.
Better?
Much.
Oh. Oh, right there.
[gasps]
Oh, a little bit more...
Oh. Oh. Ooooh...
That's much better.
Hi.
Hope we're not
interrupting.
What's wrong?
I'm just...wondering
what happened to all that
honesty we promised
each other?
What are you
talking about?
I wanna know where
my father is.
I've always told you.
We don't know where
your father is.
No-no-no-no. We don't
know, but I hear
that you do.
Where would you get
that idea?
[Jack] From me.
I overheard you on the phone,
at the chapel in Boston.
It sounded to me like
you were trying to make sure
that dear old Dad
wasn't gonna be there.
And I felt that
I owed it to Shannon
to tell her the truth.
Did you keep him away?
I wasn't trying to
do that at all.
Then you admit it.
You know where he is.
Sweetheart, I know you
can't understand this,
but I had my reasons.
Where?
Shannon,
sweetheart...
I don't want you excuses
or your lies.
You just tell me
where he is.
I wanna know.
I deserve to know.
He runs a boat tour business
in the Florida Keys.
He has for some time now.
That's an easy trip
from here.
But please don't go,
darling.
Not until we have
a chance to talk.
Stop it, Mom. Just stop.
Honey...ow, damn it!
Gee, I'm sorry,
Mrs. Bates.
If I'd known this would
have caused a problem
between you and Shannon...
You...have no idea
what you've done.
But now that you have,
don't you dare let her
do this by herself.
She needs someone
there for her.
Oh, God...
[Marla] My husband
never wanted a child.
He walked out one day,
and never came back.
And I promised myself
I would never depend
on a man again.
And I raised Shannon to be
her own person, too.
[sighs]
Don't you think
she deserves
to know all this?
Oh, I could never
tell her the details.
He is her father.
Yeah, but...now she's
assumed that you're
the one to blame.
Well, I didn't say
it was a perfect plan.
Are you always
this understanding,
or is this just
smoke and mirrors,
to make me think
you're terrific?
No. No tricks.
Nothing up my sleeves,
and...[stammers]
I'm just an ordinary guy.
Oh. Ha! No.
Not an ordinary guy.
Trust me.
[sighs]
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Okay. So now she gets
to the Keys, and...
she meets her father.
Then...
what's she goin'
to find?
[sniffs]
[sighs]
[seagulls, cawing]
Are you ready to meet him?
I've been ready all my life.
[knocking]
Hey. Can I help you?
You guys looking
for a tour?
We might not be the biggest,
but we are the best.
Actually, we're looking
for Larry Bates.
Well.
Dad?
Shannon?
Oh, God.
Shannon.
Well, uh... come in!
Come in. Please.
This place is a mess.
If I'd know you were
coming, I...
Dad, I didn't come
to see your office.
Could I- could I
maybe, umm...
get a...hug?
Of course.
Of course you can.
You have no idea
how long I've been
dreaming of this.
[nervous chuckle]
This is fine.
This is just fine.
Uh, Grace?
Hey, Grace, come
and meet my daughter.
Your what?
Oh, it certainly is.
You look just like
those photos your Mom
sends now and then.
My Mom sends photos?
This is Grace, and...
sit down. Please.
So...you must be Jack.
Yeah, that's right.
The new husband.
[stammers] You knew
I was getting married.
Yeah. I heard
somethin' about it.
[Grace] Something?
Your mother called
a couple of times,
trying to get this guy
to haul his ass up
to Boston for
the ceremony.
[Jerry] We had
a huge tour that day.
And weddings always
bring back bad
memories for me.
But congratulations.
Good-lookin' guy.
Thanks. But, uh...
We-we're not
married.
It didn't happen.
Well, thank God
for that.
I mean, I think you're both
better off for it. I do.
A romantic guy,
my Larry.
I fell for that trap, once.
Never again.
You walked out?
It was your idea.
Well, it's not something
I'm proud of.
I'm sure your mother...
[sighs] drives it into
your head every day.
You know, fills your head
will all kinds of junk
about me.
Maybe she never
said a thing.
Maybe she let me think...
it was all her fault.
And you were still some
knight in shining armor.
Shannon.
Let's get down to it.
Why are you here?
If it's about money,
I can barely
make ends meet...
No! I- I just wanted
to see you!
I have made so many excuses
for you over the years.
Why you never wrote.
Wh-why you never
tried to get in touch.
I even imagined that Mom
was hiding your letters,
trying to keep us apart.
Dad!
Okay, I get it.
And I know what you
wanna hear, Shannon.
But the fact is,
some of us aren't cut out
to be tied down by...
wives, and children.
And that's just
the way I am.
It doesn't make me
a bad person.
Damn it! Didn't you once
wonder where I was,
or what I was doing? I...
Me? No.
Because there was never
a doubt in my mind
you'd be fine.
And look at the way
you turned out.
You are your mother's girl.
Yes.
Yes, I am.
I just didn't realize it,
till right now.
Don't be like this.
Don't go away mad.
I'm not going away mad.
I'm just going away.
[seagulls, cawing]
So we'll pack up your stuff,
and head back to Boston. Okay?
Shannon?
How many chances did
Mom have to tell me
the truth?
To tell me
what a jerk he is.
And not once did she
let me think he was
anything but wonderful.
Wait a minute.
You heard what he said.
Well, if you read
between the lines,
your mother was demanding
and self-centered and just...
just drove him away.
Okay. He's nobody's idea
of Father of the Year,
but he did do his best.
Taxi!
He what?
Did you hear the same
conversation I just heard?
I got that he obviously
wasn't ready to get married,
and she just
pushed him into it.
Well, I guess you can
relate to that, can't you?
I don't condone
what he did.
I'm just saying
he had his reasons.
Take your hand off the door.
Hey. I'm just trying
to point out
that your mother isn't
totally blameless here.
Actually...it looks like
you struck out twice,
parentally speaking.
But you still have me,
sweetie. Now, move over.
Okay. I need you
to listen really,
really carefully, Jack.
I don't want you.
I can't leave you
alone, here.
Only at the altar, I guess.
A person makes one
little mistake.
I come all this way,
and this is the thanks
that I get?
Well, welcome to
your life, Shannon.
You're just like
your mother.
And that might just be
the nicest thing
you've ever said to me.
Please go, driver.
Yes, Ma'am.
Whoa!
[sighing, sniffling]
My baby.
My sweet baby.
[camera beeps]
[crying and laughing]
[whispering]
You are so beautiful.
[knocking on door]
Come in.
Front desk tells me
you're checkin' out.
Shannon's not coming back.
And I've embarrassed myself
enough for one vacation.
Well, I, uh...
thought this might be
somethin' you'd like.
I just hope that you
can read the writing.
My teachers always said
I should have been a doctor.
[laughs]
What is this?
It's my story.
In my own words,
of course.
I figure now's as
good a time as any
to get it out,
get it behind me, and...
and maybe I can move on
with my business,
and not have to look
over my shoulder
every 5 minutes,
for reporters.
The vultures.
Are you sure you want me
to have this?
Well, uh...
that's only if you're
still interested.
Thank you, Nick.
Really sorry
you're leaving.
And if you ever...
find yourself out this
way again, well...
And if you ever
get to the city.
[sighs]
You know...if we
use these pages,
we're gonna need an updated
photo to go with them.
I- I've never been very
comfortable in front
of a camera.
I warn ya.
Hey.
I know some terrific
professionals in California.
We can...put you together
with one of them.
Los Angeles.
Yeah.
That's where I did
my last TV interview.
Maybe this is the time.
Huh?
You know, they...
they broadcast
in color, now.
Hm.
Mm-hm.
[cutting engine]
Hey.
What happened to, uh...
Mr. Right?
Hmm.
Yeah, the- the honeymoon
is definitely over.
Well, you know what?
I enjoyed the time
that we spent together.
No, the pleasure was
definitely mine.
Oh, aren't we
the civilized ones,
hmm?
No harm, no foul.
Smile. Shake hands.
I was never much
for handshakes.
[laughs]
Yeah. Me, neither.
I should go up
and see my mother.
I'll walk ya. Come on.
Hm.
[both] Oh...
So, uh, what's next
for you?
Well, summer's almost over.
So I'll...
go back to the mainland,
and back to my real life,
I guess.
Hm.
Ready for that scuba lesson
you promised?
Be right there.
Take care of yourself.
Well, like my mom
always taught me,
if I don't, who will?
Enjoy your swim.
I will.
Hmm.
Well, hi.
[door closes]
I didn't expect you
to come back.
Did you see your father?
Yeah.
How was he?
Not the man
I thought he was.
Sweetheart.
I'm so sorry.
Why didn't you
ever tell me?
Because you didn't need
to know the truth.
You needed a father.
And you needed him
to be a hero.
And I wanted
to give you that.
Oh, Mom.
I love you.
I really,
really love you.
Have I ever told you that?
Not like that.
Ohh...
Oh...
[sniffles]
And I love you,
too, sweetie.
Hm.
Mm!
Are you leaving?
Yeah. I don't want them
to discover
that they can run that
magazine without me.
How about you?
[sniffs, clears throat]
Well... [laughs]
Think you could...
make room for a guest,
maybe, till I
get a job, and...figure
a few things out?
You know I could.
[Shannon] So we went back
to Los Angeles,
and I landed a job with
a major publishing company.
[Marla] And ladies
and gentlemen,
I have one more
thing to say.
I love this cover.
I love this issue.
Thank you, thank you,
thank you!
[Shannon] Okay, it helps
to have friends
in high places.
But it all worked out.
Happy endings aren't
just for fairy tales.
Wow!
Made it.
Nice to
see you.
Mmmm.
You look very
handsome.
Handsome all the way
down to your toes.
Thank you.
[Shannon] Nick's spending
more time in L.A. now,
and Mom and I
are much closer...
thanks to the best
honeymoon of my life.
Sorry. Um,
thank you.
Ahem.
See ya around.
See ya.
[Shannon] The best one
so far, anyway.
But if there should be
another one in the future,
I know where we can get
a room with a view
of the sunset.
Closed-Captioned By
J.R. Media Services, Inc.
Burbank, CA