Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
["The Rose that Grew from Concrete"
by Tupac playing]
Yes, ma'am.
Gigi. Okay. Bye.
["The Rose that Grew from Concrete"
continues]
Okay. Huh?
[speaks indistinctly]
You can't catch me!
[song continues]
[chords playing on piano]
Sounding good, baby girl.
- Finished.
- Yeah?
Let me hear it.
I can't do it with you staring at me.
What... [giggles]
All right, baby. Okay.
[playing ballad]
Why did you stop, honey?
'Cause this is the part I'm unsure of.
Let me see, honey.
It sounded great.
Okay, baby.
Okay.
You see, you were here.
And why don't we try this for that part,
with the bridge?
- What do you think, baby?
- Okay.
- Yeah.
- [giggles]
It'll be just fine, you're so talented.
Just like your mama.
All right,
don't forget to change it there.
♪ Must not have been ♪
♪ Paying attention ♪
♪ Covered in sin ♪
♪ Didn't even notice ♪
♪ How deep I was ♪
♪ I went from the ground
to the top of the cloud ♪
♪ I once was blind but now I see ♪
♪ What You sacrificed for me ♪
♪ Now through His blood ♪
♪ I'm set free ♪
♪ And, Jesus, You touch ♪
♪ Every part of me ♪
♪ Ooh ooh, through his blood ♪
♪ I'm made free ♪
♪ And I don't wanna give it up ♪
♪ I'm completely covered ♪
♪ In Your love ♪
[cheering]
- These are for you.
- Oh, baby!
- Oh, my God.
- I'm so proud of you.
You did it perfectly.
Papa.
That was nothing short of amazing,
my darling, as usual,
- but daddy gonna see you later, okay?
- Okay.
Can I talk to you outside real quick?
Just for a second.
Yes?
I got your petition. It's not happening.
- Ashley's tuition went up.
- And?
- And I need some help.
- You should have thought about that
before you enrolled her in a school
that you couldn't afford.
I keep telling you it shouldn't
have to be all on me, Greg.
Unfortunately for you, that's exactly
what full custody means, baby.
Oh, is it?
'Cause I thought,
regardless of where she lives,
she's just as much your daughter
as she is mine.
Which is why you could have
consulted me, but you didn't.
She's thriving at that school.
You know what?
You're missing the whole point.
So that's it, just no?
Yes. Because if you really wanted my help,
you would have listened to me
two years ago.
Oh, Greg. This is not about you.
Right, it's about you.
And you doin' whatever
the hell you wanna do.
Those days are over, Gi,
you gotta make a choice.
A choice? What--
What are you talking about?
Either you're gonna be a boss ass bitch
or you're gonna be a beggin' ass bitch.
But you can't be both.
You can call me when you figure it out.
Ashley, honey. Come on,
you're gonna miss the bus.
Okay!
Good morning.
Here's your breakfast burrito and your OJ.
- I can't find my gym bag.
- It's right there, honey.
Thank you.
I need you to sign this.
- What is this?
- Something about my tuition?
Ms. Wick said she called,
but your voicemail was full.
- Okay. I'll take care of it.
- Thank you.
[Gigi clears throat]
I know my little munchkin
wasn't about to leave me.
Have a good day.
- Okay.
- Mm-hmm. All right.
[man] Hello?
[Greg] Either you're gonna be
a boss ass bitch
or you're gonna be a beggin' ass bitch.
["Zim Zimma" by Joyner Lucas playing]
[groaning]
Damn.
- What?
- Bad day?
Hey, I come in peace. I come in peace.
Hey, a brother just wanna say hello.
You work here, right?
Sales.
Well, let me take you to lunch.
- No.
- No? [scoffs]
Why?
One, we're not allowed to date members.
And two... I'm not interested.
You're not interested?
[chuckles]
Okay.
[whistle blows]
Get that weak mess out of here.
["Ditty Dumb" by Niq' playing]
Hey, Rob. Hey, Chris.
You are early.
You know me. Is it a problem?
Not at all. I respect your hustle.
I always said you were gonna
run this joint someday.
Chris, I could never
see this place without you.
You need to give it some thought, though.
Right now I got real-world
problems to deal with.
- All right, babe.
- Ooh, what's up, beautiful?
- My name is Gigi.
- Oh, it's like that today?
Last I checked, my name
was Gigi yesterday too.
Well, Gigi, you look goooood today!
We're friends, come on.
- Friends?
- Friends.
Well, that's where we can start.
["Petty" by Tyeler Reign playing]
So...
You was talkin' all that mess
on the court.
I bet you ain't got nothin' to say now.
Saundra, don't nobody got time
for your drama.
[girl] Come on, bitch! Yes!
[girls laughing]
- What you gonna do?
- What?
What you gonna do?
[girls shouting, jeering]
[girl 1] Shit, somebody call a ambulance!
[girl 2] Damn!
["Gettin' Money"
by D.C. Young Fly playing]
- What's up, my man?
- Good.
- Hey.
- Make sure you take good care of that.
- Always.
All right, now, you gonna be
able to run this town one day.
- Oh, for sho', for sho'...
- For real.
Damn!
- Hello.
- [bottles rattle]
Brian, if this is one of those scenarios
where you accidentally bump into me
and touch my butt, don't.
It's not one of those days.
How about tomorrow?
How about the next day?
Brian. Jesus, you're so annoying.
- Well, persistence always pays off.
- No! It does not.
[students gasping, exclaiming]
[Ashley] Get off me!
- Let me go, get off me!
- [officer] Calm down!
[Ashley] She started it!
[officer] Come here!
On the ground!
- [Ashley] I didn't--
- Shut that little black ass up!
[Ashley screams]
Shit.
Chill.
Look, I got this.
Go. Go, go, go, go. Take a break.
I got it.
Is there any way I can pay next week?
[Ms. Wick] Yes. However, Ms. Davis,
I need to be clear.
If our tuition is not up to date
by next week,
we will have no choice but to remove
Ashley from our rolls.
I understand. Thank you.
[siren wailing]
Can I call my mom?
What's the number?
404...
555-9821.
[Gigi] You've reached Gigi.
Leave me a message.
So, Gi, what's going on with you?
You looked like you were about to explode.
[sighs] The usual, B.
Money and bills.
Well, if you would stop and holler
at a brother, I might be able to help.
Are you talking about that super secret
backpack you be getting from Bobby?
What? It's not what... it's...
Before you say anything else,
I'm a single mother who cannot
afford to be associated
with whatever kind of drug dealing
nonsense you got going on.
I prefer to get mine in tips.
- Okay. Really?
- [chuckles]
Can I call my dad, please?
I'd like to call my dad, please.
What's the number?
404-999...
6135.
Daddy?
What's up, mama?
Are y'all just incapable
of calling me by my damn name?
[chuckles]
Our friend is having a bad day.
Oh, I'm ea yin', girl, you are
too fine for all that hostility.
When the last time you had
some vitamin D?
Some what?
[Brian laughs]
Bobby, don't you have
some work to do, brah?
Damn, I can't stand nobody
who can't take no joke.
[phone buzzing]
Oh, shit.
Oh-ho-ho!
Man, look at this.
Look at these two bruisers,
they are scrappin'.
- [Brian] Oh, that's a right cross! Oh!
- [Bobby] Ow!
[Brian] Fighting like a girl!
Where are you going?
Oh! Oh-ho-ho!
Yo, B, why y'all messin'
with the old girl, man?
Man... Gigi's on one, man.
You know, the usual, man.
Look at this right here.
They are fightin'!
Aw, shit, man.
- What?
- That's Gigi's daughter.
- No!
- What?!
Oh, shit!
["Time Today" by Moneybagg Yo playing]
Ashley Davis, where is she?
B10.
[lock buzzing]
[buzzing stops]
- Daddy.
- Oh, baby.
Oh!
I'm so sorry.
- Daddy's here, baby, Daddy's here.
- [Ashley sobbing]
Mommy...
[whimpering]
Oh! Baby.
[Ashley] The cop.
It's the cop that caught me,
he just kept hitting me...
and hitting me. The cop...
- Gigi!
- [Greg] Chill out!
You'd touch a little girl!
[men] Gigi! Gigi!
Think you can just do that
to a little girl?
Huh? What the fuck
is wrong with you people?
Ma'am, I need you to calm down.
- Fuck you!
- [Ashley] Mama!
- Gigi, hold on!
- Easy! Easy! Gigi!
Mama, Mama.
Please.
Calm down, okay?
Take Ashley and go.
Take Ashley and go home, Gi.
Mommy!
Come on, baby.
Okay, I got you, I got you. I got you.
Fix it.
- You'll need to fill out--
- Shut the fuck up!
- I'll take care of the paperwork.
- [Ashley sighs]
[distant dog barking]
- Mama?
- Yes, baby.
Is Saundra going to die?
No.
No, no, no. No, baby.
But what... What will people think of me?
Some girls were taking videos
on their phones.
It's probably all over TikTok.
What have I always told you, honey?
- Don't listen to what they say.
- Yes.
♪ They say ♪
♪ Give up ♪
♪ When the goin' gets tough ♪
♪ Cliche ♪
♪ But it's easier to walk away, mm ♪
♪ You'll say, "I'll be okay" ♪
♪ Don't listen to what they say ♪
♪ Trust me, I got you ♪
♪ I'll never let you down ♪
♪ No one knows ♪
♪ All of the thoughts in my head ♪
♪ That'll leave me in bed ♪
♪ Thinkin' where to go ♪
♪ From here ♪
♪ Step one, two ♪
♪ You gotta push through ♪
♪ Step three, four ♪
♪ So much more ♪
♪ Five, six ♪
♪ Just don't quit ♪
♪ Seven, eight ♪
♪ Don't listen to what they say ♪
♪ No ♪
♪ Just don't listen to what they say ♪
♪ Mm, no ♪
[knock on door]
It's open.
[Greg] Where is Ashley?
Is she okay?
Finally got her to go to sleep.
She's being charged with assault.
What?
Yeah.
The other girl's
in the hospital, in a coma.
Have you seen our daughter?
She's not doing too great, either.
I know that. Right now, we need a lawyer.
Okay.
- Okay?
- Okay.
This is gonna cost us
about $50,000 in legal fees.
I'm gonna need you to pay half.
That is some bullshit.
This is the result of you
wanting to run the streets
instead of being a real mother,
that's what this is.
Our daughter was assaulted by cops!
On video! And you're blaming me.
Are you hearing me?
I feel like you're not hearing me.
Shh!
That will follow her for the rest
of her life. She's in the system now, Gi.
What about the cops, huh?
They in the system too?
They will be. I'm gonna handle that shit.
That will be a first.
Look, I don't even know why
I bother coming to fuck with you.
Me either.
You know what?
Just have your 25,000, okay?
[door opens]
[door slams]
Motherf...
[line ringing]
Hey, Brian.
I wanna talk to you.
Listen, if I'm gonna get
in bed with you guys--
Ooh, I like the sound of that shit there.
- Is he gonna be a problem?
- Bobby's gonna be good.
Be cool, Bobby. Go on.
As I was saying,
if we're going to do this,
we have to step up your game.
What do you mean?
I told you the other day
your little operation ain't
quite as smooth as you think.
Show me why.
Okay. You have a runner.
Her name is Vanessa.
She drops off a backpack full of cash.
She then goes to several other
local establishments
and does the same thing.
To add insult to injury,
Bobby meets her in public
and gives her the backpacks.
She gives him a to-go order of food
with a check inside the bag.
Then she goes to the nail shop
and picks up another.
It took me two days to figure out
how you washed your money.
I'm amazed you guys haven't been
caught by the Feds already.
And I'm amazed you done broke down
our whole little operation.
Mm-mm-mm. So-so--
So, tell me, are you some kind of fine
criminal mastermind or something?
So we're clear, what I am is a mother
whose daughter is in trouble.
That's it.
So how do we fix the so-called holes?
I know a guy.
What kind of guy?
The Kind of guy
who will quadruple our profits
and reduce our risks at the same time.
- I'm with that, I'm with it.
- Wait, wait, wait a second.
- What's wrong?
- We're moving a little too fast, no?
Yo, Gi, if you got a guy that can bring in
that type of dough,
guess what? You can count me in.
- We need to run this past our guy.
- You mean my guy.
- Set up a meeting.
- He'll be here tonight.
All right, you good with this?
I guess y'all got it all covered.
Good.
Let's drink to doing business.
Just business, Bobby.
You're the one came here
with your titties out. Shit.
[Gigi] Just business.
Quadruple? Quadruple money?
- Quadruple.
- Quadruple the money.
Ooh!
Quadruple. Goddamn.
[hip-hop playing]
Two bottles of Hennessey,
four bottles of Success,
and a case of Möet.
- [Brian] Got it.
- [Gigi] I know you got it.
- [speaking indistinctly]
- [Brian] Photographic memory.
- [Gigi] Uh-huh.
- [Brian chuckles]
[man] Mm-mm-mm!
Man, don't tell me
you're in there, too, brother.
[man] What's up, ma?
Brian, this Tre.
- What's up?
- It's good.
Only Tre and I need to be in
on this meeting. Y'all can wait outside.
- What? Hell no. This is my shit.
- Nobody else.
Bobby, it's cool.
- [Bobby] All right, brother.
- [Tre] I got you.
- Man, a'ight.
- You're good.
[sighs]
[Gigi] I'll see you in a minute.
- So...
- So.
You're about 15 minutes away from the Feds
blowing up your whole operation.
No risk, no reward, right?
What if I could help minimize the drama
and increase your profit?
So you're just gonna ignore
this whole gym thing.
I don't have time for games.
You here to talk business or not?
All right, we could chop it up.
Right now you're moving small amounts
of cash through a large amount of people.
Well, Bobby and Brian are the only
two people that know I exist, so...
Don't fool yourself. The streets do talk.
The streets?
You know about the streets, huh?
Enough.
Hmm.
- So, what you proposing?
- We build a wall around you.
We clean two million a month
through our network
and pay out in a way that's far removed
from anything that ties back to you.
And what's that gonna cost me?
It's 10%.
Okay, beautiful.
Tell me about this network.
- No.
- No? What you mean, no?
The whole point is to remove you from
anything that could expose you.
So I'm supposed to trust you
with $2 million of my money?
Huh? Speak.
Yeah.
Yeah?
And if anything goes left,
that's what you got your boys for, right??
So, how do you know Bobby?
We went to school together.
I was always about my paper.
He wanted in, so...
I put him down as family.
- Oh. You do know he's dumb, right?
- Yeah.
[chuckles]
Bobby's good people, let's say that.
He is good people, he's a nice guy.
Hey, enough, enough.
Maybe just a half a chromosome
away from mental retardation.
- Enough!
- Okay. All right.
I'm just saying you might wanna
watch him, he's a wild boy.
Yeah, he is a wild boy, but...
I hear you.
So, what you need from me?
Get me the money
by the end of the week.
I'll get you the money by tomorrow.
I mean, you said you had
no time for games, right?
Well, I guess we have a deal, Mr. Tre.
I guess we do.
And I like this color on you too. Yeah.
Thank you.
["Hold On, Change is Coming" begins]
♪ Ah, yeah ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh ♪
♪ Hey, yeah-eah ♪
♪ Uh-huh, oh, yeah ♪
♪ Mm, yeah ♪
♪ Come on and sing with me ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Mm, yeah ♪
♪ It's a simple song ♪
♪ Oh, la-da-da-lada- la-di-da ♪
♪ Yesterday ♪
♪ A man said to me ♪
♪ "How can you smile when
your world is crumbling down?"
♪ I said, "Here's my secret" ♪
♪ "When I wanna cry ♪
♪ I take a look around
and I see that I'm gettin' by" ♪
- ♪ Hold on ♪
- ♪ Change is comin' ♪
- ♪ Don't worry ♪
- ♪ Don't worry 'bout nothin' ♪
- ♪ I said hold on ♪
- ♪ Hold on ♪
- ♪ You can make it ♪
- ♪ Everything ♪
- ♪ Everything will be all right ♪
♪ Some people like to worry ♪
♪ Some people like to hide ♪
♪ Some people like to run away
from the pain... ♪
[knock on door]
Gigi Davis, as I live and breathe.
I saw you come in the service today.
I hoped you might pop by.
Good to see you too, old man.
Hold up with the "old man,"
I still got a few kicks left in me.
[chuckles]
Service was so beautiful. I needed that.
And your congregation is growing.
Well, praise the Lord, we do good work.
That's actually why we're here.
Hmm.
We'd like to make a donation.
Oh, well...
Much appreciated,
but as you know, sister Davis,
you don't have to come into my office
to make donations.
There are boxes and plates everywhere.
My client here has a friend
from a very, very wealthy family.
You don't say.
Hmm.
All right.
[clears throat]
Are you sure?
Oh, yes.
- How wealthy?
- Two million a month.
Well...
you are most welcome in the house
of the Lord, my brother.
- Praise the Lord.
We can have the first installment
to you in just a few days.
Ninety day turnaround good?
Ten percent commission, 60/40 split.
Thank you for your kind generosity,
sister Davis.
The pleasure's all mine, Pastor.
[Pastor] Ahem.
I-- Gigi, uh...
Would you do me a favor?
There's only one woman
more beautiful than you,
and if you should happen to see her,
tell her I said hello, would you?
[chuckles] I'll tell mama you said hi.
["She's a Bad Mama Jama (She's Buiit,
She's Stacked)" by Carl Carlton playing]
I'll be damned.
[chuckles]
I-- I--
I'm not quite sure
I know what just happened.
[giggles]
You know what you need to know.
- Okay? It's better that way.
- Okay.
You are full of surprises.
Life can be like that sometimes.
Wow. Well, you know
what they say about life.
When life gives you lemons...
Make a gin and tonic and throw the lemon
on the rim for garnish.
Well, gimme my lemon.
[chuckles]
[song continues]
- [Brian chuckles]
- [Gigi giggles]
[Brian] Yeah. This is gonna be dope.
Yes, it is.
This is gonna be business.
There's no reason business
can't have pleasure, right?
Look, I'm not here for all that.
This is a short-term deal for me.
I just need to make enough money
to take care of my daughter's situation
and I'm out.
Okay. Okay, okay, okay.
- I got it.
- All right.
[Brian] We'll get through this together...
- Yeah.
- ...and do the things we need to do.
- You know what I mean?
- That's right.
- [engine stops]
- So, what's next?
Tre sent this.
Well... Time to go to work.
- [hip-hop playing]
- [Brian chuckles]
[man and woman]
Good afternoon, Your Honor.
[judge] Good afternoon.
Where are we on this?
The State's agreed to drop
all the charges against Ashley Davis.
In conjunction, Your Honor,
my client has agreed
to not sue the city
for her daughter's injuries.
It is with complete agreement
from all parties
that the officer responsible for said
injuries be terminated immediately.
And we're all in agreement on this?
- Yes, ma'am.
- Yes, Your Honor.
Good.
Your cut.
And the expenses for your colleagues.
Well, damn, Gigi. What you lookin' like
brand-new money?
- Every job has its perks, right?
- Mm-hmm.
- Ho, shit.
Whoo.
Look like somebody gonna buy me
some brand-new shit myself.
- I'll holla at ya.
- All right, Bobby.
I'd like to pay the tuition
for my daughter Ashley Davis.
I'd like to pay for the rest of the year.
- Congratulations. Here you go.
- Thank you, sir.
Thank you.
Let's go for a ride.
Oh, my God, I'm excited!
Wait! How did...
[Ashley giggles]
Let's toast to your success.
Thank you.
- [Chris] Congratulations.
- [Gigi] I appreciate you.
- Sexy walk.
- Mm-hmm.
You might be all right, man.
- What?
- You might be all right.
- What up, boss?
- [Tre] Checkin' in. How we lookin'?
Good shit. I'm making these drops
right now as we speak.
[Tre] Good.
- Hit me when you're done.
- All right.
[Gigi] Thank you, sir.
[Pastor] It's a pleasure
doing business with you.
[Gigi] I look forward
to many more days like this.
[softly] What?
What the hell are y'all doing in my house?
Look.
The door was unlocked, I knocked.
I guess you didn't hear me come in.
You got my package?
Coming here is completely off-script.
Well, I'm rewriting the script.
And the first change
is Bobby's running point on all
my transactions.
I don't think that's a good idea.
Look, I don't know you. And I definitely
don't know if I can trust you.
Bobby's like family. I trust him.
Just like that?
Hmm. Just like that.
- So why the change?
- Listen.
Why, why don't matter.
Bobby is my man, see?
Now tell him what to do.
Come on.
You're the boss.
["Money" by Caleb James playing]
[Gigi] First, you need to go to several
banks and open up accounts.
They need to be in different names,
so you'll need ID.
I'll give you a set of checks
and you deposit them.
Make sure you only make
one deposit per account.
We don't wanna arouse any suspicions.
[Bobby] Right, girl, I got this.
This ain't brain surgery.
This is not rocket science.
Okay, Einstein.
Whoa, speaking of Einstein...
Hey, baby.
Um, what kind of drawers you got on?
You got the pink ones on?
Good. I hope you took
them big white ones off.
Take them off. Thank you.
[Gigi] This is not gonna work.
- [Tre] It's workin'.
- [Gigi] I'm serious.
Tre, one wrong move
can mess this whole thing up.
Then I suggest you train him well, then.
You're the boss.
Goddamn right, I'm the boss.
- [door opens]
- Good night, Gigi.
[door closes]
[Dahlia] Oh, this green is pretty.
[Gigi] Oh, it is.
[Dahlia] Oh. [chuckles]
What's that all about?
What's what all about?
That old cheesy grin you got from
your daddy plastered all over your face.
Things are good, that's all.
You seein' somebody?
Ma, it is not 1970.
My happiness is not tied to a man.
[Dahlia chuckles]
Okay, then what?
'Cause you sure been lookin'
awfully fancy lately.
Mm-hmm.
[sighs] It's just that,
for the first time...
probably since the divorce...
I finally feel free.
- Let's sit down. Yeah.
- Wanna sit? Okay.
[Dahlia sighs]
Ah, yeah.
Yeah, I just...
I finally feel like I don't need
anyone's permission
or approval to do what I wanna do.
And that's what you want?
Isn't that what everybody wants?
I don't know. You know,
from my experience...
doing it alone could be...
tough.
Yeah, well, I tried the whole marriage
and family thing,
and we see how that turned out.
Well, you don't have to give up.
I don't have to put
my life on hold either.
Remember when we used to come here?
[chuckles]
Baby.
I know you think you got it
all figured out,
and maybe you do.
But, baby girl, there's more to life
than just making money.
Now, do you need a man
to make you happy?
No. [chuckles]
But I also don't want you
to end up alone.
Maybe the right one needs to just find me.
I'm so done putting my life on hold.
I know what I wanna do
and I'm finally clear
on where I wanna go.
Well, just know it's awfully lonely
at the top, baby girl.
I understand.
I'm built for it.
["Because of You" by Bryan Abrams playing]
Mm-mm-mm.
Good afternoon.
How can I help you?
I'm here to make a deposit,
and, uh... get your number.
Well, I can help you with your deposit,
mister...?
Big Rob, but my friends call me Bobby.
B-Smoove, B-Nice, or just B.
Hmm. Okay. That's a lot of names.
- I'm a lot of man.
- All right.
- Let me see what we have.
- Mm-mm-mm.
- Big business, doing big things.
- Okay.
Let's see here.
Two million dollars.
Big man doing big business, baby.
Damn, but you're real fine.
Can I get your Snapchat though?
[teller] Sure.
Like that, huh?
Have a good day.
You too.
Hi.
I think you need
to come take a look at this.
- [man] I'll be right down.
- Thank you.
[emcee] I need y'all to help me
welcome to the stage
Chris "The King" Connolly!
- [Brian] You need to slow down.
- [Bobby] I can't slow down.
Man, look, man, you drinkin'
like a damn fish, dawg.
You gotta live life, motherfucker. Shit.
How y'all doing this evening?
[cheering]
I'm gonna keep this short but sweet.
After 20 years of grinding here
at Club Symphony,
it's time for your boy to step on down.
[fans, protesting] Oh, no!
- What the hell was that?
- Man, how--
How we gonna run game?
But I don't want y'all
to get this twisted. [chuckles]
Because it's getting ready
to get bigger and better.
Introducing the new club owner
of Symphony.
Put your hands together
for my girl, your girl,
Miss Gigi Davis!
[cheering]
She be worth it. That motherfucker there,
it's my shit now! I like her.
I like her a lot.
[audience cheering]
Thank you, Mr. C.
I have to say in front of everyone
thank you so much for being
such a positive influence on me
and everyone here at this club.
I've learned so much from you and...
I'm gonna miss you.
Before you go...
I think we wanna hear you
on the mic one more time.
- Can we do a song together?
- Oh, definitely.
[crowd cheering]
- ["Make You Feel" playing]
- [fan] Do that shit!
Come on, y'all,
put your hands together.
[fan] Sing that shit, baby.
♪ We've already made it this far ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh-ooh ♪
♪ And I don't plan to turn back now ♪
- ♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh-ooh ♪
- ♪ No ♪
♪ Lovin' you is my favorite part ♪
♪ Made you mine ♪
♪ Met you in your heart ♪
♪ They don't know how it feels ♪
♪ To have a love like we do ♪
♪ No, baby ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Ten toes down ♪
♪ I'm gonna stay and be the man for you ♪
♪ I'll grind for you, baby, yeah ♪
♪ I'll make you... ♪
- Now, that ain't a bad idea.
-Yes, it is.
Wish she wouldn't have did it like that
though, but that wasn't a bad idea.
[Brian] But she didn't say anything to us.
- She didn't even run it past us.
- You right.
♪ I never thought we'd end up
being this way ♪
♪ But it feels so, so good ♪
♪ When I look back in time ♪
♪ Every bit was worth it ♪
Well, fuck it. If she in charge,
I'd rather some ass and titties
around here being in charge.
Fuck it. Come on, man,
let's get some girls, man. Fuck that.
[emcee] Put your hands together
for Mulatto!
["Bitch from the Souf" playing]
- [man] What is he doing?
- [crowd jeering]
[lyrics echoing]
- [bottles rattling]
- [crowd booing]
[crowd jeering]
[man] Get your ass up!
Look at him!
[leering continues]
[laughter and jeering continue]
[Bobby murmuring]
Bobby, what the hell are you doing?
What's it look like?
I'm turning up with my people.
You're drunk. Please go home.
How you gonna kick me outta my own spot?
Excuse you?
Ain't... ain't we the new...
the new owners, right?
- We need to talk.
- Not right now.
- I need to go get me another drink.
- I'm not asking.
Hey, what the-- what the hell
y'all supposed to do?
I told you we need to talk.
And I told you fuck off, Gigi.
You always fuckin' with me.
Bobby, don't make me embarrass you
more than you already have.
Bitch, bitch, get out my face.
I'm not gonna be
too many more bitches tonight.
Bitch, didn't you hear Tre?
I'm running this shit.
Huh? I put your sorry ass on.
You wouldn't be shit without me.
You got one more time to call me a bitch.
Bitch, fuck...
Ow! Damn.
Gigi, that's how you wanna play?
Huh? That's how you wanna play?
- Yep.
- I'm gonna see your ass soon.
Y'all too big, bitch.
Congratulations on your new spot.
- Right?
- Oh, Brian.
Partners, right?
[phone buzzing]
Hey, what's up, Brian?
So you bought the club, too.
Well, if you want big things,
you have to make big moves.
Yeah, well...
I still think you're moving too fast.
See, that's your problem right there,
Brian. You think too small.
Brian, Chris gave me
an opportunity and I took it.
Simple as that.
I'm tired of working for other people.
It was time for me
to have something of my own,
so I took my cut and I bought the club.
And I was thinking that you
and I could do it together.
We make a good team.
We're supposed to be a team?
Can't you just be happy for me?
Hello?
Bye, Brian.
No, I'm not happy for you.
[Dahlia] I just want her to do so well.
[fans cheering]
- Come on, come on!
- Let's go, baby!
[Dahlia coughing deeply]
You need some water.
No, no, baby, you stay. I'll get it.
Ahem. I'll be back.
[coughing]
[coach] Stay on your toes!
Move your feet now!
[phone buzzing]
- Hey.
Ashley didn't tell me you were coming.
I wanted to surprise her.
- Oh, okay.
- And you.
- Maybe.
- Really?
I did want to bring this
to your attention, though.
Um...
Your new place of business is being
investigated for money laundering.
Yeah. We've been watching
these guys for a while now.
And it's starting to make me feel like...
your new investment might just be
another case of Gigi's bad luck.
I don't have nothing to do
with these people at all.
Got some new shoes, huh?
You know, you ever wonder why...
some people, no matter
how nice the shoes,
just can't keep themselves
from stepping in shit?
Oh, well.
Just consider this a courtesy call, uh...
You know, a baby head start,
you know what I'm saying?
Okay, Greg.
Don't let me catch you.
Hey! How you doin'?
D-up, baby, d-up!
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
Yeah, my baby got some skills on her.
You know you get that from your daddy's
side of the family, right?
[Gigi] Yeah, you got the height
from your mother.
[family laughing]
[Greg] Gigi, don't make me
take you out on that court.
Greg, don't make me dunk on you.
Hey, Ashley, nana's gonna
take you home, okay?
- All right, great game.
- Thank you. I love you.
- Good job.
- I love you too, baby.
- Can you take her, please?
- See you all later.
- [Ashley] Oh, it's cold.
- [Greg] All right, be safe.
I almost wanna say thank you.
She was actually really--
[Tre] What's up, mama?
This a bad time?
Yeah. Yeah, this is a bad time.
This is... where you walk off.
- Come again?
- Are you deaf?
- I said walk the fuck off.
- Who the fuck--
Tre, can you give us a minute, please?
What, you-- you know this clown?
Yeah, nigga, I'm her new man.
What's up?
So that's where you're getting
your new shoes from?
You think you're all that
'cause you fuckin' a dope boy now?
I'm gonna need a little bit more respect
coming out of your mouth, homie, for real.
No, this is all you need to respect,
homie, for real for real.
So this is how this is gonna go.
Tomorrow morning I'm filing for full legal
and physical custody of our daughter.
- What?
- Yes. Our daughter.
And you won't be contesting
the filing because if you do,
then I'll be compelled to tell
the court exactly why I'm petitioning,
and I don't think neither one of y'all
can have that.
Wow, wow!
- Greg, don't do this.
- You did this! It's already done.
But look at the bright side,
now you got all the time in the world
to have a whole project apartment
full of lyin' ass,
drug-dealin' ass, uneducated children
with no morals or self-respect.
- Tre.
- No, no, no, no.
Your fucking ex is a fed?
- Hey, don't... Don't say shit to me, man.
- Tre!
Tre.
- [door closes]
- [car starts]
Shit!
[car drives off]
[door opens]
Who was that guy at Ashley's school?
I knew you would ask that.
Mm-hmm.
Then who is he?
Just a friend.
Girl, do you think I'm that stupid?
Ma, I love you. And I respect you.
But I'm grown now.
I don't have to explain myself to you.
Yeah.
Well, I guess...
you don't have to explain
this either, huh?
- Huh?
- Ma.
Why are you going through my stuff?
What are you doing
with a briefcase full of dope money?
Whatever you have going on,
you need to stop it.
- Now.
- I know what I'm doing.
Do you? Do you really?
Hmm?
Who's gonna take care of your daughter
when you go to jail? Or worse.
[coughing]
- Please stop.
- No, damn it, you stop!
- [coughing]
- Mom.
- Let's get you something.
- [coughing continues]
I didn't raise you...
to get into this mess.
Mom. I'm not dad.
I'm not into any gangster stuff.
I'm not on drugs.
I'm not trying to shoot the city up.
This is just business.
Business? With a briefcase full of cash.
[scoffs]
[Dahlia sighs]
I've been through this...
madness...
with your father.
Do you know how many
so-called hustlers I've seen...
who think they figured out
how to beat the system?
It's a pipe dream. You know why?
Because you can't beat the system.
Sooner or later,
every hustle comes to an end.
[coughing]
Mommy.
Get some rest. Come on.
[coughing]
Get up. Come on. Please.
I got you.
Baby...
[coughs, clears throat]
Let me just say this, okay?
The only players that make it
to the end of this game...
winds up doing time...
or dead...
or in a wheelchair like your father.
Think about it.
- I love you.
- I love you too.
Fu...
What the hell is this? Frozen?
Oh, no, no, no!
Damn!
Man, we got a problem.
[phone buzzing]
[Gigi] Hey, Pastor.
Blessings. We have an issue.
What's wrong?
One of your associates broke protocol
and got their accounts frozen.
Are you serious?
Kidding you is not something I do.
You need to handle this.
[sighs] Okay.
I'm on it.
You remember
what we talked about, okay?
Keep your rhythm.
Fight!
Don't forget to let that jab go, okay?
- You all right?
- I got it.
Keep your hands up.
[little Gigi] I'm built for this.
Fight!
Baby, don't forget your iPad.
Why do I have to live with dad?
- It's just for a little while.
- How long?
I don't know.
Will you please help me
get your stuff together?
Why won't you just tell me
what's going on?
It is not the time.
Now, will you please help me
get your stuff together?
Ashley?
Honey, come here.
Your dad went to the courts
and got the judge to grant him
temporary custody.
- Is this because of the fight I got into?
- No, baby, no.
No.
This has nothing to do with that.
You're not to blame, okay?
Okay, well, then...
what if I don't wanna go?
Unfortunately that's not up to you.
Or me. I don't want this either, baby.
Just know that your dad and I
love you very much.
We want what's best for you.
We just don't agree
on what that is right now.
Hey, we're gonna be okay.
We're gonna get through this, okay?
Come here.
[approaching footsteps]
- Grandma.
- Baby.
Now, listen to me.
Both of y'all.
This family has been
through worse than this.
A lot worse.
My house, your daddy's house,
this house...
[coughs]
...ain't nothing but four walls
and some furniture.
What matters is that we are family,
and that will never change,
regardless of where you sleep at night.
- Understand?
- Yeah.
Yeah. It's time to go.
- Mama.
- Come here.
[gasps]
What happened to my money?
Hmm?
Bobby did exactly
what I told him not to do.
Bullshit, I did what I always do.
You can't possibly be this fucking stupid!
You had one job, one!
- Shh!
- [Gigi] One...
Tell me about my money, Gigi.
He deposited the entire two million
into one account.
- What?
- All at once.
The IRS flagged it, it's frozen.
He can't be trusted. He was probably drunk
when he did this shit.
Let me tell you somethin',
I ain't never been drunk.
Now, I might have been a little fucked up,
but I wasn't drunk,
and I can be trustworthy!
You the one that can't be trusted!
Especially coming from somebody
who got a ex-husband as a fed.
This ain't about me.
Bullshit! It been about you, Gigi.
The day since you came in,
it been about Gi-gi.
We was doin' just fine
until your ragged ass came in here
and got us caught up in your bullshit.
You were doing just fine?
You were a RICO prosecution
waiting to fucking happen.
You should know, huh?
Tre, gimme the word.
I been waitin' to pop this bitch.
I don't have time for this shit.
I gotta clean up your mess.
- [grunge]
- [Gigi gasps]
[body thuds]
Tre.
You know, Bobby was
the closest thing I had to a brother.
Yet I just put a fucking bullet
in his head for fucking with my money!
Look at him, look at him.
I said fuckin' look at him. Look at him!
- Okay.
- Mm-hmm.
Yeah, get real close.
Get real fucking close.
Yeah.
I wanna know everything.
From this moment, I need to know
every fucking thing
that's going on with my money,
you hear me?
- Tre, it's...
- Shut the fuck up! Shut up!
Hmm... Yeah.
You know, Gigi, shit's changed.
I need you to call whoever's in charge,
"cause I'm gonna need somebody to tell me
what the fuck's going on,
or I'll start doing things my way.
Hmm?
Open your fuckin' mouth,
open your mouth.
If I could do that to my best friend,
what the fuck you think I'd do
to a bitch ass federal prosecutor,
a whore of a ex wife,
or a piece of shit for a daughter? Huh?
- Clean this shit up.
- [whimpering]
[departing footsteps]
["Nobody Loves the Blues But Me"
by Little G Weevil playing]
Sorry for barging in.
Uh, my client Tre is curious
about how all this works.
I assume this stems
from our little bump in the road?
Correct. He insists on having
more information.
- A lot more.
- Insists?
Yeah. Is that a problem?
- Son, slow--
-Wait, wait, wait, no.
"Son"?
Nigga, I'm not your son
and you definitely ain't my father.
No, no, no, so what's going on
with my money, man?
You brought that to make your point?
I wasn't planning on having much
conversation with you, old man.
Granted, I'm not as young as I once was,
but, uh, in that amount of time,
I was able to learn a couple things.
What I learned was, what's better
than being tough is being prepared.
[rifle cocks]
Excellent.
Tre. Have a seat.
Are you familiar with the term
"Black Wall Street"?
No, I'm not.
[Pastor] Black Wall Street is
the most successful black economy
in American financial history.
That is, until it was burned
to the ground, the entire city,
by white supremacists in 1921.
And what's that got to do with me, man?
Well, everything disappeared
except the intangibles.
The buildings and the banks
were destroyed,
but, uh, the information,
the knowledge,
the connections, the network,
that remained.
And... [chuckles] what are we doing?
Tre, you are talking to the head
of the largest,
longest-running most successful
money-laundering operation
in the history of this country.
[chuckles]
So the church is a front?
The Lord works in mysterious ways.
This particular way is one
where we have an institution
that's under our complete control
without being challenged.
And, uh, we use that behind the scenes
to further the interests
of the black community
in every way and situation that we can.
Also, as a side note,
primarily a cash business.
The point is,
your money is perfectly safe.
Well, how would I be sure?
Give me $20.
Thank you, sister,
for your kind donation of $10.
You mean $20.
That was $10.
But she just gave you $20.
I'm gonna need you to prove that
or say "allegedly."
[laughs]
The secret is in the simplicity.
- So that's it?
- That's it.
- Well, how does it work if you--
- Hold on.
Before we go any further...
What I shared with you thus far,
I shared with you so that
you could have peace of mind,
so that you could feel better.
But any further conversation
is a bit much for me to be
having with an outsider, to be honest.
Well, I mean...
two million dollars, I would think,
puts me on the inside, so...
[chuckles]
What's funny?
Let's just say you're not
one of his bigger clients.
I don't give a shit, I told you I need
to know about my money,
so what's going on with my money?
Before you accidentally
insult the Lord and I...
Gigi, your call.
Go ahead.
My misunderstanding.
It's just a financial issue.
[chuckles]
The Lord has blessed us
to not have financial issues.
What's this?
That is to thank you for the assistance
that you gave
in building the senior center
that the community has been looking
forward to for ten years.
And that one is for
the basketball gymnasium
that you supplied the buildout for.
The community appreciates that as well.
That should help with the money
frozen in your account.
Just like that?
Just like that. Just like Gigi said.
The secret is the simplicity.
Okay. Thank you.
Ashley, have you seen Daddy's--
Oh, it's right here.
I'm moving way too fast this morning.
Whoo! You about ready?
Better get you dropped off
so I can get to my meeting.
Yeah, almost.
Can I call Mom when I come back home?
Of course you can, baby.
You don't need permission
to call your mom.
[softly] Yeah, only to see her.
Ashley, we've been through this
SO many times.
And every time you and Mama
get into a fight,
I'm the one that gets stuck in the middle.
It's not fair.
Life isn't fair. Okay?
It's about time you learned that.
I'm sorry.
I'm doing the best I can
with what I've been given.
If you do something or your mom
does something to make it worse,
it just makes it harder for me.
I'm doing my best.
Well...
forgive us for being such a burden.
Ashley... Ashley, don't be like that.
That's not what I'm trying to say.
What are you doing here?
Good morning to you too.
What are you doing here, Gi?
Greg, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I cheated on you.
I'm sorry I broke up our family.
I'm sorry I broke up our marriage.
["Never Neverland"
by Lyfe Jennings begins]
Greg, sit down.
♪ Feels like something's missing,
but I just don't know ♪
♪ It's like I'm not the same man
I was before... ♪
I was depressed.
Couldn't you see that?
I did everything I knew
how to do to be a good wife to you.
You went back on your word.
Yeah.
You refused to support me
when I wanted to get back to my music.
Do you have any idea
how much that hurt me?
♪ Those fellas live in Never Neverland ♪
♪ They'll never understand ♪
♪ What it's like to be in love ♪
♪ Never Neverland ♪
♪ Right next to Peter Pan... ♪
There's my half of the lawyer fees.
♪ Those fellas live in Never Neverland ♪
♪ They'll never understand... ♪
Look at me.
No matter what you may think of me...
I love our daughter.
You know better than anyone else...
I'm a damn good mother.
["Never Neverland" continues]
♪ You're gonna be my wife eventually ♪
♪ It don't matter what these fellas
say to me ♪
♪ There's no changing my mind ♪
♪ So you-all can pray for me ♪
♪ Never, Neverland ♪
♪ Right next to Peter Pan ♪
♪ Where nobody wants to grow old ♪
♪ In Never Neverland ♪
♪ They'll never understand ♪
♪ What it's like to be in love ♪
Hey.
Why am I here?
I just wanted to clear the air.
Clear the air? Is that what you call it?
What do you want me to do?
Our friend was murdered.
What I want you to do is to care.
I do care.
Yeah, well, you got
a funny ass way of showing it.
Oh...
What's this?
It's your bonus.
Keep it, I'm done.
- You're quitting?
- Yes.
Brian, that's crazy.
Yeah, well, people do
crazy shit when they're scared.
And Bobby's dead,
and I don't wanna be next.
[softly] Damn.
Oh.
Hey, Tre.
Everything good?
Yeah.
The accounts are back...
up and running.
That's good.
Hey... ahem.
I was on my way out.
I gotta pick my daughter up.
I don't want my ex to...
again.
Speaking of your ex...
how do I say this? Ahem.
Your ex, if he didn't have that badge,
I would have slapped the shit
out that motherfucker.
But-but-but...
I do love the fact
that he's a good father.
See, I never knew my dad.
You know, he went to prison
right after I was born,
and somebody killed him...
not too long after that.
So I never really...
I never had the luxury
of knowing what it felt like
to have a father's love, you know?
Yeah, it's fucked up.
But I gotta admit...
your ex...
he got it down to a science.
[softly] Look. Look.
He's a good daddy.
He's a good dad.
Let's zoom in so you can see her big.
She's a pretty little thing, ain't she?
Yeah.
Just like her fine-ass mama.
Damn.
I think we have an understanding, Gigi.
And I think everything's
gonna be just fine.
[shape fingers]
So tell your, uh, beautiful family...
Tre said hi.
What?
[phone buzzing]
Hello?
What?
["Precious Lord, Take my Hand"
by Kisha Grandy playing]
Oh... Okay, I'll be right there.
[sobbing]
No... ma...
[song continues]
Thank you for coming.
There isn't anywhere else
in the world for me to be other than here.
Why didn't I know the most beautiful woman
in the world was sick?
She didn't want anyone to know.
She still loved you.
Yeah.
Love was not one of the issues.
She just realized wasn't the best
environment for raising a child.
She wanted what was best for you.
Hey, Grandpa.
Oh.
- Are you okay?
- Yes.
[softy] Hey.
You okay, honey?
- You all right?
- Yeah, I'm good, Daddy.
Daddy, can I ride with Mom? Please?
- Yeah, of course. I don't see why not.
- Yeah.
- You good?
- Yes, thank you.
- How are you doing, Pastor?
- Gregory.
[Greg] Good to see you.
Unbelievable.
Look, you have to ride with me, all right?
Tell your mother you're gonna
see her later.
- But you just said...
- No buts, Ashley.
Okay?
This is almost incredible.
You really don't get it.
[scoffs]
- Excuse me.
- Sorry about your mother-in-law.
What's he doing here?
I don't know. I didn't invite him.
I just, uh...
wanted to pay my respects.
- Sorry for your loss.
- Thank you.
Take care.
All right, cool.
All right, so I'm gonna
bring the other half.
Yeah, I'm gonna bring
the other half tonight.
[Pastor] It appears your associate
is a loose cannon.
I know.
Knowing is half the battle.
It's time to take out the trash.
I'm on it.
[Tre] Ahem.
I'm... so sorry about that.
I had to take that.
It's okay.
- Thanks for coming.
- Now, of course, you know?
I'm here for you, you know?
I mean, uh...
maybe you should come
to the crib when this is done.
[Gigi] Hmm.
I've got to spend time
with the family today.
How about tomorrow?
- Yeah, tomorrow works.
- Okay.
All right.
I gotcha.
[indistinct chatter]
Hey, what's up?
Burning the midnight oil too, huh?
Yeah. Did you cash a check
for 25 grand a few days ago?
It's been traced back to an account linked
to the laundering scheme.
You're being suspended, Greg.
That's effective immediately.
Leave your shield on my desk.
That bitch!
Fuckin' Gigi. Oh, my God.
[phone buzzing]
Hello?
Did you receive a gift?
Mm-hmm.
And how did it fit?
Like a glove.
["Girls Need Love"
by Summer Walker playing]
Shit, you're a motherfuckin' beast.
Why don't I take you to lunch?
[Gigi] I'm not interested.
[Tre] Let's zoom in so you can see her.
She's a pretty little thing, ain't she?
[Gigi] ♪ Trust me, I gotcha ♪
♪ I'll never let you down ♪
So, what's up for tonight?
I have to help a friend clean up a mess.
What kind of mess?
It doesn't have anything
to do with you.
Nothin' to do with me, huh?
That don't mean I can't look out for you.
I can look out for myself.
- You can look out for yourself?
- Mm-hmm.
[Tre] Are you sure?
Is that sincerity I hear?
The big bad gangster...
- catching feelings now, huh?
- [laughs]
You know the vibe.
[Pastor] Don't be afraid
to double tap if you need to.
["For the Love of Money" playing]
[Pastor] Hello?
[Gigi] Send the cleaner.
♪ For the love of money ♪
You okay?
Ashley?
Mom, you sure this is a good idea?
It's called being the bigger person, baby.
Is that what you would do?
Sometimes in life you...
you have to do what you have to do.
And I do understand that more than most.
Yeah.
But you can't let
those moments define you.
So...
maybe that night, in that moment...
you didn't have a choice.
Mom?
Yeah.
All I'm saying is, right here, right now,
you do.
You have a choice.
And what you do with that choice
determines what kind of person you are,
and more importantly,
what kind of woman you're gonna become.
You need me to... come?
No.
I got it.
I was built for this.
Hold on, baby, don't forget this.
Hi. I got these for you.
I'm sorry about everything.
[Saundra] It was all my fault.
I'm sorry too.
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
["About Money" by D.C. Young Fly playing]
["Money" by Caleb James playing]