[air whips]
[whimsical music plays]
Whoa!
Got a couple bogies
on my tail!
-I'm gonna get you!
-Gonna tear you up good!
Oh, no!
He's still back there!
[Rottweilers growl]
I'm gonna die!
-[whimpers]
-[panting]
-He's fast!
-I mean, can't we all
just get along?
[laughs]
Suckers.
-He's over there.
-Get him!
Thor:
No one makes a fool
of Thor and Damien
and lives! Yeah!
Damien: Yeah.
[circus music plays]
[clown chuckling]
Whoa.
[panting]
Wha-- Oh, uh-oh.
[chuckling]
Whoa, too fast,
down shift, down shift.
Damien: Oh, hey!
Slow down, you!
-Chihuahua: Oh.
-Child: Hey, check it out!
-Hey, kids, how's it going?
-Kids: Whoa!
-Kids: Whoa! Hey!
-Thor: Hey!
-Chihuahua: Whoa.
-Look at 'em go!
-Thor: Hey, wait up!
-Chihuahua: Whoa!
-[kids giggle]
- [puppy chuckles]
[kids shouting]
Alley-oop!
Carrot cake, my favorite!
Chihuahua: Whoa!
[laughing]
[gasps]
[groans]
[laughing]
[growling]
Thor:
Ooh, I heard clowns
taste like chicken!
-Get him!
-[clown gasps]
-[shoes squeaking]
-[panting]
Whoo! Hello?
-Huh?
-[kids chatter]
-[squeaking]
-You better run, clowny.
[growling]
Hey, fellas,
where're you going?
[shoes squeaking]
[snarling]
-[barking]
-[screams]
[laughs]
Hey, you clowns,
over here.
-[barks]
-Hey, there goes
our lunch.
-Damien:
Oh yeah, hurry up.
He's getting away, man.
[mimics airplane]
-Whoa!
-Got ya!
Thor:
Let me out of here!
Damien:
Oh, it's muy, muy,
muy mal.
[Chihuahua barks]
[barking]
Hey, little doggie,
good boy.
-[barking]
-Come on, little doggie.
-Atta' boy, just stay still.
-[growling]
-Come here, doggie.
-Okay.
[screams]
[muffled]
Make a run for it,
fellas!
Thor:
Thanks, pal,
we owe you one.
-[dogcatcher screams]
-Don't mention it.
I'll just hang out
back here.
[screaming]
-[door creaks closed]
-[keys jingle]
[lock clanking echoes]
Male Basset:
Somebody get me...
-out... of here!
-Prim Female: What is
that terrible smell?
-Darling, do something.
-Prim Male: I demand to
see a lawyer.
-Really!
-Male Dog: Hey,
when do we eat, huh?
I'm starving.
Throw me a bone
or something, huh?
Hey, hey,
I'm innocent, I tell ya'.
I'm innocent.
It was all a big mistake.
It was just a nip.
I never even
broke the skin.
Okay, now look,
if we use the air vent,
we can be out
of here before sunrise.
[sighs]
Well, ol' boy,
you really done it
to yourself this time--
the slammer.
It's one thing
to break out of
a backyard,
but this--
I should have stayed
with that last kid.
Having cans
tied to my tail
doesn't seem so bad now.
-[sighs]
-[door opens]
[woman through P.A.]
Please bring the papers up
on the schnauzer mix.
Hello!
Anybody home?
[over P.A.]
We need a clean-up
in kennel eight.
[sighs]
[bell rings]
Hi.
-May I help you?
-Hm-hmm.
-Psst, hey you!
-Who, me?
Yeah, listen,
I'm gonna break
out of here.
-Break out of here!
-Yeah, just listen, listen.
Okay, we're gonna
get out of here tonight.
We're leaving.
[snickers]
Chihuahua:
You mean you want
to take me with you?
Mutt:
Look, will you just--
Will you just--
Stop looking at me, will you?
They're gonna get suspicious.
I'm not looking at you.
I'm not.
Mutt:
Don't be so obvious.
You understand?
-[whistles]
-Chihuahua: Okay.
Mutt:
Someone's coming.
Now here is
a nice friend.
-She's very gentle.
-Oh, no, no, no.
This won't do.
I'm looking for
a small kitty.
Oh, I thought
you wanted a dog.
Basset: Meow.
Chihuahua: Uh-oh.
It's diaper man.
-[mutt laughs]
-Basset: Spare the diaper.
Dogcatcher: Remember me?
Don't I get a last request
or something?
- Uh ...
-Dead dog walking.
This is getting
kind of serious.
-[Dogcatcher laughs]
-Mutt: So long, pal.
You can have my collar.
I won't be needing it.
And you, you can
have my fleas.
Golden Retriever:
[laughs] Oh, thanks.
Hey, Max, I got
about a dozen bones
buried under the old
oak tree in the park.
They're all yours.
Well, so long, fellas.
-Here we go.
- Huh?
-This is more like it.
-But you said you wanted--
I know what I said.
I want this one.
Oh, boy!
A grandmother!
I finally get to snuggle up
on a crocheted mat
in front of a fireplace.
-Male Dog: What a lucky dog.
-Deal's off, guys!
Stay away from my stuff
or I'll kill you.
-Grr, grr.
-You'll like him.
-He's sweet.
- Ciao, diaper boy.
No, he's not for me.
I'm getting him for
my granddaughter.
What? A kid?
Oh, put me back.
Please, please put me back!
Hmm, kind of
a strange-looking kitty.
Help! Help! Please!
-[engine revs]
-[tires squeal]
Man: Hey, slow down!
[man mutters]
Hey, how fast you going?
No peeking, kitty.
You're supposed to
be a surprise for Hayley.
I'll be mincemeat surprise
if you don't slow down.
[sighs]
Hi, my name's Stephen.
What's yours?
What's that?
"The Scarlet Pimpernel"?
What's it about?
Sounds cool.
You're new, huh?
Everyone at school
thinks you're stuck up,
but I don't.
I think you're nice.
Bye.
[car honks]
Hi, Hayley.
[tires screech]
[people muttering]
Uh-oh, we got company.
- Ow! Ow!
-Sorry, kitty.
-[huffs]
-[crowd clamoring]
Man:
Ms. Jeffries, Ms. Jeffries,
Ms. Jeffries, over here.
Can I ask you
a quick question, please?
[overlapping speech]
I have no comment.
[clamoring]
Leave me alone.
Are you hounded
by the IRS?
Are you going to
give in to the harassment
by the IRS, Mrs. Jeffries?
I am not.
I have no comment.
I have nothing
to say to you.
Please, leave me
and get off my property.
Reporter: The money
is the important part
and the viewers need to
know what's gong on here.
[clamoring continues]
[television turns on]
This is KPJK coming to you live
from the Jeffries mansion
where Ethel Jeffries,
the owner of a chain
of bakeries...
Cameraman: Hey, there's
someone in there!
-Man: Oh, yeah?
-Hey, little girl!
-Come here! Come here!
-No, don't shut the window.
Don't shut it!
The IRS has no idea exactly
how much those profits are.
The IRS has asked Mrs. Jeffries
if they could search her house
to verify the amounts
of profits she claimed,
but she has
denied their request.
Woman: Please tell us
what's going on!
-Mrs. Jeffries!
-If you could--
Mrs. Jeffries,
good afternoon.
I'm Special Agent
Bruce Mechanic.
This is Special Agent
Ellen Meiser.
We're from the Fresno office
of the IRS.
I've already told you
my money stays where it is.
Now get off my property.
The old lady's loaded?
* Dreams do come true
[laughing]
I'm rich!
-Whoohoo!
-[gun clicks]
It's a giant rat!
Giant rat!
-What?
-Put the gun away,
Agent Meiser.
Remember, we're from
the new, kinder, gentler
Internal Revenue Service.
That's right.
I forgot.
Mechanic:
Oh, we'll be back,
Ms. Jeffries,
with a court order.
You do that.
Reporter:
A kinder gentler IRS
or wolves in
sheep's clothing?
I'll be back with
the full story
right after this break.
Hayley, where
are you, honey?
Hi, Grandma,
you were just on TV.
I hope they captured
my good side.
Hayley: I guess so.
I wasn't paying attention.
-I was reading.
-Reading?
Well, I hope if was
a Nancy Drew mystery.
No, "Les Miserables."
Hmm, well, I guess
it could be worse.
It could be
"Lady Chatterley's Lover."
No, I read that last year.
-You did?
-Hm-hmm.
[sighs]
I, um--
I bought you a present.
I don't want
any more presents.
You know, Hayley,
it's been six months
since your parents died.
I can't expect you
not to be sad, sweetheart,
but to stay locked
in your room
morning, noon,
and night reading,
it really worries me.
"The love of learning,
the sequestered nooks,
and all the sweet serenity
of books..."
Henry Wadsworth Longfellow.
You know your parents
would want you to be happy.
So do I.
Thanks for trying
to cheer me up, Grandma.
Look, I know that
you like kitties.
So I went to the pound
and I bought you one.
Where?
Surprise!
How you doin', babe?
[screams]
Hey, come back.
I'm better than a cat.
So I'm short.
What's the big deal
about size anyway?
Isn't that sweet?
They're playing already.
Reporter:
Ethel Jeffries,
millionaire owner of
a cash-only bakery chain,
the IRS says she must
deposit all of those millions
so she doesn't cheat
the government out of taxes.
She claims that
if she wants to
keep all the money
in her house,
it's her business.
Yesterday, she was
quoted as saying,
"In spite of all the pressure
the IRS is putting on me
"and my bakeries,
the dough must go on."
-And now for sports...
-Thanks for the tip, buddy.
Let's go to--
So we gonna rob
her bakeries?
What? Are you
stupid or something?
Well...
yeah.
She's got millions
stashed in her house.
This is gonna be
like taking candy
from a baby,
like shooting fish
in a barrel!
Think about it,
ding-a-ling!
Yeah.
If she's got
millions in her house,
then she must have
a whole load of cash
in every one
of those stores.
Ow! Ow!
Cut it out, Stu.
I'm trying to cook
breakfast over here.
-Is my bacon ready yet?
-[sizzling]
Ow, ow!
-[sputtering]
-Gah!
[spitting]
[hacking]
[gags]
-[pops]
-[hissing]
Hey, I'm getting
hungry back here.
[gargles]
[coughing]
[hissing stops]
[gasps]
You can make
your own darn eggs.
I think I will.
Top notch, Louie.
Top notch.
[slurps]
[groans]
What a lovely backyard.
So peaceful and quiet,
too quiet.
-[gunfire]
-I smell Charlie company.
I'm going in.
[sniffing]
What? What?
[gunfire]
What in the--
I shouldn't be here.
-[gunshot]
-Come on.
Gather yourself together.
-[panting]
-[gunfire]
-It's hot.
-[gunfire continues]
What?
I can tell they're near,
but where are you guys?
-[shouts]
-[cat yowls]
[overlapping shouts]
Ow! Ow! Guys!
[barks]
I'll pulverize you!
I'll mincemeat
out of you.
Don't make me
come up there!
-Grr, grr.
-Siamese 1: Oh, yeah,
pulverize what?
My tail? Ha ha!
You're more
like a hot dog
than a real dog.
-Hey.
-Siamese 2: Hot dog?
That very funny.
Siamese 1: You shut up!
Let's jump this rat
and stick him in a box.
Siamese 2:
Yeah, with the mustard.
What are you two doing
on my turf anyway?
Siamese 1: On your turf?
Everyone knows
we run this neighborhood.
Siamese 2:
Yeah, yeah, what she said,
you tough guy.
You two have
a serious attitude problem.
Siamese 1:
Yeah, go chase
your tail!
Siamese 2:
Yeah, scram,
you hot dog.
Oh, go hack up
a couple fur balls.
-What a jerk!
-Yeah.
Although,
I kinda like him.
Typical cats,
always scratching
and clawing.
Why do the neighbors
always have to be so spooky?
Huh.
[car honks]
[knocking]
-Yes?
-Hi, Mrs. Jeffries.
Sorry, do I know you?
It's me-- Lucretia.
Oh! Yes, Lucretia.
Come on in.
I thought you
were a redhead.
That's when I wanted
to be a fashion model.
This is the new me.
My boyfriend Drac
says that models
have sold out
to the imperialist
corporate parasite.
I've decided to go goth.
Well, that's very
interesting, dear.
You do look
a little different.
That's the idea.
When me and my friends
turn eighteen,
we're all gonna get
our bellybutton's pierced
to show our individualism.
[screams]
Mrs. Jeffries,
you've got rats!
Where? Where?
Hey, be nice.
Oh, that's not a rat.
That's Haley's new kitty.
Oh my gosh.
I'm late for my rehearsal.
You know
the phone numbers
and you know
where Hayley is.
-Up in her room reading.
-Reading.
I'm gonna take my bike
and you just help yourself
to anything in the fridge.
Bye-bye.
Move! Move!
What's your name, anyway?
Mickey Rat?
What's yours? Turd face?
[knocks]
Hayley?
Hey, I'm talking to you.
Who are you?
It's me. Lucretia.
I thought you
were a redhead.
Well, I'm not,
so I'll be downstairs
and then I might
go outside for some fresh air.
So you can make out
with your boyfriend?
-What?
-Nothing. Good night.
[engine starts]
[engine revs]
Okay, she's gone.
The house is empty.
I hope.
Here, write this down.
Granny leaves on motorcycle
with saxophone
at, uh, 1947.
Nineteen?
Huh?
It's military time,
you idiot.
Just write it down.
1947.
What?
7:47.
Jumbo jet?
Ow! Ow!
Okay!
Here, hold this!
-[sizzling]
-Oh, Ohh! It's hot!
It's hot!
[gasping]
Whoo! Ah! Ah!
[groans]
Uh-oh.
-[screaming]
-[clattering]
[music from TV]
[dramatic music]
[screeching]
You all right?
[spooky music plays]
-[punching]
-Man: Emily!
[man screams]
-[crunching]
-[screaming]
[screaming continues]
-Mwuahahaha!
-[shrieks]
-[laughs]
-You stupid idiot.
You scared me
half to death.
[laughs]
You should have
seen your face.
It was classic.
You do that again
and I'll smack you.
How'd you get
in here, anyway?
[muffled]
Uh, your back door
was unlocked.
You know,
you guys really
should lock your doors
at night.
You never know
what kind of creature
might be lurking
in the dark.
[inhales]
Gross.
Come here.
Give me a kiss.
I told you.
No kissing in the house.
Why not?
It's not like someone's
gonna see...
except for maybe him.
What's happening,
hot stuff?
Eww, get away from me!
What is it?
Do my feet stink?
Lucretia, real goth chicks
don't say things like "eww."
-Yeah.
-Well, look at him.
He's freaky.
-Look who's talking.
-He's just a giant rat.
What? You too?
I think he's kinda cool.
Aw, that's what
I'm talking about.
-[TV clicks]
-Hey, I was watching that.
What are you doing?
"Home Alone"'s almost on.
I love that little
Macaulay guy.
Siamese 2:
So what do you think?
We jump him or what?
Siamese 1:
Nah, stupid.
We like cat burglars.
Hey, you smell that?
That short guy
smell kinda like a burrito.
Both:
Ahhh, burrito!
[sniffing]
I'm famished.
Hey, come back.
[barks]
-[whimpers]
-I think you better
stay here and wait
for her to cool off.
Hey, buddy, how about
some of that pop...
corn?
[huffs]
Whew! Well, it'll
take some work,
but I'll figure out a way
to open up that thing.
Open sesame.
[laughs]
Yeah, baby.
Salami, chitterlings, lobster,
pork butt!
Wait, no pork butt?
Cat food?
-Yuck!
-[glass clinking]
What was that?
[whispering]
Sorry.
[straining]
[sniffing]
I don't hear anything, but...
it smells like
a burrito out there.
[gasping]
I better check the windows.
-[electrical surge]
-[grunting]
[screaming]
Looks secure.
I'll check out back.
-[whispering]
-[giggling]
Huh, nobody here either.
Must be losing my touch.
Now where was I?
Oh, yeah, cat food.
-[wood clattering]
-[gasps]
That time I'm sure
I heard something.
Hmm, nothing.
Oh well.
[wood breaks]
[grunting]
Did you see the size
of that rat?
Let's go.
This is humiliating.
If the guys back in
the old neighborhood
knew I was eating cat food,
I'd never hear
the end of it.
Actually, it's not that bad.
Ew, I hate rats.
I just get all funny
whenever I see one.
Aw, shut up, Louie,
act like a man.
Spider!
[shrieks]
[muffled screams]
What was that, Drac?
It was probably
Hayley's pet rat.
Come on, Lucretia!
If you want to be
a high Gothic elite...
[inhaler puffs]
you have to relish
in the dark.
Be strong.
[grunts]
Get your hand
off my leg.
[farts]
Oops.
Ugh, this is some
powerful stuff.
It's locked.
Louie, stick your head
down in that doggie door
and take a look-see.
Well, why do I
always have to do that?
What if there's some big
nasty old dog in there?
If there's a big
nasty old dog in there,
I'll stick my head in.
So get down there
and take a look.
Oh.
Okay.
-[farts]
-[sniffing]
-Eww!
-Get back in there!
Huh? Hey!
[screams]
Rat!
Louie!
I heard something
that time.
It was nothing.
-[grunts]
Hey! That--
-Shh!
Rat!
-[barks]
-[screams]
-[screaming]
-Did you invite
your friends again?
No, I swear.
I mean...
[dramatically] no.
[screaming]
Louie!
Ohh!
Good luck catching
that van, fat boy!
Aww, man, they need
to put an elevator in here.
Classical again?
Girl, what you need
is some Snoop Dog.
He's the bomb.
Well, Hayley's okay.
What could those two
be after?
I'll tell you one thing--
if they come back,
I'll be ready for 'em.
Doors, check.
Windows, check.
Right flank, clear.
Left flank, clear.
Perimeter check, complete.
Everything seems
to check out.
Chihuahua- one.
Intruders- zero.
[door opens]
[rustling]
Rise and shine,
Sleeping Beauty.
How was your rehearsal?
Oh, I think
we're gonna be ready
for next Saturday.
The new base player
kept up with us no problem.
Hey.
It's 8:00.
You don't want to sleep
the whole weekend away,
-do you?
-Grandma,
I don't know about
Lucretia babysitting me.
Oh, honey.
Try not to be
too critical of Lucretia.
She-- she's just trying
to find her own way.
Couldn't she find
her way somewhere else?
You know, Hayley,
if you could just
make a small effort
to accept her way
of expressing herself,
you'd find she's
a very sweet girl.
Okay?
Okay, Grandma.
Breakfast is ready
when you are.
I'm making sausages.
Your favorite.
Thanks, Grandma.
[classical music plays]
Hey, Hayley,
what's going on?
[whines]
-[barks]
-[screams]
Ahh!
Quit doing that.
It really scares
the heck out of me.
Out, out.
Aw, come on, kid.
I'm trying to make
friends here.
I promise I won't
lick your face.
Out, dog.
All right, I'll get.
Hey, you called me a dog!
Well, now,
that's a good sign.
Maybe we could--
Ethel: Here, kitty, kitty.
Come and get it.
Oh, boy! Grandma's cooking!
Oh, I'm famished.
-You're just gonna love it.
- Here I come.
-Come on.
-I'm right here.
There you are.
I've been looking
for you everywhere.
-I brought you something.
-[squeaking]
Oh, brother.
Well, aren't you
gonna play with it?
[sighs]
If I must.
-[missile falling]
-We got to end this war.
[gunfire]
Grr.
[helicopter whirs]
-[creature roars]
-What's that?
[gunfire continues]
-[cats roar]
-Not again!
Ow! Guys, liste-- Ow!
-Hey!
-[giggling]
You want a piece of me?
Come on, come on!
Siamese 1:
A piece is about all that
is left of you, hot dog.
But I brought you a toy.
Siamese 1:
Oh, I like toys.
Both:
Shut up! Shut up!
I was kinda hoping
you could help me
with the girl.
Siamese 1:
Ah, so the lady's man
needs help, huh?
You're worthless.
What do you mean?
I just gave you a cat toy.
I'll bring you every toy
the lady buys me.
Come on.
Siamese 1:
Like we really want
your hand-me-downs.
Siamese 2:
Yeah, reject from
a reject.
If you wasn't a cat, I'd--
-Grr.
-Hey, we once licked
the bottom of her bare feet.
-Really?
-She liked that a lot.
Siamese 2:
Yeah, maybe she like it
if you do it.
That's a great idea.
I'll go try it right now.
What a moron.
He'll believe anything.
What an ignoramus!
[giggling]
[Hayley screams]
Hayley: Out, dog.
-[door closes]
-Hayley: Yuck.
[barks]
Come on, come on.
Let's go!
Let's go.
Let's get this baby
in the air.
We have lift-off!
[giggles]
Yeah, baby.
Uh, uh, uh.
Houston, we have a problem.
[screams]
I can't hold it!
She's breaking up!
[screams]
How many frequent
flier feet was that?
That must have been
at least 100 feet.
How'd he get
way over there?
Hmm.
[loud bang]
Okay, Louie,
I say we hit this place
Saturday night.
Saturday's laundry night.
Shut up, Louie.
After this job,
we'll be able to pay somebody
to do our laundry.
[scoffs]
No one's doing my undies.
-[scoffs]
-Louie, no one's
gonna care
about your dirty undies.
Mom cared.
Why am I having
this conversation?
I want to be
talking about the money,
not your underwear.
Well, you started it.
[Louie farts]
[Stu laughs]
[both chuckle]
[screams]
[groaning scream]
Ow!
Now do you
have dirty undies?
Man, you are mean to me.
Hayley: Little dog.
Hey, Hayley, you awake?
What's going on?
Hey, dog, come here.
Hey, kid, what's up?
Come on,
I got something for you.
-Really?
-[metal door opens]
-Uh-oh.
-Remember me?
[screams]
Huh? Oh.
I got to lay off
that spicy cat food
before bed.
Seems nice and quiet.
-Sleeping like a baby.
-[creaking]
I heard that.
Someone's up
in the attic.
Hey, look,
knit needles.
Hmm, don't know
much about that croquet.
Ahh, the kite.
Oh-ho, a scuba tank.
Maybe we can go
scuba diving someday.
Hey, what's this?
"Private: Keep out."
Sounds like
an invitation to me.
One more time.
Little help.
Almost there.
Whoa!
Hey, who turned
out the lights?
[laughs]
Well, I hope nobody saw that.
I got to get out of here.
[stretching]
-What the--
-[boing]
Whoa!
Huh? Whoa.
Yikes!
Aww, man, I got to
get ahold of myself.
Well, everything
seems to be in order.
I better get some shut-eye.
Wait, it's counter-clockwise.
No clockwise.
No counter-clockwise.
[mumbling, sighs]
Hayley:
Hey, dog, come here.
Come on,
I've got something for you.
Ooph, deja vu.
Poor little guy.
Okay, I'm here,
but no tricks.
All right, sis,
what's on your mind?
I've been mean to you
and I want you to know
I'm sorry.
It's not you.
It's that my parents
died recently
and I've really been mean
to everyone lately.
I love my grandma
and she's trying her best,
but she thinks
I'm supposed to be outside
playing with other kids.
I don't do that.
Well, why tell me this?
I'm a dog.
Nobody cares what
a dog thinks.
[sighs]
Nobody cares
what a kid thinks.
Is there an echo in here?
Here, I got you something.
Another cat toy?
It's a piece of chicken,
but don't eat the bone.
Grandma still
thinks you're a cat.
She's too vain
to wear her glasses.
Oh, girl, you rock.
So are we friends?
Shall we shake?
Oh, we don't play that.
Eesh.
[sighs]
Meiser:
Okay, I can handle this.
-Okay, yeah, just calm down.
-Just back me up.
I got your back.
Relax.
It's your job,
here we go.
[Agent clears throat]
No guns.
Meiser: Good afternoon,
Mrs. Jeffries...
[light chuckle]
Where are your friends,
the news cameras?
Did you forget
to call them?
We're not in the habit
of involving parties
who have no bearing
on the case.
On the contrary,
they have great bearing
on the case.
They keep you two
from acting like outlaws.
Outlaws? I can't say
I know what you mean,
Mrs. Jeffries.
Thanks for letting
the whole world
know about my finances.
What are you two
doing here, anyway?
I've got a lot
of work to do.
We want to give you
one last chance.
Do you have a court order?
No, we're
trying to be helpful.
You know, my father
built that business
up from nothing
the year that I was born.
He was a good man
who taught us to work hard
and be honest.
That's how he ran things.
We're not here
to argue whether or not
you're right or wrong.
When your father
ran the business,
he had one store.
You have over 50.
Over 50.
My accountants
have been instructed
to honestly report all taxes
and I have just
sent an accounting
of my personal cash reserve.
Frankly, Mrs. Jeffries,
we don't believe you
or your accountants.
-Oh, really?
-Hmm.
Would you excuse me
for a moment?
Meiser: Tough cookie.
Mechanic: They don't
pay me enough for this.
Yeah, cookie...
They put a man on the moon,
but they can't make
a paw-friendly faucet.
Mrs. Jeffries,
this is your last chance.
If we have to come back,
it'll be with a court order
and the police.
Get off my land!
[echoes]
[screams]
[laughs]
You guys are all wet.
[indistinct shouts]
[dog howls]
[knocking]
Hi, Mrs. Jeffries.
Hi, Lucretia,
come on in.
Keeping the same
hair this week?
I'm gonna be
like this forever.
-[Ethel chuckles]
-I'm kind of like
in love with Drac,
my boyfriend.
He's cool
and not afraid
of anything or anyone.
Really?
How do you know?
-He told me.
-Oh.
So tonight's a big night
at the new club.
Yeah, we're all
a tad nervous.
By the way,
help yourself
to the macaroni and cheese
on the stove.
-Where's Hayley?
-Upstairs...
Both: Reading.
I'm gonna go and change.
Okay.
-[television clicks]
-Oh, what you watching?
Oh, karate.
-[man grunting]
-Man: Use the attacker's
strength against him.
It's a question of balance,
not wax-on, wax-off.
Defensive posturing
and strength
could render
the opponent helpless,
and with a minimal
amount of moves,
could throw him
to the ground.
Chihuahua: Hmm.
Can I come in?
Sure, Grandma.
What's the matter, sweetheart?
Why did their plane
have to crash?
I miss Mom
and Dad so much.
Oh, honey.
So do I.
It's not fair, Grandma.
[sighs]
I wish I knew
a way to explain it...
but life is a series
of good and bad things
that happen to us.
The important thing
is how we react.
We can't let the bad things
destroy us, honey.
Sometimes when things
don't go well,
well, we just have
to accept it and go on.
I know what
you're saying, Grandma,
but it still hurts.
Can I be alone
for a little while?
Of course.
I love you, honey.
Love you too, Grandma.
Hayley, would you prefer
to live with your aunt Helen?
I think she has kids
about your age.
Don't you want me
to live here with you, Grandma?
Of course I do.
I just don't want
you to feel trapped.
I don't.
I'd rather stay here
with you.
Okay.
Wow, I thought
I had it tough.
Come on, kitty.
This kitty stuff's
got to stop.
Uh-oh.
Those goons are back.
[Chihuahua growls]
Oh! Isn't that cute?
The kitty's purring.
Why, if you wasn't a dame...
Now, kitty, you take
good care of Hayley
while I'm gone.
Bye.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Lucretia:
Goodnight, Mrs. Jeffries.
Ethel: Goodnight, Lucretia.
Lucretia: Good luck.
Fasten your seat belts,
looks like it's gonna
be a bumpy night.
[motorcycle revs]
[upbeat music plays]
[woman giggles]
[somber music plays]
[object clatters]
Stu: You want to
wake up the neighborhood?
Fun's about to start.
Here we go.
-[woman's frightened gasping]
-What are you doing?
Woman: Oh God!
Drive! Eddie, drive!
-Hurry!
-I know!
Take me home!
-Hurry up!
-[car tires screech]
[frightened chatter]
Man: Just take it easy,
will you?
-I know what I'm doing.
-Where're you going?
-[creaking]
-Hurry.
Man: Just take it easy.
This doesn't look
like my house.
Just got to get
a burger, okay?
[grunts]
This is a heavy megaphone.
-Uh-oh.
-[door rattles]
Woman: Eddie.
-[barks]
-Hey, cut it out.
[barking]
[barking continues]
-[Eddie screams]
-[barks]
-Man: Hey, kids,
what you eating?
-Kid: Pancakes!
Wake up, babe,
I'm trying to tell
you something.
Wait a minute.
You want me
to go into the kitchen?
One of the Amazing
Wallendas, folks,
right here in front of me.
They're back.
Whatever you do,
don't open that door.
-Boo!
-[barking]
-Drac, what are you doing?
The door was locked.
That was like
so uncool.
Saying "like"
is like so uncool.
They are like
so stupid.
[both grunt]
Huh?
Hmm.
Siamese 2:
Hey, here comes
the cat burglars.
Siamese 1:
Check this out.
[both giggling]
Siamese 2: Oh.
Ow.
-[giggling]
-What?
Quit screwing around.
-I didn't do any--
-Shh!
[hissing giggles]
[wicked giggles]
Hayley, I'm going
out to the gazebo
for awhile.
[both giggle]
[orchestral piano]
[laughing shriek]
[Lucretia giggles]
I'm ready for
that little rat this time.
Yeah, yeah, just get in there
and unlock the door.
Hurry up.
Little rat.
Where are you?
- [deep growling barks]
-[screams]
-[screaming]
[grunting]
There's a really
big dog in there.
I just heard, like,
a really big dog barking.
[sighs]
If you're gonna worry
about every little sound
that you hear,
I'm just gonna leave.
No, no.
I'd rather you stayed.
[gasps]
Louie, Louie...
I'll take care
of your really big dog.
Get out of the way!
[harsh breathing]
Really big dog...
[scoffs]
[metal clanks]
Strike!
[laughs]
Stu?
Stu!
* What did I do
* to deserve
this wreck of mine? *
Are you all right?
Speak to me!
Wake up.
Oh thank god!
[grunts]
Let's go try
around the front.
Hey, wobbly legs,
having trouble walking?
[groaning]
Lend me an aspirin.
Stu, we'll get you
a nice, hot bubble bath.
Where're you going?
I can't concentrate.
I got to go
check on Hayley.
[huffs]
[man on television]:
Where is he now?
There's no body.
There's no blood,
no indications
there's been an attack.
[woman cries]
I don't know what happened.
Eddie was standing
right there
and then all of a sudden
this thing jumped out
from nowhere
and started tearing him
to pieces.
I just ran away.
-I couldn't--
-That's what it is.
[television clicks]
[clock chimes]
-[floorboards creak]
-[owl hoots]
[knocks]
Hayley?
-Hi.
-Uh, hi.
Just seeing if you're,
like, all right.
Like, yeah.
Whatever.
I know I saw a wire
around here, somewhere.
Oh, there it is.
[mimics gun reloading]
[mimics gunfire]
Ohh! Ooh!
Whoa-wa!
-What are you doing?
-[high pitch warrior cry]
Practicing...
Whaa!
Hey.
Give me
back my hat.
[cats giggling]
Quit screwing around.
[barks]
She's got those things
on her ears.
[saxophone plays]
[distant clattering]
[barking]
Ah, she's no help.
I guess it's up to me again.
Do I got to do
everything around here?
-This little piggy
went to the market.
-Ow.
-This little piggy
went home.
-Ah!
-This little piggy
had pork butt.
-[screams]
Oh boy.
[screams]
Ooh, ran out of piggies.
-[crashes]
-[chuckles]
[Lucretia giggles]
Drac: Ow.
-Whoa!
-[clanks]
Wow.
Where am I, Mommy?
I don't want
to go to bed yet.
[huffs]
Get up!
[men grunt]
[barks]
There you are,
you little--
-[barks]
-Stu!
[giggles]
Have a nice trip.
See you next fall.
[screams]
[grunts]
Aww, I just can't resist.
-[screams]
-[ripping]
Where's that weird chick
with the black hair?
[scoffs]
I think the babysitter
needs a babysitter.
Louie: Did you get it?
Did you get it?
-[thudding]
-Both: Ow! Ow.
Ah, the trusty
rolling pin.
I got to get
access to that one.
[grunts]
Three, two,
one, blast off!
Piece of cake.
[grunts]
Stu: Where'd he go?
Where'd he go?
Stu: There he is!
Look what you did to me!
[barking]
Get him!
We'll stuff him.
He'll look good
in the van.
[screaming]
Thanks for flying
butt head airlines.
[grunting]
That dog is dog meat.
[coughs]
I got to find something.
There's gotta be
something I can use
against these knuckleheads.
Hmm.
Nothing. Nothing.
Oh, what's this?
Perfect, this'll work.
Here, little doggie.
Where are you?
You want to
come out and play
with Uncle Stu?
This is gonna be good.
All ready.
Hey, little feller.
Watch where you're
pointing that thing.
Aim.
Whoa.
-If I could just
get my paw in here.
-Whoa, whoa, whoa.
-Whoa!
-Fire!
[screams]
[grunts]
Oh my.
Louie, get that dog!
Louie...
[murmurs]
Uh-oh.
Louie, take him someplace.
Any place
far away from here
before I kill him!
Louie: Okay, Stu.
I'll see you later.
-Louie!
-Have a nice day.
Louie, get back here.
Don't worry,
I'll be right back.
[groans]
[whines]
[upbeat music]
What's that?
Anyway, if I thought
fourth grade was tough,
fifth grade was just
out of the question.
So at 16,
I left school
and got a job
with Mr. Smiley Freeze,
but that didn't
go so well.
Why am I not surprised?
You know,
you're not such
a bad little guy.
Heck, if we weren't
robbing you,
we would've probably
been friends, huh?
Want a chip?
[chuckles]
There you go.
-[crunching]
-Hey, you like that,
don't you?
Ah, finger food, yum.
-[biting crunch]
-[screams]
So long, stabby.
Okay, this blows.
This isn't exactly
what I had in mind.
Gotta get a taxi
out here.
What am I doing?
I got to save Hayley.
[groans]
When I get
down from here,
I'm gonna teach Louie...
[music plays]
[plate clinks]
[pop music plays]
Hey, Stu.
Louie.
How's it hanging?
Oh!
Just get me down
from here, you idiot.
[groans]
Fine.
[strains]
Whoops.
Ohh.
Ohh!
I am going to
wring your neck.
-Stu--
-You stupid...
-Stu.
-brainless--
Money, money.
Oh, right!
Right.
I'll kill you later.
You know,
there's a little
girl up there.
I just want
to get the money
and get out of here.
What are you doing?
I'm looking
for the money.
Nobody is gonna
put a million bucks
in an armoire
by the front door.
They're gonna
put it in a boiler
or a safe, somewhere.
Right.
Ahh.
Rats, rats, rats.
Ah-ha!
What are you doing?
I'm thirsty.
You don't know
whose lips
have been wrapped
around that.
There could be
nasty germs in that can.
The acids in my mouth
can handle any germs.
Oh yeah?
Well, let's see
if the acids in your mouth
can handle this?
[coughs]
[cough]
What are you doing?
Uh, I'm just seeing
if she stashed
the money in here.
You're eating!
You're not looking.
Hey, Louie.
Ooh!
[muffled]
[laughing]
Lucretia: Ow!
[laughing] Ow.
-Hey, Louie!
-What?
Check up there
and see if you can
find a light switch.
I got it.
[grunts]
[clattering]
Here we go.
Where's the money?
[clattering]
[clattering, glass breaking]
Will you--
-Hey!
-What's up?
Ow! Ow!
-Stu!
-Just get down here.
Money, money,
money, money,
money, money, money,
-money.
-[farts]
Stu: It's got to
be over here.
Where?
Do you see it?
Uh-uh.
Lucretia?
Little dog?
Anybody home?
Hmm.
I bet they're making out
in the gazebo.
Yuck.
[cans clatter]
Lucretia?
[rummaging]
You better not
be making out in the basement
with Dracula man.
Grandma says we're not
supposed to go down there.
Almost there.
I got to keep going.
Lucretia?
-[Hayley screams]
-[jazz music plays]
[snapping]
Hey! Look where
you're going.
Sorry.
Sorry, you all right?
She's good.
See any seats?
Those?
I said we're gonna
need your seats.
IRS.
-Let's go.
-Official business, sir.
I know.
Here, take your drink.
Hey, hey!
Pay your taxes.
-Woman: Sit down!
-Come on.
[angry muttering]
-Hey, hey! IRS!
-Hey!
-Hey, hey.
-Sit down! Sit down!
What's your name?
You want to mess with me?
Huh?
[angry muttering]
[jazz music continues]
Can I get you
something to drink?
Uh, I'd like, uh,
a Shirley Temple.
-Okay, and you, sir?
-Bloody Mary.
Wait, a virgin.
We're on the clock.
-She's pretty good.
-Yeah.
-[applause, whistling]
[cheering]
Ethel:
Thank you, thank you.
Thank you so much.
Take five, ladies.
[applause continues]
Let's go.
-Hey, leave her alone!
-Hey!
-[booing]
Hey, hey, hey.
Hey, calm down
or I'll find you.
-[booing]
-Watch your step.
[clattering]
[laughs]
All right.
Hey, hot stuff, ladies!
Whoohoo!
[cheering]
We're groovin' tonight,
you gals!
Yay!
What are you two
doing here?
Just keeping tabs
on a possible tax cheat.
You're not supposed
to be back stage.
I don't care
if you want to
watch the show,
but I prefer if
you stay away from here.
It's for artists only.
We're expecting to get
our search warrant tonight,
Mrs. Jeffries.
When we do,
we'll be at your house
with the police.
Bouncer: Okay.
Hey, what are
you doing, pal? Hey!
-Come on.
-Hands off, man!
-That's government property.
-Come on.
-Get your hands off of me!
-Are you crazy?
Get your hands off of me!
-Ooh.
-Bye-bye, bye-bye.
We're gonna leave her here
and that's the end of it.
She can identify us.
Well, what do you
want to do?
Take her with us?
Stu: Yeah.
Like a hostage.
Well, I'm not sharing
my half of the money with her.
I'm gonna tell you
that right now.
If you don't stop that,
I'm going to throw up.
[phone rings]
-What's that?
-It's called a telephone.
It makes noise
and strange voices
come out of it.
[phone ringing]
Louie, focus!
We've got to
find the money.
-[ringing continues]
-Yeah.
[slurping]
Eww, what are
you doing?
-That was a French kiss.
-[phone ringing]
In my ear? Gross!
[slurping]
Oh.
Get off me.
-[metal clicks]
-I can't.
[muffled]
I'm stuck.
[whimpers]
Oh, it's really stuck!
-Uh-huh.
-[yelps]
We need a mirror.
Come on.
-[phone rings]
-Come on.
-[ringing]
-Oh my god,
it's the phone!
Ow.
-[shrieks]
-Oh god, my braces.
Hurry up!
It's not like
she's gonna kill you.
Ow! Ow, ow.
-[moaning]
-[keys jingle]
[ringing]
Lucretia: Yes!
-Lucretia?
- Yeah.
Oh, yes, it's me, Ethel.
How's Hayley?
Everything's fine.
She's upstairs.
You want me
to get her?
No, no, honey,
don't bother.
No, I--
I just had a feeling
I should call.
I was just gonna watch
a karate movie on cable.
Glad everything's all right.
-I think we're a big hit.
-Cool!
-Ethel.
-Let's go.
Oh, look, look.
I have to go now.
They're calling me.
I'll see you
in a couple of hours.
Bye.
Ow!
[chuckles]
My god.
That's for almost
getting me in trouble.
Hayley?
Lucretia: Hayley?
Who the heck
is that?
My babysitter.
Maybe she knows
where the money is.
You guys are done for.
She knows karate.
Oh yeah?
Hai-ya!
You said this house
was gonna be empty.
First the rat,
and then the girl,
now a babysitter.
Ah, shut up, Louie.
I'm trying to think.
[sniffing]
Hey, this smells familiar.
Smells like-- Uh-oh.
Thor:
Well, look what
we have here,
a meal on legs.
Damien:
We don't like punks
on our turf.
Hey, fellas, it's me.
Remember?
I busted
the dog catcher's eggs.
[nervous laugh]
Remember?
-Damien: Oh, yeah!
-Thor: That's right!
We thought
you went down!
I did, but I got adopted
at the last minute
by this lady who
thinks I'm a cat.
[laughs]
What a crack up!
I can see it though.
Oh, come on, guys.
I need your help.
There's a couple of burglars
trying to steal
my new owner's money
and they might hurt
the little girl.
Thor:
Whoa there, buddy.
We don't get involved
in that kind of business.
-Capisce?
-Yeah, because there's
nothing in it for us.
-But-- Come on.
-You're on your own, man.
Damien:
We stay on our turf
and that's final.
I don't believe this!
Sorry, kid.
Thor:
Yeah, poor little guy.
Probably should
have helped him.
C'est la vie.
She's not
in her room.
I just heard a noise
in the basement.
She's not supposed
to go down there.
I'll deal with it.
Stay here.
Oh, great!
I'm back where I started!
What's the use?
I'm never gonna
get back in time
to rescue Hayley.
I shouldn't have
done that taco commercial.
Who knew it was
gonna be so big?
Hit me.
Do the world a favor.
-[tires screech]
-Come on.
This must be
the white light
everyone talks about.
[country music plays]
* God knows you loved her
* You know you lost her
Hey, little feller.
Hey, old timer.
What are you doing
out here at night all alone?
I'm trying to
save my friends.
What does it
look like I'm doing?
[chuckles]
Come on.
I'll give you a ride
and get you some food.
-Food, oh.
-Yeah.
[country music plays]
[engine starts]
Well, look at you.
What are you
afraid of, partner?
I'm scared of what
might happen to my friends,
what might happen to me.
Eh, why be afraid?
Fear is just something
to keep you from doing
what you were born to do.
-Huh?
-Maybe the odds are all
stacked up against you,
but you never know
when just the right spark hits
and cha-ching,
cha-ching it all
falls into place.
But I'm just a little dog.
And right now
you're thinking
you're a goner.
So why not
give it your all.
If you're destined
to succeed, you will.
If not...
[chuckles]
then what do you
got to lose?
Oh my gosh,
you're right!
What was I thinking?
Hayley and Ethel,
they need me.
Let me out of here.
Hurry, come on.
Come on!
Wait, now,
hold on there.
Now there goes
a good little dog.
Wait a minute.
Did that guy know
what I was thinking?
Feet don't fail me now.
-Woman: My baby!
- Did you know mosquitoes are
attracted to black clothing?
[television clicks]
What's taking...
[drumming]
I've got to
get a new girlfriend.
You know, Lucretia,
if you're gonna keep me
waiting around
here like an idiot,
then I'm leav--
Stu:
Who the hell
are you?
Watch your language.
There's a little kid here.
[high-pitched]
Uh, Lucretia?
Drac, do something.
You guys are
in for it now.
My boyfriend knows karate
and he's not
afraid of anything.
He's not?
Uh...
Stay back!
Don't come any closer!
Stay.
[ragged breathing]
[panting]
[inhaler puffs]
Big karate man.
Scary ninja man.
[both laugh]
Your boyfriend's a dweeb.
[laughing continues]
Look at him.
Stu: That's a good one.
[laughing]
[Louie laughing]
[Stu laughing]
They're going down!
[distant chatter]
-Oh, man.
-Hayley: Put you away
for a long, long time.
There's a brand new
record in the state.
It's really tough.
Stu: You guys
are making me crazy.
Now one of you knows
where the money is.
If we did,
don't you think
we would've
told you by now?
It's not like we, like,
like having you around
or something.
Huh?
[barking]
Get back here.
Unbelievable.
Wow.
Whoa!
[screams]
Whoohoo!
Whoa!
How do you
stop this crazy thing?
It's the dog.
How'd he learn
to do that?
I'll be right
with you ladies.
He's coming back.
-[yelps]
-[screaming]
Ahh!
[wheezing]
[laughing]
[screaming]
3-5 to gold leader,
I'm going in.
Ahh!
[clock chiming]
[giggling]
I sure cleaned
his clock.
Run, get help!
Who do I look like?
Lassie?
Huh? Ow.
Where'd he go?
Hmm?
Come on out
and fight like a man,
you little midget!
I know you're
out here someplace.
Hey, up here,
burrito butt!
-[laughs]
-That was a terrible shot!
You aim like a dog!
Is that the best
you can do?
I've seen better shots
at doctor's offices!
Ha! You missed me!
Why don't you show me something,
you little two-bit canine?
[fabric stretching]
[gasping]
Incoming!
[screams]
Bullseye!
Wake up! Louie!
Louie, wake up!
[groans]
He's in the attic,
come on!
Okay.
Louie: He's trapped.
[groaning]
I'm gonna kill that dog.
[grunts]
Huh? Oh!
Stu, what's this?
It looks like a...
-Uh, uh...
-That's right,
a booby trap.
-No.
-No! No, no.
-No, no, no, no.
Both: No!
Who else is up there?
Just that dog.
[both wheezing]
I'm gonna
kill that dog.
Stu, maybe
we should just go.
Stu: He's just a little dog!
A little dog!
No Chihuahua's gonna
kick my butt.
Stu?
Come on come on.
Here, come on.
Come on, chop chop.
They'll be back in a second.
They're outside.
Lock the windows.
[screams]
You get the girl.
The dog is mine.
Hey!
Want some
smack and cheese?
Mac and cheese?
No.
Smack and cheese!
Uh-oh.
You're a dead dog.
D-E-D, dead.
Check your spelling.
Hayley!
Now what?
I don't know.
Maybe we should
go next door
-and call the police.
-Good idea, let's go.
[screams]
-[Lucretia screams]
-Let me go.
Ooh! Ow!
[screams]
Both: Let me out!
Let me out!
Now that is what
you put in an armoire!
[barks]
Hey, up here!
Come and get me.
Forget him, Stu.
Let's just find the money
and get out of here.
Thor:
The scent leads in here!
Ai, Chihuahua!
You came after all.
Thor:
Our pleasure.
[barking]
[screaming]
-Damien: Eh, bandidos!
-Thor: Let's get 'em.
[growling]
[screaming]
Stu: Get out of the way!
[panting]
[barks]
[growls]
Nananana.
[laughs]
[barks]
There he is.
[barking]
-Get him.
-[barking]
[barking]
Careful.
Here, doggie.
Louie:
Time to say
your prayers.
Both: Huh?
What?
-[barking]
-Oh.
What the--
Huh?
Hey, let go of me.
Whoa!
[both whimper]
Stu, I just want
to go home.
Me too, little brother.
Me too.
[blows]
-Mommy.
-Damien: Way to go,
little guy.
-[Thor laughs]
-We'll keep an eye on 'em.
-Nice doggie.
-[growls]
-Good doggie.
-[growling]
[barking]
Sit! Sit!
[barks]
Who's the man?
[police sirens wail]
What the--
[barks]
Who are you?
We're just
checking the gas meter.
It's working good.
Lucretia.:
Help! Let us out!
Somebody!
Hayley: Grandma!
What have you done?
Lucretia, Hayley!
Oh my!
Are you all right?
I'm fine, Grandma.
What happened here?
Who are these people?
-Burglars-- they tied us up.
-Mrs. Jeffries, I'm sorry,
but you leave us no choice.
We-- What is going on here?
We have a warrant
to search and seize
sizable cash holdings.
You want the money?
Take it. It's in there.
Policeman:
We've been looking
for you two.
You couldn't find a safer
place than the armoire?
They didn't find it.
The armoire.
[both grunt]
Policeman: All right,
let's cut 'em down.
All right, guys, easy.
You have the right
to remain silent--
How'd you catch
these guys?
He's the one
who saved us.
[sighs]
Well, that's some cat,
I tell you.
Oh, brother.
Louie:
Stuart did it.
Hey, babe, you okay?
[grunts]
Oh, man.
I think I'm going
back to cheerleading.
-Stu: Oh, officer,
are those cuffs--
-Hey,
are you two
looking for a home?
Who? Us?
Come on, boys.
Thor:
Heh, she can chain
me up any day.
Louie:
Please don't
tell our mom.
Stu: Shut up, Louie.
Thanks for walking
me home, Stephen.
No biggie.
I'll see you tomorrow, okay?
Sure.
Home sweet home.
-Hi, Grandma.
-Hi.
Oh, I'm so glad to see
that you're making new friends.
He's nice.
Hm-hmm.
You know what?
I'm taking our cash
and I'm gonna
put it in the bank
as an investment
for your future.
Is it because they made you
or because you wanted to?
Ugh, those two idiots
couldn't make me
wish for sunny day.
They're back there
processing their tax returns.
I'm doing it
because you're very,
very important to me,
sweetheart.
Thanks, Grandma.
I love a happy ending.
Have you come up
with a name
for your kitty yet?
Well, I figure
when the odds are
totally against him,
he bounces back quick,
like a ping pong.
So I'll call him Ping.
Ping, I like that.
Well, it beats monkey face.
Oh, my god!
He's a dog!
That's right.
Just an ordinary dog.
[woofs]
[music plays]