No...
No. No. Please.
Shh, shh, shh, shh...
Hey, your friend Celine
is the one
that recommended the restaurant.
Yeah, she...
I don't know
what she was thinking about.
what she liked about it.
I honestly don't know
what she ordered
that could've been good.
There's nothing...
There's nothing good
on the menu.
You can't hate every restaurant
that doesn't have fries.
It wasn't just the fries.
They didn't even give us bread.
You know how important
bread is to me.
Do you like bread?
I wasn't sure whether
you liked bread
after you talked about bread
the whole way home.
What's with all the rave
about small plates?
Why can't I have
just one really big plate?
Well, we tried.
Turning 30's a big deal.
I can't just take you
to a buffet.
Unlimited food and no waiting.
What a drag.
Next year, I promise.
I've told you how much
I love you, right?
Mm. You might have
mentioned it.
But I still like hearing it.
I'm still hungry, by the way.
They do not give you
enough food.
One star, and that's generous.
I just wanna change into PJs
and make some nachos
and marathon
a bunch of trashy TV
until we fall asleep
on the couch.
Surprise!
Now, what if we did
the exact opposite
of everything you just said?
This is so much better!
- How're ya?
- Happy birthday!
I can't believe
you didn't tell me!
- Thanks for...
- Oh...
- Happy birthday, sweetheart.
- Hi.
So, 30. You think
Catherine's gonna spring
the baby question
on you tonight?
No babies until marriage,
darling, thankfully.
I don't know. She might
be getting desperate.
You're pretty much dried up now.
I can't believe
Mark's dad married her.
She really does put
the smother in stepmother.
Okay, she's coming.
- Hello, darling. Happy birthday.
- Hi.
- Thank you.
- Oh. Oh...
You remember my friend Celine.
How can I forget?
So, 30. Quite the milestone.
You know, when I was your age,
I was married with a baby.
The '50s were a different time.
It was so nice
of you and Don to come
all this way for my birthday.
Well, we actually brought you
a little surprise.
Oh, you guys didn't have
to get me anything.
Well, it's actually
for you andMark.
Mark? Uh, I'm not sure
where he's gotten to.
- Ahh!
- You're here. Oh, my gosh!
Of course.
I would absolutely not miss it.
You look amazing.
Nicole! Look who it is.
Forgive my idiot brother.
I'm... I'm Audrey.
Audrey! It's so good
to finally meet you.
No, no. No, handshakes.
You're the closest thing
I've ever had to a sister.
Oh, good to meet you.
Okay, still lost over here.
This is Mark's
stepsister, Audrey.
Oh, Catherine's daughter!
Should've guessed.
What's that supposed to mean?
Um...
It doesn't mean anything.
I'm totally kidding.
Oh!
Why are we standing here?
Let's go meet your friends.
- Come.
- After you.
She is adorable.
I cannot believe you.
You are still using that line.
It worked, didn't it?
Wait, you use that line
on other girls?
Yeah, but you were the only one
who ever fell for it.
Oh!
You guys are sweet, I'm...
I'm glad you're a normal one
because he's burnt
through a lot of, uh
questionable girlfriends.
A lot?
There weren't that many.
Well, there was Maggie,
Jamie, Nancy...
- Lisa, Molly...
- Yes. Yeah.
- The girl with the piercings.
- Ah, Kristen.
Piercing? Where?
Okay, let's try not to chase off
the normal one, alright?
I don't care who came before
as long as no one comes after.
- No one will.
- Aww.
And speaking of which...
Let's see it?
See it?
Uh, the ring?
Are you kidding? I...
I'm sorry! I thought
that mom said...
- What are you talking about?
- I'm...
Mark?
I had kind of a surprise
that involved Nicole's cake,
but...
Nicole...
I love you more than anything
in the world.
And even though we've only
known each other a few years
I feel like I've
known you my whole life
and I want nothing more
than to spend
the rest of my life with you.
Will you marry me?
- Mark...
- Is that a yes?
Yes!
Yeah!
Oh, I'm shaking.
Okay, so,
what was meant to happen?
I was gonna light the candles,
then she would close her eyes
and make a wish,
and when she opened them,
the ring would be there.
It's kinda presumptuous
that her, uh,
wish was to marry you,
right, just, like,
a little presumptuous? 'Cause,
like, if I was doing that...
- What's all this?
- Oh, hi!
Morning, lovely.
I thought I would make breakfast
to thank you
for letting me crash.
Wow, I could get used to this.
Do you come as part
of the marriage package?
I don't think Mark would
want me as a third wheel.
Thanks.
How'd you get Mark up so early,
and to do the dishes?
I have my ways.
She's making the Mark special.
"The Mark special."
Ooh, it's bliss in a burrito
and a pan of cheese and bacon.
Yeah, it's his favorite.
Um, I used to make it
every Sunday morning
while our parents slept in.
Wow. Talk about spoiled.
You know, if you want to take up
that torch once we're married...
I won't object.
Maybe you're better off
marrying Audrey.
So, I was thinking
we should start planning.
We've been engaged for 12 hours.
I know, and I kind of already
picked the venue.
We make a great team.
I'm sorry! I promise
you'll like it, though.
Timberwood?
- Mm-hmm.
- Sure.
Let's go check it out.
Audrey, you should come with us.
It's beautiful.
I wouldn't want to crash.
No. I would love
a second opinion.
- Mark is pretty much a yes man.
- Hey!
Not all the time.
Well, in that case...
I would love to.
Ahh.
There you go.
Thank you.
Mm.
I love you so much.
- I do what I can.
- I wasn't talking to you.
- Okay, then I'm gonna eat it.
- Why? Okay! Okay. Easy.
Why, if you don't care about me,
I'm...
- Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
- I'm so close.
You made this for me!
You can make yourself one.
I'm sorry!
This place is... Wow.
I know. Perfect.
I can see why you love it
so much here.
It's not just the view.
My dad took me up here
a lot when I was little.
Your mom not into nature?
She... wasn't into being a mom.
She left soon after I was born.
Dad died when I was
still in high school.
So, I don't really
have any family.
Except Mark.
And now you.
So, when are we getting married?
I can't believe they're
closing this place down.
I've dreamed of getting
married here since I was 12.
Isn't there anything we can do?
Unless you want to get
married in three weeks.
I knew dad wasn't going to be
able to walk me down the aisle
but... at least here
it's like...
he's still with me.
Like he wouldn't
miss my wedding.
Then do it!
Get married in three weeks.
You're crazy.
Nicole's a teacher. She can
take the summer off, right?
I don't think
you understand everything
that goes
into planning a wedding.
No, Mark.
What if we tried?
Kept it small,
called in a lot of favors.
But in three weeks?
Yeah.
What about all the little things
we want to kind of plan for?
What about them?
It will be here,
and it will be with you.
- That's all I care about.
- Nicole, I...
You know how much
this place means to her?
I mean, unless
you're having doubts?
No! No.
Then what's the problem?
I guess...
There isn't one.
- Really?
- Let's do it.
Okay, if we're going to do this
we have to make
some serious cuts.
Cap it at 50?
Sounds good.
Audrey, you don't
have to do that.
Oh, nonsense.
I can earn my keep.
I only need
to invite four people.
Mm, that's sweet... and sad.
Okay. Uncle Oliver and his wife.
Would you say that you're
wedding invite-close?
I guess.
You guess?
What makes someone
wedding invite-close?
- Babe...
- I don't know.
Whatever you think.
Come on. This is your family.
I need some real feedback here.
Definitely invite them.
- Really?
- Oh, yeah, invite them.
But don't work too hard in
trying to find a seat for them.
They haven't gone
to a wedding in ten years,
but they always send a check.
Done.
Thank you. I appreciate that.
May I?
Be my guest.
Um, just had a baby.
Not worth the drama.
Hasn't spoken to Mark
since high school.
- Cousin Steve?
- Cousin Steve.
How do you feel
about dogs at your wedding?
I'd say I'm against it.
So, bye-bye, Margaret.
Audrey, what are you doing
for the summer?
Ugh, I'm staying
at mom and Don's,
but only until I die of boredom.
Uh, how'd you feel
about... staying with us?
- You want me to stay?
- Only if you want to.
It's just I've got
three weeks to plan
this whole wedding, and I
could really use your help.
I don't... I don't know.
- Mark?
- Sure.
It'll be just like back home,
but this time with satellite TV.
And we could get to know
each other better
before we officially
become sisters.
Okay. I would love to.
Great! You can stay
in the guest bedroom,
and we'll feed you.
Hm!
Look at us. Not even married,
and we already have
a freeloading daughter.
Ignore him. Back to this.
I like how ruthless you are.
I can't believe you kept this
hidden from me this whole time.
I wasn't hiding it.
How did you find it anyway?
Oh, please,
you've been hiding things
in your sock drawer
since ninth grade.
I found some very interesting
things over the years.
Hmm. Do tell.
Do not!
Ah, jackpot.
Okay, this is my favorite thing.
Look at those chubby
chipmunk cheeks.
This is nice. We should
make fun of me more often.
And who is the trollop
that drew the heart?
As your fiancee, I am now
privileged this information.
Uh, let's see.
Senior year, that would be...
Becca Gould. She was one
of the... questionable ones.
I'm guessing
there was a falling out?
Yeah, things didn't end well.
This was very mature,
by the way.
That was actually my handiwork.
She went to second base
with this guy,
and I confronted her on it,
and, uh,
she punched me in the face.
- Seriously?
- Yeah.
Audrey came home
with a black eye
and wouldn't tell us why.
I had to wait till our parents
went to bed,
and then I made her tell me.
- Next day...
- Bye-bye, Becca.
Guess I'll be on my best
behavior while you're in town.
You should be.
I'll be watching.
Um, okay, I know we've
been going at it all day,
but we should probably
talk some more wedding.
That sounds like a job
for you two.
Oh, please,
you have more experience
planning weddings than we do.
What?
- Audrey...
- Well, Rachel!
Uh, Mark's last fiancee.
Last fiancee?
I, I thought you would've...
Nicole, I...
I'm so sorry.
I thought you told her.
Oops.
- Baby...
- Rachel?
- Your last fiancee?
- I'm sorry.
When were you going
to tell me about this?
Were you just going to casually
mention it at the altar?
I know I shouldn't have
kept this from you.
I've just been waiting
for the right time
to talk about it.
I feel like such an idiot.
I'm planning our wedding, and I
didn't even know
that you were engaged before?
Okay.
Before I met you,
Rachel was the first real
relationship I had.
We were happy.
At least, I thought we were.
The day of our wedding...
They found her
at the bottom of a bridge.
She jumped.
In her dress.
All she left was a note
that said, "I'm sorry."
No warning...
no explanation.
And until I met you...
I never thought I'd be able
to care for somebody
like that again.
It was just...
too painful.
- Mark...
- I know...
I should've told you sooner,
and I promise I was going to.
But part of me just...
closed off.
Baby, I'm sorry, I should've...
But...
I want you to know
that you can talk to me
about anything.
If we're going to do this,
we can't have any secrets.
Is there anything else
that you need to tell me?
No.
Are you sure?
Yeah. I'm sure.
Hey.
Hey!
I am sorry about before.
Wine tends to open me up.
No. Actually, I'm glad
I found out about it now.
It's just... so sad.
It was really hard for us,
but I think it really,
really devastated Mark.
I mean, I would practically
have to drag him
out of bed every morning.
I was... the only person
he would talk to.
He told me that he wouldn't have
gotten through it without you.
That you were there
for the whole thing.
We had a long talk.
Actually, it's funny,
I think it brought us
closer together.
Great.
I'd hate to think
that I got in between you two.
No! No, of course not.
So, what's on the agenda?
I actually have to get going.
I'm meeting Celine for some
retail therapy, dress shopping.
Great. I will get my purse.
Oh, okay.
Hi!
Oh!
I can't believe
this is happening!
Three weeks?
You're a crazy person.
I know.
I, um, see you brought
another crazy person.
I didn't really have a choice.
She kind of just
invited herself.
Well, sure.
She ruined your engagement.
Why not ruin this, too?
Celine.
Future mother-in-law.
I'd better take that.
You didn't tell her
about today, did you?
Of course not.
Try to play nice, okay?
Catherine? Hi!
Good to see you!
I kinda thought it was going
to be me and Nicole today.
Yeah, I hope you don't
mind me tagging along.
I wanted to make sure she chose
something tasteful.
Excuse me?
Look who I found
in the parking lot.
Surprise!
I didn't want you
to choose a dress
without the mother of the bride.
I'm so sorry I'm late.
It would've been great to have
had some advance notice, but...
No, you're, uh,
you're right on time.
Alright.
Shall we?
Now the first few you tried on
were a little more extravagant,
but I think you'll find this one
elegant in its simplicity.
So? What do you think?
- It's perfect.
- It really is.
It's definitely unique.
You don't usually see
a wedding dress that basic.
Personally,
I like the first one.
She looked like a tent
covered in glitter.
Well, I think Mark
would really like it.
Mark does love camping.
So?
I think this is it.
- I think this is the one.
- Wonderful.
Now, we are not
blessed with a lot of time,
so I have to get
to the alterations right away.
I am so happy for you two.
Now, I just know Mark is going
to fall in love with you
all over again when he
sees you in that dress.
Thanks, Catherine.
I'm so glad that you could come.
I left my phone
in the dressing room.
I will... be right back.
- Find what you were looking for?
- Yes, I found my phone.
Great.
Okay.
Okay, we'll put
a priority on this,
so expect a call in about
a week for the fitting.
Thank you so much. You have no
idea how much this means to me.
- Oh, it's our pleasure.
- Ready?
Yeah.
Wait a moment.
Your purse.
Oh! Yes. Thank you so much.
- You're welcome.
- Have a good day.
You, too.
I'm so glad that you came here.
Okay, but Don is expecting us.
Would you mind terribly
if I stole
Audrey away for a family lunch?
- No, of course not.
- Yeah, family comes first.
Can we do the lunch some other
time? We have a photo-shoot.
Honey, we're leaving tomorrow.
You're not gonna come with us,
we need to figure something out.
- Fine.
- I'll save you some cake.
Yeah, I'll see you another time.
So, I think I saw
a flower shop over on 2nd.
It should be on the way.
Are you sure you want flowers?
I know how you like
to keep things basic.
Okay, let's retract the claws.
I'm just saying Audrey's
kind of a giant bitch.
What are you talking about?
She's like the nicest
person I know.
I'm not saying
she's the Antichrist,
but she's creepy.
No, she's not.
You were fine with her
just inviting Catherine
without asking?
She likes the element
of surprise.
Most predators do.
Come on!
♪ Don't be gentle tonight
♪ Love me
with all your might ♪
♪ Carve your name on
♪ My soul
♪ Leave your mark
♪ In the fall
♪ Promise me I'll be
rendered breathless ♪
♪ Do it now, hurt me good,
I can take it ♪
♪ Hold me down until
I'm drenched in you ♪
♪ I want more
♪ No clever words
can describe ♪
♪ What I feel
♪ Just give me more
♪ Wanna feel you tomorrow
♪ Don't want no..
♪ Gimme more
♪ Carnivore
♪ Let me drink you again
♪ Taste the truth
♪ In your skin
♪ Will enslave to your skin
♪ My eyes water
♪ In love
♪ Promise me I'll be
rendered breathless ♪
♪ Do it now, hurt me good,
I can take it ♪
♪ Hold me down
♪ Until I'm drenched in you
♪ I want more
♪ No clever words
can describe ♪
♪ What I feel
♪ Just eat you up
♪ I could just eat you up ♪
Hey, Audrey, we're home!
Found a winner for the cake,
we saved you a piece.
Hmm, guess she's not home.
Shame. Well, extra cake for us.
You're cut off.
Pictures. I'm going
to get the laptop.
Audrey's cake
better be untouched!
Oh, no! Looks like
the box is empty.
Celine, I'm serious!
Oh, hey! You came just
in time to see pictures.
Hey, thank you for saving me
a piece. It's so good.
Of course. Nice dress.
Oh, it's yours.
Um, I hope you don't mind.
I didn't do the laundry.
No. Um, you're family.
My closet's your closet.
Come help me pick
a photo for the invite.
Of course!
Celine?
That is so beautiful.
That's it.
It's the one.
Oh, I don't know.
Wouldn't you rather...
show everybody this?
Celine!
Don't even joke!
Oh, come on.
We didn't see anything.
Thirty more seconds, and you
would've seen everything.
You made a sex tape?
Celine's brilliant idea.
Oh, come on. Tell me
that Mark didn't love it.
And you will, too,
when you're 80
and gross and wrinkled.
Anyway, back to this.
What do you think, Audrey?
- Exactly what I would want.
- Decision made!
This calls for a celebration
drink. Shall we?
Not yet. We still have
to address all those envelopes.
Well, actually I did them
when you were
at the photo shoot
this afternoon.
Here you go.
Wow, Audrey!
Look. You can't even tell
that I didn't even write these.
So I copied your handwriting,
so it looks more authentic.
By the 20th, I couldn't
even tell the difference.
Where did you get
her handwriting?
From the invitation list.
Uh, I hope you don't mind.
No!
Nicole and I were
going to do these.
Now you don't have to.
Audrey, I don't know
what to say. Thank you!
Of course!
Now I'm definitely
ready for that drink.
So, I know things have
moved kind of quickly
since you got here,
but I just wanted to say
that we're so happy to have you.
I'm happy, too.
I love it here.
We wouldn't have been able
to pull this off without you,
and Mark and I were talking,
and...
We'd be honored
if you would be my bridesmaid.
A-are you sure?
Of course, I want you
up on that altar with me
on the happiest day of my life.
I would love to.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
I think the puffball is winning.
But I was about
to turn the tables.
Fluffy here is lucky
you came along.
Thanks so much for doing this.
I know bridal showers
aren't really your thing.
Well, we can't all be cloned
from Martha Stewart's evil twin.
So, we have something for you.
Um...
Here.
We were going to give it to you
at the wedding, but...
now just felt right.
It's beautiful.
Thank you.
Thank you for being
my maid of honor.
You're an amazing friend,
and... an okay decorator.
It looks like Pinterest
puked all over your backyard.
And don't forget all
the cringe-worthy games
and activities we've
yet to experience.
- There will be cringing.
- So much cringing.
Could I get everyone's
attention, please?
Ladies, please help me welcome
a very special guest,
as we play the newlywed game!
Alright!
You owe me.
Okay, this game
consists of ten questions.
Mark will have to prove
he knows his betrothed's
deepest, darkest secrets,
and for every question wrong
he will remove
an article of clothing.
Yeah. That's not gonna happen.
Well, it was worth a shot.
Okay, Mark. Are you ready?
- Let's do this!
- Okay, question one.
What is Nicole's
favorite flavor of ice cream?
While, she might tell casual
acquaintances it's cookie dough,
the awful truth is
that her favorite
is rum raisin.
- Oh...
- Correct!
It's a legitimate flavor.
It's gross, honey. You need
to learn to accept that.
Question two.
What is Nicole's biggest fear?
Uh...
I'm gonna go with her
irrational fear of birds.
- Correct!
- It is not irrational.
- They will peck you!
- Silence!
Yeah!
Okay. Question three.
What is Nicole's
most embarrassing photo?
This one's easy.
Seventh grade,
bowl cut in overalls.
She thought she destroyed
every copy, but...
You didn't!
Show me bowl cut in overalls!
Um, that's not...
I, uh, I didn't...
Nicole...
I can't believe
she would do that.
Nicole...
I work with those people.
I-I-I teach their kids.
This is so humiliating.
What were you thinking?
I'm sorry. I don't
know what happened.
No, don't do that.
You don't get to pull a stunt
like that and then play dumb.
I promise, I didn't.
I would never...
Yes, you would! You always do.
You always have to be
the center of attention,
and you push it too far!
You humiliated me!
I swear I don't know
what happened.
Just go.
You...
Audrey!
Is it me you hate
or just Nicole?
I know you're upset that your
little joke backfired.
You can drop the act.
I see who you are.
And I'm going to make sure
everyone else sees it, too.
Celine, are you feeling okay?
Because if stress of being
maid of honor is getting to you,
I can take over some
of your responsibilities.
You stay away from
my responsibilities,
and you stay the hell
away from Nicole.
- Hi.
- Hey.
She must be so heartbroken.
Can you do me a favor?
Of course.
Can you talk to her?
I'm sort of at a loss here.
Absolutely.
I know how to handle this.
It will be okay.
Hi.
Look, it's okay to be upset.
You have a wedding
and a stepsister in town,
and a maid of honor who kind
of stabbed you in the back.
It's hard not to think
everything going wrong
is some kind of sign,
like... maybe we're
rushing into things.
Do you believe in signs?
I don't know.
Maybe.
I mean, sometimes
it's hard to ignore.
- I should talk to her.
- No.
You know what? You shouldn't be
guilted into anything.
She messed up, right?
I mean, it should be you to call
her back when you're ready.
You don't wanna say something
that you regret, right?
Yeah. You're right.
Thanks, Audrey.
I'm really glad you're here.
I'm gonna get a refill.
Want a cup?
Uh, no. Caffeine makes me
a little crazy.
Hey, it's Celine.
I know you're pissed at me,
but we need to talk.
It's about Audrey.
I looked up a few
of Mark's ex-girlfriends.
Nicole, she's...
I think she's dangerous.
I'm working late tonight,
but please call me back.
Hey.
- Everything okay?
- Yeah.
Yeah, I was just
checking the time.
Big plans tonight?
I think something just came up.
Nicole, I know
you're avoiding me, but, uh...
I have to talk to you.
I'm coming over.
It's gonna be okay.
She's still hanging on.
We can't give up on her, right?
Okay.
This is my fault.
No. No.
No, it's not.
She just...
She must have fallen. Hey.
You can't blame yourself.
I should've just
answered her phone call.
Nicole, look at me. Look at me.
This is not your fault.
Bad things happen.
But this isn't something
you're going through alone.
For the rest of our lives,
whatever horrible things
life throws at us,
we'll face them together.
♪ I hope we can be much
more than friends ♪
♪ So bon appetit je t'aime
♪ Bon appetit ♪
Audrey.
Hey! I didn't hear you come in.
- What is all this?
- Oh, it's nothing.
I just thought
that after your visit
you might want
to come home to a hot meal.
I've also cleaned up a bit,
if you don't mind,
and there's a hot bath ready,
in case you want to relax
before dinner, so take a seat.
Take a seat.
You shouldn't have done this.
Oh, it's the least I can do!
That's not what she meant.
Nicole has a wedding to plan.
The last thing she needs
to worry about is the laundry.
You've been cooped up
so much lately,
it must be nice to get out
for the night, huh?
There you go.
Did I do something wrong?
No, it's fine.
It's just Celine is...
How is Celine?
Comatose.
The doctors say
she's hanging in there,
but she hasn't woken up yet.
So awful.
Do they know what happened?
Either she somehow
tripped and fell, or...
- Or?
- Or someone pushed her.
Oh, no... the chicken.
Ah-ah ah-ah ahh!
Disaster averted...
I hope.
Dinner is almost ready.
Poor thing.
Well, looks like
it's just the two of us.
I'm gonna make sure
she's alright.
Oh, uh...
She probably
needs some space, Mark.
I mean,
I went to all this trouble.
just... stay and eat with me.
I'm sorry. Just...
Sorry.
Like, this is right there
and I think
that that's probably why you...
- Hey.
It's perfectly normal!
Morning.
How was the run?
It was good. You're right,
I feel better.
I guess that's why they call it
exorcising your demons.
You're such a dork.
Like, the biggest dork.
Audrey, I thought you
were going shopping.
Yeah, I'm gonna wait for you,
so we can go together.
I'm going to have a shower.
Actually, Audrey
and I were talking.
The wedding's less
than a week away.
And now you probably need
more help than ever...
with Celine...
So if you want,
I would like you...
to consider me...
your maid of honor.
- What?
- Perfect, right?
She can help get things
back on track.
I'm already following up
on Celine's responsibilities.
The venue coordinator is
up to speed on everything.
I just need a few details
from you regarding
the bachelorette party,
which I think...
There isn't gonna be
a bachelorette party.
My best friend's
in the hospital.
Nicole, listen.
I don't wanna talk about
replacing my maid of honor.
The position is still filled.
I'm not saying Celine didn't
make a good maid of honor.
- She did a fine job.
- Do not...
refer to her in the past tense.
- She's still alive.
- She didn't mean anything by it.
No, she never does.
Can we not do this right now
in front of Audrey?
Then when, Mark?
She's always here.
I'm so sorry.
What was that all about?
Which part?
The part where you were talking
like Celine's already dead,
or the part where we haven't
had 30 seconds to ourselves
in two weeks because
your sister's always here?
Audrey's crying out there.
Mark, I'm going to be your wife.
Could you try defending me,
for once?
Um...
Sorry.
I feel like I'm losing my mind.
My best friend's
in critical condition.
The universe is conspiring
against our wedding.
We're fighting
over stupid details.
We get married in four days.
I don't know how to deal
with all this.
Together.
Yeah.
Uh, I'm sorry. I'm... sorry.
I just... I feel like
I'm constantly waiting
for the next thing to go wrong.
I guess sooner or later,
we all turn into bridezillas.
Well, if you had
to stomp on anyone,
aim for the coordinator.
She was kind of mean
to me on the phone.
You probably deserved it.
It's possible.
Um, I should go talk to Audrey.
It can wait.
Stay here for a while.
So, this is the one
that I was talking about,
where, like, the hair goes up
but it's also down.
- It looks...
- No, I like that.
- I love that dress, too.
- Speaking of dresses...
- We should go.
- Yes.
- Yeah.
- I will be ready in one second.
Okay.
Looks like you
patched things up.
Yes. We spent the whole day
at the mall yesterday.
She's been
really sweet about it.
I still can't believe
I snapped at her like that.
Thank you. It means a lot to me
that you two get along.
Just promise me we won't bring
her along for the honeymoon.
- Deal.
- Okay.
It's David.
Probably lost his invite.
Hey, David. Lose your invite?
I'll...
Wait, what?
- He's in town.
- Already?
No, man... We aren't havin'
a bachelor party. We...
They did?
No, I guess...
Yeah, that's great.
I'll see you tonight.
Later.
Bachelor party?
I thought we were canceling.
Didn't you tell them?
I... think this is my fault.
Uh, I didn't know that you
didn't want a bachelor party,
so I called everyone, and...
I'm so sorry.
I wanted to surprise you.
It, it's just because Celine's
still in the hospital, so...
They all flew in, Nicole.
I can't just not show.
- I'm so...
- Sorry, I know.
Okay, um, just...
Try not to be too late, okay?
And maybe don't get super drunk
'cause we have a lot of stuff
to do tomorrow
for the wedding, and...
We'll make it an early night.
- And Mark...
- I know.
No strippers.
Nothing crazy, I promise.
Trust me.
Audrey, can you come in
for a sec? This isn't...
- Of course.
- The zipper must be stuck or...
- Yeah.
- Could you...
Yeah. Yeah. Hold still.
This is so weird. Are you sure
this didn't happen before?
Yes, yes. It wasn't this tight.
- Nothing was this tight.
- Okay, we will fix this.
Uh, dress lady?
You know, a lot of brides
gain weight before the wedding,
so it's totally normal.
- I didn't gain weight.
- Okay. Okay.
Coming in!
How's it going in here?
Oh. That's all wrong.
Wh-what's wrong?
It's... It was taken in
far too much.
Unless you happened to gain
a little weight, or...
- No.
- I don't know what went wrong.
- Who took these measurements?
- You did.
You took the measurements.
What did you do?
- Audrey...
- No!
It's your-It's your
perfect dress,
and you completely
screwed it up!
Well, we'll definitely
take the measurements again
and see what we can do.
How much time do we have?
Three days.
Oh, no. I'm sorry.
That is impossible.
What do you mean, impossible?
W-what does that mean?
Maybe we can try on some
of the other ones you liked,
to see if they're a closer fit.
This is my dress. This...
Sweetie, I am so sorry.
Let me go up front
and see what we got in today.
Hey.
We will find you a bigger dress.
It's not just the dress.
This is supposed to be the most
important day of our lives,
and nothing has gone right.
Maybe we shouldn't be
getting married right now.
Maybe we just rushed into it.
Is there anything...
I can do?
No. No. Thank you.
Just wanna think.
Okay.
Hey.
Hey. Uh, what are
you doing here?
I thought you had
your bachelor party.
Charlie's on his way
to pick me up.
Is Nicole here?
I wanted to talk to her
before I left.
Yeah. She wanted
some time alone.
She has a lot on her mind.
Everything alright?
Mm.
Come on. Talk to me.
It's just, um...
Something Nicole said.
I hope you don't plan
on taking advantage of me.
Welcome back.
And... maybe it's just stress.
It's just, she doesn't
seem like herself lately.
Things have been a bit tense.
Mm-hmm.
What did she say?
I don't know, Mark, it's...
not my, you know...
Audrey, what?
She said that,
with everything going wrong,
that maybe you guys
got in over your head,
and maybe you should slow down.
Slow down?
She said she wanted
to postpone the wedding.
She said that?
Mm-hmm.
I'm so happy you're alright.
How are you feeling?
I've been better.
The pain meds
aren't too bad, though.
Nicole, I'm sorry.
I don't think I'll be walking
down an aisle any time soon.
You have nothing
to be sorry about.
Besides, I don't think
there's going to be a wedding.
What?
I think
we just rushed into things.
You know, I...
I thought I could handle it,
but...
everything is falling apart.
Things have been so tense
between Mark and me.
Maybe it's not
meant to be right now.
Nicole, you can't honestly think
that all of this is your fault,
that everything that's happened
is some sort of coincidence.
What do you mean?
I found some things out
about Audrey.
She's dangerous.
She wants to stop the wedding?
And look, that's why I
didn't want to say anything,
because she's overwhelmed,
and so are you.
I mean, planning a wedding
in three weeks
can send any relationship
off the rails, Mark.
I know we've been
a little bit out of sync,
but I didn't think
it was anything this serious.
You should talk to her.
Maybe you should
call off the wedding.
I mean, just for now.
With everything that happened
with Rachel, you...
You know you don't want
to rush into things.
Mark. Mark. Mark.
Whatever happens...
I am here.
Marky Mark! It's party time!
Yeah. Just, uh,
give me a second.
What's up with him?
- He and Nicole are fighting.
- Seriously?
Your brother has
the worst luck with women.
So, where is the party tonight?
My place.
We're just hanging out.
Can I crash?
Uh...
I was totally kidding.
Come with me.
Uh, Mark's probably gonna
try and be a downer
and come home early,
so do me a favor.
Buy a few bottles
of the good stuff, on me,
and make sure...
he has... a good time.
I'll make sure.
He's a lucky guy
to have you in his life.
Oh. Sweet.
You ready? Let's do this.
Come on. I can't
stay out too late.
Can you try to have a good time?
- That I can promise.
- Okay.
He loves me.
He loves me not.
Hello?
Mark?
Audrey?
You remember that girlfriend
that you talked about,
Becca Gould?
I talked to her.
You talked to her?
- Celine...
- Audrey is lying.
Becca never cheated on Mark.
And she never hit Audrey.
She thinks
that Audrey hurt herself.
Why would she do that?
That's crazy.
I know.
It's not the first time
it happened.
She pointed me
to a lot of girlfriends
that Mark has dated,
and they all
said the same thing.
How wonderful Mark is...
and how possessive
his stepsister is.
Celine, you had
a really big fall...
and you're on a lot of drugs.
Nicole...
I didn't fall.
I was pushed.
♪ Nobody's looking for favor
this one's just for me... ♪
- Hey, baby!
- Whoa!
What...
Charlie called this?
Dude, who did it?
No, no, no...
Let's get this party
started, baby!
♪ Wrap my legs around you
♪ And you feel me
holding you tight ♪
♪ Lost inside my heavy breath
♪ I dare you to speak of her
Oh, yeah.
♪ Prisoners in my heart
♪ Just one glance
in the devil's eyes ♪
♪ I dare you to speak of her ♪
Oh, wow.
Whoo!
Hey.
Hi, baby.
- Sorry I was so late, I, uh...
- We need to talk.
Is it about the wedding?
- Audrey told me you...
- No, I...
Wait, what did Audrey tell you?
She said you told her you
were having second thoughts.
- Is that true?
- No!
I mean...
Yes, I did tell her that, but...
So you can talk
to my sister but not to me?
I'm trying to talk to you
about your sister.
Celine's awake.
She told me she learned
some stuff about Audrey.
At first I didn't know
whether or not to believe...
Why is Celine
investigating Audrey?
Because she knew
something wasn't normal.
And, and she was right.
I found this.
So you're investigating
my sister, too?
Wait. You knew about this?
She's had some problems, Nicole.
It doesn't mean
you can invade her privacy.
Invade her privacy?
She's staying in our home.
I thought we said
no more secrets?
This isn't my secret to tell!
Uh, I'm gonna leave you two...
No, you'll get out of my house.
- What?
- Audrey, don't go anywhere!
If you have a problem
with my sister, you can leave.
But it's fine. Mark, can you
take me to a hotel?
No. Mark can't drive.
Mark's had too much to drink.
I'll call you a cab.
Just, just stay here, okay?
It's fine. I'll handle this.
It's fine.
- You had a stripper tonight?
- What?
After you looked me in the eyes
and said, "Trust me?"
- How did you...
- It doesn't matter how.
I didn't ask for her.
She just showed up.
Strippers don't just appear,
Mark. They get hired.
I told them no.
Charlie must have hired her.
Did Charlie put her
on your lap, too?
- Nicole, I think...
- I don't care what you think.
Get out of my house!
Audrey, don't...
- What is wrong with you?
- Nothing is wrong with me!
Something is wrong
with your sister.
Mark, listen.
Have we ever fought like this?
Ever?
Not until she showed up.
When you found this,
was it empty?
They all were.
Damn it. She's off her meds.
Audrey is sick, Nicole. Okay?
She's not crazy. She's not evil.
- She's my sister and she's sick.
- Mark...
But if you think she's
trying to sabotage me
or my chance at happiness...
you're sick, too.
I think you're right.
Maybe we should
call off the wedding.
Audrey, it's Nicole.
I don't know what to say.
I'm so sorry.
Please come home.
Mark, I know you're angry, okay,
but you've got to come home.
It's Audrey. I...
Mark?
You're trying to take him
away from me?
Audrey, please.
Everyone always tries
to take him away, but you can't.
We're meant to be together.
It's fate.
You have to embrace
your fate, Nicole!
Audrey, what are you doing?
She's trying to
take you away, Mark.
She's trying to keep us apart!
Audrey, listen to me.
Put the knife down.
Let me help you.
Help? No, no, no.
I'm not going back
to the hospital, no.
- No, I'm not going back there.
- It's just...
I belong here with you, Mark!
- Audrey...
- Can't you see what she's doing?
Everything was fine. Hmm?
Until you decided to marry her.
I got better for you.
- I'm fine. I'm fine!
- Okay, that's, that's enough.
That's enough. That's enough.
You're choosing her
over your own sister.
I'm not going back there.
No, I'm not going back.
You can't make me go back.
- Let's talk about this.
- No. I'm going to die.
- No! No!
- Mark...
Audrey, let us help you.
- Audrey. Audrey.
- Please don't make me go back.
Audrey, I love you.
I would never hurt you.
You know that, don't you?
You love me?
Yes.
Please, let me help you.
I love you.
Please, never leave me.
- Do you promise?
- I promise.
- Please.
Please don't leave me.
How is she?
My parents are taking her
back to the hospital.
They'll stay with her
until she's stable.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have
kept this from you.
I understand if you don't want
to go through with the wedding.
Call it off?
After everything you've seen
in the past two weeks?
I've seen some terrible things.
But I also saw the way
you handled Audrey...
and how much you love her...
how much you love me.
Mark, if we can
get through this,
anything else life throws
at us will be easy.
Are you sure you want this?
I'm sure.
Also, the deposit
on the honeymoon
is non-refundable.
So...
- Hey.
- Hey, are you there?
I'm just arriving now.
- Is it everything you hoped for?
- It's perfect.
Actually, no, it's not.
I wish you were here.
It's not going to be the same.
Yeah, you're right.
You should cancel.
The way things have gone,
if I don't get married today,
I don't think
I'll get another chance.
Fair enough. How's the dress?
Not what I wanted,
but... it'll do.
You should write
that on the cake.
Okay, well, um...
You have some marrying to do,
and I have physical therapy,
so, um...
You're still coming to visit
before the reception, right?
Of course.
You'd better, and, Nicole...
Congratulations.
I love you.
Love you, too.
Wonderful to see you again,
Miss Cavanaugh.
Care to follow me
to the bridal suite?
Lead the way.
Okay, everything is all set
and running smoothly.
All you need to do is get ready.
Where were you last week?
Have a vanity here,
bathtub, bathroom through there.
I'll give you some space,
but if you need anything,
just holler, I'm right nearby.
Thank you.
Nicole...
Hello?
- Hello, bride.
- Hi.
- You okay?
- Yeah! Sorry.
Just... nerves.
I've got just the thing
for that.
Wow, bottom shelf. I'm swooning.
You should be. That's what
we drank on our first date.
- Mark!
- So.
How about a quick toast before
becoming my legal property?
Mm, you're so funny,
but no. I'm in my dress.
- You can't be in here. Now go!
- Uh, okay. Okay, okay. Just...
I came here
because I had to see you.
And tell you...
after everything
we've been through,
I've never been more sure.
I can't wait to marry you.
And we are going to be...
so happy.
Then you better let me
finish getting ready.
See you at the altar.
I don't think the blood is gonna
come out of your dress.
I suppose it doesn't matter.
Hmm?
Since you left Mark
at the altar.
First Rachel, then Nicole.
You, uh,
couldn't stand the pain,
so you overdosed,
right here in your room.
Don't worry. You left a note.
Recognize the handwriting?
You said yourself
I was pretty good at it.
Nicole? Five-minute warning.
Everything okay in there?
Be right out!
Okay!
We'd better go.
Wedding's about to start.
♪ It's my day ♪
♪ It's my town
♪ Walking down
♪ Where he was
♪ ...forever
till your last breath ♪
♪ I'll always love you
♪ To death
Audrey?
Yes, my darling.
I'm here.
What the hell is going on?
Where is Nicole?
I am so sorry.
She's gone.
What are you talking about?
She left you this.
She left you, Mark.
Everyone leaves you.
Except for me.
What did you do?
It's so beautiful.
It's so perfect.
Everyone's here for us.
Everything will be perfect
if you just say, "I do."
Nicole!
Mark?
Oh, sh... Nicole. Nicole.
♪ ...You to death
Mark!
What did you do?
She's gone, Mark.
We can still have our wedding.
They're all still
waiting for us.
You're my sister!
Who are you calling, Mark?
I need an ambulance.
My fiancee, she's not breathing.
Stop it!
I know you love me,
just like I love you.
Don't make me do something
we'll both regret.
- Audrey, you were getting help.
- I know you love me, Mark.
We danced together...
at the bachelor party.
We never danced at the bach...
The stripper. That was you?
Oh, didn't that feel so good?
Didn't that feel right, Mark?
Let me take care of you.
Get away from me! You're crazy!
She doesn't care about you!
You're out of your mind!
She doesn't care
about you, Mark!
Oh, my God. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Mark.
I can help you down the aisle.
It's gonna be okay.
Get away from me,
you crazy bitch!
I am so sorry. I didn't...
I didn't mean it.
I did.
Oh, Nicole, thank God.
You're alive. Thank... You're...
No! Audrey, no!
He loves me! He loves me!
He loves me. He loves me.
He loves me.
Nicole.
Hey, it's okay.
Audrey?
Thank you for coming.
I, um...
I know you didn't have to.
We heard how well you're doing.
Yeah, Dr. Lucado says
I'm making real progress.
And part of the treatment plan
is, um, making amends
for those that I've... hurt,
and I just want to say, um...
I'm really sorry.
I didn't realize
what I was doing.
Audrey, we know.
We forgive you.
I don't know how you can forgive
me after what I've done.
That wasn't you, Audrey.
We know that.
I don't know how to thank you
for forgiving me.
You just work on getting better.
That's all we want.
Do you have it?
Are you sure?
Yeah. No, I need
to see it to, um...
remind myself of what's real.
After everything,
we decided to keep it simple.
It's so beautiful.
I think our time's up.
Thank you for coming.
I know it can't have been easy.
We'll always be here
for you, Audrey.
You're our sister.
He loves me.
He loves me not.