[MUSIC PLAYING]
Sandra?
In here, Charles.
Oh, you're home early.
Yeah.
How was your day?
Well, clients, clients'
problems, retainers, pay outs,
all very boring stuff.
What have you
been up to all day?
Cleaning and some reading,
but mostly cleaning.
Cleaning.
Well, it is a big house.
Well, you always said
you wanted a big house.
Well, I do.
It just takes a lot of
time to make sure it's
the way I know you like it.
Well, you do a great job.
Thanks.
Come on.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Want me to make you drink?
You look like you're stressed.
You're the one that looks like
something peculiar is going on.
You OK?
Well, now that you mention
it, I've been feeling
a little strange lately.
You know, it's like I'm
outside of my body, watching.
Like an out-of-body
experience?
Yeah, you know, like I'm--
like I'm a spirit
from another world.
That's pretty heavy.
How long has that been going on?
Well, ever since you
gave me this old book.
That thing?
Listen, I'm telling you, there's
nothing special about it.
Well, where'd you get it?
Old estate sale
that the firm handled.
I thought you might like it,
so I picked it up for you.
Who's estate?
Old movie star, Vera
Montez I think her name was.
Her career was washed
up when sound came in.
She invested well, spent
the last half of the century
studying the occult.
The occult. Wait, you
don't think that this book
could be cursed, do you?
Will you stop it?
Just enjoy it for what
it is, just an old book
with some naughty bits in it.
Charles?
Mm-hm?
I want you to make
love to me, now.
Right now?
Call it silly or
superstition, but I'm on fire.
Well, honey, now's
not really a good time.
What?
I've got some important
things I got to do.
You've got to be kidding me.
It's no joke.
I-- I just said, it's
just I'm busy right
now, just a couple of things.
That's all.
Oh, you're unbelievable.
Maybe you ought
to stop reading
those little sex novels.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
[DOORBELL RINGING]
Sandra, can you
get the door, please?
All right.
Who the hell could this be?
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Can I help you?
Is Mr. Maitland home?
Yes, he is, but
it's a little late.
Is there something
I can help you with?
You have a nice house.
Uh, thank you.
I think I'll like it here.
Excuse me?
Can I speak to
Mr. Maitland now?
You know, just
wait right here.
Um, there's a girl at the front
door, and she's asking for you.
Really?
What does she want?
She didn't say.
She just said that she
thinks she'll like it here.
How peculiar.
Maybe I should look into this.
Yeah, I think you should.
Hello.
Mr. Maitland?
Yes, but you can
call me Charles.
I'm Constance, but
you can call me Connie.
CHARLES: Call me stupid,
but what's going on?
Sandra, meet Connie,
your new live-in.
Live-in?
Maid.
It's a pleasure to
meet you, Mrs. Maitland.
I don't get it.
Honey, you've
been working so hard
to try and keep
this house together,
and you look so
tired all the time.
I just thought I
would surprise you.
With a maid.
A live-in maid.
We can afford it.
You're serious.
Dead serious.
Now, what do you
think about that?
Oh, I don't know,
but thank you.
Well, maybe you could show
Connie to the guest room.
All right.
You ready?
Of course.
SANDRA: Great.
Follow me.
Thank you.
SANDRA: So I guess
this will be your room.
I hope you'll like it.
Oh, it's fine, Mrs. Maitland.
Oh, call me Sandra.
Mrs. Maitland makes
me sound so old.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean anything.
Of course, you didn't.
This is much nicer than
the last place I worked.
It's so comfy.
I don't think I'll
ever want to leave.
Well, make yourself at home.
There's food in
the refrigerator,
if you get hungry, and I'm
sure you'll find your way
around this house in no time.
What are you doing?
I was just going to
put on my nightgown,
but if you don't want me to.
Uh, no.
It's fine.
I'm sorry if I offended you.
I come from a large
family of sisters,
and we're always changing
in front of each other,
and I forgot my manners.
It's all right, Connie.
I understand.
I'm glad, Sandra.
I'm glad they understand.
I didn't want to start
off on the wrong foot.
Oh, I don't think we will.
All right, well,
goodnight, Connie.
Goodnight, Sandra.
Charles.
So what do you think?
Well, I don't
know what to think.
Aren't you happy?
It's what you wanted, isn't it?
Well, it's just, you know--
Just that what?
You said it yourself,
this house is too big.
It's taking up all of
your time, and that's
no way for a beautiful
woman like you to live.
Am I not doing a good job?
I mean, is that it?
Oh, nonsense.
I was just trying
to do you a favor.
Look at it this
way, you can have
all of this free
time on your hands
now to pursue your
own interests.
But to have a live-in, I mean,
maybe that's a little overkill.
Listen, I've got her
at a one-month retainer.
We owe her that.
If it doesn't work out
for you after a month,
you and I will sit
down, and we'll
figure something else out.
Well, I just
don't know if I want
a stranger living in the house.
I mean, when did you even
think about doing this?
I don't know, actually.
I wasn't thinking about it,
and it's hard to explain it.
Just one day, the idea
popped into my head,
and then Connie
came into my office,
and the rest is history.
Let's give her a chance.
What could it hurt?
Well, there's
something about her.
She's strange.
Please, you're acting
like you're afraid of her.
She just started.
I'm sorry.
I didn't think
anyone was in here.
That's OK, Connie.
We were just having
a little nightcap.
Would you like me
to do that for you?
SANDRA: Uh, no.
We can manage.
All right, do you mind?
Uh, no, not at all.
As a matter of fact, I think
a little toast is in order.
To you coming to live with us.
Right, Sandra?
Sure.
OK.
Thank you, you're
both so kind.
Think nothing of it.
Well, if you two will
excuse me, I'm going to bed.
Goodnight.
Is she upset about something?
Don't mind her.
She's just had a
really long day.
Excuse me.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
You know, mixing
booze and sleeping pills
will knock you on your ass.
So what?
I can sleep in tomorrow, right?
Yeah.
You know, I don't
get you, Sandra.
I work so hard to give you
the things that you want,
and once you get them,
you seem so unhappy.
Oh, don't mind me.
I don't know.
I guess I'm in a bad mood.
I know you're trying
to help, but I
don't know what I really want.
Well, you sleep on it.
I think when you
wake up tomorrow,
you'll find you have a
great day ahead of you.
Uh, aren't you
going to come to bed?
A little later, I have a few
things I want to finish up.
Love you.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Is everything all right?
Of course.
I know Sandra very well.
What you're doing is
certainly a bold move.
Yeah.
Well, with great risk
comes great reward.
But to bring me
right into your home,
right under your wife's nose,
you're a very wicked man,
Charles.
And you're a very wicked girl.
Listen, we have to be careful.
A little plotting,
a little planning,
we could do whatever we want.
Right?
Not yet.
I know she's asleep,
but she won't wake up.
Because I'm married to her.
She's dead to the
world right now.
It's booze.
It's pills.
It's every night, and that's
how she goes to sleep.
Go check.
OK.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Oh, Mr. Maitland, is
there something you require?
Of course, there is.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
What are you doing?
I've brought you breakfast.
You were touching me.
I was trying to wake you.
Where's Charles?
He's gone to work already.
He said not to
wake you till 9:00.
Yeah, right.
I don't have
anything to do today.
Do I?
You have a 1:00 lunch
with your friend Sophia.
How did you know that?
She called earlier to confirm.
Is everything all right?
Yeah.
Well, thank you for breakfast.
Will there be anything else?
No.
No, that's it for now.
CONNIE: This is a
very old edition.
Where ever did you find it?
Well, Charles gave it to
me, but have you read this?
Once.
It made me all hot and bothered.
So much sex and wild
abandon, it makes you think.
Think what?
That you can do
anything with anyone.
After all, it's just sex.
Oh, look, it's inscribed.
Wait, oh, I have never
noticed this before.
What does it say?
Well, it says, Vera,
may your hot nights
be filled with passion, Joan.
You see?
Passion goes on forever.
It never dies.
Even beyond the grave?
Who's to say?
[PENSIVE MUSIC]
[PHONE RINGING]
This is Charles.
Charles, it's Sandra.
Well, hello, honey.
How are you feeling today?
Oh, fine.
Why?
Just asking.
Well, I'm sorry.
Don't mind me.
I guess I was asleep when
you left this morning.
Well, that's OK.
You're allowed to sleep
in every now and then.
Yeah.
Well, I just wanted to
say thank you for Connie.
Well, you're welcome.
SANDRA: (ON THE PHONE)
No, I've been childish,
and I don't know why I've
been acting that way lately,
but I want to make it up to you.
Well, what did
you have in mind?
Well, I don't know, but I'm
sure I'll think of something.
Well, I can't wait.
Any big plans today?
I'm meeting Sophia for
lunch, but other than that, no.
Oh, well, tell
Sophia I said hello.
Will do.
Love you.
Love you too.
KEITH: Morning, Sandra.
Oh, Keith, I didn't know
you were working so early.
I've got some projects
out back that require
more attention than others.
Those are pretty.
Yeah, I didn't want
them to go to waste.
Do you have a vase?
I thought they'd look
nice in your kitchen.
Sure.
This'll work.
They have a certain beauty
to them, don't you think?
A fresh, unspoiled
sort of beauty.
Yes, they do.
Will you be here later?
Most of the day.
Well, I have a
lunch appointment,
but I'll see you later
on this afternoon.
I'll be working
in the backyard.
Have fun.
It's going to be hot today.
You new around here?
Yeah, I just
started last night.
I didn't know the
Maitland's were even looking
to bring out a housekeeper.
Mr. Maitland hiring me
as a surprise for his wife.
KEITH: Was she surprised?
I believe she was.
Not as surprised as she's
going to be, I suppose.
What's that supposed to mean?
Gardener's intuition.
A psychic gardener?
Wow, who would have thought it?
Look, I like Sandra.
I like her a lot.
I don't want to see her upset.
I like Sandra too, and I
think maybe with a little time
that she'll like me as well.
I am here to serve.
Didn't you think there'd
be enough work around here
to bring someone on full time.
There's not.
In fact, I have a little
free time right now.
Is that right?
Yeah, and the house will be
empty for the next few hours.
I think you and
I would make much
better friends than enemies.
Don't you think?
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Is this what you want?
Yes.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Hi, I hope I'm not late.
I already knew you
were running late.
You're funny.
No, I'm serious.
You and those cards.
Next thing you know,
you're going to be
trying to tell me my fortune.
You shouldn't be so
quick to laugh, Sandra.
If you know anything about
me, it's that I never
joke about the supernatural.
Well, OK, I'm not laughing.
Actually, I've been thinking
a lot about the supernatural
lately.
Really?
Tell me about it.
Well, it's nothing I
can put my finger on,
but there's a lot
of strange things
going on around my house.
That, and there's
like a presence
or something hanging over me.
I want you to tap
the cards four times.
Oh, OK, eeny, meeny, miny, mo.
OK, let's see, and
describe how you're feeling.
Charles gave me this book,
"Lady Chatterley's Lover,"
and every time I read it, I
have the most vivid daydreams,
like I'm inside the book.
And there's something
wrong with that?
Well, no, not in this
book, but then I found out
it belonged to a dead woman, a
silent movie star, Vera Montez,
and she used to practice the
occult. And then, this woman,
she shows up in my house,
and she becomes my maid.
Wait, slow down.
You're going too fast for me.
Well, that's exactly how this
is all happening, way too fast.
Then, this girl, Connie,
she keeps undressing, OK,
and touching me
while I'm sleeping.
OK.
So you think this all has
something to do with that book.
Oh, that would be
impossible, right?
Well, there's definitely
something unnatural going
on in your life right now.
Are you and Charles happy?
And I mean, you know,
like happy in bed.
Uh, there is nothing
going on in that department.
Actually, maybe that's the
real source of your problems.
You're not getting what you
need, so subconsciously, you're
sending out this
sexual vibe that others
are picking up on, or--
Or what?
Or the ghost of Vera Montez
is possessing the book,
and she's living out her
undead sexual fantasies
through those around her.
Oh, holy shit.
Wait, what can I do?
What you need to do is
fix your sexual problems
with Charles, and see if that
takes care of the problems
in the rest of your life.
You know what?
You're right.
That's exactly what
I'm going to do.
Good.
Let me know how it turns out.
I will.
Thanks.
That or you're bat shit crazy.
[BUZZING]
Yes?
(ON SPEAKER) Your
wife is here to see you.
My wife?
Send her in.
Charles.
Sandra.
I thought you were
having lunch with Sophia.
Yeah, we met, proved
very interesting.
Yes.
Well, out of all
of your friends,
she is the most
interesting case.
Everything OK?
Yeah, everything
is fine, Charles.
How's Sophia?
Very enlightening,
as she always is.
Again, with the
fortune-telling cards?
Well, she has a
very real talent,
and she always amazes me.
What did she say this time?
She told me that the
old book that you gave me
is possessed by the spirit
of its former owner.
The book, possessed,
by like ghost?
By ghosts or--
What?
Well, it's either
that, or we're
just not having enough sex.
What do you think it is?
Well, that's what
I'm here to find out.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Oh my god.
That can't be.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
It can't be, but it is.
It's true.
I've got to warn Sandra.
[CHIMES RINGING]
Oh my god, you must be--
Yes, I'm Vera Montez.
But you're dead.
Yes, but thanks to
"Lady Chatterley's Lover,"
I'm enjoying myself
much more now than I
ever did when I was alive.
So your spirit's
trapped inside that book?
I wouldn't say trapped,
but possessed, definitely.
But why?
I was once a big star,
the biggest in Hollywood,
and then talking
pictures came along,
and nobody wanted me anymore.
Fortunately, I had saved
my money and invested well
and I lived my life in luxury.
But I was alone, starved
for the attention of men.
And now, in death,
you're young again.
And able to indulge
in whatever I desire.
You can't possess Sandra.
It's wrong, and I won't let you.
I'm not possessing anyone.
In fact, I'm just helping
them free themselves
from their own sexual
hang-ups and enjoying
myself a little along the way.
But they can't
resist your magic.
They have no will of their own.
You've had a spell over them.
Not a big one, but I do get
what I want, and so do they.
How does it work?
First, I look at them,
and then I touch them,
and then they want me,
just like you do right now.
Your touch is like a drug.
All I can think
about at this moment
is how badly I want
to make love to you.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Hello?
Anybody home?
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Connie?
[PHONE RINGING]
This is Charles.
Uh, Charles, it's Sandra.
Oh, hey.
You made it home OK.
Yeah.
Um, yeah.
I'm at the house now,
but there's no one here.
Oh.
Well, go ahead and
start dinner without me.
I'm going to be
working late anyway.
Just don't let it get cold.
All right, well, dinner's
on the table, you know,
and that's what worries me.
CHARLES: (ON THE PHONE)
Oh, don't worry yourself.
Connie probably started
dinner and forgot something,
went out to get it.
Yeah, you're probably right.
Well, what else could it be?
You're making a big mystery
out of everything lately.
Yeah, you're right.
Of course, I am, and um,
thanks for this afternoon.
We should do that more often.
Any time.
Bye.
Is it possible?
Could this book be possessed?
CONNIE: It could be.
SANDRA: Oh, I didn't
hear you come in.
I'm light on my feet.
Where have you been?
Oh, around.
That's not a real answer.
Well, if you must know, I
went to visit your friend.
Sophia.
Sophia, why?
Let's just say we have
some common interests.
Is she all right?
Better than all right.
In fact, I think I helped to
relieve a lot of tension today.
May I?
Oh, yeah.
"Lady Chatterley's Lover."
do you know how many
times I've read this book?
No.
Too many to count.
I've spent many years
pleasuring myself to this book.
I've almost worn the pages
out, and now it's yours.
Have you ever touched
yourself while reading it?
Don't lie.
A few times.
It's good, huh?
Are you the ghost Vera Montez?
Well, I guess the
cat's out of the bag.
Are you scared?
No.
Good.
I just want to get you and
your husband back on track,
get you guys interested
in each other again.
And then what?
And then I want you to
pass the book along to one
of your girlfriends, a hot one.
I can do that.
Good.
Now, let's lay down.
OK.
What are we going to do?
I want you to read your
favorite part of the book
while I touch you.
We can enjoy this book together.
All right.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Sandra.
Where the hell is everybody?
[PHONE RINGING]
Hello?
Charles?
It's Sophia.
Oh, Sophia, you're
looking for Sandra.
SOPHIA: (ON PHONE)
Yeah, is she there?
I don't know.
Well, I just go home.
I don't see anybody.
Charles, listen to me.
Your new maid is a ghost.
She has the power
to hypnotize people.
It's like witchcraft
or something.
Listen, this whole
business is just
getting crazier and crazier.
Next thing you're
going to tell me she
turned into a bat or something.
Charles, stay away from her.
She could be dangerous.
Well, thank you
for the warning,
but I can handle Connie.
Heed this warning.
I found out the truth
from myself today.
I hear you loud and clear.
I'll tell you what, I'll
have Sandra give you a call
as soon as I find her.
Charles.
Bye.
Ghosts, witches wow.
[MOANING]
SANDRA: That feels good, right?
CONNIE: Yeah, it does.
SANDRA: Yeah, you like that?
CONNIE: Yeah.
Oh, Charles.
Don't let me interrupt.
Why don't you join us?
I don't think that's
going to be a great idea.
Charles, if we
help her now, then
her spirit will leave
the house and everything
will go back to normal.
Like a sexual exorcism.
Exactly.
Well?
Well, since I
don't believe in any
of this spiritual mumbo-jumbo,
I guess it wouldn't hurt.
Not unless you want it to.
Stand back and let the
sexorcist do his thing.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[CHIMES RINGING]
What have you
been up to all day?
Cleaning.
I mean, some reading,
but mostly cleaning.
Call me stupid, but
what's going on?
Well, it's either that, or we're
just not having enough sex.
Listen, this whole
business is just
getting crazier and crazier.
Next thing you're
going to tell me she
turned into a bat or something.
Yes.
Well, out of all
of your friends,
she is the most
interesting case.
Maybe you ought to stop reading
those little sex novels.
Mr. Maitland hired me as
a surprise for his wife.
I was just going to
put on my nightgown,
but if you don't want me to.
I was once a big star,
the biggest in Hollywood,
and then talking
pictures came along,
and nobody wanted me anymore.
SANDRA: Thanks.
That or you're bat shit crazy.
You can't possess Sandra.
It's wrong, and I won't let you.
Are you and Charles happy?
And I mean, you know,
like happy in bed.
They have a certain
kind of beauty to them,
don't you think?
A fresh, unspoiled
kind of beauty.
I like Sandra.
I like her a lot.
[SOFT INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC]