[intense rock music]
[intense rock music continues]
- Five, ten, and 15.
Now, remember you have to
wait at least six weeks
before you can sell blood again.
- Shit, I need more than
this. It's not enough.
- Well, I hope we see more of you here.
You know, you have an
extremely rare blood type.
- Well, you can have some
more right now if you want to.
I could use some another 15 bucks.
- But I'm afraid that's against the rules.
We have to wait a full six weeks
before we can accept blood
from the same person again.
- And I bet you're a real
stickler for the rules, right?
- Well, I can't accept
another blood donation now,
but you could be of great
service to this clinic
and be paid generously for the effort.
- How generously?
- How does a hundred
dollars a day sound to you?
- A hundred dollars a day?
You're shittin' me, right?
- We can begin now if you want to.
- Well, what do you want to do?
- Just let me run a few simple tests.
You see, for these sort of tests,
young women of your age
range make the best subjects.
And if we begin now, we could
be finished by the evening
and you'll be a hundred dollars richer.
- Hey, let's go.
What's in that?
- Just a type of vaccine.
I wanna test your body's reaction to it.
It was designed to stimulate
the body's defense mechanism
to make the human organism
literally invulnerable
against disease, fatigue.
When I perfect the serum,
the human life expectancy may be stretched
by 20, 30, maybe even 50 years.
And if my tests are successful,
you'll be the first to benefit.
[chuckles]
- I don't know about all that,
but as long as you keep the
cash coming, I'll be back.
- I'm sure you will.
[intense rock music]
[coughing]
- Are you okay, ma'am?
Are you sure you're okay, ma'am?
You know there's a
drugstore down the street
if you wanna get something to put on that.
It could get infected.
- No, no, I'm all right.
- [Man] Okay, you're the boss.
All right, I tried to help.
[intense rock music]
- When I left here, I felt kind of sick.
A kind of nausea, I guess.
- That's perfectly natural.
Your body is adjusting to
a new chemical component,
but in a few days, my serum
will be completely absorbed
into your blood and then you
should feel completely fine.
- But it was more than just stomach pains.
Something else happened.
I cut my leg when I fell
on some broken glass
and when I looked at the blood,
I felt a strange kind of hunger.
I wanted to taste the blood.
- Interesting. And did you?
- Did I?
- Did you taste the blood?
- Yes.
And when I did, the pain was gone.
Isn't that strange?
- Well, not necessarily.
Sometimes the mind makes
subconscious associations
between psychological trauma
and something more tangible, physical.
I'm sure that's all it was.
There, the serum's ready.
I'm slightly increasing your dosage today.
Soon I'll know if my
experiment is a success.
[people chattering indistinctly]
[spits]
- This is awful.
- [Waiter] Is there anything wrong here?
- Yeah. This tastes like shit.
- Well, we haven't had any complaints.
- Well, I'm complaining.
This isn't fit to drink.
- Well you still owe me two bucks.
You're gonna pay for it.
- Here.
I hope you fuckin' choke on it.
- I don't have to stand
for this kind of talk.
You get outta here.
- I don't know what kind of dive this is,
but it's no restaurant.
See ya.
[people chattering indistinctly]
[women chattering indistinctly]
- She looks like she's psycho.
Nicole, do we have to stand
around here all night?
I wanna go home.
- Yeah? Well, if you
go, it'll be your loss.
You know who's staying here, don't you?
- No, and I really don't care.
- You don't care that Irwin R.
Stone is supposed to be here?
Stone Productions? The movie producer?
Is any of this sinking in, Robin?
- So what?
You think he's gonna put
you in his next movie?
Just gimme five minutes
with the fat bastard.
I'll be under a contract
before his pants hit the floor.
- That's what I like about you, Nicole.
You're so humble.
- Modest, too.
That's why guys shit themselves
over me, 'cause I'm a lady.
That's him.
- You sure?
- Look.
This picture, it's him.
- Well, I guess it looks like him.
- This is it. Wish me luck.
- Well, are you gonna get
me a part in the movie too?
- Who am I, Robin?
Your agent?
Mr. Stone.
- Yes?
- I can't believe it's really you.
I heard you might be staying here,
so, well, here I am.
- You certainly are, aren't you?
- I hope you don't think
I'm being too forward.
- No, no, no, no, no.
I'll tell you what,
I'll bet you're a friend
of Mel's aren't you?
- Mel?
Oh yeah. Sure.
You know, Mel thought
you might hit it off.
What do you think?
- I think Mel's a hell of
a guy. A hell of a guy.
I'll tell you what, I
bet you you could use
a refreshment and guess what?
I have a brand new bottle of
Boone's Farm up in the room.
- Boone's Farm? Oh, that's my favorite.
Maybe we could slip on back up?
- Okay.
Okay.
Well here we are.
I'll tell you what, why don't you relax
and I'll pour us a tall glass of vino.
- Mr. Stone, I didn't
know you spoke Italian.
You're so cultured.
- I've got plenty of
surprises up my sleeves.
- Maybe so, but it's not
what's up your sleeve
I came to see.
- Mm, that sounds good.
Why don't you just relax
and let me get that glass of wine
and we'll be ready to loosen up.
So, uh, what do you do for a living?
- [Nicole] Oh, I'm an actress.
A very good actress.
- Really?
You think I might have
seen you in anything?
- [Nicole] That depends. Did
you see Alien Egg Layers?
I was the nude alien queen.
- You were?
- [Nicole] Then I had a cameo in Hell Camp
as the nude swimmer.
I'm killed in the pre-credit sequence,
so you might have missed me.
- I think I saw that one on cable,
but I'm still trying to place you.
- Does this jog your memory?
- Yeah.
Yeah, it does.
In fact, you look really, really good.
- Do you remember the
scene in Alien Egg Layers
when I lure the handsome earth stud
to my spaceship for breeding experiments?
- No, I don't think I saw that one.
- Let's pretend we're on the set
and the director yells action.
[man chuckles]
- Okay. Yeah.
Yeah, I could be up for some action.
- I bet you can picture me
in your next film, can't you?
That's what my whole career
has been leading up to,
to star in an Irwin R. Stone production.
- Irwin?
My name's Murray.
What are you talking about?
- You're not Irwin R.
Stone, the film producer?
- No, I'm Murray J. Stone,
the carpet salesman.
- I don't believe this.
Oh God, I almost fucked a carpet salesman.
- [Murray] Hey, salesman of the year.
- You're no salesman, you rapist!
[heavy breathing]
- What do you mean rapist?
I didn't touch you.
- I've got to find Robin.
She's probably met the real Stone.
He's probably giving her my part.
Robin, Robin!
[door creaks]
- Hey, listen.
I don't care what that girl told you,
I didn't touch her, I didn't rape her.
- I know that. I've been watching you.
- And you might as well know, too.
I'm not a big Hollywood producer.
I'm just a carpet salesman
that's here from Jersey.
Salesman of the year, but-
Hey you okay?
- I think I'm sick.
- You're sick?
- I need you to help me.
- Come here, lay down.
Lay down here.
You need something to drink?
- That's why I came.
To drink.
- Here.
Not wine.
- I got a couple beers
left over. You want a beer?
- A little closer.
I need to drink…
[snarls]
[Murray yelling]
[intense rock music]
[pounding on door]
- What is going on in here?
I'm trying to get some sleep.
[Caroline snarls]
[intense rock music]
What's wrong with you?
You're covered in blood,
stay away from me!
[woman screams]
[intense rock music]
[Caroline snarls]
- Your color looks much
better today, Caroline.
- You think so?
- Absolutely. I think my
serum is having an effect.
Wouldn't you agree?
- I think it is, doctor.
Do you have my hundred dollars?
- I know, business first.
We better get busy.
I have a whole series of
tests to run on you today.
- I want to show you something first.
- Really?
- Ever since last night,
I now know what that serum is doing to me.
- It's making you stronger.
It's creating the ultimate
immune system in your body.
Soon there will be no disease
or sickness that can affect you.
- But there's something else.
It's given me a strange appetite.
Do you want me to show you, doctor?
- You can wait to eat
after I'm through with these experiments.
- But I want to show you
now so you'll understand.
So you'll understand
what's happening to me.
- Caroline, you don't
know what you're doing.
- I think I do, doctor.
[intense rock music]
- Caroline, you're not feeling well.
- I'll be all right,
doctor. After I've eaten.
[screaming]
[snarling]
[intense rock music]
[people chattering indistinctly]
- You look like you need some company.
- Not-
- Come on, honey.
- Not tonight, honey.
- Oh, no…
- No, I'm in a hurry tonight.
- No, you're going with us tonight.
- No, not tonight.
- Let's go.
- I can't tonight. No, no.
No come on, I'm busy tonight. Come on.
No, get away.
Look, find somebody else. Come on.
- Come on, come with us.
- What's wrong with that guy?
- What a jerk.
Let's go find somebody else.
- All right, yeah.
Forget that guy, he's an idiot.
- We'll find somebody else.
- We're find real one.
Hey, what do you think her problem is?
- I don't know.
[laughing]
Hey lady, this isn't a hotel.
God, she's had a lot more
to drink than we have.
- She looks like she needs
to have some fun. [laughs]
- Maybe she can come with us.
You wanna come and have some fun with us?
A little drink, maybe?
Come on, let's take her with us.
She'll have a lot of fun.
- Yeah, come on.
We'll show you a real party.
- [Girl In Blue] We can
party all night long.
- [Girl In White Jacket] I
think this girl's been doing
some partying herself.
- Doing some serious drinking.
- Some serious partying.
- Let's go show her a good time.
- Let's show her a real party.
- [Girl In Blue] Trust me,
you'll be the life of the party.
Just come with us.
[laughing]
[moaning]
[snarling]
[screaming]
[sobbing]
- Dumb white bitch! Jesus.
[intense rock music]
- Forget about her. Now
it's just me and you.
- Not here.
- Take me where you want.
[intense rock music]
[sighs]
[woman sighs]
[moans]
[water splashing]
[cars passing]
[phone ringing]
- Hello?
Lisa.
What happened?
Why did you storm outta
here? What's wrong?
- Amy, look, there's no sense in even
talking about it anymore.
I'm not coming back.
It's over.
- No, don't leave me.
Please, I promise it'll
never happen again.
No, please. One more chance.
I, I, I, fucked up okay?
Okay?
No, I won't do it again!
No, please, don't, don't leave me!
- Yeah, that's what you said last time
and you promised it the time before that.
Look, I need some kind commitment.
I need a real relationship.
And if you can't give me that,
well then we're finished.
Look, I've got my things packed.
I just need a place.
I just need to get my life together, okay?
Amy.
Amy, it's over, okay? Goodbye.
- Why did I do it?
[sobbing]
[Caroline coughing]
- What's wrong?
Are you sick?
- I'll be all right.
- Are you sure?
- I just feel kind of faint.
- Oh my gosh. I, I'm
sitting here watching you.
Maybe you need a doctor.
- No!
No doctors. You have to promise.
- Okay, no doctors.
All right, maybe you're
not as sick as I thought.
- It's just, I'm so hungry.
It's been so long since I've eaten.
- Oh.
Well we can take care of that.
Come along with me.
Come along with me. Let's go.
- No, no.
I appreciate you trying
to help, but you can't.
- Listen, listen.
[Caroline coughing]
Hey, hey.
Hey.
You are getting off this street.
Come with me. I don't want any arguments.
Now come on.
[cars passing]
Oh great, thank you.
Well, come on, you said you were starving.
Help yourself.
- I can't, really. It's not what I need.
Look, you've been very
nice, but I have to go.
- I don't wanna be a bitch,
but you're not leaving this table
until you eat something, okay?
You were so weak. You fainted twice.
Now come on.
It's not filet mignon,
but it'll do for now.
[people chattering indistinctly]
- Happy?
- Well, it's a start.
So, um, I need a place tonight.
You wouldn't happen to know of
any cheap motels, would you?
- I happen to be an
expert on cheap hotels.
Although in New York,
even a roach motel can cost $50 a night.
- Oh, that's way over my limit.
Well, I didn't expect
to need a place tonight.
I had a major breakup today
and I walked out before knowing
where I was gonna sleep.
- Man trouble, huh?
[laughs]
- No,
more like girl meets girl,
girl falls in love with girl,
girl gets fucked over one
too many times and walks out.
- I see.
Look, can you excuse me for a minute?
- You're not gonna try
and walk on me, are you?
- I'll be right back. I promise.
- I'll be waiting.
[people chattering indistinctly]
[intense rock music]
[breathing shallowly]
- Come on, Lisa, let's go.
- Did you get enough to eat?
- I'm stuffed.
I know a great club a
few blocks from here.
You wanna go?
- Well you seem to be feeling better.
- Yeah, I feel great.
- Let's go.
- Oh look at that hat.
I would never wear that.
- You'd look great in that.
- Oh, no.
- Oh, sunglasses.
[indistinct chattering]
- What do you think? Don't
those look good on her?
Can I borrow that for a second?
Take a look.
[Caroline chuckles]
- Those look really nice.
- Okay, let's go.
- [Man] Is that the way it is now?
You're calling the shots?
- That's right, and I don't need you
breathing down my neck anymore.
If I feel like going to a
club, I'm going, all right?
I don't need your permission.
- Nobody fucks with my
business, fuckin' bitch.
[strange, frenzied music]
[indistinct singing]
[percussive music]
[intense rock music]
[soft rock music]
[people chattering]
- You guys need two?
- Yeah.
[train brakes squeal]
[people chattering indistinctly]
- Thanks a lot for letting us
stay at your place, Gina.
- Oh it's no problem. We're almost there.
So how long have you two known each other?
- Well, we actually-
- Lisa and I go way back.
Sometimes it feels like we've
know each other forever.
♪ Because of the
wonderful things he does ♪
[laughing]
- Wow, this is really a great place.
- Oh, thanks.
Look, I can sleep over here on the couch
if you two girls wanna take the room.
- Well, I guess that's up to Caroline.
- That'll be fine, Gina.
I hope nobody wants to
get up early tomorrow.
I feel like I could sleep all day.
- Ooh, you mean you're a night person?
- That's how it seems to work out.
When the sun is out, I just
want to curl up and hide.
Don't you feel like that sometimes?
- Well, I've been known
to sleep until noon
if that's what you mean.
Of course, I don't have any real reason
to get up at all tomorrow.
As of tonight, I'm officially unemployed.
- So you don't have to start looking
for another job tomorrow?
- Don't rush me.
- I wanna savor a little freedom first.
- I know what you mean.
I feel like I'm starting
over, but you know what?
It's not so bad when you have friends.
- [Caroline] I don't know
why I'm even going to bed.
I'm not even tired.
- [Lisa] You were acting
half dead this afternoon.
Are you sure you feel okay?
- Yeah.
I'm fine. Really.
- You know, this afternoon,
I was feeling like I didn't
have a friend in this town.
Well…
I guess what I'm trying to say is
I'm just really glad I met you, Caroline.
- You know, I haven't had
anyone really care about me
in a long time.
There's been no one to count on.
- Yeah.
- You got me.
So can I have a goodnight kiss?
[moaning]
[Lisa gasps]
[chuckles]
- I just brought an extra blanket.
It might get cold.
- Thanks, Gina.
Goodnight.
- Goodnight.
[laughing]
That was too funny.
Do you see the look on her face?
- Yeah.
- Caroline?
[tense music]
[heavy breathing]
[Gina grunts]
[snarling]
[snarls]
Caroline?
[Caroline gasps]
- Don't look at me.
I don't want you see me.
- Caroline, oh my god,
you're covered in blood.
- I didn't want it to be you, Lisa. [sobs]
I couldn't help it.
I needed someone.
- Caroline, what are you talking about?
- I need blood.
I have to have it to live.
You don't what I am.
You don't know what they did to me!
- Who Caroline? I don't understand.
- The clinic.
The clinic. They made me this way.
Everyday it gets worse.
If I don't drink blood,
I feel like I'm dying.
Every day, I have to have it!
I can't help it.
- Its not your fault.
Caroline-
- You can't stay with me!
- Whoever did this to
you, it's not your fault.
- If 1 go too long without
it, I might lose control.
I might, I might even hurt you.
- No, no, look, we'll get
through this together.
Caroline, I'm not leaving you.
- You don't know what I am!
- Caroline, I care about you.
We'll get through this together.
Look, in the clinic,
whatever they did to you,
we'll go back there and
we'll make them undo it.
- No!
No. I'm not going back.
I'm not going back.
They'll kill me if I go back.
- Okay.
- Promise me.
- All right, look.
I promise.
- You won't take me back there.
- I promise, I wouldn't
do anything to hurt you.
All right, look, no one
knows that we're here.
We can just stay here
for a few days, okay?
- What about her?
- Oh geez.
Well, we'll just have to get rid of her.
Look, I tell you what we're gonna do.
Look, you just go back to bed
and you just get some rest, okay?
All right?
Look, I'm gonna take care of this.
[intense rock music]
[squelching]
- Lisa!
Lisa!
[shower water pattering]
Where is Gina, Lisa?
- I told you I'd take care of it.
I just want to protect you.
I just want to take care of you.
- You are so good to me.
[shower water pattering]
- I love you, Caroline.
- And I love you, Lisa.
- I love you.
[shower water pattering]
[intense rock music]
- [Man] Oops, where's the key?
Okay.
[Caroline laughs]
Oh.
- Hm, let's see what
kind of music you have.
Play this.
- Mm, picked a good one.
[rock music]
♪ Oh, the light's so bright ♪
♪ And the nights are colder ♪
♪ Yeah, there's no tomorrow ♪
♪ My head's dizzy ♪
♪ And nothing can kick my sorrows ♪
♪ Oh, the lights are so cold ♪
♪ Don't believe a single
thing that I've told ♪
♪ Oh, the light is so bright ♪
♪ See if I can find my way back ♪
♪ I'll, I'll rise again ♪
♪ And I'll, I'll fall again ♪
♪ I will ♪
[rock music]
[Caroline snarling]
[Caroline breathing heavily]
♪ I will rise again ♪
♪ I, I will fall again ♪
♪ The lights, oh they're so bright ♪
♪ Maybe, maybe I can find my way tonight ♪
♪ I'll, I'll rise again ♪
♪ And I'll, I'll fall again ♪
[rock music]
♪ You made a sound like
a fight too many times ♪
♪ To find no answers in
all the places to grind ♪
♪ Seeing all the boring videos ♪
♪ I've been to that place ♪
♪ I swear, I don't want to go ♪
♪ And I'll, I'll rise again ♪
- Oh, Caroline.
Oh, you came back.
- I'm sorry, Lisa.
But you know what happens
when the hunger comes over me.
I don't wanna be near
you when that happens.
I don't ever wanna hurt you, Lisa.
- You won't.
You won't.
So how do you feel? Do
you feel better, hm?
- I'll be okay tonight.
But every day I need someone.
It's been like that ever since,
ever since I left that hospital.
- Who were they? What did they do to you?
- I was desperate.
I needed money.
I went there to sell blood,
you know, a quick 15 bucks.
Back then, that seemed like
all the money in the world.
Anyway, they told me
about these experiments
they were doing and
they needed young women.
They paid a hundred dollars a day
and I couldn't pass up money like that.
[snarling]
[man yelling]
So that was the first one,
and ever since then I've had
to do it again and again.
Every day I need blood.
Without it, I can't
even describe the pain.
When it hurts so bad, I'd kill anyone
to make the pain stop.
Make the pain stop. Please stop it.
Make the pain stop. [sobbing]
- Oh, you poor thing.
- I mean, they're all dead.
I mean, I'm just gonna keep on killing.
I might as well just end it all.
- No, Caroline, no.
And I don't ever wanna
hear you talk like that.
Now we're gonna get through
this together, okay?
Now, whatever they did
to you at that clinic,
there's got to be a cure,
but until then, I'm gonna help you.
- You're gonna help me?
- Yes. You need blood,
we'll get you blood.
Okay?
- No-
- It's the only way to keep you alive.
- No, Lisa, I can't drag you into this.
Lisa, you're the first person
I've really cared about.
- I care about you, Caroline,
and that's why I'm gonna help you now.
Now look, you're gonna need
more blood tomorrow, okay?
And I'm gonna help you get it.
- Where?
- Well, do you remember that nightclub
you took me to last night?
Do you remember there was a
boy on stage with a singer?
Well, I did some looking around
today while you were gone
and found out that he is very
easy to get to know, okay?
Now I even got his phone number
and I think he would
appreciate a phone call
from one of his admirers.
- What's his name?
- His name is Nick.
- Nick.
Hello? Is this Nick?
Oh, you don't know me, my name's Caroline.
I caught your show at the club yesterday.
I really enjoyed it. I
thought you were incredible.
Well, anyways, I was wondering
maybe if you're not busy
tomorrow, we might get together.
I think I'd like to get to know you.
Yeah, I think I can find it.
See you then.
[Caroline sighs]
Hey, you know, I really appreciate you
letting me crash here.
There's been a lot
that's come up suddenly.
- Oh, it's no problem.
Everyone at that damn club's
been crashing here lately.
- Mm I see you've got a lot
of interesting stuff here.
- Yeah, but this one here
doesn't have a name yet.
It's just about exploring sexuality.
It's got cocks and cunts
and all that good stuff.
This one here, it's called "Pipe Dreams.”
It's about pregnant women who smoke crack.
- I've always loved pregnant women.
- And I've always loved crack. [chuckles]
- I'm feeling kind of scruffy.
Do you mind if I take a bath?
- Sure, it's down the hall,
but I don't have any clean towels.
- That's okay.
[bath water running]
[television blaring]
- How's it going in there?
[knocks]
It's just me.
Just came to see if you needed any help.
- Here.
You wanna make yourself useful?
[rock music]
[Nick gasping]
[grunting]
[rock music]
[Nick grunting]
[water splashing]
[Lisa gasps]
- That's right. Just step right on in.
- What do you want?
- I might ask you the
same thing, both of you,
but just so we get started
off on a first name basis,
my name is Tony and this is my
girlfriend Gina's apartment.
Now suddenly she's gone
and you two have moved in.
Now, I'm sure there's a reasonable
explanation for all this.
- We live here now.
She doesn't even live here anymore.
- Oh, so you live here now?
[Lisa gasps]
I can see she's not here,
but the landlord seems to
think she still lives here.
And who could blame him?
After all, this is her
furniture, these are her tapes.
Even her clothes.
I bought this one for her last month.
$500.
You telling me she left
all this stuff behind?
- Look, she's just gone, all right.
You're not gonna find her here anywhere.
- You seem to be awfully sure of that.
[Lisa gasps]
- Leave her alone.
- Maybe you can tell me
where I can find her.
- Just leave her alone!
She doesn't know anything.
- You know, I'm starting to really lose
my fuckin' patience here.
One of you better start
talking and real quick.
You think I'm bluffing?
One shot and your girlfriend
ain't got no face.
Now, are you ready to
tell me where Gina is?
- Okay!
Okay.
We talked to her the night before last,
but just for a little bit.
- You talked to her?
And she invited you to come over
and take over her fucking apartment?
- No.
No, it's not like that.
I guess we told her how
we needed a place to stay.
She said we could hang
out here for a few days
'cause she was going out of town.
- That's pretty fucking
convenient, isn't it?
Especially when little miss Gina
is in to me for about two G's now.
Maybe I didn't mention this
in our little introductory,
but Gina and I have a very
professional relationship.
She takes care of me
and I take care of her.
In other words, she's
one of the highest paid
pieces of ass in New York.
Now Gina makes me a lot of money
and nobody's going to stop that.
Not you and definitely not you.
- Well, we could just go.
If you don't want us
here, we'll just leave.
- Oh, you'll just go? You
think it's that simple?
Maybe I didn't make
myself perfectly clear,
so let's try it like this:
when Gina is not making
me money, I am not happy.
And when I am not happy,
you better fuckin' believe you two
are not going to be happy campers.
You say Gina's coming back?
All right, fine.
But until she does, you're
both working for me.
You both look like you've got
a couple of hot little bodies.
Yeah.
I bet there are plenty of guys
that would pay big time
for a crack at you two.
So what do you say?
- You can go to fuckin' hell.
[slaps]
[Caroline grunts]
- I hope I didn't damage
the merchandise too much.
We might as well get comfortable.
I think we're going to be
seeing a lot of each other.
- [Lisa] You just can't keep us here.
- As long as I'm holding this,
I think I can do whatever the fuck I want.
Now you just help make
your girlfriend beautiful.
You both go to work in one hour
and you're not coming back in
here until I see $500 each.
- You gonna be okay?
- I'll all right.
- Gina used to keep some
pretty good chow around here
if you bitches haven't cleaned it out.
- No, no, no, please.
Let me get that for you.
I'll do it.
- You just take care of your face, honey.
I can take care of things in here.
- Caroline, he's going into the kitchen.
- What the fuck is this shit?
This isn't Gina's.
Those are Gina's rings…
That's her fuckin' hand!
Oh my God.
You've cut her to pieces.
[Caroline snarls]
[Tony gasps]
[yelling]
[intense rock music]
Ah, stop!
[grunting]
[intense rock music]
Get off of me!
What are you doing?
[yelling]
[intense rock music]
Get off of me!
[grunting]
[intense rock music]
[Caroline snarling]
[gunshot]
- Oh, god!
Oh…
- Lisa?
Lisa!
Lisa, you can't die on me.
You can't die on me.
Lisa, I love you.
I love you, Lisa.
[Caroline sobbing]
Lisa!
Lisa, don't die on me!
[sobbing]
I love you, Lisa.
I love you.
[sobbing]
[intense rock music]
I love you.
[soft, tense music]
Lisa!
[sobbing]
[soft, tense music]
Lisa…
[sobbing]
[soft, tense music]
Lisa.
[sobbing]
[soft, tense music]
[tense music continues]