(Multicom jingle)
(placid music)
- There's a local Ojibwe saying,
If a young woman makes her way
to the church of our elders,
she will return one day with her husband.
- Don't put any money on me.
- But it's true.
- Tease, I know I said
I wouldn't leave Alaska until
I visited some sacred grounds,
but I just can't.
(tribal chanting)
Are those ceremonial drums?
- Yes, but the sounds are deceiving here.
It's two more miles upriver.
- Two miles?
Oh, I mean, we got this far.
(tribal chanting)
What's two little miles?
(water splashing)
(birds chirping)
(tribal chanting)
(water splashing)
(drums thumping)
(speaking in foreign language)
(tribal chanting)
(drums thumping)
- I told him tat you
wanted to take pictures,
and that you've come to
give him a gift of thanks.
(tribal chanting)
(drums thumping)
(speaking in foreign language)
(tribal chanting)
(drums thumping)
He thanks you.
(speaking in foreign language)
He gives you this
necklace to remember them,
and it will protect you.
- Thank you.
(tribal chanting)
(drums thumping)
(camera snapping)
(tribal chanting)
(drums thumping)
(camera snapping)
(tribal chanting)
(drums thumping)
(camera snapping)
(tribal chanting)
(drums thumping)
(camera snapping)
(tribal chanting)
(drums thumping)
(beeper beeping)
(birds chirping)
Oh, damn.
(beeper beeping)
(birds chirping)
- There's a telephone about
three miles down the river,
near where we put the canoe in the water.
- Tomorrow, I'll be back in Denver,
slugging at a light beer campaign,
fighting for my place in the
corporate ladder, you'd think.
- Wait, you dislike your work?
- Oh, I love advertising.
Sometimes, I wonder why.
(water rushing)
Do you have a Sherry Winslow there?
I was notified she was
in an auto accident.
Oh, well, what's her condition?
Yes, yes, I'm her sister.
Well, could you please
connect me to her room?
Well, why, what's wrong with her?
Well, well, who can answer my questions?
Oh.
(phone slamming)
- [Pilot] Attention passengers,
we'll be landing in Denver in 10 minutes.
(placid music)
(motor droning)
(car door slamming)
(placid music)
(siren ringing)
- [Doctor] Clear the way, clear the way.
(chattering)
(placid music)
- What happened?
(phone ringing)
- Oh, honey, she...
She's gone.
- What?
- She's gone, she's gone (cries).
(placid music)
- Oh, she can't be dead.
No.
(placid music)
She can't be.
Where is she?
I wanna see her.
(placid music)
(chattering)
Couldn't you wait, Sher?
God, this can't be true.
What happened?
- She had severe internal injuries.
They wanted to operate
to stop the bleeding,
but when she saw the concent form
and realized there was a
substantial risk to the baby,
she refused.
- I beg your pardon?
- The procedure could
have been a long one,
there was a chance...
- What baby?
- She was just beginning
her seventh month pregnancy.
They were able to deliver her
child by caesarian section,
but I'm afraid they don't
hold much hope for him.
(placid music)
- Him, a boy.
Excuse me.
(placid music)
(door rattling)
(door slamming)
(placid music)
(Christine crying)
I'll take you home.
- No, not yet, you go ahead.
(phone ringing)
- [Nurse] Jennifer.
(chattering)
- I don't wanna leave you here.
- She asked to be cremated.
(chattering)
- I'll take care of it.
- She wants the ashes in
California near the cottage.
(chattering)
- Why didn't you tell me she was pregnant?
- Because I didn't know,
not until I'd picked
her up at the airport.
(phone ringing)
- Who's the father?
- She wouldn't say.
And now, I don't want to know.
(phone ringing)
(chattering)
- You remember last Christmas,
she was madly in love?
- She was always madly in love.
- No, this was different.
She made him sound like
some sort of Howard Hughes.
(placid music)
I sorta I wrote it off.
- She was determined to have that baby.
And it was all for nothing
(sobs) and she's gone.
(placid music)
(mother crying)
(baby crying)
(placid music)
(machine beeping)
- May I help you?
- I'd like to see Sherry
Winslow's baby, I'm his aunt.
- I'm sorry, no visitors.
- Oh, my sister died about an hour ago.
And I know that she would have
wanted someone to touch him.
Please, would you let me do that for her?
(baby crying)
(machine beeping)
(placid music)
Your mother paid a gigantic
price for your life.
(machine beeping)
(placid music)
Don't be too quick to let it go.
(machine beeping)
(placid music)
Give him a name, at least.
(machine beeping)
(placid music)
Kevin, our uncle.
(machine beeping)
(placid music)
(rain splashing)
- Hey, kiddo.
(placid music)
(phone ringing)
Kathy told me you came in, what
the hell are you doing here?
(placid music)
- I'm not staying, I'm
on my way to Sacramento.
- Well, take all the time you need.
(phone ringing)
- A couple of days.
- Are you sure?
I know it doesn't always seem like it,
but we can waddle through.
The Alaska material was incredible.
(bag rustling)
(leaves rustling)
(dog barking)
(car droning)
(spray can hissing)
- [Mother] Chris?
- Out here.
(spray can hissing)
(birds chirping)
(chattering)
Oh, they didn't.
Not Sherry, not in that.
(lid and bottle thumping)
(cupboard squeaking)
- Christine?
What are you looking for?
- The big funnel.
- Ah (laughs).
(Christine laughing)
(placid music)
(car droning)
(birds chirping)
(door squeaking)
(placid music)
(birds chirping)
(water lapping)
(machine beeping)
(placid music)
- [Nurse] Dr. Parker to OR two, please.
Dr. Parker to OR two.
(machine beeping)
- I swear, he smiled at me.
- Obviously, he thinks you're hysterical.
The doctor said he'll be
here for at least a month.
You'll have plenty of time to get ready.
- Oh, I'm not taking him.
- [Molly] No?
- But trust me, I'll examine whoever does
under a microscope.
- Oh, I guess I just assumed.
- Well, listen, I neglect my
cat, I work 12 hours a day.
I'd make a lousy mother.
- That's kinda sad.
You seem to have such
a connection with him.
(machine beeping)
(baby crying)
- [Nurse] Molly, could you
come here for a second?
(machine beeping)
(babies crying)
- And the other children are?
- Sandy is three and Tommy's nine.
Both were adopted as infants.
- We always wanted three.
- How do you think they'd
respond to a new baby?
- Like any natural family,
it'll take some time, but
the kids'll figure out
that it isn't gonna change much.
- Other than that their mother and I
won't be getting any sleep
for a couple of months,
and they won't be going anywhere,
and Sandy will be giving up her bed,
not to mention her spot in Ellen's lap.
And Tommy will have to share his spot.
- It'll be an adjustment,
they'll handle it.
(phone ringing)
- What would you ask if you were me?
- I guess I'd ask if it would be all right
to come and see him, and I'd say yes.
(phone ringing)
(clock ticking)
- Hello?
When?
I'll be right there.
(phone slamming)
(baby crying)
(machine beeping)
Where's Kevin?
- In micro surgery, in room three.
(babies crying)
(machine beeping)
- [Nurse] Dr. Philips, pick up line two.
There's a phone call for
Dr. Philips on line two.
- [Attorney] Chris, how's he doing?
- He's still in surgery.
The Harrises where here, they
went ran for some coffee.
- They called me, Chris,
they're backing out.
- Well, no, they can't be,
they were right here, they--
- They were heartbroken,
but under the circumstances,
they decided, well...
They wanted a healthy child.
(chattering)
- Oh, well, we'll have
to start all over again.
- Chris.
- Ms. Winslow?
That kid's hell bent to hang around.
He's got a long, slow recovery.
He's lungs are about two
thirds of what they should be,
and I'm not saying
that he's not gonna be
having digestive problems,
but he's one tough customer.
- Can I see him?
- Very briefly.
- [Nurse] Dr. Johnson,
call radiology, Dr.
Johnson, call radiology.
(placid music)
(machine beeping)
- I know he looks frail,
but his vital signs are better than ever.
(placid music)
(machine beeping)
- I admit right now, I'm all he's got.
(placid music)
(machine beeping)
The new parents decided to pass.
(placid music)
(machine beeping)
- Why do you wanna put
him up for adoption?
(placid music)
(machine beeping)
- I'm an executive, I don't
know how to be a mother.
- The minute you walked in here
and leaned over this incubator,
you became Kevin's mother.
(placid music)
(machine beeping)
I saw it, Chris.
(placid music)
(machine beeping)
- Molly thinks I'm your mom, Kev.
(placid music)
(machine beeping)
You're giving me another
chance, aren't you, kiddo?
(placid music)
(machine beeping)
You think you're pretty clever, don't you?
(placid music)
(machine beeping)
He's looking right at me, Molly.
(placid music)
(machine beeping)
He's looking right at me.
- Yes, he really is.
(placid music)
(machine beeping)
- I wanted to breath for him.
(placid music)
(machine beeping)
I wanted to keep his heart beating.
(placid music)
(machine beeping)
I've never been so terrified in my life.
(placid music)
(machine beeping)
(flamingos quaking)
(chattering)
- Hey mom, Grandma's got lunch.
- Where'd you leave Grandma?
- [Kevin] She's at a table, come on!
- Kevin.
(birds chirping)
(chattering)
Grandma's got lunch.
(birds chirping)
(chattering)
- Once a year, she lets me eat a hotdog.
- Oh, who is she?
- Mom.
- [Kevin] That's it, it's Mom.
- Kevin says he's gonna marry Lisa.
- I thought it was Danielle.
- I changed my mind.
- That boy's gonna pay some heavy alimony
if he's not careful.
- What's alimony?
- It's what a rich person pays
you when you get divorced.
- Never mind.
- Except my mom won't even get married.
- Oh, don't start, Kevin.
Well, what do you say, if
after we finish eating,
we all go home and have
some cake and ice cream?
- And open my presents?
- What presents?
(women laughing)
- And tell my story?
- What story?
- How she...
How my mom got me.
- Again?
- Haha, tell the story, Mom.
Tell the story.
- Well, I was in Alaska,
working on a project,
and I was going down the river.
- She was the president of a big company.
- [Christine] I wasn't
the president, Kevin.
- But you were very important.
- Oh, yes, very.
Well, anyway, my beeper went off,
and I came straight back here.
- And you were so surprised,
because you didn't even know
my first mom had a baby.
- That's right, and there you were,
lying wide awake in the nursery.
- And when you saw me,
I was crying so hard,
the windows rattled.
- Oh, who's telling this story?
(women laughing)
- And you had to cover
your ears, right Molly?
- Right, right.
- Wanna get a balloon?
- Sure.
- So, this tycoon from
Topeka we're meeting.
- Odnot.
- Right, Odnot (laughs).
What does he want from you?
- A city.
- A city, in Kansas?
- No, no, in the Saudi Arabian desert.
- A little warm, isn't it?
- Well, we're gonna put a bubble over it
with air conditioning for him.
- You are not.
- (laughs) Yeah.
(placid music)
(traffic droning)
(chattering)
- [Woman] Yeah, it's great, yeah.
- Where did you get that painting?
- Which painting?
- The one in the window,
the man on the horse,
where did you get it?
- Mason.
- On consignment from Colorado.
- Yeah, but where can I find the artist?
- I believe she's deceased.
(placid music)
- What?
- Well the work was consigned
by a family member, hold on.
(placid music)
- Who is it, who painted it?
- Sherry.
(placid music)
- Yes, Sherry Winslow,
born 1962, died 1991.
We have another of her paintings.
Would you care to see it?
- 1991.
- That's what it says here.
- Let's get outta here.
(placid music)
(phone ringing)
- Kevin, have you put your bike away?
- [Kevin] I'm going to.
- Right now.
Hello?
- Hello, my name is Mason Whitney.
I'm looking for Sherry Winslow.
- I'm sorry, Mr. Whitney,
but Sherry passed away several years ago.
- Yeah, I just recently heard that.
I guess I was hoping it wasn't true.
- Well, it's true.
- Is this Mrs. Winslow?
- No, this is Sherry's sister.
How did you know Sherry?
- I, well, we were very close.
It was some time ago.
- I'm sorry.
- So am I.
More than you can imagine.
(placid music)
- When exactly did you know my sister?
- About seven years ago,
probably not too long before she died.
- And how long were you?
- More than enough time
for me to have fallen in love with her.
We were together about six months.
(placid music)
I only wish I knew what happened.
All those years I thought, well...
Hey, thanks again for your time.
- You're welcome, goodbye, Mr. Whitney.
- Goodbye.
(placid music)
(birds chirping)
- This is terrific.
- I just spoke to Kevin's father.
- What?
- You heard me.
- How do you know it was him?
- I know, he said enough, Mason Whitney.
- Oh, after all this time, that bastard.
- You know his name?
- He doesn't know about Kevin.
What did he want?
- Well, he was asking about Sherry.
Mother, how could you be so sure
he doesn't know about Kevin?
- Trust me on this one, Christine.
- No, no, you answer me.
- Open the top drawer over there.
Take out the satin bag.
- What's this?
I thought everything was in storage.
- Well, not everything.
She must have written
it just before she...
- Mason Whitney.
You didn't mail it.
- No.
It was with the things
the hospital gave me.
And it was too painful.
I didn't even go through the bag
until after you brought Kevin home.
And then, I couldn't mail it.
Read it, you'll understand.
(letter rustling)
- "Mason, it's very hard for me to write.
"I've really missed you.
"I kept hoping you'd stop
being afraid of your feelings,
"change your mind and come find me,
"but you didn't.
"Brace yourself for a shock.
"When I asked you to marry me,
I didn't tell you everything.
"I knew I was pregnant,
"but I also knew about your
medieval sense of honor.
"You would have said yes
"and it would have been
for the wrong reason."
How could you not mail, Mother?
- Keep reading.
- "Dumb me, I never planned on dying.
"It's going to be a boy.
"My family will see to it
that he gets a good home,
"but I've always believed
"if you had given marriage a chance,
"we could have made an
incredible life together.
"And you'd have been a wonderful father.
"Now I'm leaving you the option.
"You can let my family know your decision.
"You made me perfectly
happy for a long time.
"Loving you still gives me profound joy.
"Peace."
What in God's name where you thinking?
- I know who Mason Whitney is.
He's a corporate shark.
He's a rich opportunist.
- Oh, please.
- He hurt Sherry.
He never tried to find her.
And she died.
She died trying to bring
that baby into the world.
He did not deserve to know (sobs).
And what about you?
You belonged with Kevin.
By the time I read that letter,
you were already his mother
and you loved him so much, Chris.
(placid music)
It was the right thing for
that little boy and for you.
(placid music)
I believed it then and I believe it now.
- What if you hadn't survived your stroke?
(placid music)
No one would have ever known the truth.
(birds chirping)
(placid music)
(letter rustling)
(mailbox grinding)
(placid music)
(birds chirping)
(traffic droning)
(chattering)
- Sorry, I'm late, Will.
Oh, thanks, I'll see you when I get back.
I hate to make you speed to the airport.
- No problem, picked up your
mail and I packed your bags.
- Thanks a lot.
- Surprise.
- Oh, make me a happy guy,
tell me you're coming with me.
- I know I'd come if I could.
Problem is, I'm indispensable,
just not to you.
- You don't know how lucky you are.
I'll probably take
terrible advantage of you.
- Say the word, I'll take my chances.
Mason and Elizabeth laughing)
- So, how'd you find Will?
- You forget, I'm very resourceful.
- No, no, I don't forget.
(letter rustling)
(traffic droning)
(placid music)
- What is it?
(letter rustling)
(placid music)
(traffic droning)
Mason?
(placid music)
(traffic droning)
(crickets chirping)
(dog barking)
(doorbell ringing)
- Kevin?
- [Kevin] I'll get it.
- See who it is first.
- Okay.
Who is it?
- Mason Whitney.
(door rattling)
(car droning)
Hi, I bet you're Kevin.
- Yeah.
- Nice to meet you.
- I better go get my mom.
- Could you wait a minute, buddy?
- [Kevin] Yeah, but I
can't open to the strain.
- That's okay.
You're a pretty big guy for
seven years old, aren't ya?
- More medium, I think.
- Mm, medium.
- Chris,
Mason Whitney is downstairs.
- What?
Are you sure?
- Yes.
- [Kevin] You look like
you're having a sad feeling.
(placid music)
- Nah.
- Yeah, you are.
(placid music)
- I was just thinking about somebody.
You remind me of her.
She had hair and eyes just like yours.
- I'm supposed to look like
my first mom, she's dead.
- Yeah, I know.
I knew her.
So, where is your dad?
- I don't get one.
- Why not?
- Sometimes you don't.
(placid music)
- [Mason] Would you like a dad?
- [Kevin] Of course.
- [Christine] Can I help you?
(placid music)
- He's her.
His face, it's Sherry's.
- He's Mason.
(placid music)
- Kevin, go upstairs.
- But Mom...
- Right now, please.
- Can I come in?
(placid music)
(door squeaking)
(crickets chirping)
I got the letter yesterday,
post marked, Denver, three days ago.
(crickets chirping)
- Yes, I'm sorry, it
was a miscommunication.
- Well, why now?
Because I called, because you
thought I'd figure it out.
- No, because I only found
the letter three days ago.
Let's leave it at that.
(crickets chirping)
Why did you come here?
- What did you expect me to do?
(crickets chirping)
- Well, not this.
- Well, then why send the letter?
- Because once I found the letter,
I thought it was the
honorable thing to do.
- Look, you adopted
Kevin, you're his mother.
I'm not here to mess with that.
(crickets chirping)
- Thank you.
- But I do wanna provide for him.
- Well, I've been taking
care of him, and we're fine.
- What, by selling Sherry's paintings?
(crickets chirping)
- How do you know about that?
- Well, I saw one in a gallery.
That's how I found you
here in the first place.
(crickets chirping)
I know a lot, Ms. Winslow.
I know you quit a promising
career when Kevin was born.
You freelance at home,
your mother had a stoke 18 months ago.
That's put quite a financial
burden on the family.
You make about--
- I know what I make.
Listen, I'm on a deadline right now.
If I need anything, Mr. Whitney,
I have your address in
Sacramento, I'll drop you a note.
- [Mason] Wait a minute.
(crickets chirping)
(door rattling)
(chattering)
(traffic droning)
Miss Winslow.
- [Christine] I thought
you'd be back in Sacramento.
- This isn't a whim.
(traffic droning)
Kevin's trust account, you
can draw whatever you need
to cover his expenses.
Our local attorney's name and address.
Draw up an itemized list
of any previous expenses.
Some you'll have to estimate.
- No, slow down.
You can't make up for seven
years in five minutes.
- He'll see to it that you're
reimbursed with interest.
- I told you, I don't want your money.
- And I'd like to set up
some regular schedules
to see Kevin.
- What, wait a minute?
- Don't you want your
son to have a father?
- Well, that's a very dramatic word.
I love the way it catches in your throat.
And biology aside, you're
not Kevin's father.
He can't imagine you, he doesn't
even know that you exist.
(traffic droning)
- Sherry loved me, you read the letter.
- She wasn't the greatest judge of men.
From what I can gather,
you didn't exactly move
heaven and earth to find her,
did you?
- I didn't know there was a baby.
She knew I didn't want children.
- Then I don't get it,
what are you doing here?
- I don't see why you're so threatened.
- You don't?
- No, and after this week,
I'm gonna stay here in Denver, and--
- I don't think that
Kevin would like that.
In fact, I know that
I definitely wouldn't.
- I'm growing less concerned
with what you thing, Ms. Winslow.
- Well, I might be a tad more open to this
if I thought that you at least
cared about how Kevin feels.
- Sherry loved you,
and I'm trying very hard to respect that.
(traffic droning)
Now, I'm not suggesting
that Kevin's not yours,
but the fact remains, he's also mine.
- Well, I don't happen to see it that way.
- I'd like to see him
this Saturday morning.
(traffic droning)
I'll limit my preliminary
visits to two hours once a week.
- I guess I'm supposed to
be shaking in my boots.
- No, you're supposed to be fair.
- Well, you are you to
dictate to me what's fair?
- You have my number.
- Oh, boy, do I ever.
(traffic droning)
(siren ringing)
So, he shows up barking orders
and you're telling me to cooperate?
- I'm telling you, if you don't,
my experience has taught me
that he'll take you to court.
He's a powerful man.
Is there any doubt in your
mind that he's Kevin's father?
- No.
- Well, they can demand a lot
more than two hours a week,
and he may very well get it.
Your mother deliberately withheld a letter
that not only established his paternity,
but clearly states that
Sherry wanted Mason Whitney
to raise Kevin.
- No, she gave him an option,
that's all.
- Suppose his lawyers convince the court
that you purposely did
not send that letter?
Your adoption is permanent,
but that doesn't mean Mason
can't make a hell of a case
for joint custody.
- Joint custody, can he get that?
- Look, just don't let it get that far.
- All right, he wants his
visit, he gets his visit.
But I'm going with him.
- I'll see what I can do.
(crickets chirping)
(milk sloshing)
- We're going to the part tomorrow.
- With Molly and Zoe?
- Not this time.
Mason's coming with us.
(placid music)
(crickets chirping)
You remember him?
(placid music)
(crickets chirping)
- Yeah, that's kinda weird, though.
(placid music)
(crickets chirping)
- Why's that?
- You hated him.
- Well, no, I didn't.
- He just surprised your mother, Kevin.
(placid music)
(crickets chirping)
- Then how come we're going?
Is this a date or something?
(placid music)
(crickets chirping)
- Oh, no, no.
(placid music)
(crickets chirping)
- Then how come?
(placid music)
(crickets chirping)
- He wants to spend some time with you,
get to know you better.
(placid music)
(crickets chirping)
Mason Whitney's your father, Kevin.
(placid music)
(crickets chirping)
- Really?
(placid music)
(crickets chirping)
- Really.
- Now I know why he was almost crying.
He was so glad to see me.
(placid music)
(crickets chirping)
- That's right.
- I never even knew I had a dad.
- Oh, he was in Sacramento.
- You still coulda told me.
(placid music)
(crickets chirping)
- I didn't know where he was.
- [Kevin] Oh, and he's
taking me to the park?
- That's right.
(placid music)
(crickets chirping)
- Does he know I'm not a baby
and I don't go on swings and stuff?
(placid music)
(crickets chirping)
- You can tell him that yourself.
- Cool.
(placid music)
(crickets chirping)
He was nice.
(placid music)
(crickets chirping)
Wow, a dad.
(placid music)
(crickets chirping)
So, it was a mistake?
- Yup, you see,
Sherry didn't tell me she
was gonna have a baby.
- Why not?
- Well, I don't know, maybe
she thought I'd be mad?
- Are you?
- No, when I heard about it,
I went straight to the airport,
and they said, "We don't have
a plane to Denver tonight."
And I said, "Well, you
better find me one."
- And what they find?
- They found a 400 seater.
I was the only one on
it, except for the pilot.
He called it the Kevin Special.
- No way.
- Honest.
This okay?
(chattering)
- Fine.
- This is a Stegosaurus.
- Yeah, what's this?
- Brachiosaurus.
- Right.
(chattering)
- Mom, look!
- [Christine] Watch
out, Kevin, be careful.
- They're plastic.
(chattering)
- Kevin doesn't play with war toys.
- Oh, give me a break.
- You think that's funny?
- No, I think it's very
politically correct.
(birds chirping)
- Why don't you and I have
this conversations a little later?
(birds chirping)
Kevin, let's go.
(chattering)
(car droning)
(car door rattling)
- [Mason] Kevin.
Here, these are for you.
- Sorry, Kevin, he can't accept them.
(birds chirping)
- Why don't you let
Kevin speak for himself?
(birds chirping)
- Kevin, go inside.
(placid music)
- I'm sorry, son.
I wanted you to have a nice day.
(placid music)
(birds chirping)
- I had a nice day.
(placid music)
(birds chirping)
- Kevin.
(placid music)
(birds chirping)
It's all right to say thank you.
(placid music)
(birds chirping)
- Thanks, thanks a lot.
(placid music)
(birds chirping)
- A little irrational, don't you think?
They're just toys.
- No, there's no such thing as just.
Everything you do,
everything you say has
an impact on a child.
- Well, so I've heard.
- Well, don't you patronize
me, you were way out of line.
I can't just allow some stranger
to show up and screw up his values.
- If I'm a stranger to that boy,
it's because you and your family conspired
to make it that way.
You deliberately hid him from me.
Then, when I tried to reach out,
you made it your personal
mission to interfere.
- No wonder Sherry never told
you that she was pregnant.
- You know what?
I'm gonna let the legal system
decide how to deal with this.
- Are you threatening me?
- I don't threaten, lady.
I'm gonna drag you through
every court in this country.
I'll prove you denied my
right to be his father,
and I'll get custody,
believe me, I'll get custody.
(birds chirping)
(dog barking)
- Come on, let's play.
(feet stomping)
(children laughing)
- So, what are you gonna do?
- [Zoe] Kick here, kick it to me.
- Nothing.
I called his room and he checked out.
He'd gone back to Sacramento.
This is Mason's fad of the month.
He'll get tired of wanting to play daddy
and move on to something else.
- You don't think he's serious.
- No, I think he just
wants to brag about his son
with his friends at the racket club.
- How do you know that?
- Well, according to "Fortune Magazine",
Mason Whitney is worth millions.
Everything is about power
and ego with those guys.
- Excuse me.
(chattering)
Christine Winslow?
- [Christine] That's right.
- I need you to sign this, please?
- [Christine] Oh, what is it?
- It's a court order, Ma'am.
(birds chirping)
(placid music)
- "Walter Mason Whitney
shall be entitled to no less
"than two unsupervised visits
with Kevin William Winslow,
"pending full hearing
of paternity and custody
"of above mentioned child
within 10 business days."
- Custody?
(placid music)
(birds chirping)
- Oh, what did I do?
(placid music)
(birds chirping)
- I don't see why I have to go.
- So you can give Mason a chance.
- I already did.
- And you had a good time.
- But you were with me.
- Do you think I'd let him take you
if I didn't think he could
take good care of you?
- No.
- Okay, then.
(doorbell ringing)
Comb your hair.
- I already did.
(birds chirping)
(dog barking)
- Did you have to get a court order?
(birds chirping)
- Apparently so.
- Well, he doesn't wanna go.
(birds chirping)
- He'll be fine.
- You can't force him to love you.
He doesn't want this.
- He's never had it, how would he know?
(birds chirping)
Hiya, pal.
- Hi.
(birds chirping)
- Well, give me five.
Go and have a good time, go on.
(birds chirping)
(dog barking)
- Do you like the Rockies, Kevin?
- No kidding.
- Walkers on a street.
- I know.
- He'll be back before bedtime.
- I don't have to be, do I, Mom?
(birds chirping)
- Just let me know.
- Here.
(birds chirping)
- You know, you don't have to
give me presents every time.
I mean, it can get expensive.
- Oh.
(birds chirping)
(door slamming)
(placid music)
(birds chirping)
(crickets chirping)
(placid music)
- [Kevin] Zoe's lucky, you know?
- Why is that?
(crickets chirping)
(placid music)
- She has her mom and her dad right there.
- Well, there are all
kinds of families, Kevin.
- I know, but isn't there
anyone you wanna marry?
- Nobody that I love enough.
(crickets chirping)
(placid music)
- Maybe you're too picky.
(crickets chirping)
(placid music)
- Maybe.
(crickets chirping)
(placid music)
We're pretty terrific, aren't we?
- Yeah.
Night.
- Good night.
Love you.
- Love you too.
(crickets chirping)
(placid music)
(car droning)
(feet stomping)
(chattering)
(door squeaking)
- This is a travesty!
- Well, if you could
have a sane conversation.
- [Man] Damn it, can you
just wait until we get home.
- I haven't had them for
Christmas in three years.
- And the one time you did have them,
Robby came home with a 103 degrees fever.
- [Judge] Can you please
instruct your client?
- I am not his client, not
anymore, not after this.
How much are you paying him?
- I could get a restraining
order, would you like that?
- They're my children!
Damn you.
(feet stomping)
- (sighs) I am sorry.
(feet clattering)
You must be Kevin.
My, don't you look dapper?
- It was Teddy's, he's bigger
than me, so I get to keep it.
- Lucky you.
I've asked you all to come here
today without your lawyers.
I'm hoping we can resolve
this quickly without acrimony.
Why don't you come in?
(phone ringing)
- By myself?
- Yeah, your mom and
dad can wait right here.
You and I have a lot to talk about.
(phone ringing)
(chattering)
(feet clattering)
(doors slamming)
(chattering)
- Kevin means everything
in the world to me.
- I understand that.
- You know he was premature?
Did you know he wasn't expected to live?
- Yes.
- Six surgeries in the first year.
You didn't even want a healthy child.
I can't imagine you'd
have wanted a sick one.
- Well, I can see I've
failed your character test
even before I had a chance to take it.
I loved Sherry, but I
was pushing my business.
I didn't think I could give a family
the time or attention that they deserved.
But I want Kevin to
understand that I'm here,
whether he likes me or not.
And if it takes him 20 years to adjust,
he's gonna know he's got
a father who gives a damn.
(phone ringing)
Hold on a sec.
You know, from what I understand,
before Kevin landed in your lap,
you were no stranger to
cellphones and beepers.
And you never made a
commitment to anybody.
Yeah?
- They'll be out in a minute, Kevin.
So, you're each seeking custody.
- [Christine] Yes.
- Yes.
- Well, there's usually two
options in a case like this.
I could give one of you the school year,
the other vacations.
Or I could rule in favor
of six months here with you, Ms. Winslow,
and six months in
California with you, Sir.
- That isn't acceptable at all.
Well, Kevin shouldn't be uprooted
and dragged back and forth.
- No one's asked for Kevin
to be dragged anywhere.
I'm his father,
his mother wanted him to
be with me all the time.
You can see for yourself in her letter.
- I've read the letter, Mr. Whitney.
You have a very strong case.
Frankly, so does Ms. Winslow.
I'm trying to play Solomon here.
Kevin isn't at all
interested in split custody,
and I'm inclined to agree with him.
He knows exactly how
he'd like to settle this.
- He does?
- He wants you to get married.
- Married?
- He even went so far as to ask
if I could throw you in jail,
Mr. Whitney, if you refused.
- You mean he actually thinks
that we should live together?
- No, he was quite clear.
He said married.
- Well, I hope you told
him how ludicrous that was.
- Trust me, your Honor, Ma'am,
we're not really romantically involved.
- I am aware of that, Mr. Whitney,
but it wasn't so long
ago that men and women
took a common sense approach to marriage.
It was a legal and spiritual friendship.
Couples didn't feel they had
to be Romeo and Juliette,
just two people committed
to making a secure life
for each other and their children.
- Well, we've come a long way since then.
- Oh, we certainly have.
Nowadays, you people
are running to the altar
with stars in your eyes,
expecting violins for
the rest of your lives.
And when the music stops,
you turn on each other,
my God, do you turn on each other.
I cannot order you to do such a thing.
But at least you'd have
realistic expectations.
You could give a nice
little boy a happy home.
Marriages have been based
on a lot less than that.
- We don't even live in the same city.
- I mentioned that.
He seems to think
his mother's freelance
advertising business
wouldn't suffer from being in Sacramento.
He mentioned the internet,
email, fax machine.
(Christine laughing)
- I guess I just don't
this is funny (laughs).
- Your Honor, I would
give up my life for Kevin,
but this is completely ridiculous.
- And I would give up every
cent I've ever made for him.
But she's right.
- Well, if you'd give up your life
and you'd give up your fortune,
what's so hard about getting married?
Look, folks, I am due in
court in about two minutes.
I think you should give Kevin's notion
some serious consideration.
He sees this as the best
of all possible worlds.
And I am going to be making my decision
before we leave this room today.
(placid music)
One of you could end up a very big loser.
(car droning)
- [Christine] Well, she's not
gonna go for joint custody.
- I know.
- I mean, even living together, even then.
- I wouldn't do that.
You know, that would be like lying,
send him all the wrong messages.
- Oh, please, spare me the family values.
- Well, this whole thing's absurd.
- Thanks a lot.
- You're not so sure you're
gonna win this, are ya?
- I'll appeal 'til I do.
You're not so sure you're
gonna win either, are you?
- Well, I'll match ya,
appeal for appeal.
- Good,
then I'll meet you in court.
- Fine.
- I don't know (clears throat).
Do you think we could live under one roof
if we had separate
quarters, I mean, you know,
maybe we could make some
kind of an arrangement?
- We couldn't even make
it through one afternoon
in the park.
- Yeah, you're right, yeah.
Forget that.
I mean, the trick is is to come
up with something very clear
in the beginning so we know
what to expect from each other.
Like the Judge said.
- You're not seriously considering--
- Well, no, no, no, of course not,
but you gotta admit, it is logical.
I mean, my house is big.
You can have complete
privacy, a suite, really.
There's a sitting room,
a bedroom, an office.
We'd never have to see each other.
And there's a great room for Kevin,
and the yard is wonderful.
This way, nobody loses.
- I'd never take your money.
- No, I'd only help with Kevin.
- Help, that's the operative word.
- Absolutely, I'll help.
- And I'd want a prenuptial agreement.
- Why?
You don't have anything (laughs).
- Well, I'd wanna be sure
that you didn't think
that I wanted anything, either.
- Oh.
- I suppose it would be best for him,
and that's the bottom line, isn't it?
- Mm-hm, yup.
- I mean, if we could make this work,
he'd have a real family.
- And if we couldn't
make it work, who could?
We're both professionals,
we're highly motivated,
we're successful negotiators,
and like the Judge said,
for Kevin, hey, it's
the best of all worlds.
(placid music)
- I just...
I just don't know if I could do this.
(placid music)
- Are you out of your mind?
- I hope not.
- You can't make a decision
like this in five minutes.
- It wasn't five minutes,
it was more like 20.
(birds chirping)
What if he won't go through with it?
- Then that would mean he
has a little more sense
than you do.
- Mother, you're just making things worse.
You think I know if I'm
doing the right thing?
Well, I don't, so why can't
you be more supportive?
- [Mother] Oh my god.
- What's going on?
- I'm getting married.
- What?
- You heard me, and don't
try to change my mind.
- [Molly] To him?
- Yes.
- My God.
- That's what I said.
- But you're not in love with him.
- Well, that has nothing to do with it.
How do I look?
- You look like you could be making
the biggest mistake of your life.
- Thanks a lot.
Well, are you coming?
(clock ticking)
(placid music)
- May I have the ring, please?
(birds chirping)
With the power vested in me
by the state of Colorado,
I now pronounce you husband,
and wife, and child.
(placid music)
Believe me when I say, I think
you're doing the right thing.
(placid music)
(birds chirping)
- Thank you.
(placid music)
(birds chirping)
- Good idea, Kevin.
- Yeah, it is.
(placid music)
(birds chirping)
Now, you may kiss the bride.
(placid music)
(birds chirping)
- Well.
(placid music)
(birds chirping)
(traffic droning)
(thunder droning)
- A marriage of convenience?
(laughs) Who are you, the czar of Russia?
- I know it sounds weird.
- Weird?
No, weird is not the
word that comes to mind.
I mean, one minute,
you're gonna steamroll her
with the legal system, and the
next you're married to her.
- Well, it's not gonna change anything.
I mean, you and I have
an adult relationship.
And Chris and I have agreed we can date
as long as we don't bring anybody home.
(rain splattering)
- Mason, do you have any
idea how outlandish this is?
(rain splattering)
- You know, I guess it does, but...
- I mean, could you not
have just moved in together?
(rain splattering)
- Well, that wasn't
the honest thing to do.
I think being married matters to kids.
(rain splattering)
- Right.
Then let me get this straight.
You and I are supposed to continue to date
while everyone knows that you
have a wife and child at home.
- You never talked about being married.
You like your independence.
I'm not sure I understand
why you're so upset.
I travel, you travel, we--
- We play by your rules.
We always have.
- Well, I'm sorry, Elizabeth.
(rain splattering)
(traffic droning)
- We have the Ascot Ball coming up.
- Yeah.
- We're still on the
invitations as co-chairs,
and everyone expects us
to be there together.
After that, I don't wanna see you again,
unless it's in a big
crowd in broad daylight.
Now, if you'll excuse me.
(rain splattering)
(thunder droning)
(door slamming)
(placid music)
(birds chirping)
(car droning)
- Do they let you ride your bike here?
(placid music)
(birds chirping)
- Sure.
(placid music)
(birds chirping)
- Hey, Mom, there's the moving truck.
They're here before us.
(placid music)
(car droning)
(car door slamming)
(placid music)
(birds chirping)
It's a castle.
(placid music)
(birds chirping)
I didn't know my dad was so rich.
I mean, it's too big.
- Hey, you have all your own things.
I'll make your room just
the way you want it.
Exactly like at home.
(placid music)
(birds chirping)
(door squeaking)
- Hello, you made good
time, hey Kevin, I'm Will.
- Hi.
- Come on in, like they
say, home sweet home.
(birds chirping)
Please take the bags to the rooms, please.
- So, I lied, it's not exactly like home.
- You made it.
(birds chirping)
- [Kevin] Hey, Dad.
- How was the trip?
- It was fine.
- Will, why don't you take
Kevin outside to meet Twister?
- Who's Twister?
- You'll see.
- Come on.
(birds chirping)
(pony snorting)
- [Kevin] Oh, wow, a pony.
(birds chirping)
- I brought you something, too.
- What for?
- Well, just to say welcome, I guess.
(package rustling)
It's Ojibwe.
- I know.
- The store said it was
an authentic reproduction.
Isn't that an oxymoron?
(birds chirping)
- Still, it's very thoughtful of you.
- Yeah, well, that's me.
- Listen, about the pony--
- Yeah, yeah,
he loves it, doesn't he?
I filled out an
application at Silver Oaks.
I don't think there'd be a
problem for him to get in.
(birds chirping)
- Kevin doesn't go to a private school.
- Well, I know, but not in Denver.
It's different here, it's
overcrowded, understaffed.
- No.
- We don't have a choice in this city.
- I have a choice, he
stays in public school.
I volunteer, you volunteer.
That why his class won't
be so understaffed.
The reason the schools
are in such bad shape
is because parents like us take
our kids out, I won't do it.
- That's charming.
This is about Kevin's education
and you're busy saving
the damned school system.
(birds chirping)
We'll discuss this later.
- Oh, we will?
I don't think so.
- I'm going to Taiwan on the 20th.
Maybe we can have a rational
conversation when I get back.
- I presume you'll stay in
touch while you're in Taiwan.
I mean, if you're to be
a real part of his life,
he'll need more than a
few hours with you a week.
- Give me a little credit.
- I did, but I didn't
think I'd need to tell you
not to buy him a pony.
Kevin is not spoiled, he does choirs,
he saves up for special things,
and I want it to stay that way.
- Maybe I ought to go upstairs
and come back down again.
- Not a bad idea.
(placid music)
(dog barking)
(birds chirping)
- Hey, good morning, you find everything?
- We did, thank you.
- Yeah, one thing, though.
- Your mom doesn't let
you have sugar cereal.
- [Kevin] How'd you know that?
- Ah, just a lucky guess.
Hey, what would you like to do today?
I'm not going into the
office 'til after lunch.
We can do anything you
wanna do in Sacramento.
Anything you want, what do you say?
- I say roller blading.
- What?
- Kevin, your father doesn't
know how to roller blade.
- No, I can do it, I'm a quick study.
- Can mom come too?
She's a great roller blader.
- Yeah, sure.
- I think he'd prefer to have a guys' day.
- No, he wouldn't.
- No, it's cool.
- Oh, just for an hour.
(cereal crunching)
(placid music)
(chattering)
- Is he having fun yet?
- Oh, you're not buckled up right.
(placid music)
(chattering)
Have you ever skated?
- Skated, yeah, back in '68.
(placid music)
(chattering)
- You have your wrist guards
on the wrong way around.
- Mm?
Oh.
(placid music)
(Velcro ripping)
(chattering)
Thanks.
(placid music)
(chattering)
- You're a good sport,
Mason, I'll give you that.
(Mason chuckling)
But I'll deny it if you ever
tell anyone I complimented you.
- I wouldn't dare.
(placid music)
(chattering)
- Well, let's get you up, nice and easy.
(placid music)
(chattering)
Easy.
(placid music)
(chattering)
Now, get your balance, push
off with your back foot,
lean forward.
That's it, keep going.
- [Kevin] Hey, Dad!
- Hey.
(placid music)
- Like this.
(roller blades grinding)
- Oh, I get it.
- Kevin, stay where I can see you!
(placid music)
(birds chirping)
- You go ahead, I'll catch up.
(placid music)
(chattering)
- You sure?
- Yeah.
(placid music)
(chattering)
Enjoy yourself.
(placid music)
(chattering)
I am.
(placid music)
(chattering)
(crickets chirping)
You know what?
- What?
(placid music)
- I'm really glad you're here.
- Me too.
Aren't you, Mom?
- Aren't I what?
- Glad we're here.
- I am if you are.
(placid music)
(crickets chirping)
- Night, buddy.
(placid music)
(crickets chirping)
- Yeah, I like it when
you call me that, too.
Buddy.
(placid music)
(crickets chirping)
He made me floss.
(placid music)
(crickets chirping)
I didn't tell him I hate to.
- Good for you.
(placid music)
(crickets chirping)
- He's a great kid.
(placid music)
- I think so.
- You've done a terrific job.
- [Christine] Thank you.
- I only hope I don't screw it up.
- Hey, you got him to floss,
it's more than I could do (laughs).
(placid music)
- You wanna watch a movie sometime?
I mean, after he's in bed.
(placid music)
I got a lotta tapes.
- I don't know.
(placid music)
- Yeah, probably a bad idea.
- Well, I didn't say that.
- Yeah, but you're probably thinking it.
(placid music)
And you're probably right.
(feet thumping)
(placid music)
- Tell Laurie I expect to
have to copy to him by Friday.
I'll load in the specs and
overnight the elements.
There won't be any lag time.
Well, tell him not to
have such long lunches.
I'll speak to you later.
(phone slamming)
(dog barking)
(car droning)
(placid music)
- Oh my God.
- Hi, Grandma.
- Oh, hi sweetheart.
Here, give me a hug, how are you?
- [Kevin] Good.
- Well, this is amazing.
(placid music)
Are you having fun?
- Yeah.
(placid music)
(car droning)
(car door slamming)
(placid music)
Robbie.
- Hey, Kev.
- [Kevin] I wanna show
my dad your gerbils.
- [Robbie] Yeah, sure.
(chattering)
- That one's Oscar.
Guess what the other one's name is.
(chattering)
- Couldn't be Felix?
- No, it's Mayer.
(children laughing)
Get it?
- I get it.
- Oscar Mayer.
- Uh-huh.
(school bell ringing)
- [Robby] We've gotta go.
- See you inside.
(chattering)
- Well, you've gotta go, buddy.
- Don't kiss me, okay?
(chattering)
- I wouldn't do that.
So, five me.
(chattering)
All right, you have a good day, huh?
- [Kevin] See ya.
- See ya.
(chattering)
- So far 200 have sent
checks and reservations,
and another 40 have just sent checks.
- All I know is the hotel
needs a final figure
a couple of days before.
- So, maybe we ought to start
doing phone follow ups
tomorrow instead of Thursday.
- Mm-hm.
- Oh,
I almost forget.
Jerry Erwin from Silver Oaks called
and they were trying to feel out
how much they could rely
on from you this year.
- Maybe nothing.
- Why not?
- Well, Kevin's not going to Silver Oaks.
- But it's the best school in the city.
- Yeah, well, Kevin's a
different kind of kid.
Chris thinks that he'll
never be into cotillion
and field hockey, or whatever
the hell they do there.
- She doesn't?
So, what's the alternative?
- Public school.
- You're really getting
off on this, aren't you?
- Maybe.
- I miss you.
You know, I've thought a
lot about what you said,
and I think I would like to try
this dating thing for a while.
No reason you can't stay
over every so often.
- I wouldn't do that, Elizabeth.
Listen, it's one thing when I
have to go away on business.
It's another for Kevin
to ask me where I've been
when I can't tell him the truth.
(chattering)
- You know,
I plan to dazzle you with
fancy footwork at the ball.
(chattering)
And more.
(placid music)
(papers rustling)
- Hi, it's Chris.
(placid music)
- Hi, come on in.
- Mozart?
- Yeah,
it keeps me centered.
(placid music)
- You have to eat.
It wasn't so bad, sometimes
I even amaze myself.
(placid music)
- Oh, and modest too, huh?
Thanks.
(placid music)
- It is a little strange
eating dinner downstairs,
knowing that you're up
here all by yourself.
(placid music)
Is that a problem for you?
- Well, I wasn't gonna say anything,
but it does feel a little awkward.
(placid music)
I was wondering if you'd mind
if Kevin came up here and
eat with me once in a while.
(placid music)
- Well, I'd bet he'd prefer it
if you came downstairs with us.
(placid music)
- I think that feels just
a little too hubby wifey,
don't you?
Kinda like watching a movie together.
(placid music)
- Touch,
Well, have a nice trip.
- Thanks, oh, Chris.
(placid music)
I'm gonna call him from Taiwan every day.
Thanks.
(placid music)
- Mm.
- Ugh, so when are you coming back?
- Oh, next Saturday.
But you save Sunday for me, will ya?
- Okay.
Maybe you and me and mom can
go to the movies or something.
- The movies?
Yeah, yeah, maybe.
(zipper hissing)
- What's an Ascot Ball?
- Ascot Ball, well, it's a
very big party with dancing.
(bag thumping)
- Like in Cinderella?
- Yeah, but there's not a
lotta princes hanging out.
I gotta run, pal.
I'll call ya tomorrow, okay?
(placid music)
- Almost bed time.
- Wanna read Jumanji again?
- That sounds good.
(placid music)
What's this?
- Your invitation to
the Ball Saturday night.
(placid music)
- Well, where did you get this?
- From Dad, it's for you.
(placid music)
I'll go get Jumanji.
- Oh, Mason would be mortified
if he knew you were gonna
show up in a used gown.
- [Christine] They're not used,
they're previously driven.
- Christine, this is not a joke.
- Look, I haven't bought an evening gown
since Regan was in the White House.
This is what I can afford.
- Well, passable.
But just barely.
(crickets chirping)
- I know.
- Something with a little more.
- Panache, you're right.
(placid music)
(crickets chirping)
- Chris?
(placid music)
(crickets chirping)
You do want to do, don't you?
(placid music)
(crickets chirping)
- Yes, very much.
(placid music)
(crickets chirping)
- Wow, you look beautiful.
- Thanks.
(placid music)
- Well, if your dad
doesn't come pretty soon,
I may have to go to the party with you.
- Nah.
(placid music)
(phone ringing)
- Hello?
(crickets chirping)
Oh, yes, Mason, of course she's here.
She's dressing.
- [Mason] Well, don't bother
her, my plane was late.
I'm going straight to the hotel.
- All right, I'll tell her.
- [Mason] Thanks.
- Mason, have a lovely evening.
- [Mason] I will, good night.
- Good night.
(crickets chirping)
Chris?
Mason called, his plane just got in.
He's going right to the ball.
You'll have to meet him there.
- Oh, finally, I was beginning to wonder.
- Oh, you look so beautiful.
(placid music)
(crickets chirping)
- Really?
(placid music)
(crickets chirping)
- I already told her, she
doesn't believe me either.
(placid music)
(women laughing)
(car droning)
(placid music)
- Good evening.
- Can you direct me to the ballroom?
- Second level, but the Ascot
Ball is there this evening.
- I know.
(heels clicking)
(chattering)
(door slamming)
(car droning)
(placid music)
(chattering)
- May I help you?
- I'm meeting my husband.
- May I see your invitation?
- Oh, I didn't bring it.
(placid music)
- Perhaps you have the wrong
hotel or the wrong room.
May I have your name?
- Whitney, Mason Whitney.
(placid music)
(chattering)
- Are you Ms. Fennaway?
- No, I'm Mrs. Whitney.
(placid music)
(chattering)
Excuse me, I'll find him myself.
(placid music)
(chattering)
- My, I don't know who that is,
but I've been dying to
turn up at this wake
dressed like that for years.
- A woman with a death wish.
(placid music)
Chris?
- [Elizabeth] What?
(placid music)
- It's Chris.
(chattering)
- It can't be.
- It is.
(placid music)
(chattering)
Excuse me.
(placid music)
(chattering)
- [Woman] She's in red.
(placid music)
(chattering)
- Some dress code you forgot to mention?
Ascot, "My Fair Lady".
Oh, I get it now, but it's a little late.
- What are you doing here?
- What do you mean?
- Well, it's not a complex question.
- Kevin gave me the invitation,
he said it was from you.
- He what?
- Well, after you left for Taiwan...
(placid music)
(chattering)
- Oh, oh, well, hi.
- Hi.
- Christine, I'm Elizabeth.
I've been hoping to meet you.
(placid music)
(chattering)
- Oh, oh, I'm sorry.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
(placid music)
(chattering)
- Kevin, you know, he must have...
- Hurry up, you might catch her
before she loses her glass slipper.
(placid music)
(chattering)
(heels clicking)
(placid music)
- [Christine] Would
you get my car, please?
- Right away.
(placid music)
- [Mason] Chris?
I'm sorry,
that's was unconscionably rude of me.
(placid music)
- No, it's not your fault.
- I think Kevin is determined
to get us together.
(placid music)
- Well he wouldn't do it on purpose.
- Oh, yes, he would.
(placid music)
- You think he...
I wondered why you never
asked me before you left.
(placid music)
- Our son has very good instincts.
Chris, I'd like it very
much if you'd stay.
(placid music)
- Please don't be gallant.
- I'm not,
I'm being honest.
(placid music)
- A little lady in red.
- The lady in red is very beautiful.
(placid music)
She is also my wife.
(placid jazz music)
(chattering)
- Does this mean you'll
teach me how to roller blade?
(placid jazz music)
(chattering)
Mm?
(Christine giggling)
(placid jazz music)
(chattering)
- Let's get outta here.
- Oh, yeah.
(placid jazz music)
(chattering)
- But I've gotta go, you know.
- Go ahead.
- Meet me at the door,
don't get lost, now.
(placid jazz music)
(chattering)
Hi.
- Hi.
- I um...
- Don't say anything.
I saw you dancing, it's okay.
(placid jazz music)
(chattering)
- It's not okay.
- (chuckles) Mason,
we've tried this for a long time.
It's never been right for you.
(placid jazz music)
(chattering)
- You're being very noble.
- (chuckles) Well...
(placid jazz music)
(chattering)
It's always been a long shot.
(placid jazz music)
(chattering)
Go take your wife home.
She's a knockout.
(placid jazz music)
(chattering)
(placid music)
(crickets chirping)
(door slamming)
(placid music)
- You want a drink?
- No.
(placid music)
(birds chirping)
Mason.
- My shirt?
It fits.
(placid music)
(birds chirping)
- It does.
(placid music)
(birds chirping)
It all does.
(placid music)
(birds chirping)
I'm not a substitute for Sherry, am I?
- I loved her.
(birds chirping)
But I shied away from
commitment all my life.
(birds chirping)
- Me too, until Kevin.
- No way this is a romantic interlude.
(birds chirping)
It's way past that.
(placid music)
- I'm willing.
- To love me?
(birds chirping)
(placid music)
- I already do.
(birds chirping)
But my life isn't charity balls
and chauffeured limousines.
- Well, you've gotta
give the Porsche a try.
(placid music)
(birds chirping)
- (laughs) And you?
(placid music)
(birds chirping)
- I think I fell for you way back
when you vetoed the plastic sword.
You were so serious.
(placid music)
(birds chirping)
I'm willing, too, Chris.
(placid music)
(birds chirping)
I want you to be my wife.
(placid music)
(birds chirping)
- Because?
(placid music)
(birds chirping)
- Because I love you very much.
(placid music)
(birds chirping)
(water rushing)
(placid music)
- How much further?
- [Christine] Two miles.
- Two miles.
(water rushing)
(placid music)
- There's a local saying
that if a young boy makes it
to the church of the elders,
he'll return some day
with the one he loves.
(water rushing)
(placid music)
(Multicom jingle)