Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
[eerie music]
Based on a true story
Stephen, only use
weapons for good.
Okay?
Only good.
Now, just as I taught you.
Stand up straight.
And draw.
[eerie music]
Where are you, guys?
I got you.
[thunder rumbling]
[wind howling]
[alarm beeping]
[Emily] Stephen, come on.
[Randy] Something smells good.
Good morning.
[Randy] Morning.
How are you?
Mm, much better now.
Alexa, you are not going
to school dressed like that.
- Dad.
- Dad what?
Do what Emily,
what your mom said.
Cover yourself up.
- Thank you.
- Really?
You're going there.
I'm the head cheerleader.
I'm supposed to look like this.
[Randy] Cover up.
Not a happy daughter.
[Randy] I know honey, I know.
[Emily] Here's your coffee.
Thank you, baby.
Hi.
[Michelle] Morning.
Morning.
Oh, guessing that outfit won't
make it past the front gate.
Why can't you dress normally?
What's wrong with
the way I'm dressed?
Jesus.
Stephen, please don't take
the Lord's name in vain.
Look, if you come dressed to
football practice like that,
you'll be the laughing stock.
And what's with the
black nail polish?
Who wears that to play football?
He could be an Oakland Raider.
Please don't
encourage him, please.
You know, I don't
even like football.
It's stupid.
Besides I'm tired of having
my ass slapped all day
by a bunch of grunting
jocks in tights.
He does have a
point there, honey.
Yeah.
I just don't wanna see
my son dressed up like...
Like a what?
You know you're not my real dad,
so I don't know why you care
about how I'm dressed or what...
God dammit, I'm trying
to get you to focus.
Nice.
You're gonna be late for work
and you two will
be late for school.
So let's all move it out, okay?
That's enough, honey.
Yep.
I will see you at
practice today.
We have a big game on Friday.
[ominous music]
Alexa, be in the car.
Have a good day.
[Randy] Thank you baby.
Stephen, move it.
Now.
[soft music]
Honestly.
[eerie music]
[bell chiming]
[kids chattering]
[Carol] Alexa.
Alexa.
Yes?
Don't forget to tell the girls
that practice is 30 minutes
earlier today, okay?
And don't be late.
All right, I won't.
I'll tell them.
See you.
[eerie music]
[kids chattering]
Bye.
Stop it, you idiot.
[Ben] No one here to stop me.
[Alexa] Really?
Later.
Hey, don't.
Let it go.
Come on, let it go.
[bell ringing]
[eerie music]
[kids chattering]
[Girl] Did you get the
homework that's due today?
Hey, what are you
wearing to practice today?
A tutu?
[soft music]
[kids chattering]
[demon growling]
Stephen O'Connor.
[ruler whipping]
What in the Lord's name do
you think you're wearing?
How dare you enter
these sacred grounds
wearing such evil clothes?
My last name is Tade.
It is not O'Connor.
He's like the
devil, Sister Clare.
Yeah, gay devil.
Quiet, all of you.
You will go to confession
for the entire second period
and this will not go unpunished.
[eerie music]
[Father DuMal] I'm
sorry I'm late to class.
Yes, you are.
Class is almost over.
Let's turn to chapter 12.
And get started.
You're getting
to know the inside
of this office pretty
well, aren't ya?
Your Grandpa Joe, we're going
to honor in a couple of days,
has been an integral
part of this church
for more than 30 years.
You are part of his family now.
He looks on you like one
of his true granddaughters.
How do you think he'd feel
about what just went on outside?
[bright music]
Altering our yes,
not very fashionable
or glamorous school uniform
and sashaying across the grass
for the entertainment
of our male students
sets the wrong example.
I know.
I want ya to have fun, Alexa,
but I need you to
respect yourself.
Otherwise no one's
gonna respect ya.
You want the boys to
treat ya properly,
they're never gonna
treat ya properly
if you draw them
into temptation.
[bright music]
I'm sorry, Monsignor.
Okay.
Now go on, get back to class.
[Alexa] Thank you, Monsignor.
You're welcome.
[bright music]
[bell chiming]
Possession is
when Satan enters
and takes over the physical
as well as the mental
capabilities of the person.
However the soul
will remain free.
Satan acts through...
Through the victim.
Without the victim's consent.
Thus the victim is
morally blameless.
[eerie music]
Satan does not act alone when
he possesses an individual.
He works side by side
with many spirits.
[eerie music]
Hey faggot, are you gonna
ask God to forgive you?
Spirits of lust.
Spirits of hate.
Destruction.
[eerie music]
Suicide.
Torment.
[eerie music]
Enough you assholes.
[Father DuMal] Stephen.
Now who can find me an
example of that in the Bible?
Michelle.
There's an example in Luke.
The case of the possessed man
in the territory
of the Gerasenes.
And then Jesus asks,
what is your name?
And he replied Legion because
many demons had entered him.
Come with me.
We will address your troubles.
Well, right.
Well it was a good class.
Enjoy your day, girls.
[Michelle] Sister Clare?
[Sister Clare] Yes.
What do you think is
wrong with my brother?
I think someone is inside him.
Not like possessed...
No one is troubling
your brother, dear.
But something is.
And Sister, sometimes
I feel it, too.
Like a dream you can't remember
and you know it's really
important, but it's...
Twins often transfer thoughts.
You know I am aware
of the troubles
that your brother has had
since your father left
and your mother remarried.
Stephen doesn't
believe he left us.
You have to be strong
for him, Michelle.
Nothing happens without
divine intervention.
God never wills evil, but
if we have to face it,
He gives us all the power
to defeat it, child.
[soft music]
[Student] I gotta
tell ya something.
[eerie music]
No, no, leave
him alone, Father.
Please.
Stephen.
Don't go, Stephen.
[tires squealing]
Michelle, are you all right?
Yes, yes, I think so.
[Joseph] Oh God.
Grandfather, what
are you doing here?
I'm sorry.
I'm taking my last exam.
I have my ordination and
orientation on Sunday.
And I'm late.
Listen.
Yu have a good day.
You're sure you're okay?
I'm fine.
I'll see you Sunday.
[Joseph] I'll see you Sunday.
Okay.
Sweetie?
Next time you look where
you're going, okay?
[wind howling]
[door creaking]
[whistle blowing]
[Cheerleader] One, two,
three, four, five, six, seven.
As you can see our
curriculum extends
well beyond the pulpit
and the classroom.
[Boy] I wanna do that.
Monsignor, can I
be a cheerleader?
[Monsignor] Can
you be a cheerleader?
How 'bout a linebacker?
Do they dance?
Sometimes when they win.
I wanna be that girl.
Well you can be a cheerleader
and you can just be yourself.
You feel free to look around
and stop by my office
on the way out.
Let's do it again.
All right girls,
one more time.
More energy.
Five, six, seven, eight.
I personally thought
they were very good.
[Carol] That's why you're
not a dance instructor.
[Alexa] And one, two,
three four, five, six.
And one, two, three, four.
Keep going on the whistle.
Do not stop until you
hear the whistle blow.
Let's go.
Oscar.
Tempo, tempo.
[Man] Bounce,
bounce, bounce, bounce.
Go.
Hey, no.
Get him over there.
Get.
Down.
[whistle blowing]
Stephen, why aren't
you out there practicing?
Stephen?
[energetic music]
Coach.
[Randy] Father.
Have a good practice.
Thank you.
Hey, let's go.
Stephen.
Hey.
Come on, let's go.
Come on.
Let's go.
Gimme this, will ya?
Phone, gimme the phone.
Come on.
Okay look.
Line boogey.
290 Z.
All right?
Hey, you got this.
Let's go.
Show them what you can do.
[soft music]
How's it going?
Well, I'm trying to
get Stephen to step up.
Line boogey.
290 ZX.
All right, guys,
line boogey 290ZX.
Line boogey 290ZX.
Ready.
[All] Break.
Did you make it
to mass last Sunday?
No I talked to Jesus about it,
but he told me to sleep in.
Okay, watch this, watch this.
[soft music]
Yes, Stephen, yes.
[whistle blowing]
Way to see it, yes.
That's the way, that's the way.
If that boy's focus
matched his talent,
he'd be an all league
candidate next year.
[whistle blowing]
[Randy] Okay.
Ben, watch his
waist, not his feet.
[Quarterback] On the one.
Hut, hut.
[heartbeat pounding]
I'll get you bitch.
Hey faggot.
What are you
wearing to practice?
[Alexa] Stop it, you idiot.
[Ben] No one here to stop me.
[Randy] What's with
the black nail polish?
[Father DuMal] Come with me.
We'll address your troubles.
[Quarterback] On the one.
[Ben] He's the
devil, Sister Clare.
[Sister Clare] You
will go to confession
for the entire second period.
[heartbeat pounding]
[soft music]
[whistle blowing]
That's targeting.
[Stephen] That's for
my sister, you bitch.
[Randy] Hey, hey, Ben, Ben.
You all right?
[eerie music]
Nice hit.
This game is about scoring
points not settling scores.
Catch the ball next time.
[eerie music]
Good.
You're good, let's go.
[Alexa] One, two, three,
four, five, six, seven, eight.
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight.
That is not how we
play football here.
You understand me?
Come on, let's go.
Laps.
Laps, come on.
Laps, laps, laps, laps, laps.
Let's go, let's go.
Little hustle.
[Monsignor] Is he all right?
[Randy] He's a
football player.
He'll be fine.
Got what was coming to him.
Oh yeah, I know.
[soft music]
This is the proudest
day of my whole life.
[soft music]
Our life.
This is your day, Joseph.
If I could, I would not
take anything from you.
I spent most of my life
working for the church.
Without you, I never
could've gotten so far.
[soft music]
In a few months, it's
our 50th anniversary
and that will be the
happiest day for our family.
[soft music]
Grandfather Joseph.
Hey.
Alexa.
You're so beautiful.
Michelle, my baby.
God bless you, Michelle.
Hi dad.
I am such a blessed man.
Look at the four
beautiful women.
And now two.
Two granddaughters.
Yes indeed.
How are you, how are you?
[Joseph] Randy, God bless you.
Thank you for coming.
Congratulations.
Great to see you.
[Joseph] Oh wow,
how you girls doing?
Oh, we're okay.
[Michelle] Yeah, we're good.
[Joseph] Yeah.
[Alexa] You excited
for your big day?
Am I excited?
Yeah.
Come on, this is a great
honor for you, grandfather.
Well you keep up
your Bible studies,
you'll be right
behind me, sweetie.
Stephen.
Hey, come on.
Little pep, buddy, little pep.
Stephen.
You look great, pal.
What the hell is his problem?
It's okay.
Stephen, don't be rude.
You greet your grandfather.
Sorry.
[Joseph] You know
how it is, don't you?
Yeah, I do.
I do.
[eerie music]
Don't be so distant.
We are blood.
Joseph has sacrificed himself
for our church for many years.
His devotion to
bringing God's children
into our fold is unequaled.
He's nurtured our boys to
adolescence into manhood,
even sometimes delivering them
to the church's greatest
blessing, the priesthood.
If we could award
a greater accolade
than the Diaconate
on Joseph, we would,
but I know that
Joseph's greatest reward
is our Lord's respect and love.
On behalf of our
church, the Vatican,
and all its dominions,
we thank you, Joseph.
[Joseph] Monsignor, your
words and praise were too much.
I don't deserve this.
Stephen, what's the matter?
Lamb of God who taketh
away the sins of the world,
have mercy on us.
Lamb of God who taketh away
the sings of the world,
have mercy on us.
Lamb of God who taketh
away the sins of the world,
grant us peace.
Now I'll ask that we
all approach the altar
in order to receive
the body of Christ.
As Deacon, this will
be Joseph's first time
providing the Eucharist.
The body of Christ.
[Monsignor] The
body of Christ.
[Joseph] The body of Christ.
Amen.
[Monsignor] The
body of Christ.
The body of Christ.
[Monsignor] The
body of Christ.
Amen.
[eerie music]
[Monsignor] The
body of Christ.
The body of Christ.
[eerie music]
Amen.
[soft music]
The body of Christ.
[Monsignor] The
body of Christ.
[eerie music]
[Joseph] The body of Christ.
[Monsignor] Lamb of
God who taketh away
the sins of the world.
[ominous music]
[speaking in foreign language]
The mass has ended.
Go in peace.
[soft music]
[Alexa] Do we really have
to go on this stupid trip?
I had a date.
Yes, you do.
Come on.
The lake house is where your
grandparents were married
and it's gonna mean a
lot to your grandmother
to have us all there.
It's the anniversary, okay.
Look, it'll be fun.
You're gonna see your cousins.
You're gonna enjoy my
brilliant barbecuing.
That's right.
I don't know what's worse.
The cousins, your barbecuing,
or that creepy house.
That's funny.
That's what Stephen used to
call it when he was little.
That's what he called it?
- Mm.
God, ew.
Ew, ew.
[Emily] Okay, I'm gonna go see
what's keeping mom and Michelle.
[Randy] Okay.
Emily.
It's been six years since
he left you and the twins.
Isn't six years long enough
to find forgiveness
in your heart?
He never left.
Let's go.
Come on, ladies.
[soft music]
Let's go, ladies.
Let's go.
Thank you, thank you.
Coming.
It would be nice to
get there before dark.
Thank you.
Help you out over here.
Stephen, hey.
I am not listening
to that awful music
for the next two hours.
That's the kind of
music the devil uses
to possess your body.
I don't know about possession,
but it might make
his eyeliner darker.
Yeah, we got
proof right there.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hey.
Everybody just chill out.
Got a long ride ahead of us.
Let's go.
[soft music]
After you.
[hand knocking]
Come.
I said come.
[soft music]
[ominous music]
[Alexa] Two weekends from now,
I'm gonna take you
out to a party.
To a party.
[Michelle] That's
not gonna go very well.
I wouldn't be comfortable.
[Alexa] You're gonna love it.
[Randy] We're
gonna throw a party.
We're gonna throw a
party at the house next.
[soft music]
It's a beautiful day.
All right, let's get
this truck unloaded.
Tomorrow we party but tonight,
we chill and get some rest.
I'm gonna go for a swim.
No, no, no, no, no.
We need your help.
Stephen.
All right, don't
expect anything else.
I don't understand how
you guys can be twins.
You guys are nothing
alike at all.
Michelle, guess what?
Thank you.
- Appreciate it.
- Got it.
Yup.
Yup, don't worry about it.
Dad's got the rest of it.
Stop complaining.
You're big and strong.
Come on.
Always the way.
[Emily] Stephen, come on.
[Father DuMal] Always
been drawn to this place.
Yes, you have.
Where's Monsignor Canell?
I'm sorry.
He couldn't make it, but
he sends his well wishes.
Ah.
Well, Rosemary will
be disappointed,
but I know it means a lot to
her that you're both here.
Enjoy.
[Father DuMal] Thank you.
Hello, Rosemary.
Hello, Sister Clare.
Boys versus girls.
Except for what team is
Stephen gonna play on?
That's not funny, guys.
Yes, it is.
He just expresses
himself differently.
[Cousin] Okay.
Rosemary.
It's a bittersweet
day, isn't it?
For who?
[Father DuMal] For...
I know who you meant.
[ominous music]
What are you guys staring at?
The past.
Okay.
Whatever.
[ominous music]
[heartbeat pounding]
Is it finished?
Come on, Stephen.
Show him what you got.
[soft music]
No.
It can't, can it?
Because they will remember.
[ominous music]
Fine, no problem.
We'll play O'Connor's
versus Younger's.
[soft music]
[heartbeat pounding]
[eerie music]
All right, we know
what we're doing, right?
Oh yeah.
And if you run like your
mother, we'll be fine.
You remember the plan?
If not, ask her.
Okay guys.
[Randy] Alexa, help us out.
[Alexa] Got it.
Here we go, here
we go, Stephen.
Hey baby.
[Randy] Hey baby.
Here we go.
[Joseph] Hey ho,
hey, hey, hey, ho.
Let's go, hike
the ball already.
Hike the ball already.
Come on.
Let's go.
[Joseph] Hike, hike.
[soft music]
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
[Emily] Dad, dad.
Stephen, what did you do?
Stephen, what the
hell is your problem?
He's an old man.
Yo, Stephen hit him hard.
I can't believe how hard
you hit your grandfather.
What made you
do that, Stephen?
I'm gonna go outside.
[soft music]
What's down there?
Why is this door always locked?
[soft music]
[eerie music]
[heartbeat pounding]
Come on, Michelle.
[soft music]
As it is in heaven.
Give us this day
our daily bread.
Do you believe in heaven?
Yes.
I do.
And hell?
[soft music]
Where's grandfather?
You really think God
can hear your prayers?
I do.
How come he never
hears mine then?
Oh Stephen.
He hears you.
Do you hear him?
[soft music]
I don't hear God.
You will.
Soon.
All things will be revealed
to you in just a short time.
I'll join you down
there in a second.
Okay.
[soft music]
You shouldn't say anymore.
You swore on the Bible.
When you're
forbidden to use words,
you must rely on actions.
Food's up.
Randy O'Connor's gourmet
burgers and dogs are served.
Come and get it.
Starving.
I'm taking bets we'll
still be alive tomorrow.
Oh?
Oh really?
Well, hold on.
Serve.
You're serving.
Absolutely.
[soft music]
My beloved family.
Thank you all for
making this journey
and for ending
here with me today.
After 50 years of
marriage to the same man,
his predilections,
and his church.
There are things I
have not spoken of
in order to keep
this family together.
[eerie music]
Things are not what they seem,
but today all things
will be revealed.
[eerie music]
And I will ask your forgiveness.
Playing with fire.
Thank you my heavenly father
for keeping me from harm.
Don't do it, Rosie.
And from danger.
Let thy holy angel lie with me
that the wicked foe may
have no power over me.
Amen.
[soft music]
Mom, stop.
Are you okay?
Yes, Emily.
I'm fine.
My chains are broken.
What are you talking about?
Have courage, Emily.
Don't drown it.
[soft music]
Okay.
Dessert anyone?
Let's just clear the plates.
Come on, kids.
Help clear please.
They were mine the
moment they were born.
[wind rumbling]
[soft music]
[speaking in foreign language]
What the hell?
Look.
[speaking in foreign language]
Mom.
Rosemary.
Get down from there.
What are you doing?
[speaking in foreign language]
Mom.
Mom, what are you doing?
[speaking in foreign language]
[soft music]
What is she saying?
[speaking in foreign language]
[soft music]
No.
[Randy] Okay,
okay, okay, okay.
[soft music]
I think we should
let them be alone.
[eerie music]
What was that?
What did I see?
I don't know.
I see it all the time.
That really scared me.
[thunder rumbling]
Don't let it.
I'll always take care of you.
You always have.
Yea though I walk
through the valley
of the shadow of death.
I will fear no evil.
For thou are with me.
My rod and my staff
they comfort me.
Amen.
Now Michelle has a special
prayer for her grandmother
and we will end with that.
Michelle.
[soft music]
Help me, Lord, to understand
this mysterious death
and to be healed by your grace
and made whole once again.
May the soul of my
tormented grandmother
find in the savior's love
forgiveness and reconciliation.
Lord in your mercy,
hear my prayer.
Amen.
Thank you, Michelle.
My sincerest sympathies
to you and to your family.
Rosemary was a wonderful woman
and it's a very great loss.
I'm very worried
about Stephen.
He was very close
with his grandparents.
When are you planning
to return home?
I'd like to gather her
friends at the church
for a farewell ceremony.
That would be lovely.
We have to pack
Rosemary's things
and go through her paperwork,
but it shouldn't be
more than a few days.
All right, well
if you need guidance
or you just wanna talk, don't
hesitate to call me all right.
Thank you, Monsignor.
You're welcome.
[eerie music]
Monsignor.
There's a lot of
bad energy here.
You should get going
as soon as possible.
We will.
We should go inside.
Okay.
And we're gonna get going.
But just remember, we're
here for your family.
[soft music]
I'm weighted by guilt.
What guilt, Sister?
Rosemary.
The torment.
The soul.
We will pray for her soul.
And you are innocent
of any wrongdoing.
You have been a
good friend to her.
Not a friend.
A friend would have spoken
the truth years ago.
Speak the truth to me, Sister.
I don't have the strength
to face those demons now.
I pray you do.
Sister Clare please.
Takes everything.
[soft music]
Do you see?
Help me to.
I am trying.
Stephen, Michelle,
come inside please.
[soft music]
It's like talking
to a brick wall.
I don't know how to reach him.
Just keep your heart open.
Only the truth will
heal his troubled soul.
[ominous music]
Why is it so cold in here?
[Randy] I don't know.
The thermostat is up
as high as it can go.
Then why is it
so freaking cold?
[Randy] I don't know.
Is Stephen still
locked in his room?
Yeah.
And you know what?
It's rude.
It's rude never
talking to his family.
[ominous music]
No, he's taking
this all really hard.
He's getting weirder.
[Emily] Okay, this
has been really hard
for all of us today.
Please don't be mean to him.
He's not even in
his body anymore.
It's like there's nothing there.
I mean, did you see
him at the funeral?
Alexa please, just stop.
[soft music]
I'm gonna go to bed.
Me too.
Maybe it's warmer up there.
[Randy] I'll join
you guys in a minute.
Dad.
[soft music]
I'll hit the
lights and join you.
We can all use the
goodnight sleep.
[soft music]
Stephen, you must be freezing.
Michelle, pass me your blanket.
I'm not cold.
What do you mean
you're not cold?
It's freezing in here.
Maybe if you wore more clothes
and stopped dressing like a
whore, you wouldn't be so cold.
Hey.
Don't talk to your
sister like that.
Well maybe if I were a
little more liquored up, Mom,
I could ignore what was right
fucking in front of
me this whole time.
You do not talk to
your mother like that.
I'm sorry.
I just wanted to make
sure I wasn't being rude.
[suspenseful music]
He's hurting.
You can't blame him.
What was that?
Let's just go to bed.
[dramatic music]
[Woman] Joseph.
Who's there?
[dramatic music]
Turn your music down, Stephen.
We're trying to sleep.
[energetic music]
It just got really
quiet in here.
[Alexa] What?
Whatever, let's
just go back to bed.
It's too quiet.
[Woman] Joseph.
Stephen?
No, no.
I'm here, Joseph.
[eerie music]
[Randy] You feeling all right?
[Stephen] Yeah, I'm fine.
Okay.
So what was all that noise
last night in your room?
What's that about?
[Stephen] I wasn't
making any noise.
It sounded like an
earthquake, Stephen.
[Stephen] I didn't
hear anything.
Look, your mother's
still really shaken up.
I need you to keep
it down today, okay.
Please.
I found my dad's bow
and arrows in the shed.
Taking them out.
I don't think
that's a good idea.
I second that.
I'm going out.
The house is warming up so
I'm gonna go take a shower.
Yeah.
You know whatever was
wrong with the furnace,
it's definitely fixed itself.
[ominous music]
[Man] And drop.
[soft music]
Skip.
Let it fly.
[soft music]
Daddy?
Stephen, where have you been?
I went hunting.
What happened to you?
Randy's made a
beautiful dinner.
Why don't you go
and wash up, okay?
I'm not hungry.
Take the salad to the table.
Okay.
I don't know how to
talk to him, Michelle.
I'm trying, mom.
I'm here for him.
I know you are.
Come here.
Thank you.
[wind howling]
[Alexa] Is it just me
or are things getting
really weird around here?
What do you mean?
Really, Michelle?
Your grandma kills herself
in front of everyone
and now Stephen with
all this freaky shit.
What do you think I mean?
Okay, I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to
sound like that.
No, you did.
But it's true.
Things are not right.
Weird as you say and
I don't know why.
I was taking a shower earlier.
And?
I sensed a presence.
Presence?
I felt a presence
and when I turned,
there was writing in the mirror.
Words like someone had traced
them in the condensation.
What the hell?
What were the words?
Help Stephen.
It said help Stephen.
[eerie music]
[children screaming]
[door creaking]
[eerie music]
Relax, Stephen.
Get away from that boy.
Don't you touch him.
You didn't see this.
I didn't want to.
[suspenseful music]
Evil prick.
What the hell is going on?
I don't know.
It's Stephen's room.
[children screaming]
Furnace must have
stopped working again.
It's so cold.
[Stephen] Liars burn.
Stephen.
Oh my god, what have
you done to yourself?
Oh Jesus.
[speaking in foreign language]
What's he saying?
DuMal led me.
DuMal.
Led me.
Led you where?
Malo.
Who's evil?
Killers.
[hand pounding]
[eerie music]
He loved us.
And they want his soul.
[soft music]
Daddy.
Who baby?
It's the church.
It's the goddamn church.
No.
[kettle whistling]
Oh my god.
Let me take a look.
What happened?
I'm fine.
I'm okay.
I had to restrain him so
he didn't hurt himself.
What?
I didn't realize
he was so strong.
We should call
Monsignor Canell.
Why would we call
Monsignor Canell?
He can help.
Michelle, you
gotta get serious.
Stephen is crazy.
Your brother is crazy.
No amount of religion
can sugarcoat that.
How do you explain
the knife, dad?
We all saw it fly into his hand.
We need to work out
what we're going to do.
I'm gonna call the doctor
and I'm gonna get him sedated.
He needs our help not drugs.
You heard what he said.
Help me.
I am gonna help him.
I'm gonna get him
sedated, Michelle.
Do you think the part
of Stephen's problem
is that you are so hard on him?
Michelle, I've
tried my hardest,
but nothing that
I might have done
could have turned him into
that thing that was up there.
My brother was fine
and perfectly happy
when we had our real dad.
And how long ago was that?
Michelle, wait.
You can't pin this on my dad.
Michelle.
God.
[soft music]
She did not mean that.
Yeah, she did.
It's true.
Baby, I am not the problem here.
I know you're not the problem.
He is.
And when I say he, I
do not mean Stephen.
I mean his dad.
His abandonment has
taken away all the good
that was in that little boy
and it's left a
gaping hole of despair
and I can't handle it anymore.
[soft music]
[Father DuMal]
Saint Michael's.
Monsignor Canell?
[Father DuMal] Michelle?
Yes.
[Father DuMal]
This is Father DuMal.
Father, I need to
speak to the Monsignor.
Something's terribly
wrong with Stephen.
He was screaming terrible
things last night about killing
and he said something
about you, Father.
About that you led him.
Led him where?
I don't know.
He was yelling about
the church and you.
Not really you.
Just our.
[Father DuMal]
Your who, Michelle?
Our dad.
Listen Michelle, your
family's going through
a very traumatic time right now
and none of you are
thinking clearly.
Please let me speak
to Monsignor Canell.
I'm sorry but Monsignor
is busy right now
and he can't take the call,
but I will pass the
message onto him.
Okay?
Okay.
Thank you for
calling and God bless.
Thank you, Father.
What's wrong?
I'm not sure but something is.
[Stephen] We want his soul.
[ominous music]
Well?
Well, he doesn't
have a temperature
and his vital signs are normal,
but what's abnormal
is for someone
to move continuously for so long
with no respiratory or
heart rate increase.
It's not his body.
Whatever is wrong
is in his mind.
So, what can we do?
I gave him a sedative
so he'll stay calm
until you head back tomorrow.
Any change, call me.
Thank you.
No, I haven't done anything.
You're the help he needs.
[thunder rumbling]
Appreciate it.
We should get going.
Did you call Monsignor again?
I'm waiting for
him to call back.
I'm sorry about what
I said to your dad.
No, no, it's fine.
I know sometimes
he can be a jerk.
Alexa, I know
Stephen's not crazy.
I think he's possessed.
Shut up.
You're scaring me.
I'm scared, too.
That's why we need
Monsignor Canell.
Well call him, Michelle.
Call him right now.
[phone ringing]
[Monsignor Canell]
This is Monsignor.
I've got him.
[Monsignor Canell]
This opportunity
to share Christ with you
and with your family.
Please leave your name and
number and I'll call you back.
Monsignor, this
message is for you.
It's Michelle Tade.
We really need you.
I know we already
called Father DuMal
and he said you were busy,
but we really need you here.
Hello.
[dial tone humming]
[ominous music]
[Boy] Can't you
just let him go?
[Man] Hey Stephen,
can you help me?
[Boy] Please, please.
[Man] Please help me.
Release my soul.
[ominous music]
[floor thumping]
He never did anything wrong.
Oh sweetie.
Neither of you did.
Okay?
[eerie music]
[floor thumping]
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Baby.
Calm down.
He's sedated.
[Alexa] How?
Get busy.
Go pack.
I know you haven't packed yet.
We're out of here tomorrow.
Really?
Really.
Called the doctor to come
back tomorrow morning
to give him a shot just in case,
so we can get him home safely.
Get him to a hospital.
I'm really worried.
I know.
We all are.
Come here.
I know.
[soft music]
What did he say?
Who?
Stephen.
I guess in Latin in his room.
Do not lead me
into temptation.
What did he mean?
[Michelle] I don't know.
He said Father DuMal led me.
I know.
Led him where, Michelle?
[soft music]
He said he led him to malo.
To evil.
[wind howling]
You came.
Thank God, you came.
Of course we did.
I'm so happy to see you.
Father DuMal wouldn't let
me speak to the Monsignor
and Stephen's been
screaming terrible things
about Father DuMal about
him taking him places
and making him do things...
Calm down, child.
Why don't you let us in?
I'm coming.
Monsignor.
Monsignor had
prior commitments,
but I can sure you
he is very concerned.
Your brother has been putting
these malicious thoughts
into your head, Michelle.
[eerie music]
I understand that
you have questions.
Why don't you come
take a walk with us?
And we can discuss everything
that's been going on.
We could use you to
help us to find a way
to best help your brother.
[Sister Clare] Father.
What?
Nothing.
[soft music]
Come on, Michelle.
[door creaking]
[ominous music]
Stop.
I won't go with you.
I'm not my brother.
No, you're more dangerous.
You don't have to do this.
Tell the truth.
It will all end.
What truth?
What did you do to Stephen?
Where did you take my brother?
I took him to hell
exactly where I was taken.
Where Joseph took
all those poor boys.
Joseph was...
Shut up.
No, I won't.
He's dead.
You don't have to
protect the past anymore.
I'm taking her back.
No, you're not.
[suspenseful music]
[Michelle] Stephen.
He won't let you do this.
Stephen.
Oh God.
[ominous music]
Stephen?
Randy, Stephen's missing.
[ominous music]
Please Stephen.
Don't go.
Leave him alone, Father.
Don't go, Stephen.
Please help me.
[ominous music]
Why?
Stephen.
[Boy] Come on, grandfather.
Go on.
Tell him that you'll
take care of me.
I see.
I forgive you.
[ominous music]
[Father DuMal] You
can't forgive me.
No.
[suspenseful music]
[Emily] Michelle.
Michelle.
This is not acceptable.
Not at all.
You do not do this
to the family.
Enough.
I can't take this anymore.
[wind howling]
[heartbeat pounding]
Someone's here.
Who?
[thunder rumbling]
Don't know.
[hand knocking]
[thunder rumbling]
I want to see the boy.
You're too late.
Monsignor, he has killed.
I want to see the boy.
All right, I'll stay
here with the girl.
You will stay with me.
[ominous music]
Give me a cloth.
[demon growling]
You stay with them.
[ominous music]
Stephen.
It's Monsignor Canell.
[demon growling]
I'm here to help you.
You touched those boys.
You let him touch him, too.
Did you masturbate
when you watched?
[thunder rumbling]
Where's grandfather?
[speaking in foreign language]
Joseph, they are children.
Don't kill the father.
Kill the prick.
[thunder rumbling]
Don't touch me there, Father.
It hurts.
If he speaks the truth...
He doesn't.
They're lies.
He's the devil.
The demon spewing fifth.
He's trying to turn
our faith against us.
[Rosemary] Joseph, I swore
on the Bible I would never tell.
My soul is burning.
[Child] Please.
Keep him from me.
I want to go home.
How many more must
die 'cause they know?
'Cause you can't shut them up.
Killer.
[child screaming]
Let me go.
I have to see him.
He's still my child.
[ominous music]
[boys crying]
[demon growling]
I command you through
the blood of Christ,
release Stephen Tade's soul.
God.
I command you in the name
and power of the holy spirit.
[demon growling]
Father DuMal, where
are you taking me?
Where did you take Stephen?
To molest him?
What is he talking about?
Hey grandfather, you said
it was for God but it wasn't.
It was for your
shriveled old prick.
Tell them.
Who is he talking to?
Forgive those who trespass.
[soft music]
His grandfather, the molester.
What?
The killer.
Tell 'em, grandfather.
Tell 'em.
How you took care of me.
How you took care of all of us.
Stephen, Stephen.
Baby, you need to listen to me.
Your grandfather
died a month ago.
[Rosemary] He
couldn't leave you.
[ominous music]
No door would open for his soul.
Your mother speaks
the truth, Stephen.
We buried him
under the oak tree.
I closed his casket.
I commended him to the earth.
You were there.
That's right.
He's there begging
for a blowjob.
[eerie music]
You need to leave now.
Your presence only
fuels the demon's power.
[Emily] Monsignor, please.
You are the demon.
You're not an instrument of God.
Impurities have poisoned
your heart and your soul.
What have you done, James?
[eerie music]
What has he done?
I'll tell you what he's done.
If you don't need to,
maybe you're just like him.
I am not like him.
Stephen, and you.
You are not like him.
[eerie music]
Do you see the
devil, Monsignor?
I see nothing, Stephen.
Expose a child to the worst
and a priest will
be their salvation.
[Boy] Tell them how
you took care of me.
Destroying a child's life
is not God's way.
It was for him.
[ominous music]
You.
Here, let me help.
Do not touch him.
[ominous music]
Stephen.
[Monsignor Canell]
Free this child.
Stephen.
Come on, Stephen.
I know you're in there.
No.
[ominous music]
Please, Stephen.
[speaking in foreign language]
[ominous music]
We cast you out.
Every unclean spirit.
[ominous music]
Free this child from evil.
What the hell do
you know about evil?
We command you, be gone.
[ominous music]
Open your eyes, Monsignor.
Can't you see?
[ominous music]
Let him go.
Please, Stephen.
We command you.
[ominous music]
Come on, come on.
Our Lord commands you.
[Randy] Come on.
[soft music]
Let.
Him.
Go.
[ominous music]
[Stephen] Killers, killers.
[Man] You can
do anything, son.
I've always been
here to help you.
[ominous music]
In the name of the
father, of the son,
and of the holy spirit as it
was in the beginning is now
and ever shall be
world without end.
Amen.
They killed my father.
Please.
Tell me you can see.
I do see, Stephen.
Mom.
Stephen.
[Stephen] Mom.
Stephen, Stephen.
[soft music]
He loved us.
He tried to save me and he
did everything that he could.
He didn't leave.
They took him from us.
[soft music]
I'm so sorry.
I am so, so sorry.
I couldn't save any of them.
You saved many, Stephen,
by what you've
done here tonight.
You are a strong, young man.
[soft music]
Lord.
May I be in extremis.
May I fight every abomination.
Every corruption.
[soft music]
You're gonna believe a
possessed boy, a demon.
He's trying to destroy us.
Destroy you.
You have no idea what I
have had to endure for this.
Please do not try to
justify these evil acts.
You deaconized a child abuser.
[Emily] Michelle.
Oh baby.
You did.
You let it happen under
your watch for 30 years.
You didn't see.
I'm not to blame.
No.
You.
This is your fault.
I am to blame.
I've blended my trust and
my belief in the church,
but you need help, my son.
[soft music]
[ominous music]
Detective Kerry, please.
Monsignor Canell
from Saint Micheal's.
[suspenseful music]
[girl screaming]
[gentle music]
And I through blindness
have been guilty
of placing more faith in the
church than in our creator.
From this day forward I pledge
to be a vigilant witness
and purveyor of truth
to eliminate the evils
that have hurt our children
and plagued our church.
[soft music]
Thanks for driving
us down here.
Yeah.
I just needed to spend
some time here, you know.
I do.
Your father was very
special, Stephen.
He is.
I like what we have.
It's different.
I just wish he would've
taught me how to aim.
[Emily] Oh, he did, Stephen.
[Michelle] Just close your
eyes and you'll remember.
You can do anything, son.
I've always been
here to help you.
I never left.
[gentle music]
[Rosemary] You can
never silence me again.
Oh, come on.
[Emily] Randy.
Last chance to see it.
The people that bought it
are moving in tomorrow.
Lucky family.
[Joseph] They were mine
the moment they were born.
He's still here.
I know.
I feel him.
[Alexa] Dad.
[hand knocking]
[Randy] Hey.
[Emily] Randy, open the door.
Come on.
[Randy] Alexa, Emily.
[Emily] Randy.
[soft music]
[Stephen] What the?
[girl screaming]
[Man] Then I saw
there was a way to hell,
even through the
gates of heaven.
[soft music]
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
[gentle music]