As a woman, I know better than
to walk alone at night, but...
in my dream,
I always walk alone.
I'm alone
and I walk, and...
and I look
into the houses...
'cause there's no curtains
or blinds, and I...
I see the people...
the families.
And they smile and wave,
and I wave back.
Friendly.
But I don't feel friendly.
I feel angry.
Jealous maybe, because--
because they are families
and I don't have a family
and I probably never will.
I walk away defeated
and so full of hate, I...
I don't even know
where I am, or...
who I am.
[footsteps]
And then suddenly, I...
I hear footsteps behind me.
And then they stop.
And-- And I turn.
But there's no one there.
It's just a....It's just a...
empty street and sidewalk.
And then I...
I hear footsteps again,
but this time it's closer.
And I know now that
that person wants to hurt me.
So I run and I run,
screaming for help,
but no one helps me.
I find, uh...
a dark house,
and I hide in the closet.
But the footsteps
are getting closer...
and closer...
until they just
pause outside the door.
The door opens.
Inches.
And I look up to see...
the person ready to strike me.
And it's me.
You mean your father.
No.
Up until now,
it's always been
my father, but now it's me.
And now the scared little girl
in the closet is someone else.
What do you think that means?
♪♪ [ominous, rumbling]
[bell rings]
[crowd chattering]
[Judge] Logan McQueen.
The State of Florida finds you guilty
of manslaughter in the second degree.
I hereby sentence you to a term of imprisonment
of not more than five years
and not less than one year.
Said period to be served at a facility selected
by the State Department of Corrections.
Your commission as a sworn peace officer
is hereby suspended.
[men chattering]
[voice on P.A.] Lockdown in section B to section D.
Something's going down.
Call for backup.
Police! Hold it![woman screams]
Hold it!
[gate buzzer]
I didn't kill the kid.
Well, D.A. Barker thinks you did.
Where's my money?
Excuse me?
[Barker] Half a million dollars was in that bag
when it left my hands.
And only $310,000 was counted out by your own forensic officers.
[Logan] It was you, Charlie, who took the money.
I couldn't imagine
it would escalate.
I never thought
they'd pin Pepe on you.
You betrayed me.I betrayed myself.
I turn the money
over to Barker,
and he buys that I saw
Catarato shoot Pepe.
You wouldn't last
two weeks in prison.
No reason for both of us
to end up behind bars.
No matter what kind of
spin Miss Myler puts on this,
I'll be forced to own up
to a crime that I did
not commit.
[bell rings]
McQueen!
Round's over.
Let's go!
Let's go.
[men's taunting chatter,
indistinct]
[gate buzzer]
Hold it. We're
goin' this way.
Population's
havin' a meeting.
Let's go.
Now we're even.
Get lost.
You took my brother down.
Now I'm taking you.
Come on.
Uhh!
Uhh! Unhh!
[yelling, shouting]
[bell rings]Hold him!
[Guard]
Back away from the gate!
All right, break it up!
[indistinct shouting]
Get down! Get back!
Put 'em down!
Hold it right there!
[gate buzzer]
Okay, Logan, it's time
to go to the Row.
[men taunting]
It's just too dangerous
here for ex-cops in the
general population.
It's going to be lonely
on Death Row,
but it'll be a lot
safer for you.
♪♪ [opera]
[Guard] You don't have
long to go, McQueen, so...
just play by the rules,
and we'll get you out
of here in one piece.
[gate closes]
Open number 2.
[Guard]
Opening 2.
[buzzer]
Rather stunning...
ain't I?
I ain't gonna be
here that long, pal.
Admit it.
♪♪ [opera continues]
[chuckles]
Ray Earl Winston.
"Lucifer's Right Hand."
I know who it was.
Ever see what he
does to journalists?
Ties 'em in knots.
Get yourself
another hero, pal.
[prisoner coughing]
Close number 2.
[buzzer]
[Prisoner]
Logan McQueen.
News travels fast
through these walls.
Now, the logan was a war
wagon with a battering ram,
used in medieval times.
McQueen?
"Of the queen."
War wagon for the queen.
Now, that's a name.
My name's
Sebastian Allgood.
Allgood.
Somewhat ironic, considering
my present gravidity.
You'll stop pacing,
once you realize
you have no place to go.
I'm sorry I overreacted.
Thanks for tracking
that thing down.
How was
the family reunion?
It was great.
I've never seen
my mom so happy.
And I rounded up these old
eight millimeter movies
of me and my dad.
When he saw it,
he just crumbled.
How sweet.
Hey, sorry about that
report being a day late.
Don't worry about it.
One advantage
of working for Dad.
I'll just blame it
on Daddy's little girl.
See ya.
[phone rings]
Good morning.
Laboratory testing.
[people chatting]
[sigh]
[Woman]
I'll just blame it
on Daddy's little girl.
[Sebastian]
Tell fortune of her blindness.
Tell nature of decay.
Tell friendship of unkindness.
Tell justice of delay.
And if they will reply,
then give them all the lie.
Faulkner, Cather,
Hawthorne,
Shakespeare.
The eminent ones.
They have the power
to traverse
the latitudes and
the longitudes of time,
outside these walls.
Professor.
Ah, speak again,
bright angel.
Why are you in here?
Did you bore your English
literature class to death?
[laughing] Oh, no.
It was the ultimate act
of malignant narcissism.
What the hell
does that mean?
Revenge.
Oh.
Premature death served
no purpose for him.
Or his victim.
Or soon, me.
He killed my wife.
And you,
Mr. McQueen?
Well, I know
it'll sound familiar...
...but...I didn't
do anything wrong.
Unfortunately, I did.
Most of us don't get
what we deserve,
for which we are
eternally grateful.
My action, which was
a commitment to revenge,
has found its equal
in punishment.
[Woman]
Brian, what are you
tryin' to do?
Kiss up to Dad?He's the boss.
Hey, I'm off the clock.
He's Dad now. You want me to
stay and help you finish up?
No, no,
you go on ahead.
Okay.
[gasps]
Gonna be a while.
Take the stairs
if you're in a hurry.
[sighs]
Hello?
Can anybody hear me?
[door opens]
[gasp]
Hello?
[door closes]
[footsteps]
[metal pipe drops][gasp]
[door opens]
[hinges squeal,
door closes]
[grating, clattering]
[bang]
The elevator's fixed.
[clicking switch]
[elevator bell rings]
Hey there.
Aah!
Walk me to my car.
I feel so silly,
I really scared
myself, didn't I?
Are you gonna
be all right?
Yeah, I'll be
fine. Thanks.
I'll see you
tomorrow.
Good night.Good night.
[police sirens]
[beep beep]
♪♪ [ominous wordless choir]
[buzzing]
[rumbling tone]
Ohh!
Logan McQueen.
Caught...back in between.
Logan.
[tauntingly]
[crow cawing]
[knock knock knock]
Professor.
Logan.
I think I would like
to borrow a book.
Good. Let's see.
Billy Budd.
An innocent man swings
from the yardarm,
betrayed by his shipmates.
Not his fault.
But it was his fate.
He knew that.
That was his beauty.Well,
thank you very much.
Now I know how it ends.
No, Logan. You don't.
[gate buzzer in distance]
Captain Waters.
Detective Higgs.
I want a shot
at the bombing case.
You do?
That's a pretty tough case
for a rookie detective.
Bombs and murder mean
press and politicians.
That makes for a long day
and maybe a short career.
I'll work
26 hours a day.
I'll think about it.
[footsteps]
We'll be movin' you
over tomorrow.
You, uh...decide
on your last meal?
Just tell His Honor that
a meal won't be needed.
I'm no longer
consumed with being.
[Guard]
You want to see
the chaplain?
My soul has all
the footing I'll ever need.
Good night.
[gate buzzer]
[prisoner coughing]
Professor.
Yes, Logan.
I didn't know you were
leaving us so soon.
I've been here a long time.
And only a little...
with a friend.
Logan...
I want you
to know something.
Yes?
Forgiveness.
Forgiveness?
Go on.
Your anger.
You were forced to write
a book without knowledge.
Forced to build
a wall without stones.
I'm not sure I understand.
You will.
[Radio Announcer]
Now, that's a check
of the weather
and the traffic together.
Turning to local news.
Funeral Services
are to be held today
for car victim
Janine Junkermann.
Police Detectives say
the background check
of the 31-year-old woman
is still in progress.
They continue to search
out for possible motives
in the bombing.
Police say they have
little to say.
Open number 1.
[buzzer]
Allgood.
It's time
to move you over.
I'm already there.
Permission to speak
to Mr. McQueen?
Did you know
that state law requires
the executioner
actually to sterilize
the needle?
I see you're absconding, too.
Yes.
We'll both be free.
Logan, about Duffy.
It is very difficult
for a man to remain
a wonder to his family.
In all of time,
very few men have.
I would like Logan
to have this book.
Perhaps someday
that will resonate within.
When it does, touch one,
so that others
may be touched.
Thank you, Sebastian.
[buzzer]
Nice flowers.
Got a secret lover,
Miss Karen?
He's no secret.
We're engaged.
Lucky guy.
Good night.
See you tomorrow.
See you.
[ominous wordless choir]
[rumbling tone]Uhh!
[rumbling tone continues]
Mr. McQueen!
Can you remember
a bad dream?
[Prisoner] Shut up.I'm living one right now.
I've just had
a dreadful dream
I would love to tell.
Visions of cars
and dreams of bombs.
Pretty women tangled
in the fires of hell.
[Prisoner]
Tell somebody who cares!
I just did.
I just told
someone who cares.
[gate opens]
[Guard]
Open number 2.
[buzzer]
Must feel pretty good
gettin' out of here.
And we only just met.
Yeah. I'm sorry
we didn't get to talk.
How many were there?
14.
And I condemn myself.
You know,
I begged God...
to form me differently.
But he blessed me
with a capacity...
for cruelty.
But it's the face
of the bomber.
That's the thing that's
so odd, Detective...
McQueen,
obviously no longer
a part of the machine.
But don't go away.
I see the bastard's face.
[Prisoner]
Shut up, Winston!
Just as plain as day.
The man's a poet.
[men chattering]
[Duffy]
Hey, come on.
Give us a break, you know?
We're retired cops,
you know?
He made a mistake,
but who doesn't?
[Duffy]
We're more than friends.
You know, when you've
been partners as long
as me and Logan,
you think the same.
That's the thing.
You know every move
the other's gonna make.
Two more minutes,
and you move it.
He'll come out,
jump in, and I'm gone.
There he is now!
Hey, Logan!
Mary and Joseph,
you look great!
Hey, your hair's
a little long, but
you can get that cut.
You lost
a little weight,
huh?
Hey, where you goin'?
Hey, I got the car
right here.
What? You forgot
you forgave me?
Want me to meet
you over there?
Okay, wait there.
I said wait there,
will ya?
Where do you think
you're goin'?
He's just circlin'
the block.
Get in the car. I'll take
you to a barber shop.
Oh, are you still
mad at me?
Logan. You wanna walk?
Walkin' is good.
That-- That's healthy.
Yeah, you still
think I shoulda--
I should've turned
the money in?
It wouldn't have helped
you, and you know that.
You still would have gone in.
Ohh...Logan...
[stammers]
[car horn]
Uhh! Uhh!
[screeching tires]
[Driver]
Nice driving, moron!
We still have some
debris to sift through.
The only thing that
connects both cases
are those cards found
at the crime scene.
Anything on 'em?
Disjointed lettering.
Symbolism.
A message.
Some form of symbolism.
It's handwritten
Gothic style.
There's no results yet
from the FBI lab
on inks, paper stock,
bomb components.
No prints, witnesses.
Other than the cards,
there's no leads.
Well, find some,
detective.
[Man]
I was playing with
Woody Herman's band.
That's where
I met GoGo Gloria.
She was a real good sport.
She traveled with the band.
She didn't sing or anything.
She just traveled
with the band.
She had a whole lot
of round bruises
on her body,
from guys touching her
with a ten-foot pole.
I'll never forget
the first time I saw her.
She was sitting
on the Golden Gate Bridge,
dangling her feet
in the water.
Logan, my man.
Where you been?
Oh, I was havin'
so much fun,
I lost track of time.
Hey, what kept you?
[chuckles]
I beat you here,
huh?
Your money's
no good here today.
My money was no good where
I was, but it's good here.
Not today.
I'm buyin'.
Not this time, Charlie.
Got your stuff
in the back.
Good.
You know, you're welcome
to stay in Bo's room
till you get back on your feet.
Who's Bo?
♪♪ [blues]
[soft growl]
The vet says he's got
another year to grow.
I hope you didn't pay
for him by the pound.
Just a puppy, huh?
Yeah. Cute,
isn't he?
Yeah.
When he gets to be real size,
he'll make me look thin.
That'll never happen.
[laughter]
You know,
I was thinkin'.
I could put a phone
line for you in here.
It'd be
your own place.
Bo's and my place.
Bo, you got a problem
if Logan stays
in your room for a while?
He says it's cool.
He did?
One thing, though.
Please don't
give him any people food.
He's got a fizzy stomach.
[soft growling]
All right.
You have
your own zip code.
[Bo panting]
[soft whimper]
[panting loudly]
I feel guilty
about this, but I...
I think I'm actually gonna
feel relieved when he's dead.
You need to trust that
there's a life as yourself.
Not as a dark seed
waiting to sprout
in my father's trail.
I'm not sure what
I'm capable of anymore.
Whether I like or not,
I am his daughter.
It sure is good
to see you here,
Mr. McQueen.
Well, it's good
to be seen anywhere.
And no one knows about it.
It's our little secret.
Damn!
Well. It looks great.
I want to tell you
somethin' I haven't said
in about a year.
Thank you, Davey,
I took her out
a couple of times.
She still runs
like a scalded dog.
The trophies are in the trunk.
Trophies?
You mean you had
it in competition?
Logan!
I got a carburetor
that ain't carburatin'.
Well. You look different.
Youlook different.
I mean, uh...
you got a jacket on.
You're out of uniform.
I'm a detective now.
I'm proud of you, kid.
Thank you, sir.
Listen, I could use some
advice on a case I'm doing
from a fellow detective.
I ain't no detective.
It's turned serial.
It's two female victims.
Both car bombings.
The case is about
to blow wide open.
I'm listening.
[Radio Host] You're tuned
to Miami's best talk.
And today we're taking
about these car bombings.
Now, look, the police say these incidents are unrelated,
that there's
no reason to panic.
I don't know about
you folks, but, I mean,
I'm not buying this.
I'm thinking serial killer.
[Logan]
He wanted to know if
I'd had any dreams.
Tells me he's having
dreams about women
and fires of hell,
car bombs.
He says that he sees
the face of the man
responsible.
[Woman caller]
I'm ridin' the bus.
I'm not gonna
get in no car
while this guy is out
there blowin' women up.
[Radio Host] Now, hold on. First of all, what makes you think this is a guy? Huh?
Women are equally capable of inflicting pain and sorrow, lady.
Welcome to the nineties. Don in Coral Gables, you're on Miami's best talk.
[Male caller]
Has everyone
forgotten Biscayne
and what happened
there five years ago?
♪♪ [blues]
Sorry about his breath.
This should help, though.
Not now. Go away.
Could I at least ask
the question first?
No, thanks.
Winston won't talk
to anybody but you.
So what?
What's happened to you?
What's happened?
What's happened is I feel
no obligation to you
or your fellow
police officers.
You see, they took away
my badge and my name.
Well, the captain
says he'll pay you.
25 years of pension
they took away from me.
So you'll do it?
I'll think about it.
[gate slams closed]
♪♪ [opera]
[buzzer]
[gate opens]
[turns music off]
What? Is that
for me?
Here's your mail.
Thank you.
Wagner. Wagner.
Big stuff.
Why did they move you
to Sebastian's cell?
That's the way it goes.
Next man down...
gets moved in here.
You're the next man
to walk?
Well, I'm paying
ultimate retail
in very short time.
I guess I'll be, uh...
seeing your friend
Sebastian.
No, I doubt that.
Every one of my victims
had a more beautiful death
than any single thing
any one of them ever
did in their entire life!
Trust me.
You wanted to tell me
something about your dreams.
You went to school,
right?
Yes.
Well, obviously,
then you understand
that everything
has a price.
What's your price?
Two things.
Prisoner here,
Ernie Haflin.
He gets released.
He's only got
two months to go.
And then, uh...
...my daughter
comes to see me.
I'm not sure I can grant
all those requests.
You give me nothing...
I give you...nothing.
I don't understand.
Just tell the police
what it is I want.
I'll even give you
a preview of my dream.
The killer leaves
a little calling card...
at every scene.
Correct?
I don't know.
You will.
Now, if you'll excuse me.
I have another meeting.
Those are copies of the calling
cards found at the crime scene.
What else didn't
you show me, Mr. Higgs?
The Captain wanted
you to see Winston
without knowing
any of the inside
details. He wanted
to make sure
that Winston's dreams
were legit.
Here, you want to see
the rest of the file?
You might wanna take
a look at these.
Oh.
All the bombings took place
within an 8-mile radius.
What the hell kind
of device did he use?
I'm still waiting
on the lab test.
In other words,
you don't know nothin'.
Who's gonna contact
the daughter?
Winston insists
that youdo it.
I haven't been paid yet
for my conversation with
the Prince of Darkness.
You will be.
The Captain says he'll
throw in an extra $500
to talk to the daughter.
Make it 7.
I have to get a haircut.
Thanks a lot.
She's great.
[chuckles]
Hi.
I'm--
I thought your wife
was coming, too.
No. Just-- Just me.
Come on in.
We'll do it over here.
Oh, why not?
You're not afraid, are you?
Not yet.
You won't feel much.
Well, that's too bad,
'cause, you know,
I like to feel something.
Don't you like
to feel something?
Sit.
I only do arms,
backs, and chests.
No privates, no legs.
Infections are too risky.
How did you get
interested in this?
It's a hobby.
[electric needle buzzes]
I think we have a
misunderstanding.
I'm here to talk
to you about your father.
My what?
Your father.
Who sent you?
The police.
[takes off gloves]
Get out.Sorry?
Get out!
I'll take that as a no.
Now!
Hi. I'm Bud Dee.
I'm here for you to do me.
You do serpents?
Yeah. Great.
Come on in.
Wait in here.
She'll do your arms
and, you know, chest,
but she doesn't
do private parts
or anything
like that.
Just get out
of here!
Your father
wants to see you.
Do you have a subpoena
or a summons?
No, I don't, I don't
have either one.
Then get the hell out!
[gate closes, bell rings]
♪♪ [classical]
[Prisoner]
Hoo hoo! Hello, baby!
Well.
Back so soon?
It's not
happening.
Excuse me?
It's not happening.
They need proof
that your dreams
are true.
It's not happening.
And yet you show up
with a rather lovely
young art student.
They need more information.
[chuckles]
You know, until
my conditions are met...
I'm simply not gonna tell
you about my dreams.
You have to
give me more.
Well, I was right about
the cards, wasn't I?
You were right about
the cards, yes.
But that doesn't help
them catch the bomber.
Haflin walks out.
My daughter comes
here to see me.
That's two.
And then you get to hear
what my dream is.
That's three.
Your daughter does
not want to see you.
That is not her fault.
She would rather have her
fingernails pulled out...
than see you.
You are so sophomoric.
What about Haflin?
They're working on it.
I'm very disappointed
in you, Mr. McQueen.
Well, I'm
used to that.
My mother wanted me
to be a doctor.
I loved my mother.
I didn't likeher.
She sent me down
the road that I took.
It all came out
at my trial.
All kinds of evidence.
And I told the truth.
I'm guilty.
But you know what's odd?
Nobody, not one soul,
ever asked me why.
Don't you find that odd?
I think the doctor called it
a "transference of aggression."
I couldn't kill
my own mother.
I didn't even know
what women looked like.
Why did you pick me?
Because you understand pain.
And we have a bond.
You're wrong.
Oh, no.
If you wanna see your daughter,
you give me some proof,
some information
that I can take
to her and show her
that you tried to help
get this bomber!
There's gonna be
another bombing.
Tonight.
A young woman.
Her first name
begins with an "S."
Susan. Maybe Sandra.
A
Samantha.
You dreamed this?
Check for any female first
names beginning with "S."
Concentrate
on Sandra and Susan.
Those were the two
names he used.
Dan, you got that list?
Yes, sir.
All right.
Anything?
[beeping]
[Radio Reporter]
No leads, no motives,
no suspects
in the city's car bombings.
These were the words
of the police investigators
on hand today when
questioned at City Hall
at a press conference.
Police said that...
[crowd chatter]
I want these people
out of here now.
No! No more questions.
We said everything
we're going to say.
Thank you.
No more questions.
[Radio] We cannot catch a guy
running around with wires and plastic explosives,
crawling under you car.
Come on, people.
Don't worry, Daddy,
I didn't tell Mom anything.
[Dad]
I want it to be
a surprise.
As far as she knows, my party
is a complete surprise.
Okay. Well, get here
as soon as you can.
I will. I'll hurry.
I love you.
I love you,
too, Daddy.
[ominous wordless choir]
[explosion]
I'm tellin' you,
this whole thing is nuts.
I agree with you.
Releasing Haflin,
a convicted felon.
So what?
He only has two months to go.
This woman's name
was Sandra.
Okay, it's
just like he said.
Sandra. How the hell
does he know that?
That's pretty thin,
don't you think?
When I was there, he never
had a single visitor.
He hasn't had
a visitor in 7 years.
His cell is searched
daily.
Mail's clean.
Never calls anybody,
and nobody calls him.
You talked to him
twice.
I think you qualify
as his best friend.
I'm flattered.
Captain Waters says we gotta
give him what he wants.
Oh, he does,
does he?
Yeah.
He says, "What do we
threaten him with?
He's already
on Death Row."
What the hell is
the connection between
Haflin and Winston?
Haflin is
a small-time con artist.
His father knew Winston.
Well, you know now
that Haflin's out,
he's gonna do
somethin' for Winston.
We're on him.
What I need you to do is take
another run at the daughter.
She hates me as much
as she hates her father.
I hated my father
at times growing up,
but I still loved him.
How many women did
your father kill?
[police siren]
[car door closes]
[starts motor]
[chatting]
[Guard]
Open number 2.
Haflin, let's go.
You're out of here.
[buzzer]
The Attorney General
stuck his neck out,
but it's our head
that's in the noose.
I wanna know where
Haflin is every second--
what he eats,
when he sleeps.
This guy could shed some
light on the bombings.
I hope.
Okay.
[Higgs]
Mr. Burton,
I'm very sorry
about what happened
to your daughter.
They give the beginning
detectives the grief
counseling, huh?
Listen, I will do
everything possible
to make sure that
justice is served.
You know how I see it?
Justice?
It would have been just
if my daughter could have
lived her whole life out.
I'd feel a lot
better, detective,
if you had a little
less shoe leather.
Grief counseling!
Shoe leather!
What the hell is that supposed
to mean, "shoe leather"?
I think he's right.
He didn't come here
to see a preacher, you know.
He's lookin'
for a bad-ass cop.
Like you were?
Yeah.
Well, look where
it got you.
I always hated this office.
[knock at door]
[knocking]Dee, open up!
Come on, I know
you're in there.[pounding]
Let's go!
Ernie, is that you?
Who else are
you expecting?
You never know!
You gonna let
your brother in?
You alone?
I doubt it.
You look good.
[stuttering]
You-- You-- You--
You look like crap.
[mocking]
You-- You-- You-- You.
You spend five years
in a crap hole,
you look like crap.
Winston r-really
got you out, huh?
When are you gonna grow up?
How is the old man?
How's he supposed to be?
He's lookin'
at the needle
in a few days.
H-He say anything about me?
You? Yeah, he
sends his regards.
That's it?
His regards?
Nice fish.
That's what he said?
He sends his "regards"?
Nothin' else?
Nothin' else what?
Winston. Nothin'
else about me?
No.
What's he supposed
to say? I mean,
it's hard enough
for him to get a message
to me, you know?
What'd he get you out for?
He's got an errand
he wants done.
I guess
I'm the only guy
he trusts.
What?
Just a little something.
That doesn't concern you.
The department's profiler
thinks Winston's daughter
fits the psychological M.O.
for a serial killer.
Let me ask you a question.
Where Janice works,
does she have
access to chemicals,
stuff to put
together a bomb?
She not only
has access,
she has the expertise
to use it.
You fight southpaw?
Yeah.
But you're right-handed.
Yeah, I've-- I've never
boxed a southpaw before.
Nothin' to it.
Now, see how I made you
move to your left?
Yeah.
What am I doin'?
I'm making you
go left.
Yeah?
You know why?
Why?
Ohh!
You don't wanna come
into that hook, see?
Yeah.
So, you wanna keep
circling this way, right?
Ah! Uh-oh. A punch.
Yeah?
I'm not as fast
as I used to be.
Mm-hmm.I lead with my right,
you just come over the top.
Like this!
Or like that?
Yeah.
Felt good.
Thinking maybe, uh...
I should ask Janice
a couple of questions.
Well...do yourself
a favor.
Stay away from Janice.
Yeah?
Sounds more like you're
doing yourself a favor.
Really?
Yeah!
Ohh!
[Man] Ohh! Ohh!
Listen, kid...
I don't do anybody favors.
[breathlessly]
That was a good punch.
Hi.
Flowers are the earth's
way of smiling.
You read that in a book?
A book by Tibetan monks.
And what's so special
about them?
Because they give
their lives to God?
Can I come in for a second?
I'll leave, you know.
I mean, all you gotta do
is just say go, and...
I'm outta here. Okay?
You're a cop?
Well, I used to be,
yeah.
My name is Logan McQueen.
I don't have
all day, Mr. McQueen.
Yeah, I can see
you're very busy.
You know, they grow
right up through cow manure.
And the more manure,
the stronger
they grow.
If that was the case,
I'd be about 35 feet tall.
[laughs]
Can we sit down,
just for a second?
Well?
Winston knows way too much
about the car bombings.
Details that only the killer
or the police
would know.
And how do you know this?
Well, this is gonna
sound...strange, but...
we were, uh...neighbors.
Uh, I was, uh...
in the same cellblock.
See, when I was
a cop, I...
It's a long story.
I don't have time
for your long story.
Okay.
He's predicting...things.
Details. About victims.
Now, my father is
no psychic. He's psycho.
Maybe he's just
asking for forgiveness.
He is looking for a one-way
ticket back from the dead.
And you don't even know it yet,
but you are playing his game.
I'm not playin' his game.
I'm just tryin' to keep
someone from being killed.
He won't give me
any more information
until you go
to see him.
All the victims were women.
Your age.
All of Winston's victims
were women my age.
He knows something
from somewhere.
I was a junior in college
engaged to be married...
...when the details
started to come out
of who he killed
and how he--
And at first, I didn't--
I didn't believe them
because he was my father.
Midway through
the trial, my--
my fiancé...
broke off our engagement,
and my so-called friends,
they started
to look the other way.
I didn't blame them
because I couldn't
even look at myself.
I started to take on
his guilt.
Except...he didn't
have any guilt.
[sniffles]
[breathes shakily,
sniffles]
[sigh] You know,
my eyes aren't brown,
and my hair comes
out of a bottle.
Got a new nose,
a new name.
I buried her.
So please...
You know, I've walked
through a few mine fields.
Think I stepped on every
mine that was there.
I know about betrayal.
About losing
everything you have.
If you want to talk
sometime...
...about anything...
[beeping]
Uhhh!
[Woman]
He's moving.
Get set.
What do you want?!
I'm out.
Not on parole.
Out.
I got a life
to rebuild here.
Leave me alone.
Wanna tell me what you're
doin' out here for your
friend Winston?
I'm doin' nothin'.
He was a friend
of my father's.
He got me out
as a favor.
Are we supposed to
believe that?
Why ain't you
home havin' babies?
[loud chatter]
[loud chatter in Spanish]
[police sirens]
[loud street chatter]
You got something for us?
Cool.
[indistinct chatter]
Shit. [laughs]
Hey,
check this out.
Hi.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
My money no good?
Your money's fine.
We appreciate it.
Oh, you're gonna
keep it, huh?
That's right.
Whoa.
That was forty dollars'
worth.
I'll come back
next week again
and get forty dollars'
worth from you.
Muscle, take Mr. Haflin
down to number four.
Just...wait here.
Go ahead.
[chuckles]
♪♪ [Blues]
[Logan]
Entrez-vous.
[growls]
Does he bite?
Just cops.
Yeah. I brought
your money.
No, no, no.
I don't take checks.
So, tell me
what happened.
I followed him
into this dive.
And then I had
my little altercation.
Well, great. So we just
get a search warrant,
go in, and search
the place.
I don't think that'll
do any good, Mr. Higgs.
I think he went in,
got what he wanted,
and got out.
We've gone over every
inch of the crime scene
about fifty times now.
I don't think these
bombs are personal.
I don't think
they're about revenge.
I think they're
about somethin' else.
What?
Don't you see
the similarity between
the Winston killings
and the bombings?
Now, that was about being
somebody.
I think this guy
wants to see his name
in the paper.
[Bo pants loudly]
Where you been?Ohh!
You-- Are you crazy?
I've been worried
about you.
I did that thing
for Winston.
[laughs]
I got you!
[laughing]
Whoa.
That's Winston's
stash, Dee.
His stash?
It's all gotta be
worth a quarter mill.
Why do you got it?
It's for his daughter.
He thinks she's gonna
come visit him before
he takes the needle.
Like an inheritance?
Yeah.
Only she ain't gettin' it.
Mmmhh.
You're gonna cross him?
I got other plans.
He trusted you.
We're gonna get
away from here.
You and me,
little brother.
Yeah.
Yeah, great.
Right.
Yes. [chuckles]
[Radio] A spokesperson for the Police Department
[phone rings] scientific investigation division, has said that
everything is being done to expedite the investigation.
The spokesperson would not comment at this time
what similarities, if any...
[Machine] Bo's place.
I'm not here, but Bo is,
and he's listening.
[beep]
Logan, this
is Janice Lynn.
I just saw the news.
I need to talk.
We need to meet.
[Bo growling]
[beep] They're blond,
and they're professional.
And according
to my little pin drop
on the map, folks,
all these bombings
are taking place
in about an 8-mile radius.
We'll go to Louis who used
to be a police officer
up in Carol City.
Louis, you're
on Miami's best talk.
Yeah, I'm an ex-cop, and I'll tell you the problem
is all these silly laws and judges
gettin' in the police officers' way.
My day, you stopped a guy, you searched the car.
Now you gotta call a judge to ask a guy what his name is.
That's the problem with everything now.
Okay, enough
of the polite talk.
I didn't come here
for a date.
Oh, that's a relief,
you know, because
I didn't wanna have
a date with you.
Besides, the food
isn't any good here.
Are you having me
followed?
No, but I could.
Somebody has been asking
about me down at the lab.
Human Resources says there's
a background check in progress.
If it's your cop friends,
I want you
to tell them
to stop.
Oh, I could tell 'em.
Wouldn't help.
And I want you
to stay away, too.
I will.
Okay, I will.
Do.
Mmm.
This is on the house.
Not now.
Not Now.
Oh. Uh...[chuckles,
sets glasses down]
I don't do this.
You don't do what?
You don't drink?
Drink with men.
Why not?
Well, eventually
the conversation
gets around to me,
and when they find out
I'm the daughter of...
Oh. I see.
"Check, please."[pouring wine]
The honest ones do.
The others, they can't
wait to tell their friends.
[chuckles]
Yeah.
It's important to have
somebody to talk to.
Somebody that--
Well, I had a--
I had a partner.
He was like
a father to me.
The only man
I ever trusted.
He betrayed me.
Forgiveness is hard for you.
Oh. At last we have
something in common.
It's gonna break my heart if
you two don't order something.
Well, we wouldn't
want to do that.
What? Order something
or break my heart?
Either.
Oh! [chuckles]
[crickets chirping]
[chuckles]
I had fun.
Oh. Well...
I had funner.
[both chuckle]
I think I actually
was laughing.
Oh, you laughed.
Yeah.
It's not like me.
Oh, maybe it's, uh,
it's the real you.
Thank you for making
sure I got home safely.
It was very sweet of you
to go out of your way.
It wasn't out of my way.
Yeah. You-- You live
at Trumpet's.
Yeah, I do, I...
Well, it was a little
out of my way, but...
it wasn't a...
a lot out of my way.
Okay.
Yeah.
You know, I have a pretty
good bottle of wine.
We could go out
on my patio and talk,
and I could laugh
some more, and...
Laugh. Um...
wine.
Patio [chuckles]
That's...
I haven't done this
in a long time. I'm...
...you know, rusty.
You know.
I'm not very good at it.
Okay. Good night.
Ho! Whoa!
No, hold it!
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
Don't-- Don't--
Don't, uh...
Don't let me...
talk you out of it.
Mmm. I promise
I won't, uh,
I won't-- I won't
rush you into things.
Oh.
Rush.
Hmm.
Well, if you have
a violent urge
to rush,
[laughs]
go right ahead.
Hey, there's wine
in the kitchen...
Mm-hmm...
glasses in the cupboard.
You can chill them
in the freezer.
I'll be right back.
All right.
Wine is in the freezer.
The glasses
are in the cupboard.
You put them in the
freezer. And then I'm...
Oh, what the hell,
I'll find it.
[wind chimes]
♪♪ [ominous]
Janice.
Janice!
[car engine starts up]
[car speeds off]
[police radio]
...requesting backup.
[Dispatcher]
We're sending backup.
[Woman] I've been
through that area.
Mark everything,
what? Series "C."
Why do you think
she ran?
I don't know.
Maybe she got
bored with me.
What were you
guys doing here?
We were talking!
She mention she was
under psychiatric care?
What the hell's
the matter with you?
If Winston was your father,
you'd be out baying
at the moon.
She has to talk
to somebody.
Yeah, well, her doctor
tells me she's having
psychotic episodes.
Seeing burning bodies.
What the hell
ever happened
to doctor-patient
confidentiality?
Listen, she had the means,
she had the expertise.
She is not the bomber!
You don't
know that.
The hell I don't!
Look at that!
Look at it!
It's so obvious
that it's a paid job,
even you
could see it!
I've been
waiting for a break
on this case for weeks.
Okay, maybe her psychotic
episodes are real! Huh?
Did you ever
think of that?
The daughter of
Lucifer's Right Hand
carries on
the family tradition.
It'll play great
in the press!
Ohh!
Sorry.
I'm gonna need
some time.
Oh, this is gonna
take some time.
Gotta get all this
evidence sorted out.
How much time?
48 hours.
You know what I
recommend for the lip?
What's that?
Salt and ice.
Don't forget
the tequila.
Where in the hell
is your brain?
We should be on our way
to Mexico by now.
It serves my purpose.
It's all a game.
A game?
You are out
of your mind!
Just like Winston is!
You're sounding
just like our father.
He didn't like
Winston, either.
I didn't like it when
he talked like that.
I fixed him!
Maybe you should think
about gettin' rid of her car.
I didn't
bring it here.
Do it for me?
Don't be scared.
[car starts up]
He's wacko.
He was in prison.
♪♪ [La Donna è mobile]
What is that?
This is a jazz joint,
but I can listen
to the classics
when I'm closed.
Rigoletto.
I just like the sound of it.
It's pure passion
and expression.
Here, this book
that came with the CD.
It explains all about it.
I never read it myself.
Coffee.
♪♪[Rigoletto continues]
We are alike.
I with my tongue.
He with a dagger.
I am a man who mocks.
And he is a man who slays.
If I am evil...
you have done my bidding.
Oh, such love.
My daughter.
You are my life.
If you have a secret,
let me share it.
If I do not ever
speak to you again...
...I will...kill.
♪♪[Rigoletto continues] [indistinct P.A. announcement]
You forgot somethin'.
Hey.
My daughter!
She ain't comin'!
Well. Then we're back
to the old arithmetic
again.
Let's talk about opera.
The bomber's
calling card.
[laughs]It adds up to "Rigoletto."
Mr. McQueen
lands on the green.
You wanna hear about
my latest dream?
No!
I wanna talk about
who's responsible.
The girl is blond.
She works in a lab.
She's got a name.
Her name is Lynn.
What's the matter?
Did I offend you
with what I said?
[chuckles]
You're talking about Janice.
Janice?
Janice, your daughter.
That's right.
She changed everything.
She changed her hair,
she changed her face.
She changed her name.
Her name is Janice Lynn.
What?
She's the next to go!
What are you
talkin' about?
I'm talkin' about
who is responsible!
You hear me very,
very clearly.
Dee Haflin!
He wanted a father.
I needed somebody
to trade information
with the police with.
Just so I could see my
daughter one more time
before I died,
for God's sake.
I know I broke
her heart.
How'd you communicate?
Bar codes. CDs.
CDs would come to me,
and they had bar codes
on the front of 'em.
We had our own alphabet.
I knew exactly
who he was gonna kill.
I knew when he was
gonna kill 'em.
I knew where.
What else?
What else?!
Take the man's life!
It's rather obvious.
You remember how
Rigolettoends?
The daughter--
they find her in a bag
all cut up into little pieces.
[crow cawing]
Ohh...
[Officers]
Go! Go! Go!
Go! Go!
Go, guys! Go! Go!
[indistinct shouting,
chatter]
Upstairs!
We got
a cold one here.
[flies buzzing]It's Haflin.
[Officer]
Got a body in the front.
Watch your backs!
Get another inspector.
There's jewelry and money.
[indistinct shouting]
[clattering]
Detective Higgs!
Second floor!
What's up?
Check it out.
Well, this makes
the kid brother
the lead dog.
And Winston's gonna
be the one he's gonna
try to impress.
Hey! Hey,
now where you goin'?
Hey! Logan!
Where you goin' now?!
Logan!
[indistinct chatter]
He's always doing
this to me.
[water dripping]
[officers talking]
You first.
You see anything
under there?
Nothin'.
But that don't mean
there's no rats down there.
We can tell
Higgs we looked.
Oh, we--
we did.
They'll be leaving soon.
[Logan]
I'm telling you,
Janice is not a suspect.
She's the next victim.
Now we've gotta find her.
Okay, Higgs?
[sigh]
They found Janice's
car.
Little Havana.
Stripped it down.
The only prints that
were identifiable were
the Haflin brothers'
and Janice's.
This kid is playing
a deadly game
of hide and seek.
Your problem is gettin' home
without gettin' tagged.
What'd you just say?About what?
About the game?
I said your problem
is gettin' home
without gettin' tagged.
That's it.
Why...Why, Charlie
used to say that.
He'd say, "When you
can't find it, look down.
It's right
in front of you."
[moans]
Shh! Shh!
[muffled attempt
to talk]
Shh!
It sucks havin' to be
awake for this, doesn't it?
I'm sorry.
Shhh!
Shhh.
You don't have to. You--
You can just let me go,
and I-- I won't tell.
I promise.
No, I do have to.
That's how he's gonna know.
Who?
Your father.
Ta-da.
What does this got
to do with him?
He's why I've been
doin' the bombs--
to prove to him
I could get away with it.
He didn't think
I could.
Did he want you
to kill me?
That's myidea.
[Woman on radio]
He wanted to marry me.
[Second woman]
Now, just listen
to me a minute.
Just hush up. Just listen
to me for one minute.
[snoring]
[radio chatter continues]
[Second woman]
You are not
an independent person.
You need to get
yourself independent
right now.
I want him
to marry me!
[snoring] That's all I want!
Just listen
to yourself
for a minute.
It's time for me
to give hima lesson.
He-- [laughing]
He-- He tricked me!
All he cared about...
All he ever cared about
was
you...
...ou!
Shhhh! I'm not crazy.
I'm not crazy.
I'm just kiddin'.
I'll, um...
I'll go see him now.
No, no, no, no, no...
No, no, no, no, no.
No, no. I did it
all for him.
He-- He-- He--
He was my mentor.
He said I could
be somebody.
[chuckles]
People respect fear.
He said that they would
call me master of the game,
but he didn't care, really.
That was just a lie.
A lie. Lie.
No, I'm sure. I'm sure
that's not right.
I'm sure.
That's a lie.
You're just like him.
He's gonna get exactly
what he wants.
You're goin' to him...
piece by piece.
[thump, footsteps]
We're not alone.
Finally the game
gets interesting.
It's all right.
You all right,
kid?
Yeah.
Huh?
Logan.
[Dee]
Logan!
Logan?
I b-b-bet you can't
catch me. [laughs]
Come on, Logan!
Oh, yeah!
[grunting]
[crashing]
Oh, you lost your gun.
You can't come up here
without your gun.
The hell I can't.
[clinking]
Kaboom!
Ha ha ha ha!
Ha ha ha ha![clattering]
Where's the ball?
Ha ha ha ha!
[clattering]Oh! Run!
[giggling maniacally]
No, don't.
Don't come up.
Don't. No, no, no.
Don't-- Don't come up!
Aaah! Aaahh!
Aaahh! Aah!
Aah! Aaahh!
Aaaahhh!
Get away!
Get away from me.
Get away from me!
No! No!
Uuhh! Ohh!
I, uh...
wrote this for her.
I tried to...
...I don't know,
write it all down.
Tried to explain it. I--
I don't know that I even...
can explain it
to myself.
You know
I can't take that.
[indistinct prisoner shouting]
I just, uh...
I'd like her to know
that I loved her.
That's all.
I'm afraid it's...
late.
I'm goin' down soon.
There are, uh...
are not gonna be
any friendly faces.
I wonder...
would you...please
be there for me?
Yes.
[buzzer]
[Woman on radio]
And according to a spokesman
for the Mayor's Office,
a vote will be forthcoming.
And in other news...
He came in drunk
while I was closin'.
I watered his
drinks, but, uh...
smells like
a long-term bender
to me.
[Radio]
...was executed
at 12:01 this morning.
Ray Earl Winston had been
on Death Row for over...
Come on, guy.
Oh, Logan.
Come on.
Logan...you
gotta talk to me.
You gotta.
I can't stand it.
All right, Bo.
Here you go.
[panting heavily]
Logan?
Logan.
You gotta forgive me.
[tearfully]
I can't stand it.
Uh...Logan?
Are you out
of breath, Logan?
[mumbling]
Oh. You're
there, Logan.
Well, Sebastian.
I've read the book
four times now.
I'm doing
all right on balance.
But I'm still working
on forgiveness.
Thank you.
That's just what
I wanted to say.
[seagulls squawking]
Well.
What a fantastic job
you've done of healing.
[laughs]
You sure know how
to flatter a girl.
The prison sent, um...
sent me a letter
from my father.
Yes.
No, I can't forget what
he was or what he did.
Forgetting and forgiveness
are very far apart.
Should I read it?
Well...
I think that's
something that
you'll have to decide
all by yourself.
[tearing paper]
[chuckles]
[sigh]
[Sebastian]
Perhaps someday
that will resonate within.
When it does,
touch one so that
others may be touched.