(subtle jazz music)
- Hey Mickey, you should be a comedian.
(laughter)
(subtle rock music)
- Hey Bernie, how's he doing?
- [Mickey] Yeah, I had
a really good day today.
I woke up, I ran the marathon,
got my balls pierced,
got my tongue pierced,
got a couple of tattoos on my forehead
and uh, uh, I still at
time at the end of the day
for a root canal job.
Uh, I joined the cellular craze too.
You know, they got these
new phones that vibrate,
so I bought three of them actually.
One, I use for calling,
one, I stuck up my ass,
one, I got wrapped around my dick.
Here's my number, let it ring a long time.
You got to hand it to Chris Reed
for putting so much
emphasis on spinal research,
but I, I don't know.
I mean, is it a smart idea
to compete in the sport as an amateur
where there's a uh,
ambulance at the finish line?
Oh, what's the matter, sir?
Don't you understand English?
- Actually, I speak perfect
English, you're just not funny.
(laughter)
- [Mickey] That's my
time, ladies and gentlemen
and I also want to say thank you.
I've had a good time.
Get off me, will ya?
Who the fuck is this guy?
Out of here.
Ah, fuck you.
(subtle rock music)
- Hey Mickey, you should be a comedian.
- Hey Bernie, blow me.
(laughter)
- Sell it, baby!
- Just come to the plate with me.
- We got investors.
- What is the bottom line?
- We have investors and people closing!
- I'm not saying don't
pay your medical bills.
- Or can you not close
your eyes in a hurricane?
- But if I double your money in a month.
- Can you close or can you not close?
- Now we decide if you piss standing up,
or if you piss sitting down.
- Wake up.
- Huh, huh?
- Getting into bed with
Mickey, as they say,
is so safe, you don't even need a condom!
What are you worried about?
You're making money!
- Get your checkbook, I'll hold.
- Hey, you saw that, you saw it?
Good for you, pink slip!
- Hi Audrey.
- Fuck off.
- So what the fuck's going on, Mickey?
- [Mickey] Watch your language.
- Yeah, I'm gonna shove this phone
so far up your fucking ass,
your mouth will have a dial tone.
- [Mickey] Why can't you drive her?
- Blow me!
- I asked one favor.
- Yeah.
- Well, why can't you just
do me one favor as a friend?
- The only way you're gonna
close a deal, all right?
You gotta be aggressive!
- Fuck you, Mickey.
- There has to be some log,
it's harassment in the workplace.
I'm not gonna take this from you.
- You're gonna do this
for me, you have to.
- No, I'm not going to do it for you.
What?
Is this supposed to scare me?
- Do you ever see giraffes fuck?
They don't stop until they've done it!
- Why don't you take your gerbil, and uh.
- Did this guy just, did
you just call me a pussy?
- Yeah, I just called him a pussy!
- Take the livestock with you, all right?
- Livestock, nice.
- Fine, I used to sell a lot
when I was in Boy Scouts.
- Oh yeah, I'm sure you
did a lot of cookies.
So you were in the Girl Scouts?
- Hello Mister.
- I'm not doing it.
- [Audrey] Yes you are!
- No, don't.
- You're late.
- Audrey said 10 o'clock, it's 10 o'clock.
What are you talking about?
- Have you ever heard the expression,
if you're not 10 minutes
early, you're late?
- No, I haven't.
Have you ever heard the expression
that if you want to get
to where you're going,
call a tow truck?
- Francis!
- Excuse me.
- Of course.
- One, two, three.
- [Dad] Francis!
Your sister, she's on the phone.
- Can you open the doors please?
And pull that lever up.
- This?
- Yes.
Hit the top orange button on the left.
- Thanks for the warning.
- And then the red button
on the left, please.
Can you step on the ledge?
I go on backwards.
Okay.
Just hold the door.
- Like this?
Jesus Christ.
Yeah, this is a lot better.
- Just close the door.
- How are your nuts?
- Fine, thanks.
How are yours?
(whimsical music)
- Stop sign.
- [Mickey] Yeah, I see the stop sign.
What about it?
- Stop at it.
Don't roll through it.
Where'd you learn how to drive?
- What's her problem?
Like you don't know what
I'm talking about, right?
- Stop sign.
- [Mickey] I see the stop sign
and I'm going to stop the car.
- Stop at it.
- [Mickey] I'm stop,
you can't feel the fucking car stopping?
- [Sally] I almost flew out of my chair.
- I'm going to go now.
- [Sally] No, no, no.
- [Mickey] Which way do you mean?
- [Sally] Just turn right here.
Just pay attention, would ya?
- [Mickey] I was paying attention.
- To the road.
Right down there where
the people are standing.
Easy over the bump.
- [Mickey] Look at this.
What's happening here?
There's your picture.
- I am.
- [Francis] I'll get the
door, you get the straps.
- Uh no, I'll get the door.
Come on, one side, let me through.
Come on, look out.
Come on, get back will ya?
Come on, this thing's dangerous.
Hey, I warned ya.
Here it comes.
Behold.
- Hey Jack.
Oh uh, Jack Walker, this is.
- Mickey Schwinn.
- Welcome, Jack.
- To meet you, nice.
I'm going to go find
the handicapped entrance
and uh, look inside, okay?
- Listen, I'll take it from here.
Why don't you find the moron entrance
and come and watch the show?
- Ready, Sally?
- Right on, Jack.
- [Reporter] I'm here at the University
and the crowd you see behind me
is here to welcome Dr. Sally
Kelly back to the University.
Dr. Kelly is the world famous
physicist and astronomer
whose book, I Need My Space,
is the number one seller
on the New York Times.
Can I help you?
- I work with Dr. Kelly, we work together.
My name is Mickey Schwinn.
- Oh, that's great, sir.
Could you just step away?
I'm doing an interview for television.
- So am I.
- [Sally] So, Audrey says
you're in a comedy show.
- [Mickey] Yeah, I do open mic.
- [Sally] To the left.
- Adios.
- [Sally] Look uh, thanks for helping me.
Maybe I'll owe you dinner or something.
- Yeah, okay.
- [Sally] Sorry about the leg thing.
- Don't worry about it.
Yeah, sure, bye.
(phone ringing)
- Hello?
- What's the matter, you
got a dick in your mouth?
- Mickey, how did it go?
What happened?
- What a cunt, that's what happened.
- Were you mean to her, Mickey?
Mickey!
You bastard!
(phone ringing)
- Don't fucking ask me
if I hung up on you,
'cause you know I did.
- [Sally] Hello, Mickey.
It's Sally here.
Sally Kelly.
I wanted to thank you
for driving me today.
- You did already.
- [Sally] Well, I'd still
like to take you out to dinner
and thank you.
- Why don't you send over a pizza here
and we'll call it quits?
- All right, what address?
Uh huh, and what toppings?
Drink?
Second choice?
Fine, I'll have it delivered
right over and thanks again.
What a prick.
- How are we doing today?
- I was supposed to call, wasn't I?
- [Jack] Sally, can I get you anything?
Glass of water?
- No, I'm okay.
What's up?
- Your book tour.
I strongly suggest you reconsider flying.
- Okay, I'll think about it, no.
- Who's going to drive you, Sally?
- What do you mean, who
is going to drive me?
Joseph is going to drive me.
He should be back from
his stupid funeral by now.
- Sally, there was no funeral.
He doesn't want to come back.
He quit.
- Why?
Jo likes me.
- Joseph doesn't like you.
- Oh.
Give him more money.
- Sir.
Yeah, sir.
Look, sir.
I tell you what, you let
me know when you're through
and let me know when
it's my turn, all right?
Yes.
Look at your close, look
at the closing statement.
Look at it and look
where it says net worth.
That's all you want to look at.
Jesus.
- Oh, Mr. Schwinn.
- Yard sale?
- Yeah, yard sale.
More like a client who dropped
by to review his portfolio,
didn't like what he saw.
You know how much money I
made for this guy last year?
- [Mickey] No.
- Tell you, $308,000,
but because I said it
was going to be $400,000,
he does this to my desk.
Greed, it's the deadliest of all the sins.
- Yeah Trent,
I got a guy who sent in
$20,000 for silver to go up.
It went up.
Copper to go down, it went down.
He's got $3,000 left in his account.
What's happening?
- Is he outside?
- No, he's in Arkansas.
- That's good.
- [Mickey] Hey Trent,
Trent, you're dotting the
I's and crossing the T's?
- Yep, but this is probably
a mistake in accounting.
- You're accounting.
- Yeah, I am accounting and
you're being taken care of.
- I ain't talking about me.
- Well listen to this, okay?
I am as blue blooded and
all American and God-fearing
as any businessman in this country, okay?
But I'm the little guy,
I'm not a big conglomerate, all right?
This company works on my
blood, sweat, and tears.
- I don't give a flying fuck
about your blood, sweat, and tears, okay?
You call this guy, you talk to him,
and then I'm going to talk
to him after you talk to him.
- Yeah, I'll call him.
- When?
- I gotta get my phone
fixed first, it's broken.
- Call this guy.
Um, I'll leave the file
on your uh, your desk.
Call him, I'm not kidding around.
- I'll call him, all right?
You go do what you do,
just bringing money in.
- [Mr. Costello] Hey, anybody out there?
Come on, let's go.
So, you ready for your report card?
- I want my own spot.
- I know you do.
- I think I'm ready.
- Majority to one.
- Mr. Costello, am I wasting my time?
- Yeah, no.
I mean, no, no.
It's not.
You see, Mickey, there's
something missing, you know?
I mean, I don't know.
I mean, I saw a sack the other night
and this guy, right?
He was kind of uh,
you know,
I don't know.
Oh, he was doing this thing, you know?
And he was,
you know,
I don't know, guess you had to be there.
- You sure you were?
- You ain't ready.
I'm going to take a pass.
- So what do I do?
I just beat it around
town, doing the standup,
doing the open mic and you
tell me when I'm ready,
that how it works?
- Yeah, yeah.
Open mic, yeah.
- And you think I'm funny?
- Yeah, yeah.
I mean, you know, you
keep doing it, you know,
the mic, and the, yeah.
- Mr. Costello, thanks for
your time and the pep talk.
- Hey, all right.
- I don't know what you guys do in there,
but I wouldn't go in there right now.
- Why?
- There's a lot of guys in
green jackets that say sheriff.
- Have a nice weekend.
- What the fuck happened?
- We got shut down.
- Why?
- I don't know.
- Who are they looking for?
(overlapping speaking)
- Hey, hey Mickey man,
I saw you on TV with some
chick on wheels, man,
on the news, man, what's
up, what's that about?
- You saw that?
How'd I look?
(engine revving)
- [Sally] God dammit, you made me,
do you know that there's nobody there?
- I'm sorry.
- What are you, a stupid idiot?
- Save sorry for your boyfriend.
(upbeat rock music)
- Hello?
- [Sally] That homosexual prick, Joseph,
just left me on the side of the road.
- Where are you?
- [Sally] I'm at the observatory,
I was picking up some stuff.
- Well, did you call the
Automobile Association of America?
- [Sally] Look, you don't
want to come and pick me up?
- No, no, no, I'm not saying that.
I'm, I'm not saying that
I don't want to come over.
Look hold on, I'll take care of it.
(phone ringing)
- Mickey here.
- [Audrey] Mickey, I need a favor.
Mickey?
Mickey!
- Yes?
- [Audrey] Look, it's Sally.
She just called, she's
hysterical, she's stranded.
Where are you?
- [Mickey] I'm in my car, Audrey.
I'm on the fucking 405.
I haven't moved more than
nine inches in the last hour.
They stopped traffic,
I'm in the middle of a fucking
boom box gang war, okay?
That's where I am.
- Well, can you just get
over there and help her out?
- Why don't you?
- Mickey, I'm on a fucking
bust job, for Christ's sake.
I've got a DUI, he said he needs help.
Mickey!
- Where is she?
- No keys?
- Nope.
- Okay.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, 30 minutes, all right.
Are you sure you can't hot wire the car?
- Yeah, I'm, I'm sure I don't
know how to steal a car.
- So you ever going to
ask me what happened?
- No.
- About four years ago,
I was celebrating my important book deal
and it was raining really hard
and I had brought my new
Mercedes convertible over.
- I'm sorry, did you
say you were a doctor?
What a fucking racket that is?
How's business?
- Good, I'm uh,
just starting to get ready for a book tour
and my publisher's sending
me out for a book signing
and local lectures at local campuses.
You know how it is?
- Do you have a private jet or something?
- No, I'm taking the van.
- Who are you going with?
- [Sally] Francis, my nurse and Audrey.
- Audrey's gonna flake,
so that leaves you and Florence
Nightingale out on the road.
- Florence doesn't drive.
How about you?
- [Mickey] Oh, you know,
the business with me
is like gangbusters, phones
literally off the hook
and the comedy thing,
fuck, I mean, you know.
(upbeat music)
- [Sally] The cosmological
expansion due to, did you get it?
- I'll be honest with you, all right?
I don't get it.
I mean,
how many people do you know
who don't have physics degrees?
- Do you understand, Francis?
- I get it.
- [Sally] See?
- Yeah, do you now?
- Yeah.
- All right, then explain it to me.
Tell it to me like you're
telling it to a 10 year old.
- Okay.
- What is it?
- I can't explain it, I'm hungry.
- [Mickey] Okay so the answer
is, you're hungry, let's stop.
That's the explanation
I'm looking for, right?
Is that it?
I see by the captain's log
that we'll be checking in,
we'll be getting to the
hotel long before dark.
Check-in and we're going to eat, okay?
You can't wait until then?
Crawl in the back and
have a fucking banana.
Nice hotel.
- Hello?
- [Mickey] How are you?
- Good, how you doing?
- Dr. Sally Kelly.
- Okay.
- Sir, you're in the wrong hotel.
This is the Stilton, you're
looking for this Stilton Suites.
This happens all the time.
- Oh, does it?
- And it says a convention town.
- You got suites?
- Yeah, we do, we have suites here.
- Stilton, right?
- Correct.
- Hey look, you guys
been pulling this crap
for thousands of years.
Give me the rooms and
stop screwing around.
- Sir, we're fully booked.
This is a convention town.
- So what?
- I want to help you out though.
- You see what I got over my shoulder?
Okay?
Get on the fucking phone right
now and get me two rooms.
I made a mistake.
I'm not Superman, okay?
- [Sally] Oh, I know you're not,
but do you have to prove it?
What was so difficult
about reserving a room in a real hotel?
- It wasn't difficult, I
fucked it up really easily.
It's not my field.
- Do you see that teepee?
- You see that vacancy sign, huh?
What can I tell you, Sally?
This is a convention
town, I'm checking us in.
(knocking)
- Yes, come inside.
Just open the door, come inside.
- Hey.
- Hi.
- Yeah, you got a phone call
from, from the hotel, right?
The guy coming over with the
broad in the wheelchair, right?
So give me two rooms, right?
- Okay, so I got only one room.
- What are you talking about?
Didn't you tell him you had two rooms?
- Yeah, before I told,
when he did call me,
I told him I got two rooms,
but when you come down all you
had before, I rent the room.
- What the fuck is that?
- This American business.
- What?
- American business?
This is American business?
- Yeah, who come first, we
do the business, that's it.
- The fuck?
How many rooms you got?
- Okay, you how many people, sir?
- There are three, there are three people,
there's the girl, the nurse,
then there's me, two rooms.
Now you're talking.
- Okay, I get right the one room,
you can stay in the one
room, I don't mind, sir.
- I mind,
I don't want to stay in
the fucking room with them.
Give me two rooms.
- No, I got only one room, sir.
Please don't do like that, please.
- Let's go, how much?
- This is just unbelievable.
- I'd believe it if I were you.
- Oh great, there's even a step.
- There is not.
See, what are you talking about?
Hey so listen, if you get
into trouble or anything,
send me up a smoke signal.
- How?
- How the fuck the should I know?
Matches or something, okay?
Am I fired?
- Not yet.
- Goodnight Sally.
Goodnight Sally.
I'm not going anywhere
until the door closes.
I'm going to hear the lock, okay?
(knocking)
- Francis.
Who is it?
- [Man] Security, homeland security.
There's somebody in your car.
- Mickey, will you knock it off?
Are you out of your mind?
- [Man] Ma'am, there's
somebody in your car.
- What's he look like?
What's he look like?
- He's curled up in a ball,
he's got wild, crazy curly hair.
- It's okay, we know him,
he's just looking after some
equipment, thanks, good night.
- What do you want me to do?
- Scram, would ya?
- Hey, how'd you sleep?
Great hotel, right?
Just like the Stilton.
- How would you know?
- What do you mean, how would I know?
I slept here last night.
Hey uh, my shower is so fucked up.
I, I need to take a, you know,
I'm gonna use your shower.
- No, no, listen, there's a lot of stuff.
It's messy in there,
there's a lot of stuff.
No, go, go, go shower
somewhere else, okay Mickey?
- Your hair looks good.
I grew up with five sisters,
what the fuck you
worried about, all right?
I've seen it all.
(water running)
(subtle piano music)
Good picture, you're not too bad looking.
Can I go now?
- Sure you can find your way back?
- I'll put it on the top of my to do list.
- Hi.
Who can I make this out to?
Okay Jason.
See you at the lecture tonight?
- [Comedian] That was a very
touching movie, wasn't it?
I had one question about that movie.
How did he wipe his butt
when he did number two?
I was like.
- Can I get you something?
- Yeah, you know any jokes
that nobody's heard in the
whole world that are funny?
- Tons.
- Who should I make this out to?
- To Billy, please.
- Okay, Billy.
Well, I hope I get to see
you at the lecture tonight.
- Oh, I'm Ernie..
Billy's my wife's name, she'll be there.
I got her a telescope for our anniversary
on account of her interest in your book.
- Well, did you read it?
- I tried to, but I didn't understand it.
My wife tried to explain it to me,
but I don't think she
really gets it either,
but I looked through the telescope.
- Come here a second.
- Well the voice of Mr. Bill came from.
Oh no, not my back.
Hey, hey look, you've been a great crowd.
You haven't been a great
crowd, but thank you anyway.
- Okay, who's next?
From Los Angeles, dude,
the comic stylings of Mickey Schwinn.
(applause)
- Thank you, ladies and gentlemen.
How you doing tonight, okay?
Anybody over here have any
acupuncture done on them?
- Yeah.
- [Mickey] You have, dear?
Worked out for you okay?
Yeah, it did okay for me too but you know,
I'm waiting to get dressed,
they got me alone in the room.
I'm looking at the packs of
needles and take it home,
trying to, gonna try some
cat-a-puncture, okay?
Three minutes later,
the cat's running around
with needles out of his head
and his ass, screaming his head off.
Didn't work out for him too
good and as a matter of fact,
I don't think any of the
pets I've ever had in my life
have ever appreciated what
I tried to do for them.
Chris Reeve.
- In human experience,
this is called the glue
that keeps people together,
that allows them to grow
as individuals for love.
- Where there's an ambulance
at the finish line.
Where are you going?
Okay, yeah, drag her,
just drag her out, okay?
Uh, had a breakthrough
the other day at analysis.
- So you don't need a telescope,
all you have to do is look at your wife.
- Oh.
- How many people
understood what I just said?
Okay, picture this.
- That um, that Chris Reeve joke,
I, I'm a little embarrassed
to say, but I laughed.
- No, I know somebody in a wheelchair,
they're paralyzed from the
waist down, can't move at all.
I guarantee you that they would
laugh too, I guarantee it.
- Two people fall for each other
and there's an explosion of feelings.
This energy can act to
repel the two people
and also attract them.
- So, what do you, what
do you do for laughs?
- Well, right now I'm driving
this scientist around,
this doctor, a book
tour, taking care of her.
You know, maybe you saw
us on TV the other night.
- Who?
- The broad I'm talking
about in a wheelchair.
Now she's really high end,
you know, the one that looks like a model,
except like a model sitting
down all the time, right?
She's got beauty, brains, class,
little tough to deal with,
but she's really, really unbelievable.
She's going to pay for this.
- No she isn't.
- [Sally] Mickey, would you
stay in the lane, please?
I mean, you're drifting
over to the side, come on,
and use your indicator when
you change, that's the law.
- Hey Sally, you ever planning to drive?
No?
'Cause I'd really like
to get in the back seat
with a note pad and take some lessons.
- Yeah, well you could use some lessons.
- Really?
Why don't you drive anyway?
Yeah, you got cars with
buttons and all of that shit,
that could outfit you.
What are you going to do
if I have a heart attack
and I got to go to the hospital?
What are you going to do?
- Nothing.
(upbeat music)
- [Mickey] Stop sign.
(laughter)
Watch the road.
- Okay, I'm watching the road.
- Are you watching the road?
- Are my, are my feet on the pedals?
- Yeah.
Wanna go back and fool
around a little bit?
Look that, watch the road.
- [Sally] It'll be okay.
- [Francis] I hope so.
- What'd I do now?
- I have to go home.
- So?
- So it's not all about you.
- You ever read Freud?
What?
- She's going, we're staying.
- You move around a lot?
- Yes, when I'm not at the hospital,
- Well, when you're at the hospital,
you got an answering machine, right?
- Yes.
- You're gonna check it?
- Sure.
- How could somebody have
four strokes in four years?
- I don't know.
- Hey, look at the bright side, all right?
He's probably good for
another four or five,
before it gets serious.
- Can we not talk about this?
- [Mickey] Hey, aren't you
gonna be in the way back home?
- [Francis] No.
- [Mickey] 'Cause I could
turn around right now.
She gave you a beeper, right?
- No, I don't have a beeper.
- She didn't give you a fucking beeper?
- Are you afraid?
- Yes.
- Mickey, she'll tell
you what she needs, okay?
And look it, you can't do this,
I'll see you later, Sally, anymore.
You have to stay with
her, she can't be alone.
I do things for her, you
know, private things.
- Yes.
- She could do them on
her own, but she doesn't.
- Why?
Why?
- Because I don't know, she's.
- Spoiled, right?
Shit.
(knocking)
- [Sally] Come in.
- [Mickey] Hi.
- Hey.
- I'm going out for about an hour or so.
You catching up on some reading?
- [Sally] Um, I don't have
any work to do tonight.
I'm taking the night off.
- [Mickey] Tired, right?
- [Sally] No, not really.
- You want anything before I go?
- No, I'm fine.
- And this place is gonna
be so filled with smoke.
- Yeah well, I'm in a wheelchair,
I don't have emphysema.
- Well, you can't have that too?
- Yeah, but I don't.
- Sally, you get in front
of your audience, right?
And you got to try to
explain to them, you know,
make them understand, right?
- Yeah.
- [Mickey] Right?
What do you do after that?
- What do you mean?
- You don't go anywhere after that?
That's it, right?
- [Sally] Right.
- I got to make these guys like me,
I got to make them understand,
I got to make them laugh
and if I, if they don't laugh,
I look like an idiot, right?
All right?
You're at a lecture
and they don't understand
what you're saying,
they look like idiots, right?
- Right.
- Do you see what I'm saying?
- I see what you're saying.
- There'll be a lot of guys on before me.
- I don't mind.
- [Mickey] Some of them
might not be that funny.
- That's okay.
- I might be one of them.
- But you told me that you were funny.
- Don't hold me to it.
- Whoa, so you were bullshitting me?
- I was lying.
- Wow, you're getting good.
- Thank you.
That means a lot coming from you.
- Well, you could have
parked in the handicap area,
you know?
- If it's all the same to you,
I kind of prefer to save those spaces
for people who have to
crawl in to get there,
or the guys who park
in the handicap spaces
at the golf course and play 18 holes
and break their clubs over their knees,
or people who have too
much jewelry, 80 years old,
they can't make it, the
oxygen's too long to walk.
You being handicapped?
Come on, get the fuck out
of there, I want to go in.
- All right, let's see the show.
(subtle country music)
- Hi.
Where's the sign up sheet?
- For what?
- Amateur night tonight, open mic night.
- So what's your name?
- Mickey Schwinn, like the bicycle.
- Like what?
- The bicycle.
- Schwinn.
I'll uh, I'll call you when you're on.
- Okay.
(subtle country music)
- Can I buy you a drink?
- Yeah, sure partner.
- Yeah?
- Yeah, to the road.
- To the road.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, sure.
- You sure?
- Yeah, are you okay?
- Yeah, yeah.
What did you say?
- I didn't say anything.
(subtle country music)
- One more time for Big Jim Benny.
- Thank you very much.
- Now the Cowboy Palace
announces Mickey Schwinn.
(applause)
- Good evening, ladies and gentlemen,
or howdy, whatever you
say in dry gold chair.
I had a horse once,
but he ran out of matches and
rolling paper, so I shot him.
Let me ask you something, just
to get acquainted, all right?
Just to get to know each other,
how many guys out here
have ever had a blow job?
- Why, are you gay?
- No, but I can be, if you want.
I'm you know, flexible,
you know what I mean, partner?
So my girlfriend says to me the other day,
she says, hey, you know,
you're not spending
enough time on foreplay.
I asked her, I said,
what do you think six
months of stalking you was?
- Well, she's a whore.
- She's a what?
- [Man] She's a whore.
- That's right, I thought
you'd said something else.
A lot of my friends are, you
know, divorce casualties.
A lot of money goes into these lawyers.
We got something different
out in California
with doing our own lawyering,
with taking care of our
own divorce, a lot cheaper,
goes something like this,
maybe you guys could learn something.
Ladies and gentlemen of the
jury, state of California,
your honor,
I'll be representing myself
in this divorce proceeding.
If you will turn to article
four, section B, exhibit A,
it clearly states, my
wife is a fucking cunt.
I'm resting my case.
- Maybe you should have
got yourself a Jew lawyer.
- A Jew, I did get a
Joe lawyer, no he was a.
- A Jew lawyer.
- [Mickey] I did, I got a Joe lawyer,
Joe White, a big fucking dumb white guy.
Maybe you know him.
No?
Anyway, I'm in an S and M
bar once and uh, you know,
I'm working on this broad,
that's a cowgirl to you guys,
and I'm working on her, I get her home
and I'm going through the, you know,
get your ass up in the air
and pay tribute to your master routine
and she turns to me
and she goes, you know,
I don't like being spoken to like that.
I go, where did you come from, baby?
What chatroom did you wander into?
This an S and M bar.
- This is bullshit, man.
- Give me a chance to show you
my heart's in the right place, okay?
I don't want you to think ill of me
when I leave here and go down yonder.
Let me dedicate a joke to
your home state, all right?
And then hopefully you'll,
you'll take it in the
spirit of which it's given.
Where are you from, what's
your home state, sir?
- Alabama.
- Crimson Tide.
- That's right.
- That's great.
For Alabama, is this
guy your second cousin,
or did you fuck him three times already?
Hey you know, I could see by
the horse tail on the wall,
that my time is up
and I'm so tired from busting
sod and everything like that
and then Victoria Barkley is coming over
and uh, happy tails.
Put it down, show's over.
Show's over, let's go.
- Come on, you were great,
I want to celebrate.
- Don't do this to me.
Come on.
- Oops.
- Honey, you're scaring
me, this is terrible.
You okay?
- Listen guys,
he's got a lot of things to
do this next couple of days,
basically take care of me,
so if you please just don't beat him up.
I'll send him back to you, okay?
- You're going to hide behind
a little girl in a wheelchair?
- Yeah, I am.
Come on.
- Hey, watch this.
Hey there Pilgrim.
- [Mickey] Bed-y bye time.
Oh God.
- Ask them, go on.
Go on, ask them.
- She wants to know, with all due respect,
if you thought anything was
funny, any of the jokes.
- Ask them if they got it.
Ask them if they got it.
- Come on, come on, let's go.
Okay?
All right?
It's not going to happen again, okay?
I assure you, okay?
This is it.
You're not ready, you're not up to this.
It's nothing to be
ashamed of, get in there.
- Come on, let's get out of here.
- Okay.
- Look, you might want to
uh, check that rear tire,
it looks a little low.
- Thanks partner.
Hey, you know, I'm really sorry
the horse didn't rape
me in the parking lot
because I know how much you
would have enjoyed that.
I'll do better next time.
I'll try to be more attractive.
- Squeal, squeal.
- Let me tell you something, all right?
The push came to shove.
I can take care of myself and
you in a situation like that.
- You couldn't punch
your way out of a bank.
Come on, Mickey, admit it.
- Paper or plastic?
- I haven't laughed so much in years.
(subtle Spanish music)
(upbeat Spanish music)
- Oh my God, Mickey.
I can walk, I'm cured.
Oh yeah, I can't walk, but I can cum.
- You came?
You okay?
- Yeah, are you okay?
- Yeah, a little different, but.
- [Sally] It was a little
different for me too.
Never done it before
with a guy who didn't have
his high school diploma.
- Equivalency and I don't
have that either, okay?
- Now what do we do?
- Okay, do you uh, try this out, okay?
- What?
- This uh, uh, I got into
trouble the other day with my,
one of my friends.
- What, what happened?
- He asked me to take his
kids to the petting zoo.
It started raining and it got cold
and I lost the directions,
so I took them to the supermarket.
You know, hey, you want to pet the cow?
It's ground beef or a filet.
Wanna see the chickens?
They're eight pieces or four pieces.
He gets really pissed off
and what does scarred
for life mean anyway?
You know what I'm saying?
- Are you a musician?
- No I'm, I'm the guy inside Barney.
- You weren't the guy inside Barney.
- What makes you say that?
- Well even though he's inside of Barney
and you can't see him,
he still would have to be
better looking than you.
Ha ha.
- Nice way to talk, kid.
That's lovely.
Hey sweetie.
- What?
- I think you took a leak.
- Get me to the room.
- What's the magic word?
- Get me to the room!
- Okay.
Sally, for what it's worth, they,
I used to know a guy at the
country club, Mr. Schwartz,
and the lifeguard was
pulling him over constantly,
saying look,
we're getting complaints that
you're peeing in the pool
and Mr. Schwartz would say,
everybody pees in the pool
and the lifeguard goes, but
not from the high diving board.
It's no big deal.
Want to go shopping?
- Oh hold on, this is nice.
It's a nice color.
What do you think?
- Try it on.
- I'm not going to make
it in the dressing room.
- Just put it on here.
- Here?
(subtle music)
- How's business?
- Yeah I mean, it's the
woman behind the scenes,
the one behind the book, the woman.
- What else do they want to know?
- Well, personal things.
- Yeah, like what?
- I don't know.
- Like who your lover is?
- Maybe.
- You're ashamed.
- No, I'm not.
- You're ashamed, I'm like
your Back Street girl.
The fireplace.
- Yeah, you like this?
- [Mickey] Roosevelt, fireside chat.
- [Sally] Eleanor or Franklin?
- Both presidential.
How's the mustache today?
Hi.
- Hi, is this Dr. Kelly's room?
- That's her.
- Hi.
- I'm Donna.
- Hi I'm Laurie, we're
here for the interview.
- Hello, I'm Lucy and I'm
going to be doing your makeup.
- [Sally] How do you do?
- Do you mind?
- [Sally] No, no, not at all.
- How's it going?
- [Lucy] That is so wrong.
Do you have a black turtleneck?
- Uh yeah, I have a black turtleneck.
- That's great.
Can you put it on?
- Uh, sure.
Excuse me.
- Oh.
- Sally, I'm gonna take off, okay?
- Okay, see ya.
- All right, bye.
- Bye.
- Have fun.
- 12 to 17, all the sex
questions are out, right?
- Right.
You can load up on the space stuff.
- No, that looks fantastic
in front of there.
Okay, here we go.
All right.
Now, is there anything you
want to start off with,
Dr. Kelly?
- Yeah, let's talk about sex.
- Aren't you the guy
that checked in with that
girl in the wheelchair?
- What did she do?
- Nothing, nothing, but
I've been there, pal.
My wife had a disability.
You guys got it made now,
it's a whole new deal.
- What are you talking about?
- Electric, they want something,
they get it just like that.
Would have made my life
a hell of a lot easier.
- Is that right?
- Yeah.
You mind if I sit down?
- No, go ahead.
My name's Ken Sherry.
What's yours?
- Uh, Mickey Schwinn.
- What's wrong with her?
- Well you know, be honest with you,
she's got a really big fucking mouth.
- No, no, no, I mean the disability.
- Oh well, you know, Mr. Sherry,
you see her in the wheelchair, right?
That's all you need to know.
- Yeah, we were always one
operation away from something.
What are you doing here?
- Oh, she's a scientist, she
wrote a book, she's pushing it,
helping her out, you know,
we're on the trail together.
- Didn't I see her on one
of those telethons at Easter
with Jerry?
- Oh, you know, you're
thinking of Jerry's kids,
well Sally's kids, whole
different operation.
Completely different franchise.
I gotta take a piss.
- Uh, excuse me, you're
coming back, aren't you?
- What, you want to talk some more?
- [Ken] Yeah.
- I'll come back then.
- You wouldn't bullshit me, would you?
- Mr. Sherry, the bullshit
starts when I come back.
Sally's kids.
I don't know my own strength.
S-H-E-R-R-Y.
- No sir, we do not, I'm sorry.
(subtle piano music)
- Mickey, Mickey,
I've got to go to the bathroom.
- Go to the bathroom.
(thunder crashing)
That's my girl.
(upbeat music)
- Ah, thank you very much.
See you.
Hi.
- [Betty] Hello.
Honey, you know, you're so
much prettier in person.
- That's very sweet of you to say.
Who should I make this out to?
- [Betty] Oh, to Betty Parker please.
No, no, no, just make that Betty.
- [Sally] Okay Betty.
- [Betty] So how long are
you going to be in town?
- Oh, we're leaving tomorrow.
- [Betty] Oh, that's such a shame.
You know, I have a nephew
that works here at the college
and he's planning on being
at your lecture this evening
and I just have this feeling,
the two of you would
be wonderful together.
- [Sally] Oh, you do?
- Yes.
- [Sally] Is he a professor?
- [Betty] No, but I do have
his picture in here some place.
Where is that?
Here it is.
See, he's in a wheelchair.
- I'll take it from here, just.
- Take what from here?
- Just go.
- I don't even want to
know what I did this time.
- Get away.
- But you know what?
You take it.
- Be back in an hour.
- Take it.
(upbeat music)
- Thank you.
- Are you ready, Dr. Kelly?
- So in human experience,
this is called the glue
that keeps people together,
yeah right.
Um,
um, in, in the planets, in
the galaxy between planets,
this is called Turner's
so-called funny energy of matter,
or the dark force.
So at this time, if anybody
would have any questions,
I'd be happy to answer them.
Yes sir.
- [Malcolm] Dr. Kelly, Malcolm Roberts,
Scientific journeyman.
- [Sally] Yes sir.
- [Malcolm] You referred to the
dark force, which I'm sorry,
I just kind of lost you a little bit
when it came around to.
- [Sally] Could you repeat that please?
- When you were speaking
about the dark force,
I kind of lost you there.
- What, what did you just say?
- I'm sorry, I'll speak up.
The dark force, did
you find that when you?
- Sir, did you just tell
me to go fuck myself?
- I beg your pardon?
- Did you just tell me to go fuck myself?
- [Malcolm] Am I hearing you correctly?
You know, lady,
I think that that glue that
keeps the universe together
is having a hard time
keeping you together.
- [Sally] You know what?
Go fuck yourself.
- You okay?
- Did you just hear that?
- Yeah, I did.
Are you okay?
- I'm fine.
- All right, now I, I think,
I don't think this is your room, let's go.
Come on.
- Get out of here.
No, get rid of the him.
- We're already getting rid
of him, he's gone, let's go.
- Get away.
- Come on, let's go.
- Just get away from me, would you?
- Get your hand over here.
Come on, let's go.
- Get off me, Mickey!
Get away!
Will you stop it?
Mickey!
Hey Mickey.
- [Mickey] Hey, how you feeling?
- [Sally] Do you want to go to dinner?
- Do you remember this afternoon?
- What am I, a desk?
- I can't make a fucking phone call?
- Yes, I remember this afternoon.
- I thought we could talk about that.
- Yeah, well I don't
want to talk about it.
I want to go out to dinner.
- Well, you know what?
I think it'd be a good idea
if we like got room
service and stayed in here.
- No, no, I want to go out to dinner.
(speaking French)
- I'm sorry madam, I don't speak French.
- This'll do.
He doesn't drink.
- Yeah, I do.
- [Sally] No you don't.
- Yeah I do.
- [Sally] You're driving.
See anything you like on the menu?
- [Mickey] Well Sally, you know,
I don't speak French either,
so uh, what do you think?
French toast, French
fries, French dressing.
What do you recommend?
- I'm sorry, I didn't
mean to embarrass you.
- [Mickey] I'm not embarrassed,
I'm just fucking hungry,
if you'll pardon my French.
- Do you wanna dance?
Dance?
- Hey, Sally, what is it with you?
I got to wheel you around the dance floor
and we'll hold hands,
or do I get to hold you
up and drag you around?
I'm tired, I'm hungry, that's it.
- You're lazy.
- That's not true.
- It is true.
Every time I want to do something,
you give me this bullshit
about not exerting myself
and to take it easy.
You're like Mr. Shortcut.
- [Mickey] Yeah, you're
like Mrs. Special Olympics.
Sally, I'm sorry.
- [Man] Hey Pally.
Cut the little lady some
slack, why don't you?
- Just suck your dick, why don't you?
- Oh, good luck.
- Hey Sally look,
I'm not saying I'm the most
tolerant person on earth, okay?
I know I got my shortcomings,
but I've also got my long Cummings too
and it ain't hopping around
from city to city with you.
I mean, I like it, I like it,
but you're dropping the ball,
you're losing your focus.
People are paying to see you.
They're lining up,
paying, and they walk in.
What do they get?
Go fuck yourselves?
What is that?
- Who are you to tell me
that I am dropping the ball
when you don't even have a ball, okay?
And what is this about, use it in my act?
You don't even have an act.
- Hey Sally, congratulations.
You just turned into a
first-class bitch on wheels.
- Well, you know what, Mickey?
I don't see anybody lining
up to see you, okay?
And paying any money, okay?
- No, I line up to see them for nothing
and I give it my fucking heart.
I don't phone it in like you do.
What do they get from you, huh?
What are you teaching them?
What are you doing up there, huh?
What?
Tell me.
(upbeat music)
- No, don't tell me I'm wrong
because I know I'm right.
I'm looking at you and you look exhausted.
You've been running around
in too many circles.
You've been partying too much.
You're not really taking
charge of your life.
- No, no, I'm fine.
- Look who dropped by
the Old Cracker Barrel
to chew the fat.
- [Dad] Sally,
you just got fired from
three speaking engagements.
You're not letting anybody
do anything at all for you.
Have I left anything out?
- No.
- Sally, have you ever
heard of the expression,
a blessing in disguise?
I mean, you're here, you're home safe.
I mean, it's not the end of the world.
There will be other lectures.
You need to get back to your work,
which in the end, it's going
to help a lot of people.
I mean, there's certainly
nothing wrong with.
- Knowing your limitations,
is that what you're trying to say?
- [Dad] Sally, I've always
respected your instincts.
- We're worried.
- But maybe this once, did
you ever consider the fact
that maybe you were on
the road with some guy
who was just out for a free ride?
- I mean, it couldn't be your fault.
I mean, what kind of person
would take advantage of someone
so, well, so vulnerable?
- [Dad] What do you think the chances are
of this guy sticking by
somebody in your condition
for any period of time?
- 50/50.
Let me rephrase what you're trying to say.
He is not good enough for me
and I'm not good enough for
anybody, isn't that right?
- Well, that about sums it up for me.
- [Dad] No, it doesn't sum it up for me.
We're talking about my
daughter's life, not a career.
- But no, the point that she's making
is the whole thing that
we're talking about here.
- But no.
- We fucked.
I fucking hate him.
- [Audrey] The man is an idiot.
This isn't the first time.
You know, he came out with
this color two years ago
and he called it Ferrari red.
It's the same color and now
he calls it Lamborghini red.
Like I wouldn't know the difference.
I have to ask you something.
Should I feel guilty
about putting you and Mickey
together in the first place?
- It's okay.
- We're so different, Sally.
- Oh, are we?
- Well picture this,
you're living in a luxury
penthouse apartment
and you're looking over the balcony
and you see a moving van.
Now very quickly, are
they moving out or in?
- In.
- I see them moving out
and that's a difference
between you and me.
You're the real optimist
and you're really lucky.
- Okay, picture this,
you get out of a limo
and you're escorted into
a hot disco gambling
restaurant bar and I'm
rolling along by your side
and you are looking great
and your walk is all sex
and grace and purpose
and then you see a
combination Marlboro man
and film director walking towards us.
Quickly now, very quickly,
which one does he ask to dance?
Quickly now, you or me?
You walking bitch.
- He picked you, Sally.
- [Mickey] Hi Mr. Costello,
you're looking well.
- I'm not in your way or anything, am I?
- I'll let you know in about five minutes.
- Oh really?
- Yeah, haven't you ever
heard the expression,
if you're not 10 minutes
early, you're late?
You said I wasn't ready.
I went out on the road
and you know something?
When you're right, you're right
and I'm going to tell you
something, you were right.
I'm not going to tell you
they did any newspaper
reports on me out there,
but I was pretty fucking funny,
sometimes.
Mr. Costello, what are we doing here?
You buying the Brooklyn bridge?
Give me a spot, any spot.
- Mickey.
- No, you listen.
What am I, what's going to happen
if you put me up there one night, right?
And I'm not funny.
Am I going to read about you
in Variety the next morning
that you hung yourself in the garage?
Am I?
- No.
- You got the balls to give me a spot.
- Starting two weeks from tonight.
Thursdays, 2 o'clock.
In the AM.
That's your spot.
- I don't know what to say.
- Just try to come up with something, huh?
- Thanks.
You won't regret it, I
won't disappoint you, okay?
I won't disappoint you, I gotta go.
- Comedians.
- Mr. Costello, I forgot
to tell you something.
Joe, I'm broke.
Can I have an advance?
- Sure, no problem.
You just put one foot
in front of the other
and advance yourself the fuck outta here.
- We got shut down and you
know how that goes, okay?
I don't have any money,
so as far as your last paycheck goes,
I'm sorry, but we're
going to rebuild, okay?
Just like they did in Jerusalem.
God is my witness, if they
can rebuild in Jerusalem,
then we can certainly rebuild here, okay?
And it's not your fault,
it's not my fault.
It's the government's fault
because they're cracking
down on the businessman,
which is what I believe
myself to be, okay?
And they're taking away from our freedom
because what is our freedom
without free enterprise, okay?
And as Esau said to Jacob,
I need you back as a closer, okay?
And I've been wrongfully accused
and God have mercy on them
because the Lord does have mercy on those
that wrongfully accuse,
instead of smiting them with
the jaw bone of an ass, okay?
Now Mickey, I had spoke to
some of your old accounts.
Now I want you back, I need a good closer.
You're the only one I know that can.
- What we'll do is this,
I'll come in for two weeks
and you will pay me cash.
No business checks, no I owe
you's, no chits, cash, okay?
- Two weeks, two days, two
hours, whatever you want
and the cash, I can
give you that right now.
- [Mickey] Oh, and another thing,
I don't need any more sermons, all right?
So lay off the Christian,
power lifting bullshit, all right?
- Okay, that's fine.
So why don't you knock off
for the rest of the day
and get yourself some sun maybe
and go have a lap dance tonight
and come in tomorrow
morning refreshed, okay?
- [Woman] So I'm sort
of, you know thinking,
why not just get that
highlights all through, right?
It's like blonde and a little bit of red,
or whatever to spice it up and
just sort of catch the light
and sort of shimmer in the sun,
make me feel a little summer-y,
and then she suggested just
get an inch cut off here
and you know, a web,
and just have it sort of
off my neck a little bit,
you know, like so it'll swing
a little bit more freely.
- Hi Lynn.
- [Woman] Highlights here and maybe a few,
just like a little
gold, red, I don't know,
just highlight the curls to
catch the light a little bit
and then just, you know,
just to get it a little
bit off my neck, like that,
just to cut a couple inches.
What are you looking at?
And just um, you know,
sort of get it a little
bit off my neck maybe,
or what I could do is pull
the whole thing up like this
and have it kind of splash like that.
- Audrey, you know where
Mickey works, right?
Well get over here
and don't give me any of
that DUI bullshit, okay?
How about I owe you?
I'll be downstairs.
- You're talking about security grants?
- You want to know how much
it's going to take to get in?
Well let me tell you.
- Did I hear you say that
you're worried, Harold?
No, no, no, there's no worry here.
- I'll tell him you called.
Thanks, bye-bye.
Hi.
- Hi, we're here to see the
guy that runs this place.
- Can I let him know
what this is regarding?
- May I help you?
- You can help me.
I'm here for my father's $20,000.
- $20,000?
Hey man, I'm just one of the guys.
I just, you know, where's my phone?
- How you doing, man?
Hey, how you doing?
- Yeah, I'm here for my father's $20,000.
- Okay, not a problem, great.
These guys with you, then?
Okay, you are?
I'm Eddie.
- I need to speak to somebody in charge.
- You take this metal,
you just listen to me?
It's from their ass into your pocket.
- Okay, it's not a problem.
He just stepped out
for a couple of minutes
and I'm gonna just uh,
get him on the phone.
If I can get you a beverage or something
while you're waiting?
- It ain't going to be a habit,
I'll call you back, over and out.
- I left slash serviettes
this time for you guys.
Thank you very much.
- Oh my God.
Are you the owner of Sally's Kids?
- You ever remember a time
when you downed a couple of?
- I hate you!
I hate you, when I ever met you!
- I admit that I lie and I
cheat on the telephone, okay?
This is what I do, I wear a black hat.
I hate the fact you ever
came into my God damn life
and if I ever see your fucking face
in my God damn house again,
I will personally have you killed, okay?
You little piece of shit!
Was I a mercy fuck?
- You know, I was going
to ask you the same thing.
- Aw, fuck you.
- Same fucking thing.
- Do you want to be with me or not?
- I don't know.
(phone ringing)
- Kelly residence.
- Sure, can you hold please?
Thank you.
(subtle piano music)
- Saddle up, Mickey, you're on.
- Okay, if you have anything left in you,
let's put it together
for the comedy stylings of Mickey Schwinn.
(applause)
- Good morning everybody.
How you doing today?
Every 30 days around my household,
I get the same question from
the old lady like clockwork.
Hey Mickey, am I different
when I menstruate?
Come on, you can tell me.
Do I act different towards
you when I'm on my period?
Let me think.
Yeah, first of all, you're
bleeding all over the joint.
Look at my face.
(laughter)
Got a question for you.
Why is it every time you're having sex,
every time you're getting laid,
you hear the same thing
over and over again?
Fuck me, fuck me.
Honey, I thought I was,
unless you're talking to
some guy under the bed.
(laughter)
By the way,
my wife says I don't spend
enough time on foreplay.
I asked her,
what do you think six
months of stalking you was?
(laughter)
Anybody do the psychic hotline yet?
No?
You get addicted to that
and you run out of questions, right?
Hey, psychic hotline, yeah, it's me again,
I just ordered a pizza.
Will it get here on time?
Aliens from outer space.
Why is it that they're
always smarter than us?
A far superior intelligence
from way beyond
that's going to come here
and teach us the way.
If they're so smart and
they're so superior,
you know what they're going to teach us?
They're going to teach us
how to suck their dicks.
(laughter)
Ladies and gentlemen, that's my time.
Thank you very much, tell your friends.
(applause)
- That was Mickey Schwinn.
He did pretty good, keep an eye out.
- Hey Mickey,
you should be a comedian.
- Hey Bernie, thanks.
Hey, I'm going on record to say that uh,
I'd rather be with you than without you,
so I love you.
You happy now?
Over and out.
Let me tell you something
about immigration.
(speaking Spanish)
Set this straight here.
Half of the guys in Washington.
(speaking Spanish)
- They don't want you in the country.
- They're a bunch of half-breeds.
(speaking Spanish)
- Mongrels.
(laughter)
- The other half, right?
The other half,
their parents came over
maybe two seconds before everybody else.
(speaking Spanish)
- What we should do is this.
You make everybody married
by law, somebody different.
(speaking Spanish)
You marry somebody from Germany.
- [Mickey] No Mexican, all right?
You marry somebody from
France, a French girl.
(speaking Spanish)
You marry somebody from Italy, no Mexican.
I marry a Mexican.
(laughter)
(speaking Spanish)
- That way, in about 50, a hundred years.
All the babies, the ninos, right?
Everybody's the same,
everybody's everything, right?
And then,
and then you could hate everybody
else for no reason at all.
(laughter)
- This is the address for
tomorrow, seven o'clock.
- All right, I'll be there.
- Mickey, you did a good job today.
- Okay.
Thanks, I'll see you there.
(laughter)
I gotta go home, I gotta go to sleep,
and I got to go to work at two o'clock,
that's in the AM.
- Work, what do you call this?
- Hey come on, don't take this
the wrong way or anything,
but a monkey could do this.
- That's why you're so good at it.
(speaking Spanish)
(laughter)
- Hey Hector, you know what?
Sometimes I think it might be better
to have somebody to
laugh with and to go out,
make somebody laugh.
Do you know what I mean?
- Yeah, yeah.
- Thanks, see you tomorrow.
- [Hector] See you tomorrow.
- All right.
(engine revving)
Shit.
Fucking cock sucker.
Go around me.
(subtle music)
- Hope you got insurance.
Mad I didn't call?
- [Mickey] Oh yeah, you know something?
I did call you and I think
you do owe me a message.
- Yeah, what was the message?
- I said that I loved you
and that I'd rather be
with you than without you
and I asked you if you were
happy and then I hung up.
Hey Sally, look I mean, if
that's not the right thing,
I mean, you know, I mean, I,
I'd love to take you
out for a seasonal drink
in the spirit of friendship.
- I don't know, Mickey.
God.
- You know what?
I can take you out to a nice restaurant.
I'll take you out to a
real French restaurant
and you know, I'll behave
myself and you know,
I'm telling you, just save
the last dance for me.
- On one condition.
- Anything.
- I drive.
(laughter)
(speaking Spanish)
(upbeat rock music)
(singing in Spanish)
- Fuck, right?
- Yeah, yeah you are.
(singing in Spanish)
(upbeat rock music)
(subtle rock music)
(singing in Spanish)
(upbeat music)