Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
[birds chirping]
[Forrest] I once believed that no man can
own land any more than a tree squirrel can.
I found myself restless
in a place
where anyone can do
as they please yet very few do.
I was young and life was already
passing me by...
[water trickles]
...so, I unanchored,
burning my few seconds under the sun,
drifting in search of reality
rather than luxury.
I couldn't see it at the time,
but my lust was merely a lull
before a brutal
inescapable storm.
[motorcycle engine revving]
[mellow music playing]
[boat rumbling]
[wind howling]
[mellow music playing]
Why do you live out here?
I love the smell...
and the birds and the turtles
and the cannonballs.
I love the way the light
reflects off the water...
and, yeah, these stars.
And it's quiet.
I don't know.
I just think
everybody struggles...
and if I'm going to struggle...
it better be for a life
that's worth it.
This to me, this is my life
that's worth the struggle.
This is how I want
to barely get by.
I don't really have
any big plans.
I think that's the best part.
Are you happy here?
I am.
[mellow music playing]
[Everly] Okay,
I've got a question for you.
Okay!
[Everly] What do you use
the binoculars for?
[chuckling]
Nothing!
[Everly] Oh, my God,
busted lone man on his boat.
[Forrest]
What would you use them for?
- Perving on people.
- [Forrest] Exactly.
[laughing]
Exactly.
Well,
I'm really no better than you.
Do you want a beer?
Well, no,
because then it'll make me pee.
And then I'll...
And I don't know where you...
I don't know where that happens.
There's a toilet.
You have to flip the bed up.
[Everly] Oh, my gosh.
You don't have a curtain
or anything?
- [Forrest] I mean, I go outside, obviously.
- What, for all of it?
[Everly] Yeah, I haven't quite...
[Everly] You poo in the lake?
[chuckles]
Well, if you have to, yeah.
[Everly] If you have to?
You have to, like, every day.
You do that every day.
Well, I'll use the bathrooms.
I mean, it's all right
to pee in the lake but...
- [Forrest] You can't poop in the lake?
- No!
[laughs]
[Everly] Oh, my God.
Have some manners.
[upbeat music playing]
[motorcycle engine revving]
Hey!
Can you, uh...
do that somewhere else, please?
[laughs]
[water splashes]
Wait a minute! Oh, oh.
- Oh, why?
- People are watching.
[laughs]
[mellow music playing]
[Forrest] Where'd you learn
to dance like that?
[chuckles]
Kind of all over, you know, I...
Well, I first started ballet
when I was seven, in New Zealand
and then we moved to Australia
for a little bit
and then I learned more,
like, modern and stuff,
and then we came to Missouri.
- [Forrest] And here you are!
- Here I am!
[chuckles]
[Everly] Yeah, on the lake
dancing on a boat.
So, how do you plan
on taking care of me
when we get older,
Mister Lake Man?
I thought you were going
to take care of me.
[gasps]
[Everly] No, I got to dance.
Oh, we'll figure it out.
The money will come.
I think it's probably
more important
we measure success
in life experiences.
Don't you?
Yeah.
I like that.
You want to turn her port?
Not bad!
- [Everly] I get it right?
- You did.
Oh, I knew I had a 50-50 chance.
Port and left
both have four letters.
Okay. Good to know.
- [Forrest] Does that make sense?
- Yeah, it does, it does.
What's the front
of the boat called?
That's the bow.
What's that rope
that you've been playing with?
- This rope? Halyard.
- [Everly] Mm-hm.
It raises and lowers
the mainsail.
And what are those little things
blowing in the wind?
- These little things?
- Mm-hm.
Telltales.
Man, does everything
have a name?
I think so.
Okay. What's this thing called?
Gunnel, gunwale, gunwale.
- It's a weird one.
- Mm-hm.
What's this?
What's this little guy called?
- I don't know.
- [Everly] Uh-huh.
I knew there would be something.
Well, I'm going to hit the head.
- [Everly] The what?
- To run the bilge.
No?
- I'll be right back.
- Okay.
[water trickling]
- Cue wind.
- [Everly] We're not going anywhere.
[chuckles]
We're in a dead spot.
Here, cut us port, other way.
[Everly] No.
So, that's... It's opposite.
- [Everly] Okay, well...
- Yeah, I know.
I, technically, was right.
See the little ripples
in places,
lines of ripples
across the surface, that's wind.
Take us starboard.
- [Everly] Starboard.
- Starboard.
And then watch, watch the little telltales.
They level out
and it's time to tack,
and the wind will pick us back up.
Yeah, we did it too slow.
Oh, there we go!
Good, let that go.
Come over here real quick,
pull really hard.
- There it is!
- Look at that!
- [Forrest] There it is.
- I did it.
- Not bad.
- Sailing.
- We are sailing, mate.
[Forrest] There's actually a really good
place to go camping right down here.
[Everly] I've never been
camping before.
[Forrest] You've never been
camping before?
- [Everly] No!
- You're kidding.
[Everly] No, I mean,
I've always wanted to go.
The idea of dinner over the fire
and waking up to the
birds chirping is quite lovely.
But I've never been.
I don't know
how I feel about that.
What kinda dad
doesn't take his kid camping?
[birds chirping]
[Forrest] Where do you see us
in the future?
In the future?
Yeah, together?
I see us in the wild.
[Forrest] My Uncle Ellis, he has his
business up in the San Juan Islands.
It takes people fishing
and whale watching.
Does pretty good.
Maybe some point, we can move
the boat up there, do that too.
You know, we really wouldn't even have
to wait if we don't want to, right?
- Mm.
No, I guess not.
Hey, do you have
any measuring cups?
I don't.
Mm.
[giggles]
- [Everly] What?
- [Forrest] What are you doing?
- What else am I supposed to do?
- I don't know, you're hilarious.
[Everly] Don't drink out
of the bottle, you grump!
- You're kidding me, right?
- No, I'm not kidding you.
Have some manners!
You just poured that
in your hands.
Yeah, well, I mean, I'm...
it's different.
Well, here's
your measuring cup right there.
What?
[laughs]
You're not going to get any,
you're not going to get any pud.
No, pud for you.
[mellow music playing]
[Forrest] All right.
I usually use hotdogs
but we're all out
so we're using
rotten chicken right now.
[Everly] That's revolting.
- [Forrest] They love it.
- [Everly] Okay!
[Forrest] They love anything
if you're patient.
That's a trick.
You know what?
I think you have something.
- Really?
- Oh, yeah.
Here, stand up! One, two, three!
No!
No, no, no, no! No slow down.
- [Forrest] Look at that!
- [Everly] It's huge!
- Oh, my God!
- It's making a noise.
Oh, my God. It's tentacles.
[laughs]
Oh, oh, crikey!
What... what is, what is it?
[Forrest] I don't know. You must
have snagged something on the way in.
What on earth!
Is fishy okay?
- It's okay.
- Okay.
- What do you got there?
- I don't know.
- It's a little bit wet.
- What's it say?
I don't know. I can't tell.
It's got a little fishy.
It's supposed to say,
"You're a keeper, move in with me."
Aw!
- Are you sure?
- Come here, yeah! Of course.
You're okay with living on a
boat with me and catfishy?
I mean,
I pretty much already do.
All right.
[smooches]
All right, now,
take that guy off the hook.
No way!
[laughs]
[Forrest] I'm going to go get some
things from the country market.
- Do you want anything?
- I'm good.
Surprise!
[Forrest] Wow!
These look great.
- Did you make them?
- Yeah.
- You okay?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
What's wrong?
I just got into it with my mom
earlier before I left the house.
Was it bad?
Yeah.
She wasn't exactly thrilled
that I was moving out here
with you, so.
Well, I can't say I blame her.
I guess I didn't really turn out
how they wanted.
[Forrest] Neither did I.
Well, I can't wait to meet them.
[laughs]
Anyway, look, none of that,
none of that matters.
- No, it does not.
- Doesn't matter
Look, you've got sail...
sailboat curtains and folded rags.
I bought you something.
Oh, yeah?
Do you want to
tuck those behind you?
Yes.
- You bought me a little kiwi.
- That's a little kiwi.
And it does have two stickers,
give me that.
Who needs that?
- Well, thanks.
- Let me make sure.
[crunches]
Oh, well, it's good.
- You eat the skin?
- Not normally.
[laughs]
I got that a little later.
It's still good.
I like your dedication.
Oh, my God!
Look, I look like a little fish.
Pretty little fish.
[laughs]
Mm-hm.
Oh, God.
[huffing]
You ever feel like so many
people have it all wrong?
How do you mean?
They spend all this time
and energy
investing in retirement...
they may never see
and they don't invest anything
in the right now.
[chuckles]
Does that make sense?
I mean, maybe they don't want
to be huge financial burdens
on their families
as they get older.
[sighs]
Yeah, if you live that long.
Why wouldn't you plan
to live that long?
[calm music playing]
- Mogul Bandit.
- Who's Mogul Bandit? - Why, I am.
[mellow music playing]
- [wind howls]
- [rope rattles]
[Forrest] You okay?
Yeah, I'm okay.
I was just really feeling
those waves up front.
[Forrest] My first mate's
never gotten seasick before.
[Everly groans]
Don't worry, we'll be back
to the cove soon.
[rattles]
[calm music playing]
Not hot.
- [Everly] How are you?
- Well, getting off here soon.
[Forrest] It's busy like
it's a weekend or something.
[cashier] Yeah, fortunately,
I won't be here tomorrow.
Oh, that's lucky.
Neither of you
have your ears pierced, do you?
[Everly] I do.
- Really?
- [Everly] Yeah.
[cashier] My uncle just got
his ears pierced.
- [Everly] Really?
- It's like two weeks ago, but they're still,
they're getting infected.
[coin rattles]
- [cashier] You want your receipt?
- [Forrest] I'm good.
- [cashier] All right.
- [Forrest] Thank you.
Bye!
[Forrest] You got up early.
Oh, yeah, I went to see
that place where you said
you could see the elks
but I didn't find any.
Listen,
I've been thinking about it.
If we wanted to move the boat,
we wouldn't have to wait.
- My uncle Ellis didn't...
- I'm pregnant!
- [Forrest] You're sure?
- I'm sure.
- How do you know?
- I took a test.
When?
[Everly] I can't believe
my mom was right,
she said this exact thing
would happen
if I came out here with you.
[Forrest] Your mom?
How could your mom have
possibly known this whole thing?
Did you tell her?
I'm not going to tell them.
[Forrest] You have to tell
your parents.
[Everly] I can't tell them.
[sighs]
[yells]
Just a spider, Jesus.
[Everly] You don't understand,
I can't tell my parents.
I don't have that sort
of relationship with them.
- What are we going to do?
- I don't know.
We can't afford a baby!
What were you thinking?
What?
I can't believe I fell
for this whole thing.
[Forrest] Fell for this?
Yeah, all this talk of adventure
and travel
and we'll get off the lake and
it was never going to happen.
It could happen.
[Everly] How? How's it going
to happen? We've got no money.
We live in the middle of the
damn continent on a lake,
on a boat, and I'm pregnant.
Even hospital bills alone.
You don't even have a job.
You don't have a job either.
Just get it aborted.
Are you kidding?
Well, it's obviously the worst
thing that could happen to us.
[Everly] You make me sick.
[Forrest] People do that.
[Everly] I can't believe
you'd even say that to me.
I didn't think
you were like that.
Well, I thought we were
on the same team.
That didn't take long
to fall apart, clearly,
you've done nothing wrong here,
and this is entirely my fault.
You're a jerk!
[Everly]
We are on the same team.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry too.
I mean, it's not like it's the first
time it's crossed my mind, you know?
I guess I just freaked out
when you said it out loud.
- You sure?
- Yeah.
I can't really see
any other way.
[huffing]
It's not like I can go home
like this anyway.
We'll figure it out.
[motorcycle engine revving]
Hey.
Talk to me.
[sobbing]
It's too much. I don't know if I can
go through with this whole thing.
I'm with you, you know that.
You're not doing this alone,
I'm with you.
Whatever you want to do,
we can make it work.
You don't have to.
Well, I don't want to know if it's
a boy or a girl until it's born.
I don't want to know.
I don't want to...
- You don't want to know?
- No.
[sighs]
You know what this means?
We're going to have
to baby-proof the boat.
[sobbing]
[wheezing]
[laughs]
Stupid.
[Forrest] So, now that
we're going to have a kid
for the rest of our lives...
[scoffs]
...we're probably going to have
to move off the boat.
Well, I don't necessarily think
that's true.
[Forrest] You don't think so?
I mean, maybe...
maybe when it gets to school age
but I think while it's still
little, it'll be okay.
Anyway, by the time
it gets older,
we'll have a sidecar
for the bike, so...
[chuckles]
This is crazy,
we're going to have a family.
[Everly] Yeah!
[chuckles]
[sighs]
[Everly] Good crazy?
Yeah!
[birds chirping]
[cawing]
Just get it over with.
[rattles]
Hey, it's me!
I'm sorry I haven't called
in a while.
Yeah, I'm fine.
I'm still out at the lake.
How have you... No!
Mom, no, I'm happy!
Isn't that what you want
to hear?
I don't...
Look, that's not why I call...
I didn't call
to fight with you, mom.
Mom, I wanted to tell...
I don't know!
I don't know when.
Yeah, he's taking care of me just fine.
He's treating me
really well, actually.
I don't know what you want.
I... Yeah, you know what?
I'll talk to you later.
Mm-hm. Yeah. I'll send you
a Christmas card, okay? Bye!
[phone thuds]
I'm sorry.
I just can't talk to her.
[leaves rattling]
It doesn't matter.
Just start calling her grandma.
She'll get it.
It's not funny.
[indistinct chatter]
Mmm!
I knew you were going
to do that.
If it wasn't you, it was someone
that was going to...
Can you see the little...
my little belly?
I can see it.
I can see it just barely.
- You're not just pushing it out?
- No!
That's really there.
[groans]
How's it going?
I'm almost done
and then I have that one...
- Yes.
- ...and then I have that one.
- Look at the dinosaur!
- That's cute!
That is really cute.
[Everly] Hey, did you see the top
over there with the raccoon on it?
- I saw that.
- Isn't it cute?
- It's adorable.
- Yeah.
I can't afford anything
in this store.
- I know.
- I'm sorry.
I understand. It's okay.
Why does it have
to be so expensive?
- It's tiny.
- Hmm
- You want to go?
- Yeah.
[truck engine revving]
Keep it coming.
Yup.
- Oh, man!
- Nailed it!
Is that gonna be okay?
- That'll work.
- All right.
- Hope you're thirsty!
- Well, yeah.
Yeah. That would be great.
That's a ratty ass boat.
[giggles]
- You ever fish out of it?
- Occasionally.
You do any good fishing with it?
Oh, absolutely not.
Oh.
So, when are you going
to get a real job?
[laughing]
- I'll let you know.
- Hey, I appreciate the beer.
[Forrest] Don't drink all those
on the way home.
No!
[bottle rattles]
[birds chirping]
You learning anything?
Yes, I'm learning a lot,
actually.
Someone calculated
that enough sperm
to provide the present
world population
could be put in a top hat.
That's how little they are.
That's really gross.
Can you imagine?
[birds squeaking]
[calm music playing]
[mellow music playing]
- That looks perfect.
- It's going to work.
[Everly]
So, I've been thinking...
The baby's already
getting pretty expensive
and we haven't even been
to the doctor yet.
[sighs]
I know.
I've been looking.
I have, but if I take a
full-time job in town right now,
I'm never going to be able to
finish painting the hulls
by spring like I said I would.
I think the money we get from
that, plus what we have now,
we're going to be fine.
It'll be enough to get us
through pregnancy.
[Everly]
Well, that's the other thing
is that I don't think we're
covered on my parents' insurance.
[calm music playing]
We don't have to worry
about that right now, not yet.
[Everly] You don't think?
No, and even if we wanted to
invest in a real place to live,
we're never going to be able
to sell a boat
in the middle of winter time.
Yeah.
[mellow music playing]
[motor cycle engine revving]
[rattling]
[sighs]
[wind howling]
[door creaks]
- [Forrest] So, I've been thinking.
- [Everly] Yeah.
I still like the name Mahi.
[laughs]
You won't let that go.
We've been over this.
It's going to get teased
its whole life.
People are going to say
its name twice.
- What about Marlin?
- What's with you and fish names?
[Forrest] What's wrong
with fish names? Fish are cool.
I mean, there's not a fish
in my belly.
[chuckles]
No fish names.
[Forrest]
Well, let's just call it Bruce.
[giggles]
What about Mako?
- I like that.
- [Forrest] Mako, the boy
or Mako, the girl.
Just, Mako, the baby.
- Baby Mako.
- [Forrest] Baby Mako.
- That's sweet!
- [Forrest] You like it?
I like that.
I like it.
Oh, my gosh, it's kicking.
- Really?
- Uh-huh.
Do it again!
Kick me! Come on!
[Everly] I don't know
if it does it on demand.
[quacking]
[door creaks]
Oh, do not go out there.
It's a bit chilly.
What do you think the baby's
going to be like?
[calm music playing]
I can't wait to take it
to my grandparents' place.
I can't wait
to take it swimming.
[calm music playing]
[rain rustling]
[thunder rumbling]
[water splashing]
Oh, boy!
Forrest!
[Forrest] Hang on!
- [Forrest] What?
- I think the baby's coming.
[tense music playing]
- [Forrest] What?
- The baby's coming.
[Forrest] Already?
- You're sure?
- Yes!
Put the stuff that I folded,
put it in your bag.
[tense music playing]
Stop! Hey!
[motorcycle engine revving]
Sorry.
All right coming in right here.
[indistinct chatter]
Okay, okay.
Squeeze my hand.
Squeeze it hard.
Push, push.
[gasping]
You're doing good.
[doctor] Deep breath.
Deep breath.
Okay.
[yelling]
[sniffing]
[tense music playing]
[gasping]
You're good. You're doing good.
No!
- Why is... why isn't it crying?
- I don't know, baby.
[tense music playing]
- It's okay.
- What?
He's all cleaned up, if you guys
would like a moment with him.
Wake up.
His name is Mako.
Thank you.
- [nurse]How do you spell that?
- M-A-K-O.
[nurse] Would you like a picture
with Mako?
- No, thank you.
- [Everly] Yes.
I don't want to bury my son
without being able to remember
what he looks like.
[camera whirs]
[sighs]
[clicks]
[door opens]
[nurse] I'm going to have to ask
you a couple questions if it's okay.
We never actually got
your address, what is it again?
We live on our boat right now
on Lake Lotawana.
[nurse] So...
I can give you
my parents' address if you like.
[nurse] Okay, that will work.
And as a service,
we provide
for our families here,
we can offer cremation for free.
Does that sound like something
you would like to do?
Can you give us some time
to think about it?
[nurse] Unfortunately,
due to the situation,
we need to go ahead
and make our decision.
[water bubbling]
I love you.
I love you too.
[stones rattling]
[birds chirping]
[calm music playing]
[crickets chirping]
Whoo, whoo, whoo!
[Forrest] Hey, Everly.
Hey, Everly.
[sobbing]
Hey, come here, come here.
I can still feel him kicking.
And hear him crying.
[Forrest] I'm so sorry.
I don't want to be here anymore.
[indistinct chatter]
[yelling]
This is stupid, the way we've
been acting towards each other.
We're supposed
to be on the same team.
Remember that?
[Everly]
What are we going to do?
We can't even pay
the hospital bills.
It's not really any way
I'm getting around that.
You can't really measure that
in life experience
and pay them that way.
- [Forrest] We will figure it out.
- We'll figure it out?
- Yeah.
- Really?
That's what you say every time,
that's your answer
for everything.
- You're just lazy.
- Yeah, and you...
This is your excuse
for being lazy.
[Forrest] You know, you've been
really enjoyable lately,
especially tonight.
[Everly] I don't even know
what we're doing anymore.
[Forrest] Well,
I don't really know either.
[water splashes]
[panting]
[coughs]
[huffing]
[calm music playing]
[door creaks]
[door closes]
[thuds]
[rustling]
[motorcycle engine revving]
[upbeat music playing]
[bottles clank]
[Forrest] Thanks, man!
[motorcycle engine revving]
[water bubbling]
Hey!
Hey, loner, over there on the
boat, I got a surprise for you.
You're going to need to put
some pants on though.
Poison ivy where we're going.
[light music playing]
Here, take this.
Do not look inside.
[light music playing]
[motorcycle engine revving]
[horn honks]
[glass bottles breaking]
[gloomy music playing]
[crickets chirping]
[bag thuds]
Shit.
Matches are soaked.
Let's just go to bed.
[indistinct chatter]
[knife clanks]
[vessel clanks]
[door opens]
[door creaks]
Hey!
That little octopus is cool.
Yeah.
Where'd you find that?
I just got it
when I was out the other day.
Cool.
Out where?
I notice we got
some new kitchen stuff too.
[birds quacking]
[door opens]
[door closes]
[doll thuds]
[footsteps thumping]
I'm going to put this stuff in the bedroom.
Can you put the groceries up?
[mellow music playing]
I'll get them.
Grab your life jacket, sweetie!
The Carruthers
are going to be here any minute
and we're going to go out
for a quick boat ride.
[keys clanking]
[footsteps thumping]
Sweetie, don't forget
to go to the bathroom!
[switch taps]
[mellow music playing]
Shh!
Michael, do you need any help?
[door closes]
Hey!
- [Everly] They're gone.
- Are you crazy?
This is so stupid, come on!
We got to get out of here.
Oh, my God.
Are you done?
[door opens]
[door closes]
Who the hell are you?
Hey! Hey!
Run!
Right, right, right.
Oh, my God.
[panting]
That was crazy, huh?
We took their stuff.
[sighs]
[laughs]
That was incredible.
Let's get out of here.
[birds chirping]
- Look at this!
- [Forrest] This looks amazing.
[laughs]
I do feel a little bad though.
- Now they got to go get more.
- Oh, don't.
Next time,
we'll get some milk too.
[spoon clanks]
Next time?
[Everly] Yeah,
I was thinking tonight
we could go to that cove
over near the canoe club.
We almost got caught last time.
This time, we were stupid.
[Forrest] We weren't stupid.
We had no idea they'd come home.
It's just bad luck.
I haven't even ever been close
to getting caught before.
I thought you might be over it
after that.
No way. That was the best one.
I can't change your mind, can I?
[upbeat music playing]
This whole thing
is a refrigerator.
There's ice.
Your favorite.
[laughs]
We should have brought
a bigger bag.
Should have bought
a bigger house.
But I still love this
wee octopus.
Hello.
It can live in our zoo
with our new pelican.
Oh, they match. So mean.
[Forrest] We're going to have
to separate them
because I don't think
they get along in real life.
Where are we going to put
all this shit?
I can't believe I took this.
[giggles]
Damn, this is a hard one.
He should actually go on
the other side of the piranha.
- Oh, you're right.
- [Everly] If we made a base for him.
[Forrest] Oh, my God,
you're right.
[Everly] Yeah. Oh, look at them!
They're friends.
[Forrest] We don't need
any of this shit.
[laughs]
- But look how nice it looks.
- It's true.
[upbeat music playing]
[ball thuds]
We got to get back here.
What are you going to do
with that?
Mm, I was thinking
we could sell it.
I don't like this.
We should go.
This isn't us.
Really, we should leave.
This doesn't feel right.
Hey!
Are you listening to me?
Hey! Can you wake up?
Wake up?
I don't even know you right now.
Well, you think
you've got it all figured out?
You think you understand
everything? You don't!
I don't understand.
I'm standing right here
and I understand.
You're losing it
and you know it too.
We messed up. I'm not going to
let that happen again.
[Forrest] This is what
I don't understand.
[gunshot]
[tense music playing]
[sad music playing]
[mellow music playing]
[calm music playing]
[lively music playing]
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull