(eerie music)
(lightning crackling)
(shuddered breathing)
- [Man] Lucy.
(jangling)
(thunder rolling)
(dramatic chorale music)
- [Woman] Near the sea, up a long lane far from town,
lies the house of one John Ambrose,
a haunted man.
The house stands abandoned, left to Ambrose's ghost.
Some say he was once in love with his demon
and to this day he still revisits the house
to pay tribute.
(carriage rattling)
Nobody knows the whole story.
Some say the lady that lived here
died of a broken heart.
Others say that her lover murdered her
in a violent rage after finding her
in bed with another man.
But this much is certain.
- [Driver] Whoa!
- [Woman] She blames him for her death.
- This is what I wanted you to see.
- Sarah, these old superstitions of yours, they--
- Help me down.
I want to go inside.
- Okay.
(horse nickering)
We might be a while.
(gate creaking)
What about the man who owns this house?
- The place is abandoned.
The whole town's afraid to come near this place.
Relax, James.
We're all alone.
We could live here, James.
Together.
Nobody'd have to know.
Just us, alone.
Let the rest of the world be damned.
- We'll move in tonight,
right after I'm done with my studies.
- Don't make fun of my dreams.
Mm.
(romantic orchestral music)
(both laughing)
James?
- [James] Hmm?
- Have you told your father you want to study painting?
- No.
It's out of the question.
I'm to be the third generation managing the flax mills.
Decided at birth.
- You ever think of telling your parents about me?
- You know, I would.
I just couldn't possibly explain.
- No, of course not.
I'm sorry.
It was a stupid question.
Almost as stupid as imagining we could live here together,
escape from the world.
I have bad news.
I've missed my time.
- Dear God.
- I don't know what to do.
- Now, you mustn't worry.
I'll take care of you, Sarah.
Everything will be fine.
- Goshen College, home for the young bon vivants
of minor education.
James, my good man.
- Fletcher.
- Cards tonight in the commons?
Jenkins and Graham are in, bring your father's wallet.
- I can't tonight.
- Oh!
Brandy and cigars are in the offing.
A good time shall be had by all.
- I have a prior engagement.
Give my regrets to the boys.
- Drinking watered down beer with
overripe fishermen in Portsmouth.
When are we going to stop being ashamed
of our higher social standing?
Will you slow down?
You look as if your trousers have caught fire!
- There is a lady expecting me.
- God's eternal source of spontaneous combustion. (laughs)
- Perhaps you'd...
You're a man of the world.
- Why do I get the feeling I shall have to
pay for this compliment?
- I need a referral.
(lighting crackling)
- [Driver] Hey-ah!
Hey-ah! (horse clopping)
- James.
James!
- Hmm?
- Look at me.
I'm scared.
Don't leave me, James.
Promise.
- I promise.
Uh, wait here.
- Yes, sir.
- Don't worry, Sarah.
Everything's gonna be all right. (clears throat)
(dog barking nearby)
(dramatic music)
(knocking)
Mr. Tilton?
- You can call me Dr. Tilton if it makes you feel better.
You're a nice looking couple.
Don't get married. (chuckles)
Ten dollars in advance.
- (scoffs) Ten dollars?
- End of the month, landlord's raising the rent,
the godless bastard.
Drink this.
Go ahead.
(Sarah gulps)
Won't take long.
You wait here.
- (stammering) I'll be right here.
Be brave.
(door slams)
(horse neighing)
(thunder rolling)
- [Tilton] On the table, there, miss.
Up you go.
It will all be over soon now.
(eerie music)
(Sarah screaming inside)
- Sarah?
- Just the laudanum.
- Laudanum?
You don't have ether?
- You have no idea how much it costs
to ship that up from Boston.
Relax, bit of rest, she'll be right as rain.
Up to her old tricks in no time.
- [Sarah] James.
- Calm yourself, Sarah.
I've got you.
Come on, shh, shh.
(Sarah crying)
Go.
Go!
Go, driver!
(horse clopping)
(dramatic music)
(Sarah groaning)
Look at you.
Dear God.
Faster, driver, faster!
It'll be okay, it's all right.
Be strong, we'll be back to,
we'll be back to your room soon.
Everything'll be all right.
Okay.
Oh my God.
Faster, faster!
(suspenseful music)
(James grunts)
(door crashing)
Okay, there.
Here, all right.
Shh, shh, okay, okay.
(Sarah shuddering)
(paper rustling)
(match striking)
Shh, shh, shh.
- [Sarah] I'm cold.
- I know, I know.
I know.
I know, I know.
Okay.
I must go for help.
- No!
- No, that's--
- I... - No.
- Just, just...
Someone will...
I will come back, okay?
I will come back.
- No. - All right?
- No!
- Hold on, okay?
- Please don't go, please.
James.
You promised you wouldn't--
- I will come back.
- James!
James!
James.
- I'll come back.
I promise.
(Sarah crying)
(thunder rolling)
(crowd chattering)
Barkeep.
- Wait your turn, kid.
Next?
- Ah! (laughing)
Never! (laughing)
- I heard a cry upstairs.
I think there's a...
I think there's a girl in trouble.
- What?
- Yeah, a girl, she needs help.
Somebody had best look in on her.
- [Barkeep] Uh, in a minute.
I'll see to it in a minute, do you want a drink?
- No.
(patrons laughing and chattering)
But you'll go to her?
- I said I will in a minute, okay?
- But you will go to her?
- [Barkeep] Is there an echo in here?
Next.
- [James] Excuse me.
(rain falling)
(Sarah crying out)
(blood dripping)
(whispering) Sarah.
- [Sarah] (shouting) No!
- (whispering) Sarah...
- [Sarah] We could live here James.
Let the rest of the world be damned.
(Sarah screaming)
(breathing heavily)
- James.
James, are you ill?
- No, I'm fine.
- Oh, fine!
James, please talk to me.
I'm your friend.
(water splashing)
Did you...
Um-- - False alarm.
- [Fletcher] All the same, you really don't look well.
You know, I know a fantastic spot in Connecticut,
they have these mineral baths.
I swear they'll soothe you a hundred times over.
- Uh, Fletcher, I'm fine.
(clears throat) Thank you.
- [Fletcher] Very well.
I'm going to see what horrors
they've cooked up for our breakfast.
(James sighs)
(marketplace crowd chattering)
- Excuse me.
Uh, how much for the flowers?
- Penny a bunch, sir.
- I'll take them.
All right, there you are.
- Thank you, sir.
- Thank you.
(horse whinnying nearby)
(crowd chattering)
(bell tolling)
- [Fisherman] It was me she had the warm welcome for.
- [Fisherman] Whitehall, you never laid down with a woman...
- Aye, many a time, many a time!
- Why is everybody outside?
- Arr, they gave us all the boot.
Found a corpse upstairs.
- Ah, easy, lad.
'Twas only one of the local wenches.
And sure, isn't the first time
an unhappy customer gave one of them the knife. (laughs)
(melancholy music)
- Leave on, leave on!
- Nah! (scoffs)
(dramatic music)
(horse whinnies)
- Yeah, come on.
- [Sarah] (whispering) James.
- [James] Sarah?
- [Sarah] (whispering) Just us, alone.
(horse trotting)
- [Man] Out of my way!
(horse whinnying)
Yah!
- [James] Who are you?
Sir!
(dramatic music)
Sir, who are you?
Yah!
Sir!
(dramatic music)
(carriage rattling)
Whoa.
- Well, well, well, if it isn't
the midnight rambler himself!
How are we today, James?
Oh, wait, let me guess.
Fine!
- He doesn't look so fine.
- I'm fine.
- Oh, there you have it.
- Such a delusion.
- Because you're a fool, Jenkins.
Why hate a movement whose main idea
is to encourage women to wear less petticoats?
- I never thought of it that way.
(Fletcher sighs)
Oh, hell!
It's Professor Ambrose.
If he sees me I am a dead man.
- Ambrose?
- Hide me, Fletch, quick.
- [James] Who is he?
- [Jenkins] I missed his lecture last week.
He's coming for me, I know it.
- He's not coming for you, you coward.
The coot probably doesn't even know you exist.
- Who is this man?
- I didn't even know the man came out in the daylight.
- For God's sakes, who is this?
- Will you please settle down?
- I'm sorry, I'm just...
Jenkins, what do you know about him?
- Well-- - No, no.
Let's use this bait to retrieve our friend.
Whist tonight at eight sharp.
You bring the brandy, we'll bring the gossip.
(thunder rolling)
- Rumor has it he used to teach at Harvard
and that he resigned after rumors
that he killed a man.
Nobody really knows much about Professor Ambrose.
Except that he has a penchant
for teaching highly suspect metaphysics
and what's described in the course catalog
as a physics class.
And that he's brilliant.
- Crazy is more like it.
- Depends on who you ask.
Some say he's still haunted by the ghost of his victim.
Anyway, rumor has it he's a dying man.
You should attend one night, James.
Quite interesting.
- It's all the rage with the young poser iconoclast set.
- (scoffs) Just because the material he teaches
is over your head, Fletcher.
- I would just like to know
why anyone would leave Harvard University
to teach at Goshen.
- Well, he must have done something.
(dramatic music)
- So what's the sudden interest in Ambrose?
- Mm, curiosity, really.
Interesting character, that's all.
(carriage rattling rapidly)
(frightening music)
(James gurgling)
(thunder rolling)
- God! (coughing)
God.
What if God did not exist?
Faith.
We take it for granted and yet
we find it so difficult to believe
in other unseen phenomena.
Why?
- Ah, yeah, he's a friend of mine, sir.
He just wanted, wanted...
- Uh, James Farrow, sir.
I'm just auditing.
(Ambrose clears throat)
- Just auditing?
Sampling the waters as it were.
- I suppose you could say that.
- Without a determination to swim,
that can lead to drowning.
- Sir, I simply...
(Ambrose clears throat)
- Voyeurism is a dangerous occupation, Mr. Farrow.
I have no time for peeping toms,
so either commit or exit.
- I'll stay, sir.
- Well, the choice is yours.
You have free will, I hope.
(clattering)
Gravity.
Gravity and sleep do not always coexist amicably.
(chair thudding)
- I'm sorry, Professor Ambrose.
These late night classes--
- That's quite all right, Mr. Dickens.
(sighs) Sleep.
Some consider the ultimate sleep to be death.
I do not.
No, death is a mere passage to
a different mode of being, a separate plane of existence.
There remain mysteries. (coughing)
So keep your eyes and your minds open,
gentlemen, the very survival of modern man
depends on it.
(wind blowing)
(dramatic music)
(lock clicking)
- Sarah?
Wait!
Wait, Sarah!
(voices chattering)
(wind howling)
(dramatic music)
(James crying)
(Sarah screaming)
(eerie music)
(water flowing)
Sarah!
(James gasps)
(James shuddering)
Hello?
(door creaks)
(door slams)
Hello?
Sarah?
(cracking)
- Damn you, sir!
Out! (coughing)
Out of my house!
Out, out!
Out! (coughing)
(pounding)
(dramatic music)
- Sir?
This one's got initials on it.
- They've all got initials on them.
(waves lapping nearby)
We're looking for a man with dirty fingernails.
(James straining)
(James shouting)
(James grunting)
(slicing)
(James gurgling)
(James shouting)
- For God's sakes, wake up!
You're screaming like a stuck pig!
(James muttering)
James, you're babbling, wake up!
- I'm sorry.
I'm fine.
I'm just having a bad dream.
- Yes, well, yeah, I can tell you now
I am concerned about you.
Perhaps I should just postpone my holiday entirely.
- No.
No, don't be foolish.
I'm fine.
- Fine?
Shall we confer with Mr. Webster
over the definition of that word, fine?
(eerie music)
(James muttering)
James, what?
What is it?
- Uh, nothing.
(Fletcher scoffs)
(James shudders)
(wind whistling)
- Struck down in the flower of her youth.
Sarah was a kindly girl, not given to harsh words
nor temptations of the flesh.
We beseech Thee to gather into Thy bosom
our newly departed one in the name of
our Lord Jesus Christ, amen.
- [Mourners] Amen.
(James crying)
(eerie music)
(mourners gasp)
- [Sarah] Come, James.
(James gasps)
- Struck down in the flower of her youth.
Sarah was a kindly girl, not given to harsh words
or temptations of flesh.
We beseech They to gather into Thy bosom
our newly departed one in the name of
our Lord Jesus Christ.
- [Mourners] Amen.
Our Father who art in heaven,
hallowed be thy name.
Thy kingdom come, thou will be done
on earth as it is in heaven.
Give us this day our daily bread
and forgive us our trespasses...
(rain falling)
- Professor Ambrose?
It's James Farrow, sir, the new student.
- What are you doing here?
Are you following me?
- No, sir, uh, I was...
I was...
I just saw you and, um,
may I sit for a moment?
(Ambrose sighs)
Sir, do you believe in an afterlife?
(Ambrose chuckles)
- Life is multifaceted, Mr. Farrow.
- Then your belief is--
- It's not a question of belief, young man.
It's a matter of knowledge.
Good day.
- But how can you be so certain?
- Because I have, on numerous occasions,
witnessed a phenomenon for which there is
no rational explanation.
- So the stories are true?
- What stories?
- Gossip, really, sir.
And I'd much rather hear the truth.
They say you killed someone and you're a haunted man.
- What do you want of me, hmm?
- I believe I'm being haunted by the ghost of a dead woman.
- Mr. Farrow, the mind...
No one has sufficiently explored its complexities.
There is a certain Dr. Freud in Vienna
who writes of a dream therapy--
- No, I beg your pardon, sir,
but these images, they're too vivid.
They're too real--
- [Sarah] James.
(thunder rolling)
- Mr. Farrow?
Mr. Farrow.
- Uh, I'm sorry, I...
I thought I...
- Perhaps you've been working too hard.
Good night's sleep--
- Professor, I need to know.
Professor, would you...
Could you tell me of this ghost of yours?
- Telling of this story will bring
nothing but sorrow.
- But there might be some similarities.
I mean, there might be.
Sir, please.
I am...
Lost.
- Very well, then.
But not here and not now.
Tomorrow night in my study.
- Thank you, sir.
Thank you.
- Breathe not a word to your colleagues.
- No, of course not.
- Not a word, I warn you.
(Ambrose coughing)
(rain falling)
Get up, get up!
Come on! (horse clopping)
(mournful music)
- [James] (shouting) Sarah!
Sarah!
- [Sarah] Just us, my love.
Come to me, James
Come to me.
Promise me.
(knocking) (James gasps)
- [James] Who is it?
I said who is it?
- Oh, it's me, Jenkins.
Hey, where's Fletch?
I need to get another drink.
- He's gone, he's visiting his sister in Providence.
- Oh.
- Jenkins, it's late.
- Well, why are you up?
- I couldn't sleep. (sniffles)
But you should.
- Okay.
Did you hear the latest about that girl in Portsmouth?
- No, why?
- Oh, they say it's murder.
Now they're looking for someone.
- Oh.
Well, thanks.
Goodnight.
- No, hey, wait.
I bet I know who did it.
- What?
What do you mean?
(Jenkins laughs)
- Fletcher! (laughs)
That's why he left town.
I knew the moment I saw that guy's
eyes he was a killer. (laughs)
(thuds) (Jenkins groans)
- [James] Jenkins?
- Yeah?
- Goodnight.
(door shuts)
(thunder rolling)
(dramatic music)
- I was happily married once.
When I first met my wife, Lydia,
I was like you, a student.
But being from another country,
almost friendless and certainly penniless
with barely enough money for bread,
let alone books.
But looking back now,
that was the time of my life.
I loved her more than...
(fire crackling)
Maybe more than I should.
Most men in my position would have been delighted
to find that their wife was pregnant
for the first time.
I, however, could not imagine
losing any part of her.
I feared that a child would take her away from me.
My wife died in childbirth.
I lost the only happiness I'd ever known.
She'd took my heart with her to the grave.
Yes, I believed that I had been cursed.
Left to raise my daughter on my own.
(dramatic music)
I never told Lucy that the house had been
left to us both by her mother's estate.
My excuses about paying rent were pure invention,
a device to ensure a safe distance.
She was my flesh and blood,
but her mother's death haunted me.
Being a father is not a position
for which I was ever suited
and Lucy must have sensed my remoteness.
And then, finally, we'd come to an arrangement.
She looked after me, I looked after our affairs and...
And one day I returned from lecturing in Boston.
(horse galloping)
(dramatic music)
- Father!
- Get out.
- [Man] Sir, allow me to explain.
- You, sir, are trespassing in my house.
- This man...
Is to be my husband.
We seek your blessing.
- My blessing?
How can you even imagine--
- Because I love him.
Please.
Just share a glass of wine with us.
- Get out of my house.
- [Lucy] Please, Father, if you'd just--
- Out!
- If you would just listen, I need you.
- Father, please!
I want your blessing.
(glass shatters)
- How dare you defy me!
I will arrange any marriage of yours.
- Sir, if I had known.
- Well, now you know, sir.
And mark my words, if you go against my wishes,
I will make sure that your name is destroyed
- Do not let him do this to us.
- And as for you, I curse you.
You're dead to me.
Dead!
Eventually (clears throat)
my anger died.
I went back to the house in hope
of affecting a reconciliation, but...
It was too late.
(dramatic music)
There was a note for me.
It was from him.
He said that she was dead,
that she'd passed away after falling into a coma.
He wrote that the life had simply gone out of her.
That I had taken her will to go on.
(crying) I was stupid.
(dog howling nearby)
(Ambrose crying)
Purgatory.
A way station, an in between place
where souls who have died seek expiation
or revenge.
(bell tolling)
That is all for tonight.
Go.
(students chattering)
- Boo!
(laughing) Hey, you know that murder in town?
- Jenkins, do you have anything else to speak of?
- It's all the talk of town, okay?
I was just going to say now they suspect a young man.
Possibly a college student. (laughs)
Is that keen?
Maybe it really was Fletcher.
- Don't be absurd.
(bell tolling)
- Tomorrow, noon.
At the cemetery where we first set out.
I'll finish my story if you wish. (coughs)
(dramatic music)
(Sarah laughing)
(water flowing)
(Sarah laughing menacingly)
(water sloshing)
- [Sarah] Alone together.
Come, James.
- Lucy.
When she died, I tried to make a stone of my heart,
just as I had after my wife's death.
I fought my emotions with all my strength.
(chuckle) But I still had not learned.
Then one night I was awakened from my sleep
by something.
(mysterious music)
(moaning) Who's there?
Oh.
Hmm.
(rattling nearby)
Who is it?
(doorknob rattling)
Who's there?
Hmm?
(doorknob rattling)
(pounds door)
(door crashing open)
What?
Who?
Lydia?
Ah?
Oh.
Lucy?
(flowing)
Oh, ah!
Who are you?
What do you want?
(Ambrose grunting)
(birds singing)
- So it was a dream.
That was it, wasn't it?
- I prayed that it was only a dream.
But that night, in my sleep, the apparition returned.
(door crashing open)
(glass shattering)
(Ambrose moaning)
(Ambrose sighs)
Ow.
Everything was as it had been, but it was no dream.
I tried to get on with my life, but...
But my work suffered.
And when I tried to explain to my colleagues
what was happening, they...
I ruined my academic reputation.
They asked me to resign my position.
No other institution would take me.
The house, the house was my only means
of support left to me.
I resolved to rent it out,
to be rid of the place once and for all. (sighs)
But she had other ideas.
As you can see, it's quite well kept.
The house is a little cold during this season, but we,
I have a plentiful supply of firewood.
(door opening)
In truth, I'm quite sorry to be moving away.
The house has been in my wife's family for generations.
- Did you hear that?
- Oh it's probably just the wind.
The house is extremely well ventilated
for the hot summer months.
Excuse me, sir, allow me.
Uh, this room, I...
Well, the view from this window,
I think you'll find, is quite exceptional.
(eerie music)
- Oh!
- There was nothing I could do after that.
No one would come near the place.
Not to rent it, not to help farm it.
It was then that she came to me with a proposition.
"Leave this house to me," she said.
- (whispering) Leave this house to me.
I have marked up the will.
Go off and live elsewhere.
But when you need me to do so,
I will be your tenant, for you can find no other.
- [Ambrose] "I will be your tenant,
since you can find no other."
And she gave me a bag of coins
- You can find no other.
Leave this house to me.
- But there was a condition attached
that I must come in person every week to collect the rent.
It is a ritual to which I will never grow accustomed.
It grows more toxic with each visit.
A slow death.
(dramatic music)
A bag of coins and a glass of wine.
An offering, which I so heartlessly refused
when she was alive. (coughing)
- The coins she gives you, are they real
and of this world?
- Oh, you question my sanity. (chuckles)
Well, why should you be different?
I question it myself.
Oh yes, yes, the coins are real,
but old, always old.
None of them dates beyond the day that she died
and each week I feel my soul becoming more poisoned.
I survive upon this ghostly rental,
but I cannot say how or why.
The line between dream and reality has eroded for me.
Practical and rational things mean nothing to me.
Some things cannot be mended.
(bell tolling)
I shall be late for an appointment.
That is my story.
For what it is worth.
Do not repeat it.
- Sir.
May I accompany you on your appointment?
- You know where I'm going.
- Yes.
It's the end of the week.
(sighs) I need to see, sir,
with my own eyes, what you see.
- God in heaven, why?
- If I could just see what you've seen, then--
- Then you would know that you are not insane,
that perhaps you have imagined everything eh, eh?
- No, this girl.
God, she has a name.
She's Sarah.
We used to uh...
In my dreams she appears to me at the house,
at your house.
We were there together.
Then she had dreams that maybe we could live there.
And now I think she demands it.
I mean, she...
She calls me to the house.
- There is no peace to make with the dead.
Move on with your life.
And upon your life do not follow me!
- But...
(thunder rolling)
Excuse me, miss?
Pardon me, miss.
(James shudders)
(suspenseful music)
(thunder crashing)
(knocking)
(door creaking)
- Doctor Tilton, yes?
(carriage rattling nearby)
(people chattering)
- [Policeman] Yes.
Well, what does that mean?
Had you seen him before?
- [Tilton] That's him.
- [Policeman] You!
Hey, you!
Hold it!
(crashing)
- What do you think you're doing?
- Sorry!
(tense music)
- [Policeman] Hold it!
Stop!
Hey, stop!
Let's go.
- Ah!
- [Policeman] Go that way!
- Out of my way!
(eerie music)
- Stop!
Hey!
(men grunting)
Stop!
(gun fires)
(splashing)
(barkeep gasps)
(James panting)
(fire crackling)
(nervous tapping)
(doorknob rattling)
- You look like bloody hell, James.
- Good to see you, too, Fletch.
- Still not sleeping, eh?
- I can sleep when I'm dead.
- It might come sooner than you think
if you don't take care of yourself.
- [James] What is that?
- Laudanum.
Four drops of that,
you'll sleep like the dead, I promise.
- Thank you.
(James shuddering)
- [Man] Sloth, hmm?
Anger.
Acute human passions.
- Sarah...
(bell tolling)
(glass smashing)
(Sarah shouting)
(James starting)
(dramatic music)
(thunder rolling)
(creaking)
(horse clopping)
(wind whistling)
(horse nickers)
(Ambrose mumbling)
(eerie music)
(Ambrose breathing deeply)
(coins jangling)
(foreboding music)
(Ambrose gulping)
(students chattering)
- Sweet dreams?
- Quiet.
Professor Ambrose has taken ill.
This extracurricular class is henceforth terminated
and I'll be teaching at appropriate hours.
That is all.
(students chattering)
- James.
Join us tonight for dinner.
No excuses.
I'm worried about you.
(horses trotting)
- Professor John Ambrose.
- I'm quite aware of my own name, sir.
Who, may I ask, are you?
- Inspector Ryan, Portsmouth Police.
I'm here on police business.
- Yes, that would follow.
- Professor, if you don't mind me saying so,
you don't look well.
- Thank you, Inspector.
Impeccable detective work.
But please, tell me how I may be of service to you.
(dramatic music)
(thunder rolling)
(guests chattering)
- [Woman] It was wonderful.
- I heard it was the clap.
Got it from a French whore in Boston. (laughs)
- I'm surprised the man's sick.
All this time I thought he was already dead.
(Jenkins laughs)
- Fletcher, don't speak of what you don't understand!
Forgive me, I'm--
- It's forgotten.
- The police have a new lead on their murder case.
- What are you, sleeping at the constabulary?
- It's a big story.
Can I help it if I have a natural vocation as a journalist?
- That would explain the copious amounts
of alcohol you imbibe.
- What?
- What's, what's the big news, Jenkins?
- There was a chase in town the other night.
The man got away, but they got plenty of good evidence
and a lot of eyewitness descriptions.
- Well, were these eyewitnesses blind?
Did anyone recognize him?
- Yes, they did.
And they know where to find him.
- [Fletcher] Yes, tell us.
- Oh, I'm not so stupid now, eh?
Found out he's a student.
Right here at Goshen.
- (scoffs) Are you kidding?
- No, I'm not.
(thunder rolls)
- Excuse me.
(Fletcher sighs)
- Mm-mm.
(rain falling)
- Huh?
- I take it everything is fine.
- Please, Fletch, just leave me be, please.
- Did you take the laudanum?
- It didn't work.
- What do you mean it didn't work?
- [James] I still had the nightmares.
- Well, try more, take five.
- I took six.
(horse whinnying)
(horse clopping)
- Oh, my God, Jenkins didn't have
his head up his arse for once!
I'm gonna go see what's happening.
You coming?
- No, thanks.
It's uh, it's not for me.
You have fun.
(tense music)
(men chattering)
(lock clicks)
(knocking)
- [Policeman] Open the door, Portsmouth Police!
(men chattering outside door)
Open the door, Portsmouth Police!
(lock clicks)
- We're looking for a man named James Farrow.
Do you know him?
- [Man] His room is at the end of the hall.
- Thank you.
Farrow!
(knocking)
Open the door, Portsmouth Police.
Open the door, Farrow.
(knocking) Open the door!
(policemen chattering)
(thunder crashing)
(horse trotting)
- [James] Professor Ambrose.
- [Ambrose] Get on.
- [James] You don't realize the trouble
you're gonna be getting into.
- [Ambrose] Get on.
(horse clopping)
Get up, get up, come on!
(suspenseful music)
Thank you, sir. (coughing)
- There you go.
- (groans) Thank you.
- I should fetch a doctor.
- No, no, no, no.
No.
For me the end is the cure.
- Don't talk like that.
There must be something I can do.
- You?
You did me a great service by listening to my story.
- Sir, if it's...
If it's money you need, I can--
- No.
- You need someone to collect for you.
- Oh, no, no, quite the contrary. (coughing)
Mr. Farrow, please, listen to me.
Somehow, telling you of these things
has pulled the veil from my eyes.
And I have...
I have you to thank for that.
But now you, you shall have a chance.
For you it is not over yet.
Please do not pursue this obsession of yours.
- Sir, this is far too real to be any obsession.
- Real or unreal, it doesn't matter.
Only you can rid yourself of this ghost.
Please.
Please, do not make the same mistakes that I have.
Get out of this place.
You are not safe here.
- Sir, without this money you will die a pauper
and I've seen a pauper's burial
and I will not let that happen.
I'm going to the house.
- Fool, forget the house!
- I cannot.
- Let the past go.
Do you understand what I'm saying to you?
Live, James.
Live.
- I cannot spend my life running away.
It may not be the house,
but it is most definitely what is inside.
(Amrose sighs)
She is waiting for me.
I know that now.
- No.
No.
(dramatic music)
- [Sarah] James.
(horses trotting)
(rain falling)
(muffled conversing)
- The house.
- Of course.
(door creaking)
(wind howling)
(James gasps)
- Sarah?
- James.
- Don't drink the wine!
- [Sarah] Drink the wine.
Come to me, James.
Come to me.
- I'm with you now.
- Don't!
- Drink the wine, James.
Drink.
- [Woman] No, it's poisoned!
- Drink.
- Don't!
Don't you understand, don't drink it!
What have you done?
- Wait.
Sarah!
Sarah, I thought...
(groaning)
- [Lucy] Who are you?
- Sarah?
- My father sent you here to do his bidding, didn't he?
- Lucy?
You're not a ghost.
(groans) What have you given me?
- Poisoned it to keep him sick.
I had to raise the levels.
A person gains immunity over the years.
I have to fetch a doctor.
- No!
All these years.
How can a man be so deceived?
- Look at you.
- But he said that you had the power
to make him lose consciousness,
to break through locks.
- I drugged him with ether.
I loosened the screws in the locks.
It's very easy when a man wants to believe.
- (scoffs) Why would you do this?
- You don't know my father.
- Yes, I do.
- No, you don't.
- Your father loves you, Lucy.
- Because of my father I lost
the only man I've ever loved.
- People make mistakes.
- You tell my father he can go to hell.
- Lucy!
Your father, you still have a chance.
He's dying.
- Dying?
(horse whinnying)
(door slamming)
- We're looking for James Farrow.
(James groaning)
- Come on, then.
Come on, now.
- Daddy?
Daddy.
(horses trotting)
(James groaning)
- Yeah, leave him.
(dramatic music)
(cell door shutting)
Belong to you?
- I never meant to hurt her.
- That may be, but the girl didn't have to die.
- I'm so sorry.
- It's too late, I'm afraid.
I'm done here.
Get this man a doctor.
- [Tilton] I'm a doctor.
- [Ryan] Let him see the boy.
(James groaning)
- [James] No, no.
- I'm all you got.
- (groaning) No!
Ah!
- Arsenic poisoning, there's nothing to do.
Poison'll do more damage coming out
than it did going in.
(James grunting)
You'll just have to let the poison
run its course, sonny.
It'll work its way out.
In a day or so, you'll be right as rain.
Up to your old tricks in no time.
Or you won't.
(James groaning)
- Get him out of here!
- You can't treat me like this!
I'm a surgeon!
I'm a doctor!
(Tilton shouting)
Damn you!
I am a surgeon, I demand respect!
- [Ryan] I'm sorry, son.
(cell door slamming)
(fire crackling)
(Lucy crying)
- [Ambrose] Where's my rent?
- (crying) Father?
(house exploding)
(Lucy screaming)
(James gagging)
- Forgive me.
(dramatic music)
- [Tilton] I'm a surgeon!
I'm a surgeon!
(Tilton shouting)
(mournful music)
You killed this woman!
(shouting) You!
(Tilton shouting)
(dramatic music)