>> Morning Odie.
>> Here you go, boy.
>> Ah.
>> Well, I guess I'll go
shower and shave.
>> Thanks for sharing thatwith me, Jon.
Yes folks, this is my life.
While it may look vital andstimulating, it really isn't.
That's because Jon's a dork.
He really needs to get a life,and I intend
to help him find one.
Why?
Because Jon's my friend, and I'ddo
anything to help my friend, nomatter what.
Unless of course, there'ssomething good on TV.
Ah, time for my favorite show,Yukon Stinky.
This week, Yukon Stinky insultsa polar bear.
Can't miss that.
Eh, Jon's life can wait.
>> Well, Stinky, I guess thiscase is closed!
>> Give em heck, Stinky.
>> This is WBOR, the all
national anthem, all the timechannel.
Next, by popular demand, theCanadian national anthem.
>> And, if you're not completelysatisfied with your
Ajax nose hair tweezers,
we'll refund all your tweezednose hair.
>> Take that.
And that.
And that!>> Oh.
>> And that.If it's not too much trouble!
And if you don't mind!
>> That should be enoughstimulation for one morning.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6,
7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12.
>> 141, 142, 143, 144.
Garfield, did you know thebedroom ceiling has 144 tiles?
>> The living room has 214.
>> I'm bored.
>> Why don't you organizeyour sock drawer?
>> I'd organize my sockdrawer, but I just organized
it last night.>> I'll be the judge of that.
Whoa, I'm impressed.
All nicely tucked and sorted, bycolor and size.
>> These are the winter
socks.
The summer ones are in the otherdrawer.
Here we have your natural fibersocks.
Here's your man made fibersocks.
And of course, here you've gotyour blends.
You know what, Garfield?
>> You need a life.
>> I need a life
>> Yep.
>> There's more to life, thansocks.
>> There's underwear.>> There's a bigger world out
there beyond the sock drawer,and I'm gonna live it.
>> Nice touch.
Haven't you got a life yet?
What are you waiting for?
Do I have to do everythingaround here?
>> How to make friends, andfool the rest?
>> Obviously, a book on
sincerity.
>> I forgot, I had this book.
Hey, this chapter on gettingdates, is just the ticket.
>> Great, read it and give mea full report.
The sooner you get happy withyour life,
the sooner I can get back tomine.
Humans, never satisfied.
If only they'd learn to be
content with the simple thingsin life.
Like lasagna, a good nap,
family, dog breath.
>> It says here, a singlesclub is just
the ticket, for a happening
kind of guy like me. Let's
get to work.
>> Whatever.
>> Hey there, would you liketo dance with me?
>> Sure, why not.
>> Yes, yes.Did you hear that, Garfield?
She wants to dance with me.
>> It's a miracle.
>> Come my dear, let's cut arug.
>> Hey jerk, disco is dead.>> What?
When?
Boy, you learn to dance, then
zango, 14 years, later theychange it.
>> Go figure.
>> It says here, a laundromatis a great place to meet chicks.
>> Looks like a great placeto take a nap.
>> Clean chicks.
Pardon me, I couldn't
help but notice your frillylittle uh, uh, tutu thing there.
Are you a ballerina?
>> Why, yes I am.
And I couldn't help but notice,your teddy bear boxer shorts?
Are you a dweeb?
>> Why, yes he is.
>> It says, here a video
store
is a great place to meet chicks.
>> Can we get Old Yeller?
I love movies with happy
endings.
>> Interested in checking outa little romance?
>> Will you be renting thattape, sir?
>> No, he'll be eating ithere.
>> Pardon me ladies.
I seem to have lost my
Olympic swimming medals aroundhere, somewhere.
I might have lost them overthere or over there.
I just can't remember.
Oh well, I think I'll do somepush-ups.
Out of my way creep, oops.
>> Nice going, Jon. Here weare, trying to find you a
life and all you can thinkabout, is eating.
>> So, as I was
saying to myself
when I saw you standing there,this is obviously
a chick er, lady of distinctionand exquisite
taste, to be shopping in
such an expensive store.
Did I tell you, what
lovely eyes you have?
And by the way, I
wanna thank you
for listening to me this
long, without hitting
me or shoving anything
in my mouth.
That means a lot to me, itreally does.
Hey, I tell you what.
Let's get out of this place, and
grab a cup of coffeesomewhere, okay?
This way, my lady.
>> Oh, let's give him
a hand for trying.
>> Huh, this may come as
a surprise to you
Garfield, but I'm just not verygood at getting a date.
>> No, go on.
You're putting me on.
>> Hello there.
>> Don't flatter yourself.>> Strike one.
>> Maybe, I oughta just
forget about meeting anyone,ever.
Maybe, I'll become a nun.
>> As long as it gets
you out of the house.
>> Hi there.
>> Take a hike.
>> No thanks, I just took one.
>> Strike two.
>> What is it Garfield?
Is it my breath, my looks, mypersonality?
Why can't I, yo there.
>> Buzz off.
>> Buzz.
>> Strike three.
>> Yes sirree bob.
It times like this, I sits backand feels blue.
>> Oh no.
>> And when a man feels this
blue, he's just got to get itout.
>> He's gonna sing.>> A man's just gotta sing.
>> And I thought that peoplewere jolly.
>> And now, this word fromour sponsor.
>> Friends, are you lonely,bored, a loser?
Is your idea of a fun Saturdaynight,
sitting home, watchingtelevision with your kitty cat?
Are you so boring, that youcould make cheese yawn?
Are you so out of touch, youthink disco is still in?
Have you ever passed time bycounting ceiling tiles?
Compared to you, does a slugseem hyperactive?
Well friend.If this is you, cheer up.
There's help for you at theLorenzo School
for the Personality Impaired.That's right.
At Lorenzo School for thePersonality Impaired, we
can show you how to get a life.
We can take, even the most under
interesting and tiresome bore,and turn him into
someone vital, energetic andself assured.
We'll show you how to makefriends.
How to make good music, how tomake good
first impressions, how to doimpressions, how to have fun.
And at Lorenzo's School for thePersonality Impaired,
we've got
a proven track record.
>> I thought I'd never have
a personality, but after
only 14 weeks
at Lorenzo's School for thePersonality Impaired,
I now have a great personality.
>> Six months ago, I was aschool crossing guard,
crossing the street was my life.
Now thanks to Lorenzo's Schoolfor the
Personality Impaired, I am abull fighter.
And why am I carrying thisstick, you ask?
Why, that's to keep the womenaway.
>> I wonder if they couldhelp me.
Remember, friend, atLorenzo's School
for the Personality Impaired
our motto is, if you can get apulse you can get a life.
>> Well, maybe they'll take youanyway.
>> Hello, hello, welcome to
Lorenzo's School for the
Personality Impaired.
May I help you?
>> Uh, yes, I'm here to get alife.
I mean, I have a life, but it'sboring.
Well it's, it's not that it'sboring so much as,
I just, I just don't haveanything unusually
interesting going on. Uh, notat the present, anyway.
Not that I couldn't of course,you might say
>> I'm kinda in-between.>> Yes, I see.
Well, we'll just start you rightout
in room 1A, that's how to make
a good first impression.
Down the hall, first door onyour right.
Have a nice life.
>> I'd settle for a nice
lunch.
>> I wonder if this is theplace.
>> 104
>> 25
>> Yeah.
This is the place.
>> How do you do?
My name is Lorenzo.
And what is your name?
>> Jon, Jon Arbuckle.
And this is my, are you
uh, the Lorenzo in thecommercial?
>> In person.
>> Gee, on TV you sounded so,so.
>> So what?
>> So alive.
>> Oh ha, that was lip syncyou know.
My body, Charleston Heston'svoice.
Its a, its theatrical thing,it's done quite often.
>> I see.
>> Onward and upward, shallwe?
Have a seat Mr., Airbuckle?Good morning class.
Welcome to the Lorenzo School,
for the Personality ImpairedInc.
Remember our motto is, if youcan
get a pulse, you can get a life.
So the first thing we're goingto do
this morning, is check ourselvesfor a pulse.
If you don't have one, pleaseraise your hand.
Oh my, I see we have several.
Well uh, keep your hands up inthe air, while my
able assistant, Priscilla, willcome around
and give you a second opinion.
The first step to becoming avital person,
is to make a good
first impression.
Now, how do I do that, you mightask?
Well, I'll tell you how I dothat, you might ask.
You do that by walking right upto the person,
looking them right in theeye,
giving them a firm
handshake, and
saying, hello, my name is so andso.
Everyone, turn to the personnext to
you and give it a try, now.
>> Hello, my name is so and so.
>> Hello, my name is Jon.>> Hi, I'm Mona.
>> Hello, my name is
Garfield, you probably
noticed I'm quite short and haveexcessive body hair.
>> Was that okay?
>> Was what okay?
>> My first impression, Ireally
have no idea what I'm doing.
>> Oh, good.
>> Huh?
>> Neither do I.
How was mine?
>> Your what?
>> My first impression.
>> Oh, fine!I guess.
>> You guess? I knew it!>> What?
>> I have something betweenmy teeth, don't I?
>> Oh no, no, your teeth arefine!
See?
>> See what?>> I'm blowing it!
I'm making a lousy first
impression.
>> No, you're not!
I guess.
>> Yeah, what do we know.
>> The second part of today'slesson,
is learning to dress for
success.
>> Huh, I'm naked.
>> In all modesty, I mustconfess,
in some circles I amconsidered a fashion plate,
if you will.
Let me share a few of my fashionsecrets with you, now.
Rule number one, notice how I've
coordinated my pocket protectorwith my socks.
Well, my left one, at any rate.
When it comes to color, I thinksay, wear all the same color?
Your ensemble should be havevirtual smorgasbord,
for the eyes.
Notice how I've accented
my green tweet slacks with this
plaid jacket and this stringtie.
>> Why do I have this suddenurge, to play golf?
>> Nothing impresses peoplemore, than
when you speak in a foreignlanguage.
Say for instance, Canadian.
Now, this is an easy language tolearn.
You just talk like you normallywould,
except occasionally, you throwin an eh.
Example, I'm going to town, eh.
>> I am going to town, eh.
>> Great, let's all go totown, eh.
Maybe we can have some lunch,eh?
>> I was so shy in gym class,
I had my sister take my showersfor me.
>> I was so shy, I almoststarved to death once,
because Ididn't tell my dad I was hungry.
>> You're not shy.
>> Oh yes I am.>> No, you're not.
You're like that guy on thebeach yesterday.
>> Uh, what guy?
>> Oh, just some guy.
He was walking around flexinghis muscles, and
looking for his Olympic swimmingmedals.
>> You don't really have tolearn a
language, if you can sound likeyou speak it.
People are really impressed ifyou can speak French
or if you can sound like, youspeak French.
Example.
>> Oh.
>> Very impressive, no?
>> You know, I've had just
about enough sophistication forone day.
How about you?
>> Hey you, Monsieur dumbguy, remember me?
What am I, chopped liver?Duck pate?
Foie gras?
Why am I getting so hungry?
>> That's a funny story.
>> Oh, it's been a wonderfulday, Jon.
Class was great and dinner wasfun.
But most of all, I reallyenjoyed talking to you.
Until I met you, I thought I wasthe only person
in the world, to get my tonguecaught in an elevator door.
>> And we didn't even have tospeak French.
>> What?
>> Think about it.
We had a wonderful eveningwithout having to
rely on anything, we learned inclass today.
>> You mean, we can be
ourselves
and still have a good
time?
>> Mm-hm. It's a theory worthpursuing.
>> What a concept.
>> I know, I've been workingso hard
to be what I thought otherpeople wanted.
I almost forgot, who I was.
>> Well, I'm glad I met theyou, you.
>> Huh, I was fresh out ofother me's.
Do you know, I've never beenable to open up
to anyone like this before,other than my cat that, is.
>> Other than my cat, thatis.
My cat.
Yesterday, I had a name.Yesterday, I was his bosom
buddy, his confidant, today I'mhis cat.
I can't believe it.
Jon's actually met someone wholikes
him, and it's not even hismother.
What's this world coming to?
Who would have guessed?
Oh no.
Poor Jon!
He doesn't know, what he'sgetting into.
I must stop him, before hemultiplies.
>> Then in my senior year, Iwas voted
most likely, to sit around thehouse, a lot.
And then, Garfield, what are youdoing?
>> Let go of her, Jon.
Who knows where that hand hasbeen.
>> What a sweet cat!
>> Don't listen to her Jon,she's trying
to get to you, through me
>> Would you like me toscratch behind your ears?
>> Oh that's good, she's verysmart, Jon.
Once she has me in her clutchesshe'll perhaps,
just a little bit behind thisear.
Jon listen carefully, it's alla.
Just a little lower, this is alla sinister plot to
get you to
oh, yes there ah,
oh, yeah, yeah.
>> Excuse me.
>> You okay?
>> Oh, I'm fine really it's,it's
just that I'm, I'm allergic tocats.
>> Oh. For a minute there, Ithought
you said you were allergic tocats.
>> I am. I.
>> Oh no.
>> Aw, too bad.
What a shame.
She was so cute, and such a goodear scratcher, too.
Well, come along, Jon, saygoodbye to your little friend.
It's time to fix dinner.
>> This is terrible!
>> I, I'm sorry, Jon.
>> Can't you take shots foryour allergy?
>> They don't do me any good.
>> What can I do?
>> You can chuck her on thechin, say it's
been nice knowing you, kid, andsend her on her way.
>> What if I shaved my cat?
>> Hey, ho, hi, time out!Jon, what's with you?
>> Oh, Mona, you are so
sweet.
We could really have beensomething, you and me.
>> There's something to besaid, for seniority.
>> Can we still see each
other sometime, Jon?
>> I'd like that.
>> Good.
>> Not without a chaperon,you won't.
Jon's more than just a friend tome, he's my meal ticket.
>> Come on.
I'll take you home.
>> Hang on.
Wait for me. You're notleaving me behind.
There's more than one way toskin a cat.
So to speak.
I saw this on a freeway once.
>> I'm sorry I'm allergic toyour cat, Jon.
>> I'm sorry for us.
I like you Mona.
>> I like myself, when I'mwith you Jon.
>> What?
>> Mercy
>> No. That's Merci Bocu,>> Merci beaucoup.
>> No, Jon.