- It is my high honor
and distinct privilege
to introduce to you
the President-Elect
of the United States
of America, Donald Trump.
[cheers and applause]
crowd chanting: USA! USA! USA!
- I pledge to every citizen
of our land
that I will be president
for all Americans.
And this is so important
to me.
- Middle America hates Mexis.
Who knew?
[laughs] Oh, that's right.
I did.
So bow, motherfuckers!
[giggling]
- I'm reaching out to you
for your guidance
and your help...
- [sighs]
- So that we can work together
and unify our great country.
[cheers and applause]
- RIP, nation of immigrants.
[laughing]
It sucks to be right.
Hey, don't hate the player.
Hate the game pool.
All I do is win, win, win.
Win. [laughing]
- Psst.
- ...tremendous potential.
I've gotten to know our
country so well.
Tremendous potential.
It's gonna be
a beautiful thing.
- What's up?
- How's everyone feeling?
- Like an orange antichrist
murdered their
immigrant dreams.
- [scoffs]
- [laughs]
Don't worry.
I'll crack the whip
and make sure
they pull it together
for the 11:00.
- Okay, but focus on
local elections.
And let the network
do the heavy lifting.
I will tell you how wonderful
you are.
- Wonderful enough to be
promoted to executive producer?
[mumbling]
Thank you, thank you,
thank you, caballeros!
What? Uh-huh, uh-huh.
Uh-huh. Pay up.
- Here you go.
There's your money.
- Give it to me.
- Nope.
- Give it to me!
- Que no te daré, chica.
- How did you know, puta?
- Because I'm jaded as hell.
- Psh, yeah you are.
- Okay. Let's get this thing
rolling, guys.
[dramatic synth music]
♪ ♪
- Bienvenidos
a Noticiero Unimundo 45.
A las 11:00.
[crowd chanting angrily]
- Down with Trump!
all: Down with Trump!
Down with Trump!
- [humming]
- Let's go to Maria Alejandra,
please.
- Nos acompaña el vocero
de latinos por Trump
del Sur de California.
Ahora que ganó Trump.
¿Cuál será el próximo paso?
- Bueno,
la seguridad nacional
es un asunto muy importante
para nuestro
nuevo presidente.
O sea, que
necesitamos deportar
a los mojados inmediatamente.
- Deport wetbacks immediately?
What the fuck?
Maria Alejandra,
wrap it up now.
- Los ilegales
son una vergüenza
para nuestra comunidad.
crowd: Not my president!
- Menos para mi abuelita,
que vino sin papeles,
porque no le quedó otra.
- Cut to the reel.
- It's not ready yet.
- Lo escuchó aquí primero.
Las deportaciones masivas
son inminentes.
- She's repeating
that nonsense?
Maria Alejandra, uh,
repeat what I say.
Acaba de escuchar
información no verified.
- Your Spanish is so bad,
you sound like a Mexican Yoda.
- Cállate, Darth Hater.
- She took off her earpiece,
remember?
- Reportando en vivo
desde el condado Orange,
María Alejandra de la Torre
Guadalupe Venegas Villaflor,
Noticias Unimundo 45.
- Do you think our viewers will
actually believe this shit?
- No sé.
No sé.
[phone chimes]
- [sighs softly]
[upbeat music]
- I know. You've warned us.
- Si ese idiota gana,
me voy a la chingada.
- Bueno, como dijo Zapata:
"Mejor morir de pie que vivir
de rodillas". ¿Que no?
- But you're not fighting.
You're running away.
- Ah, pues tienes
un buen punto.
She's smart. [chuckles]
- We go bye-bye, hm?
Adiós, USA.
- [sighs] Mamá, por favor,
listen to me.
Um...
Me van a dar una...
Promotion?
- ¿Te van a ascender?
- Yes. Ah, uh...
Y con dinero, yo...
Yo, um, hire...
an immigration lawyer
and get you green cards.
- Mi'ja, tal vez
deberías contratar
una maestra en español
también, ¿verdad?
- I don't need a Spanish
teacher, papá.
Mi español is very bueno.
- I no need no lawyer.
They don't like me? I go. Hm?
- So instead of dealing
with an immigration lawyer,
you'd rather go back
to narcolandia?
- Por lo menos,
los narcos de Sinaloa...
...speak the Spanish.
- Oh, okay.
Uh, so then the drug dealers
can speak Spanish to you
as they shoot you.
[laughing] Okay, great.
- No te rías.
María Alejandra de la Torre
Venegas Guadalupe Villaflor
dijo...
- María Alejandra is clueless.
[sighs]
Ella no saber nada.
You should be listening to me.
- ¿De veras?
Ay, pues mira,
si tú sabes tanto,
¿por qué no dices
tú las noticias, mm?
- And then she said,
if I knew more than Ms. Mexico,
then why wasn't I on TV?
As if those light-skinned
egomaniacs
could tell their asses
from their mics
if it weren't for the likes
of people like me.
- Oh. Oh, dang, that's--
that's messed up.
- That's all you have to say?
- Oh, I'm just getting
ready for work, you know.
- [laughing] Okay.
I know you.
You're holding back.
- What do you want me to say?
That I'm surprised that
your parents are leaving?
'Cause I'm--I'm kinda not.
- Oh?
- Yeah.
- [sighs] Mexican people
don't know how to fight.
There.
Happy?
Is that what you were
looking for?
Is that what you wanted?
- Oh, I'm sorry.
My people aren't
as woke as your people?
- Why are you saying that like
you aren't a part
of the problem?
- Wait, me?
- Yes, you.
Did you forget our plan?
Infiltrate--
both: To renovate.
- We're a local station.
And Dante hates those
kinds of stories.
- See, you always
do what he says.
I swear, you're like one
promotion away
from being a full-fledged
sell-out.
- Fuck you.
- [scoffs] Fuck me?
Fuck Unamundo.
You been there, what,
like, six years
and they still got you
behind the scenes?
- That's where I want to be.
- Oh, yeah, sure.
- And Spanish TV isn't like
mainstream TV.
The men can look like trolls,
but the mujeres?
They've got to look like
Malibu Barbie.
Not like extras
from "Apocalypto."
- Well, most of your audience
looks like extras
from "Apocalypto,"
so it kinda works.
- [sighs heavily]
So what you're saying is that
if my parents leave,
it's on me,
because I haven't done enough?
- What I'm saying is,
empower Latinos
and fight the power, boo.
[mumbling]
Not like that, okay.
Not that, don't do that.
[claps hands]
- I have a journalism degree,
but my parents would
rather listen
to some right-wing
beauty queen than me.
- It's not the end
of the mundo, mami.
- All these years I've been
climbing the fucking ladder
to make my parents proud.
Now? [chuckles]
- My mother's in Puerto Rico,
and I'm okay.
The only person that loves me
is 3,345 miles away.
But I'm okay.
The people on camera,
they have the power, but us,
we have no power.
Nada.
Luna, don't do it!
[gasps]
- How could say there would be
mass deportations?
- Why don't you learn how
to speak English already
and go work at Fox News?
- ¿Cómo? They hire?
La gente necesita estar
preparada para lo peor.
¿Sí entiendes eso, mamasita?
- Prepared for the worst?
You don't even know what's
going to happen,
but what we do know is that
because of you,
some of our viewers
are self-deporting.
- Bueno, me imagino que será
mejor irse voluntariamente
de este país a que te echen
a patadas como perro, ¿no?
- You know,
the only reason
you're on air
is because you speak
like a Mexican
and you look like a German.
- [scoffs]
- La única razón por la cual
tú nunca en tu vida
vas a salir al aire,
aparte de tu pésimo español,
por supuesto,
es que al igual
que nuestros televidentes,
tú tienes un enorme complejo
de inferioridad.
[chuckles]
Arréglate, mi amor.
- One of my stories died.
I'd like to use the extra time
to do a public service
announcement.
- What's our competition
at 11:00?
- Um, sleep.
- A PSA that late
is like Ambien.
- This one will keep them
tuned in. Trust me.
- Fine. But keep it under 30.
And Luna, put it on
after the weather.
- Um, sure.
- Mantente seco
este fin de semana.
O sea, no lloverá.
Solo estarás mojado
por el sudor.
[giggles]
[soft dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Luna, ¿estás lista?
Porque ya,
en tres, dos, uno.
- Um... [sighs]
Soy Luna grande
productora de noticias,
Unimundo 45.
Estoy aquí para adiós decir
a mis padres
que se van, ah, porque, um...
They're self-deporting.
Mis padres van porque...
they listen to everything
that María Alejandra
de la Torre
Venegas...
Jesus, how many names
does she have?
Unfounded, uh, reportaje
mass deportation--
deportaciones.
Maybe you should be ashamed
because
we aren't rich enough to get
visas or because we don't--
- Paulo, cut it off
immediately.
- You want me to get Luna
off the air?
I thought she had
your permission.
- Immediately.
- ...or our faces
are too fat for us
to belong in this country
or for me to belong on camera.
- Dante says cut to commercial.
- So I know how you feel.
- That might take me a minute.
Or 12.
I mean, olvida, right?
That we've probably been
in this country
way longer than
la primera dama
uh, Melania, or, um,
americanos importantes, uh,
like Charlie Chaplin or...
el, uh, gobernador
Schwarzenegger.
They were undocumented too.
Eran indocumentados.
Ah, and forget that we,
uh, like, raised their...
uh, escuincles
and make their avocado toast.
Y pagamos taxes.
Fuck that.
This country is better
because we're in it.
El país es mejor
con nosotros.
I mean, we've been on this land
long before those gabachos
took it from our ancestors.
California era de México,
señores.
So don't give up.
No se rinde.
Sangre Maya tener.
You are Aztec warriors.
Stay and fight!
Pelea por
tus civil rights!
¡Y viva la Raza, cabrones!
¡Viva la Raza, cabrones!
♪ ♪
[calm music]
- [singing indistinctly]
- ♪ You can't break me ♪
♪ Only raise me ♪
♪ I'm not alone,
I've got all my friends ♪
♪ They inspire me ♪
♪ To be young and free ♪
♪ Now I'm strong,
there's no stopping me ♪
♪ Follow me, follow me ♪
♪ F-f-follow me ♪
♪ I'll take you to a place ♪
♪ That you would rather be ♪
♪ Follow me, follow me ♪
♪ You would rather be ♪
♪ Tonight ♪
♪ You only live once ♪
♪ Baby that's tonight,
that's tonight ♪
[bright tone]