I am exhausted.
I can't wait to get home.
Only 30 more minutes to Ocala.
Watch out! That looks
like a body on the road!
What--?
Aren't you gonna call
-the police?
-No signal.
I told you,
nothing good ever happens
when I come through this town.
Can't even...
Can't even die right.
- The Central
Florida economic news
is not getting any better.
From a high of 12,474,
the Dow now sits at 7,500
and experts fear
it could go even lower.
2008 is not shaping up to be
a great year economically,
either for Central Florida
or the US.
And if you didn't see it,
viewers, last night,
CBS's 60 Minutes did a profile
on the growing problem
of homelessness
and they cited Orlando
and Central Florida...
- ...as the epicenter
of homelessness in the nation.
Right. And in this segment,
members of a downtown
Orlando church
are arrested
for feeding the homeless
So on one hand, we're
the epicenter of homeless...
You're not really 60.
You really work
for The Washington Post.
You really have 400 000 people
following your blog daily.
You have the body
of a 30-year-old.
Okay. Maybe 46 and a half.
Okay.
That's enough damage control
for now.
You have a mom to check on
and an editor to placate.
And I love you.
Onward.
Okay.
What part of responsibility
don't you get?
- It's eleven o'clock
in the morning.
You could have had
three job interviews already.
Hey. Hey, stop it.
What are you trying to do?
Kill me, woman? Let go.
I'm having a very trying day.
Don't tempt me.
Mercy's never been
their gift, sis.
And hard work...
-...was never yours.
-Ha, ha, ha.
You didn't even make it
to the driveway last night.
Ah!
You don't have a job.
I need help with mom.
You are not killing it.
I got things cooking.
I really do. I...
I had, I had two job interviews
last week. Two.
And I don't know
if you've noticed,
but there's this,
uh, thing, like a...
...recession...
...e-- everywhere.
It's coming all around, so...
You're just gonna have
to get some help.
-The alcohol is killing you.
-What?
What's going on with you?
Who d-- Who died
and gave you the keys
to the kingdom, Your Majesty?
You see, I am simply a subject,
able to travel through
and make my own path.
- The only path you're on
is a downward one.
Let me get you into a place.
You, you need some help,
Tony. Real help.
I don't need help.
When I need you I will call you.
What I do need...
I need some sleep.
I'm meeting Mom and
the Director Devonte at noon.
Would love some support.
Meet me there.
Okay. Okay.
Uh, just gimme a minute.
Picking myself together.
Noon. Please don't be late.
You know me.
Yeah, that's why I said,
"Don't be late."
I know me too.
Me is fine.
Me just need some sleep.
Okay.
You could have closed
the curtain!
Hey.
No, no. This no sleeping place.
Go. Go.
I got customer coming.
You don't go?
If you don't go, I call police.
Give me police.
Hey, Sport.
Can I get you something?
Cup of coffee?
Donut?
I, I'm powerful hungry
right now.
In that case, let me
pick us up some breakfast.
Is your brother coming?
Apparently not.
Um, so we'll just go ahead.
Certainly.
Dr. Ortiz is recommending
a more substantive plan
for your mother's care.
Even with increased dosages, her
dementia is worsening.
We had two incidences last week
of your mother trying to leave.
We can no longer
take care of her here.
She's going to need to be
transferred to a more secure
memory care unit.
We have a couple of suggestions.
One in particular.
Grand Vista
is our recommendation.
I'll do whatever is necessary.
Give her the best days
you possibly can.
Thank you very much.
Claude Anderson.
Sure do appreciate you...
...more than you know.
Well, mm.
I'm supposed to feed
the hungriest.
Hm. Well...
...pretty good description of me
at the moment, sir.
I'm gonna tell you
probably the first honest thing
I done said all year.
It was the first decent meal
I done had in a week.
And I'm addicted to cocaine.
And I don't care
whether I live out the day.
Are you open
to me driving you by
and showing you a place
where you can get some help?
What kind of help?
The kind you need.
Drug rehab.
I don't know
whether I'm ready for some help.
Well, truth is,
only you and God know that.
You make the first step...
...I think He'll help you
make the next one.
Hey, Mom.
It's your Brandi.
You know, I don't drink.
You must be
one of my second graders.
This place here
can be your best trip ever.
You ain't going
in there with me?
No. I gotta go back to work.
My job is to just
deliver you here.
I'll check in on you later.
All right, folks.
Everyone, let me have
your attention, please.
Everybody, eyes up.
All right, everyone.
Listen up, please. Listen up.
Probably hear some rumors about
what's coming down the p--
Well, well, well, Brandi.
Nice for you to join us
for this cheery meeting.
Aren't they all cheery?
Folks, we used to buy ink
by the barrel,
but now we are bleeding it
by the barrel.
It's a perfect storm
of growing digital consumption
and falling ad revenue.
The new owners are making
some substantial changes.
It's touching every department,
including Editorial.
Senior staff
across all departments
are going to be reassigned
or given an early retirement
provided for by the paper.
And two of you
will be reassigned
to different bureaus.
You know, I hate it.
I don't even know how long
my Senior Editing post
is gonna stand.
You'll know more as I know more.
- Harry.
- Sit down.
We're on our third owner, Brandi
They are making the decisions.
They must keep the paper afloat.
Sometimes there's
greater forces at work that--
Oh, Harry... Spare me.
Are you 12-stepping me?
You gonna let me finish?
You were
in the first round of cuts,
but I fought hard.
The best I can get
was you transferred
to Lake County Bureau.
Lake County?
Oh, you've got to be kidding me.
My mother is deteriorating,
you know.
That's the assignment
if you wanna stay in the game.
-Well, I appreciate
the heart, Harry.
-Oh, all I can do, sweets.
-My blog is, is starting
to post some decent numbers.
-True.
-True, but what?
-Your acerbic wit and comments
- haven't exactly endeared you
to the new management.
Oh, you sound like my ex!
The Brass is keeping
you on for the time being.
They're just lowering
your volume a bit.
-You get Lake County.
-They might as well have
assigned me to the Everglades.
Well, it is what it is.
But... I will still be
your editor.
Hey, the lotto came up.
You won Lake County.
Yeah. I'm a winner.
Big time.
Have a good day, Brandi.
All right. Thanks.
Mrs. Kapoor,
just to let you know that the,
the church is still
very interested
in purchasing your motel.
My husband and I have
talked about this,
and we know
what the church wants.
And I also know
that the other Indian families
will not be very happy
with us if we sell to you.
But...
...my husband is not well.
And we want to move
closer to our children.
Do you have the money? 600 000?
Um, that's something
I would have to work on.
For sure. But...
...how soon would you be
looking to, to, to sell?
Soon.
I trust you Lord, but...
...six hundred thousand dollars
plus repairs...
...a million dollars.
This isn't going to hack it.
Traveling to see my mom
is exhausting
and these small town stories
are killing me.
Lake County is part
of our subscriber base,
so they get face time.
Your job, dear,
is to provide content.
Since I've been here,
nothing I've written
has risen above page B8.
Oh, I got one for you.
A tip I just got
about a church story.
What? Religion news?
You know, that's not me.
I know. I want you
to dig on this a little bit.
Church in Leesburg
wants to buy a motel.
Am I so low
that you send me to cover
real estate transactions?
It's what they wanna do
with a motel
that makes this
a bit more unusual.
Harry, I am the last one
to cover this story.
I despise organized religion.
This church is a bit different
While back, they voted
not to build a new sanctuary
and use their money
to build shelters
and drug treatment
centers instead.
Okay. A bit different.
Now they want purchase a motel
and turn it into a shelter
for homeless families.
Listen, editorial
likes local stories
tied in with a national
news cycle.
This could be a good time
with the 60 Minutes piece.
It's worth looking into.
You are not squirming
out of this.
First Baptist Leesburg,
a Southern Baptist church
on the main thoroughfare.
Oh, you mean the group that
created their own denomination
so they could keep slavery,
that one?
A jewel piece.
Marvelous. I can't wait.
All right, go easy.
I got a good feeling about this.
-Well, you know me.
-I do know you.
Listen, that story
you did about the pastor
defrauding a church,
that was one thing.
This is another.
Do some digging.
My gut tells me
there's some kind of story here.
Oh, are you sure
your gut didn't have
too much salsa last night?
All right, Brandi. Get on it.
-Thanks for seeing me.
-Chairman of
the Finance Committee?
Of course, I'm gonna
see you.
Sorry to interrupt your study,
but this is getting urgent.
I assume this is
about last night's meeting.
We've had some good years,
but now it's...
I guess I was
really successful in preaching
in the great recession, huh?
It's the economy.
We all know it.
People were afraid,
especially our seniors
on a fixed income.
Right now, we just hunker down
and try to survive.
Gene, I don't think
I read anywhere
in the scriptures about
hunkering down.
Think they lean more
to stepping out
and, and trusting
that God will make a way.
I understand cash flow
and right now
we just don't have it.
The working capital is negative
and we are borrowing
short-term operating capital
from designated funds.
Now, with us being
$200,000 below budget...
...here's a list
of suggested layoffs.
Oh.
I hate it, but...
sometimes we just have
- to step back
from the needs around us.
And sometimes...
...we need to step forward.
I am trusting God
and so is every member
of our committee.
However, 200K is 200K
and we will live
within our means.
-Anything else?
-All plans are on hold
until we get the ship
in an upright position.
-God's got a plan.
-So does the Finance Committee.
Cec, Chaplain Pete
wants see you in his office.
Okay. All right.
I'll be right in a second.
Let me put my stuff on my bunk.
Am I in trouble?
Not in the least.
Okay, Cecil, this is the deal.
You've made a strong recovery.
You finished the first phase
of the program.
You've been A plus.
That's a first.
I can't read.
Ain't never made an A in school.
We wanna talk to you
about your next steps.
Mr. Pete, I don't wanna leave.
I'm afraid
I'll just mess it all up
and go right back to living
in the pit I was in before.
Is any way I can have
some more time?
That's what we want.
We have six beds reserved
for our disciples program.
We feel like you
would be a great asset
to the other men.
Arrange it. Set me up.
That's what I want.
Sign me up, please.
That's my family now.
And I love my mama,
and I, I look forward
to seeing them all, but...
...I ain't fit to be...
...back on my own again.
-Hey, friend. How are you doing?
-I'm fine, sir.
Cecil Clark.
Glad to have you here.
My name's Cecil too.
Yeah. I stay over
at the Men's Center.
-Okay.
-Just been made disciple,
so you probably be
seeing me quite a bit.
- Well, we can never have
too many Cecils around here.
-Glad to meet another one.
-All right.
I'll bet a lot
better looking one.
Oh, come on now.
Hey, we have
to do lunch sometime.
-I'd like that. I'd like that.
Look forward to it.
-Good deal.
-All right.
-Great to meet you.
Oh, likewise. Thank you.
- Good morning.
-Hi. How can I help you?
-Brandi Michaels.
I'm from the Orlando Sentinel
to see the pastor.
Great. He's expecting you.
You can head right in.
Ms. Michaels, hi.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
Please.
Real curious on, uh,
on why you wanted to meet.
Well, first off,
I'm not the religion reporter.
I do local news,
community affairs,
opinion, the courthouse,
and some political.
So in the downsizing,
you got Leesburg.
Something like that.
My main reason for being here
is to learn more about the motel
I've heard you're buying.
And how did you hear about that?
It's not a mystery.
We review all the city
commission agendas
and we noticed the church's
special use request.
Well...
...as the news
has repeatedly pointed out,
- homelessness is the real deal
here are in Central Florida.
You know, right now we are
just buried with requests.
We have families
where the mother and father
have lost their job
in the same week,
with single moms and dads
trying to do anything they can
to keep their families together.
Lake County has the highest
unemployment rate
in, in the entire state.
-So, I've heard.
-It's like The Grapes of Wrath.
You know, we're,
we're thinking about
and praying on,
on what we can do.
Well, when you buy this motel,
-what exactly are you planning
on doing with it?
-If we get the motel.
-There's a question?
-Oh, there's a big question.
A big giant if .
Right now we're underwater
with our budget,
and it'll take
about a million dollars
to acquire and fix it up.
And it has to happen
very quickly.
So, we are very much
living in the world of if.
Why are you pursuing
a piece of real estate
without the resources?
Sometimes you just have
to jump off the boat.
I'm hoping the Finance Committee
doesn't fire me.
-Well, there are worse reasons
for being terminated, I guess.
-Yes. Yes, ma'am.
Well, I look forward
to meeting one of the residents.
Oh, yes, uh,
I have just the man for you.
His name is Cecil.
You can ask him
anything you want.
They're expecting you
over at the Men's Center.
-Great.
-Ms. Michaels, just curious,
uh, do you have a church
you attend anywhere?
I ask the questions,
please remember
and respect that.
I'll do my best.
May I help you, ma'am?
Yes. The pastor
has arranged for me
to tour the facility
and meet one of your residents.
Chaplain Pete has you
set up to meet with, uh, Cecil.
He's just finishing up
the dishes from lunch.
I'll grab him for you.
Cec, you've got visitor.
Cec, lady from the paper
is here to see you.
Okay.
- Brandi Michaels.
- Hey.
I'm from the Orlando Sentinel.
Ms. Michaels, nice to meet you.
I'm Cecil Johnson.
-Pleasure, pleasure.
-Nice to meet you.
Uh, is there a place
we could go sit?
-And d-- do you mind if...
-Oh, everything's fine.
We can...
-Actually, here. Right this way.
-Thank you.
This interview
shouldn't take super long
Oh, my time is your time,
Ms. Brandi.
- I always like talking
about what the Lord is doing.
I'm working a story
about this church
intending to buy
the Big Bass Motel
and I asked the pastor
if I could talk with someone
who's, who's been on the streets
and you were the victim.
Well, sure I am not a victim
no longer, Ms. Brandi.
Well, it's just
figure of speech.
Uh, can we start
with your background
and your journey
in getting here?
I grew up in,
in Georgia, around Atlanta.
Uh...
Never saw my dad...
until I was 18.
And even then,
when I saw him for the first
time, it was in the casket.
My mama primarily did cleaning.
She took up ironing.
But we was, we was always broke
and I just got tired of watching
my mama work herself to death.
So... I always worked to do
what I could do,
whenever I could do it.
You know, when I was 13,
we, uh, ain't had much money.
I had cardboard in my shoes.
My momma couldn't
afford me no shoes.
So, so, I hopped the truck
and followed the workers
up to New York
where they was picking apples.
Right away, I started
shacking up with an older woman,
worked on one of the crews.
It didn't last too long
'cause police came
and picked me up
'cause I was under age.
So when I came back,
I was in school some,
but then I quit
and I started working again.
But, uh, when I got
introduced to crack...
...I lost everything and..
...ended up homeless in Atlanta.
So, my mama moved
out here to Florida.
And, uh, she was trying to,
you know, keep me
away from the drugs,
but that didn't work.
I just got deeper into it.
Started dealing myself and...
...got in trouble with the law.
What happened?
-What's happening, bro?
-What's up, troopa?
-Yeah, just killing, my bro.
You all right?
-I'm good, man.
-You'll be here for a minute?
-Yeah, I'll be out
here for a minute.
All right. I gotta take care of
something. I'll be right back.
Be right back.
♪ Heartbeat ♪
♪ Looked for one
It couldn't be found ♪
♪ You got me ♪
♪ 'Cause I took too long
to figure you out ♪
♪ Honey, you're so lost
you'll never... ♪
I went up
to a juke joint one night
where he was hanging out
with a woman.
Well, his name was Slim,
worked on one of my crews
and he owed me some money.
♪ Fallen angel, I'm on to you ♪
♪ Watch me evade ♪
It was a lively night,
partying, drinking, music.
It's a good time.
♪ You and sin a synonym ♪
♪ Heads spin
Waiting to see me fall ♪
♪ Patient
Prey on the innocent ♪
♪ She's a gold digger
Gold digger, gold digger ♪
♪ Heartbeat ♪
The truth is I was pretty
lit up myself that night.
♪ Honey, you're so lost
You'll never be found ♪
Slim.
♪ Heartbeat ♪
I've been waiting
two weeks for you.
You promised me my money today
and here I got to come
look you up.
Just pay me
what you owe me, man.
I'll be on my way.
But you can forget about me
loaning you any more money.
You off my crew.
I'm done with you.
Man, get outta here, junkie.
I'll pay you back
when I'm good and ready.
You gonna do is
waste it on crack anyway.
Slim, I ain't playing
with you, man.
Pay me my money.
♪ Small talk ♪
♪ Be the death of me ♪
♪ Ya got a taste
for the living like a zombie ♪
There's your payment.
♪ Turned it all around
You're a monster now ♪
♪ Know I chalked you up
Now I put you down ♪
♪ Undercover under palm trees ♪
♪ Walking dead in your head ♪
♪ I'm the man
I'm the man, yeah ♪
♪ Try to take me down
Never love me now
♪ Now you let me down
Throwing dirt around... ♪
Shooting a man landed
me in prison. But...
...that didn't help me at all
'cause, uh...
...when I got outta prison,
crack was my girlfriend and...
...you know, I just
got back deeper into it.
Cecil, I'm sorry.
Give me, give me a sec.
Hello.
Yeah, I'm finishing up
an interview.
What?
Okay.
Cecil, I'm so sorry.
I'm, I'm gonna have to run.
-Well, that's all right.
-I'll, uh, I'll call the Center
and reschedule
for a second interview.
I got no problem.
You know, I was just ready
to get to the part
where I get to tell you
about the angel that I met.
Angel?
As in feathers and wings?
I'll let you decide.
- Okay. Well, we'll pick it
back up when we next meet, okay?
-Thank you.
-All right. No problem.
Look forward to meeting
with you again, Ms. Brandi.
And what's happening that you
need to speak to me so badly?
It's just, um...
I, I'm flat busted and I need,
I need to borrow 200 bucks
-or my, my lights
are gonna get shut off.
-Mm.
Forget about it.
How much did you invest
in that hangover?
You need to join the workforce
- and drop the alcohol.
- Great.
I'm the only 52-year-old
in Orlando with two mommys.
Thank you.
Tony, you have a choice to make.
Just because dad
went down this path,
it doesn't mean you need to.
When I saw you laid out,
hungover the other day,
it brought dad back, everything.
Great. Great.
I'll tell you what I'll do.
I'll, I'll go sit,
I'll go stand on, uh, 436
and I'll just beg for money.
How about that?
Oh, good plan.
You can stand out there like
a Vietnam vet with a sign...
...along with
all the others who were,
like, born in 1980.
Uh, you know what?
That's a great idea.
Thank you very much.
You know what?
This conversation is over.
Thank you for nothing.
The Planning and Zoning Director
will see you now.
-Great to see you...
-Yes.
-...again, Pastor.
-Yes, yes, yes.
This is Bill Jones.
He's the Director of Operations
and he's the one heading up
this project.
Here are, uh,
some more members of the team.
There's the Director
of Community Affairs
-and the Assistant City Manager.
-Pleasure.
Our team has taken a look
at the church's proposal
and we're finding it
problematic.
Taking care of the homeless
is problematic?
Within current zonings, yes.
We just wanna show you
what you're up against
with the Zoning
and Planning Commission
and the City Commission.
-Okay.
-One, your current zoning
is church use
and this will take
a special exception use permit.
- Excuse me?
- This is not church use.
This would fall under commercial
zoning and not church.
Gentlemen, church
is not what happens
on Sunday mornings
from a 11:00 to 12:00.
This is... church use.
This is exactly church use. We,
we f-- feed the hungry
and, and house the homeless.
That's what
we're supposed to do.
So, o-- our position
is that this is 100%
church use zoning.
Plus you wanna build this
on a commercial corridor.
The city's cleaning this up
and developing
commercial businesses
for the benefit of the citizens.
T-- T-- This is for the benefit
of the citizens,
only for those who have less.
The church's attitude
is admirable,
but there's
an additional problem.
You're infringing upon
the city's historical district
and there is someone
in the commission who feel
you're exacerbating the
homeless problem in our city.
We're taking
men and women off the streets.
-I'd classify that
as helping solve the problem.
-Yes.
One commissioner's comment was,
"If you feed a stray cat,
you're just going to attract
more cats."
Some of the city see you
as contributing
to the homeless problem.
And now you wanna purchase
a motel and attract even more
homeless people to Leesburg?
Some of the
commissioners are not excited...
-...to put it mildly.
-Speaking of,
I understand you don't even own
the property yet.
Yeah, I'm meeting again
with the, the owners
of the motel tomorrow.
Once you get this
fully under contract,
you can make it pass
with the full commission,
but, uh...
don't hold your breath.
Okay. All right.
I, I'm changing
your job title now.
You're now
Director of Stray Cats.
I'll stop by
the pet store on the way home.
Sheesh.
I need the school board's view
on homelessness in Lake County,
uh, and on an organization
attempting to buy a motel
so that they can house
homeless families.
Haven't heard about that.
Who's trying to buy a motel
for the homeless?
A church,
First Baptist, Leesburg.
Why? Is there
a problem with that?
No, no. Not hardly.
Two years ago they adopted
one of our F schools.
They helped raise it
to a C school.
Mm.
Well, they're trying
to buy this motel.
And from what I hear, they say
that there's a higher incidence
of homeless families.
Central Florida has been in harm
because construction
and development have sold.
Our county has the highest
unemployment rate in the state,
and it shows most in the kids.
Our last in-house census
showed over 1000 kids
classified as homeless,
either living with a relative
or a surrogate
or even with their family unit.
Which means you have tenants.
-I know, I, I'm going to--
-Well, you're gonna
have them leave today
or I'm gonna terminate
your lease.
They'll be gone today.
Uh-huh, good.
So you think
a short-term solution
would make a difference?
My vote would be
to have one in every city
in our county.
We are gonna go
on a new adventure, okay?
And it's gonna be so much fun.
-Come on.
-Okay.
Okay. Okay.
Children and families are
living in pay-by-night hotels.
There are tents,
you name it.
You can imagine
how it affects their education.
Thanks.
This has been helpful.
Hi. I came as soon
as I got your call.
Thank you.
We will still sell to you,
but we can only
give you 30 days.
Th-- Thirty days?
So far,
we have nine cash offers.
I guess if God could create
the Earth in six days,
He can buy a motel in 30.
And if we don't have the money
in 30 days,
then I guess we're out
on the street, so to speak.
You did get my attention
with the angel thing.
Yeah, well...
...I'm done for sure
that's what it was,
an angel, pure and simple.
Chaplain Pete thinks so too.
Okay. I'm all ears.
Okay. Well,
lemme see where I leave off.
My mom was praying
in the other room
while I was smoking crack.
Jesus...
...I know we done
talked about this
many a times.
So, I had to get outta there.
I've buried three boys!
I ain't letting this one go!
-The devil has
a strong hold on him!
-Just let me die.
It's gonna have to be you
who break the devil's knuckles!
Can't do this
to my mama no more.
Just let me die.
Please.
Please, Lord.
Can't take it.
Just make me go.
Watch out.
Can't even die right.
Ended up falling asleep
in front of a convenience store
where a man came
and picked me up.
Brought me right here.
I'll check in on you later.
It's nice that he noticed you
and was willing to get out
of his own comfort zone.
Oh, I promise you,
he was really
out of his comfort zone
I waited a few days
for Mr. Claude to come back
like he said he would...
...but it never happened.
So...
...after he didn't call,
I decided to call
where he work.
I just wanted to tell him
thank you for bringing
me into the Center.
BAHR Construction.
Oh, yes. How you doing?
My name is Cecil Johnson
and I was, uh,
I was hoping to speak
to one of your Road Supervisors.
Which one?
Claude Anderson.
I'm sorry.
We don't have a Claude Anderson
that works here.
-Well, this is BAHR Construction
on Telebox Road, right?
-Yes, it is, sir.
Yeah, well, see,
a few weeks ago I met a man
named Claude Anderson.
He drove a gray truck
and had one of your signs on it.
Said he was one
of the supervisors
on your road crew.
I'm sorry, sir, but
we don't have any gray trucks.
All of our work trucks
are white.
Sir, I don't know
who it is you met
that purported to work for us,
but we don't and never have had
-a Claude Anderson work us.
-That don't make...
I know I met him.
I'm really sorry, sir.
There's no one by that name
who works here
and he certainly
wouldn't have had a gray truck.
Okay.
All right. Thank you.
See Chaplain Pete think
that was an angel
that brought me here.
I think so too.
I mean they never
had a Claude Anderson.
Saw the man once,
never saw him again.
And they for sure
didn't have any gray trucks.
I'd like to talk
a little bit about race.
For a mostly
white church to be doing this,
I'm, I'm curious
about how you've been treated.
Like a king, Ms. Brandi.
The September 6th meeting
of the City Commission
is called to order.
Let's stand for the pledge
and for the invocation.
I pledge allegiance to the Flag
of the United States of America,
and to the Republic
for which it stands,
one nation under God,
indivisible,
with liberty
and justice for all.
The first agenda
on the docket tonight
is First Baptist, Leesburg,
and the request for
a special exception use permit
to purchase the Big Bass Motel
to use as a shelter
for homeless families.
Planning staff,
your observations
and recommendations, please.
All the departments have
reviewed the application,
gas, no comments,
public works, no comments,
electric, no comments,
police, questions
on security and the homeless,
planning, out of zoning approval
can only be approved
with the issuance
of a special usage permit.
Pastor, any comments
from the church?
Uh, just, just a few.
We realize our homeless feeding
and drug rehabilitation programs
don't always match
eye to eye
with the dreams and vision
of the city planners
here in Leesburg.
But...
...we believe
they are closely aligned
with the heart and mind of God.
We feel the commission
needs to take note
that in the middle
of a great recession,
that Florida has the highest
unemployment rate in the nation.
And our county has the highest
unemployment rate in the state.
At this moment, right now,
we are sitting on the pinnacle
of the unemployment problem
in the nation.
To not acknowledge that,
it's, it's very shortsighted.
Just today we received a call
from a family where both
the wife and the husband
lost their jobs
in the same week.
Three kids, no backup
and no place to go.
We know this
isn't an end-all solution...
...but it is a big step
in the right direction.
That is all.
Okay. The commission
will hear from the public
and anyone withstanding.
Doreen Norris, 1440 Herndon St.
Speaking for our neighborhood,
we don't think
this is a good idea
in the least.
We are only one block away.
Just one block.
A-- And, and,
and while we understand
that this is a very good thing
that the church is doing,
all right, we just feel
in our beautiful,
recently-deemed-historical area
that this is just not right
- to do to a neighbor.
- Yeah,
- great-grandfather
ran the first...
...bootlegging operation
in Leesburg.
-Seriously?
-Mm-hmm.
Next please.
- Hm.
- Don't judge.
John Walderman,
Quality Auto Parts.
Land of days, what is this
commission thinking about
that it's gotten this far?
We've had monthly meetings
with the city
to d-- develop this corridor.
Now you wanna put
a homeless center
right in the middle of it!
- I hope you have more
brains than that.
Yeah!
Come on, Marge.
Marge Roberts, my husband
and I own Leesburg Pharmacy.
The reason my husband
is not here,
is that he's at our store
fending off the homeless.
Every day...
...the homeless,
they're panhandling
and accosting our customers.
If you vote for this...
...you're only voting to worsen
in the problem in our city.
Yeah.
Next, please.
Jerry, Jer-- Jerry Baker,
809 High Street.
One thing no one's mentioned
here is property values.
Far as I'm concerned, ch--
churches are like parasites.
They pay no property taxes
and the rest of us have,
have to carry the tax burden.
Isn't that right?
You'll see it! You'll see it!
I got 45 signatures
right here, Mayor,
against this proposal
from my neighborhood!
Let's stop this!
Trey Grantham,
King Developments.
For the record,
we have a client interested
in purchasing the motel.
They have a proposal tied
into the city's comp plan
that would be an appropriate
use of the property.
Have you talked
with a property owner?
We have engaged
the Kapoor family.
Uh, they are of course,
honoring the contract
with the church
for the next few days,
but our offer
is substantially higher.
The family will accept our offer
if the church is not able
to acquire the property
or the City Commission
denies the zoning variance.
Well, I see
some others want to speak,
but the commissioners
have a stack of, uh,
emails and letters
in regards to this issue.
Commission members,
what is your pleasure?
I move we table it.
Study the issue a bit further.
I second that.
We don't even know
if the church is gonna be able
to purchase the motel.
I'd favor a development more
in line with our comp plan.
The motion is to table
this proposal
until we see if the church
is able to move forward
and we look
at our comp plan more closely.
All in favor to postpone?
Opposed?
Okay, very good. With a,
uh, five-to-zero vote
the proposal is postponed
for city staff
to evaluate this more
in relationship
to the development
in the city comp plan,
and to see whether First Baptist
will actually be able
to purchase the motel.
Meeting adjourned.
Welcome to Lake County.
Well, if your faith is
supposed to move mountains,
I recommend a steam shovel.
This is not looking good.
Well, encouragement
at every corner.
-Let's regroup.
-Yeah.
Cecil, you all right, man?
Like you swallowed
a handful of stress beans.
Yeah. I'm fine.
Hello, Cec. Let's go.
Come on.
First fishing trip
with the pastors.
We'll try not to disappoint.
A report said
that the fish are probably
all up and down channel lakes.
So we are gonna get them.
This is gonna be a good time.
All right.
Time to go knock them dead.
Grab that cooler,
uh, behind you there.
I got mine. All right.
Right behind the seat.
Hey, hey.
Where you guys been?
Two boats are already out
of their spot by the spillway.
Bait shop was stacked.
Got here as soon as we could.
Well, hey, we ain't waiting
any longer. Let's go.
- All right.
- Cecil, come on!
We playing this trip around you.
Come on, Cecil!
That cooler's not gonna
put itself in the boat.
You know, maybe he's not
used to being around
certifiables like y'all.
Says the guy...
Come on, Cecil!
Cecil.
Cecil, you all right, man?
What's going on?
I'm gonna go che--
check on him real quick.
Hey, Cec, are you okay?
Uh, hey, you guys
go on ahead, okay?
Just bring the gear
by my place later.
- I'm gonna get Cecil back.
- All right. Take care.
Hey Cecil, you--
Are you okay, man?
Y-- You afraid of the water?
A-- Alligators or...
Why won't we go grab
a cup of coffee?
Cherokee saying...
..."If you listen
to the whispers...
...you don't have
to listen to the screams".
I see the screams.
Would you like
to share the whispers?
You afraid of the water?
White men.
I don't trust any group
of white men.
You're afraid
of three white pastors?
I mean, I've had people
walk out on my preaching before,
-but never
from a free fishing trip.
-Nothing personal.
It ain't even you.
I don't trust
white guys, period.
Cec, my man.
Really didn't wanna
be out too late that night.
- You got lot in store
for you tonight.
- Yeah, man.
Got some of that new stuff
in from Columbia,
make you think
you can fly there.
Tried to tell them
I just got a job
and had to be there
at 6:00 in the morning.
But they insisted.
Huh, it's your call man.
But tonight,
we're gonna light it up.
It ain't like
they had to pull my arm off.
I kind of wanted to go.
So I told them, "Let's go."
And for you, my brother...
...we're gonna introduce you
to Charice.
Ooh, yeah, Charice.
Plus I wanted
to meet their Charice.
Where this Charice at, man?
- What you mean?
- That's here.
- I mean, it's here.
We're meeting in here?
Yeah.
Y'all convinced her to meet
y'all out here, that's--
Yes. She always
want be on the private jets.
Okay.
That's okay, Cecil.
- You'll have fun.
- Yeah, man.
Hey, Charice.
She's around here somewhere.
-Where did it go?
-I don't know.
Why don't you go
look over there?
- Come on, man.
- Okay.
Whoa, no! Oh, come on, man!
No. No, come on, man.
Let go!
- Come on, Cecil.
- Let me go, man.
Let me go, man! Come on!
Come on, man! Come on.
- I told you, you're gonna
have a good time here, Cecil.
-What do you think?
Beginning to see this coming?
-Yeah, he does.
Ugh, no. Come on.
What did I do, man?
I say, he is about done.
We can just, uh,
throw him in the canal,
leave him for the gators.
One more.
All right. One more, one more.
Let's go.
You know...
...I wouldn't want to go
fishing with us either.
When I got out that truck...
...saw them three guys
down there...
...three white men
waiting on me like that...
...everything just came
flooding back.
That's why I couldn't
bring myself to come
down there with you.
You know,
Mr. Claude picked me up
and brought me back
to the Men's Center.
That there was an angel.
So really,
this is the first time
I've even gotten in the vehicle
with a white man since then.
I'm honored it was me.
You know you're safe
here, right?
Yeah.
This home.
I know it.
Okay.
Speaking of it,
let's get you home.
And you know what? And if
you wanna talk about this more,
another time we can.
Mind if we don't say anything
to Chaplain Pete about this?
It stays here.
- Hey, Cecil.
- Hey.
Hey, thanks for coming out.
-Glad to, Mr. Clark.
-Oh.
You know, I'm always
looking for more work.
Please just call me Cecil.
Ah, can't do that.
You know,
two handsome guys like us,
people might confuse us.
Yeah, folks might.
Uh, would you like a bite?
Uh, no, no. I'm fine.
I, I already ate over
at the Center.
-Okay.
-But I rushed
right over 'cause, uh,
-Pastor Cliff said
you wanted to talk with me.
-I do. I do.
I know Ms. Louise
gave you some equipment
to get you set up in
your lawn maintenance business.
She sure enough did.
I already got
a few lawns set up for me.
Well, Cecil,
I admire initiative
and a man that will work.
That is the American way.
There's a reason I have
a 50-foot American flag
flying outside.
I love this country,
and the opportunity that God
gave me to build this business.
Mrs. Jackie and I
had been blessed
far more than we ever imagined
when we first got married.
But this business
is not just about me,
but about helping others also.
Pastor Cliff has told me
a little bit about your journey,
and I'm all in for encouraging
a man on the upward path.
Mrs. Jackie and I have
decided to give you
your first truck
through Cecil Clark Chevrolet.
When you go outside,
the keys are waiting for you.
That's it, Cecil.
You're officially
in the lawn business.
You got to be kidding me.
I...
I don't know what to say.
Mr. Cecil, that's...
...by far...
...the nicest thing anybody,
Black or white...
...ever done for me.
Listen, Cecil...
...Mrs. Jackie and I
have quit seeing color.
I grew up in Alabama,
surrounded by racism.
But you know what?
My surroundings didn't determine
who I was gonna be.
I judge a man on his character.
And what he does, Black or
white, makes no nevermind to me.
Mrs. Jakie and I have
stopped seeing color,
and the opportunity
that God will let me see
all the colors in his world.
Oh, man.
You got me?
Yes, sir, Mr. Cecil.
Yeah, I got you.
Good.
Now, let's go look
at your new work truck.
Come on.
I hope you like blue.
Hey, Pastor,
I got something for you.
-You always got something
for me.
-Yeah, I know.
But... this time
I really got something for you.
That there is $300 for my
first job in the lawn business.
Yeah, God gets it first,
but we all got to give
if we think
we're gonna get this motel.
Cecil, I can't tell you
how much this gift means.
Oh, my pleasure.
When I was in need,
church invested in me.
I just wanna do the same thing.
When you, uh,
when you go home tonight,
I'd love for you
to read Luke 21.
There's a story about a woman
in there that I think
you'll find interesting.
Well, I'll do it.
Chaplain Pete done made me
the night watchman.
So, I got
plenty of time to read.
Yeah.
-You have a good day, Pastor.
-You too, Cecil.
- Hey.
- Brandi.
I'm on it.
The piece is finished.
I think you love it.
It really came together.
Great. I'm sure it did.
Listen, this is not
the standard get-it-in call.
Editorial says,
"Hold on the story for now."
No, you have to run it.
You didn't wanna do this piece.
Things change.
You have to run it tomorrow.
No. Not a chance.
Best would be in back
a local and state.
Harry, don't do this.
You have to publish
this tomorrow.
Why tomorrow?
Well, the City Commission
is having a vote
and I want the community to know
what's really going on here.
It's a chance for the people
to see beyond their noses
and, and really
make a difference.
Please.
All right. Well,
I can't guarantee anything,
but I'll run it up the flag pole
because you insist.
Oh, that's all I can ask.
All right, sweets, email it over
and I'll take it into editorial
for a quick look
and final approval.
Please make it happen?
You're the best.
-Yeah. Well, tell it to my wife.
-Sure.
And that was the last
part of it.
- Uh-oh. Y'all--
- Oh, Cecil.
-Y'all--
-Come on in and have a seat.
Have a seat.
Y'all double teaming me. Am I--
-I ain't in trouble, am I?
-No, you're in big,
big time, big trouble.
Uh-oh.
Listen, um,
Cecil, how would you
like to become
a teacher in the church?
I'm not sure I can.
I can barely read.
Plus, I...
I don't know when somebody
coming to the church
and say, "What that scoundrel
doing up there?"
Well,
i-- if the scripture is true
and, uh, and I believe it is,
then everything is,
Everything's forgiven.
It's in your past. It's gone.
Chaplin Pete and I
would like you to start up
a 12-step program.
Look, the most effective teacher
is someone
who has already
navigated successfully
what they're teaching.
And, and we think
you'd be perfect.
Okay. Well, what would I do?
Well, you would just love them
and help them walk
the same journey you walked.
What do you say?
Well...
- I'm gonna have
to pray about that.
Well, you would also
be the first Black teacher
and leader...
...in the 152-year history
of this church.
It's about time.
- Hey, y'all quit looking at me
like that.
I'm keeping ready to run up
outta here, I'll tell you.
Think on it. Pray on it.
We think you'd be perfect.
- And you just let,
let me know in a few days.
Cecil, everything
you've been through,
God custom made you for this.
The funeral home is here.
Are you okay for them
to take her away?
Yes.
Wait. Wait.
Just one second.
Okay.
Can I help you?
I just felt the need to pray.
College kids just left,
but I can open the chapel
if you need for a few minutes.
Look,
you can't imagine...
Come on in.
It's a good saying...
...right now it feels like
an impossibility.
Okay. It's been a while
since we've talked
and I'm here
because I need help.
I'm sorry.
This is the first time ever,
I'm gonna trust you.
I'm a mess.
Well, now you commanded us
to take care
of widows and orphans...
...I'm trying.
I need about
a million dollars and...
...to change five commissioners.
Help me.
Thank you for a wonderful mother
who did nothing
but love and support me.
Forgive me.
Forgive my... sarcasm.
Forgive my negative attitude
towards people
who I suppose
are doing the best they can.
I have a brother who's
killing himself in a bottle.
I've done everything I can.
Could you help him?
I just wanna say...
...I see something
different here...
...and my story needs
to be published on time.
But it's not about me anymore.
It's about people who need help.
So...
So, please...
Please.
- "To Senior Editor,
Harry Cobb...
...and the editorial board
of the Tribune Company...
...very rarely does a writer
have an opportunity
to pen something that will truly
make a lasting impact.
But here...
...in a small
Central Florida town,
I have a uncovered that story.
This story is not only about
a desperate need, but was...
...also, for me, a voyage of...
...discovery of who I am...
...and why I write.
The attached is the result
of my research
and interviews on homelessness.
My eyes have been opened,
and I hope..."
Hmm. No.
"...even pray that your eyes
will be opened as well
to see the value in this piece.
Brandi Michaels, Staff Writer,
Lake County Bureau."
- Good morning.
- Oh, not so fast.
Pete just called
and Channel 7 out of Orlando,
is across the street and wants
to do an interview with you.
-What?
-Yeah! There's an article
in the paper. I haven't seen it
yet, but apparently,
there is a front page article
in the Sentinel
about the motel project
and Channel 7 wants
to do a segment now
to headline
on the six o'clock news tonight.
Oh, and you have 57 messages and
counting, all about the motel.
-Uh, uh, could you go get me
a copy of the paper, please?
-Mm-hmm.
And I'll, and I'll read it
when I get back.
Okay.
Great.
♪ You can't judge a book
by its cover ♪
I guess, it's a,
a television interview.
-I don't, I don't really know.
-Really?
There's also something
that ran in the paper.
I don't...
♪ ...by the same ♪
♪ Take out all the value
of your word ♪
♪ And put it on my back ♪
♪ Pierce my skin
Give me drugs act to blame... ♪
Is this the church
buying the motel?
Uh, yes, ma'am.
We are trying to buy it.
Good.
Here are blankets, comforters
and sheets for six beds.
Uh, thank you very much.
That's amazing.
- Just bought them
at JCPenney this morning.
All brand new.
- Wow.
- This is great.
-All right.
-Oh, maybe come back the rest.
-Oh, yeah, I will.
See you in a bit.
-Run them into the office.
-Thank you, ma'am.
Thank you so much.
-Oh, my pleasure.
-Thank you.
-W-- What?
Pastor, Pastor. Here.
I read the article
on the front page today
and here is a check.
And I will be back next month
with another one.
-Janet, I'm sp-- speechless.
-You know what?
After reading
what that Sentinel writer
wrote about those kids,
I'm gonna do everything I can
to treat those homeless children
just like they were
my very own kids.
God bless you.
-God bless you.
-Thank you.
You must be the pastor.
-Y-- Yes, sir. That's me.
-That's great.
Listen, Lake County Chopper
is gonna be kicking in.
We got 5K for you.
And when the rest
of the brothers hear about it,
you can count on us
for some more.
That is amazing.
-Thank you.
-No, glad we could help. Yeah.
God bless.
Pastor Lea,
Wow, what a unique idea,
buying a motel or the homeless.
Yeah, I, I guess
that doesn't happen every day.
What is your motivation?
Well, our founder
has some pretty clear words
for us about, um,
those who have less.
And, and during this recession
it's these homeless families,
they, they are certainly
the ones who have less.
Kind of like baby Jesus
needing a place to stay?
Yeah, that's, that's
one way to look at it, yes.
Well, I am so enthused.
Just since our camera crew
started setting up,
- I've seen several
donations that...
...for lack of a better word,
drive in.
Yes, ma'am. It's incredible.
It, every, every penny is going
towards buying the motel.
Um, and we, we need
$600,000 by next week.
Well, the writer beautifully
described the project
and told the community
to get off their wallets
and do something
for homeless children
and families in this recession.
This is
truly inspirational, Pastor.
A 180 degree turn
from the church fraud story
we ran last month.
-Yeah.
-Shannon Moser reporting
live in Leesburg.
This story,
we will be following.
- Pastor Lea?
- Yes.
-Pastor Paul from All Saints.
-Oh!
- Great to see you.
- Same here.
Interesting timing
on the article today.
We had our parish missions
council meeting this morning.
The, uh,
article in the paper was
our main topic of conversation.
Well, the council was unanimous.
Here's $25,000 to assist
with the down payment.
- I, I'm speechless.
- Don't be.
We share your burden
for the homeless
in our community so...
-Thank you.
-You're welcome.
Take care. Have a great day.
Wow.
Barry Jones, BB&T,
regional vice president.
You have no idea
how glad I am to have found you.
-W--
-When 60 Minutes ran the special
on homelessness
in Central Florida,
our executive team decided
to adopt Central Florida
as a focus for our company
and employees.
When we saw the piece
in the Sentinel today,
we knew we had found our cause.
So we estimate
it's gonna take you about
a quarter of a million dollars
in the initial renovations
when you buy the building.
This check should cover that,
plus we'll be doing more
as the project progresses.
Plus we will be offering you
our lowest commercial loan rate
if you need it for the mortgage.
I would like to stay longer,
but I got to get back.
But my assistant will be
following up with you.
Have a nice day.
Wha--
- Do you believe
just what happened?
I think I just changed banks.
You got that right.
Wow.
Mm. Here you go.
You have some visitors.
Well, this is either, uh,
very good news or very bad news.
You want the good news?
Or the very good news?
Uh, I, I'll take the former.
Steve Pullum,
personal, uh, representative
for Bernice Jefko
and her estate.
Uh, nice to meet you, Steve.
Mrs. Jefko was adamant
about what she wanted done
with her estate.
And as, uh, as most people know
she was a quiet
but a very determined woman.
Well, I, I honestly
didn't know her that well.
I mean, whenever
she could make it to church,
she would always, sort of,
slide in the background
and she was always very quiet.
But she was always smiling.
Well, she may have been
quiet in her living,
but she was not quiet
in her giving.
Bernice was a dairy farmer and,
although she never made
what you'd call
big money,
what she did have was land.
And lots of it.
And may I add,
very valuable land.
That is correct.
And it is legitimate.
When she found out that you
gave up building your sanctuary
to help the needy people
in this community...
...it made a big impact on her.
She never forgot it.
Her will
leaves you several
million dollars' worth
of prime real estate.
So you can both
build your church...
...and expand your operation.
She was of sound mind
and at full
testamentary capacity
even though
she was dying of cancer.
You need to read your own sign.
Now, there's still a lot of work
that my office
has to do with her estate,
but I wanted to come here
and tell you personally
about her request
and, and, in light of the,
in light of the article.
Wow.
I never,
ever, ever,
never ever thought
that my religion-mocking sister
would be driving me
and dropping me off...
...at a church.
Well, I never thought
I'd see you be sober.
But I can see that for you now.
Do we gotta?
Yeah, you gotta.
Just remember I'm the executor
of mom's estate
so I determine
where every dollar goes.
Listen, this place
will help you.
I've seen it with my own eyes.
It's gonna be awesome.
Come here.
Good bye.
-I love you.
All right.
-I'm Cecil.
-Hi. I'm Tony.
Nice to meet you, Tony.
Welcome to home!
Come on, man.
Are you excited?
You guys ready?
Welcome to your new home.
-Thank you!
-Don't thank me.
-Thank her.
-Oh.
Congratulations.
Hey.
-Hey, hotdog.
-What's up?
You're up.
Your piece on the Samaritan Inn
lit up the scoreboard.
Few things for you.
Thing one,
The Post called.
As a follow-up
to the 60 Minutes piece,
they want to do
a series on homelessness,
the best practices nation-wide
addressing it.
Thing two,
you are a finalist with
the Florida Press Association
for the Frances DeVore
Public Service Award.
Thing three...
...the City Commission voted
four-to-one last night
to make
the zoning change permanent
for the motel to become
a homeless shelter.
Two hundred people
showed up to the commission
and supported your article.
And?
I can tell
you have something more.
I do.
The Brass wanna bring you
back to Orlando.
And they want to give you a seat
on the editorial board
for the entire chain.
You hit the Florida Lotto,
girlfriend.
You're welcome back
to the motherland.
Thanks, Harry.
Great on the first three things,
but on thing four,
I think I'm just gonna stay put.
What?
You wanted out.
I know, but I'm developing
a story that I wanna pursue.
All right, superstar.
Well, listen, come visit us
in Orlando, all right?
-Okay.
-We miss you.
Take care.
Later.
-♪ I was guilty ♪
-♪ Guilty ♪
-♪ Of all the charges ♪
-♪ Charges ♪
♪ Doomed and disgraced ♪
-♪ But Jesus ♪
-♪ Jesus ♪
-♪ With his special love ♪
-♪ Special love ♪
♪ Saved me by his grace ♪
-♪ He pleaded ♪
-♪ Pleaded ♪
-♪ And pleaded ♪
♪ He pleaded my case ♪
♪ Am so glad that ♪
♪ Jesus dropped the charges ♪
♪ Ah, Jesus dropped the charges
Now I'm saved ♪
♪ Now I'm saved
through grace and faith ♪
-♪ I was guilty ♪
-♪ Guilty ♪
-♪ For so long ♪
-♪ So long ♪
♪ Lived in sin too long ♪
-♪ But Jesus ♪
-♪ Jesus ♪
-♪ With his special love ♪
-♪ Special love ♪
♪ Reached out
with his arm so strong ♪
-♪ He picked me up ♪
-♪ Picked me up ♪
-♪ Turned me around ♪
♪ Gave me a brand new song ♪
♪ Ah ♪
♪ Jesus dropped the charges ♪
♪ Jesus, ah, Jesus ♪
-♪ Dropped the charges ♪
-♪ Now to him I belong ♪
♪ Now to him I belong
Look here ♪
-♪ You may remember ♪
-♪ Remember ♪
-♪ And remember ♪
♪ Some of the thing I've done ♪
-♪ But Jesus ♪
-♪ Jesus ♪
-♪ With his special love ♪
-♪ Special love ♪
♪ Forgave me from everyone ♪
-♪ He put me ♪
-♪ Put me ♪
-♪ On the right road ♪
-♪ Right road ♪
♪ Lifted my heavy load ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Jesus dropped the charges ♪
♪ Now I'm free ♪
♪ Now I'm free down in my soul ♪
♪ Ah-ah ♪
♪ He dropped the charges ♪