[Upbeat music]
- [VOICEOVER] Okay. I'm
walking through it now.
[Screaming]
It's dark out here.
[Distorted speech]
This place is kinda creepy.
Found some blood in the dirt.
[Distorted speech]
I don't see any animal tracks,
just some footprints.
[Crying]
Leads up to an old house,
I'm gonna follow it
and see where it goes.
Oh god.
[Static]
[Yelling]
There's more blood, yeah there's
definitely blood out here.
[Heavy breathing]
[Static]
It looks like a slaughterhouse.
Wait, I see something.
I see them, they're out here.
[Yelling]
Hold on, I'm running
towards them.
[Yelling]
- You wanna set that up?
- Yeah.
- Coffee? Just made it.
- Yep.
Between a baby and a phone...
Did you sleep?
- Margie told me to
disconnect the phone
after the third time
stackman called.
- Should've
[sighs]
- So you weren't able to a
word out in interrogation one?
- Kid's scared as a
mouse, not a peep.
- Mmm. Couldn't even
explain away the blood?
- Nope.
Waiting on transportation
to the hospital
to get checked out, but,
ours in the meantime.
- So we don't even know
what we've got yet?
- Well, apparently,
the camera washed up
on a creekbank after some rain
pushed a dead tree downstream.
Someone found it bashed
in and covered in muck.
- Hmm. They made it work.
- Techie was able
to get all of it
transferred onto video tape.
- Listen, I don't mean to be
out of line here stackman,
but I'm assuming
that we got called in
at three am because this is
the councilman's kid, right?
I mean, technically, this is
not a missing person's case,
it hasn't been 24 hours yet.
- 26, so technically, it is.
- You don't think these
college kids are just
on a bender back there
in the hills somewhere?
- Councilman reported them
missing over 24 hours ago,
the mayor wants us on this asap.
We've got one of them in there,
beat up pretty bad
and not talking.
- Fair enough.
[Pop music playing]
- [Kim] Seriously?
- [Chase] We are up,
yes, yes, this is live!
This is live ladies.
Come on, let me see that face.
Say something Kim, who are you?
Where are you from
and what brings you
to the dead mountains of
Timbuktu middle of nowhere?
- Is anyone else
getting a signal?
I'm not getting anything, ugh.
- [Chase] Okay,
and Amanda, hola.
- Hola.
[Laughing]
That's the only word
you know, isn't it?
- [Chase] No. Yes, yes it is.
- Yeah, that's what I thought.
- Can we just let
the record show
that I am the only guy here.
I just want the record to show,
that this is how
I spend my break,
me, Amanda Dawson, and Kim...
What's your last name?
- Does it matter?
- And Kim does it matter.
Just the three of us,
here, this is how I roll.
[Laughing]
[Upbeat pop music]
- [Kim] You have an ID?
- [Chase] Of course I do.
I got this, trust me.
Also, just keep the engine
running, I'll be a sec.
Be right back.
Hello, what are
you listening to?
- The blues. How can I help you?
- [Chase] I love the blues.
A bottle of Jamaica rum, please.
Thank you. Oh.
- ID please.
- [Chase] Ah, bluesman like
yourself doesn't miss a beat.
Would not expect
anything less, my friend.
[Phone ringing]
- Yeah?
Hey, hey, hey!
- [Chase] Go!
- [Amanda] What?
- [Chase] Go! Go!
- [Amanda] Oh my god!
- [Chase] Go, go, go!
- [Amanda] What did you do?
- [Chase] Just go, hurry!
- [Amanda] Oh my god,
chase, are you serious?
- [Chase] Come on Amanda, go!
[Crashing]
- [Kim] Oh my god!
- [Chase] Holy shit. Go!
- [Amanda] What?
- [Chase] Go, go!
[Car speeding off]
- What are you doing,
you can't just leave,
Amanda, go back!
- [Chase] We'll be
fine. Keep driving.
- We have to go back, oh my god,
you guys, we have to go back.
- [Kim] Yeah, go.
- [Chase] Relax, it was
just a little Fender bender,
we'll be fine, okay?
- He could've gotten
the license plate chase!
- [Chase] No way, trust
me, we're gonna be
out of here in a
couple of days anyway,
they won't even
know where to look.
- That was totally
just a hit and run.
- [Amanda] What? No, no, no.
- Yeah, it was and
now we're gonna be
on the news when we
get arrested for it.
- [Chase] Stop.
- Holy shit.
- What? What is it?
- Pause the tape.
- [Chase] ...Not gonna be
able to find us out here.
- Jesus.
That was Katie Levenger.
- In the truck?
- Yeah.
- That's wishful
thinking, isn't it Rooney?
- I have been studying this case
since the day she disappeared.
I am telling you, that was her.
- What else do we know
about Katie Levenger?
- I'm looking at a
hunter, goes by Tooley.
Morland and I shook his trailer
up in Coulson county, a
few guns, nothing else.
- Talked to a
couple of witnesses,
custodian of her
school and the priest,
both put him at same
areas, day she disappeared.
- [Rooney] Look.
- This is the hunter?
- [Rooney] Yeah.
He's got a few
priors, petty stuff.
He's a bad seed though.
- Guys.
- [Amanda] Oh my god.
- [Chase] Holy shit.
[Ominous music]
- Roll the tape.
- Holy shit.
- That was totally
just a hit and run.
- [Amanda] What? No, no, no.
- Yeah, it was and
now we're gonna be
on the news when
we get arrested.
- [Chase] Stop.
Kim, so melodramatic.
These Hicks are not gonna
be able to find us out here.
Trust me.
- Why the hell were you
running out like that anyway?
- [Kim] You totally stole
that bottle didn't you?
- [Chase] I forgot my fake ID,
I didn't realize it
until I got in there.
- Seriously, you
just, you stole it?
Seriously chase?
- [Chase] We'll
be fine, alright.
- [Amanda] God, why
do I listen to you?
- [Chase] Come on.
Water under the bridge.
We're gonna have fun tonight.
[Singing]
You might wanna speed
up a little bit.
[Laughing]
Don't be mad.
You did good, good getaway.
[Laughing]
- Stop.
- [Chase] Okay,
where's the bottle?
I know I brought it up here.
I think we could all
use a little drink,
maybe you guys won't
be so pissed off at me.
Come on, I said I was sorry.
- I don't care, Amanda's
gonna probably have
a hit and run on her record,
which probably
means prison time,
but I was just a helpless
passenger mister officer.
- [Chase] Can you please
stop with all that?
You're freaking her out.
She would get a slap
on the wrist, maybe,
and that's only if they
catch her, which they won't.
Hey.
I'm sorry, I really am.
- Why do you have that thing on?
Are you trying to
incriminate me even more?
- [Chase] No! I'm...
Documenting the best
weekend of your life.
You're gonna want this
for posterity, trust me.
Can you ever forgive me?
Dearest maiden, I beg of thee,
forgiveness, for I have sinned.
- Okay, get up.
- [Chase] I knew it.
- Get up!
- I'm serious!
- You are a bad
influence, you know that?
- [Chase] That is
the best complement
a girl like you
could ever give me.
- Is this what you were
looking for, asshole?
- [Chase] Yes. Yes it is.
Wow.
Very nice, very nice.
Okay, Kim, you're up, come on.
Where are you?
- Look, if you're gonna
be mad all weekend,
just get it outta
your system now,
and then come take
a drink with us.
This is where we are, you know.
I can't change it,
it is what it is.
- [Chase] Thanks.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, oh yeah.
- [Amanda] Oh my god!
- [Chase] Woah!
Nice, Amanda,
where'd you get her?
- We're a package deal.
[Laughing]
You got a little dribble?
- Yeah.
- See? And if you push this...
It makes up for all the shadows.
Here, look at this
little screen.
- That's so very interesting.
- I can tell you're
fascinated Kim.
Where's the other...
- So you really think
you have a shot?
- Does it matter?
[Laughing]
- Well, not to her, I
mean, she loves it, but...
[Electronic squeal]
Woah.
- [Chase] Wait, but what?
- Well, she'll never touch
you, you know that right?
I mean, she's not into younger
guys, even the hot ones.
Not that you're...
[Laughing]
This whole perfect Princess
thing she's got going on?
It's not real.
But, I guess, work it if
you've got it though, right?
I mean, I'd do her.
What button were
you trying to push?
On the camera?
- [Chase] Oh.
[Camera snaps]
- [Both] Woah.
- This shit is stronger
than I thought.
Um, okay, so...
Just rewind one second.
You just say you'd do her?
- Okay, relax there tiger.
I'm just sayin, you know,
don't get so caught
up in the act.
She'll chew you up and spit
you out when she's done.
Just kinda funny, that's all.
- [Chase] So you two have
been friends for how long?
- Like, forever.
- [Chase] I see the
bond is very strong.
- Unbreakable.
- Okay, goozer, wills, Donnie,
I'm about to document every
second of this weekend,
not just for a
couple of douchebags
who didn't think I
could pull this off.
But really, just for
any man who's ever,
had a dream.
Every second of this weekend
will be better than
every remaining second
of all your lives combined.
That's a promise.
[Laughing]
- What are you doing?
- [Chase] Here we are,
looking for the female
in her natural habitat.
The trick is to approach slowly.
These females scare very easily,
but if done just right,
then it's worth every second.
- Oh my god, chase,
what are you doing?
Get out you little perv.
- Oh, I didn't know you
were in there, I'm so sorry.
- You better erase that.
- Of course, I'm doing
it right now. I promise.
Love the pink lace though.
No, turn it off, I wanna
see how much I can get.
- [Kim] How close
are we to the town?
- [Chase] Uh, kinda far.
My parents have had this
place for like a year.
They say it's very peaceful.
Kinda creepy though, huh?
- [Amanda] What
are you guys doing?
- [Chase] Hmm.
- [Amanda] What?
- [Chase] People out there.
Can you see that light?
It's like a fire.
- [Kim] Let me see it.
Okay, this is kind of creepy.
- [Amanda] Hey, I wanna see.
- [Kim] Is that the truck?
- [Amanda] What?
Oh my god that's it,
it's a truck with one headlight,
a guy and a little girl.
- [Chase] There's no way.
- [Amanda] That's totally it,
I just saw the little girl.
You even said that barely
anyone lives out here.
How far out is that?
- [Chase] I would say
maybe a half mile.
- [Kim] Isn't that a
little weird chase?
It's like the middle of nowhere.
How'd they get out there?
- [Chase] I have no idea.
- [Kim] Is there an
alarm in the house?
What if they see the house
lights and try to walk up here?
[Banging]
- Was that from inside?
- Okay, that was a little
weird chase, what was it?
- [Chase] I don't know.
- Okay, well it definitely
came from inside the house.
Do you wanna call the
police or something?
- [Chase] No, relax,
it was just a noise.
- Kim, don't call the police.
- [Chase] The woods
are full of noises,
it was probably a
raccoon or something.
- You have raccoons
living in your house?
- [Chase] Okay, first of
all, this isn't my house,
this is my parents
mountain house.
We don't know if that
was inside or not.
- Chase, I have
extremely good hearing,
that came from downstairs.
Where are you going?
- [Chase] Going to prove
you wrong, supersonic ears.
- By yourself?
- [Chase] You wanna come with?
- No, just, fine.
We'll wait here.
Chase wait, just come back here.
- [Chase] Now you want me.
Okay.
Hello?
[Door bangs]
[Chase sighs]
Shit!
Woah.
Hi. Oh, Jesus.
- [Kim] Where is he?
- [Amanda] I don't
know he's been gone...
[Growling]
Wait.
Chase?
[Yelling]
[Girls screaming]
[Laughing]
- Oh, my, god.
Who's the puppy now?
- Oh my god! Honestly,
what is that?
[Laughing]
- You know, we can
leave right now,
it's not that big of a deal.
You know, we can get home safe,
do something else
instead for the weekend.
- No.
- What do you wanna do?
[Chase sighs]
- Let me see that bottle.
I'm goin down.
- What are you talking about?
I stole the bottle,
I told you to drive,
I'm feeling guilty
and I wanna go
tell him I'm sorry.
- You're stupid.
- Chase, that's
almost kind of sweet,
but no, that's not gonna happen.
- He's probably
a really nice guy
just out camping with his kid.
I'll explain that we are
very dumb college kids,
who are very irresponsible,
and I'll give him
my insurance info.
- You weren't even driving.
- Doesn't matter, I'm sure
he'll take me up on it.
His car's a beater.
- You're not going
down there, okay?
You're just, you're not.
I dunno, let's, like,
watch a movie or something.
- Oh that's exciting.
I'm going down.
You coming with?
- Knock yourself out.
- Look, I'll call the
police in the morning
and I'll report myself.
- [Chase] I'll handle it.
- No! You're not!
You're staying.
- [Chase] But, you're
not my girlfriend,
so, oh, you can't
tell me what to do.
Unless you wanna
make it official...
- You'd let your girlfriend
tell you what to do?
- I'm going. Later.
[Crickets chirping]
Okay.
So, it's a little bit colder
out here than I thought.
But, I am not an idiot,
I brought warmth.
Thanks mom and dad.
[Sighs]
[Gate creaks]
This is dark.
Alright.
Where's the water? No water?
God, it's like 20
degrees colder down here.
So, there are two hot
drunk girls up there,
and I'm all the way down here.
Yeah, this is stupid.
[Twig snapping]
Hello?
You gotta be kidding me.
[Branches breaking]
[Everyone yelling]
[Laughing]
- Oh you scared the puppy.
- [Chase] What are you doing?
[Laughing]
- You deserve it.
- [Chase] Seriously, not funny.
Not out here.
- Oh please.
- [Chase] Okay fine, I
get it, I hate you both.
Satisfied?
- Oh, did the little
puppy pee himself?
Let me see...
- [Chase] You're lucky
I didn't attack you,
I thought you were
a bear or something.
- So can puppies attack bears?
Cause I didn't know that.
- I didn't know that either.
[Laughing]
- [Chase] Did you come
out here to harass me,
or was there something else?
- No, we got scared,
that house is creepy.
This looks like
fun, what's goin on?
- And we're just a
teeny little bit drunk,
so we figured, what the
hell, we'll come out here,
and protect him from
the big mountain man.
- [Chase] Okay, fine, let's go.
Try not to be so loud
when we get closer,
it's a little dark out here.
- [Kim] Oh, okay, shh shh shhhh.
[Girls laughing]
- Sure you're cool
with that thing?
- [Kim] Uh, yeah,
I'm not an idiot.
- Two hands.
Shine it over here.
We're gonna have to
cross this thing.
- [Kim] Why is
there a fence here?
- [Chase] To keep people out.
- [Kim] Out of what?
- Probably not the best
time to get into this.
Don't worry about it.
No one ever really
comes back here,
you're not supposed to cross
the other side of this.
- Why is that?
- It's nothin, come on.
- What are they trying
to keep us out of?
- These back-country folks,
just a tad uneducated,
you know, a little
superstitious.
- Of what?
- Just, come on, it's nothin.
Don't worry about
it, Kim, come on.
My biceps of steel
are slowly giving way.
- [Kim] Ugh, we've
been walking forever.
- It's been like ten minutes,
we'll know how close we are once
we get to the top of this hill.
- [Kim] Have you ever
been out here before?
- No, not past the fence.
Especially at night.
- That's comforting.
- [Kim] So, there
aren't like any
wild animals out
here, are there?
- No, they cleared all
of the wolves and coyotes
years ago when they made
this a nature preserve.
- [Kim] Really?
- No, but you're cute.
- [Kim] You're telling
me that there are
actual wild animals
on the loose out here?
- Of course there
are but the less
noise you make, the better.
We're not gonna be
attacked by anything
as long as we don't
draw attention
to ourselves we'll be fine.
Oh, and watch out
for snakes too.
- That's a joke, right?
Right?
- Come on.
[Kim sighs]
- [Kim] You gonna let your
girl walk all alone back there?
- [Chase] I thought you
said she was bad news.
- [Amanda] I can hear you.
- I know, just playing.
- [Amanda] Is it bad,
now that I'm sobering up,
starting to think we're really
stupid for being out here.
- We're fine, only like
a mile from the house.
- [Amanda] I thought you
said it was less than a mile.
- I was guesstimating, I think
we're a lot closer though.
[Kim screams]
Shh! You're gonna
wake the bears!
- Don't do that.
- [Amanda] Guys, seriously.
- Can I see it?
- [Chase] You just had it.
- Yeah, I know, but it
makes me feel better.
Like I'm watching
a movie instead of
walking through Sherwood
forest at two am.
- [Chase] Here.
Did you do that?
- [Amanda] No...
- [Kim] Don't look at me.
- Shit. It's a camera.
- Hey, a what?
- Must be set up
for trespassers.
- [Kim] For trespassing what?
- I told you, it's
a nature preserve.
Probably just some sort of
tracking device or something.
To snap pictures of trespassers.
- Good, awesome,
that's just one more
reason I'm gonna be arrested.
- [Kim] Why is this a
nature preserve again?
- It's a kinda historical
landmark, sort of.
- [Kim] For what?
- The native people
lived out here
a couple hundred years ago,
I guess this is like
an old burial ground,
I don't know, the locals
are weird about it.
So they made it a preserve.
- [Amanda] What, you mean
like a giant graveyard?
- Well, when you
put it that way.
- So you brought us out
in the middle of the night
to walk through some
Indian cemetery.
- No, I didn't. I
came out here alone.
And it's not like a cemetery,
it's more of a burial ground.
Which is why they
made it a preserve.
Don't worry about it,
they're all dead anyway.
- [Kim] You really know
how to comfort, don't you?
- Either way, I think
we're almost through it,
which means we're
almost to the campsite.
Plus, we haven't been attacked
by any evil spirits yet, right?
That was a joke,
everybody just relax.
- Okay wait, how
do you know they're
not just camping
on the preserve?
- I told you, the locals
are weird about it.
I don't think that guy would
bring his little girl out here.
- [Kim] Okay...
- Listen, we'll just
go talk to this guy,
and see if we can't salvage
what's left of the night.
Okay?
Don't act like I
kept this from you.
I didn't even think about it.
And who cares if it
was a burial ground?
What does that even mean to you?
- Let's just get this over with.
[Chase sighs]
- Amanda.
- [Amanda] I think it
came from that direction.
- [Chase] Just wait,
see if we hear it again.
[Yelling]
- I heard that.
Chase?
- [Chase] I don't know.
- You think maybe
it was an animal
or something, like a deer?
- [Chase] Didn't sound like
any animal I've ever heard.
- Maybe it just, we're
close to the campsite?
- [Chase] Did that
sound human to you?
- [Kim] I don't know.
- Okay, I'm really freaked
out, can we go back?
- [Chase] Just wait.
Let's get to the
top of this hill.
Maybe Kim is right it could be
right over that crest out there.
- You just said it
didn't sound like that.
- [Chase] Just give
it another minute.
- [Kim] God, it's
quiet out here.
I really wish you didn't tell us
what we're sitting in right now.
- [Chase] It's just
messing with your head,
come on, once we clear
through these trees,
we'll be able to see
them from that hill.
- You better be right.
- [Chase] I'm always right.
Amanda, can you say
hi? Maybe smile for us?
Good enough.
Kim, anything for posterity?
- I have to pee.
- [Chase] Excellent.
- [Amanda] What are they doing?
- [Chase] Can't tell,
it's just the guy.
- [Kim] Where's the little girl?
- [Chase] I dunno.
- Maybe we should come back and
talk to them in the morning?
When it's not this creepy.
I'm sure they'll still be here.
- [Chase] Do you realize how
far we are from the house?
We're almost there.
You're not gonna be able
to relax until we fix this.
Come on.
- No, no I don't think so.
- [Chase] Okay. Then be careful.
All we need to do is
go down this hill,
cross through this valley,
once we get to the
top of that hill,
we're there, ten minutes Max.
Okay, be careful walking
back through the cemetery.
- You're such an asshole.
- [Chase] Oh, come on.
- Fine.
- [Chase] Wow, these guys
are serious about this huh?
- Do you think that's why
he parked on the other side?
Because he didn't
wanna pass through?
- [Chase] Maybe.
- What if he followed us
out here because I hit him?
I mean, what are the chances
that he parks facing us?
- [Chase] You're
overanalyzing this Amanda.
Come on, I'll do the talking.
I can handle this, trust me.
- [Amanda] Is this it?
- [Chase] Yeah. It was.
- [Amanda] Chase,
what are you doing?
- [Kim] Okay this is,
this is too weird.
He obviously doesn't
wanna see us.
- [Chase] He doesn't
even know who we are.
- I'm pretty sure
he knows it's us.
- [Chase] In a matter
of only four minutes,
they packed up and disappeared?
- Okay, I'm officially
freaked out, can we go now?
- [Chase] So what, he
saw us, why is that bad?
Oh, what?
Amanda.
- [Amanda] What?
God, is that hair?
- [Chase] Yeah.
- [Amanda] Let me see that.
Oh my god.
Chase, this is
that little girl's.
You don't think that's her hair?
[Kim yells]
- [Amanda] What?
- [Chase] Kim?
- [Amanda] Kim?
- What is this?
- You shouldn't have brought it.
Any of it, it just
doesn't make sense.
Why would you feel the
need to bring that shit?
- I wasn't gonna leave
it, chase, it's evidence.
- Evidence of what?
We didn't even see anything.
- Between the hair,
the bloody dress,
what do you think he
was doing out there?
- I don't give a shit what
he was doing out there.
We should've left
their stuff there.
You think he went home?
He knew you were
coming and he hid,
now you've got some
fucked up bloody dress,
and he's gonna want it back.
- He wouldn't have left
if he knew we were coming.
- Oh, so you think he
just decided to leave
in the middle of the
night for no good reason,
just before we got there?
- [Kim] Maybe he
wanted us to find it.
- Tell me you didn't
bring the other stuff.
You took the bow?
- [Amanda] Yes!
- And the hair?
- I brought all of it!
What did you want to do chase?
It's covered in blood.
- So what are you gonna do?
- Call the police, tell
them what we found.
- Ugh.
This is how this stuff starts,
this has nothing to do with us.
- [Kim] This had
nothing to do with us,
until you insisted
we come out here.
- Thank you.
- [Kim] And Amanda?
How do you expect
to call the police
if we don't have any service?
- We'll go in the morning.
- [Kim] I feel like
he saw us, like,
he could've been watching.
- We need to put it back.
- [Amanda] No.
- Amanda.
- No!
What are you gonna do chase?
You want to come
take it from me?
This has a little girl's blood,
I'm not leaving it behind.
I don't care what happens next.
- Fine!
Then we need to keep
moving, give me this.
- [Amanda] Could you shine
the light this way please?
It's really dark.
- [Kim] This is
really bad Amanda,
this is really bad, I
really hope you know that.
- I don't know.
They saw the girl,
what are the chances
he just randomly parked there?
- Why wouldn't Tooley
just go to the house?
Why did he park a mile away?
- Maybe he knows the perfect
place to Bury a body.
- Wait, we have to
fast-forward through this
and get to the meat of it.
We still have two
kids out there.
- We got this off the
kid in interrogation one.
I think we're gonna
find that Levenger
kid's body out in the preserve.
We're gonna have
to watch all of it,
I'm gonna put on another pot.
- Has Katie's priest
seen our hunter, Tooley?
- Yeah, father
Gallagher said that he
hadn't seen him in a
while but he did see him
milling about the school
the day she was taken.
- And he got a good look at him?
I mean, you trust his account?
- Yeah, very specific.
He's been in town a long
time, knows a lot of people.
He actually just baptised
my little girl last week.
- My kids go to Saint Mary's.
Father's a sharp guy.
- The custodian?
- He also said that
he was certain.
- Let's watch this, come on.
- [Amanda] No,
seriously, I can't see.
- What's wrong?
- I dunno.
[Tape fast-forwarding]
We have audio.
- [Kim] We didn't
come this way before.
- Stop messing with that thing
and keep the light going.
I can't see.
- [Chase] We're fine, if
we follow this river bed,
it'll keep us from getting lost.
- [Kim] Well, what if the
light goes out on the camera?
- I put a fresh battery in,
before we came down.
- [Kim] You guys
think that there's,
any way that this whole
thing isn't what it seems?
Like maybe her dress
has catsup on it?
From her dinner and she...
And she maybe, you
know, just changed.
And then the bow fell
off her head, and then...
- Catsup, really?
What are you doing? Come on.
- [Kim] What is it?
- [Amanda] Chase?
You're being really
weird, what are you doing?
- Check it out.
[Urinating]
It's a sprinkler.
- [Kim] Come on!
- You couldn't wait? Really?
- You gotta go, go,
don't make me hold it,
I've been drinking all night.
- [Kim] Fine, just
hurry, please.
- Are you done?
[Chase sighs]
[Zipping]
- Did you see that?
- [Kim] See what?
- [Amanda] Chase, really?
- You guys didn't see?
- [Amanda] Chase,
we're all even, okay?
Stop it, this is not
a time to mess around.
- [Chase] I'm not
messing around.
- [Kim] Chase,
just, let's just go,
who cares what's in there?
- [Chase] Hold on.
- Do you understand how
annoying you're being?
God!
[Rustling]
- [Kim] What was that?
Amanda wait!
- [Amanda] Chase, come on!
- [Kim] Wait, I saw someone.
- [Amanda] What?
- [Kim] I think I saw someone.
- Chase is just trying
to be funny. Chase?
We're gonna leave you here!
- [Kim] Amanda! Amanda!
There was someone
standing right there,
I saw an arm and it reached out.
Someone was standing
right in front of him,
oh god, it was
standing right there.
- Kim! Stop okay,
stop fucking around!
- [Kim] Oh my god, Amanda.
Someone followed us out here,
someone's watching us.
It's the guy, we have to go!
- Stop it!
Stop, you're freaking me out!
We can't just leave him here!
- [Kim] No, Amanda,
there was someone
standing right there, I swear.
- What, he just reached
out there and grabbed him?
- [Kim] Yes! Let's go!
- He didn't even make a sound!
Don't you think he would've
screamed or something?
No, he's gonna pop
out any second now!
- [Kim] No he isn't
Amanda, let's go!
- [Amanda] Chase?
- [Kim] Amanda, don't!
- Chase, please, god, we
have to go back to the house!
- [Kim] Let's go!
- Chase, please.
I am asking you.
- [Kim] Amanda, I don't
think we're alone.
Come on, you know, we can,
we can go back to the
house and we can get help
and then we can come back
out here and look for him.
Please, Amanda, please.
- Maybe if we turn on the
night vision we can see him?
- [Kim] Okay fine, just hurry.
- I don't know how to do
it, how do you do this?
God, I can't find
it, can you do it?
- [Kim] Here, here. There.
[Gasping]
Oh god, go! Go!
- Go, don't stop, just go!
[Heavy breathing]
Keep going okay.
Go ahead, keep going.
Oh my god! Oh my god!
- [Kim] Come here, come here.
[Heavy breathing]
Come here.
Do you see any more?
I think it's this...
Don't you think maybe we're
drawing attention to ourselves?
- [Amanda] What are
we supposed to do?
Whatever's out there is
staring at us right now.
Oh god, how many
of them are there?
- I don't know, like
ten, maybe more.
We have to get
back to the house.
- [Amanda] Okay,
let's keep moving.
[Rustling]
Shh. Shh.
[Twigs breaking]
[Rustling]
- They're everywhere. No.
- [Amanda] Where's the
switch, flip the switch.
Kim, flip the switch!
Kim, come on, come on.
[Growling, howling]
[Yelping]
- Shit, there's some more.
- [Kim] We should run.
- [Amanda] No, we can't,
they're everywhere.
[Howling]
- Here.
Go on! Leave us alone!
Go! Go away!
Leave us alone!
Go, shoo!
- [Kim] It's working,
it's working.
[Hitting sticks together]
I haven't heard anything
in a couple of minutes.
- I think they're gone.
- Yeah, or they're just
quietly surrounding us again.
- You could be right.
Let's go.
Kim, slow down, you're
gonna wear yourself out.
- Well, then you need to hurry,
because I refuse to be
out here any longer.
Too young and too pretty to
die in the fucking woods.
[Kim yells, water splashing]
- Kim! Kim!
Kim! Kim!
[Water splashing]
Kim? Kim!
[Crying]
[Screams]
Oh my god, oh my god.
[Both crying]
You're freezing.
[Coughing]
[Gasping]
Oh my god.
- There's something really
really wrong with this place.
- We should go.
Let's go, let's go.
- [Kim] Can you set the
light up behind you?
- [Amanda] Figure this out...
[Water dripping]
- You know, we could be on
a beach somewhere right now?
That's where people go.
They go to happy places, Amanda.
This isn't a happy place.
- Yeah, I know that.
- Did you know that Adam Woodson
was trying to get
me to go to that
resort we went to last year?
- So why didn't you go?
- Because I thought
it would be more fun
to run for my life in the woods.
Why are we here?
- What, I didn't want
to wait at the house
while chase was out
here by himself.
- No no, in the boonies?
Here in general?
You had to put in more time to
keep chase pining for you?
- What?
No, I'm sorry Kim,
do you want him?
Because it's pretty apparent
that you're begging for it.
[Kim laughs]
- If I wanted him, I
could have him, trust me.
- Okay, so then it's because
you think that I might?
- I'm not doing this right now.
- No, please, let's.
- You don't even
know him that well.
How do you know that he
isn't hiding in the bushes
watching us and
laughing his ass off?
- No, he wouldn't do that.
- Pfft, no?
You need to not be so
trusting of people Amanda.
You know, I know that you think
they're all like
innocent little puppies,
but they could end
up surprising you.
- You know what, I
hope you're right.
I hope he is hiding,
because that would mean
that he's okay and
then we'd be okay.
- No it doesn't.
This isn't gonna get any
better, it's too late.
- What, that's my fault?
- Oh, well it isn't?
Awesome. Put the dress
down and let's go home.
- I can't do that.
Fine, whatever, I guess,
yeah, it's too late.
- Let's go.
- No.
One day this is
gonna mean something.
I don't know what, it's...
It'll make a difference.
It has to.
- God, what's the point?
The dress is ripped
to shreds anyway.
- Okay, we should go.
Let's go.
- Fine.
Don't forget all the pieces
of your precious dress.
Why do we seem so far away?
- I don't know, we've been
walking the right direction,
I just...
God, I don't remember
it being this far.
- [Kim] Neither do I.
- Yeah. How's the battery?
- [Kim] Still have half left.
- Okay, yeah, let's keep
the light going then.
- [Kim] You know,
maybe if we just walk
in as straight a
line as possible.
[Screams]
What was that?
- I don't know, I think, I
think that's just the wind.
- Can you shine it over here?
I don't wanna rip my
shirt on the branches.
What? I already lost my hat.
- [Amanda] Do you smell that?
- No.
- [Amanda] It smells like,
burning hair or something.
- I don't smell anything.
- [Amanda] No, it really smells
like something's burning.
[Yelling]
Oh my god.
Hello?
Are you okay?
[Yelling]
Are you hurt?
Tell us, tell us what's wrong.
[Yelling]
Here Kim, take this.
- [Kim] No, Amanda.
Amanda, you can't go in there.
- Tell us, tell us what's wrong.
[Yelling]
Oh my god, we have to help her.
- [Kim] No, Im
not going in there
and you're not going in there,
she has to come out here.
- Okay.
Here, just come out and
we can help you, okay?
[Screaming]
Look, if you don't come
out, we're gonna go get help
and then we'll
come back, alright?
[Yelling]
Everything's gonna be
fine, just come out
and then we can help you.
[Crying]
Oh my god Kim, we
have to go in there.
- [Kim] No! Amanda you don't.
You don't know what's
inside those bushes.
Consider...
- Here, give me the flashlight.
- [Kim] No, I'm not
giving it to you.
[Yelling]
- She could be dying,
what if this is hers?
- [Kim] It doesn't sound
like a little girl.
- Does that sound fake?
Give me the flashlight.
- [Kim] Fine, but
it barely works.
Please don't do this.
- What if we came
back and she was dead?
How would you feel?
- [Kim] What about me?
- We'll be fine, she's
hurt, she can't do anything.
- [Kim] Amanda,
please, come back.
[Rustling]
- [Amanda] Hello?
Hello? Are you in here?
I can't see you.
[Flashlight drops]
- [Kim] Amanda?
Amanda?
Oh. Amanda?
Manda?
[Gasping]
[Rustling]
Oh!
Help!
[Crying]
[Screaming]
[Static]
[Crickets chirping]
[Sighs]
- Alright, let's go, come on.
- We don't know what
we're dealing with here,
there's got to be more to see.
- Maybe more of the same.
[Fast-forwarding tape]
- [Rooney] Wait,
hold it, hold it.
Go back a couple seconds.
[Footsteps]
Woah.
Pause it Finch.
It would be pretty small.
- Yeah.
- [Rooney] Female?
Come on.
- There's one more tape.
Could be more darkness.
- [Rooney] Woah,
woah, wait wait wait.
[Gasping]
- [Chase] Relax, relax.
- Chase?
- [Chase] Yeah.
Are you okay?
- Ah. I don't know.
- [Chase] Are you hurt?
- I don't know,
I don't think so.
What happened to you?
[Rustling]
- [Chase] Did you hear that?
- [Kim] What is it?
- [Chase] Who's there?
[Footsteps]
- [Kim] Oh my god. Oh my god.
Honey, oh my god, are you okay?
- [Chase] Are you
hurt, are you hurt?
- I don't know.
- What happened to you?
- [Chase] Are you okay?
- I couldn't see, I don't know,
something grabbed me and then,
I don't know.
- Was it a woman?
- I couldn't see, it was
really strong though,
I tried to fight
but, I don't know,
I must've blacked
out or something.
- [Chase] Are you hurt?
- I don't think so.
My sweater's gone though.
- Where did you wake up?
- I woke up in this
field and I just,
I started running.
Oh my god, oh.
- [Chase] Oh.
- Oh my god, what happened?
- [Chase] Relax, relax.
- What happened?
[Crying]
You still haven't told
us where you went.
- Is that thing on? I
don't see the red light.
- [Kim] Yeah, it's recording.
What is it? How come you
haven't told us what happened?
- I'm not gonna tell you.
- Yes you are.
- No, I'm gonna show you.
- Chase please,
please, please, please.
We have to go back, please.
- We're not going
back to the house.
- [Kim] Why not?
- Because I don't really
know where it is right now.
We've wandered too
far off course.
We're going somewhere else.
I have to show you something.
- Chase.
- I still don't completely
believe it myself,
but it's real, all of it, and
it's gonna blow your mind.
No no no no, keep rolling.
We shoot everything. All of it.
- What are you getting at?
- All of this, as bad
as it is right now,
is gonna be worth something.
Especially after I
show you what I've got.
- What happened?
- There's something
living out here.
[Hisses]
Shit.
- [Kim] Seriously, chase.
Just tell us what
happened to you,
what's living out here?
- You first.
- [Kim] I told you I don't know.
- Well you have to
remember something,
what do you remember?
- [Kim] Something chasing
me, like from the bushes,
I don't know, I just
remember getting hit.
I didn't see anything.
- I did.
- What did you see?
- I woke up and it was
looking right down at me.
- [Amanda] It?
- Yeah, it.
It was looking right down at me,
thought I was still out.
- [Kim] Where?
- When I was looking
in the bushes,
I saw a hand, it looked limp,
so I thought maybe it
was like a dead body,
like that little
girl or something.
- Was it?
- No. The hand reached
up and grabbed onto me
and dragged me in
holding my mouth.
- [Kim] Oh my god,
what did you do?
- I got free and ran.
Sucker's fast, it
would not stop.
- What is it?
- Are you sure you wanna know?
- Yes chase!
- Then follow me.
- Why?
- Because I caught it.
I caught it and
trapped it in a cage.
You okay?
- [Kim] What is this place?
I don't see any lights.
- I pounded on the door, I
don't think anyone lives here.
So I broke into the cage.
[Chains rattling]
That's it.
- [Kim] I'm not going near that.
- Don't worry, it can't
get lose, trust me.
- What did you do?
- Come on.
- [Kim] Chase,
chase, you know what?
Who cares what's in
there, just, let's go.
Seriously, this is so stupid.
[Rustling]
What was that?
- [Chase] Just come on.
- [Amanda] Is it still in there?
- I hope so.
- [Kim] Wait a minute.
- Kim, come on, it's over here.
- [Kim] I can't see anything.
[Gasps]
[Screeching]
This is bad Amanda, really bad.
- Amanda.
- What were you thinking
bringing her here?
Are you trying to get us killed?
We have to go, Kim,
Kim, we have to go.
Forget chase, forget
the whole thing.
- Come on, Amanda, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I don't know
what you wanted me to do.
Just relax for a second, I
couldn't just let it loose.
- I want you to call the police
and let them deal with this.
- First thing in the morning,
we'll call the police.
I get it, but there's
no land line here.
We have to go to my
parents for that,
and I'm a little bit
turned around right now.
- [Kim] Well, why don't
we find another house?
- Yeah, look around, let me know
if you see any lights,
because I don't.
- [Kim] So what, we're
just staying here?
- Sun comes up in
a couple hours,
we can just hole up
here, no one's home.
- [Kim] Beautiful.
- How badly is she hurt?
- Pretty bad.
- [Kim] What is that?
- I hit her with it.
- God.
Guys, I think we
have to help her.
- [Kim] God, Amanda.
- I understand you're concerned,
but this thing tried to kill us.
- Don't you think if
she wanted us dead,
we'd be dead by now?
- I think she did try, but
something got in her way.
- I can't let her die,
I have to help her.
- Okay. Fine.
But promise me that if
that thing gets dangerous,
you're gonna back off.
I don't want you getting hurt.
- I'll be fine.
- [Kim] Wait, what
am I supposed to do?
- Keep rolling, you're
gonna wanna remember this.
[Chains rattling]
- [Kim] Oh my god.
Chase.
- Here, give me this.
You guys stay here.
[Gasps]
Shit.
Uh-oh.
[Door creaking]
Oh, shit.
You again.
- Detective?
- Yeah, come on in.
- I've got Angus
out in the field,
I think you need to hear this.
Angus, Angus, come
in. What's your 20?
Come in Angus.
- [Angus] Okay, Im
walking through it now.
It's dark out here, this
place is kinda creepy.
Found some blood in the dirt.
I don't see any animal
tracks, just some footprints.
Leads up to an old house.
I'm gonna follow it
and see where it goes.
There's more blood.
Yeah, there's definitely
blood out here.
- Do you see any bodies?
What else do you see Angus?
- [Angus] It's pretty dark sir.
I'm going through some trees.
Yes sir, I see them.
I see them, they're out here.
I'm running towards them.
Jesus, it's those kids,
it's those students.
Two of them.
Looks like a butcher
came through here.
They're dead sir,
they're both dead.
- Angus, do you have a
good ID on the students?
- [Angus] 100%
sir, I'm positive.
They've been dragged a bit.
All torn up here.
- Do you see a little
girl out there?
- [Angus] No. Have
someone send the coroner.
- Angus, listen to
me, you sit tight.
We're gonna get some
additional units out to you.
Alright? Just sit tight.
- [Angus] Copy that.
- Get some units out
from Warwick county,
this may not even
be our jurisdiction.
He shouldn't be out there alone.
- It's a long story captain,
but I'll get on it though.
- And send the coroner.
- Yeah.
- Shit.
- What is it about
this preserve?
- I heard about a
little girl disappearing
out there 20 years ago.
But I was just a kid, I
never found a record of it.
Gotta say, I'm a
little nervous about
Angus being out there alone.
- Well, he'd be smart
to keep his gun close.
[Static]
- [Amanda] How do we know
it isn't waiting outside?
- We don't.
- [Kim] So, what?
We're just supposed to
stay in here like bait?
- You wanna go out there?
She'll tear you to
pieces. Trust me.
You're worried aren't you?
Hiding behind that thing.
- [Amanda] Maybe she left?
You know, maybe
she's gone by now?
- Maybe.
We're not going outside
until the sun comes up,
we've got about two hours.
- [Amanda] And you feel okay
staying in someone's house?
- [Chase] Doesn't look like
anyone's been here in a while.
Power's not even on.
It works.
- Is there any way we
can get a better view?
You know, maybe see if
it's waiting for us?
- [Amanda] I saw a balcony.
Maybe we can see
something from up there.
- Okay.
Hold on.
[Floorboards creaking]
[Water dripping]
[Crickets chirping]
- [Amanda] Chase,
help me click this on.
- [Chase] Here, let me get it.
[Electronic screeching]
- [Amanda] Do you see anything?
- [Chase] No.
- [Kim] Well maybe we
can make a run for it?
- [Chase] Where?
I still don't know where
the house is from here,
we have to wait til morning.
[Sighs]
Let's get some food and water,
I feel like Im
about to pass out.
Kim, shine the light over here.
[Paper rustling]
[Grunts]
- [Amanda] Hey, you guys.
- [Kim] Oh, stop, Amanda!
[Amanda gagging]
[Spitting]
- Let it run for a little.
[Water running]
- [Amanda] Where's Kim?
- God, I think she went
looking for clean water.
I'll go check.
- [Amanda] Yeah, this
house isn't creepy at all.
[Banging]
Chase?
Chase!
[Banging]
[Glass breaking]
Chase?
Kim? Chase?
[Knocking]
You guys!
[Glass breaking]
[Heavy breathing]
[Banging]
[Screaming]
- [Kim] Help me! Please!
[Crying]
[Knocking]
- [Chase] Amanda, come on!
It's me, open this door, hurry!
Amanda come on,
open the door now!
We have to go! You
can't stay in here!
- Why, what happened,
what happened?
- Come on. Come on!
Amanda come on! There's no time!
- Why is there
blood on you chase?
- What? We have to
go okay, please?
Hurry, come with me.
- Who's blood is that?
Who's blood is that chase?
- Hey, hey, it's me okay?
It's me, Kim's hurt.
Please, please, just trust me.
Okay?
- Where is she?
- She's down there, okay?
Come on.
Please, please, please.
Amanda, I'm sorry, come on.
- Kim, Kim, oh my god.
Kim, Kim.
- [Chase] Amanda.
She's dead.
- What? What?
- [Chase] I couldn't
help her, I tried.
It was already gone.
- Oh my god.
- [Chase] We have to get in
the safe room and stay there.
Come on. Amanda, come on.
- We can't just leave her here.
- There isn't time, Amanda,
it's just for now, okay?
We just have to
leave her for now,
okay, we'll come back for her.
I promise.
Come on, come on.
We have to keep quiet okay?
It's gonna be okay.
I know you're scared,
it's gonna be okay.
[Amanda crying]
I'm so sorry, about Kim.
This is all my fault.
- No it's not, you didn't
know this would happen.
I feel like I should've
never brought her here.
We should've never
left the house.
- No, don't blame yourself.
It just got so out
of hand, you know?
No one is to blame here,
if anyone is, I'm the asshole.
I should've listened to you.
I am so sorry.
- It's okay.
- Look at me, look at me.
Do you trust me?
- I trust you.
- I'm going to protect you.
[Banging]
- She's back.
What are you doing?
- I'm gonna handle this.
- No, chase, don't go out there.
- I have to.
- No, no no no.
Stay here please.
- We can't just
sit back and wait.
- You don't have to go.
You don't have to go.
- Just sit tight.
Don't leave this room.
[Crying]
- [Chase] Who are you?
No! No, no!
[Footsteps]
- Chase?
- It's dead.
- What?
Oh, oh my god!
[Crying]
Oh my god.
Chase.
[Banging]
Please.
[Crying]
Just leave us alone! Please!
[Doorknob rattling]
Leave us alone!
[Banging]
[Crying]
- Where's the dress?
- What?
- The dress.
Where's the dress?
No!
I can't let you leave.
I'm sorry, I really am.
You should know, I never
meant to hurt anyone.
You have to understand,
this will hurt the church,
do you know what that means?
Sweetheart, please, can
you do me one favor?
Will you close your eyes?
I can't stand to
look at your face.
[Crying]
I'm so sorry, darling.
[Screeching]
[Yelling]
Ow.
[Thuds]
[Growling]
[Heavy breathing]
[Somber music]
[Static]
[Crying]
- She's alive!
[Police sirens]
[Somber music]