(waves crashing)
(film reel clicking)
(birds chirping)
- Look at this,
look at this, honey.
Grab the camera.
Our little Roger's
playing basketball.
You know what I think?
He grows up, he's
gonna be a champion.
Roger, do you know what
my father used to say?
If you believe in yourself,
nothing is impossible.
Hey, Roger, do you
believe in yourself?
Roger, I asked you a question.
Do you believe?
Ah, come here.
Give me a hug.
I love you.
(upbeat hip hop music)
♪ Hey yo, man ♪
♪ You wanna be a star ♪
♪ Come on ♪
♪ One, two, three, let's go ♪
♪ What's up man ♪
♪ I need the flavor ♪
♪ I really wanna know ♪
♪ Ladies and
gentlemen, let's go ♪
♪ I know you wanna
be a big player ♪
♪ Mini get it on the
court, come closer ♪
♪ You wanna be a giant like me ♪
♪ Take the ball and
prove you can be ♪
♪ Get low, rush the
flow with your boys ♪
♪ We're gonna bust
it, doing it right ♪
♪ So do what you came to do ♪
♪ I wanna see you score some ♪
♪ Mini now I wanna
hook some out ♪
♪ We're gonna jump
and dunk alright ♪
♪ Now there ain't
no holding back ♪
♪ We're gonna get
you out of this fog ♪
♪ Little man, when
you're dribbling low ♪
♪ Then bouncing it
back and forth ♪
♪ Come one do what
you came to do ♪
♪ We're gonna play
B-ball together ♪
♪ Uh huh ♪
♪ Don't say it ♪
♪ I really wanna know ♪
♪ To the big yeah ♪
♪ Clap clap clap to this ♪
♪ Move move move to this ♪
♪ Come on shake,
shake, shake to this ♪
♪ Move your body over me ♪
♪ Clap clap clap to this ♪
♪ Come on move,
move, move to this ♪
♪ Come on shake,
shake, shake to this ♪
♪ Move your body over me ♪
♪ Clap clap clap to this ♪
♪ Come on move,
move, move to this ♪
♪ Come on shake,
shake, shake to this ♪
♪ Move your body, go go Mini ♪
(kids chattering)
(ball bouncing)
- Come on, Roger, you afraid?
- Not of you, Chevy.
- Lucky shot.
- Uh huh, just like
the last seven.
- If only--
- If only what?
If you were four feet taller?
- Yeah, like Kareem
Abdul Jabbar.
(laughing)
Man, we have been here forever.
I wish we were kids again,
when size wasn't a problem.
- Yeah, but your game still was.
Hey, Chris.
Hey, come shoot some
hoops with your old man.
- No, I can't Roger,
I have homework.
I should get home.
- Don't worry about it.
Come on, play.
(bicycle bell dinging)
- Is the circus back in town?
(upbeat hip hop music)
Look, midgets
playing basketball.
- [Both] Dwarves, not midgets.
- Why do you even
bother coming here?
- Whale watching,
what do you think?
- What, you think just because
we're dwarves, we can't play?
- Uh huh.
And what about you, Chris?
Why aren't you playing
basketball with your little daddy?
(laughing)
- He may be little,
but Roger here,
he's deadly from the
three point line.
- Oh yeah?
Prove it.
- Yeah, prove it.
♪ Gotta prove it on the court ♪
♪ My skills got mad game ♪
♪ Take your position ♪
♪ I'm about to
put you to shame ♪
(suspenseful music)
(laughing)
- Come on, let's bounce.
- You get it in every time.
And the one time you miss?
And how are we
gonna get it down?
- How am I supposed to know?
I got an idea.
(upbeat rock music)
- [Chevy] That's it.
- Come on.
- You always fall short.
(laughing)
(record scratching)
(upbeat rock music)
(steady instrumental music)
Hi Natalia.
- Well howdy.
Hi Levy.
- My name is Chevy.
- Are you sure?
- Anything interesting
in the mail?
- Yeah, I just got a letter
from my mom from Paris.
Did I ever tell
you I'm from Paris?
Not from Paris, France.
From Paris, Texas.
- I thought I picked up a
hint of a French accent.
(laughing)
- It's not a French accent,
it's a Texan accent, Benny.
- Chevy, like the truck.
- Mercy, would you look at
what's coming to greet me.
Tyrone, we're gonna be late
for the basketball game.
- I play basketball, too.
- I'm sure you do.
But he plays real basketball.
Bye bye.
(steady instrumental music)
- You got it buddy, come on.
(upbeat hip hop music)
Come on, don't just stand there.
Come on, keep going.
Yeah, Chris, yeah, go, go buddy.
Don't take that from Jimmy, man.
You're better than him.
Yeah yeah, good job, buddy.
- Susan, Roger, how are you?
- Hey Linda, good to see you.
- Oh it's great to see you
getting involved with your son.
- Oh, we love to support
Chris in anything he does.
- Good job, Chris, good job.
- Well I hope you'll
be coming down
for out fundraiser on Saturday.
We're gonna need as many
parents as we can get to volunteer.
- Shoot, Chris.
Shoot, you got it.
- Basketball great Dennis
Rodman's going to be here.
- Really?
- The Worm?
- [Linda] Yes.
- Nice job, Chris, go.
Come on, Chris, go go.
Come on, go.
- [Susan] Get it, get it.
- You got it, you got it, go.
♪ Bah bah bah bah bah bah ♪
- [Jimmy] Like father, like son.
(gentle instrumental music)
- Chris.
Chris.
- Can you knock before
you come in my room?
- I thought I'd see about us
going to see Dennis
Rodman on Saturday.
Your principal told me about it.
- No thanks, I've got
better things to do.
- I just thought you'd enjoy
seeing an NBA legend,
because you love
basketball so much.
You're gonna show 'em
in college, Chris.
- I didn't get the
basketball scholarship.
- [Roger] What,
you didn't get it?
- No, look.
What are your plans
for me now, Roger?
You can't even afford
to send me to college.
I'm stuck here.
(door slamming)
(gentle piano music)
- What's wrong, honey?
Talk to me.
- I don't know what
to do about Chris.
I don't know what to say.
- He's a teenager.
Remember what we were
like at that age?
You know he loves you.
- He calls me Roger.
He doesn't even call me dad.
(upbeat dance music)
(intense rock music)
(light electronic music)
Chevy.
Am I good father?
- Of course you are.
Why do you ask that?
- I don't know.
(phone ringing)
Chris didn't get
the scholarship.
- That's too bad, Rog.
(paper rustling)
- He doesn't look up to me.
- Dude, you have to be on a
ladder for him to do that.
- I think I'm an
embarrassment to him.
(steady instrumental music)
- Rog, do you think
I'm attractive?
- Chevy, I've been
wanting to tell you,
I've been in love with
you since kindergarten.
- Stop it, I'm serious.
Tall girls call me
cute and baby doll.
I don't think they
really like me.
But if I have that operation,
I could be taller.
- No, not that again.
- But I'll be able to
play basketball better,
and she has a thing
for basketball players.
- Who's she?
- She's so beautiful
and she's tall.
- Why do you only
date tall women?
- Because there are more
tall ones than little ones.
- Yeah, but it never
works out for you.
I mean, what's wrong
with dating a dwarf?
- 50,000 dollars?
That's a lot of money.
- That could be
my son's tuition.
- What are you talking about?
- You wanted a chance
to prove yourself.
Well here it is.
- What are you talking about?
- All we need is
three more players.
- And where are we gonna
find three tall guys
to play with us?
- We're not.
- What do you mean?
You're not seriously thinking.
Whoa.
(spitting)
(upbeat hip hop music)
- You can't be serious.
- I thought you wanted
to take a stand.
- We don't stand a chance.
(metal creaking)
- I think you guys are scared.
- Yeah, of getting
stomped like bugs.
Those guys in Venice play
real basketball, man.
- Real basketball?
And what do we
play, video games?
Who says we can't take them?
- I don't know what to say.
- My dad always
told me to believe.
If we believe in ourselves,
nothing's impossible.
- Let's play for fun,
like in the old days.
- You know, you realize
the last time we played,
Charles Barkley had hair?
(laughing)
- Come on.
Together we can do anything.
At least let's give it a shot.
- Why not?
I got nothing else to do.
- Okay, I'm in.
- Alright, yeah.
(upbeat music)
Oh.
Need some help
down there, player?
- [Chevy] No, I'm good.
♪ Chevy, George, Nick,
and this Roger guy ♪
♪ Used to play B-ball
in junior high ♪
♪ But now they
don't have style ♪
♪ They don't have grace ♪
♪ Tripping and fumbling
all over the place ♪
♪ People say they can't play ♪
♪ Just because they
look that way ♪
♪ So they're small,
they're not tall ♪
♪ Bounce, double dribble,
and show them all ♪
(women scat singing)
♪ Give 'em some room,
and give 'em some time ♪
♪ I bet you a dollar
and I bet you a dime ♪
♪ They're gonna be winners,
they're gonna be great ♪
♪ They're gonna be
the envy of the NBA ♪
♪ People say they can't play ♪
♪ Just because they
look that way ♪
♪ So they're small,
they're not tall ♪
♪ Bounce, double dribble,
and show them all ♪
(women scat singing)
- Come on, guys,
that wasn't so bad.
- Are you pulling my leg?
- I think I pulled a muscle.
- So we're not in
championship form.
We just need to practice.
(gentle music)
- Come on, Roger.
We can't do this on our own.
- We need help.
- And if we really wanna play,
we need a fifth player.
- We need to stand up
and believe in ourselves.
- What we need is a giant.
Someone who knows how to play.
- Why don't you
just call the NBA?
Hello, NBA?
Yeah, this is Roger.
Can you send us a fifth player?
(laughing)
(upbeat hip hop music)
- Hm, what about a giant
who used to be in the NBA?
- Who?
- You can't be serious.
- And how are we gonna get him?
- Money.
If you ain't got
money, you got nothing.
No women, no cars.
No good lawyers
when you need one.
(microphone screeching)
It's not important
if you win or lose.
(microphone screeching)
(woman whispering)
- Because if you do your best,
you'll always be a winner.
(microphone screeching)
(woman whispering)
- Just follow your
dreams, whatever they are.
(shushing)
(farting)
- Thank you.
Thank you again, Mr. Rodman.
(clapping)
Thank you, thank you so much.
- [Dennis] Check please.
- Oh.
I almost forgot.
Well, it's been a pleasure.
- Now's our chance, let's go.
(upbeat hip hop music)
- D.
D. Rod.
Yo, D, yo.
- Mr. Rodman.
Mr. Rodman, could we
talk to you for a second?
- Not now.
- We just need a minute.
- Yeah, we're fans, man.
- Big ones?
- Yeah, like you said in there,
we're trying to
follow our dream.
- And what would that be?
- We're gonna form
a basketball team.
- What?
Are you serious?
- Yes, we're training every day
at the park down the street.
- Yeah, we wanna play
in the Venice Beach
basketball tournament.
It starts in eight weeks.
- You can help us win
by playing with us.
- Or you could be our coach.
- Am I being Punk'd right now?
Look, time is money.
I don't have the time,
and you guys don't look
like you have the money.
So you know what, bye.
- Can you at least think
about it, Mr. Rodman?
- Hey, at least we tried.
(gentle music)
I'll see y'all later.
- Where are you going?
- Yeah, I'd stay, but
I gotta head home.
I got real work to do.
- We're still gonna do
the tournament, right?
I'll see you at
practice tomorrow.
Who needs Rodman, anyway?
(upbeat hip hop music)
- Chevy?
Why the long face?
Something wrong?
- What are you, my shrink?
- Hey, you don't have
to bite my head off.
I was just trying to help.
- Sorry, Lorraine.
I didn't mean to
take it out on you.
I'm just a little depressed.
- Could've fooled me.
Come on, what's the matter?
Talk to Dr. Lorraine.
- I wanna be a
basketball player.
- Are you gonna stop being funny
and tell me what the problem is?
- I wanna play
basketball with Roger,
and my old friend
Nick, and George.
I wanna compete in the Venice
Beach basketball tournament.
- That's great.
If that's what you wanna
do, then go for it.
I'm behind you all the way.
- But there's a little problem.
Look at us.
- Yeah?
- We're dwarves.
- No.
Come on.
I've known you for years.
And what we are has
never stopped you before.
Look at me.
This is the hottest
diner in Venice Beach.
Do you know how many tall,
boob-alicious blondes
tried out for this job?
And guess who got it.
Me, with my fabulous
personality.
- [Customer] Hey,
what about my fries?
- What about 'em?
- But this is different.
- How?
- Because this is impossible.
- So, what do you want?
- I want people to respect me,
I want people to
like me for who I am,
and I wanna win the
basketball tournament.
And I want,
and I want a steady girlfriend.
- No.
What do you wanna eat?
- Oh, the usual.
- Coming right up.
(upbeat rock music)
- I don't know what
you can do anymore.
You've done it all.
You showed up in a wedding
dress at Rockefeller Center.
You go-go danced in a cage.
You dyed your hair
every possible color.
You did way too
many reality shows.
You think you can
change your image
by making public
appearances at high schools?
Who are you trying to fool?
- What are you saying?
- You're a freak.
I made you a freak.
And you know why?
For the money.
You make money, I make money.
But now there's
no money anymore.
We need to find a gimmick.
- Funny, yesterday a
bunch of dwarves came
and asked me to play basketball.
Something, some tournament,
something like that.
You know, they're talking
about following their dreams.
They even asked me to coach 'em.
- We have sunk to a new low.
Wait a minute.
Hold it right there.
Do you see the
possibilities, the publicity?
This could be a goldmine.
It's never been done before.
You know what we
can do with this?
Think about it.
The great Dennis Rodman,
next to these tiny little,
what are they called?
Who cares?
They're just teeny weeny, mini.
That's it.
The Minis.
(laughing)
The Minis, it's perfect.
I gotta start making
some phone calls.
Where are they?
- Who?
- The Minis.
- I don't know.
They said they practice
down in Venice Beach.
- Well then go find them.
You're still here.
Time is money.
Get me my Minis.
(upbeat pop music)
- Hey, thanks for
giving me a lift.
- I don't mind being
your chauffeur,
but when are you gonna
get your own car?
- When I'm ready.
But if I had that operation,
I wouldn't need the
pedal extension.
- Even with that operation,
you still won't be able
to reach the pedals.
Get over it.
Maybe we should find
three more players.
I think Nick and
George bailed out.
- That's what you think.
- Nick.
- Hey.
- All right.
Looks like we only
need two more players.
- Hey, what about me?
- George.
- Hey, George.
- The old team is
back in action.
- [All] Yeah.
(clapping)
- Yeah, the old
dinosaurs are back.
- Yeah.
You know it.
- Hey, what's with the limo?
- Hey Minis.
Are you still looking
for a fifth player?
- Minis?
- Catchy, huh?
Our agent's idea.
- Agent?
- What agent?
- I want that proposal on
my desk tomorrow, you hear?
(gentle music)
(phone beeping)
Bob, you're fired.
Yeah?
What does he want?
What, is he nuts?
You tell him to call me.
I'll cut him down to size.
Minis.
Get in here.
Have a seat.
Can I get you anything?
- Well, actually.
- Okay so you're fine, good.
Now, let's get down to business.
Whose idea was it
to put a midget
basketball team together?
- [All] Yours.
- Not midgets.
- Yeah yeah yeah.
Dwarves, midgets, whatever.
From now on,
you're the Minis.
Get it?
The Minis.
Sleepy, Dopey, Grumpy, Sneezy.
You might be little, but
I'm gonna make you big.
Big big big big big.
- Well, we're ready
for the challenge,
and we're gonna give you 110%.
- 110%?
That's not enough.
From now on, I want 200%.
I want 500%.
I want every inch of you.
Hey, I think I
just made a funny.
(chuckling)
This is the big league.
We are here to make
money, lots of money.
- But money isn't
everything, you know.
- Would you shut up?
Let's listen to the man.
(chuckling)
(sniffing)
- Do you smell that?
- Don't look at me.
- I smell endorsements.
I smell commercials.
I smell your own comedy special.
I smell a miniseries.
A Mini miniseries.
- So what about a short film?
- There you go.
- Who are you?
- Who am I?
I'm your agent.
Okay, time is wasting.
And Dennis?
- And time is money.
- That's what I wanna hear.
I gotta set up photo shoots,
interviews, costumes.
- What about basketball?
- What about it?
- Don't we need to practice?
- No problem.
Got that covered.
- Minis.
(upbeat music)
♪ They made fun of
us in high school ♪
♪ They stepped on us,
we were the fools ♪
♪ But now we're
gonna make 'em pay ♪
♪ The Minis gonna
have their way ♪
♪ You know I don't
like it when they say ♪
♪ That we're too
little, we can't play ♪
♪ We winners know
we're not that tall ♪
♪ We're gonna rock
at basketball ♪
♪ I am not a little boy ♪
♪ I'm not a doll,
I'm not a toy ♪
♪ The Minis, The Minis ♪
♪ We're gonna stand
up and command ♪
♪ I'm a Mini, yes I am ♪
♪ The Minis, The Minis ♪
♪ I am not a little boy ♪
♪ I'm not a doll,
I'm not a toy ♪
♪ The Minis, The Minis ♪
♪ We're gonna stand
up and command ♪
♪ The Minis, The Minis ♪
♪ I'm a Mini, yes I am ♪
- I think we may have a problem.
Things aren't working
out the way I expected.
- Come on, man.
Don't give up on us.
- I'm not.
We gotta be more creative.
♪ They put us down every day ♪
(upbeat rock music)
♪ They never ever let us play ♪
♪ Tired of the harder
they're waiting for ♪
♪ We're gonna rock
at basketball ♪
♪ So what, we're
different, you and me ♪
♪ But that's a good
thing, can't you see ♪
♪ Gonna stand and be a man ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm a Mini, yes I am ♪
♪ Hey Mini, you're the guy ♪
♪ Mini, Mini, you're divine ♪
♪ Go Minis, go Minis,
go Minis, go Minis ♪
♪ Jump, jump, shooting high ♪
♪ Come on, Minis, you can fly ♪
♪ Go Minis, go Minis,
go Minis, go Minis ♪
♪ Go Minis, go Minis ♪
♪ Hey Mini, you're the guy ♪
♪ Mini, Mini, you're diving ♪
♪ Go Minis, go Minis ♪
♪ Jump, jump, shooting high ♪
♪ Come on, Minis, you can fly ♪
♪ Go Minis, go Minis ♪
- [Roger] Dinner.
Chris?
- How many times do
I have to tell you
to knock before you come in?
- I'm sorry, champ.
Hey, I didn't wanna say anything
'cause I didn't wanna jinx it,
but Jack told me today he
has some big things planned.
So you know what that means.
We'll have the money
to send you to college.
- Mom already told me.
- That's great, isn't it?
- Yeah, I guess all my
dreams have come true now.
- What?
What did I say wrong now?
(gentle music)
- Need a hand?
- Oh, I'm fine.
Thanks, Chimney.
Here, this is for you.
- What's with the
stuffed animal?
- You haven't seen my
place before, have you?
Come on in.
Make yourself at home.
I'm just gonna put these
bags in the kitchen.
(cow mooing)
Well, what do you
think of the decor?
That's French for decoration.
- So I take it you like cows.
So this is what mad
cow disease looks like.
- I was Miss Bovine
a few years ago.
And then, I was runner-up
in the North American
Miss Hosting.
Oh.
(cow mooing)
I could go on and on and on.
But, anyway.
What did you do today?
- Well, I hung around
with Dennis Rodman.
(cow mooing)
- You were hanging out
with Dennis Rodman?
- And we've been
practicing every day.
- You put together
a basketball team.
- Yes, and we're gonna play
in the Venice Beach
basketball tournament.
- You and Dennis Rodman?
(cow mooing)
- Yeah, we even
have the same agent.
- You and Dennis Rodman
have the same agent?
- Yes, and Jack said we're
gonna be big big big.
- Really?
Can I get you
something to drink?
- Wow, thanks.
Anything but milk.
(laughing)
- You are so funny.
You know what?
Why don't I make you a nice,
home-style Texan meal?
- Mm.
(upbeat rock music)
(siren wailing)
(gentle rock music)
- Hey guys.
The usual?
- Sounds good.
- Not me.
Today, I want my
eggs well scrambled.
With some home fries.
No, I want a grilled
chicken salad.
Gotta keep in shape, you know?
- Woo, you're in a good mood.
It's been a while.
How's it going?
- We've been practicing 24-7,
and we're getting
better every day.
- Well, that's not why
I'm in a good mood.
Do you remember that sexy blonde
that lives in my
apartment building?
- She's from Paris.
- Texas, that is.
Well, she almost had
a cow when she heard
I'm playing basketball,
and I'm gonna be a star.
I think she's warming up to me.
- Chevy, does this
Miss Texas like you,
or your newfound fame?
- What do I care?
As long as I get the girl.
(cell phone ringing)
- Hello?
Yeah.
Alright.
Sure, we're on our way.
That was Dennis.
Sounds important.
I hope everything's okay.
- That gold digger's gonna
crunch your heart like a crouton.
Probably got legs
taller than I am.
I hate her.
What?
What are you looking at?
- Hi, I'm Megumi Hosogai,
and we're down here today
at the Venice Beach courts
meeting some very, very
special basketball players.
The Minis.
Well little man, tell
me about your team.
- Well there's really
not much to say.
It's just me, Roger,
Nick, and George,
and of course, Dennis Rodman.
- He wasn't joking.
He's really doing it.
- Let's try to get a
few words from Dennis.
Dennis, I know this tournament
is open to everyone,
but don't you find
it a little unfair
having an NBA star
playing against amateurs?
- That's not what
this is all about.
This is about showing people,
no matter who you
are, big or small,
when you play as a team,
you can do anything,
and remember, it's not
important if you win or lose.
If you do your best,
you'll always be a winner.
- You're such an
inspiration, Dennis.
- Stop it, will you?
I have a headache.
- Get ready, California,
because you're gonna
be hearing a lot more
about The Minis.
(upbeat music)
♪ You're living the
American dream ♪
♪ Your face is on a magazine ♪
♪ Four guys like you,
I've never seen ♪
♪ I wanna be like a Mini ♪
♪ You're looking good,
you're dressing fine ♪
♪ The girls are
calling all the time ♪
♪ You've done the
talk shows on TV ♪
♪ I wanna be like a Mini ♪
♪ You got the thing,
you got it all ♪
♪ You got the life,
now play B-ball ♪
♪ You made it big
though you're tiny ♪
♪ I wanna be like a Mini ♪
♪ You're looking good,
you're dressing fine ♪
♪ The girls are
calling all the time ♪
♪ You've done the
talk shows on TV ♪
♪ I wanna be like a Mini ♪
♪ You got the thing,
you got it all ♪
♪ You got the life,
now play B-ball ♪
♪ You made it big
though you're tiny ♪
♪ I wanna be like a Mini ♪
♪ You're looking good,
you're dressing fine ♪
♪ The girls are
calling all the time ♪
♪ You've done the
talk shows on TV ♪
♪ I wanna be like a Mini ♪
♪ You're living the
American dream ♪
♪ Your face is on a magazine ♪
♪ Four guys like you,
I've never seen ♪
♪ I wanna be like a Mini ♪
♪ You're living the
American dream ♪
♪ Your face is on a magazine ♪
(beeping)
(laughing)
- Roger.
Roger.
- Susan.
- You guys are adorable.
Did you know that The Minis
have their own online store?
- Must have been
one of Jack's ideas.
- Get over here, come here.
You have to take a look.
It's unbelievable.
I bought all The
Minis merchandise
that I could get
my little hands on.
- Oh no.
- Oh yes.
Look, T shirts,
(beeping)
backpacks,
basketballs, of course,
Mini hoops, action figures.
- Action figures.
- Uh huh.
- Life-size?
- No.
But when you put them in water,
they increase in size by 600%.
- Not bad.
Do you think it
would work on me?
- Oh silly.
There's even gonna
be a video game.
- You know, I could've gotten
all this stuff for free.
- I know, I know.
But with all the money
that's coming in.
- Speaking of which,
Jack just gave me
another check today.
- Oh, what are we gonna
do with all this money?
- I'm sure you'll figure it out.
- Oh you're darn-tootin'.
You just concentrate on winning
that tournament in two weeks.
- Yeah, but, where's Chris?
- He's doing his
thing at the hospital.
- He's got a thing?
- Mm hmm, volunteering.
- I didn't know that.
- Well how could you, darling?
You're never here anymore.
- Susan, I'm doing
this for Chris, for us.
- Honey, you can't buy
your son with money.
You are a great father.
Even before the team
and all of this,
you gave Chris everything
that he wanted.
He's just,
growing up.
Our baby isn't a baby anymore.
- Oh.
(birds chirping)
- Well.
Look who it is.
A celebrity.
Oh, he's ignoring us.
Now that his dad knows Rodman,
he thinks he's better than us.
Did you hear me?
Oh, now Chris is being a snob.
His little father's famous.
Been on all the talk shows.
But he'll always be a loser.
Like father, like son.
- Jimmy.
You really get off by making
fun of others, don't you?
Does it make you feel like a
man when you insult people?
Ooh, Jimmy's so cool.
You act so hardcore in front
of all of your friends,
but I wanna know what you're
like all alone, one-on-one.
Because let me
tell you something.
My father is not a loser.
He wins every single day
by putting up with
low-lifes like you.
And so what if he's a dwarf?
My father is bigger
than you will ever be.
(steady funky music)
♪ Woo ♪
♪ You better give
up, get my way ♪
♪ I'm coming after you ♪
♪ Nowhere to run,
I like to play ♪
♪ A little bit of
house with you ♪
♪ I wanna bet a shuffle ♪
♪ Tonight's the night ♪
♪ Feel like falling in love ♪
♪ I'm 24-7 so hold on tight ♪
♪ The way, we can do it ♪
♪ Now where's the
fun I like to play ♪
♪ I'm coming after you ♪
♪ I wanna bet a shuffle ♪
♪ Tonight's the night ♪
♪ Feel like falling in love ♪
- I don't dance.
- He loves to dance, go, go.
He worships me.
Can you believe that's your dad?
♪ Ooh ♪
- Excuse me.
I need to go freshen up.
♪ Ooh, with you ♪
- Hey Chevy, she's
pretty fine, dude.
- She sure is.
And now since I
have a lot of money,
I could finally
get that operation.
- What operation?
- To make me taller.
- Say what?
- Let me explain.
It's a limb-lengthening process.
It's where they pull
apart your bones about
one millimeter per day.
- Well that sounds
pretty serious.
- Everything has a risk.
I can't walk for
about four months,
maybe some muscle loss.
Could be some nerve damage.
Might be could
make me paralyzed.
But that's a small chance.
But this is my big chance.
After about 10 operations,
I could be this much taller.
- All this for what?
A few inches?
- Man, I'll sell my soul
to be as tall as you.
I'm sick of people looking
down on me like I'm a freak.
- Look at me.
To my eyes, we all freaks.
- I know.
When people look
at me, it hurts.
It hurts so much more than
that operation ever could.
- No, you don't
need the operation.
You know, you stand taller
than anybody I know.
- Really?
- Right on, brother,
you the man.
♪ When I think of what
we've been through ♪
♪ I can't believe that
our dreams come true ♪
♪ 'Cause we believe we
can reach the stars ♪
♪ We're gonna win
being who we are ♪
♪ We're dancing under the
bright lights, feeling alright ♪
♪ Couldn't be better ♪
♪ Night life so out of sight ♪
♪ We're happy together ♪
♪ Party with friends,
the fun never ends ♪
♪ At the woman ♪
♪ You and me, one big family ♪
♪ And fun with the
people, ooh ooh ♪
♪ Ooh ooh ♪
♪ Ooh ooh ooh ♪
♪ We're dancing under
the bright lights ♪
♪ Feeling alright,
couldn't be better ♪
♪ Night life so out of sight ♪
♪ We're happy together ♪
♪ Party with friends,
the fun never ends ♪
♪ And they'll want more ♪
♪ You and me, one big family ♪
♪ With all of the people ♪
♪ Ooh ooh ooh ♪
- Oh no.
Who the hell are you?
This is my husband.
- We're just dancing.
- No, no. No.
- Just a dance.
- No, no.
- I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
- You better get going.
Bye.
- Hey.
Come on, let's go get a drink.
I need a drink.
- You're not having the
greatest time, are you?
- It's not that.
- What is it?
You've been so distant.
You've been like
this for a while.
Is it the scholarship?
I mean, don't worry.
We have more than enough money.
- I don't care about that.
- Okay, what do you say tomorrow
after the tournament,
we take a trip down
to Northern Heights,
check it out.
If you don't like it,
there's plenty of other schools
with great basketball teams.
- Basketball,
basketball, basketball.
I don't care about basketball.
- Take it easy.
- I don't wanna play basketball.
- What do you mean?
That's what you've
always wanted.
- No, that is what you
have always wanted.
I played basketball because
you wanted me to
play basketball.
You never asked me
what I wanted to do.
- Okay, what do you want to do?
- Nevermind.
- Oh come on, Chris.
Talk to me, I'm your dad.
- I just want to
make people laugh.
- That's fine.
If you wanna make people
laugh, become a dwarf.
Look at me, I'm tiny.
- That's not funny.
- Well, come on.
- I've been volunteering
for a while now
at the community center.
- Yeah, your mom
told me about that.
- And at the hospital.
- That's great.
- And I want to be a clown.
- Huh?
- I want to be a clown.
- Are you serious?
- Yes.
- A clown?
- And I want to go
to clown school.
- Clown school?
- In Paris.
- Oh.
Paris, Texas?
- No, Paris, France.
- Oh, I can't believe this.
Did Chevy put you up to this?
- No, I'm serious.
- Chris, we have the money.
You can do whatever you want.
- Then you weren't
listening to me.
Because I just said
I want to be a clown.
- Chris, why didn't you
tell me this before?
- Because you never asked me.
(upbeat dance music)
- This has been such
an interesting evening.
I met so many people.
- After the party at
my place or your place?
- It's late, you know.
I have an audition
tomorrow morning.
And you know what?
I have a piercing headache.
- Lately, you've been
having a lot of headaches.
♪ I surrender, la la la ♪
♪ Move in closer, la la dee da ♪
(upbeat music)
(crowd cheering)
(speaking in foreign language)
♪ Are you ready ♪
♪ Come now, come now,
come now, come now ♪
♪ Break it down, break it down,
break it down, break it down ♪
♪ Come now, come now,
come now, come now ♪
♪ Get down with it, get
down with it on fire ♪
♪ Get down with it,
get down with it ♪
♪ Get down with it on fire ♪
♪ Get down with it,
get down with it ♪
♪ Get down with it on fire ♪
♪ They laughing, then my toes ♪
♪ They like my flow
and see how it goes ♪
♪ They laughing, then my toes ♪
♪ They like my flow ♪
♪ And see how it goes ♪
- Minis, I just got you
a national commercial.
This is the big one.
Ready?
This is just an idea.
(ominous music)
The diaper company went gaga.
You get it?
Goo goo gaga.
Listen to the jingle.
♪ For number one
and number two ♪
♪ Mini diapers offer you ♪
And I am this close
to getting you
a hemorrhoid commercial.
- But, hemorrhoid.
- Butt, exactly.
You said you wanted
to be noticed.
- By playing basketball.
By showing people we could
do anything if we believe.
Not by being spokespeople
for a diaper commercial.
- Don't bite the
hand that feeds you.
You're nobody without me.
My father always told
me I'd be nobody.
But look at me now.
I got money.
I got power.
I got fame.
I got The Minis.
Where'd everybody go?
- Don't worry, Jack.
I'll talk to them.
- At least there's one midget
who knows how to play ball.
- Dwarf.
- Whatever.
(people chattering)
- What are you doing?
- Are you kidding?
Diapers?
He's turned us into freaks.
- What's wrong with that?
He's just doing his job.
He made us famous.
Without Jack, we
didn't even exist.
- Exist?
Are you listening to yourself?
I can't believe
you're on his side.
- Yeah, you would say that.
You have a family that
loves you, a normal life.
I need this.
Sometimes you need to give
a little to get a little.
Roger.
- I'm through with
all this, Chevy.
Better get back in there.
Organ grinder needs his monkey.
- I like money just
like everyone else.
You're going over the
edge Jack, even for you.
- If it wasn't for me,
these Smurfs
wouldn't be anywhere.
- Do you know that before
the five NBA championship,
I used to work at 7-11?
And I used to work at
the airport as a janitor?
- So?
That was the time I
used to play basketball
for the love of the game.
I lost it 'til I met Roger,
Nick, George, and Chevy.
You know, thanks to those guys,
I understand that
life is more important
than money and fame.
- Who are you,
and what did you do
with my Dennis Rodman?
- You don't own me.
- You're under contract to me.
You're all under contract to me.
You're nothing without me.
- You're nothing without us.
(ticking)
(shaver vibrating)
(upbeat instrumental music)
- Those guys just don't get it.
I mean, how can anybody
say no to all that money?
You have to milk it
for all its worth.
At least you're still
gonna do it, aren't you?
- We're not The Minis anymore.
- Well.
(cow mooing)
What are we gonna do now?
- What are we gonna do?
- Of course, silly.
I mean, if you're not a Mini,
how could things work out
between the two of us?
(gentle music)
(knocking on door)
- Chevy?
What are you doing here?
It's late.
Come on in.
I'll get you a cup of coffee.
Saw the billboards.
You guys are all over the place.
You must be thrilled.
Something's wrong.
What happened?
- I got fame.
I got money.
I got the girl I always wanted.
But--
- But?
- But I'm not happy.
I think she was just
using me for my money.
- I'm not gonna tell
you I told you so.
But I told you so.
Don't you understand
that you need someone
who loves you for who you are?
And not for what you have.
Oh Chevy, what am I
gonna do with you?
- I didn't just lose
the girl of my dreams.
I also lost the team.
I lost my friend, best friend.
I need Roger.
- Then you know
what you gotta do.
After leaving a tip.
- Maybe I was a little hasty?
Did I do the right thing?
- Of course you did.
- Diapers.
We'll give him diapers.
Make him cry for his ba-ba.
- We put this team together
to prove that we
could do anything.
- Yeah, but now what
are we gonna do?
- You do what you set out to do.
You play basketball.
You don't need Jack for that.
(doorbell ringing)
I'll get it.
- But we don't have
a team anymore.
- Roger.
- Chevy.
- I know what's important now.
- Apology accepted.
- What?
I never said I was sorry.
- Oh come on, man.
- It's cool.
- Thanks, Rog.
- I feel a hug coming on.
- Come on, guys.
- [Both] Hug, hug, hug, hug,
hug, hug, hug.
(clapping)
- I think I'm gonna cry.
(doorbell ringing)
That's gotta be the pizza.
- So what are you gonna
do about the game?
- It's too late in the game
to find another player.
- What are you doing here?
- Well let me guess.
You came here to
convince us to come back?
Well we're not coming back.
- Enough's enough.
A man's gotta stand up
for what he believes in.
- Hey, I'm on your side.
- We don't care what
you have to say.
What?
What do you mean?
- I'm on your side.
We're a team, aren't we?
I told Jack to hit the road.
You know what, let's
just roll with it.
- Can we do it?
(light majestic music)
- Together, we can do anything.
- You think we can win?
- I don't know if
this team can win,
but you know what guys?
You already won me over.
(laughing)
- Yeah, yeah.
- Minis, Minis.
(cheering and clapping)
- Minis.
(intense electronic music)
(people cheering)
- Welcome to the first annual
Venice Beach
Basketball Tournament.
Today, eight teams will be
competing against each other,
but only two of
them will qualify
for tomorrow's final game,
and the chance to
win 50,000 dollars.
Everybody's attention
is focused on The Minis.
The team made up of
four little people,
and ex-NBA star Dennis Rodman.
(whistle blowing)
(upbeat dance music)
♪ Ooh la la ♪
♪ Ooh la la la ♪
♪ You know we play to win ♪
♪ Play to win ♪
♪ Ooh la la la ♪
♪ We've got crazy reflex ♪
♪ I could swing like
Tiger with a complex ♪
♪ You come at me like ♪
♪ Hmm what's next ♪
♪ Serve you well ♪
♪ Like a dance contest,
you say we can't ♪
♪ Jump jump, get
you on the rebound ♪
♪ When I dunk dunk ♪
♪ Running rings around you ♪
♪ Think you're drunk drunk ♪
♪ Now who's the
little punk punk ♪
♪ You know we play
to win, play to win ♪
♪ You know we play to win ♪
♪ Ooh la la la ♪
♪ You know we play
to win, play to win ♪
♪ You know we play to win ♪
♪ Ooh la la la ♪
♪ You can't keep the
little man down ♪
♪ About to blow this like
I'm the Terminator now ♪
♪ We got game now,
who got shade ♪
♪ So tell me, who's to blame ♪
♪ We got mad skills and
the odds are against us ♪
♪ Small but fly,
you can't pace ♪
♪ Stakes are high,
you can't erase us ♪
♪ Gonna dribble you
out of the NBA status ♪
♪ Ooh la la la ♪
(people cheering)
- The Minis just
won the first game,
and thanks to the
incredible Dennis Rodman,
they now qualify
for the semifinals.
Unfortunately, we saw
a little too little
from our little players.
- I can't believe it.
- I told you we
can do it, right?
You gotta believe in the man.
Have faith.
- But one man did all the work.
- Wouldn't have won without
Dennis, and you know that.
- So where's the victory?
Dennis played the whole time,
we just stood there and watched.
I mean, I wanna play basketball.
- Relax, Rog.
Don't forget, we're all a team.
- Nick's right.
Five fingers make a fist, man.
- Maybe we need to think small.
(whistle blowing)
(upbeat rock music)
♪ You know we really don't
care what people say ♪
♪ You know we're
gonna B-ball anyway ♪
♪ Don't think we're scared,
I'm gonna tell you why ♪
♪ We're gonna make
the big boys cry ♪
♪ You say we can't make it ♪
♪ If there's a rule,
we'll break it ♪
♪ We'll shake it,
earthquake it ♪
♪ We're gonna make
our dreams come true ♪
♪ Ooh ooh ooh ♪
♪ The laugh's on you ♪
♪ M-I-N-I-S go go Minis ♪
♪ Go go go go go go Minis ♪
- Dennis,
Think I can fly?
♪ Go go Minis ♪
(glass cracking)
♪ Our dreams come true ♪
(glass shattering)
♪ Ooh ooh ooh ♪
♪ The laugh's on you ♪
♪ Go go go go Minis ♪
- It's incredible.
The Minis have won again.
And it's official.
Tomorrow, final game,
The Minis versus
The Venice Vipers.
Reporting live from
Venice Beach courts,
I'm Megumi Hosogai.
(locker slamming)
- So, how was your flight?
- You're just jealous.
- I'm the one that threw him.
- What?
What are you talking about?
- I won't take credit
for that basket.
- Ooh, Minis.
- Congratulation.
- Hey Les.
- Hey honey, are you ready?
- Gentlemen, it's
been a pleasure.
- Is my winner ready?
- Yeah baby.
- Come on.
- You coming, Nick?
- Yeah sure, let's go.
- Have a good one, fellas.
- Tonight, I feel like the
tallest man in the world.
Who needs that operation?
- I'm clubbing in
Hollywood tonight.
I need a wing man.
- Love to, man, but I'm beat.
- Rest up, baby.
Yeah.
- Hey Dennis.
Chev.
- What are you doing here?
- I wanna go party.
- I don't feel like it.
But I wanna spend time with you.
- There's this really
great party in Hollywood.
- It's okay, you should go.
- But I need a Mini to get in.
- Oh.
You should go with Dennis.
- Really?
Dennis, Dennis.
Bye bye.
(gentle melancholy music)
- [Lorraine] Chevy, Chevy.
- Hey Lorraine.
- I saw everything on TV,
and I rushed right over.
Are you okay?
- I am now.
- You wanna do something?
Just the two of us.
- You know what, I'd love to.
(bright instrumental music)
♪ Live every moment ♪
♪ Take it easy, take your time ♪
♪ There's a voice
deep down inside ♪
♪ You can do anything
you want to ♪
♪ Now's the time
for you to try ♪
♪ Live every moment ♪
♪ Spread your wings,
now you can fly ♪
♪ You are a shining star ♪
♪ That's what you are ♪
♪ Be what you want to be ♪
♪ You can do anything ♪
♪ Stand up and sing ♪
♪ Be what you want to be ♪
(upbeat dance music)
(crowd cheering)
(speaking in foreign language)
♪ Are you ready ♪
♪ Come now, come now,
come now, come now ♪
♪ Break it down, break it down,
break it down, break it down ♪
♪ Come now, come now,
come now, come now ♪
♪ Get down with it,
get down with it ♪
♪ Get down with it on fire ♪
♪ Get down with it,
get down with it ♪
♪ Get down with it on fire ♪
♪ Get down with it,
get down with it ♪
♪ Get down with it on fire ♪
♪ Get down with it,
get down with it ♪
♪ Get down with it on fire ♪
♪ They laughing, then my toes ♪
♪ They like my flow,
and see how it goes ♪
♪ They laughing ♪
♪ Then my toes ♪
♪ They like my flow,
and see how it goes ♪
(water splashing)
(birds chirping)
(engine revving)
- I didn't know you could drive.
- Isn't it a normal thing to do?
(horn honking)
(cows mooing)
Yee-haw.
(upbeat electronic music)
(crowd chattering)
- Today it's Minis
mania out here.
Many, many people gathered
at this basketball court
to dream, to believe
the impossible,
to experience magic,
to cheer for the
team of little men
who showed us that
nothing is impossible,
and if we really want to,
we can achieve our dreams.
No matter how big
or small they are.
(upbeat hip hop music)
- [Announcer] Ladies
and gentlemen.
Welcome to the final game
of the first annual Venice
Beach Basketball Tournament.
- [Crowd] Minis, Minis, Minis.
- [Announcer] Here
come the great,
the mighty, the Minis.
(crowd cheering)
- [Crowd] Minis, Minis, Minis.
(horn blaring)
Minis, Minis, Minis.
- Tallest man on the court.
- Huh, you don't stand a chance.
- Try breath mints, man.
They're not expensive.
- Alright gentlemen.
Championship game,
let's keep it clean.
Play ball.
(blowing whistle)
- Look, it's Carmen Electra.
(upbeat hip hop music)
♪ Hey yo Minis ♪
- Go Roger.
♪ Come on, one two
three, let's go ♪
♪ What's up ♪
♪ I need the flavor ♪
♪ I really wanna know ♪
♪ Ladies and
gentlemen, let's go ♪
♪ Clap clap clap to this ♪
♪ Come on, move
move move to this ♪
♪ Come on shake,
shake, shake to this ♪
- Go Minis.
♪ Move your body, all day ♪
♪ Clap clap clap to this ♪
♪ Come on move,
move, move to this ♪
♪ Come on shake,
shake, shake to this ♪
♪ Move your body, all day ♪
♪ I know you wanna
be a big player ♪
♪ Really get it on the
court, come low son ♪
♪ You wanna be a giant like me ♪
♪ Take the ball and
prove you can be ♪
♪ Get low, rush the
flow with your boys ♪
♪ We're gonna bust
it, doing it right ♪
♪ So do what you came to do ♪
♪ I wanna see you score some ♪
(helicopter chopping)
(crowd cheering)
♪ Mini now hook some out ♪
- Yes.
♪ We're gonna jump
and dunk all right ♪
♪ Now there ain't
no holding back ♪
♪ We're gonna get
you out of this fog ♪
♪ Little man, when
you dribble it low ♪
♪ Then bouncing it
backward and forwards ♪
♪ Come on do what
you came to do ♪
♪ We're gonna play
B-ball together ♪
- Yeah, yeah.
(crowd cheering)
- Woohoo.
♪ Uh huh ♪
♪ Know what I'm saying ♪
♪ I need the flavor ♪
♪ To the figure ♪
♪ What's up man ♪
♪ I really wanna know, come on ♪
♪ I'm gonna take it
with the big ball man ♪
♪ Get back on the court,
make your move, man ♪
♪ Show you can slope
just like a Superman ♪
♪ Nobody never
scared me, any man ♪
♪ Grab the ball,
you're the man ♪
♪ You're the best,
never lose control ♪
♪ Show the zone,
never take it slow ♪
♪ Come on come on, better
to make that flow ♪
♪ Move your body,
Rodman, boom boom ♪
(crowd cheering)
♪ In a minute, you can
make me feel this ♪
♪ If you never make
major business ♪
♪ Stay where you
play, it's my game ♪
♪ You got the ball ♪
♪ You better show
them that play ♪
♪ Jam, jam, jam Minis ♪
♪ Come on move,
move, move Minis ♪
♪ Come on left,
right, dominate ♪
♪ Move your body, work all day ♪
♪ Jam, jam, jam Minis ♪
♪ Come on, move,
move, move Minis ♪
♪ Come on right,
left, dominate ♪
(crowd cheering and clapping)
♪ Well a big one ♪
♪ Basketball court,
you see it once again ♪
♪ Go go go Minis ♪
♪ Clap clap clap to this ♪
♪ Come on move
move move to this ♪
♪ Come on, shake
shake shake to this ♪
♪ Move your body ♪
(crowd cheering)
♪ Clap clap clap to this ♪
♪ Come on move
move move to this ♪
♪ Come on shake
shake shake to this ♪
♪ Move your body, work all day ♪
♪ Jam jam jam Minis ♪
♪ Come on move move move Minis ♪
♪ Come on left,
right, dominate ♪
- That's my baby.
♪ All day, jam jam jam Minis ♪
♪ Come on move move move Minis ♪
♪ Come on right,
left, dominate ♪
♪ Move your body, work all day ♪
(crowd cheering and clapping)
- Go Minis.
- Shoot, shoot, you're
all on, come on.
Take the basket.
(blowing whistle)
(crowd gasping)
- Dennis.
- Are you alright man?
Don't leave us.
- Give him mouth to mouth.
- How is he?
- Need a paramedic quick.
(blowing whistle)
- Gurney, quick.
- We can't do it
without you, Dennis.
- Yeah you can.
I believe in you guys.
- Come on, guys.
Back up fellas,
let's get in here.
Who's your substitute?
- We,
we don't have one.
- You have 10
minutes to find one.
Otherwise, you either have
to play by yourselves,
or forfeit the game.
- 10 minutes will do.
- Good.
- Now what are we gonna do?
- We're almost there.
- We could've won this.
- And we still can.
- [Crowd] Minis,
Minis, Minis, Minis.
- Can you hear it?
No one, no one is gonna
tell me to give up.
I will never give up.
(banging metal)
Never.
Four guys, three guys, two guys.
I don't care, I'm
finishing this game,
with or without you.
- You wouldn't need a fifth
player, would you dad?
- What?
- Well, I asked if you
guys needed a fifth player.
- No.
You called me dad.
Hey, whatever you wanna
do with your life,
I'm behind you all
the way, alright?
(squeaking)
- Come on, we can do this.
Because we--
- Are.
- The.
- [All] Minis.
Minis, Minis, Minis, Minis.
(upbeat dance music)
- The Minis have decided
to finish the game,
even without Dennis Rodman.
The crowd is going crazy.
And if any crowd goes crazy,
it's a Venice crowd.
(upbeat music)
♪ Oh, oh ♪
♪ Coming out, The Minis ♪
♪ They're the
little you and me ♪
♪ It's time to go
for what they want ♪
♪ And who we want to be ♪
♪ United, playing all together ♪
♪ They're gonna win
and gonna do it right ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Coming out, The Minis ♪
♪ Every color, every creed ♪
♪ We are all the same inside ♪
♪ We're family ♪
♪ United, you'll find us again ♪
♪ We're gonna win, the future's
looking bright ♪
♪ Throw your hands
up in the sky ♪
♪ Minis are playing to win ♪
♪ They got the power to fly ♪
♪ If they don't watch out ♪
(whistle blowing)
♪ Go go Minis ♪
(crowd cheering)
- Okay, we're only
down by one point.
- We can do this.
- That's what Dennis has
been trying to tell us.
- Get in position.
- Position for what?
- Yeah, for what?
- We gotta stand tall.
- Are you nuts?
- We just gotta believe.
- On three.
- [All] One two three, Minis.
(crowd cheering)
(whistle blowing)
(upbeat music)
(grunting)
- Come on, George.
Get on up here.
(majestic music)
(grunting)
- Oh, oh.
Oh.
(grunting)
(crowd cheering and clapping)
(majestic music)
(blowing whistle)
- No good, no good.
- What?
- Come on.
- That was an illegal formation.
The basket is not
good, the Vipers win.
(crowd booing)
- What's up with this?
- They can't do that.
- Where does it say that?
Show me the rules.
- Game over.
- [Roger] Dennis, you're okay.
- What did the hospital say?
Wait, you didn't get hurt.
- You didn't need me to win.
- But Dennis, we lost.
Really, man?
Look around.
- Minis, Minis, Minis,
Minis, Minis, Minis,
Minis, Minis.
- [Crowd] Minis, Minis, Minis,
Minis, Minis, Minis, Minis,
Minis, Minis,
Minis, Minis, Minis,
Minis, Minis, Minis, Minis,
Minis, Minis, Minis, Minis
(horns blowing)
Minis, Minis, Minis, Minis,
Minis, Minis, Minis--
(majestic music)
- I am so proud of you.
- That's my boy.
(crowd chanting)
- When I grow up,
I wanna be a dwarf.
- [Crowd] Minis, Minis, Minis.
(upbeat instrumental music)
Minis, Minis, Minis, Minis,
Minis, Minis, Minis, Minis.
- Where's Chevy?
- [Crowd] Minis, Minis, Minis.
♪ Sometimes I'm strong ♪
♪ And sometimes I'm wise ♪
♪ Sometimes I am invincible ♪
♪ It's all a pack of lies ♪
♪ Here I am, just a man ♪
♪ I've got nothing in my hands ♪
♪ Lift me up ♪
♪ Help me please ♪
♪ I'm here down on my knees ♪
♪ When the days are
dark and lonely ♪
♪ And the world's
falling apart ♪
♪ I know you'll be
there to help me ♪
♪ And mend my broken heart ♪
♪ When the sky above
comes crashing down ♪
♪ And hope gets swept to sea ♪
♪ I know that you'll
be there for me ♪
- I have one more
surprise for my team.
♪ When the days are
dark and lonely ♪
- I love you, dad.
- I love you, son.
- I believe.
I'll always believe.
♪ Be there to help me ♪
♪ And mend my broken heart ♪
♪ When the sky above
comes crashing down ♪
♪ And hope gets swept to sea ♪
♪ I know that you'll be there ♪
♪ For me ♪
♪ You're living the
American dream ♪
♪ Your face is on a magazine ♪
♪ Four guys like you
I've never seen ♪
♪ I wanna be like a Mini ♪
♪ You're looking good,
you're dressing fine ♪
♪ The girls are
calling all the time ♪
♪ You've done the
talk shows on TV ♪
♪ I wanna be like a Mini ♪
♪ You got the thing,
you got it all ♪
♪ You got the life,
now play B-ball ♪
♪ You made it big
though you're tiny ♪
♪ I wanna be like a Mini ♪
♪ You're looking good,
you're dressing fine ♪
♪ The girls are
calling all the time ♪
♪ You've done the
talk shows on TV ♪
♪ I wanna be like a Mini ♪
♪ You got the thing,
you got it all ♪
♪ You got the life,
now play B-ball ♪
♪ You made it big
though you're tiny ♪
♪ I wanna be like a Mini ♪
♪ You're looking good,
you're dressing fine ♪
♪ The girls are
calling all the time ♪
♪ You've done the
talk shows on TV ♪
♪ I wanna be like a Mini ♪
♪ You're living the
American dream ♪
♪ Your face is on a magazine ♪
♪ Four guys like you,
I've never seen ♪
♪ I wanna be like a Mini ♪
♪ You're living the
American dream ♪