[light music]
[Caller On Voice Mail]
Hey, Christina, listen,
I know you've been through
three drafts on this already,
but the client came back and
asked for some more revisions.
Hey, it's me.
I think you're flying again.
I haven't heard from
you in a few days,
so I just thought I'd say hi.
So hi.
[Caller 2 On Voice
Mail] I keep being asked
about the schedule and I have
to check with Andy and obviously
wants to get your timeline.
[caller speaking in Spanish]
[cell phone buzzing]
[Gloria] Christina,
what did you do with
my mortgage bills?
I just wanna put them in
the mail like I always do.
I know, but I put it
all on auto-pay for you,
you won't have to do anything.
[Gloria] It's that easy, is it?
Well, that's what I do.
My rent, my loans.
I hear a ding on my phone.
I get emailed a
theme and loans paid.
I have like eight of them.
That's why my phone's
always dinging.
[Gloria] Very funny, Christina.
So here are the critical
docs, offer sheet,
fairness opinion and peer group.
Good. Did you eat?
So bad.
I stole like five of those
pop chickens from the plane.
Oh God.
[light music]
[cell phone beeps]
I was just in Atlanta
doing a deposition.
And then after this
one was Cleveland.
Hey, Jim.
- Cleveland.
- Yeah.
How are you?
Well, you know what they say?
Teaching law beats
practicing law.
How's your mom?
Oh, still going a
hundred miles an hour.
She'll be excited to see you.
Yeah.
So Andy's got you flying
all around the country.
I told him you were a superstar.
I don't know about that.
He's in town doing a deposition.
I'm covering from another one.
So you wanted to talk to me?
Yeah.
Well, you were so helpful,
introducing me to Andy.
I was wondering if maybe you had
another recommendation
for another firm?
Maybe here.
They're not offering
a partnership.
Oh, they are.
I think two, three years.
Who knows?
I just, I keep having
these conversations
in my head about it.
And sometimes I imagine
I'm back in law school
and I'm having
that talk with you
about taking the job
in the first place.
You know, you
graduated in the middle
of the financial
panic yet you wouldn't
even consider a job here.
You headed off to California
and you've been marching down
that road for the
last six years.
Yeah.
And it's good work.
One day, I'm talking
to an investment banker
in the next I'm flying
out to meet real estate
developers and Andy's
been very supportive.
Yeah, 'cause you provide value.
Sometimes I think it's more
that I have time to give.
If that makes sense.
Well,
I'll start asking around.
I'll be discreet.
But if you leave before
you make partner,
you won't have any security.
You know, sometimes work
helps me make decisions.
Like if I'm struggling with
some personal thing, like,
like when my son was sick
and there were all the
doctors and all that,
and I just dived into
my notes on some lecture
and my mind would just work,
work, work, work, work.
And sometimes in a flash,
the answer to the other
thing would appear
and I'd click open another
window, start writing.
And there it was.
[cell phone buzzes]
Hey Marisol.
[Marisol speaks in Spanish]
You can call anytime what's, up?
No one.
It's just there to protect you.
So you have the space to
do what you need to do.
[Marisol speaks in Spanish]
I'm sorry.
Can you speak in English?
[Marisol] Yeah. Sorry.
My boss is gone now.
I just didn't want
him to understand me.
Oh, it's just,
I barely remember
Spanish and I only hear
when my mom's yelling.
[Marisol] My mom is
always yelling in Spanish.
[speaking in Spanish]
[light music]
The gym's closed.
[cell phone buzzes]
Marisol, what's going on?
[Marisol] I'm pregnant.
I'm sorry.
I wanted to tell
you before, but-
It's okay.
I can't do this. I'm done.
It's okay, just breathe.
Marisol?
[Marisol] I'm
not, I'm not ready.
[Bob] Hey Christina,
this is Bob from Lip Tech.
Just responding to your
additional keyword search.
I couldn't find.
[Caller On Voice Mail]
Hey, so I just sent you
a long email, I'm gonna need
you to write another revision.
[Caller On Voice Mail] So
not sure if you saw the email,
but Andy-
[Bobby] Hey, it's me, Bobby.
I'm just checking in.
Is everything okay?
[Joanne] Department
of Education.
This is Joanne.
Oh, hi.
Good morning.
I'm helping my mother move
her retirement account online.
[Joanne] Ma'am she's gonna
have to do that herself.
I'm gonna need to
put you on hold.
But I have her
account information.
Hello?
Hello.
How we doing, everybody good?
Not bad temporary digs, right?
Christina, can I speak with you?
So the judge asked for a
revised version of the motion.
I already gotta be in
two different places
at the same time today.
I mean, I can do
it, but it'd be tight.
Rose, she's working on Larry.
I cannot deal with her today.
I never know when she's
finished a fucking sentence.
Everything goes
up and up and up.
Last week she comes
into my office.
She tells me the sixth circuit
just came in and I think
what it means is possibly I
just tell me the decision.
Don't think in front of me,
every email starts with, hi,
with an exclamation
point at the end of it.
Yeah, well, I do that
too, just not to you.
Well don't, I will
block your partnership.
Just don't block hers.
She'll be gone in a year,
probably already
sending out her resumes.
Anyway, this needs
to go out by five
and then you can
prep for tomorrow.
Rose has you covered on that?
Oh, I haven't even looked at it.
She said the clients-
You'll win her over,
whatever, this is good for you.
Right, right.
Not too much.
[light music]
I could take a crack at it.
No, I got it.
Start it tomorrow.
Long version or short?
Short.
So this deal feels like
it was brokered in Buffalo,
not in New York.
The price point is really low.
Beautiful.
How is Jay?
Oh, good.
You know, busy.
Like always keep telling
him they should give him
a cot by the trading desk.
Well, I really appreciate
you squeezing me in like this.
Oh, it was great to see you.
What's going on.
Well, I have a
doctor back at home,
but traveling and,
I wanna make sure this is real.
Congratulations.
Was it, was it a surprise?
I remember running last night.
Is that okay?
Yeah, of course.
And I had a cup
coffee this morning.
A cup of day is fine.
[cell phone buzzes]
Do you need to get that?
No, that's just my mom.
How is she?
Good.
Well, okay.
So it looks like you left
a couple blanks here.
Sorry, I'm always facing.
Yeah, welcome to
pregnancy brain.
So your last period
was six weeks ago.
Previous pregnancies, none.
One.
Was a long time ago.
We can just finish this
after the ultrasound, yeah.
[cell phone beeps]
[upbeat music]
I got here early
because I wanted
to speak to you now because
I am completely jammed,
but you were late so now I'm
conferencing on another call.
Have to run.
You are in excellent hands.
Hi.
No, I can hardly hear you.
This office is terrible.
Can I call you right back?
Yep.
We're borrowing a few
rooms from another firm.
We can go somewhere else.
Your bio is impressive and
Andy speaks highly of you.
How much time will you
need from me tomorrow?
Well, we reserve the whole day.
We'll walk through
all the documents
that are likely to raise
questions to practice from.
You need a whole day for that?
We should review everything.
Haven't you done that already.
I'm familiar with the document.
You're familiar.
Why am I paying you
and an associate?
What, a combined $1,200 an hour,
plus what Andy's gonna charge me
for that little introduction?
I'm sure he didn't
bill you for that.
Of course he did,
he's an asshole.
But he's effective.
Just not loyal enough
to drop whatever
it is he's doing to
handle my deposition.
I left Goldman to
start my new company.
And now that I'm small
potatoes, I get the associate.
I want you to feel prepared
to the questions for routine.
It's not routine, it's my life.
The deal's being held up.
My fees being held up.
They're not claiming I
did anything illegal.
They're claiming I didn't
broker a high enough price.
They're claiming that
I am incompetent.
These law firms
troll for clients.
They find anything that
looks out of the ordinary.
They announce that
they're investigating.
It's frustrating,
but it's very common.
They're suing because
I brokered the deal.
This is personal.
I already have meetings
with clients tomorrow
who are starting to get jittery
because they're wondering
is every bank she sells
gonna get caught
up in litigation.
Every hour I pay
you for is personal.
So how much time do you need?
[cell phone buzzes]
Hey mom, can I call you later?
[Gloria] Why did you not
tell me you were in New York?
Were you not going to see me?
I'm not in New York.
[Gloria] Luz Martinez saw you.
She said you're staying
at the hotel she works at.
Well, she must
have been mistaken.
[Gloria] How can that be?
I don't know, but I'm
working and I have to get back.
I'm excited to see you soon.
Mom?
[Gloria] I'm busy too.
Please keep this away from me.
Let me know if
there's an emergency.
Otherwise, just tell
everyone I'm sick.
[mellow cello music]
That's okay, it went to
notification, ignore it.
[Andy] In my mind just,
work, work, work, work.
And open a window,
start writing.
And there it was.
And sometimes in a flash,
the answer to the other
thing opens up to you.
[melancholy music]
[cell phone buzzes]
Marisol.
[Marisol] I'm sorry
to call so late.
Is this okay?
Yeah.
What's going on.
[Marisol]
Everything's different.
I feel like, like
everyone's looking at me,
like everyone knows
that I'm pregnant.
It's in your head.
No one knows until you
tell them, you can make
a plan and get through this.
[Marisol] You just
make it sound so easy.
Yeah.
Well, when I was your age,
everything was a secret.
[Marisol] I just, I
just hate it so much.
But if you bottle all
of that up after a while
you become the secret,
and then who are you?
You know what I mean?
Marisol?
Come find me.
[knocking on door]
Hey, how's the,
how's the prep going?
Did a girl named Marisol call?
A few times.
Is she a client?
She's pro bono.
How do you have time for that?
I don't.
Did she leave a message?
No, but you got a
lot of other calls.
Are you going running?
I need to wake up.
I'll see you.
[light music]
Marisol?
Hey, just give me a sec.
[upbeat music]
Christina.
Christina, come on,
Christina, open the door.
What's going on that
you can't tell me?
Christina.
Mom.
Are you okay?
What are you doing here?
A guy named Bobby
called my school
to tell me that he
was worried about you.
And to ask me to check on you
at this hotel in Brooklyn.
Thank you, gracias.
What time is it?
Why didn't you tell
me you weren't done-
Shit, I have to meet with
a client in 20 minutes.
I am very busy too.
I am missing an IEP
meeting with parents
of a child who
needs many services.
This might change the
trajectory of his entire life.
Is it really that
dramatic, mommy?
Yes.
And why can't you take
a moment to come see me?
I'm prepping a deposition.
What for?
It's a bank. The
client's very important.
And you have to live
in California to do this.
You can get rich bankers
richer right here.
Do you know how few
women have made it
as far as I have at that firm,
a few women who look like me?
I get it.
I know, but that
doesn't give you
the right to go
through all my bills
and all my paperwork
as if I am some invalid
who cannot open a
statement once a month.
What do you think
the DOE is saying?
I'm trying to help you.
The last time I was
home, there was a pile
of bills stacked on the table.
You miss payments.
You double pay.
I put time in my
students not money,
and that's my business,
you mind your own.
Fine.
I'll come see you tonight.
What time?
I don't know.
I'll call you.
You changed your hair?
Yeah.
What have I done so wrong.
[knocking]
Holy shit.
I still have 10
minutes to get ready.
Can I have my phone please?
Yeah, your mom just called
and Bobby called a few times.
I told him you were
really, really sick.
All right, come get
me in five minutes.
[phone rings]
- Hey.
How did you get my mom's number?
[Bobby] I had to
Google her school.
Why would you call her?
[Bobby] Because I was worried.
Rose kept going on and on
about how sick you were.
No, I'm sorry. I'm not sick.
[Bobby] You know,
I'm not a mind reader.
If I did something wrong,
you've gotta tell me.
I'm pregnant.
[Bobby] Ah.
Hello?
[Bobby] I don't
know what to say.
I'm now gonna ask you a series
of questions about
your background.
What colleges did you attend?
And what degree was conferred?
I attended Queens College,
bachelor of science
and economics, 1993.
That's Queens, New York part
of the city college system?
We can't all go to Columbia.
It says you attended
from '87 through 1993.
Was there delay
in the completion
of your degree due to academic
or disciplinary reasons?
I took time off to work.
Earn any graduate degrees?
No.
Any certifications
in advanced study
for finance and securities?
No.
Your first job outta college.
I was hired as
an analyst at STL.
We have you
starting there in '95.
Where were you before that?
I interned and I bartended
anyone can Google me
and see the deals
that I have brokered.
Look,
the plaintiff's attorneys are
gonna ask you these questions
they do it to raise
doubts about you.
You didn't go to Harvard.
You didn't go to Wharton.
They're gonna make you
put that on the record.
They're gonna ask you about
your relationship with Mark.
Where'd you meet him? How'd
you secure him as a client.
They're going to imply
that I had a
relationship with Mark?
Have you seen him?
I suggest you answer these
questions with confidence.
You presented this
offer sheet to the board
of directors we'll
call document three.
Is this the offer
sheet you presented?
One moment.
Yes, that is correct.
Right, and the
standard is to share
a report of comparable deals
in the region to make it clear
that the price for
the bank is fair.
It's part of what's called
your fairness opinion.
And yet you didn't choose
any banks from the region.
This is document
four, peer groups.
Did you present this?
Hello?
Um,
yes, that is the peer group.
And you included
a bank in Harrisburg
and another in Dayton,
banks whose price points
are closer to 1.3
or 1.4 times book,
as opposed to any in
the New York Metro
where the comparable
prices would be two or 2.1.
Do you have a question?
Well, any study of similar deals
in the region would
show much higher prices.
It's like,
you're pretending this
deal's in a rust belt.
Seems like a very low price.
It's not like we're
talking about some bank
that's headquartered
on Fifth Avenue.
This bank is based in
Red Hook, Brooklyn.
The market share is
not likely to increase.
It took me two years
to find one buyer.
Now, how do you
expect me to say that
without offending the
board of directors
and drive the price
down even lower.
Christina, just turn it off.
Marisol texted you.
She said that her ex show up
at her job sounded
like an emergency.
Call the DA's office
and tell that we need
a restraining order enforced
and give them Marisol's
info on my phone.
Then call her,
tell her help is on the way,
tell her to walk
through her safety plan.
How much longer
is this gonna take?
Just a couple more hours.
- You alright?
- Yeah.
Can we just get on with it?
We'll call this document five.
Is this the fairness opinion
you presented for vote
to the board of directors
at King South bank
and was the vote unanimous?
No.
No, it wasn't unanimous.
No, this isn't the fairness
opinion that I presented.
These numbers are off.
Could she be wrong?
There's like 30
different versions of it.
I triple checked.
And did you ask the CFO if this
was absolutely the latest draft.
Oh.
Okay. Thanks.
He's sending the correct draft.
Jesus.
Can you just keep
going without it?
No, everything
revolves around it.
I'm so sorry.
What are we waiting on?
We're just getting a print
out of the correct draft.
We can pick back up in
about 20, 30 minutes.
You mean to say that
you're putting eyes
on this for the
first time right now?
We made a mistake.
Andy said you were a star.
You're in great hands.
I put my star associate on it.
His words.
[light music]
[Andy] Is this
Rose or is this you?
We fixed it. It's fine.
[Andy] No, it's not.
She left me a voicemail
yelling about malpractice,
sounded like she was in a car.
She said she'd be back.
[Andy] I'm not sponsoring
you for partnerships,
you fucking chase clients away.
While you're waiting.
I need another motion drafted.
Hold on.
Any word from Marisol?
Yeah.
I spoke to her boss and he
said that she left with Jason.
What?
All right, just keep calling.
And also I need some research.
Go back 10 years, look
up peer groups listed
in every merger in
the New York Metro
and include Boston,
LA and Chicago.
Look for anything
that sticks out.
- Is he?
- He's fine.
I work so hard.
Harder than I did in Boston.
Yeah, I know.
But you've never worked
for anyone else before.
It's different.
You have to listen more.
To what.
Are you there?
Oh yeah, go ahead.
[Caller] The judge has a problem
with the language
you put in there.
[light music]
We have the correct draft now.
Just wondering on her ETA.
Hello?
We have a lot more
material to review.
Can I speak to her?
Well, where is she?
What are you thinking about?
Must be something
your eyes are burning
a hole through that screen.
Why is it that
no matter how hard
I try not to make
the same mistakes.
Are you talking about having
the wrong draft of
my fairness opinion?
No, that was
comparatively minor.
Not to me.
What is your most
advanced degree?
JD.
Any advanced certification
in mergers and acquisition law?
No.
Any specializations whatsoever?
What makes you think you can
conduct business with experts?
My whole life,
I've been surrounded by
people who don't look like me.
Don't talk like me.
I learned to ask
myself questions.
What are they thinking?
What do they want?
What am I thinking?
[light music]
[Assistant] Look,
she's at her hotel,
but she can't speak
with you right now.
I understand.
Just give me an address.
I don't want anything,
just an address.
[light music]
We've been trying to
get a hold of you all day.
You're upset. I get it, but-
All right, we have
a bunny for you.
I told her nanny to stay
within five blocks of the hotel,
but they went exploring,
found a playground
with some monkey bars.
And of course her
elbow popped out.
I met them at the
emergency room.
I figured a dislocated elbow
was a good enough excuse
for a wine delivery.
And this lawsuit was
a good enough reason
to make it a $200 bottle.
Thank you.
My kids have weak elbows,
it's my husband's side.
Is he here?
He is back in San
Francisco working
and it's just easier
for me to bring
the nanny and the
kids along with me.
I apologize, again, I-
Don't walk into
a room unprepared,
even if it's not your fault,
people will use it against you.
If we could have two
hours tomorrow morning
before the deposition
you'll feel very prepared.
With what, more legalese?
If you're trying to justify
a decision with words,
good luck, words might
as well be stones.
I've been researching
peer groups,
not billing it to make up for
before I haven't finished yet,
but I can provide you
with some healthful data.
Do the work first, then promise.
I'd never let my daughter
do this in a million years.
You sure you have
his stomach for it?
I wanted to be a prosecutor.
Then I interned for
an ADA and realized
that putting people in cages
for a living's not for me.
And I had to pay off
my student loans.
My mom she's worked
in education 30 years,
two master's degrees.
And with the hours she
puts in the out of pocket,
it's minimum wage.
And my dad got laid off.
When I was a kid
she worked weekends,
cleaning houses, babysitting.
I wanna see my kids
on the weekends.
You have kids?
No.
Can I ask you something?
That's a $200 bottle of wine.
Aren't you the least
bit curious to try it?
No, I'm very curious.
I just.
It's none of my
business, I'm sorry.
No, I,
I just found out today.
Was it a surprise?
Oh yeah.
Well, I will drink for
you because you are screwed.
Who's the guy?
Another attorney,
different firm.
I told him today.
Don't tell anyone else.
Not until you
absolutely have to.
When are you up for partnership?
Three more years.
Get that in writing.
Do not let them defer you
because you took time off
for maternity because they will.
[Pat] How long
have you been dating?
Six or seven months.
He's really nice, I just,
I just don't know
him that well yet.
[Pat] How long does
it take to know someone?
I've been with my husband
20 years and sometimes
still in the middle of the night
I wake up and I look over at him
and I just think who are you?
[light music]
Mom?
So you went to law school here.
You grew up here.
You couldn't find a
firm here to hire you.
I just felt like I could live
my whole life in one
place in one way,
or I could see what
else was out there.
Maybe even be someone else.
You know?
I do.
And I love it there,
I go running every day.
And you can see city and
mountain beaches all in one run.
It's like this whole
world opens up around you.
It's takes my breath
away every single time.
Still,
I think that no matter
how much everything
around you changes-
It's still just
always gonna be you.
Yes.
I may not have shown it,
but I liked you the moment
Andy introduced you,
'cause I saw myself
with all that promise,
all that baggage.
A long time ago, I was
going through something.
I don't know if I
was dreaming it,
but I saw the
light inside of me.
An actual light?
I was so scared that
people would see it.
And I didn't understand that.
I just wanted it to stop.
And just as quickly it
was gone and I missed it,
and I'd always felt like
I'd done something wrong,
and years go by,
and the other
night it came back.
I know it sounds
stupid, but I felt that-
[phone rings]
[Marisol] Hi, this is Marisol.
Please leave a message.
Hey, I'm sorry I
missed your calls.
Could you call me back and
let me know that you're safe.
If, if you're worried at all,
I'll send the cab to
take you wherever or,
I'll send you a plane ticket
and you can come with me.
Whatever you want.
Just,
just let me know you're okay.
[knocking]
Hey, got your research.
Did you talk to Andy?
No.
He asked me to fly
ahead to Cleveland.
Are you okay?
Yeah. Yeah.
Thank you for this.
It's gonna help a lot tomorrow.
You should really call Andy.
Okay.
Oh, I forgot to tell
you when I had your phone,
somebody called a few
times and I wasn't sure
if it was an emergency.
So I picked up, it was an
old professor of yours.
He said that there was
someone he wanted you
to meet before you leave town.
I'm not looking for another job.
I would never ever tell anyone.
And no one would
blame me if you were.
This is so-
You just started.
A year from now this
is all gonna seem.
What, normal?
A year from now
I'll be eight years
from partnership.
I applied for a job in Oakland.
I think I might get it.
It's this nonprofit.
I'd get to work with people
who aren't millionaires,
weekends off.
Of course they only have funding
for 12 months and
it barely pays, but.
It sounds like a great job
for someone coming outta law
school with a trust fund.
Yeah, I know how lucky I am.
Tell myself all the time.
Sorry.
That sounds great.
I'll see you in Cleveland.
[light music]
[indistinct chatter]
That's all, excuse me one sec.
Hey, I called you last night.
I even emailed.
Did you check your inbox?
No.
I was able to move my
deposition to tomorrow.
I can take over here.
You can go ahead to Cleveland.
No, I'm good. We worked it out.
She asked me to come.
She insisted.
I was at her hotel last night.
Yeah.
She told me.
Did you offer to
stay up all night
and do extra research for free?
Like you're some fucking
junior associate at her bank.
I was trying to help.
Do not ever offer
to work for free.
It makes you look cheap.
When you're getting sued
you don't want a bargain lawyer.
I'm gonna go talk-
No, no, no, no, no.
Look, she likes you.
Okay, but this isn't personal.
This is transactional.
I don't want to be here.
I haven't seen my kid in a week.
Now get some sleep.
You look terrible.
Jesus.
Oh my God, I'm sorry.
You look tired.
All right.
Now, can I have the research
you were working on last night?
[cell phone buzzes]
Please?
Hey, where are you?
Are you okay?
[Marisol] Yeah. Sorry.
I was up all night
talking with Jason.
I told him about the
baby and he's excited.
He broke the restraining
order less than a week after.
[Marisol] No, I
asked him to come.
What?
[Marisol] I thought
I texted you that.
Maybe you did.
[Marisol] We're gonna
make a plan like you said,
and maybe you're right.
I should have
waited to tell him,
but I'm just so
tired of secrets.
Of course.
[Marisol] Last night was
the first time in so long
I felt excited.
Is that crazy?
[light music]
Hey.
You're back.
I am.
You didn't do anything wrong.
It isn't like that at all.
It's just not developing the way
it should be at three
and a half weeks.
And probably this
week it'll feel
like you're having your period.
This is common, actually.
It doesn't mean
anything long term.
It happened to me
before Carly was born.
Twice actually.
I didn't know that.
After the second
time I was feeling
really low and Jay said,
maybe we should take this
opportunity to work on ourselves.
Set some goals, learn
a new instrument.
Really decide who we wanna be.
Did you do it?
No, maybe he did.
I...
just wanted to be sad
for a little while.
[light music]
[suspenseful music]
Relieved I guess.
At least that way we have
time to figure things out.
If we want that.
[Caller] If we do.
I'm sorry.
I didn't return your calls
I was going through something.
I can't explain it.
Wow.
If you wanna try I'm here.
[Charlie] Hey
Christina, it's Charlie.
Andy said you might have some
time today to work on a brief.
So I figured I'd
call you and see.
[Caller] Andy's
really stressed out
and he's wondering
where you are and-
[Caller 2] Hey Christina,
wondering if we had some
time today or tomorrow.
[Andy] Hey, Christina,
what the hell were
you thinking today?
Are you on your way
to Cleveland or not?
And also have you been
working on that petition?
[Bob] Hey Bob from Li tech,
I'm actually gonna
need some more.
[Caller 4] Hey Christina,
I still haven't heard.
[Gloria] Please call me back.
I'd like to see you
before you leave.
[light music]
[Christina] I'm right outside.
Where?
Have you been paying off
my student loans with
your retirement money?
Not all of them.
Just a little.
I never asked you to do that.
Did you know your grandma
sent me her pension checks.
It killed me.
It started when you were little
and I was still in school.
What was I gonna do?
But I took them
and I give you some
of mine so I can remember her.
And because,
you are special,
I knew it from the first
moment I held you in my arms.
It was like a lightning
bolt went off.
I knew you were meant
for great things.
And here you are partnership
now and who knows?
I'm not gonna be partner.
Why would you say that?
I just do the same
thing every day.
Day after day, I write about it.
I prayed about it.
I'm done.
And I don't, maybe
I'll come back here.
I just wanna start over.
No, no, no, no, no,
[speaks in Spanish],
listen, you're not quitting.
You've worked too hard.
You've come too far.
Look at you.
Look at what you do.
I don't help anyone.
Think about the
people you could help
as a partner at the firm.
Now it don't matter.
It's important, Christina.
Don't do that.
Okay.
So now you know what you want
and what you don't
and it's out and good.
But running won't help
you, you need more time.
Let it come,
until then you've got
to go back California.
I can't even do that.
I have to go to Cleveland.
Then you go and you take my
love with you wherever you go.
We're pioneers.
Remember when I told you that?
[speaks in Spanish]
[light music]
I think about you all the time.
- I'm sorry.
- Mm-Hm.
Call me when you get there.
Excuse me.
Good morning.
- Thank you.
- Yes.
There's no parent
coordinator on the east door.
Vicky's already
heading down that way.
You ready for your big weekend?
I'm going to keep power walking
until I fit into that dress.
Another parent tour?
Yes.
You have any of those?
[speaks in Spanish]
Pasculi's got that one,
Regaria's got the one upstairs.
We had a vandalism
in the bathroom.
Pauli's on his way
now to clean it up.
More of the same.
Yeah.
There's definitely some genital
like drawings
reminds me of Carlos.
Vegas, I remember.
Yes.
Excuse me, did
you wash your hands?
No.
Go back in there.
I shouldn't have to
keep reminding you.
Patricia asked me to tell
you that your doctor called.
Oh, what's wrong?
Ray's feeling a little sick
and the nurse won't
be in until nine.
Hm.
[both speaking in Spanish]
Take him to the office
and get him a bucket.
Feel better, buddy. Come on.
Remember that we have the vote
for honor society
today at lunch.
We already did that.
Yeah, but we needed
to reschedule that one.
Excuse me,
you just wasted five minutes
of your class time and
you can't get that back.
Go.
Reminder 9:30,
we're going to be sitting in
on Karen's new drama unit.
As soon as I are you going
to sneak in all those things?
I just thought we'd go and see.
It could be fun.
Yes. It could be fun.
But what's the purpose or is it
just another entertaining thing
someone is asking them to do?
[speaking in Spanish]
So we have Roberto
from Mrs. Earls class
to join you this morning.
Wonderful.
Good morning students
and teachers.
My special guest for
morning announcements
is Roberto from
Miss Earl's class.
And what is this
nurse showing us?
It's my all about sharks.
And what's it all about peace?
Is it a story?
No. It's a research report.
Just to read it
all about a topic.
And what are these parts?
Shark habitat, shark diet.
How do sharks
protect themselves?
My chapters.
What a smart idea to organize
your report into chapters.
Are you ready for
the pledge, Roberto?
A pledge allegiance.
To the flag.
To the flag of the
United States of America.
What's your character's name?
- Caroline.
Oh, that's a fun name.
Hey, how does Caroline move?
Oh, kind like a
Do-si-do sort of thing.
Okay, well now you're
building a character.
That's awesome.
Thanks.
Do you have the attendance too?
Yep. Got that right?
You haven't heard anything
from the superintendent
yet, have you?
Heard what?
Well, you know,
I know they have
to open up your job
to the whole district
once you retire next week.
I just wondering if you hear
anything from Carmen yet?
Nothing.
How's the basement coming along?
Oh, well we have rented
a power standard
for the weekend.
I just, I hope that Tina knows
what she's doing
because I do not.
Aren't you eating?
Hey, remember that
We have the vote for
Student Honor Society.
We already voted.
Yes. Yep.
But we really need
to vote again.
Why.
No.
Agnes already bought the cake?
I told you absolutely no party.
You did.
And Agnes bought a cake.
Surprise!
[all applaud]
[all cheer]
So you obviously,
you don't officially retire
for another two weeks.
Don't say that word.
Yes.
But we just wanted an
opportunity to thank you
for all the amazing
work you've done here.
It's 12 straight years, right?
Yes.
- Yeah.
12 straight years
of the highest ELA
scores district-wide.
That's you.
Okay.
All right. All right.
And obviously we
moved up your party
a little bit
because we also know
this is a big weekend for you.
And we wanted the
opportunity to invite
a special guest
from out of town.
Oh my God, my baby's here.
Oh congratulations.
Thank you.
I'm going to be such a wreck
before the wedding even starts.
Look at this
beautiful bride to be.
Aww.
I better speak
quickly so we can get
the kids back to work.
Yes.
But my God, for one time,
I don't know what to say.
My heart is full.
[light music]
Of course the prayer
is much longer in Hebrew.
But in essence, what
it says is blessed art
thou oh Lord, our God, master
of the universe, et cetera.
And then Helena,
you will come up and present
Christina with your necklace.
Oh, you can practice that.
Thank you, Rabbi.
You look beautiful.
So tall, so thin, so
good for our gene pool.
Thank you.
And then I will
circle behind you,
I will put on this
precious necklace.
I will lean over to
my boy and I will say,
I love you, son,
son, good luck.
Thank you, Helena.
So I'll just be standing
here holding the stick.
You'll be holding up
the pole of the huppah.
[speaking in Spanish]
And then the Christina,
you will circle Robert
seven times to the left.
Practice, go ahead.
[light music]
And what's all this
with the necklace.
Is that a Jewish thing too?
All the women in
Bobby's family wear
that necklace on
their wedding day.
And did Art use it for his
next two wives after Helena?
You told me a rabbi and a
priest were officiating.
[speaks in Spanish].
I explained all this
three times in an email.
Yes, and I said I wanted
to talk with you about it.
Why didn't you call me?
[speaks in Spanish].
Stop, stop, stop.
I don't wanna have this
conversation right now.
When then, because I
really wanna speak with you.
Can we have dinner?
I'll come to the hotel afterwards
and we can go for a walk.
I'm just excited for us
all to sit together now
and just celebrate.
Mom?
[clinking]
Bobby, your family
has been wonderful
and welcoming and your
father Art and Gemma.
So kind of you to
host this dinner.
And of course,
thank you, Helena.
I know my baby's very loved.
I was watching
Christina practicing
the circling with
Rabbi Winthrop.
Weinthrob.
I'm sorry, Weinthrob.
And I could see her passing
when she was a little girl
running around my
school and I could
also see her again in my school.
When was this?
Five years ago?
She had just graduated
from law school
and I had her come to
speak to my students,
wearing her cap and gown.
Christina told me she
was moving to California.
I said, what?
California?
Just a couple of years.
That was the plan.
Remember what I said?
You might meet
someone out there.
Salud.
[All] Salud.
[clinking]
[light music]
[speaking in Spanish].
Bobby, [speaks in Spanish],
tax attorney with
irritable bowel syndrome.
Huh.
[speaks in Spanish]
[knocking]
I heard you come in.
I'm in the adjoining room.
Hi.
I would like to invite you in,
but I am supposed to
meet Christina outside.
We're going for a walk.
Oh lovely.
It was a wonderful night.
Yes.
Let me ask you
something, Gloria.
What do you think about my
ex-husband's latest wife?
- Jim?
- Yeah.
Seems lovely.
Lovely.
Is she even 12?
Christina says you
dabble in fortune telling.
Yeah, sometimes,
but mainly it's just,
just nonsense.
Well, I'll let you
go, have a good walk.
If you can't sleep, knock.
- Thank you, Helena.
- Of course.
[cell phone ringing]
[light music]
[Christina] Hi, it's Christina.
I can't take your call to
please leave a message.
Christina.
I've called you.
I've left you two messages now,
please let me know
you're okay, please.
[eerie music]
I keep having this
dream that there's
a light coming out of my chest.
Is that crazy?
Maybe my subconscious
know something I don't,
like maybe it's related
to this problem.
Well, I wouldn't
call it a problem.
Your blood work looks good.
TSH is up a bit.
Your ultrasound did show
one of your nodules has
gotten slightly bigger.
It's most likely nothing,
but I'd like to
schedule a biopsy.
My daughter's
wedding is coming up.
We'll have the results quickly.
It's likely we just need to
change your prescription.
I know how this goes.
I've been through it before.
I remember, but you don't
know how it's going to go.
Well, I do know
something's wrong,
and I don't know what I
should tell Christina.
Can I share something with you?
I dream about baseball,
every night,
just hitting the
ball to the left side
of the infield and
running around the bases.
And I never get to home plate.
I just keep hitting it to
third base and running.
Why the left side of the field?
I don't know.
I haven't picked up
a bat in 30 years.
It doesn't make any sense,
but every night there
I am running the bases.
[light music]
Excuse me.
Good morning.
Thanks.
There's no parent
coordinator on the east door.
Vicky's already
heading down there.
You ready for your big weekend?
I'm going to keep power walking
until I can fit into that dress.
Another parent tour.
Yes.
[speaks in Spanish].
Yeah. Pesculi's got that one.
So there was another
incident in the bathroom.
More drawings.
Holly's on his way there now.
Okay, I think we're gonna get-
I didn't do it.
I believe you, go back in
there and wash your hands.
I already did.
Then go to class.
Reminds me of Carlos.
- Rodriguez.
- Yeah.
Not as bad.
Tell the teachers to
check their bathroom logs
and to send me a list of boys
who went to the bathroom
between eight and 9:00 a.m.
I promise you it was not me.
Excuse me.
Excuse me?
Can I help with?
Yes, please.
With Christina.
That's my daughter's name.
Let's take a walk, Christina
Did your class make these?
Yeah.
Which one is yours?
This one.
How did you think of your story?
My family goes to the beach
a lot and I was the only kid who
didn't know how to swim and
everybody else knew how to swim.
So when I finally learned I-
[light music]
Mommy?
[speaking in Spanish]
You're analyzing poetry
and writing plays and
even learning Latin.
I can't give you that here.
All I do is test, test, test.
[speaks in Spanish]
Someday you will
[speaking in Spanish]
Hush.
Someday you will be
a poet or a doctor.
Anything you want,
we're pioneers,
we're doing things in our family
no one has ever done.
Be proud.
Okay?
Vika's here, she'll
take you on the train
up to your school.
[speaking in Spanish].
Oh, we have Roberto from Mrs.
Earl's class joining
this morning.
Wonderful.
Good morning.
My special guest for
morning announcements is
Roberto from Miss Earl's class.
What is this you're showing us.
It's my all about sharks piece.
Good, now you are
building a story.
I think we need
another volunteer.
What's your character's name?
- Me?
- Yeah.
- Richard.
- No, no.
Now not your real name.
Your character's name?
- Richard.
- Okay.
Good. Good.
Now how does your
character walk?
Come on up.
Yeah, well.
Yeah, come on.
Oh yeah, okay.
Midgard, he walks with a smile.
Ooh.
Yeah, I used to be six feet,
but now I think I've
shrunk an inch or two.
In fact, I'm afraid
to measure myself.
Ooh.
See, now that's good because
now we know a secret.
You are afraid to
measure yourself.
So when was the first
time that you started
to thank you were shrinking?
Ah, yeah, that happened when
I first started working here.
Oh.
Yeah.
And when I first
met Miss Hernandez,
I mean Miss Smir Hernandez.
Right?
That's right.
I'm just observing here.
So when I showed up the
first day I started shrinking.
Here comes Miss Smir Hernandez.
Shrinking, huh?
Yep, I was just that day-
Shrinking.
Mm. Yep.
The first thing
you need to know,
if you want to work here
is you need a calendar.
Anything that needs to
happen goes on the calendar.
Otherwise everything gets
away and nothing gets done.
Parent workshops, you
put it on the calendar,
teacher evaluations
on the calendar.
You don't want your
mailbox overflowing.
You want to know when
you're going to answer them.
Put that time.
[All] On the calendar.
Time to eat.
Well, when do we go home?
Home, we sleep on the desks.
What do I tell my wife.
To bring us sleeping bag.
Excellent. Okay.
Let's line up over here so we
can do the next
character exercise.
[speaking in Spanish]
Did you know that
Tina keeps a journal?
Is that something
most people do?
I don't know.
Do you?
No.
Are you eating?
I was cleaning out
our bedroom, you know,
for the new flooring
and I grabbed a bunch
of books and it just, it
fell and flipped open.
I didn't even realized what
it was at first, you know?
And it was mostly
about our kids.
Yeah, but the weird thing is,
she didn't even mention me.
I just, I stopped
reading about her
and just started looking
for a little clue about me.
Why are you telling me this?
Have you heard anything
from the superintendent yet?
No.
Hey.
Remember that we have the vote
for the Student Honor Society.
What?
Surprise!
[all applaud]
And obviously
we moved up the
party a little bit
because this is a very
special weekend for you.
Andy gave us the
opportunity to invite
a special guest
from out of town.
Oh my God.
[all cheer]
My baby's here.
Surprise.
I,
When I began here.
It's true.
We're supposed to be shut down.
We sometimes had
police in the building,
running down the halls, right?
I think about that a lot.
I wasn't even certified
yet to be a principal.
I was taking classes
on the weekends.
So I cleaned houses.
We had to pay for it.
I used to leave Christina
with a babysitter
who I think only spoke Polish.
On those nights,
coming home from Manhattan.
I'd be trying to write plans.
But the progress
here was so slow
and I'd be thinking
on the train.
It is so hard to love
other people's children
as much as you love your own.
[light music]
I was watching Christina
practicing the circling.
It was very evocative.
I could see her,
when she was a little girl,
she'd make a new friend.
She'd load up this red wagon
we got her and put all
her favorite toys on it
and drag them over
to her friend's house
and give them all to her friend.
It happened a few times.
She dragged this wagon onto
the subway all the
way up to Park Avenue.
Imagine the parents probably
worried we had bed bugs.
I can see her now
dragging that little red wagon.
I could get her a red
SUV if it would help.
Hilarious, Sandro.
- I'm just saying.
- Just hilarious.
Generous bride.
Lucky us, here's to them.
The happy couple.
- The happy couple.
[clinking]
[light music]
[cell phone rings]
[Christina] Hi, it's Christina.
I can't take your call.
Christina, it's mom.
Please call me.
Hey, what is that?
Hey, stop.
Hey, hey, hey.
[light music]
[knocking]
Do you have anything
that can help me sleep?
Just one.
Gloria,
I wanna tell you something.
When I was getting
ready to marry Arthur,
my mother tells me that
her mother had a necklace
with a different diamond on it
for every generation
of our family
going back hundreds,
hundreds of years,
our people were furriers.
They had money.
The necklace she tells me
is like looking
into a kaleidoscope.
It holds the history
of my entire family.
So many carats.
Here.
Just breathe this in normal.
- Oh no, no.
- You won't regret it.
[coughs]
Good. Good.
My grandmother, the
one with a necklace.
Gassed at Auschwitz,
whole side of my family gone.
And those diamonds,
who the hell knows
who's wearing them now.
And my mother tells me this,
the night before my wedding,
and then she hands me this.
All of the life, my mother
Lily put away money bit by bit.
So that for my wedding,
she could buy me this.
Go ahead.
You open it.
I only wish to God
she were here to see
Christina wear it.
And tomorrow I will add another
diamond to it for Christina.
I know it's a little bit
much, but that's my taste.
And someday she will give
this to her granddaughter.
And if somebody takes
it, we start again.
You know, when I had cancer
and they had to operate,
I decided great.
I'm gonna get new breasts
and they're gonna
be better than ever.
Who's that man who keeps rolling
the same Boulder up the hill?
I don't know.
Well,
just keep,
I just keep rolling my boulder.
And I've got my dignity.
Sound familiar?
Oh, whoa.
No, no, no.
Just sit. Just sit.
Just sit, sit, sit.
You're okay.
I'm just.
Dizzy.
It's all right.
That's alright.
Gloria.
I think you're
searching for something.
I just wanna talk to Christina.
Do you know what
you would say to her?
Okay.
It's okay. It's okay.
Listen to me.
My mother taught
me how to do this
when I was a
little, little girl,
I cannot remember a time
when I could not read palms.
Trust me.
Close your eyes.
Really, do it.
Let everything go black.
Now where we go.
[light music]
That's right.
Now breathe.
Someone is writing on
the walls of your memory.
The words are in Spanish.
I can't greet them.
Morning.
There's no bearing
coordinator on the east door.
Vicky's heading
down there right now.
Wait.
There's been some vandalism.
[knocking]
I didn't do it.
Go back to class.
Go.
Tell the teachers to
check their bathroom logs
and to send me a
list of boys who went
to the bathroom between eight
and nine and check
their hands for ink.
What are they doing?
I don't know.
One of their parents
must have called them.
Excuse me.
Please wait in my office.
Hello?
Where are they going?
It's not just in the bathroom.
It's everywhere.
What are you doing?
Get back to class now.
Let's go. Come on, go, go.
Get to class.
Your doctor's office
keeps calling.
Not right now.
And Roberto from
Mrs. Earl's class
is in your office is
waiting to do morning arch.
Can you handle that, please?
Handle it.
We've been working
together for 15 years
in the next two weeks
you'll be the
principal, act like it.
Okay.
[speaking in Spanish]
Good, that's good.
Now you're building
memories for your character.
Great.
Now who's next.
[All] Me, me, me.
Mom?
Christine.
I'm sorry.
We had an emergency here.
I wrote the play for you
and you didn't even come.
Well, tell me about it now.
No.
Well, wait, we wait.
Look at me, honey.
Look at me.
What was it about?
About a mommy who has a
light coming out of her chest.
Told you I didn't do it.
Found the boy responsible
for the vandalism.
Let go of me now, let go of me.
Relax. Relax.
Excuse me. Let him go.
We don't have these
problems here anymore.
Ma'am did you look at his hands?
He's only 13.
Please let him go.
Get these handcuffs off of him.
Let him go.
Christina, wait for me here.
Christina?
Back inside, back inside,
get back into your classroom.
Back to your class.
Back to class now.
Now.
Christina?
Don't do that.
Don't touch the armor,
go to class now.
[light music]
[Christina] Mom.
Christina,
Christina.
Mom,
graduation was last week.
Do I really have to wear this?
Yes.
I want the students to know
what someone who graduates from
law school looks like,
look how beautiful you are.
Mom, stop.
I've been putting
this off all week.
So I'm just gonna say it.
I took a job in California.
California.
They offered a lot of money,
way more than anyone else.
And you know how many
student loans I have?
I'll go out for
a couple of years
and I'll pay off my loans
and then I'll come back.
What if you meet
someone out there?
That's not gonna happen.
Why do you say that?
Because I know guys aren't
exactly knocking down my door.
I mean, look at me.
I am looking.
Yeah, I sound like
one thing and I look
like another, can't
figure myself out.
I'm tired of trying
to be someone I'm not.
Besides, I like California,
it's like a chance for
me to start over again.
You never mentioned
you were unhappy.
Mom.
You did everything
you had to do.
I know how lucky I am.
It's just hard
disappointing you.
Hey.
Remember we have the vote
for Student Honor Society.
What?
Surprise!
[all applaud]
Where's Christina?
Where's Christina
I'm feeling disoriented.
I feel like my heart's
skipping beats.
I didn't hear any
irregularities in your heartbeat
and your blood work is fine.
TSH is up a bit though.
And your ultrasound did show one
of your nodules
has gotten bigger.
It's probably nothing, but
I'd like to schedule a biopsy.
I know how this goes,
I've been through it before.
I remember, but with
Victor it was an MRI.
A lot of times spots can
show up on x-rays just
if you move around a little bit
when the picture's being taken,
but I'd like to schedule an MRI
just to rule out a few things.
What kinds of
things to rule out?
[speaking in Spanish]
Victor and I had
many good times.
Most of them, I
wish I had a camera,
but you can't stop to grab it.
You have to remember
it all, the feeling,
the warmth of it.
I think if we have
enough of those moments,
maybe they burn in,
my mother was a woman
of very few words.
So when she spoke, you listened.
The night before my wedding,
she came in my room,
sat in my bed and talked
about marriage and my future.
So later tonight, Christina,
you and I will have a nice talk.
It all comes around like the
circle in your Jewish thing.
I can see you pulling
that wagon, honey,
what I wish I could do,
what I wish I could
say to you then.
There are so many things
I would like to tell you,
but I'm supposed to make it
snappy because it's a total-
[crash]
Oh my God.
What am I trying to say?
I'm sorry.
[light music]
[cell phone rings]
[Christina] Hi, it's Christina.
I can't take your call.
Please leave a message.
Christina, could
you please call me?
Can I make a prediction?
I think I know how it's gonna
go for you with your doctor.
The growth will be benign,
but they're gonna need to check
you every six months
again, again and again.
And that may be hard.
Like that, man,
with a sword tied to one string
forever hanging over his head.
What's that guy's name,
or whatever.
And you'll ask me, am
I gonna live with that?
And I'll tell you
that it takes time,
and you'll say,
but I don't have time.
And I'll answer time
is everything.
[thud]
[suspenseful music]
Christina?
Hush, hush.
You're okay. You're okay.
You're okay.
You must have been
sleep walking,
it was the Ambien.
It'll be morning soon.
You should finish your dream.
[suspenseful music]
Hush, hush.
[speaking in Spanish]
Oh.
Look at you.
Oh my God.
So beautiful.
You know, we're working on it.
I'm sorry I didn't come out.
I was mad, I didn't
wanna take it out on you.
It's fine.
So what did you
wanna talk to me about?
[sighs]
[light music]
It's all good.
I never meant to drive you away.
I just,
I'm sorry I haven't
always been there for you.
[Christina] You're
always with me.
I just love you.
You're my light.
Be happy.
[melancholy music]
[light music]