[Rooster crows]
[Horse whinnies]
[Horse flutters]
- Whoa.
Hold now, hold.
[Horses whinnying]
[Flutters]
[Horses neighing]
[Gunshot]
You sorry piece of horse flesh.
[Horse grunts]
Now, you see what you done?
They got away again.
[Traffic sounds]
[Birds tweeting]
- That was your daddy's
favorite painting.
- I used to catch him
staring at it.
- Hmm.
- So, what are you
going to do, Abygail?
- I don't know.
I never expected judge Travers
to leave me a thing,
let alone be so generous.
- Well, you're family.
You've been with us since...
[Sighs]
I can't remember
when you weren't here.
- Just a minute.
You can never quite tell
what's inside
a person's private heart
and soul.
Your father didn't talk
much about himself,
but you can tell a lot
about a person
by what they hold onto
over the years.
- Well, what is it?
- It's something your daddy
should have told you about.
But you know men.
They put things off.
- No, not daddy.
He was Mr. Discipline,
Mr. Schedule, Mr. Perfect.
- That was his judge's persona.
That was how most people
saw him,
but he was still a man.
- You know what's in here,
don't you?
- Yes. He showed it to me once
debating how to tell you.
But he just never
got around to it.
I'll be here
if you want to talk.
Honey, your friend Larry
is here.
- Thanks, Abygail.
[Door shuts]
Hey, Nat.
You shouldn't have had
to call me.
I should have come
on my own.
What's up?
- I have something
to show you.
Here.
Can you believe it?
- I'm sorry.
I don't get it.
- My father, the ever honest judge Charles Everett Travers,
he was married before.
- Before?
- Before my mother.
Yeah, it's a little secret
that he carried to his grave
with him.
Why didn't he ever tell me?
- I'm sure he had his reasons
for not telling you.
- Oh, don't defend him.
- There's nothing to defend.
I'm just saying that he probably had his reasons
for not telling you this.
I never know what to do
in these situations.
- What situations?
When was the last time
a friend of yours came to you
and said that her father
was married before her mother
and to a trick rider no less.
- A trick rider?
- Yes, a cowgirl.
She rode horses in a rodeo
like a sideshow clown.
- Well, she rode horses.
You ride horses.
- I am not a cowgirl.
- Well, they were very young.
- I wonder if my mother knew.
- Well, I'm sure she knew that he had a life before they met.
I mean, people do remarry.
And I'm sure that if
she lived longer
she would have told you.
- But how come
he didn't tell me?
- Well...
Check her out.
She's pretty cool.
I mean, look at those clothes.
I dig that hat.
I bet she stood on the back
on galloping horses.
Don't you kind of wonder
what they had together?
- I don't know what I wonder.
[Laughs]
I don't even know
what I feel.
[Sniffs]
- Hey, come here, pal.
It's going to be ok.
It will be all right.
[Flapping]
[Squeaking]
[Horse neighs]
[Dog barking]
[Bell rings]
- Hey, Lulu. Hey.
[Laughs]
[Splashing]
- I'm supposed to do
all that, Sam.
- Yeah, I know, but I know
you can't reach.
And I don't want to have that
two foot dirty streak
down the middle of my window
like everybody else
in this town.
[Squeaking]
Go get me ten dollars
worth of gas.
- Morning to you too, Sam.
- [Laughs]I'm sorry. Good morning, Lulu.
You look tired this morning.
- Psychology test
on deductive reasoning.
I studied 'til two.
- You're on time for work.
I'm impressed.
- Well, have to be here
at the crack of dawn
as if anyone but a moron
needs gas at this hour.
- Jess, if she's still
holding on up there,
should be service
for something in this world
even if it's for us morons.
What's this?
Some new policy?
I give you a ten.
You give me a fifty?
- It's the fifty you gave me
for Jess.
- I told you to put this
in her fruit jar.
- I did, but she took
one look at it
and knew exactly
where it came from.
Says you know she's not
a charity case.
- That is the hardest headed
woman we'll ever know.
- She ain't ever...
- isn't.
- Isn't ever going to
let us repay here
for anything she or her mama
did for us.
That's just the way
she is.
- We're just going to have to
keep on trying, aren't we?
[Laughs]
See you, Lulu.
- Bye, Sam.
[Bell rings]
[Phone ringing]
[Fax sounds]
[Phones ringing]
[Chatter]
- Bennett, Martin and Jordan.
May I help you?
Oh, hello, Max.
Uh, let me check her extension.
Can you hold?
- Yeah, Nancy?
- Natalie, Max is holding for
you on line one.
- Thanks.
Hey, Max, what do you have?
Really?
Right here in California?
[Pen scratching]
[Keys jangling]
[Car alarm beeps]
[Country music playing]
[Chatter]
- Just seat yourself, honey!
Specials are up on the board.
I'll be right there.
Here you go.
- Thank you.
So, tell me, your salads,
are they...
- your best bet's
one of the specials.
Just passing through, are you?
- Well, no, I’m...
I'm looking for someone.
Actually, I'm writing an article on old rodeo performers,
and I understand one of them
used to live around here.
- Lots of 'em.
It's kind of a mecca.
Or it was. Well, those days
are gone for good.
Um, chili's good today.
- Yeah, fine. Whatever.
- One chili, Billy!
- Uh, onions?
- Oh, no. Thank you.
- Hold the onions.
- [Laughs]
- Here's some more water just
in case the chili's too hot.
Sometimes Billy gets a little
carried away back there.
- Thank you.
Uh...
Can you tell me
where I might find
a Maggie Mae Jarrett.
She was pretty well known for...
- trick riding, honey!
Everybody that knows anything
knows about Maggie Mae Jarrett.
- Good, good.So maybe you know where she is
or where I might find someone
who knows more about her.
- Oh, rodeo folks pretty much
ended up all together
west of town at shady grove.
You take the first dirt road to your right, look for the names.
Third row on your left.
Her place is the newest.
- Thank you.
- Enjoy.
Mm.
[Groans]
[Stomps]
[Coughs]
[Slurping]
[Rattling]
- Just freeze.
[Hissing]
He'll slither off as soon as
he figures out
you're not going to hurt him.
Must be a nest
around here somewhere.
I see one almost every time
I come out.
- Uh, a nest?
- Yeah, ever seen one?
Dozens and dozens of little ones
just wiggling and writhing
all over the place.
It's really interesting.
- Can you just do something,
please?
- Yes. Hey, go on. Get!
Go on. Get. Go on.
- [Sighs]
- Go on.
You ok?
- No, not really.
- You don't look like
you're from around here.
You got family buried here
or something?
- Uh, no, I’m...Researching.
- Researching?
- Yeah.
Yeah, I'm writing about
rodeo performers.
- Oh my goodness. You're here
for Maggie Mae and her pals.
- Yeah.
- That's my mama.
I'm her daughter
Jessie Mae Jarrett.
You can call me Jess.
- Daughter?
- Yeah, daughter.
Nice to meet you.
Um, I didn't get your name.
- I didn't know
she had a daughter.
- Boy, that snake really
upset you, didn't it, hon?
- Yeah, the snake and the chili.
- Sally's diner?
Oh, lord. But the snake's gone.
Got to make you feel
a little better.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Did I get your name?
- Oh, no, it's Natalie tr...
Natalie Travers.
- From?
- L.A. Los Angeles.
- Ok.
Natalie Travers
from Los Angeles,
it's nice to meet you.
You can follow me on back
to the house.
I'll tell you all about
Maggie Mae Jarrett,
the greatest rodeo queen
of her day.
Come on.
Come on!
[Rattling]
[Engines start]
Come on in.
[Horse neighs]
Got a lot more of these
when you're ready.
- Oh, no, thank you.
- Not a coffee drinker?
- Uh-uh.
- Hard to trust a person
who's not a coffee drinker.
- Oh...
This looks like
an old pinup photo.
- Mm. Maggie Mae was painted
on the nose of a b17
during the second world war.
Some of those old guys, they
came all the way from Chicago
just to meet her.
Do they do this sort of thing
a lot?
- Beg your pardon?
- Do they assign something
to somebody
who doesn't really know
what they're writing about?
- They expect us
to do the research.
- Listen, I've got go out
and start filling the tank
for the horses.
I'm going to be
right out by the barn.
So you can just look
all you want, ok.
And I'll be back in before I go down to the pasture.
You ok?
Ok.
[Truck approaching]
- Hi. Who are you?
- Natalie Travers.
And you are?
- Hungry.
What are you up to?
- I'm a writer.
- Yeah? What do you write?
- Articles.
- For...?
- Magazines and newspapers.
- Any I've heard of?
- I doubt it.
- Where's Jess?
- Uh, she's outside somewhere
by the barn.
I... I didn't get your name.
- Luella Suzanne Nichols.
I don't use that middle one.
It's too cute.
My friends call me Lulu.
I live here. Jess took me in
after my parents died.
[Door shuts]
[Groans]
- All right.
- I thought he was
a goner.
- Just keep him out of the green for about a week.
He'll be fine.
[Neighs]
[Sighs]
- That's my best rope horse.
I'm obliged to you, Sam.
- You'll get my bill.
- That's not a very friendly
thing to say.
- Yeah, well, you called a vet.
I came, and I did my job.
You looking for a friend, you’re barking up the wrong tree.
Go call somebody else.
- This is about Jess
and them wild horses.
- She's just trying
to do a good thing, Tom.
She's trying to fulfill
a promise.
- Now, those wild horses,
they get in my herd.
That's a blood line ruined.
- They're just looking
for water, Tom.
You could fix it
if you really wanted to.
- Sam, Jess is just as crazy
as her mother was.
It's not my problem.
She is not going to
drill on this land.
- I'll doctor your animals
because that's my job.
But I won't hear any harsh words about Jess or her mother.
You got that?!
- [Snickers]
If I was ten years younger,
I'd give you the what-for.
- If you were ten years younger,
your dad would be
kicking your behind.
- You just keep them horses
off my property.
- Yeah, yeah.
[Engine starts]
- Billy makes the chili
on Friday.
He keeps adding chili powder
every day
to kill the taste while
it's dying.
By today, it would be dead.
- [Whispers]
Stop it.
- Now I'm going to be dead.
- Where you staying, hon?
- [Sighs]
I was planning a round trip.
- Well, you're not tripping
anywhere today,
not 'til this is over.
You just stretch on out there.
I'm going to get you a blanket.
And you, miss cheery,
go get your homework.
- [Sighs]
- "To my loving husband
Charlie, always Maggie Mae"?
[Birds tweeting]
[Chickens clucking]
[Footsteps]
- Got an extra one here in case you get cold during the night.
- I don't... I don't want
to impose.
- Jess takes in strays
all the time.
She's got a dozen
old wild horses up there
she's trying to keep
from getting shot
by our rabid neighbor.
Oh, geez, I'm all out of paper.
You wouldn't happen
to have any,
being a writer and all,
would you?
- Uh-uh.
- How about a pen?
- Lulu, leave her alone.
I have a paper and pen
over on my desk.
Listen, we're going to have to haul the water
up to the horses right now.
It's going to take
a little while.
So, you just, you know,
wait here and relax,
make yourself comfortable, ok?
We'll be back
as soon as we can.
- You might need this.
Guess what I discovered?
That lady has a picture
of Maggie Mae in her car
just like this one.
- Hmm.
Writers do research.
These old rodeo pictures aren't
exactly classified documents.
- But this one says
"to my loving wife Charlie."
The one she has is from
Maggie Mae to Charlie.
- You should not have
taken this out of the book.
- I wonder what she's
really up to.
- You really don't
believe her, do you?
- Gut feeling, Jess.
All I know is
something tells me
she's not what she says she is.
- I don't know what
she's all about either,
but I do know she's
one sick puppy,
and she needs some help
right now.
- I say she's trouble.
- Drop it, please.
[Brakes squeal]
- Anybody home?!
- [Grunts]
- Oh...
Hey. That must be
your car out front.
Where's Jess?
- Uh, I'm not sure.
She'll be back soon.
- Oh.
Sam Nelson.
Hope I didn't scare you.
- Uh, no, no, no.
[Laughs] I'm probably
the one who's scary.
- No.
- I'm Natalie Travers.
- I don't remember seeing you
here before.
- Oh, this is my first time
here.
- Are you selling something?
- No.
[Strains]
No, it's nothing like that.
- Oh, you all right?
- I'll be fine.
It's just something I ate.
- Oh.
- Hey, looks like our visitor's
going to live.
Sally's chili.
- Oh...oh.
Well, I hope you feel
better than you think you look.
- Thank you.
- Sam's a vet.
He could take a look at you.
- Sure.
Um, I'd be happy...
- whoa, whoa.
Wait, you're just
a veterinarian?
- She's just a writer
doing research on Maggie Mae.
- Who do you write for?
- I...
Um...
- Freelancer?
- Freelance, that's right.
- What does that mean?
- Well, that would mean that she is broke and starving, right?
[Laughs]
- I don't think so.
Have you seen her car?
And those shoes?
- Lulu.
- Well, it's nice to know that freelancing pays.
Oh, Jess, here's
the lease agreement.
- What did his lawyer say?
- Oh, Tom's not going
to change his mind.
That agreement was written
when water rights
weren't even an issue.
I know that's bad news,
but you know what?
I'll water them tomorrow,
take my turn, all right.
- No, Sam, it's not
your problem.
I appreciate the offer,
but Lulu and I
will take care of the watering.
- Can't we just put them
in the corral
where we actually have water?
- That sure would make life a lot easier, wouldn't it, Jess?
- Hey! Come on.
Maggie Mae would not have that and you know it.
Neither will I.
We're going to honor those
horses the same way she did.
- Well, I'm going to
go out to the barn
and check on old buster.
He's limping.
Oh, it was nice meeting you.
- Would you like
something to eat?
- Ugh! No.
[Door shuts]
[Horse neighs]
[Door squeaks open]
- You know where I come from...
People say goodbye
face to face.
They don't leave a note
on the kitchen table.
I'm surprised you found
something to write with.
- I'm sorry. I didn't want
to wake anybody.
- Ah, where I come from,
people don't lie about
who they are
or what they do for a living.
They just kind of come out
and say what's on their mind.
We're obviously not
from the same place,
Ms. Natalie Travers.
- But where I come from
people don't...
- the guy in the picture here
with Maggie Mae,
Charlie Travers...
Recognize him, do you?
- Yes. He's my father.
Charles Everrett Travers.
- Figured it was
something like that.
Why did you come here?
- I don't know.
- They were married.
- See, my father was
a very distinguished judge,
and I just can't
imagine them together.
- Well, Maggie Mae always
talked about a Charlie Travers,
the only man she ever loved.
Guess she's not quite la-di-da enough for you to imagine.
- No, that's not what I meant.
My father was your father, too,
if what you're telling me
is true.
- If what I'm telling you
is true?
So now you're calling me a liar?You've got a lot of nerve...
no, I didn't want to...I didn't mean to insinuate that.
Maggie Mae could have had
somebody else in her life.
- Not very likely.
She went to her grave
in love with that man.
- Well, if they were so in love,then what happened?
- She ended it.
She said Charlie was destined
for greater things
than being married
to a rodeo queen.
So she sent him packing
and never told him about me.
- I just found out
about all of this.
Uh, daddy just died.
- Maggie Mae six months ago.
Get in the truck.
- Well, I really should...
- get in the truck.
[Door slams]
[Engine starts]
♪
I wanted you to see this
before they left for the day.
Horses were here
before we were.
And Maggie Mae used to say
we were the squatters.
- There aren't very many
of them.
- Yeah, well, there used to be.
Used to be big herds of them
running wild
all over this place here.
And some of them scattered,
you know.
They got caught and broke.
Make real good cow ponies.
And the land behind us
went blm.
That's when the water started
drying up,
and horses started
breaking down fences
all over this place just trying to get to the water.
People started shooting them,
and it was...
- shooting them?
They can do that?
- [Laughs]
People do it every day
all over this country.
I mean, for good reason
sometimes, you know,
because wild horses,
they can be pretty destructive.
And a thirsty wild horse,
my goodness,
they can just rip your ranch
to shreds.
[Sighs] But sometimes,
you know what,
people just shoot them
for sport.
- Well, there has to be laws.
- Yeah.
Legal or illegal, the horses
are still all dead.
You know, these... these guys
just showed up
on our leased land here
a little while ago.
There's no brands,
no earmarks, no nothing.
Sam says they're wild.
- Where we they before?
- Probably hanging on
the backside of the blm.
You know, this place is
probably stored
in one of their primitive
memory banks, you know,
and then they just
instinctively returned here
kind of in a feeling
that this was their home.
Problem is, their home
is all dried up now, too.
- Well, if you have a lease,why don't you just dig a well?
- I don't have the right.
Even if I did,
I don't have the money.
You know what,
this whole place
used to belong to Maggie Mae.
At one point in time,she sold it to old Hayden grove,
and he leased it back to her
for grazing rights,
and it was a fifty year lease for a really low sum of money,
of course by today's
standards anyway.
And then at some point it got handed down to his son,
old Tom, and now Tom really
wants me to break this lease
so he can turn around
and lease it to somebody else
for a lot of money.
- Well, why don't you just
hire an attorney
and sue him for drilling rights?
- It's a legal battle
that I would lose.
According to this lease,
all we've got is
surface water rights
and natural spring rights
in a land where there's no rain.
[Sighs] And all the Springs
are dried up.
- So you water them.
- Yeah, every day.
We haul the water up here,
and then see we run it down
to that old tub down there.
- Wow, that's commitment.
- I'm trying to keep
my mama's dream alive,
to give these horses a place
where they can live in peace
and run free, you know,
like their kind have
ever since the beginning.
[Horse whinnies]
[Sighs]
Maggie Mae was a dreamer.
And she had a really big heart.
Maybe knowing that
you could just accept it
that she and Charlie were...
she and Charles Everett Travers
were just two young fools
in love.
Maybe some day we'll just
both accept that.
[Engine revving]
- I still think there's
more to that woman
than she's letting on.
- Why did I let you
take psychology?
- It's just common horse sense.
- You're too suspicious.
- You know something
you're not telling me.
- Nothing you need to
be worrying about.
We've seen the last of her.
[Distant revving]
[Horse whinnies]
- There's only two of 'em.
Maybe we got lucky
and the rest of 'em left.
- That wouldn't be lucky,
and you know it, Lu.
- I don't see why not.
- Because it would upset Jess,and you know it.
They came for water
in the first place,
and they'll all be back.
- Just forget it.
- Oh, no, no.
It's something.
Come on, let's hear it.
- I'm starting to feel like
I'm next.
- Next? What are you
talking about?
- I'm stuck working
at the gas station with Jess.
Me and some idiot
like Tim ray Marcus
out of boredom's sake.
Watering these darn old horses for the rest of my life!
It's like my whole life
is being planned out for me.
- Whoa.
It's not really about
the horses then, is it?
How long has this
been building up?
- I don't know.
Just got a good look
around the other day.
I think it has to do
with those I-talian shoes.
- I'm not really following you here on that.
- That writer that's not really
a writer, Natalie Travers.
- Right, right, right, right.
- I mean, did you see her?
- I saw her.
- That blouse was silk,
you know.
- It was.
- And that car.
I bet her new shoes
cost more than my saddle.
- Better not have.
[Laughs]
- It's not funny, Sam.
It's not funny at all.
- You're right, you're right.
It's not funny.
Jealousy is not funny.
- I'm not jealous.
- Oh, yes you are.
- Well, what I'm saying is,
Sam, she...
she had choices in life.
Some of us are just stuck.
- So you're saying that
this life
doesn't give you the things,
the stuff,
like cars and shoes.
Well, you're probably right.
But there's more to life
than Italian shoes.
- You ever sorry
for the choices you made?
- I'd rather regret
something I did
than something I didn't do.
You know what I mean?
Come on. We're almost done here.
Was that really silk?
- They met the summer
your dad finished law school.
Got married in a fever
under new Mexico skies.
But his family
put the pressure on.
They had political ties.
They had it all lined up
for him.
Big law firm and all.
He came on out
to California alone
to cinch the job,
find a place to live.
- She divorced him?
- It just about killed him.
- And he never knew
about Jessie Mae?
- Oh, honey,
if there had been
any mention of a child,
your daddy would have moved
heaven and earth to find her.
You know how responsible
he was.
Maybe Maggie Mae moved on,
found somebody else.
- No, not according to Jessie.
- Parents don't always
tell their children everything.
You know that now.
- This conversation is over.
- Look, I'm your best friend,
right?
- Yes.
- Now, come here.
I want to show you something.
Check this out.
- What is it?
- [Sighs] Birth certificate,
new Mexico.
"Maggie Mae Jarrett, mother.
"Jessie Mae Jarrett,
child, and father.
And father."
- Yeah, John Doe.
- Precisely.
I want you to drop it.
- Well, if she's my sister,
then... then ethically
and morally
she is entitled to
half my father's estate.
- Boy, you really are
your father's daughter.
- I just want a definitive answer to the question of birth.
- Well, there's only one way
to find that out.
- [Sighs]
Yeah, I know. DNA.
- DNA takes two pieces
of the puzzle.
How you going to
pull that off?
- I'll figure something out.
- Hi.
- Well?
- "Well" what?
- Test results were today.
- Oh, yeah. I forgot to get 'em.
- Oh really?
I might just forget
how much I love you
and paddle your behind.
- [Laughs]
I passed 'em both.
- You did?
- Well, not with flying colors.
But I passed.
- Oh, you proud little peacock!
- I studied hard
for those grades.
- Yes, you did, and you should be proud of yourself.
I'm proud of you, honey.
I really am proud of you.
- [Laughs]
- Hey, you hungry?
- My belly is rock bottom
empty.
- Ok, I'm going to go get us
some burgers,
and we can eat 'em
on the way to water.
- Sounds like a winner.
- Close up the place
for me, hon.
- This early?- We're celebrating grades here!
- [Laughs]
- Now those horses that
Jess is trying to protect
are going to ruin our herds
and they're going to
tear up our pasture land
if we don't do something
about it.
Now, norm and Phil,
you know I'm right.
[Scattered mumbling]
We've got to stand together.
We've got to put pressure
on Jess
to get rid of those horses
once and for all.
- Tom, I told you before
my diner is not a meeting hall for hotheads.
Now, just keep it down,
or get out.
- Sally?
- Here we go...
- In fact, just stop this talk all together.
- Oh, no, not on my account.
Go right ahead, Tom.
Do your speech.
- I'm finished, Jess.
- Good. Then, it's my turn.
With your permission?
- Oh, have at him, girl.
- [Sighs]
I'm ashamed of you guys.
I expect it from Tom here
because he's trying to get me
to break my lease so he can
make some more money.
But he's just trying to use you.Can't you see that?
I mean, not one of you
has anything to gain
from those poor old horses being ground up into pet food.
- It's not just about the lease,
Jess.
- Tom, you weren't a good liar in high school,
and you're not a good liar
now.
- What's that supposed to mean?
- Inviting me
to the senior prom,
telling me I was
your only choice
when three other girls
had already turned you down.
[Laughter]
- [Laughs]
[Laughing and chattering]
- I need two burgers
to go, please.
- Wait, wait. I just want
to know... did you go?
- Where?
- To the prom with Tom?
- Well, heck yeah I went.
I was crazy about him then.
- [Laughs]
- I don't know why.
- Billy! Billy!
Two burgers to go!
- I haven't seen you
in those for some time.
- Yeah, I'm glad they still fit.
I am going riding.
My horse has become
more of an investment
than a pleasure,
and I just hope
I remember how.
- Oh, you'll be just fine.
It's just like riding a bicycle.You never forget.
- I remember you teaching me
how to ride a bike.
- You got so many scrapes
on your knees
I went through two boxes
of band-aids.
[Laughs] Your father almost had
a conniption fit.
[Laughs and sighs]
Have fun!
- Hey, Natalie.
Good to see you back.
- Hey, J.J.
It's good to be back.
Ah. Hi, Bobby.
- Good to see you.
Been a long time.
- Yeah.
- Tristan will be real happy
you're back.
Not that I haven't taken
good care of him myself.
- Oh no, I'm sure you take
excellent care of him.
- Do you want me to tack him
and warm him up for you?
- Yeah, please.
- All right.
- Ho.
[Sighs]
Hey.
You ever want to just run,
just take off like the wind?
Huh?
I'm sorry it's been
such a long time, old man.
I haven't had
my priorities straight.
All right, let's go.
[Clicks tongue]
[Clucking]
- Here you go.
- Hey.
- I thought you left
about an hour ago.
- Whoa. Old buster here
was hard to catch.
Maybe he feels the same way
I do about riding the fence.
You know, this was
your mama's promise.
- Well, if it bothers you
that much...
Here.
Feel that strong about it,
then I'll do it.
I'll do it myself.
- Don't you ever get upset?
Always nice and calm.
- Lulu, there's
a few things in life
you can only do properly
if your heart's in it.
- I should have kept
my mouth shut.
- No. No, you shouldn't have.
Lulu, look at me.
I do care about
what's in your heart.
I always want you to tell me,
ok?
And you're right.
It was my mama's promise.
- Darn it!
[Thud]
[Horse whinnies]
[Sighs]
- Ah!
[Gasps]
- Jess!
Jess, are you...
- I'm alive, I'm alive.
- This is all my fault.
Let's get you up.
- Oh, no. I can't.
Something's broke.
- I'll be back quick.
- Yeah, I'll be right here.
[Rooster crowing]
- Now this is going to be
real cold at first,
but you have to leave it on
for ten minutes, all right.
- Do you really think
she's your sister?
- When I was little
mom and Maggie Mae
talked about a guy
named Charlie.
- Well, at least now we know
he really existed.
- Yeah, well, you're
living proof
that he existed.
[Laughs]
- He never knew about me.
- Why not?
- They lived on a little ranch outside of Santa Fe,
and, you know, they're all
happy and in love and stuff.
And one day I guess
they just woke up,
realized they were
from two different worlds.
And so he...
He went on out to Los Angeles.
He was expecting Maggie Mae
to follow him.
- Yeah. Knowing Maggie Mae,
she'd have none of that.
- She told him she was
going to follow him.
[Sighs] You know, I grew up
my whole life
thinking Maggie Mae
wasn't afraid of anything.
But she was. She was...
She was afraid that one of them was always going to have to be
giving up too much.
You know, she didn't want it
to be him.
So, after he left,
she filed for divorce,
and then she found out
she was pregnant.
And then she couldn't
rodeo anymore.
So she came out, she got
as close as she dared get,
and just watched him from afar.
She was always
proud of him.
- She never told him
about you?
- No.
Guess she started to once,
you know, after I was born,
but, uh, by that time
she found out
that he was engaged to be married to Natalie's mama.
[Sniffs] And she didn't
want to cause him anymore pain.
- Ah, that's a tough one
for a young girl.
- You had to live with her decision all your life.
What does miss prissy pants
have to say about all this?
- Yeah, what does she say
about this?
- Hey, can we just drop it?
- Better get going.
Don't want to be late
for school.
Hope you feel better, Jess.
- Thanks, hon.
- Since when does she care
about being late for school?
- [Laughs]
- Look, I've got to
get out here.
But I'm going to be back soon,all right.
You stay put.
[Traffic sounds]
[Phones ringing]
[Muted conversations]
- Hey.
- Hello.
- I'm here to see
Natalie Travers. Is she in?
- Do you have an appointment?
- This is a family emergency.
- Family emergency?
- Natalie's sister
is sort of my mother.
- That would make you Lulu.
- You know her, Larry?
- I'll take it from here, Nance.
Well, you're exactly
as Nat described.
- Am I supposed to know you?
- Oh, no.
I'm Larry Griskin,
Nat's best and sometimes
only friend.
- You sound like Sam.
- The vet?
- She told you about Sam, too?
- I believe I detected a little
something-something there.
- I detected the same
something-something from Sam.
- So...why are you here?
- I really need to see her.
- Well, she's been coming
into work a little later
every other day,
and she's calling it getting her priorities straight.
- Well, I need to talk to her
about those priorities.
- Ok.
Well, you'll find her here.
There you go.
- Thanks.
- You're welcome.
Oh, Lulu, it's that way.
- Nice talking to you.
Do you know where I can find
Natalie Travers?
- Over there.
- Hey.
- Hey, can I help you?
- Yeah, do you know where
I can find Natalie Travers?
- Yeah, sure.
She's right out there.
She's really something, huh?
- Yeah, she is.
So, the way I see it is,
like each other or not,
you are sisters, so...
- half-sisters, maybe.
- Whoever came up with
that expression anyway?
- I mean, what does it mean?
The way I see it,
it's all or nothing.
I mean, Maggie Mae wasn't
my real grandmother.
Jess isn't my real mother.
Sam isn't really my brother,
but when push comes to shove,
real doesn't really matter.
You know what I mean?
Your daddy never even
knew about Jess.
You do.
Do you have anything to eat
that's not designer food?
- Does Jess know you're here?
- She'd kill me.
Please tell me you have
ice cream.
- No.
- Those shoes you wear,
they gave you away.
You're not a starving writer.
And they're way too sexy.
You could probably be cool
if you wanted to.
Jess wouldn't ask you
for anything,
but there is a way
you could help.
It takes a lot of work
to keep that ranch going,
and she's going to be in a cast for another six weeks.
Of course, we realized
you're basically incompetent
when it comes to hard work
and pretty much selfish.
- Wait a minute!
Incompetent and selfish?
You barely even know me!
- Well, from this point on,
that's your fault.
You can call me Lulu.
[Crickets chirping]
I stopped by the station.
Billy Joe said
everything's running smooth,
and you don't need to worry
about a thing.
Just get well.
Oh, he said he placed that fuel order you told him about.
- How was class today?
- Psychology 101.
Kind of a hands-on thing.
- You were in an awful big hurry to get out of here this morning.
- I didn't want to be late.
I had some studying
I had to do.
- Very admirable.
Do we need to talk?
- No.
- I know suspicious
when I see it, young lady.
[Silverware clinking]
[Horse neighs]
- Oh, Jess.
I truly wish that
you would stop
hopping around on that leg.
- Who's hopping?
I'm sitting.
Don't you have some animals
you can go doctor or something?
- I was talking to
a few of the boys
down at the diner today,
and they said that you
had a run-in with Tom grove,
and I heard it was a good one.[Laughs]
- It wasn't exactly
a run-in.
I talked,
and he just skedaddled.
- One of the horses went down.
I found her in the hollow just on the other side of the Ridge.
- Went down or was shot?
- Natural causes.
- Yeah, those poor old horses.
They don't have anybody to
talk for 'em but me,
and I'm laid up here
like one wing pigeon.
- Well, I can keep an eye
on things.
I mean, it's the least
I can do.
- Don't you get started on
how much you owe me, young man.
- Oh, I wouldn't dream of it.
- Good.
[Slapping gloves]
- Lulu didn't show up
for school yesterday.
- I knew something was
going on with her.
You have any ideas?
- She's got a lot going on
in her head these days.
We've got to start thinking
about Lulu's future.
That's what's eating on her.
[Fountain bubbling]
- Abygail.
- Your father always
sought the truth.
Oh, he would be
very proud of you.
And so am I.
[Engine revving]
[Crickets chirping]
- You staying for dinner?
- What are we having?
- My famous stew.
- Ah, duty calls.
Chip's on vacation,
and I've got to
clean the clinic.
So...
[smack]
- No stew, no bread.
- You, young lady,
got to stay off that foot.
It's going to swell,
and you're going to have to
hobble around
the rest of your life,
all right?
[Knocking]
I'll get it.
- Fine.
Because my vet says
don't be hobbling on my leg.
- Hello, Sam.
- Hey, yourself.
- Hey, going to keep me
in suspense here,
or are you going to
tell me...
- it's, uh...
- Hi.
- Hello.
- So, it's a viable offer.
I... I... I've never written
a book before,
but there's a first time
for everything, right?
- Yeah.
- Don't you have
something to do?
Somewhere to go?
- Oh. No.
- Then take off your hat.
- So I was also thinking
I could stay in town,
but I think it would be
more efficient
if I stayed here.
[Unlatches]
- Hi.
- Hi. Lulu, you're just
in time to vote.
I think it's tied.
- There is no tie.
Sam does not live here.
He doesn't get to vote.
- Hey.
- Let me explain.
I sincerely want to write a book about Maggie Mae,
and I think it would just be
a lot faster
if I could stay here and do the research every day.
And Jess would get all
the credit and all the money,
and I could do chores
to pay for my room and board.
- [Laughs]
- So what do you say?
- Uh...we will do it
on a trial basis.
- Come on.
I'll show you the spare room.
- What?
[Grazing sounds]
[Truck approaching]
[Engine shuts off]
- Oh, what time did we
have breakfast?
- A little past five.
There's a five in the morning
and five in the evening.
This is the morning.
- Oh, don't be such
a smarty pants.
- Connect the hose here, ok.
Then the water runs downhill
to that trough.
- How many times a day
do you have to do this?
- Depends on the number of
horses and evaporation.
If we had another trough,
we could skip a day.
Truth is, Jess would come here every day anyway
just to check on them...
that's the way she is.
- Yeah, she's real committed
to these horses.
- This watering just takes a big bite out of life, that's all.
But then have someone to do
your work for you, don't you?
- Don't even go there, Lulu.
You know I like pointy shoes.
I heard him saying something
about a spring?
- Oh, that's long dried up.- Ok, wait, where is the spring?
- Out there somewhere.
Besides, it doesn't matter.
Tom won't let us
drill on his land anyway.
- Let me figure this out.
- You figure this out,
and I'll...
I'll...
- You'll...
- I'll be really, really
grateful.
- Can't you just wait
for Lulu?
- She's got classes.
It can't wait.
- Well, how about if
I call Sam?
- He's got a business
to run.
I don't want to bother him.
You want to take me or not?
- Well, can I at least
drive my car?
- I can't bend my leg.
- Is yours automatic?
- Three on the tree, chickadee.
- What?
[Gears grinding]
Well, that wasn't bad.
Only stripped the gear
four times.
- I truly am sorry,
miss Jess.
I tried to pay for
the fuel delivery,
but there wasn't enough
money in the register.
- It's ok. It's really ok.
You know, I called the company.
They're going to have that guy stop on his way back down, ok.
[Change jingles]
So, I want you to take this,
tell that guy just to keep
pumping 'til it runs out, ok.
- Yes, ma'am.
- Now, listen, Billy Joe.
You've been doing
a really good job here,
really good job.
I want you to take
ten out for yourself.
- Thank you, miss Jess.
Ma'am.
[Screwing lid]
- He'd be living in the woods
if he didn't have this job.
He's such a hard worker,
and, boy, he's as honest
as the day is long.
He's a little slow
on the uptake.
- You know, I have some money.
- I don't want your money.- No, it would just be a loan.
- What do you really
want from me?
- I don't know what you mean.
I just offered to loan you
some money.
- You know what I mean.
- You know what, Jess.
I don't want anything from you.
Really.
- [Sniffs]
Well, then if you really want
to do something for me
you could cast those
legal eyes of yours
on my old lease and tell me
exactly what's in it
for your room and board.
- You got it.
[Sighs]
So where are we going?
- Riding.
[Laughs]
Does it matter?
- No, I guess not.
- So, Jess says you were able
to take a look
at the lease agreement.
- Yeah, I did, I did.
And what I gathered
from the document
is that whatever existed
when the lease was signed
still applies.
So basically it's
a grandfather clause.
However, the lease
is very specific
about not drilling a new well.
- So if we can find
that old spring
and make it productive,
then we won't be breaking
the agreement?
- Correct. If we can
find the well.
The question is
how are we going to do that?
- Oh, that's easy.
I know where it is.
- [Sighs]
It's so beautiful here.
So open and free.
- I can just see Maggie Mae
out working cattle
in that big old hat of hers.
[Laughs]
Oh, that must have been
good times for all them.
For Jess, it's been
nothing but rough times.
What little she had
she shared with my mom and me
and now Lulu.
She just hunkered down here,
put one foot
in front of the other
praying that good times were coming around the corner.
- Are there good times?
- [Sighs]
I honestly don't see how.
It's Lulu that worries me.
It's a whole big world
out there,
and she wants a shot at it.
- She deserves a chance
to make her own choices
about her life.
- She's only 18.
There's plenty of time
for that.
- By the time I was 18,
my whole life was
mapped out in front of me.
- Is that a good thing?
- Let me put it to you
this way:
It's what brought me here.
♪
- I didn't know phd stood for
post hole digger.
This is the pits.
[Rattling]
- Are you sure we are going
to find
a spring down here somewhere?
- I don't know.
- All I know is that
this all seems to mean
something to her.
- I'm not buying it.
She's got an ulterior motive.
- She's out there digging
her behind off seriously.
I know it doesn't
make any sense
a woman like that
digging in the dirt
trying to fit in,
but you've got to admit
she's helping out.
- What? You think I'm terrible because I'm not cozying up...
- no, no.
That's not what I said, Jess.
- Well, try walking in my boots for a minute here.
- We will never know
what would have happened
if Charlie and Maggie Mae
would have stayed together.
But it didn't, ok.
I know your life has been
pretty hard.
And Natalie's looks like
a piece of cake from here.
- Oh, what are you saying?
I'm jealous?
- No, that's not what
I'm saying.
- Well, then what?
- Say she's making
a lot of effort. That's all.
Just that's what I want you
to think about, ok.
[Sighs]
Look, I'm tired.
I had a long day.
I gotta go.
Um, can I help you?
- No, no. I just want to sit.
Thank you.
- Can...
Thanks.
Goodnight.
- [Sighs]
[Chattering]
- I bought those on sale.
- Oh my gosh. I...
- hang on. I think these
might fit you better.
- I'm so embarrassed.
- I'm sure my foot is probably a lot wider than yours.
- No, no, no, no.
- Really!
I knew these were too tight
when I bought 'em.
- Why did you get 'em?
I'm sure they cost a fortune.
- Oh, the theory was that they’d make me feel better at the time.
I guess that's why I dragged
them all the way out here,
kind of a security blanket.
- They feel great.
- I'll make a deal with you.
If your boots fit me,
we'll trade.
Do you have another pair of
boots?
- Yeah.
- So we have a deal.
- Deal.
- Excellent.
- Do you think those are
a little out of your league?
- No, I don't.
I know what I want out of life,
and I'm gonna get it.
And it's not just
expensive shoes either.
- Well, when I was 18,
I did everything everybody
expected of me.
I wish I'd had her spunk.
- Morning!
I was told I could
find you here.
- Well, good morning
to you, sir.
- [Laughs]
Sir? Awful formal.
Ma'am.
- [Laughs]
Hello, Sam.
- That's better.
Looks like you got roped
into some watering chores.
- Ah, I volunteered.
- [Laughs]
First rule in ranching:
Never volunteer for anything.
- Oh, I guess I missed
that rule.
- [Laughs]
Look!
You got boots.
- Yeah, you noticed.
Lulu and I did some trading.
- [Laughs]
- They don't seem so wild
right now.
- I wouldn't want
to ride one.
- [Sighs]
- [Laughs]
So...how's the writing going?
- Oh, well, it's all there
in black and white.
In living color actually.
Yeah, you know, I just...
I didn't see it.
I didn't understand.
Maggie Mae was
a remarkable woman.
And all this because of
some simple curiosity
about her being married
to my dad.
- He was a big deal
in her life.
- What if they'd just
taken the chance?
What if Maggie Mae and Charlie
had just said
"to heck with everybody else"
and stuck together?
- Well, you wouldn't be here
talking to me right now.
- [Laughs]
That's true.
- So...what about you?
Would you have taken
that chance?
[Knocking]
- Hey.
- Can I talk to you
for a second?
- Oh no, I'm all out of shoes.- Now I'm all out of boots.
- [Laughs]
What's up?
- [Sighs]
There's something
I thought you should know.
I watch you struggle with this night after night.
Jess used to write
for the newspaper years ago.
She even started a book
about Maggie Mae,
but she didn't have the courage
to send it to anyone.
I think that's why she's
kind of funny about all this
because you're doing
the very thing
that she always wanted to.
- [Laughs] Yeah, except
I'm not doing the very thing.
I mean, you know,
I can write legal briefs
and stuff like that, but when
it comes to creative writing
I... I... I... suck.
- [Snickers]
- Wow.
- And then there's Sam.
- What about Sam?
- Well, I think he's...
You know.
- No, I don't know.
- I think he's falling for you.
History repeats itself.
- What?
- Your father and Maggie Mae?
- [Sighs]
Oh...
- I want you to see this
for yourself.
- Yeah.
- [Laughs]
[Laughs]
She's digging her behind off.
[Horse approaching]
- Tom.
- Oh no.
- You there.
Stop what you're doing.
Ho! There's to be no drilling
as part of the agreement.
- Relax, Tom.
We're not drilling.
You can see that.
- We've been over this
time and time again.
You and your darn horses
are out of here.
You best be getting yourself
a lawyer.
- Allow me to introduce
myself.
I'm Natalie Travers.
I am Jess's attorney
Bennett, Martin and Jordan
in Los Angeles.
Perhaps, you've heard of us.
We're the second largest
firm in the state.
Now, we have more than enough
proof
that there was once
a spring here.
So based on the grandfather
clause of the lease...
page 12, section 8...
what was there then
is part of the deal now.
- You know where I stand.
- Yeah, you're standing
on leased land.
You're trespassing.
And if you do it again,
I'll see to it
you spend 30 days
in county jail.
- [Snickers]
- Jess!
Ya! Ya!
- Can't you find anything better than peanut butter and jelly?
- Oh, I haven't had
one of these in years.
This is delicious.
- Can I make you
a cup of tea?
- Oh, I'll have coffee.
- Coffee.
- Uh-huh.
- We have corrupted you
all the way to coffee, have we?
- Well, does this mean that
you trust me now?
- I didn't say that.
- [Laughs]
Listen, Jess,
I have a confession.
- I'm listening.
- Well, I really did talk to
a very successful publisher.
He's a former client of mine,
and he's very excited
about the book.
And I think we can get
a deal, but...
- But? That's the hardest part.
I mean, that's usually
when people give up.
What do you mean "but"?
- Well, I tried,
but I'm not a writer.
And I don't want to
abandon the project
and just go home.
And I... I'm just a lawyer.
- You're a darn good one.
I can still see Tom's face,
thank you very much.
- I've got to tell you
the truth about something.
I used the book
as an excuse
to come back here.
I have a lot of things
to work out in here
and in here.
Anyway, I think we can
get this book published.
I really do,
but I can't write it.
A little birdie tells me
that you can.
So...do we have a deal?
I'll make you one of these.
- Oh, yeah, now we've got
a deal.
- [Laughs]
[Groans]
Oh.
Both: [Sighing]
- Oh, and to think I broke all ten fingernails for nothing.
- You know, I'm starting
to think you might not
be so bad after all.
- Yeah, the jury is still
out on you
and this water project.
- Sam thinks it's
going to work.
It'd better work.
We can't keep on hauling
this water forever.
- Well, Sam's an optimist.
- He tries to see
the positive side of things.
He hasn't had
an easy life, you know.
His dad was killed
when he was young,
and he and his mom moved in
with Maggie Mae and Jess.
- Yeah, he's quite the guy.
- Know what I said
the other night about Sam?
Jess said it, too.
She said, "well,
here we go all over again
with the two of them."
- They seem to be settling in,not drifting away.
- Settling in is good.
- We all need it.
- I'm getting to like this.
I know where to find you
in the morning.
[Laughs]
- Don't get used to it.
- [Laughs]Oh, you're not a morning person?
- This can't last forever.
This isn't my world, remember?
- Hey, hey, hey, hey.
What was that?
Where did that come from?
- [Sighs]
Reality. Reality is where...
- hey, hey, hey. You know,
hey, turn around. Look at me.
- [Sighs]
- You told me when you
were young your mom died
and you never got to know her.
Now your dad is gone.
You're searching for something.
You think just maybe
you're going to find it here.
Don't you see that?
You could have Jess
as a sister.
- But it would never work
for us.
- Know what? Just have
a little bit of faith.
That's what Maggie Mae
and Charlie didn't have.
We could have something
different.
Something like this.
[Kissing sounds]
You're not going to
believe this,
but everything's going
to be just fine.
And it's not going to be because you made it happen, Natalie.
Don't try to control it.
Just let it happen.
[Engine starts]
[Fluttering]
[Tapping]
- Yeah, I feel like
such a worthless lute.
You guys going off
to do all the work,
and I'm staying home.
- Well, you have a book
to write.
- Well, that's not work.
- [Laughs]
It is if you don't know how.
Right, Natalie?
- Got that right.
- I was just checking
on the horses.
They're gone.
[Car doors slamming]
- They were settled in
yesterday.
- Well, something obviously
scared them off I think.
- Tom grove.- The fence might be down again.
- Tell you what, if it was
Tom grove, I'm going to...
- We've got to get
to the dig site.
Hurry up!
[Sighs]
- Oh!
I don't believe it.
You hit water.
- We really did it.
- See, all you need is
a little bit of faith.
[Laughs]
- And a lot of digging.
[Lapping sounds]
- What's your friend
doing re?
- Um, I don't know.
Law firm business, I guess.
- Cowboy boots, dirty jeans.
Ooh, you're turning into
a real country girl.
- Only on the outside.
- [Sighs]
I tried to reach your cell.
- I can't get any signal
out here.
- Is that her boyfriend?
- No, he's just a friend
from work.
- What's he doing here?
- Law business.
- So, I drove up
to give you this.
It's all there.
- What does it say?
- Open it and see.
- Oh, come on, just tell me
what it says.
- It should be a surprise.
Plus, I gotta go.
I met this woman
who's into sailing.
We're spending the weekend
in Catalina.
- [Laughs]
- Oh, and I took care
of that thing
you wanted me to take care of
from your note.
- Yeah, thank you.
- No problem.
- Thanks for everything.
- Nice seeing you all.
And take care of my pal here.
- Come on. Let's go
get something to eat.
[Engine starts]
- Yeah, peachy.
- Legal stuff?
- Just some unfinished business
I have to bring closure.
- Natalie, I...
- yeah.
- I bet... I better get back
to the clinic.
All right.
[Engine starts]
[Clucking]
- I don't see why
you have to go.
- There are several reasons,
one of them being that
I have a whole other life.
- It isn't a life.
It's an existence.
What about Sam?
- Tell Sam I said goodbye.
- "Goodbye"? That's it?
The man is twitterpated
over you.
You like him, too.
I can tell.
- Well, we come from
two different worlds.
You're the one
who said that.
- I didn't say it
exactly like that.
I just don't want Sam
to get hurt, that's all.
- Neither do I.
That's why I have to leave.
I'm sorry, Lulu.
- So am I.
- [Sighs]
Thank you.
Thank you for everything.
What's this?
- I did something sneaky.
I'm not proud of it,
but it's done.
- DNA results?
- Yours and mine.
- What's it say?
- I don't know.
I didn't open it.
- You're not even
a little bit curious?
- I was.
But somehow that doesn't seem
to matter very much
anymore.
Thank you.
- Get out here
before I start blubbering.
[Engine revs]
Here.
- I can't believe this.
- What?
- It's a bank draft.
For five... five hundred
thousand dollars?
I think I'm going to faint.
- Well, don't do that
because I can't pick you up.
- Why do you think
she did it?
- Read the last paragraph.
- She is your sister.
- Apparently so.
[Tapping]
- Hey, come on in.
- We need to talk about your
brief on the Rosenthal case.
- Yeah, I finished it.
- Oh, I read it.
It's very good.
- Thank you.
- Unfortunately, the depositions are from
the Levinson versus Connor case.
- You're kidding?
- No.
- Let's face it, Nat.
Your mind's not
into your work.
I don't believe your heart
is either.
- I have no idea
what you're talking about.
- You're in love.
- You're nuts.
- Yeah, well, I know love
when I see it.
I've been there...Once.
- All right, I'll straighten out the brief thing.
- Ok. And why don't you try to straighten out
the other love thing too.
- Get out.
[Sighs]
[Horses fluttering]
- [Sighs]
[Engine starts]
- So how's your sister?
- She's great.
Well, she was this morning.
By tonight,
she could hate me.
- [Laughs]
- Relatives, you know.
- See you later, old fella.
♪
- Lulu gave me your goodbye.
I don't ever want there
to be a goodbye between us.
- Ever?
- Ever.
- Me neither.
♪