♪♪
[man]
If she died in
a boating accident,
why hasn't the boat
been found?
Well, could be
the boat sunk.
Could be she's not
in the lake.
Could be it come up
and they didn't find it.
Hey, there's no shortage
of possibilities here.
[music playing,
people chattering]
You Tony Carbo?
Nat Leming,
Minneapolis Star.
Hi.Whatever he's drinking,
and-- and hit this.All right.
Scotch.Sure, I'll be right back.
I was wondering what you could
tell me about John Waylan.
The son-of-a-gun
never told me a thing.
I asked him if there were
skeletons buried.
He said no.
You don't think,
you know, real skeletons.
Statement for the press.
Quote.
"Mr. John Waylan
had his dark secrets
"and he had his own way
of dealing with them.
"And in the end,
it destroyed him.
Unless he was already
destroyed."
[cheering and applause]
[man]
A young man whose integrity,
whose earnest desire to serve
the people of this state
makes him a candidate we can
all be proud to get in back of.
When you're working
for John Waylan,
you're working
for yourselves.
You're working for
your children.
Politics, as usual,
has failed long enough.
[applause]
A fresh approach
is what is needed.
And John Waylan is the fresh
face that we can count on.
[cheering and applause]
Thank you very much,
ladies and gentlemen.
I cannot begin to tell
you how grateful I am
for such a wonderful turnout
and such a warm reception.
[cheering and applause]
These are hard times
in Minnesota.
We have serious
problems with our economy,
crime, our schools.
Now, my honorable
opponent, Mr. Chandler,
would have you believe
that he and Washington
can make these
problems disappear.
Just like... magic.
[cheering and applause]
Now, I happen to know a little
something about magic.
But you don't want tricks,
do you?
[crowd]
No!
Real problems
needs real solutions.
Can I tell you something?
What I can do, and what I
will do as your next Senator,
is make this state reappear as
the great and better place
we all want it to be.
That's the magic
worth doing, isn't it?
[cheering and applause]
Yeah, hi, I'm looking
for a Richard Thinbill.
Hey, over here.
I didn't tell anybody
your name, but I got
to tell you, man,
I got a hard time
believing this story.
You believe
whatever you want, man,
I'm telling you the truth.
He was at the massacre?
I did three years on account
of what happened at Son My.
I'm telling you,
man, he was there.
Look, there had
to be records
of who was in
the platoon, right?
Yeah, well, maybe he
doctored the records,
if you know what
I'm saying.
Or maybe they
didn't need any more men
to court martial,
I don't know.
Decisions like this,
they're made up here,
you know what I'm saying?
And no one followed up?
Nobody knew his name, man.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
You didn't know his name?
Nobody wanted to know
anybody's name.
We knew what we called
each other, that's all.
I was Face,
the Lieutenant was Spud,
there was Boots,
there was-- whatever.
He was always doing,
like, tricks,
you know, like,
magic stuff with his hands.
Yeah, we called him
Sorcerer.
Folks, I have known Johnny
since I can't remember when.
Mm-hmm, since people
called me Johnny.
[laughter]
When did I first meet him?
I think he was ten years old.
And he did that
flower trick then.
A little better then,
I hope.
No political messages,
I recall.
Speaking of which, I have
a perfectly nonpolitical message
for the two of you.
My son's got this
beautiful old cottage
up on the Lake of the Woods
not far from ours.
As soon as the election
is over, why don't you--
Oh, no, no, no, Rebecca.
Are we talking a cottage
in the woods?
Yes.Mm-hmm.
And it's where you take
the phone off the hook?
[Rebecca]
Mm-hmm.
And you lie
in front of the fire?
What do you do all day?
Just sleep and swim?
And make love?
Who'd want to do that?
We'll take it.
This better not be
another campaign promise.
No telephone.
Tony, you old outlaw,
come with us.
We'll have a drink.
The night is young.
I've got to go over
some stuff with John.
Claude's buying and they
need their sleep.
Go.
Looks like
a good campaign.
Thank you.
[together]
Good night.
Mr. Waylan?
Nat Leming,
Minneapolis Star.
If I could talk to
you for one minute.Look, I'm sorry,
you had the whole
evening.
Call Tony Carbo
in the morning.
He'll set something
up for you.
It's about Son My.
[sighs]
I don't know where you
came up with this garbage.
Hey, hey, I just wanted
a statement.
The army has records.
You check them.
You'll see where I was.
Okay, all right,
I'll do that.
Now, off the record,
if you ever come up to me
with this crap again,
I will rip your face off.
Ladies and gentlemen,
we all know that two solids
can't occupy the same space
at the same time.
I'm only in the sixth grade
and I know that already.
Now, I ask you to watch
the billiard ball in my hand.
Solid.
Then I ask you,
how can it also be...
[blows]
...a ping-pong ball?
It's not bad.
Is that it?
Actually, I've got
two more tricks.
In that case,
let me get a refill.
[Kathy]
John?
What's the matter?
I, um...
I don't know what
I'd do without you.
Kathy,
I need you so much.
Sorrow, it seems to me,
may be the true absolute.
John grieved for Kathy.
She was his world.
They could have been
so happy together.
I'm no psychiatrist,
but if you ask me,
politicians in general
are pretty insecure.
So, we go public.
We're performers.
We get up on stage,
and we sing and dance
and do our little show.
Anything to please the folks.
Anything for applause.
[applause]
It's like the old
good news/bad news joke.
The good news is, you're here,
you're working, that's great.
So, you think your hubby's
gonna be a good senator?
Yes, I do.
I do.
Well, you're right.
You want to know why?
I'll tell you why.
Because he doesn't
like to compromise.
[scoffs]
He says one thing upstate,
he says another thing
in the city.
You don't call
that compromise?
It's eating him up.
Eats him up is good.
That means he has principles
but he does what he has to.
Thank you very much.
[Tony]
The lad's got
a certain magic.
He knows the trick
is to get elected.
[Kathy]
At any cost?
He wants this, Kathy.
He wants this
real bad.
Scary, isn't it?
When someone wants
something that bad.
They were under pressure
for a long time.
Maybe she just went to
the boat to get away from it
for a couple of hours
and got lost.
Or maybe she found herself,
and just kept on going.
[man]
Stars on the Horizon.
Well, I'd say this one
goes on the mantle.
Kathy's out buying
a frame right now.
Here, take it.
If I look at this
one more time, I'm gonna
become unbearable.
Oh, let's look into
the future a minute, John.
"An attractive candidate
with unlimited potential."
Does that sound vaguely...Mm-mm, no, no.
I don't think
we should say it?Presidential?
I don't think we
should say...
[cheering and applause]
You've got the polls?
John in a walk?
A walk? A backstroke!
We're 22 points ahead,
gentlemen.
[cheering and applause]
Yeah!
Ha-ha.
[thunder rumbling]
I thought we had a deal.
No secrets.
You were gonna
level with me.
Front page photograph.
You think your little
massacre in Vietnam
is gonna be
a campaign issue?
Is it true?
What?
The things in the paper.
Things?
About you.
The massacre.
You know what
I'm talking about.
Everything's true.
Everything's not true.
Just hang in there, okay?
I'm your wife.
Right.
So?
So... nothing.
[woman on TV]
What we're seeing
throughout the country
is a great deal of very
sweeping change.
Sweeping incumbents out
but just as emphatically
sweeping new faces in.
Some of this is unexpected,
or at least the extent of it.
But undoubtedly the biggest
shocker of the night
isn't even a shocker.
In the Minnesota Senate race,
John Waylan,
the odds-on favorite,
plummeted in the polls
with the revelation
of his role
in the infamous
Son My massacre.
Early returns indicate
that Waylan
may not even carry
his own home district.
[cheering and applause]
Ladies and gentlemen.
My friends.
All of you who worked so hard.
It's been one heck
of a ride, hasn't it?
[cheering and applause]
Sometimes it was hard to
keep going, to keep dreaming.
But I always knew
I had your support.
I always knew you shared with
me the dream of a new start,
a fresh beginning
for a brilliant future.
A... a brilliant future.
I can't tell you how much
it means to know
that you gave me
your faith, your trust.
You gave me your love.
It is love,
isn't it?
I'm so...
I am so...
[grunting]
Stay there!
Just stay there!
Are you afraid of me?
Is that it?No!
You think I kill children,
that's why you're
afraid of me?
No!Oh, Kathy. I love you.
You know I love you.
I love you so much!
I don't want to lose you.
[sobbing]
It was such
a long time ago.
All I want to know is
one thing, Cowboy.
How come
you didn't tell me?
For heaven's sakes, Tony.
No, I mean that.
We're friends.
Friends tell each other.
It's simple.
You want to play Russian
roulette with the truth,
Senator,
that's your business.
I just want to know why
you had to deal me in.
Tony.No.
This isn't doing any good--
No, no, no.
No problem.
I would have
thought of something.
Wait a minute,
wait a minute, I got it.
It's coming to me...
a whole new spiel
that will turn this thing
and make it work for us.
"A village is a terrible
thing to waste."
Tony!You like it?
You can have it, the next
time you run for office.
Is there anything
that I can do?
Pat...
I can't believe he never
said anything about this.
I'll leave the keys for
the cottage in your mailbox.
You'll need
somewhere to go.
[sighs]
We've lost everything.
Not everything.
We have each other.
I'm getting a beer.
You want anything?
Sure. Where are the fish?
Fish.
It's not my calling,
I guess.
[phone ringing]
[sighs]
I could stay
here forever.
Forever?
Forever.
Okay... you can get a job
with one of those fancy
law firms in Minneapolis,
and we'll get
a cheap house.
No, we'll rent.
That way, we can
pay off some debts,
and in a year
or two we'll...
we'll jump on
a plane to Verona,
or wherever else
we want to go.
And we'll... and we'll
be happy together
and we'll do all the wonderful
things we've never done.
We'll do it.
We'll go out
and make it happen.
Verona, huh?
Okay, let's do it.
You promise?
Absolutely.
What about babies?
Especially that.
I might be too old.
No, you're not.I'm 38.
No sweat.
We'll have 38 babies.
Hire a bus in Verona.
You think so?
For sure.
I promise.
This stupid thing
we've got to get through.
Stupid?
I didn't mean...
Of course not.
John, I don't always
use the right words,
but all I mean is, that
there's this man who I love,
this wonderful man, and I
just want him to be happy,
and that's all
I care about.
Kathy.
Come here, please.
Happy.
Nothing else.
There were flies everywhere.
They made a sound
like tracers.
Moving past.
Big flies.
Like the blue flies back home
but they didn't
have any color.
Sometimes you couldn't
see them.
Just the sound
and the movement.
The movement of the sound.
Whenever I think of the 'Nam,
I think of the flies.
[knocking]Come on in.
What do you mean you
weren't discriminating,
Private Thinbill?
[woman]
That's all there is.
I didn't discriminate
against the individuals
in the village, sir.
They were all the enemy.
All the enemy was
to be destroyed.
[man] So you killed men, women and...
[video fast forwarding]
I remember Sorcerer, he was
trying to hold Boots' lungs
on the inside,
and I was on the radio,
and that's when
the lieutenant said
we was gonna waste Son My.
[clears throat]
Killed every one of them.
Every one.
The lieutenant.
Me.
Weatherby.
The Sorcerer
and all the others.
And we just left 'em there.
Left 'em for the flies.
Where are you?
Hey!
[laughter]
Amazing, the things
you find down there.
Oh, really?Yes.
It's amazing what
you find up here.
I have a secret to tell you.Okay.
Come below.
[Kathy laughing]
The only thing
I haven't figured out,
besides from how we make
38 babies in Verona,
is how we pay
for the tour bus.
You serious?
No. But I can be.
[both chuckle]
Credit cards.
Oh, that's good.
I like that, very creative.
Of course, they cut them
off after a while.
Mmm.
I know.
I bet you have some
campaign money left over.
Sorry. Bad joke.
It's all right.
No, really, I'm sorry.
It was just a joke.
It was a good one.
John...It's clever. Very clever.
All right, stop it.
What?
I admire your quick wit.
I said stop!
Well?
We're stopped.
What now?
That's what
I'd like to know.
Meaning?
Meaning we can't
go on like this.
There was an election.
You lost, it's over.
We've got to move
on with our lives.
Just put things
behind us?
Yes. Exactly.
I know it's difficult,
but sometimes these things--
These things have
a way of working out.
That's not...Maybe even for the better.
Yes.Oh, good.
Ever since the election,
I've been waiting
to find out why it
was such a good thing
I got my butt handed
to me like that.
Maybe now,
you'll tell me.
Maybe it wasn't good for you,
John, but it was good for us.
Okay.
Go on, you're on a roll.
You haven't noticed the way
we're moving apart?
Did you happen to notice
we were in the middle
of a political campaign?
What did you expect?
People's attentions
drift off.
We didn't drift, John.
Continents drift.
People move apart.
I want you to be
yourself again.
About whom we've heard
so much lately.
Then maybe we can get
back to who we were.
Well, I guess my sister
was so in love with him
that she couldn't even see what
was happening all around her.
Like this pixie dust.
Sprinkle a little love,
and you end up fooling yourself.
Claude.Hmm?
Hey!
John! Kathy!Hi!
Hi.
What a beautiful
day for a walk.
Yes, it is.
We went for a swim and...
Glad you did.
Would you like
some iced tea or--
I'd love some.Johnny.
What's the matter with him?
He's so distant.
I mean, measured in feet,
yards and miles sometimes.
Does he talk
to you about it?
Which "it"?
The election?
Vietnam?
Either.No.
He's been that way
since his father died.
Come sit down.
[sighs]
[applause]
Good evening,
ladies and gentlemen.
I am Johnny Waylan,
the man who knows.
Thank you. Thank you.
[applause]
[barn door opening]
What are you doing?
I was just...
I just was...
What you better just is
just mind your own business.
It ain't
a perfect world, son.
You got those gizmos,
those tricks.
What I got...
Well, everybody's got
his own way.
Wouldn't you say
that's about fair?
Dad?
When I get things set up,
will you come see the show?
Show me a politician, and I'll
show you an unhappy childhood.
Same for magicians.
He actually thought
of himself as Sorcerer.
That's how it seemed to me.
Kathy was his
main audience.
I don't know how she
put up with it.
I guess she hoped
that he would pull off
a real miracle some day.
Can I ask you
a question?
Always.
Why didn't you talk
to Claude and Rebecca?
You know the answer
to that.
Well, John, it's been
almost two weeks now.
You're gonna have to talk
to somebody sometime.
You may as well
start with them.
They've always been
on your side.
No one's on my side.
What do you want, John?
What do you want
people to say?
Do you want 'em to
say it was nothing?
It was trivial?
Just a little mistake?
They can't do that.
They can put it aside.
They can forget
about it, but...
those that don't, they'll
just drop out of our lives.
And we'll move on.
That's all.
What about you?
Can I?
I don't know.
But I need your help.
I need you to help me
understand.
I just want to be
part of your life.
Don't shut me out.
All right, ladies,
that was great.
Thanks a lot.
See you on Thursday.
[applause]
Hi. How you doing?
Look, please.
I just want to ask you
a couple of questions, okay?
A couple of
simple questions.
Look, I told you I don't
want to talk to you.
Okay, but you know where
they went, right?
Oh, come on,
you're her sister.
Of course you know
where they went.
Hey, look, I'm not trying
to hurt anybody here.
I'm just trying
to tell a story.
Leave them alone.Hey, he's a public figure.
Yeah, well, not anymore,
thanks to you.
What more do you want?I want what happens after.
Another story.
Maybe even a better one.
Well, that's not a story.
That's an autopsy.
Thank you, thank you.
Silence please.
Where are you going?
I'm out of eggs.
I'm gonna run into town.
It's not much of a town.
Could you use
a little company?
You're sure
you want to do this?
"Sooner or later you're
gonna have to face people.
Might as well start
with the eggs."
That's a quote.
More or less.
[Mr. Waylan]
I've spent enough
money on him already!
[Mrs. Waylan]
We have to get him
something, just once.
Can't you do
something for him?
[Mr. Waylan]
He's got enough of
that stupid stuff.
What do I have to
give him more for?
[Mrs. Waylan]
Because it's his birthday,
for heaven's sake!
[Mr. Waylan]
Don't you take
that tone with me!
He's just trying
to please you.
With what?
Making things disappear?
He's a child.
Do you even hear
what you sound like?
[smacking, woman gasping]
[Mr. Waylan]
That'll teach you to
take that tone with me.
Do you want to sit out here
while I order some breakfast?
Sounds great.
Hello?
Hi.Hi.
Hi, can we can
order some breakfast
while I pick up
some things?
Whatever you want.
Uh, scrambled eggs,
bacon, toast.
You bet.
Well, they have
the Minneapolis paper.
They wouldn't reveal your
whereabouts at the office.
Apparently, somebody's
trying to interview you.
What do you have to
read that stuff for?
[waitress]
Here we go.
Thank you.
I don't have to read it.
I just think we ought to
know what's going on.
It's not even
front page news anymore.
In another day or two...
It'll all be
forgotten?
Tell me about it then.
They tried to
interview my sister.
If she tells them
where we are...
She wouldn't do that.
[gasps]
Think about Waterloo.
Think about Napoleon.
Life's over.
You're a dead man.
I bet he's still
having nightmares.
I bet he's out there
somewhere swatting flies.
Can we believe that he was
not a monster, but a man?
That he was innocent of
everything except his life?
Can the truth be so simple?
So terrible?
[ringing]
[Mr. Waylan]
How you doing?
How can I help you?
Oh, it's you.
What are you looking for?It's his birthday.
I told him he could have
whatever he wants.
Isn't that something?
He's a lucky lad.
Yeah, he is.
So, what can you show us?
Birthday. Right.
Did you really mean
anything he wants?
How bad is this
gonna hurt?
Well, it's something
he's wanted for a long time.
You know what I'm talking
about, don't you, Johnny?
Do you?
All right.
Let's have a look.
Oh, thank you.
Over there.
Is this what you want?
Yeah!
Okay.
Ready?
Yes![chuckles]
Something, isn't it?
Johnny, raise the blade.
Give me your arm.What?
Your arm.
Trust me.
You have strong arms.
Over here.
[clears throat]
Now, you know what to do,
don't you, Johnny?
Well, how would he know?
Sure, I do.
It's easy.
Go ahead, Johnny.
Look, he's just a kid.
There's got to be
instructions or something.
He was absolutely terrified.
My father.
And it was the only time
in my life with him
I felt any connection.
And then he was dead.
At his funeral I used
to imagine myself
crawling into the casket
with a hammer.
I wanted to kill him
for dying.
[sniffling]
Instead, I used to
pretend he was alive.
I'd lay in my bed at night
in my room, and I'd say,
"Please, don't be dead,"
and he'd be there.
And he'd wink at me and say,
"Well, hey, kiddo,
keep talking."
And we'd talk about
baseball and school.
Even in Vietnam
I used to imagine...
myself coming home
in my uniform,
and I'd get off
the bus, and he'd be there.
And he'd smile at me
and he'd say,
"Good job, son.
I'm proud of you."
But what happened
over there--
What happened over there
had nothing to do with this.
But why would you--
Why what?
You keep looking for reasons.
There are none.
Because something--
Something what?You're not a killer.
Apparently I am!
Why can't you
understand that?
He didn't talk much.
Even his wife,
I mean, I don't think
she knew the first thing
about-- about any of it.
[footsteps approaching]
Hi.
How's your sister?
Oh, she's fine.
She... she just needed
to talk, that's all.
[wood creaking]
John?
[phone ringing]
I thought you were
coming swimming with me.
Why did you, um,
connect the phone?
You know, the water's
really beautiful.
I'm going swimming
later, you might...
Why did you
connect the phone?
Because that's what
telephones are for.
No, I just wanted to
call my sister
and see if those people
were still bothering her.
Then why didn't you disconnect
it when you were finished?
I could have done that,
but I didn't.
Why, did it
hurt you?
Did you pick it up?
No?
Well then, I guess it didn't
really bother you, did it?
Kathy was no angel.
There was that affair.
I guess that must have
hurt him pretty bad.
I mean, they were in love.
Honest love.
Just like Claude and me.
He reminds me of that--
that famous onion.
You peel away the layers,
and there's always more there.
We need to talk.
Make some decisions.
What do we want to do?
We're doing it.
We can't stay here.
You know that.
I thought you wanted
to stay here forever.
That was just talk.
What's this?
[sighs]
Okay, what do you want?
I just want
our lives back.
I mean, no one's
prosecuting you, John.
We don't have to hide
out in these woods
like a couple
of fugitives.
No more hiding?
Is that what you want?
No more secrets, everything
out in the open?
Yes.Fine.
[John]
We were on patrol in the brush.
Someone tripped a mine.
Take a hit!
Come on!
[John]
Three of us were hurt.
Come on!
There wasn't anything
I could do.
There was no
magic dust this time.
There was just terror.
Months of terror.
Months of slaughter.
And then something snapped.
There was a village.
We all knew it was
full of civilians.
I don't think
I can hear this.
Isn't this what you wanted?
The truth?
[gunfire continues]
[John]
We killed everything that moved.
[woman screaming]
Scums!
Get up! Come on!
Get up! Shoo!
Git! Git!
Come on, get up!
Get up, you piece of filth.
[gunfire]
[John]
So many of our men had died.
We wanted to
kill something.
We had to kill something.
It didn't matter what.
Animals,
old people, children.
It went on forever.
Man, which side are you on, man?
Come on!
[John]
All the bodies
just became one body.
[gunfire, explosions continue]
The war would have got 'em
them sooner or later.
We just made it sooner.
But you weren't shooting.
Oh, it doesn't matter.
You weren't shooting.
I was there!
Don't you understand that?
But you didn't shoot!
I was there!
Kathy, I'm part of it.
Don't you understand?
Stop it!
Oh, Kathy!
Kathy!
[Thinbill]
My mind just went.
I just killed.
I just killed
any way I could kill.
It just came.
I didn't know
I had it in me, sir.
[man]
What were your orders?
Kill everything
that breathed.
And the troops
on your right and left?
They were obeying
these orders?
Yes, sir.
Everyone was firing, sir.
Eyeballs for eyeballs, sir.
That's one of your famous
Bible regulations.
Kill the 'Nam, kill it.
Grease the place.
Kill it.
[teapot whistling]
Wow.
Kathy?
Kath?
Kath, you up yet?
Kathy?
Kathy!
The guy was a magic man.
He could fool people.
He sure fooled me.
Keeping all that
stuff inside.
It must have
driven him crazy.
I think my sister was
almost scared of him.
I remember this
one time when Kathy...
Uh, no, I don't think
this is something
that we should talk about.
[sighs]
[John]
Taxi!
[driver]
Just back from 'Nam, huh?
I seen it on your chest.
Just want you to know,
there's plenty of people here
proud of what you guys
are doing.
I've got something for you.
But first, I've got to
tell you a story.
One day we were on patrol,
and I saw something
moving on the trail.
There were two snakes
lying on the ground,
and they were eating
each other's tail.
They were trying to
swallow each other up.
And I thought about us.
And then one day
I was in Saigon,
and I met this guy who
makes things out of jade,
and I told him the story.
I remember it was...
it was...
it was raining like crazy.
Do you like it?
It's beautiful.
I love you, Kath.
Just like those
weirdo snakes.
It's a vision
of perfection.
The circle gets
smaller and smaller
as they devour
each other.
Which one's left?
Neither.
Did you have a fight?No, nothing like that.
Did she tell you where
she was going?No.
Did she do anything
like this before?
Sometimes.She did?
Sometimes she needed
her own space.
She'd go off to her sister's
or to a friend's, or...
Something's happened to her.
People run out of gas,
lose an engine,
all kinds of nutty stuff.
It happens
more than you think.
Kathy had her own history.
That affair of hers,
the way she used to take off
now and then.
I remember once
during the campaign
we had a conversation
about how sometimes
you need to
sort of unstick yourself.
Maybe she finally did it.
Okay, now, let's start
at the beginning.
When did you first
notice that she was gone?
This morning.
I went for a swim.
What time was that?
It was very early.
I don't understand.
Where is she?
Let's call the sheriff.
Johnny, where's the phone?
Oh...
I'm sorry.
Operator?
Sheriff Lux, please.
All right, what kind of
problem we got here?
Art, good of you to come.
Claude.Vinny.
Hi.
Vinny Pearson.
Hello.Art Lux.
Art's the sheriff here.
Sheriff.
Vinny's his deputy.
John Waylan.
John and his wife Kathy
are guests of mine
at the cottage here.
As I told you,
Kathy seems to be missing.
Right, yesterday morning?
That what you said?
Yes, that's when
I noticed she was gone.
Right.
[sniffing]
That your car back there?
Yes, it is.
Well, then,
she's not driving.
How 'bout a boat?
Well, she wouldn't have
known how to use it.
Then you do own a boat.
It's my boat, I told them
they could use it.
And it's still here?
It must be.
Can we have a look?
We keep the...
I don't understand.
She must have thought
she could handle it.
Or else she wanted to
get out of here real bad.
Okay, so she
took the boat.
What do we do now, Art?
Let's get back to the house.
I'll make some calls.
Okay.
You known this guy
very long?
Yeah, a long time.
Sorry about the election,
Mr. Waylan.
Voted for you myself,
not that it matters.
Big "X" right by your name.
Well, the weather
looks like it's holding.
It's a young woman
in good health.
That right, Mr. Waylan?
Yes, she's in
good health.
What was she wearing?
Uh, she was asleep,
in her pajamas.
Pajamas?
Or she may have taken
something else, I don't know.
I'd have to go through
her closet.
She was in pajamas.
Just put it out
that way.
Well, that should be okay.
Get lucky,
find her tonight.
If not...If not, what?
Find her tomorrow.
Getting a search up,
and I had Lois
put in a call
to the colonel.
You gonna get your boat
or come in mine?
No, I'll take my own.
Between the regulars
and the volunteers,
could be we'll have
100 boats out on the water.
I wouldn't worry too much
if I were you.
I appreciate that.
Could be she just took
her out for a ride.
Million coves, you know.
Dozens of islands,
382 miles of coast.
You'd be surprised
how easy it is
to get lost
out on the water.
I suppose so.
I can't thank you
enough, really.
You know,
down in Minneapolis,
you're a very important man,
Mr. Waylan.
I wouldn't say that,
not any more.
Fact is fact.
And up here,
I'm just a hick sheriff.
And Vinny, he's just
a part-time deputy.
Couple of rubes for sure.
But I'll tell you
one thing.
We'll find that
little lady of yours,
you can go to sleep on that.
Guaranteed in gold
we'll find her.
Uh, according to Claude,
your phone wasn't hooked up.
Yes, that's right.
Any particular
reason why not?
Well, we came up here
to get away.
I just lost an election.
I didn't want to get
any calls.
The way you lost it,
Senator, I wouldn't think
you'd be getting
all that many.
I wouldn't let Vinny bother
you too much, Mr. Waylan.
It's just his way.
Another 'Nam type.
You know what I mean?
That so?
Yeah, but I didn't
kill any babies.
[clicks tongue]
That's good.
I always like
that in a man.
Ah, that phone thing
bothers me, Sheriff.
Yeah?I don't know.
A man's worried about
his wife, you'd think
he'd hook it up in case
she called, right?
[siren sounding]
[train whistle blowing]
What can I do
for you, sir?
Can you fill it up?
Hey, can you tell me where
I can find Vinny Pearson?
You're talking to him.
She just ordered breakfast.
He didn't say a word.
No good morning,
nothing.
Scrambled eggs.
His wife?
If that's who
she was, yeah.
She's over there,
she gets some eggs,
you know, some canned stuff,
and the paper.
She sits down,
she's reading the paper.
He's boiling, you know,
I can see that from here.
All of a sudden
he grabs the paper,
he just rips it out
of her hands.
They don't say another word
the whole time they're here.
It was like they were
a million miles apart.
Kind of gave me the shivers,
if you know what I mean.
Well, one thing
you should keep in mind.
Case like this, it's not
all that unusual.
We run into it, oh,
six, seven times a year.
There was something wrong
with that guy.
I could almost smell it.
Oh, man.
They said there weren't
gonna be no civilians.
Didn't they say that?
No civilians?
They said that.
I guess they were
Communists.
What do you think?
Probably.
Look, maybe we should...
I don't know.
Like, maybe we should
do something.
What?
You know... report it.
Tell somebody.
Talk.
And then what?
Hmm?
[whispering]
Go away.
Go away!
[sighs]
Sorcerer-- man, the guy
had a million moves.
All the lieutenant has to
say is a few magic words,
and the whole
village disappears.
Now, that's magic.
[laughing]
Maybe she ran off with
her lover, or some other guy.
But it wasn't love.
And it wasn't
infatuation either.
I think maybe she just
needed to break away.
[John shouting indistinctly]
[John]
You could have lied.
Hey, kiddo,
you did good.
You could have lied.
I did!
My dreams.
My dreams!
Ladies and gentlemen...
hook yourself up
to forever.
You don't
explain a thing.
No notes. No diagrams.
That's the magic.
Dark secrets.
Absolute evil.
Lies!
Lies.
I tasted defeat.
It tastes like
poison politics.
St. Paul and Minneapolis,
gone.
The suburbs, gone.
The unions, gone.
Ambush politics.
No bodies...
No numbers.
Twenty years of love...
dissolving...
like tissue.
One plus one...
equals...
[teapot whistling]
...neither.
[whistling continues]
In the rain I would
dream about you,
how much I needed you.
I wanted to crawl inside you,
stay there forever.
Oh, yeah.
[boat starting up]
Kathy said he used to
yell things in his sleep.
Bad things.
She thought he needed help.
Well, whatever happened between
them on the night in question,
things just weren't right.
All that Sorcerer crap.
Look, a guy makes up a name
for himself, you gotta wonder.
I mean, like he didn't even
know who he was.
Vinny's right,
some things just don't add up.
I don't care what Waylan says.
One plus one don't ever
equal zero, not in my book.
[banging,
Kathy screaming]
[heartbeat pounding]
I don't know.
I keep imagining these horrible
things have happened to her.
Maybe she left
the boat somewhere
and made it for the road.
It could be she'll call us from
Minneapolis when she's ready.
They'll find her,
or she'll call.
It's got to be
one of those two.
Did she ever say
anything about leaving?
Not in words exactly.
Apparently ever since
the campaign,
even before that,
she felt we were...
[sighs]
She was glad when
I lost the election.
She felt things
would be better
with politics
out of my life.
Were they?
How could they be?
We're the same people.
John, those stories
about Vietnam.
Did Kathy know
anything about that?
I tried to tell her
the night before she left.
She ran away.
But she came back.
I guess so.
That deputy, Vinny.
Yeah?
He thinks
I killed her.
Do you?
Does it matter
what we think?
Yes.
You're good.
Okay.
There you go.
Give me your hands.
Hello, Pat.
Nothing?No, nothing.
You should have called me
instead of letting me
hear it on the news.
I thought she'd be back.
Do you have a bag
or something?
No, I didn't think,
I just ran to the airport
as soon as I heard.
Sheriff, this is
Kathy's sister,
Patricia Hood.
Sheriff Lux.
Hi.How do you do?
I don't know, it just
doesn't make any sense.
I don't get it.
Get it?
Well, she just left,
in a boat.
Where was she going?
Any thoughts on that,
Mr. Waylan?
Into town, I guess.
I don't know,
maybe she went for a ride.
A ride?
Maybe.
For no reason?
She didn't
need a reason.
Sometimes she took off.
For no reason?
No, she had reasons.
Way too many.
You know, she was
having an affair.
It meant nothing.
It didn't feel
like nothing.
Is that why
you killed her?
Well, aren't you
gonna deny it?
Would you believe me?
No.
I didn't kill her, Pat.
I loved her.
There's not much here.
Kitchen, living room and...
Why don't you take
our bedroom?
I'll be back.
Wait, where are you going?The search.
When she said
she was going to visit you,
that was really to see him,
wasn't it?
What do you
want to know, John?
The guy was a walking
panic button.
Just something
to wake you up.
She just wanted you
to stop her.
Why didn't you?
I was never much good
at stopping things.
[boat motor sputtering]
[knocking]
[knocking,
door opening]
Miss Hood?
Sheriff.
Can we come in?
We'd like to look
around a bit.
Oh.
You're not gonna have
a problem with that, are you?
No.
No, not at all.
Please.
Kathy?
I'm sorry, John,
I wasn't thinking.
I didn't have anything
to wear, so...
[sighs]
It bothers you,
doesn't it?
I can go put on
what I was wearing.
The National Guard's
sending in infrared scanners,
but... I don't think
they're going to work.
Why not?
They detect
body warmth.
It's been three days.
[John sighs]
What happened maybe
is that Kathy drowned.
Something freakish--
boating accident,
maybe a sandbar.
There's a million
possibilities, Claude.
So, you think she's dead?
No.
I don't see why everybody
always assumes the worst.
Sometimes people just
up and walk away.
That's possible, isn't it?
If it was an accident,
her body would
have come up.
We looked every single
place there was to look.
We had more than
200 boats out there,
planes, helicopters,
sniffer dogs.
We even brought in
the National Guard.
No luck.
If she was setting fires,
we would have found her.
If she wasn't,
she wouldn't have lasted
six days in those woods.
She didn't just vanish.
The only place we haven't looked
is at the bottom of the lake.
That's where the boat is,
that's where she is.
No, thanks.
[dialing]
[phone ringing]
[John] Hello?
Mr. Waylan?
Sheriff Lux.
We're all here at
the command post,
and we've pretty much
run out of ideas.
You're gonna give it up,
just like that?
No, not exactly.
Well, that's what
it sounds like.
We still got places to look,
if you know what I mean.
No, I don't know what you mean.
Sir? I don't know what you mean!
[phone clicks]
[thunder cracking]
You ready?
Yeah.
[men chattering]
I just wanted you to know,
unless anything else
turns up, we're closing
out the investigation.
You said that yesterday.Well, that was the search.
I'm telling you
the investigation
is closed, too.
If she comes back,
if you hear from her,
if you here anything about her,
you'll let us know?
Of course.
Looks like you got away
with it, Senator.
She left.
Yeah, and what did you
do with the body?
She left.
What about the boat?
She couldn't take living
with a killer, is that it?
You're sick.
You are sick.
[spitting]
Sorry about that,
Mr. Waylan.
John?
Hey, John!
Rebecca, over here.
Hey, John.
We've been looking for you.
[Rebecca]
It's turning colder, John,
we're closing up the cottage.
The car's all loaded up,
we're going back to the city.
It--No.
It's been six weeks, John.
There's really no point
in your staying.
I know that.
John, you're not
gonna find her.
You're just driving
yourself crazy.
You can have
the cottage and the boat
for as long as you like.
I'm not gonna
try to stop you,
but it just doesn't
make any sense.
[teapot whistling]
[grunting]
My guess?
I don't need to guess.
He did it.
He offed her.
Vinny's the theory man,
I deal in facts.
The case is wide open.
It doesn't matter
we didn't find any evidence.
That just means he dumped her
good and deep.
Evidence ain't the truth.
It's just what's evident.
Maybe she counted on John
too much to name the things
that made her happy.
Love wasn't enough.
That's the saddest
thing of all.
All I know is that they came
into the store awful unhappy.
They sat there unhappy,
they left unhappy.
'Course, there's another
possibility
nobody's even thought of.
Now, just stick this in
the back of your mind somewhere.
He doesn't have a practice
he can go back to.
He's facing about
300-grand in campaign debt.
Right.
So, first, she vanishes,
and then he vanishes.
And then, they both
pop up somewhere else.
Free and clear.
The Sorcerer's last
and best trick.
John Waylan?
He's beyond knowing.
For all my weeks of struggle
with this depressing record,
all the interviews,
all the travel,
the man's soul,
for me, remains an absolute
and impenetrable unknown.
[siren blaring]
Sheriff!
Hurry up,
you gotta hear this!
What is it?
Come here.
Listen to this.
[John]
We fall in love.
How could I?
My bed was made,
I just lay in it.
Who's he talking to?
Beats me.
Let me something about her.
God, for all I know.
My life. My soul.
Did I mention
any of this before?
Did I tumble in love?
I did.
Did I stay in love?
Oh, yes.
We fall in love.
You have to picture that.
Her skin.
Her soul.
Oh, Kathy.
[Leming]
At no point did John Waylan
admit to the slightest knowledge
of Kathy's whereabouts,
nor indicate that he was
withholding information.
Which brings me to wonder,
is it possible that
even to John Waylan
everything was
the purest puzzle?
That the one day he woke up
to find his wife missing,
and missing forever,
and that all else was unknown.
[John]
It's a vision of perfection.
The circle gets smaller
and smaller
as they devour each other.
[Kathy]
Which one's left?
[John]
Neither.
[Leming]
The ambiguity
may be dissatisfying,
even irritating.
But one way or another,
it seems
we all perform
vanishing tricks,
defacing history,
and slipping day by day
into the graying shadows.
Our whereabouts
are uncertain.
All secrets lead to the dark,
and beyond, there is only maybe.