- While most four year
olds are playing with toys,
Angelo Inglesian was
casting pagan spells,
doing drugs, and having
sex with adult women.
His father was a
practicing pagan,
mixing elixirs and
collecting herbs
from the Albanian countryside.
At five, he was excited
to study paganism
under the pagan Pope of Olympus.
By the time he was 11,
he was dealing drugs,
pimping out his cousins and
even deeper into paganism.
At 15, he had a
major drug overdose.
He died and went to hell.
- Babe, I don't wanna do
your hippie shit today.
- Shh.
Just listen.
- Okay.
- Underneath your skin.
- Uh-huh.
- Below and between
each fold in your brain,
there is your
stupid machinery.
Picture this.
Organs vibrating.
- Stork man.
- A voice crawled into my brain
like a parasite whispering,
"You've been doing
drugs, Angelo,"
"but you never reached
the opalescent epiphany."
"You've never been super high."
- These organs
have no past, no future,
no preconceived notions.
Sign this thing.
- Yeah.
I'm uh, I'm gonna be a dad.
- Oh,
congratulations, that's great.
- Yeah, my baby's in that box.
- Oh.
Hope it's all right.
I didn't drop it or nothing.
- No man, man.
It's all good.
- It came out of the
floor and grabbed me
and I knew immediately I had
to get home to my mother.
And then before I know
it, it got real dark.
- It is dark in there inside
the depths of your body.
Let the light shine in.
♪ Ah ♪
- Benny Boom.
All right, man.
- All right, you have fun.
- Yeah, yeah, thank you.
Yo, so I didn't used to fuck
with queers, you feel me?
Then I realized that dudes-
- Yeah, all right.
- Are down for anything.
Like they'll fuck anything.
- All right bud, I'll see ya.
- I got a dick so I'm
gonna fuck with it, man.
All right, I'll see ya.
- So I got into my
car, started driving.
I remember the orange
glow of the street lamps,
started to double, triple.
I knew that if I focused on
the glow, I could find home.
♪ Um ♪
- Roscoe?
Roscoe?
- This was real.
You can't even
describe the fear.
- Hello?
- The things started to come
out from underneath the car.
They grabbed me by my
mouth and pried me open.
- And what
did they look like?
- They were worms.
- Hey.
- Roscoe?
- Wow.
I,
I think I just killed
my own childhood.
- Damn dude.
That sucks.
- Wow.
- Oh my God.
That is amazing.
You went so deep.
- Yeah, I guess
that's kinda cool.
- I did good, I did good.
- Yes, you did so good.
I'm so happy for you.
- Wow.
- Wow, wow, wow.
That was amazing.
- I feel,
I feel,
good.
Babe, I think that's enough
hippy stuff for today, okay.
- Really?
- I'm spent.
- Close the
windows, it's fucking cold.
- No.
No, we're gonna leave it open.
Look.
- No, it's freezing.
- There we go.
- I just,
I feel like,
I feel like we are in
here so much, you know?
I, I, I wish, I wish
things were more open.
- Are you okay?
How are you feeling?
- Oh, I, I feel hungry.
- I feel energized,
but with nowhere to go.
- Welcome home.
You're like my test kid,
'cause I uh, there are a lot of,
there, there are
a lot of reasons
why I can't have a
real kid right now.
I got a lot of problems.
I'm uh, I'm horny.
I'm on pills.
And then there are
the hospitalizations,
mentally, um, wards.
A lot of time spent in wards.
Mm.
Hungy?
Hmm?
Woo.
Can you say, "Daddy?"
Can you say, "Dadda?"
Sorry, I don't have a mama yet.
I have to find one for you.
But I'm gonna raise
you to be a man.
Hm?
Can you spit?
Yeah.
We're gonna get you
spitting in no time.
- Oh God, it's even better.
- Hey, what the fuck?
- Come on, Clown King.
Come on and fuck me.
- No, no.
You know what, dude, you know?
You know what?
Your mouth is just a big
hole that needs cutting up.
You know what I mean?
- Let's go.
- No one gives a
fuck what you think.
- We know you're eager
to begin operating
the Youth Series Pleasure Doll.
Yeah, no duh.
Please take a moment to read
some useful documentation
about your new device.
The Youth Series is
specifically designed
for versatility and
comfort in a compact form.
When in use,
pay attention to the
amount of pressure applied.
Some users have
experienced tissue damage
when exerting too much force.
Add to the experience
by running warm water
on your pleasure doll.
Warmth is relaxing and
encouraging circulation.
Cold water is invigorating
and refreshes the body.
Do not heat in the microwave,
stove top, or oven with fire.
Do not massage any single
area for more than 30 minutes.
Keep out for each of
children and pets.
Fuck!
God, Benny, you fucking idiot!
- You wanna be my
baby or my daddy?
- Um.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh.
I'm sorry.
- It's no big deal.
- It's, uh-
Happens all the time.
It's 'cause I have to-
- You're into stuff like this.
Are you scared?
- Yes.
- Take it.
I won't hurt you.
Unless you want me to.
- Please don't.
- Okay.
- Yeah, I'm, I'm sorry.
I don't like this.
- Okay.
Well, you got 15 minutes.
You can do whatever you want.
- I want a kid.
A, a baby.
- Yeah?
Well,
sounds like you should
get pregnant.
Oh God.
- You can be the mom
of my baby if you want.
- Come here.
Come on.
Okay, Daddy,
how about you tell me about
the first girl you ever kissed.
- Her name was Maggie.
- And
what was she like?
- She smelled like hamburgers
and she had dried tomato
sauce on her face.
She cornered me behind the
house and made me kiss her,
and I remember thinking,
"Don't kiss the tomato sauce,"
and I was so fixated
on the tomato sauce
that I landed right on it.
And after that I started
humping pillows during nap time.
- Do you still hump pillows?
- No.
That's kid stuff.
- Then what do you hump now?
- I don't know.
- I
have another idea.
Isn't it cool?
- Yeah.
- Do you wanna eat one?
We could do it "Lady
and the Tramp" style.
- Uh, nah man.
I'm, I'm good.
- Why not?
It'll make you feel good.
- It's a living thing.
- You should buy
these worms from me.
I'll sell 'em to you cheap.
Just try them.
You'll like 'em.
- Thank you.
- Why didn't you take
the worms, Benny?
Why didn't you take
the fucking worms?
You know what?
Fuck it.
Hey, I just wanted to say
that I had a really great time
and I would totally
do worms with you for-
- Hey.
Did you leave this
behind 'cause I found it.
Uh.
- Uh,
yeah, thanks.
Was there a girl in here?
- Nope.
Just me.
You okay, man?
- Yeah, I'm sorry.
I'll, I'll go.
I, I just need a place.
- A place, uh, for what?
- Place in the dirt.
- That sounds dark.
Sometimes I feel bad.
So, it's okay to feel
that way sometimes.
- Oh no, uh, nah man.
I, I meant like a
place for these worms.
Careful.
- Sorry.
Let me see.
Whoa.
- Yeah, man.
I'm just trying to
like preserve life.
You know?
- I understand.
Worms are life.
- Worms are love.
- Yeah.
- I didn't used to
fuck with queers.
You feel me?
- What do you mean?
- But then I realized
I got a dick,
and dudes will fuck anything.
You can love anything.
Fuck any damn thing, like,
I got a dick, so I'm
gonna fuck with it.
The girl I was with said you
can take these like drugs,
and um, she wanted me
to take one with her
like "Lady and the Tramp,"
but I said "No way."
- No way.
- Yeah.
It was pretty hot, dude.
Anyway, man.
I got a kid at home I
gotta take care of, so.
- I feel you, man.
- Yeah.
- I'll take care
of these for you.
- Oh, okay, yeah.
- Worms spawning worms.
Some of them were hairy,
some of them were slimy,
and they were all
different sizes.
There were itty bitty
ones in my mouth
wrapped around my tongue.
Some of the worms were in
makeup and bras and panties.
They kept saying,
"Come make love to us."
They were all laughing.
- Laughing at you?
- Yeah, and they said,
"We tricked you."
"You were doing spells,"
"and this is a setup
to take you to hell."
They were tormenting me.
- God damn it.
- Reminded
me of my past.
Everything I ever did in
my whole life on this earth
was down there.
- Hey, who told you
you could be in there?
Sure as hell wasn't me.
You got 10 minutes to
pack your bags, buddy.
"Hey, I'm a baby."
"Your mom let some
weirdo nut in her"
"and now I live in
here."
This could be fun.
This could be great.
God's plan, right?
- How'd you get out?
- I see this big worm,
bathed in purple,
come out of the mush.
Scared all the other worms away.
I heard him say "He's mine."
"Leave him to me."
And he says to me, "Because
of your mother's prayers,"
"you work for God now."
- Do you feel
like we're one thing?
- Yeah, I feel-
Plugged in.
- You do?
Yes.
We're one thing.
Transfer your energy to
me and I'll do the same.
Okay?
Please do this for me.
Okay, you ready?
- Mm-hm, yeah.
- Close your eyes.
- Uh, okay.
- Okay.
- Do you feel it?
I wanna feel it.
- I'm sorry it's only 2%.
Thirsty baby.
I met your mom today.
I think you're gonna love her.
She's great.
We didn't like do
the thing, you know?
But it felt like we did,
plus she's like so
beautiful and nice.
I think she's gonna help us.
I think she's gonna help
you become more real.
Everything's got a purpose.
Everything's gotta do
what it's gotta do.
I think I can help you.
♪ I have a hand gun ♪
♪ I have a hand for a gun ♪
♪ Where do we go now ♪
♪ Where do we go ♪
♪ I have a hand gun ♪
♪ I have ♪
- Cool worms, bro.
- What are you guys doing?
- She says it's cool.
- Is it cool?
- Oh, hey Roscoe.
- Hey babe.
- Jared is letting
me do the spider thing.
You would never let me
do the spider thing.
- Is that why you
guys are fucking now?
- You wanted this.
- I, I don't remember that.
- You said you wanted
things to be more open.
- No, I was talking
about the window.
I wanted the window
to be open, that's-
- Anyways.
We were wondering if we could
have the house for the night.
- I'm, I'm just
gonna do some worms.
- What are worms?
- Shut up, Jared.
Oh.
- Be careful.
This guy's trying to get away.
- You're gonna-
do them?
- Yeah, do you um,
do you wanna do worms with me?
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
- What do you do?
- Just, just
take this guy right here.
Go ahead, grab that one.
Open your hand.
- Oh
my God, oh my God.
Okay, and then it's,
it's uh, it's pretty easy.
You can um,
well, you can snort it or,
or chew it or bake it,
broil it, wh- whatever.
- I'm ready.
- Okay.
Ready?
- I'm ready for it.
- Mm.
- Let me see.
- What do you think?
What do you think?
- Oh my God.
Oh!
Ooh.
- Wait.
We should snort ours.
- I don't know.
Is that cool?
- Yeah, it's fucking cool.
- Mm.
- Seems like she's
having a good time.
- I can
feel it. Oh my god.
- Ah, ah.
Yeah!
Yeah, you got it, you got it!
Ah!
- One more, one more.
- I can't do it, I can't do it.
- No, you're gonna do it!
- We're gonna do it!
- Stay with me.
Hey baby, stay with me, baby.
Sam. Sam!
Sam!
Get her help.
- Echopraxia.
In echopraxia,
the equation of body to land
become literal, natural.
Delusions become of the earth.
Similar to a poem.
Similar to a worm.
- What is echopraxia?
- When an insane man
watches television
and sees himself in its message,
echopraxia is when he
follows the message's order.
You must realize
your full potential.
- Realize your full potential.
- You walk
like you're half worm.
Worms don't have limbs.
- Jesus Christ.
Look at that fucking-
- He's a nice boy.
Don't hurt him too bad.
- All right.
Here's how I imagine it.
You're like a shell and
inside you is the yolk.
And once I'm done,
you'll break out.
You'll be real.
Okay.
- Hey!
- Oh, fuck!
- You got my best girl pregnant!
- I'm gonna be a dad?
Oh, oh!
No, no no!
Stop, stop!
Please!
Fuck you.
Stop.
Stop it!
- Fucking jag.
- No!
No, no!
- It's yours, Benny.
I want it to be you.
- Baby!
Baby, come back!
Come back, we were so close!
No, baby, come back!
- Benny.
Everything happens for a reason.
Hey.
I did those worms.
It felt great, man.
Messed everything up.
- Fuck you, bitch.
- Hey, what, what's up?
Benny!
- Fuck, fuck.
- Well, I'm sorry if I came
at an inconvenient time, man.
- I'm usually better.
- Yeah, me too.
- No, I mean,
better at swimming.
- Oh, well, I mean I'm
gener- generally just better.
- They work?
- Oh yeah, they work, man.
Come on, do some worms.
Become one with the earth.
- All right.
- One with the dirt.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- How long does it
take for it to kick in?
- Just wait for it.
Wait for it.
- No man, you're
fucking with me.
- You'll know.
You'll know.
- Fired up!
Fired up!
Yeah!
- Why are you staring at me?
- You're beautiful, Clown King.
- Well, fuckin' quit it, bitch.
- You're not my first
clown king, Biff.
- Oh, I know.
- Yeah, I'll get another
one if you're mean to me.
- Yeah, I know.
- I'll bash your
fuckin' skull in, okay?
- Okay, okay.
We have these though.
- We gotta save those.
- Please.
Oh, God damn it.
Oh!
Ooh.
Oh fuck.
Oh, God, oh-
- How do you feel now?
- Like I could murder the world.
- Henrietta!
- Let me find these guys.
I'm here!
I'm here.
- Ben-
Benny, I found some.
Benny, Benny, I found some.
Oh, hey, hey.
Hey.
- I gotta
find Henrietta.
I gotta find Henrietta, dude!
I gotta find Henrietta.
- Henrietta.
- Henrietta!
Help me find her, man.
Henrietta, open up.
Henrietta, Henrietta.
- Oh, Henrietta, there she is.
- Henrietta, Henrietta.
- I'll help you.
- Henrietta!
I'm here!
- Whoa.
- Shit, bro.
Sorry dude.
- You wanna do
some worms with us?
- Worms?
- Worms.
- Yeah bro, they
get you fucked up!
- You shoulda, you
shoulda just said that.
I like getting fucked up.
Yeah, come on in.
- All right, man.
Let's fuckin' do it, man.
Yeah, man!
That's what's up.
Let's do this.
- All right, let's do it.
- Oh yeah, man.
You can smell this shit
through the fucking cosmos.
- There's only
wrong way to do worms, man.
- Not do worms?
- Yes.
- Just put it in here.
Bottoms up, y'all.
Oh.
It's got a zip to it.
- We're just trying
to keep it real,
and it's yuppie fucks like you
that stop us from
getting in the dirt!
- Henrietta, can you
say hi to the Worm King?
- Hi, Wormie.
- Spell worm for me?
- W-O-R-M.
- Very good.
- You doing okay there, buddy?
- What's your
favorite shape, Henrietta?
- I like octagons.
- How many
sides does that have?
- Eight.
- Wrong!
An octagon has an infinite
number of sides and points.
An octagon is just
a misunderstanding.
You have to unlearn your shapes.
- Okay.
- Your
shapes are all wrong.
Once you unlearn your
shapes, you can do anything.
There are no more rules.
- Yo Dennis.
- Nothing is real,
and everything is permitted.
- Yeah, man?
- I didn't used to with queers.
You feel me?
So I can do this?
- Yeah, me neither.
- Yeah, but then I realized
that dude's fuck anything.
Like you can love anything.
Fuck any damn thing.
Like, I got a dick, so
I'm gonna fuck with it.
- You must
realize your full potential.
Realize my full potential?
- Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa.
Dude.
- What, what?
- What the fuck, man?
I'm not about that shit.
What the fuck?
- No, wait.
No, you were just
talking that you-
- Not now.
There's too much fucking
shit going on, dude.
- You know what, Benny?
Fuck you, man!
- Fuck-
My baby drowned at the beach!
- Huh?
Your kid drowned?
- Yeah, today.
- Oh fuck.
Oh my God.
- You know what, I have to go.
- Yeah,
you do have to go.
- Yeah, I know. I'm
gonna go right now.
- Yeah, then
fucking go then, Roscoe.
- Yeah, I'm leaving right now.
- Yeah, fucking go.
Wait, Roscoe, wait!
- Man.
- It's like, all
I wanna do is watch TV.
You know?
That's all I wanna do, is
just watch a little bit of TV
and I can't even
fuckin' do that.
Like, it doesn't seem to have,
they don't seem
to have any sense
of what human beings really
like wanna watch, you know?
So I have to go stab a homeless
guy or something, you know?
Whatever.
I'm not saying it's right.
Hey, hey, hey.
What's up?
You got any worms tonight?
You look familiar.
- You bitch, bitch!
- Benny!
- No, these
guys are crazy.
Benny, you gotta
get me out of it.
Benny!
- Oh, fuck you!
- You don't touch
my friend, Benny!
- Oh, I'm sorry.
I do know you.
- Do you like pornos?
Shut up.
Do you watch porno?
Shut up!
- Roscoe!
Roscoe.
- Cozy.
- Answer me.
Shut up.
Do you watch porno?
- Yes!
- Oh, shut up!
- Give it.
- What do you want, babe?
Come on, you know, you know.
Just, tell 'em what you want.
- Psh-
- We want a gun.
- Do you have any wor- worms?
- Yeah, we like worms.
- We don't have worms.
- Yeah, I know you
don't have worms.
- You want
something off the dollar menu?
- Hey.
I just wanna do worms
with you guys, okay?
- You wanna do worms with us?
- Give it to me.
- Woo, let's go!
- Hi,
can I help you?
Hey.
Hey, what the hell?
What the hell do you think-
Ooh!
- All right,
where are they?
I know you got 'em somewhere.
Why don't you just tell
me where they are, huh?
Over here?
No, I'm really not
seeing any of the worms.
Where the fuck are the worms?
- It's
the wrong season.
There's no worms.
- You okay, chief?
- They got cigarettes?
- Oh, cigarettes.
You want some cigarettes
now that you've
seen a bleeding guy.
You're a big smoker, huh?
Enjoy.
- It's
the wrong season.
- Why'd
you stab that guy?
- He looks like every
other faceless person
I've seen and forgotten.
- He's suffering, Roscoe.
- Oh, oh, oh, oh!
- You have
to unlearn your shapes.
Your shapes are all wrong.
- Man.
- Benny, your problem is
you never unlearned
your own shapes.
Your shapes are all wrong.
- What a shitty day this
turned out to be, dude.
These guys are way not cool.
- I'm the cool one now.
- What do
we got here, huh?
Look at this guy.
- He's so cute.
- Oh my God.
- He looks
like a nice guy.
Oh, he says hello.
- Hey, take
this beer, man.
Take that.
Chuck it.
- Yeah, throw the beer.
- Throw the beer.
Throw the beer!
- Yeah, throw the beer.
- Throw the beer.
- Throw the
beer, throw the beer,
throw the beer!
- Throw the beer,
throw the beer, throw the beer!
Throw the beer, throw
the beer, throw the beer!
- Throw the beer, yeah!
- Oh, he did.
- Roscoe, what
the fuck did you do, man?
What the fuck?
Dennis!
- Hey man, you all right?
- Dennis!
- Hey, dude. Dude, are you okay?
We return with
- Come on, buddy boy.
- Angelo Ingelian.
- Welcome to the party.
- He
died and went to hell.
- Hey,
it was just a can.
Do you think Dennis is okay?
- Yes, I went to hell.
- What
did you find there?
- I ate
the demon's cuisine.
Since I experienced
the worms of hell,
I eat them to remind me of
the path to righteousness.
- Get down there.
- We want some worms.
Want worms.
- Oh yeah?
- Give me some
worms, please, pal?
I want worms right now.
- Yeah, you do.
- Yeah, we want worms.
- Yeah, we all want the worms,
but do you want the worms?
- I want the worms.
- Here come the worms.
- Yeah.
- Welcome
to the worm hole.
- Sorry for your
shit life, worm fuck.
This is gonna feel kinda shitty.
- What are you gonna do?
- Um, I don't know.
I've just been
having a hard time
telling the difference
between a dream and real life.
You know?
- This feels really real.
- Yeah, but that's just
because you're looking out
through those two
fucked up eyes of yours.
You know?
- No, man, this is
definitely real life.
- See, I've always had a hard
time telling what is real.
It's like the internet
tells you things
and then doctors tell
you something else,
and then your family
and all of this stuff.
Do, you know what I mean, right?
Like I just-
- Try these wormies.
- Okay, I don't
think I like this.
- What do
you got for him?
- Oh, we've got
something really amazing.
- What do you got?
- He's got a boner.
- Is that a boner?
- Is that a boner!
- Ooh, look at that.
- No, Benny, no.
Stop.
Stop it, Benny.
I'm sorry, Benny.
- This.
This.
- It's cool, bro.
- What?
Benny, no.
- It's all good.
- Benny, help.
Benny.
- Just listen.
Underneath your skin below
each fold in your brain.
There is your stupid machinery.
Organs that vibrate,
lubed up with blood.
These organs have
no past, no future,
no preconceived notions.
Oh, just let the light shine in.
Come on.
Let your organs sing!
Come on, you got this, okay?
You're okay, you're okay.
Shhh-
I love you.
I love you so much.
I love you, Roscoe, I love you.
I love you. I love you.
It's okay.
♪ We are gonna be fine ♪
We're here, we're
here. Just breathe.
- I'm sorry.
- No, no no no.
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
Yes yes.
There we go, there we go.
You're entering into a fit.
You got it, you got it.
I love you so much.
I love you, Roscoe, I love you.
I love you. I love you.
It's okay.
- My baby's your baby, Benny.
- I didn't cum inside you.
How could it be my baby?
I didn't even come
at all, Henrietta.
- All the sins of the world
are collected by the earth.
They seep into the soil and
are consumed by the worms.
The dirt becomes the worm.
The worm becomes the man
and the man becomes dirt.
And my baby will absorb
the burden of man.
- Your baby.
Sounds fucked up.
- You're the worst
person I've ever met.
I really mean it.
I have never
seen someone
as horrible
as you.
♪ Dig ♪
♪ A hole ♪
- Carcasses of the men that
have transgressed against me!
For their worm shall not die.
Neither shall their
fire be quenched.
♪ When you ♪
♪ Go digging ♪
♪ After all those little worms ♪
♪ All those little worms ♪
♪ You got what you wanted ♪
♪ A shiny, slimy one ♪
♪ And it's ♪
♪ Not enough 'cause ♪
♪ 'Cause you can't
hold it back ♪
Here he comes!
♪ You can't hold it back ♪
♪ You ♪
♪ You thought ♪
♪ You'd be in a garden now ♪
♪ Dancing around ♪
♪ Kissin' all your friends ♪
♪ But you're deep down ♪
♪ Where screaming
won't make a sound ♪
♪ Turn in your keys ♪
♪ Put on this gown
and come with me ♪
♪ We've got ♪
♪ What you needed ♪
♪ A fresh, tilled hole ♪
♪ Somewhere to hide
from your dreams ♪
♪ Bite off my skull ♪
♪ Suck out the juice
and toss me down ♪
♪ Fill me up ♪
♪ With worms ♪
♪ Love me, I'm all worms ♪