Now this is more like it.
Relatively safe, quiet.
Quiet?
It's a ghost town.
It's the off season.
Look how peaceful this is.
You're going to be missing
this after Memorial Day
when the place is
crawling with tourists.
Maybe.
I just hope
someone's hiring.
Yeah. Start slowing up
'cause we should be
coming up to it.
What's the address?
Uh, it's the Viking Motel.
We're living in a motel?
Oh, yeah. They rent out
long term when there's
no tourists around.
There it is.
At least we know what
we'll be paying in rent.
So will everyone else.
I hope it's
a safe neighborhood.
You're kidding, right?
You can never be
too careful.
Yes?
Hi, I'm Rick Holland.
This is Kathryn Bennett.
I spoke to you last week
about the apartment.
Now wait a minute.
You called last week?
Yes, I told you
we'd be arriving
today or yesterday,
and you said a unit
would be available.
You came here
yesterday or today?
Well, which was it?
No. We called you
last week from New York
about an apartment.
Oh, New York!
You're the couple
from New York City!
That wasn't yesterday
that I talked to you.
That was last week.
- How was the drive up?
- Oh, great.
I suppose you want
to see the unit.
Oh, I thought the unit
was on the second floor.
It is.
Too many keys.
I tried to have
just the one master,
but these people
keep changing
the lock on me.
What do you think?
Well, it's fine.
I just-- I thought
we were going to be
on the second floor.
Well, this is the model unit.
It's been empty
for quite a while, so I
just use it to show people.
All the units are the same.
The one you two
would be getting is
on the second floor.
But I'm getting old,
and you can't expect me
to go traipsing up and down
the stairs all day long,
showing apartments if
people aren't going
to take it.
That's fine,
if they're all the same.
It's a great deal, you know.
During the summer,
I can get $120 a night
for a unit like this.
But it's a been a little slow
the past few years,
so we're all filled up
with long-termers.
Now there's no guarantee
that you can stay past
the off season.
We were pretty busy
last summer,
but we'll just have to see what
the tourist traffic is like.
Now, there's
no pets allowed...
and no drugs.
And you'll have
to sign a paper
saying that you're not gonna
fool with the smoke detector.
Hey.
Well, we've actually
found someone who's
immune to your charms.
I guess.
- Oh, God.
- It smells in here.
Probably just needs
airing out.
Finally, a bathroom.
- Oh, my God. Oh, my God!
- What is it? Honey?
- It's disgusting!
- What is it?
Turn on the light!
Don't come in!
- Oh! I'm gonna puke.
- Just get out of there.
Wash yourself off
in the kitchen, I guess.
- I can't believe this!
- I'm going to puke.
- Excuse me. Excuse me! Hey!
- Yeah?
We just moved into unit 16,
and the whole bathroom is
covered in excrement!
- What?
- Excrement!
The lights were off
and my girlfriend
went in there and
got it all over herself!
- What are you talking about?
- Excrement!
Feces! Poo-poo! Shit!
It's everywhere in there!
And you want me
to clean it up?
Well, Mrs. Farthing
was beside herself,
apologizing.
Are you gonna be
all right about living
on the first floor though?
I just don't think
I could ever feel clean
in that bathroom after that.
Me either. I can probably
rig something up
for these windows.
If it makes you feel better,
but, honestly, I think
this town looks safer
than where my dad lives
in Westchester.
But there's a lot
of drifters and bikers
that go to towns like this.
Stop worrying.
We'll be fine.
Hey, you know,
the previous tenant in here
was a writer too.
Really? What kind?
Well, she didn't say,
but she did refer to him
as "Mr. Warren."
Oh. You think it was
Peter Warren?
Yeah, I think so.
He's from up here, you know.
Maybe that'll give you
inspiration.
To write a crappy best seller?
Let's hope not.
- Still, it's pretty cool.
- [voice on radio]
What is that noise?
Mrs. Farthing said
the woman next door
has a police scanner,
so we may need to move
the head of the bed to
the other side of the room.
Um, in the meantime,
why don't you, uh,
take those dirty hands off me
and get in the shower
while I unload the car.
Sounds like a plan.
Warren!
Hi.
Are you all right?
Oh. Yes.
Yes, of course.
New neighbor.
Yeah, yeah.
We're moving in
next door.
I'm Rick.
Of course you are.
Oh, hey, moving in?
Want a plant?
Excuse me?
A houseplant.
A fern maybe?
Never mind.
Oh, hey, I guess
I should get to know
my new neighbor.
The name's Ted.
Hi, I'm Rick.
Rick Holland.
Of course you are.
[police scanner]
[voice]
Kathryn?
Kathryn. Beautiful name.
So what brings Rick and Kathryn
from New York City
up to our
horse's neck of the woods?
Well,
I work in the theater,
and New York is
pretty expensive.
We moved up here
so I could finally
get some writing done
and maybe open
one of my plays
in Portland.
You know, kind of
an out-of-town tryout
before bringing it
back to New York.
The theater? I hear
these satellite TV people
are putting you folks
out of business.
I think
we'll be okay.
Ah, you do.
[police scanner]
Rick?
[thump]
[scanner off]
I thought that we'd be
getting a lot of snow
up here this time of year.
Not snow.
Rain.
You see? Wet.
Yeah, I saw that.
I guess I thought,
you know,
this time of year
we'd be buried in snow.
Snow, sleet, rain.
We get all sorts of
miserable weather here.
The worst of the snow
generally piles up inland.
Here on the coast,
it's usually rain this year.
Gonna be a wet winter.
Forty days and forty nights.
Well, I guess I'll--
I'll be seeing you around.
Oh. Goodbye.
Goodbye.
I... I want your teeth.
This place isn't a motel.
It's an insane asylum.
- You mean that man?
- [groans]
One minute he doesn't
want to talk to me,
the next minute
he won't shut up.
And then he said
he wanted my teeth.
And you were trying
to drag me into it?
- What do you mean?
- I heard you calling me,
but I wasn't
coming to your rescue
wrapped in a towel.
I didn't call you.
I heard you.
These walls are paper thin.
I might have said your name
a couple of times.
It might have been
that lady's scanner too.
I can't believe how loud it is.
Yeah. We'll move the bed.
I just hope old Ted
doesn't snore.
I'm definitely
doing something tomorrow
to secure these windows.
I was out
in the parking lot
taking the stuff in,
there was
a guy out there
staring at me,
like he was
casing the joint
or something.
He was probably
just checking the rates
on that sign out there.
But you should
definitely fix the window
if it makes you feel better.
Ah, you're probably right.
Sorry I'm such a coward.
What?
Nothing.
Can you grab the top sheet?
Yeah.
This mattress is
just a little uneven.
You're not a coward.
City living
does that to people.
If I'd been broken into
as many times as you have,
I'd have security issues too.
Come on.
Let's go to bed.
I'm gonna start looking
for a job tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
I thought that we were
going to take a couple
of days to, you know,
settle in and...
explore, get comfortable.
After I get a job.
We've got to have at least
one source of income
until you make us rich.
As a playwright?
You're going to be
selling fried dough for
a very, very long time.
I'm just waiting for you
to sell out and get some
of that Hollywood money.
Don't hold your breath.
[Ted singing]
[thumping]
What the--
What's he doing
in there?
[singing continues]
Do you think he's okay?
He's singing.
What?
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
It's awful.
[stops]
- You think he heard us?
- No, I don't think so.
What time is it?
It's 2 a.m.
Must be his bedtime.
[police scanner]
I thought old people
were supposed to be quiet
and go to bed early.
Should we
bang on the wall?
We don't want to seem like
jerks our first night here.
- [rattling]
-  [singing resumes]
This is ridiculous!
[rattling continues]
Oh, my God!
What is that, an earthquake?
In Maine?
It's just a crazy old man.
It's freezing in here.
[ringing]
[ring]
Ted! It's Rick
from next door!
What the hell's
going on in there?
I'm trying to sleep!
Well, how is anybody else
supposed to sleep
with all this noise?
It's just a freight train.
In a few weeks,
you'll be sleeping
right through it.
Now go back to bed.
Sorry.
Sorry!
Damn kids.
So much for not
looking like jerks.
I just want
to go to bed.
It's freezing
in here.
Something's wrong
with that answering machine.
I hope it wasn't my dad calling.
It's bad enough he's all alone.
I don't want him
worrying about me.
It's probably
just a wrong number.
Mrs. Farthing said that
our line's not even supposed
to be active until tomorrow.
[police scanner]
[silent]
Aah!
[gasps]
What? What is it, honey?
Having a nightmare?
Yeah.
It was my mom.
She was here.
She was yelling at me.
[yawns]
It was just a dream.
Your mother loved you
so much.
I know. It's just
it was just so real.
Oh, my God.
You're burning up.
Oh, it's just
the long underwear.
It was just a dream,
Kathryn. You gotta...
stop feeling guilty
about that stuff
all the time.
I know.
You know,
if I had been there
when she died,
I wouldn't feel this way.
Well, why don't you
call your dad
in the morning?
That always
makes you feel better.
[upbeat]
[loud static]
[tuning radio]
[news talk]
- [static]
- [off]
[phone rings]
[ring]
Hello?
Hi, honey.
Hey. How are things
in the working world?
Thrilling.
Very quiet, lots of books.
You sound out of breath.
The phone scared
the crap out of me.
Oh, sorry.
How's the writing going?
[coughs]
Good, good.
I've got some ideas here
that I'm working on, you know.
Oh, great.
Well, I just wanted
to give you a call
and say I miss you.
Aww. Hey, do you know
what you'd like for dinner?
We can make something
together when I come home.
You just keep working,
okay?
I love you.
Bye-bye.
I love you too.
[ring]
- Hello?
- [woman] Is Kathryn there?
No, she's not.
Can I take a message?
I have to talk to Kathryn.
She's not here.
May I ask who's calling?
Rick? Is that you?
Who is this?
It's Barbara,
Kathryn's mother.
Who is this?
Is Kathryn there?
I have to talk to Kathryn.
Who is this?
What do you want?
Rick, is that you?
It's Kathryn's mom.
This is not funny!
This call can be easily traced!
What is your problem?
I'm dead.
[disconnects]
[line rings]
[woman]
Pine Point Library.
- Sorry. Wrong number.
- [hangs up]
[dial tone]
[phone ringing]
[police scanner]
That noise is really
getting to me tonight.
- What noise?
- The scanner.
You can't hear it?
- You're not used to it yet?
- No.
Can I get you anything?
[Rick on tape]
Okay, now, Gary has
come into the apartment.
He kisses Carol quickly,
then walks to the window and
begins pacing back and forth.
Carol:
"Didn't find anything, huh?"
Gary: "No. The cops came by
and started harassing me."
[click]
...walks to the window
and begins pacing
back and forth.
Carol:
"Didn't find anything, huh?"
Gary: "No. The cops came by
and started harassing me."
Carol says: "No wonder,
with all the bodies
"that have been turning up
in the dumpsters around here.
I mean, look at you."
Gary gets kind of
sarcastic here.
"Trash-picking's a dirty job.
You want me to wear a tuxedo?"
[woman on tape]
Keep your mouth shut!
- Honey, what's wrong?
- Nothing.
Aren't you hot?
It's boiling in here.
Uh...
You're sitting by
the heater over there.
Kathryn...
Do we have any more
of that wine left?
Yeah, I think so.
A little bit.
Good.
I wouldn't mind
a small glass myself.
Sure.
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
[Rick on tape]
"Look at you."
Gary gets kind
of sarcastic here.
"Trash-picking's a dirty job.
You want me to wear a tuxedo?"
Carol is, what, she's just
trying to show her concern.
Bla bla bla bla.
She says something like,
"I just worry about you
wandering out there alone
at night by yourself
with a killer on--"
[click]
Gary: "No. The cops came by
and started harassing me."
Carol says: "No wonder,
with all the bodies
"that have been turning up
in the dumpsters around here.
I mean, look at you."
Gary gets kind of
sarcastic here.
"Trash-picking's a dirty job.
You want me to wear a tuxedo?"
Carol is, what, she's just
trying to show her concern.
Bla bla bla bla.
She says something like,
"I just worry about you
"wandering out there alone
at night by yourself with
a killer on the loose,
and I'm not crazy
about being left alone."
[tape continues]
[woman on tape]
Keep your mouth shut!
Ohh!
- Oh, I'm sorry!
- It's okay. Are you okay?
- Uh...
- You're all hot again.
I feel like I'm freezing.
Can we just--
Can we just go to bed?
Yeah, sure.
[ringing]
[line ringing]
- [Rick] Hello?
- Kathryn, could you--
Oh, no. It's okay.
I was just calling home.
Everything all right?
Yeah. I just forgot
to tell my boyfriend
something. Did need me?
I was wondering if,
before you go to lunch,
you could give us a hand
with the bar coding
over at audio-visual.
Oh, no problem.
I've still got
over an hour.
Great. I wish we had
ten more like you.
Hey.
You seen Stacy?
Who?
Come on. Don't act like
you haven't noticed
the only other piece of ass
on this property
besides your wife.
The cleaning girl?
Uh, no,
I haven't seen her.
I saw you drinking
down at the...
Tidal Basin earlier, right?
Yep.
Thought so.
What are you doing there?
I'm trying to write.
Yeah? What are you writing?
A play.
Really?
I'm a writer.
Yeah. Well,
writer-actor, really.
That's how me and Stacy met.
We were doing, uh...
Glass Menagerie
over at the Portland
City Theater last year.
Really?
You know, I was going
to go down there and--
Everything
all right here, Rick?
Yes, Ted.
Everything's fine.
Let's hope so.
Uh, I gotta go.
I'll see you later.
- Maybe I'll buy you a beer.
- Yeah, sure.
Okay, man.
I'd watch that fella
if I were you.
Thanks, Ted.
I will.
- Well, here's Princess Kathryn.
- Hi, Ted.
- Howdy, milady.
- How are you?
Can't complain.
Doesn't do any good anyway.
See you later.
Well...
Aren't you worried about
someone coming in
and robbing us blind?
I thought the place
needed airing out.
I can't argue with that.
I'm just wondering
what's happened to
my paranoid boyfriend.
There's nothing out there
to be afraid of.
[kiss]
Have you been drinking?
I stopped into a bar
to get out of the rain,
and I may have had
a beer, yes.
It smells like more than one.
And in the middle of the day?
That's not like you
at all, Mr. Holland.
I thought I was the drinker
in this relationship.
The way my writing's been going,
I'll take inspiration in
whatever form it may come.
You know, if things
aren't going well,
maybe I can help you.
- You can't help me write!
- Okay, okay.
I'm sorry.
I'm just tired or something.
- Or something.
- What?
Nothing. Forget it.
Why don't you just go lie down,
and I'll make us some dinner.
- No, that's not fair to you.
- Sure it is.
You've made dinner
every single night
since we've been here.
No. I haven't done
the dishes.
That's fine. It'll just
take me a few minutes.
Is it okay
if we close the door now?
- Yes.
- Thank you.
I'm all caught up.
Is there anything
I can do to help you?
Caught up?
It's not even noon yet.
You're amazing.
I suppose you could
give me a hand with
the new acquisitions.
Sure.
You know,
it's really a great way
to get first dibs
on the new materials.
There's an awful lot of this
paranormal stuff in here.
Oh, I know:
ESPs, UFOs,
talking
to the dead.
I think it's good,
though.
It gives people a little
something to think about
in their lives.
A little mystery.
Oh, you think
you have a poltergeist?
No. Just crazy neighbors
and my boyfriend.
Oh, how's he doing?
I think he has a fever.
But it's not just that
I'm worried about.
What wrong?
I think spending so much
time alone is starting
to drive him a little nuts.
He goes out,
but he just ends up in bars.
And it's certainly
not helping him
get his writing done.
Well, uh,
maybe he's homesick.
Maybe.
Oh! Phantom stains.
Nothing a little
old-fashioned
elbow grease
and a stain remover
won't cure.
You know,
it's just mold.
My friend Maria
lives down the street.
She had
the Clorox bleach out.
She had everything--
- Looks like
an early day, ladies.
- What is it?
Bomb scare.
Time to go home.
Damn. Those kids these days.
This is their idea of a joke.
Well, at least you can
go and take care of that
homesick boyfriend of yours.
I guess you're feeling better.
Jesus.
God.
[arguing]
Coming!
Oh, hello!
- Is it rent time again?
- No.
- You're supposed to be at work.
- There was a bomb scare.
Oh, yes,
at the library.
Mrs. Lameire
told me about it.
- She heard it on her scanner.
- Uh-huh.
There's a problem
in our room.
It's the mattress.
It's got something
all over it.
It looks like blood.
Could you come--
[arguing]
You there!
I thought I told you
to stay off this property!
Mind your own business,
you old bat!
Stacy, leave that trash
in the gutter where he belongs
and get back to work.
I'm sorry.
If I see you anywhere near
that girl or on this property,
I'm going to call
the police!
Stacy!
Mrs. Lameire's toilet
is still backed up,
the poor woman.
I'm sorry!
I'm going!
Now, did I hear you say
something about blood?
Well, yeah.
It's a stain.
It was there before,
and now it just keeps
getting bigger,
and it's ruining
our sheets.
Oh, that's just mold.
No, the mold is
a whole other problem
altogether.
That's just mold.
Shouldn't let it
get this bad.
Truthfully, the whole place
can do with a scrubbing.
I'll send Stacy in,
if it's too much for you.
No. No, thank you.
It wasn't mold. I told you.
It was a dark reddish brown,
like blood.
I don't see anything
like that in here.
It must be in the bed.
Sometimes I come home
and it's almost all dried up
and faded away,
and then that night it's back
and it's seeping through
the sheets.
Well, it's been
so damp lately.
It was right here.
Oh, my.
That's nothing.
You should have seen it
five minutes ago.
Oh, dear.
- What?
- Now I remember.
This mattress...
was in room 16
when Mr. DeLuca
was living there.
He was the victim
of a home invasion.
It was terrible.
They never caught the buggers.
Bikers, I bet,
or maybe even Canadians.
I don't know what
this world is coming to.
Well, what is it
doing in here?
We cleaned everything up
after--
well, you know--
and then we switched
the mattresses from
the one upstairs.
The stain was so small
compared to the blood
that was everywhere.
And then this room
was never used.
It hasn't been used
in ages, so...
I just forgot all about it.
That happens
when you get older.
Sometimes your mind
just doesn't think straight.
I am so terribly sorry.
I'll call
the Bedding Warehouse
right away
and have them haul
this evil thing away
and bring you
a brand-new one.
Thank you.
Don't thank me.
I can't believe I made
such a terrible mistake.
And you've been
sleeping on this
all this time?
You should have
come and told me.
How quickly do you think
the new mattress
could be here?
I really don't want
Rick to see this.
He gets pretty upset about
things like home invasions.
Oh, they come pretty fast.
I'm sure they'll be
in and out of here
before your boyfriend
gets back from work.
Well, that's the problem.
He works from home,
so I have
no way of knowing
when he'll be here.
Oh?
I thought he went out
and got himself a real job.
Playwriting!
Still, he keeps
pretty regular hours,
9:30, 10:00,
then he comes home
just before you do.
Really?
I am not sticking my nose
in where it doesn't belong.
Really, dear.
I just like to keep
an eye on things.
Of course.
Well, I'll go call
the mattress folks.
[sighs]
You're home early.
What are you doing home?
Somebody called in
a bomb scare
at the library.
What's all this?
Mrs. Farthing said that they
have to change the mattresses
every certain number of years.
It's some state regulation
or something.
I see you cleaned.
Just a little.
The place just needed
a little cleaning up.
I was gonna do it.
Hey, what's all this
"You're home early" stuff?
Mrs. Farthing was telling me
about your daily routine.
Nosy old farts just can't
mind their own business!
Where do you go
all day?
I take walks.
You know that.
Sometimes
I stop into this bar.
Oh, that I can tell.
You smell like a brewery.
You want me to stay cooped up
in this little place all day?
I need go out someplace
where I can sit,
think, write.
There are such things
as libraries.
I'm not going to the place
where you work to write.
I didn't mean my library.
There are two other branches.
But, of course,
they don't serve beer.
Why are you doing this?
Is it because I didn't do
some of my household chores?
I'm sorry.
Let's just forget it.
I'm trying to
adjust to, you know,
things in this apartment.
And I...
I don't know.
I'm not comfortable
here and...
I need to go out and
get comfortable to write.
You don't have to
explain yourself to me.
Just don't drink
all of my earnings away.
Fine! I'll get a job!
I was joking, okay?
I don't want you
to get a job.
That would defeat
our whole purpose of--
Hey, what's going on?
What's going on?
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
I'm just not
feeling well.
Hey, no, no.
Just lay down.
It's all right.
You're not seeing
someone else,
are you?
[chuckles]
Not the way you're thinking.
What does that mean?
Uh, no, it's, uh--
Nah. It's--
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
No. I have been hanging out
at this bar, yes,
with a guy and writer--
that writer-director guy.
He's a writer-director.
We have a lot in common.
[mumbles]
At least
you're making friends.
Yeah.
You don't have
to stay here
with me all day.
Oh, no. I'm just going to try
to get some writing done
in the laundry room.
You rest.
Cleanliness
is next to godliness.
[loud rattling]
What's wrong?
I just remembered
I need to go out.
Do you need anything?
- Where are you going to go?
- I need to meet Phil.
- Who's Phil?
- That writer-actor guy
I told you about.
He was going to have a meeting
with a big producer and--
- Oh, yeah?
- He might be able
to help me out.
Okay. Well, can you
call him or something?
I don't have his number.
Look, I won't be long.
The laundry is almost done.
I'll take it out
when I get back.
Okay, okay.
Can I take the car?
- Yeah, of course.
- Thanks.
Rick, can you take the--
[ringing]
- Hello.
- [static]
- Hello? I can't hear you.
- [woman] This is the end--
[garbled]
Leave here now--
- Hello?
- Oh, Claudette.
- Can you hear me all right?
I can now. There was
a lot of static on the line.
How are you feeling?
Awful.
I just-- I can't
shake this thing.
It's been three days,
and I don't feel any better.
If anything, I feel worse.
Have you gone to a doctor?
No, not yet, but if
I don't get better soon,
I'm going to have to.
You really should
see someone.
I know,
but I can't afford it.
I'm supporting us both
right now.
You don't have insurance?
No. My policy
from the last job ran out,
and I haven't been
at the library long enough
to get a new one.
[sighs]
You know, I didn't want
to bring this up,
- but...
- What?
The director's
being a bitch.
She says that since you're
a new hire and you've been
out for a couple days now,
that you have to come back
to work with a doctor's note
or else they're going
to have to let you go.
I'm sorry.
That's okay.
I understand.
I tried to explain to her
how great you are.
That's all right.
I'll try to get a good night's
sleep tonight and see if I can
get in there tomorrow.
You sound terrible.
Why don't I try
to find you a doctor?
No, that's okay.
You know, I'm not being
totally selfless.
If we lose you,
I'll have to do all
of the work again myself.
Well, who do you see?
My doctor can only take
people through HMOs.
I'll see if I can find
some sort of clinic
or something, okay?
That would be great.
Thanks, Claudette.
It's my pleasure.
I'll let you
get some rest now.
Take care.
- Bye.
- Okay, thanks. Bye.
That's it?
One page?
[sighs]
Sorry I was out so late.
Phil and I had a lot
to talk about.
You didn't have to do that.
I said I would bring that
laundry in when I came back.
I didn't want Ted rummaging
through my underwear.
How did your friend's meeting
with the producer go?
Pretty well.
He said pretty well.
Is there anything in it
for you?
Maybe. I've got to get some
writing samples together.
You have anything?
Yeah. What do you think
I've been working on
this whole time?
One page.
There's more to it
than that.
What have you been doing,
going through my stuff
without telling me?
I didn't read anything.
I just looked at it.
I know I shouldn't have.
I'm sorry.
I can't take this.
I can't work like this.
I get no support from you!
No support?
I've done nothing but
support you since we got here!
That's not what I mean.
I'm sorry.
It's just
in this little room and--
I can't concentrate.
And I feel like I'm
going insane in here.
Why don't you talk to me
about this stuff?
You used to tell me everything.
Now you just clam up.
I just need
to be able think.
I can't think
in this apartment,
and I can't think with you
hassling me all the time.
I didn't realize
I was hassling you.
You don't understand.
I mean, you're not
a creative person.
Writing is not like
sitting at a desk,
typing in names
into a card catalog.
I need to...
I need to concentrate.
Maybe if you had some dreams
of your own, you'd understand.
Dreams of my own?
I have dreams of my own.
I just put them all on hold,
so I could help you
realize yours!
And I took all the same
creative classes
as you did in college.
The only difference is
that I actually graduated!
You took the safe route,
while I actually
went out and did stuff.
And look where it got you.
You're an assistant
at a library in the
middle of nowhere.
That job and all
the others before it
are what's made
this trip possible.
That's what paid
for the car,
and that's what paid for
the computer that you're
supposed to be writing on,
not to mention all the beer
you've been drinking.
Don't worry.
I won't forget that!
How could I ever forget that?
What is it?
I just don't feel so good.
I'm sorry, Rick.
I just--
I don't know why
we're fighting so much.
You're really drunk,
and I feel like death.
Could we please just try
to work this out tomorrow?
No.
I'm leaving.
Come on. Please?
Just come to bed.
I can't stay here anymore.
It's driving me nuts.
Well, maybe I can just
work a few extra hours,
and we can get a place
that's bigger.
I'm tired of living
in the middle of nowhere!
There's nothing here!
I've been trying
to tell you for days now,
but you've been so sick.
Tell me what?
Tell me! What?
Phil made a deal
with that producer.
He's going out to L.A.,
and he's going to be
developing a TV show.
I might be able
to get on board.
It's not 100%,
but once he gets in,
I'll probably be able
to get a job.
L.A.?
You hate L.A.!
And TV?
Whatever happened
to never selling out?
It's a chance to get
my foot in the door.
- I'm not getting any younger.
- God! So that's it?
So that's it. This was
just a whole waste of time.
We're moving to L.A.?
No. Just me.
I need time alone
to write and...
Well, Phil's going to need
a roommate out there.
And what am I
supposed to do?
Stay here.
You seem to be doing all right.
There's always New York.
You can go back there.
So it's over?
You don't love me anymore?
It's just not good times
for us right now.
I mean, uh...
My career
and my life,
I mean, it's too
up in the air for...
us to have got so tied down
like we got here.
I've got to think
of my future.
of my writing.
I need to be able to write,
go and write
and experience living.
Oh, yeah, by living in
Hollywood and getting drunk
all the time with Phil?
[sobbing]
It beats slaving away
at some nine-to-five job,
worrying about
credit card payments.
Okay.
Okay, fine.
So when do you go?
Tonight.
What?
I said I've been trying
to tell you for days!
I just came to pick up
a few things,
and then I've got
to go meet Phil.
He and Stacy got into a fight,
and she kicked him out.
Wait a minute.
The housekeeper's boyfriend?
That's your friend Phil?
Yeah. He's a nice guy.
You can't be serious.
You're 34 years old.
What's happened to you?
Nothing.
I just gotta
get out of here.
So you're just
abandoning me here?
The rent is due
in two days. I either
have to move out tomorrow
or pay it for another month
and stay here by myself.
Take my advice: Move out.
Where am I supposed to go?
This is so sudden,
and I'm really sick.
You have credit cards.
You've got a job.
You'll be fine.
[sobbing]
Why are you
doing this to me?
- I don't know.
- No.
- Goodbye, Kathryn.
- No, no.
No, Rick, no. Please.
Please, Rick, please.
I'll... call you.
Thanks for getting
the laundry.
No, Rick. Rick, Rick!
Rick, please!
No, no, no, no!
[sobbing]
[coughing]
[phone rings]
[ring]
[answering machine beeps]
[Claudette]
Kathryn,
it's the library again.
I've been calling you
for a few days now,
and I'm getting
really worried.
Please pick up, Kathryn.
I don't know if I should
come over there
or call the police or what.
Please give me a call
at the library or at home.
It doesn't matter what time.
Just let me know you're alive.
[hangs up]
- [knocking]
- [Claudette] Hello!
Kathryn?
- Hello?
- Who is it?
Kathryn, is that you?
[knocking]
Hello? It's me.
It's Claudette. Open up.
Oh, thank God!
You're alive!
I just-- Oh!
What happened to you?
Um, I'm so sorry,
Claudette.
I... I just woke up.
I was going to give you a call.
I was gonna listen
to your messages.
Give me a call? I've been
trying to get in touch
with you for a week.
- What?
- I've been calling you
since last Thursday.
Wait. What day is today?
- It's Tuesday.
- Tuesday?
I lost a whole week.
Oh, God.
You know, I can't believe
I've been so stupid.
You're so together at work, and
you've got those fancy clothes.
I didn't think
that there was a problem.
- That eye.
- What? What problem?
Come on. I'm not stupid.
I'm from Maine.
Our winters
are long and cold.
- I know about this.
- Wait. You think I'm a drunk?
- Well--
- [chuckles]
No, I mean, I'm just--
If you admit
that you have a problem,
then we can do something
about it and you'll get better.
I don't know. Maybe you can
even get your old job back.
Oh, she fired me?
Well, you know,
I... I warned you.
Look, Claudette,
I know what this
must look like,
but I'm not an alcoholic
or a junkie
or whatever this
looks like to you.
I-- I just, um...
I've just been
really sick and...
and Rick left me.
Oh, I...
I didn't know.
I'm sorry.
Yeah, he just left.
It came out of nowhere.
But you know, maybe--
I mean, if he's
the kind of guy who's
going to do that to you,
you don't need him.
Rick didn't do this.
He would never.
- He's not like that.
- Well, then who did?
Well, I don't know.
I just woke up with it.
I mean, I must have
fallen out of bed or--
[sighs]
Okay, look.
I've got to go back to work.
I just, um...
You know, I have some numbers
of some doctors. Would you
just take them and--
No. Thank you very much,
but I told you
I really don't think--
It doesn't have to be now.
Just take them and call me
if you need anything.
- Okay.
- How are you set for money?
I have another check
coming from my last week
of work, don't I?
Right.
They'll mail it to you.
But is that enough?
Well, I have some money
in the bank, and I have--
Oh, the rent was due days ago.
[laughs]
Well, I'll be fine, Claudette.
Thank you so much for coming by.
Oh, no. I was just--
You had me all worried.
Thanks.
No. Look, just please--
Oh, listen. Would you--
Would you take
these back for me?
I can't really afford
any overdue fines.
Yes. Please just call me
if you need anything.
- I will. Thanks.
- Okay.
- Okay, bye.
[knocking]
Yes? Can I help you?
Hi, Mrs. Farthing.
It's Kathryn Bennett
from unit 13.
Unit 13 is rented.
You'll have to go
somewhere else.
No, it's me, Kathryn.
I already live in 13.
Oh, it is you.
I didn't even recognize you.
I'm sorry this is so late.
I've been sick.
I hadn't realized
it was that time already.
I was wondering
where you were.
I haven't seen
that man of yours
around lately either.
He moved out.
Oh, I see.
Why don't you come in
and rest for just a minute?
Oh, you look terrible.
- No, I'm all right.
- I insist.
Oh, my goodness! Oh!
- You all right, dear?
- I'm sorry.
Come in.
Oh.
Shh. Your head is getting pink.
You have to be careful.
Your skin is so fair.
You can get a sunburn
even though it's not summer.
Oh.
Oh, thank you.
I'm sorry the room
is such a mess.
Oh, it's not so bad.
It just needed
a little picking up.
It's hard keeping up
with all that mold.
You know, Mrs. Farthing said
she thinks that's what's
made me so sick.
Maybe.
What, you don't think so?
Whenever I'm in there,
I feel something.
It's like the room
is creepy, evil.
Do you know what
I'm talking about?
The place has always seemed
a little depressing to me.
It's like all the unhappiness
that you experienced in there
is still lingering.
It's like it's haunted
by bad feelings.
You think I'm crazy.
No, I don't.
I know what you mean.
Well, I can put some
herbs and stuff in there
that are supposed to cleanse
the spirit of the room.
- If nothing else,
it smells nice.
- Oh, that's okay.
Actually, I already did.
Thank you.
Why are you being
so nice to me?
I never thought
you liked us very much.
I'm sorry.
You know I was having
man troubles of my own.
Sorry.
Oh, it's okay.
It's over now.
He's gone.
I'm better off.
[Mrs. Farthing]
That's enough, Stacy.
We have to let this pretty
little lady get her rest.
- See you later.
- Thanks.
How are you feeling?
- A little better, thanks.
- Well, you look it.
I know how much
you like to read,
so I brought you the paper.
And these are some of the books
that the man who used to live
in your unit wrote.
He wrote a few of these
all while he was living here.
They're all about the lives
of various local celebrities
and politicians.
Eww!
I didn't mean
to bring out that one.
So it was Peter Warren.
That's his real name,
supposedly.
Lord knows why he decided
to use it for this trash.
Once he started making money
writing this nonsense,
he moved out of here.
He's a really famous writer.
I wouldn't know.
I don't read
that sort of trash.
And neither should you.
You're sick enough as it is.
Stick to his good ones.
They're all true stories,
you know.
Everyone should read.
Helps you
to keep an open mind.
- All done!
- Oh, thank you.
I'll have to
make it up to you sometime
when I'm feeling better.
Forget it.
- Did Mrs. Farthing
give you those?
- Yeah.
Pretty seedy, huh?
I didn't know Peter Warren
wrote this kind of stuff.
I don't think
he brags about it.
You can see why
he used a fake name.
I've never heard
of half these people.
You would if you were
from New England.
That guy was a very prominent
minister around here.
Very important guy.
Then one day this book
comes out and tells
the world that he's gay
and that he paid some woman
to have a baby for him,
then the woman goes
and kills herself
and the baby.
Did you know him?
No. It was
way before our time.
Most of it's supposedly
not true anyway.
But don't tell
Mrs. Farthing that.
She makes everyone
read these books.
They're horrible.
But actually I like
his horror stuff.
I've never read any of it.
I used to think those books
looked kind of trashy.
Oh. You know,
I can lend them to you.
You should actually read them
because the first one was
written in your apartment.
Oh, okay. Thanks.
Sure.
[Mrs. Farthing]
Stacy!
See you later. Bye.
Aha.
Good afternoon, milady.
You're looking radiant today.
Thank you, Ted.
How are you?
Still plugging along.
Haven't seen you out
basking in the sun lately.
Oh, I have a new job.
It keeps me indoors a lot.
I'm doing research
on the Internet.
The Internet?
Of course.
Hey.
You want a cactus?
- What?
- It's a cactus.
They grow in the desert.
They don't take much water.
This one's been
in my back pocket
for I don't know how long.
You want it?
I don't think so.
I'm with you.
I can't seem to
stay away from plants.
Somebody
drops in for a visit,
they give me plant.
My nephew and his wife drive
all the way across country
from Amarillo.
They smuggle me a plant.
Comes my birthday,
all I ever get is plants.
Really?
I'm learning
to hate them.
Trees, yes,
but houseplants,
they shrivel up,
they get bugs and
spiders on them.
Who'd want them things
in their house?
And plus, our apartments
don't get very much sunlight.
You know, you're right.
Maybe that's why
mine are all dying.
What's that you're reading,
Ms. Kathryn?
Oh, uh, Peter Warren.
Oh.
That rattlesnake.
Not a good neighbor?
Good enough neighbor.
Just a bad man.
Really? How so?
I introduced him
to a friend of mine.
- Didn't end so good.
- Did something happen?
Well, it seemed like Warren
wanted to make it big
by exposing folk''
dirty laundry.
[sighs]
My friend worked
for this minister.
I suppose Mrs. Farthing
has forced that book
on you by now.
She has.
My friend Kurt looked after
the church grounds.
It paid chicken feed.
Time come when he needed
some cash real bad,
so he let himself
sell Warren
one hell of a story.
Anonymously,
of course.
There were things
going on at that rectory.
Nothing criminal.
Just stuff ordinary folks
might not expect
of a minister.
I read all about it,
but I didn't quite
understand it.
The reverend was gay,
but he paid some woman
to have his baby?
It didn't make
a whole lot of sense to me.
Warren exaggerated some.
Doesn't matter if
it was true or not.
It ruined the reverend.
Kurt never
forgave himself.
That's terrible.
That book did in
a lot of people.
Guilt can be
a real killer.
Yeah.
Say, Ms. Kathryn,
now that you're single,
maybe the two of us
could get together
for dinner and a drink
and some good talk.
Uh...
I think it's probably
a little too soon for me
to start dating again, Ted,
but thank you.
You're very sweet.
Well, you can't blame
an old fool for trying.
I'm going to check my mail,
then I'm off to the races.
- Good night.
[water running]
[Kathryn screams]
[screaming]
Oh, my God!
What's wrong, Kathryn?
Th-There's... m-m-man
in the show--
- Is it your boyfriend?
- No! Old man! Old man!
Are you all right?
Are you hurt?
[stammering]
Hello? Hello?
[gasping]
There's nobody
in there.
There's no one
in there. It's okay.
No! In the shower!
I didn't see anyone
in there. It's okay.
Just relax. Calm down.
Let's go to
Mrs. Farthing's place,
and we'll just relax.
- No one's in there?
- Nobody's in there.
Come on.
It's freezing.
[whimpering]
It's okay.
You're still
not well.
- It's okay.
- No, I'm all right.
Oh, God.
[whimpering]
I swear.
Nobody's in there.
Let's lie down
on the bed.
It's okay.
[tapping]
How you doing?
- Fine. Yourself?
- Not too bad.
I just hope the next time
you decide to go streaking,
you'll invite me.
[laughs]
How about a drink
with an old man?
I promise to be
a perfect gentleman,
and I won't
offer you a plant.
Um...
I'd love one.
A drink, not a plant.
- My place or yours?
- Yours. Definitely yours.
So, no union card,
no work.
That's mainly why
I retired from the rodeo.
Do you miss it?
I miss the crowds,
the cheering.
I miss the pretty ladies
who used to come up after,
looking to get acquainted.
But the ground got too hard,
my head got bonked
one too many times.
So I went roaming
God knows where.
I ended up here.
What brought you to Maine?
I come for the waters.
Time does go by,
but look at me.
I'm 76 years old,
I'm sitting here drinking
with a beautiful woman
young enough to be
my granddaughter.
Now, you promised
to be a gentleman.
Don't mind me,
Miss Kathryn.
I'm just a harmless
dirty old man.
Though you're the first lady
to come in this place since--
well, since the last time
Mrs. Farthing forced
spring-cleaning on me.
I had some
good times though.
Hold on a second.
You know, after you
got me talking about
my old friend Kurt,
I dug out these photos.
Sentimental, you know.
Oh, now, I know
I just saw one of him
in here somewhere.
- Is Kurt still alive?
- No.
He drank himself
to death.
That thing
with the minister.
That's terrible.
After Reverend Martin
hanged himself,
Kurt lost it.
I suppose I should feel
sort of responsible too,
but what's done is done.
- It's not your fault.
- That's what I told Kurt.
Kurt come here a day or two
before the book came out
and begged Warren to stop it.
Warren said
it was too late.
Kurt tried,
but what could he do?
I told him to leave his guilt
in that room with Warren
and get on with his life.
And did Warren ever
say anything to you about it?
Same thing he always said:
"The truth must come out."
I always wondered why,
if he was so concerned
about the truth,
he didn't use his own name
on those exposés.
And whatever happened
to the woman--
the woman who was paid
to have the reverend's baby?
So she claimed.
So it wasn't even true?
Reverend Martin was
as gay as a wind chime.
Baby was probably
some biker's.
But that crazy lady was obsessed
with the reverend and wanted
to be part of his life,
even if it was only
in Warren's book.
She even threatened
to kill Kurt if he told
anybody it wasn't true.
But why did she
kill the baby?
Psychotic.
She wouldn't
let up on Kurt,
Warren or Martin.
If she hadn't killed herself,
she'd still be here
hounding somebody.
Oh, wait a minute.
There it is.
That's Kurt and me.
We went to the races with
a few other old fogies.
Even won a few bucks.
That was the last time
I saw him smile.
You know, Ms. Kathryn,
Mrs. Farthing never even
let out that room
till you came along.
I think you kind of
brighten the place up.
I have to go.
Already?
- Oh, Ms. Kathryn, I'm sorry.
- No.
- I promised to be a gentleman.
- You were. Thank you.
Thank you.
Good night.
Night.
[click]
- Hi. It's me.
- Rick.
I hope you're doing okay.
I just wanted to call
and see how you were doing.
[click]
[woman]
Leave.
[rings]
[beeps]
[woman]
Kathryn?
Oh, my God.
It's me, Mom.
- Mom!
- [high-pitched tone]
[woman]
Keep your mouth shut!
[rings]
Kathryn, it's time to leave.
You will stay here
and keep your mouth shut!
[rings]
Kathryn?
Mom, I'm sorry.
There is nothing for you
to feel sorry about, dear.
This guilt isn't yours.
It's time for you
to leave it behind.
[rumbling]
Kathryn!
Stupid damn keys.
Never could get
these keys to work.
Kathryn, open the door!
Kathryn, go!
I love you.
- [knocking]
- [Mrs. Farthing]
Kathryn, are you there?
Kathryn, answer me!
[Kathryn]
I can take one more question
before the signing begins.
- Yes?
- Ms. Bennett.
Your first book focused
on Peter Warren's
earlier career,
writing kiss-and-tell books
under the name of
"Monty Briggs."
Now you write about
Warren himself,
saying that the inspiration
for his best-selling
horror novels
comes from
his own delusions,
that he is plagued by
the guilt-ridden ghosts
of people whose trust
you claim he betrayed.
What do you say to
your critics who feel
that your current work
is just as exploitative as
the supermarket paperbacks
that you criticize Warren
for having written?
The truth must come out.
Captions by VanKirk Media
www.vankirk-media.com