♪ ♪
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
Just need your signature.
What are these?
Powers of attorney.
Account transfers.
The deed to this place.
You're signing over
the family business to me.
Now why would I do that?
Because it's time.
- You're not ready.
- We've been over this.
I know it, and your
mother knows it.
You're weak, dad.
People used to fear you.
We used to own cops;
we used to own politicians.
We ran entire neighborhoods.
We don't anymore because
no one is afraid of you.
You're still afraid of me.
♪ [OMINOUS MUSIC] ♪
I'm gonna give you a choice.
Retire, or forced retirement.
♪ [OMINOUS MUSIC] ♪
[SIGNING]
♪ ♪
- Thanks, dad.
- Son, listen to me.
All this was always
gonna be yours.
Just needed more time.
A few more years you'd
take over-
[GUNSHOT]
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
I'm not afraid of you.
♪ ♪
[CROW CALL]
[GUN SHOT]
♪ ♪
ALDEN: Wayne, where
the heck you going?
Come on, slow down
for Pete's sake.
♪ ♪
[GUN SHOT]
Wayne, I'm getting
tired of this!
[GUNSHOTS]
♪ ♪
I'm gonna catch you
sooner or later.
Shoot.
[YELLING]
There's some pretty good coffee
at the station!
♪ ♪
C'mon, Wayne!
Wayne, this is getting old.
Dangit, Wayne, sneakers
ain't scared.
Okay, we got our exercise. Stop!
♪ ♪
Hey Wayne, we can do
this all day you know?
How about this?
How about I take out the
handcuffs, leave 'em here,
you put 'em on yourself.
[ENGINE STARTS]
[FOOT STRUGGLING]
[GUNFIRE, RICOCHETS]
♪ ♪
[TRACTOR ACCELERATING]
[SIGHS]
ALDEN, V/O: So there I am
thinking maybe I've
tempted fate long enough;
I've had a good run.
Mm-hmm.
So what really happened?
♪ ♪
[TRACTOR CRUSHES WOOD]
Huh, looks okay.
♪ ♪
Thank y'all for comin'
out tonight.
Now, I realize that my
retirement may come as a shock
to some, seeing as how I'm still
so young and spry.
But the decision was made easier
by the fact that both counties
are in such capable hands.
Which reminds me y'all gotta get
out and vote for Dante Hill
next month in that special
election.
Now, those of you who know me
well realize that I have mixed
feelings about all this.
- No kidding.
But I am looking forward to
having a little time to do
some fishing and learn how
to play the guitar better.
And from what Skooter says
I guess
we're gonna play golf, really?
It has been an honor to serve
Maksville county
these past 30 years.
This is a place where I met
my wife and raised my daughter.
I made friends.
I made friendships that I think
are gonna last a lifetime.
And more recently I've
come to realize that...
I can still truly care
about somebody.
I couldn't have done
it without you.
So, thank you.
[APPLAUSE]
I need a drink.
Nice speech.
Well, I meant everything I said.
Appreciate the vote of
confidence.
- And the endorsement.
- Not that you needed any
seal of approval; you're
running unopposed.
Well, you did put the Prattlers
in jail for me.
There is a certain Wayne
Prattler who still needs
your attention.
- On the top of my to-do list.
I'm gonna grab a beer.
You want anything?
I'm fine, thanks.
Hey... I have something
to give you.
My dad came home
with it one day.
I never learned how to play.
Johnny Cash?
- Had it authenticated.
Are you sure you wanna
give this to me?
I mean you got it
from your father!
He claims he won it
at a poker game.
Makes me like it even more.
I'm not sure what to say, Jo.
Thank you.
[PHONE VIBRATES]
Sheriff Porter.
Okay, I'll be right there.
A silent alarm's going off at
the check cashing place on Main.
Hey, I can come along.
Alden you can't leave
your own party.
Well, it's probably
a false alarm.
We'll be back before
anyone knows we're gone.
♪ ♪
[ENTRANCE BELLS
JINGLE]
[CLATTERING IN STORE]
♪ ♪
I use that same technique when
my TV's on the fritz.
JO: Sheriff's department.
Slowly raise your hands
above your head.
Now stand up and turn around.
♪ ♪
Dad?
- Hey Joanna Banana.
♪ ♪
ALDEN: Sit down.
JOANNE: We had an agreement.
You don't work where I work
and I don't arrest you!
I'm sorry, angel, but I
have a gambling debt.
You've had one since the day
I was born.
Yeah, but this time I owe
the Atlanta Syndicate.
Last I heard you were a member
of the Syndicate.
I retired, or at least
I tried to.
I don't know if you've
heard but Saul Dalton
took his own life.
Yeah, we get the news here dad.
I had an installment plan
all worked out.
But when Zed took over...
he quadrupled my payments.
JO: How much do you owe?
Hair shy of a quarter
million. [WHISTLE]
- What?
- I mean, honestly, who'd have thunk
Tom Brady could keep it up?
I decided I better come out
of retirement before
Zed breaks my thumbs.
But, since I've been out
of the game for a while...
As an insurance policy, you
decided to commit your crime
in my county...
Yeah, I figured it'd be...
smart to have
a get-out-of-jail free card.
[CUFFS TIGHTEN]
You're charging me?
Don't do the crime if you
can't do the time.
He was in and out of
prison for most of my childhood.
When he was around...
Well...
At least it wasn't boring.
FBI raids, skipping town
in the middle of the night...
being his lookout, his alibi.
To me it sounds kinda fun,
sounds interesting.
He did get me a car for
my high school graduation.
That was generous.
It was also stolen.
I spent my prom night
at a police station.
Okay, he's not gonna win
father of the year.
But Jo, he's the only
one you got.
He came to steal from
my county because he knew
I'd cover for him, because that
is what I have always done.
Yeah, with his record he's
looking at years.
Well, at least if he's in prison
Zed Dalton can't expect
him to pay back his debt.
That's a tough one.
Putting your father in prison,
that's one you can't take back.
♪ ♪
ALDEN: Hey,
where'd everybody go?
You expected them to
stick around even after
the guest of honor
ditched his own party?
I had to go check on
a break in with Jo.
I realize that your eyesight
isn't what it once was, but...
did you happen to notice
that there was a big cake
with "Happy Retirement"
written on it?
I don't actually retire
until tomorrow when
I hand in my badge.
And then, what?
Done for good.
Okay.
I gotta wash dishes.
♪ ♪
ALDEN: Can you put
this on my tab?
Thought you retired, Sheriff.
Well, it's my last day but
I gotta fix the hammock up.
[METAL DETECTOR ALARM]
Calvin, you got something
don't belong to you?
What? No...
[THUNK]
Shoot.
[ALARM CONTINUES]
ALDEN: Stop!
♪ ♪
[GRUNTS]
Calvin, Calvin, Calvin...
get up.
You have the honor of being my
very final arrest as a sheriff.
Big whoop.
As a matter of fact, your
grandfather was
my first arrest.
That's kind of poetic justice.
You Prattlers have been giving
me work all these years.
It's amazing, c'mon.
He committed the crime in
my county but I arrested him
in yours; jurisdiction
thing again.
I'll prosecute with pride.
Have you made a decision about
what to do with your dad?
I'm gonna cut him loose.
Dante said he'd watch my county
for a few days, so I can
drive him to Atlanta.
- You're not planning on
negotiating with Zed are you?
Only as a last resort.
Well, then I ought to be there.
I don't want to get
you involved.
And I don't want you dealing
with a syndicate in Atlanta.
I can handle myself,
thank you very much.
I'm sure you can.
C'mon, it's not like I got
anything else to do.
That's because you're retired.
Alden, you can't save the world.
Who says?
[PHONE VIBRATES]
My informant says he's got a
retirement present for me.
♪ ♪
- Hey Bo, what do you got?
- I got a line on where
my cousin Wayne's
been hiding from you.
- Yeah?
- You know that abandoned trailer
on the edge of Noon's Creek?
- Yeah, sure.
He'll be there till tomorrow.
Where after that?
Nowhere.
Claims he's not intimidated
by you
once you become a civilian.
Well, it's a shame
that all Prattlers
aren't as honest as you are.
You do realize my cousin ain't
the type to go quiet, right?
Wouldn't have it any other way.
♪ ♪
[TRAILER SHAKING]
[GRUNTING]
♪ ♪
Son of a-
Hey Wayne!
Ah... what are
you doing?
Let's call it poetic justice.
I gotta talk to you.
♪ ♪
Prattler's your CI.
One of the good ones.
DANTE: I didn't realize there
was such a thing.
It's an exclusive club.
I bet.
♪ ♪
Listen Alden, um...
It's been a real pleasure
to serve under you.
I hope I can make you proud.
I have no doubt.
Here.
[SIGHS, LAUGHS]
This is really hard.
♪ ♪
Well, I guess that's it.
Good luck.
♪ ♪
Well, it's about time.
So, what's the plan?
Try to clean up
your latest mess,
without getting us both killed.
♪ ♪
Four, three, two, one...
Noon.
[GRUNTING]
[WHISTLING]
Well, that was fun.
♪ [PLAYING GUITAR] ♪
♪ ♪
MADDIE: Atlanta?
You remember Nat Prattler, right?
- Yes, I do.
Nat went away to college,
he didn't fall off the planet.
Well, anyway he's graduating.
Gonna go down there and help him
get out of his dorm room
and maybe take a look at the
city while I'm there.
You know, it's not like I got
a job to worry about anymore.
That sounds so nice.
Maybe I should get somebody
to watch the diner and I could
go and help you guys.
Oh, well um...
actually I'm planning on
crashing on his floor
to save money on a hotel.
Meh, I've slept on
a floor before.
Yeah, but he's-
Well, he's got a couple of
roommates so it might be...
Uh no, no...
fair enough.
You know, I'm actually...
kind of relieved.
- About what?
I just...
Okay, honestly I expected
you to keep trying to
find excuses to do police work.
Well, it's nice to know
I can still surprise
you once in a while.
I'll see you later.
♪ ♪
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
Congratulations, Sheriff.
[CHUCKLING]
Thanks, Tom, but it's not
official until
next month's election.
That's all right,
that's all right.
Man oh man.
This place brings back
some memories.
I bet, you were...
Alden's deputy for what
five years?
Six, yeah.
Used to think someday I'd end
up where you're sitting.
Well, seeing that car that
you drive, I'd say that
you made the right decision
getting your realtor's license.
Maybe, but...
I'd definitely be lying if
I said I didn't miss it.
So, what can I help you with?
Well, I just thought I'd swing
by, give the place one last look
before I head up to Atlanta.
The housing market's
going crazy, so...
Hey listen, if you're ever in
the market you let me know.
Thank you, but between my car
payments and student loan debts.
No pressure.
Just thought I'd make the offer.
If I ever need anything
you'll be the first call.
Pfft, yeah.
♪ ♪
[VIDEO GAME SOUND EFFECTS]
[KNOCKING]
Hey, Nat.
What the?
Alden...
what are you doing here?
Well, you said I
should come visit.
Yeah, uh, but I'm moving out.
I know, I'm here to help.
For sure, yeah.
Is there a problem?
I'm throwing a party tonight.
And you know, having the
sheriff on the guest list,
it's gonna really...
kill the vibe.
I mean, you're in luck,
I'm retired.
- Oh?
- I got some boxes out in
the truck for your textbooks.
- Oh, we use iPads now.
Yeah, right.
[SIGHS]
Well, in the message you said
you have some news for me.
Oh, I do.
I'm afraid you ain't gonna
like the headline, though.
DANTE: Bo said that Johnny
Prattler's out of prison.
ALDEN: That's impossible; he's
not up for parole for a year.
Yeah, well apparently he ratted
someone out to get
his sentence reduced.
That sounds like John.
DANTE: He's talking about how
he's going to inflict his wrath
all over my county like some
type of redneck super villain.
[ALDEN CHUCKLING]
ALDEN: Look, Dante...
you gotta let him know who's
in charge; who's the new
sheriff in town, literally.
DANTE: Yeah, hey how's your
first official day of
retirement treating you?
It's one big party.
Well, glad somebody's
having a good week.
Say hi to Nat for me.
♪ ♪
CRYSTAL: I appreciate you
coming all this way
to pay your respects.
I'm sorry for your loss.
You and Mr. Dalton were
together a long time.
High school sweethearts.
Let me fix you a bowl.
Oh, no thank you, I ate already.
Nonsense, you are
skin and bones.
Do you remember coming
out here as a little girl?
My dad and Mr. Dalton
would play chess.
I'd play with
the animals outside.
Oh [LAUGHS] I remember
a particularly surly goose
kept picking on the runt
of the flock.
And I spent the entire
afternoon trying to protect it.
[BOTH CHUCKLING]
It's no wonder that you
chose the vocation that you did.
I know your daddy's proud.
Well, he's actually
why I'm here.
I'm not sure if you heard but...
he owes your family
a gambling debt.
I prayed he was keeping
those demons at bay.
Me too.
Well, he and Mr. Dalton
had a payment plan worked out.
I'm sorry Joanne but I don't
have any involvement with
the family business, never have.
You'll have to deal
directly with my son.
Well, the thing is...
I'm concerned...
about what he might do...
if my daddy can't
make his payments.
I know Zed has a reputation.
And granted, some
of it is earned.
But he's not unreasonable.
♪ ♪
I tell you what...
I'll ask Zed to come up
with a plan that is
mutually beneficial
for old time sake.
I would appreciate that.
Rick visited Saul to
the very end.
He would come
and they'd play chess
and Rick would let him win.
[LAUGHS]
He does have a good heart.
Now, eat up before
you waste away.
JOHNNY: She says to me, you
gotta be this high to ride...
[LAUGHTER]
Isn't it a bit early
for you to be drinking Johnny?
Ah, c'mon now you're late.
Boys just throwing me a
get out of jail party.
Still going strong.
Just what did you do
to get an early release?
Well, just 'cause a man
likes to drink from the bottom
of the barrel of bourbon doesn't
mean he doesn't have
friends in high places.
Sure hope that's milk at the
bottom of that bottle, Calvin,
'cause you're still
a juvenile delinquent.
Oh now, that's a sippy cup.
You got anything better
to do than come around here,
harass taxpaying citizens?
- Yeah, we pay your salary.
I'm just here to
deliver a message.
Oh man, I wish you were
here to deliver a pizza.
[LAUGHTER]
Look, if you think that you're
gonna take advantage of me
and my limited experience,
think again...
Boys...
I ain't been out of
the clink for less
than a day and ole
Johnny Law here is just
laying down the law.
I'm serious.
If I catch you so much
as jaywalking...
Oh hey, okay.
Yes sir, acting sheriff.
- Let's go.
- Get your hands off-
Sit down!
You're gonna wanna take
your hands off of him.
♪ [OMINOUS MUSIC] ♪
I said, sit down.
♪ ♪
Well, look who's growing up.
Alright.
Don't you worry boy.
♪ ♪
Just so we're clear, you're not
here on any official capacity.
I have no legal authority
outside my county.
I'm not wearing a wire.
I wish you could've come to me
first instead of feeling
the need to go behind
my back to my mama.
I meant no disrespect; I'd been
meaning to pay her a visit
since your father's passing.
I know she appreciated that.
She also asked if I'd consider
relaxing your father's payment
schedule.
Will you?
I can do one step further.
I can forgive his
debt completely.
And what would he need to do?
Jo...
You on the other hand.
What's the name of Van Zandt's
guy we got out of prison?
Johnny Prattler.
If Mr. Prattler were to
re-establish my family's
business dealings in
your county, well...
all I'd ask is that you
be a little less competent
at your job.
- No.
I swore an oath of office
and I can't break it.
Yes, you can.
Otherwise your father...
♪ ♪
I can't tell you
how hard it is grieving
the loss of your father.
Zed, I'm not about to
abandon my morals for
some wanna-be gangster who
wears way too much cologne.
Let go of me.
- Go find her father.
Break his knee caps.
[PUNCHING, GROANS]
♪ ♪
Get your hands off her.
Have we met?
ALDEN: No.
But in a city like this there's
always somebody like you.
Until there ain't.
C'mon Jo.
- Tell your father,
I'll be seeing him around.
That goes for you too.
♪ ♪
Hey, what are you doing here?
Saving your bacon.
My bacon wouldn't have
needed saving had I not
listened to you and
kept my dad locked up.
And speaking of not listening I
told you not to come to Atlanta.
Look, I'm not the kind of guy
who's gonna sit around when
I got a friend in trouble.
- Or sit around in general.
And what's that
supposed to mean?
Oh, admit it you were
retired for a day and
already bored to death!
- Boy, you know everything, don't ya?
I just...
I didn't want to get you
involved in my mess.
Look, Jo, I can handle
guys like Zed.
Maybe, but my dad can't.
♪ ♪
[HANDCUFFS RATTLE]
You're under arrest.
- What did I do?
- Jaywalking.
Are you serious about that?
C'mon.
- Absolutely.
Okay, listen I hear
you loud and clear, I do.
The problem is I just didn't
care for your attitude too much
back there at the bar.
- Oh...
No, you misunder-
Me and Alden, we used to just
joke around with each other.
I'd say I'd shoot him and he'd
say he'd throw me in jail.
Just throw away the keys.
So, it's kind of like hazing.
- Yes, exactly like hazing!
You will not regret this,
I promise you.
I already do.
Yeah, you have a nice day now.
RICK: You pointed
a gun at him?
ALDEN: His men had their
hands on your daughter.
I appreciate you looking after
her, and you trying
to look after me.
But instead of a prison
sentence I got a death sentence.
Oh, Zed's not gonna kill ya.
He'd never get his money back.
What I owe is nothing
compared to his reputation.
Yeah, I've seen that
samurai stuff.
But in my experience
people who try to be
intimidating rarely are.
- Zed Dalton's the exception
to the rule.
- Huh.
- He won't let this slide.
- Which is why I gotta
take him out before
he takes me out.
Whoa, dad, you're not
killing anyone.
No, I don't mean it that way.
I'm no rat, but I
know things about Zed.
Things the FBI would be
very interested in hearing.
BOTH: Like?
Like he murdered his daddy.
♪ ♪
I'd come by and play chess
with Saul every week.
I'd gone to the bathroom when
I heard him arguing with Zed.
[GUN SHOT]
He signed the power of attorney,
Zed didn't need to kill him.
I wonder why he did it.
Because he's a
sadistic psychopath.
And the police weren't
the least bit suspicious?
Saul had dementia, so the notion
of suicide wasn't a stretch.
From what I hear they
barely investigated.
Well, it's too late
for an autopsy,
not that the word of a
career criminal carries
much weight with the FBI.
- Not to mention the feds
aren't interested unless
they can seize his assets.
Saul owned a baseball team,
so that office is legit.
But there's evidence in there
linking the family to
organized crime.
- How do you know?
When Saul's mind started going
he began keeping
records of everything.
Between the safe and computer
there's more than enough
to get the FBI's attention.
Except they need probable
cause to obtain a warrant.
What if I just gave them
the evidence?
You can't give them
what you don't have.
I can if I break in and take it.
You're not committing
a felony even if it is
against a crime boss.
- Hypothetically,
if we did...
- We?
Do you think you can do it?
I mean from what I just
witnessed...
I'm a bit rusty, granted...
- W-w...
If we got caught none of this
evidence would work in court.
And what about security guards
and an alarm system?
- I know the code.
- Assuming Zed hasn't changed it.
And when do you know the first
thing about computers.
I don't.
Yeah, but you do, Jo.
You keep sending me emails.
That doesn't make
me Mark Zuckerberg.
I'm a computer science major.
♪ ♪
Nat, the mask is
beautiful, lose it.
♪ ♪
Rick...
Oh, for Pete's sake.
I can do this, I can do this.
You've got five seconds
and then we're out of here.
Four... three...
Go, go, go!
[DOOR CLOSES]
[BEEPING]
♪ ♪
Rick...
I can't believe I have
a trig midterm tomorrow
and you have be hacking
into a killer's computer.
[BEEPING]
I got this.
I know how you feel,
lawman to felon in 48 hours.
[BEEPING STOPS, SIGHS]
Curse of fat fingers.
You got anything?
♪ ♪
[BUTTONS BEEP]
Rick: First try, I still got it.
Where did you...
get all of this?
Criminal informant, he worked
for the syndicate for decades.
- And you trust him?
- Not really, he's my dad.
Okay, just so I got this
straight...
a sheriff's criminal father
is willing to testify to seeing
Zed Dalton murder his father?
In exchange for immunity and
witness protection.
Never thought when I woke
up this morning that I'd
be in the middle of
a Shakespearean tragedy.
- Welcome to my life.
- Yeah.
Mount up!
Okay.
How's it going, your first
couple of days as
interim sheriff?
Well, I mean, just the usual
Prattler nonsense.
Yeah, goes with the territory.
Yeah, I had to respond to
a B&E but other than that
it's been pretty uneventful.
Oh, where's Jo?
She said she had to go
down to Atlanta to handle
some business.
Police business?
Uh, I assume so, but
she didn't say.
♪ ♪
And then there were none.
[DISH CLINKS]
How long you gonna
make me do this?
Till I feel you're
properly punished.
The punishment does
not fit the crime.
Excuse me, what did you say?
Maddie, put the sprayer down
before somebody gets wet.
Okay wait, let me get
this straight.
You feel like you're
the victim here?
I didn't do anything wrong!
You lied to me.
It was a sin of omission.
Did I fail to disclose
certain items
on my itinerary? Yes.
Did I actually lie to you,
I don't think so.
[SPRAYING]
Ah, hey!
- One day!
- Hey, c'mon Maddie stop!
That's how long you
can stay retired?
It wasn't police business;
I was just trying to help Jo.
Okay, look.
I... I'm just not gonna
be able to do this Alden.
My father died in
the line of duty. I-
I won't do it again.
- I understand, I understand.
I understand.
This is it; I'm done.
My police business is all over.
I'm officially, officially
retired.
Actually I'm going to
play golf with the guys.
I promise, I promise it's over.
So...
I know it's tradition for
the sheriffs to meet here...
You sit on your side of
the line and I sit on mine.
Right, but...
some traditions
were meant to be broken.
You want to stop coming here?
No, no, but if and when Maddie's
able to sell.
Well, I did try that
new bistro the other night.
On a date?
No, my softball team went
there after our game.
I've been wanting
to try that place.
Well, we can go together.
Oh...
If and when Maddie's
able to sell.
Right.
How's your food?
Delicious.
Best burger I've ever had.
Oh, great, glad to hear it.
♪ ♪
SKOOTER: Really improved my
stance, yeah. A little bit Nicholson,
a little bit Hayden. ALDEN: All
right. SKOOTER: That's what he said.
ALDEN: Look, I'm almost
finished, I'll be right over.
I'm gonna have to borrow
another ball.
How many balls have you lost?
- Ah, who's counting?
- Fourteen.
[ALL LAUGH]
Maddie got an offer
on the diner.
Oh hey, that's great!
Yeah, I was beginning to think
it was never gonna sell.
Does this mean you two will be
hitting the road in an RV?
It looks that way, pretty soon.
Well dang, I guess there goes
your application for
a membership out here.
- ALDEN: Me?
[ALL LAUGHING]
♪ ♪
[TIRES SCREECH]
BURGLAR: Hands, hands!
Let me see 'em!
You, open the register!
♪ ♪
So, the thieves disarmed the
glass break sensors to avoid
setting off the silent alarms.
Yeah, you're definitely dealing
with professionals.
You think that word's gotten
out that there's an
inexperienced sheriff?
[PHONE VIBRATES]
Hold that thought.
Deputy... Interim Sheriff Hill.
Okay.
So, there's a car on fire
down by Chapman River.
May be your getaway car.
Yeah, let's check it out.
[FIRE BLAZES]
Uh, I'll run the plates and
see who they stole it from.
There's no need.
It's my car.
[GUNFIRE]
So, what are you wanting?
[PHONE RINGS]
Hey...
- JO: Alden...
we're pinned down
and taking fire!
Where are you?
I'll be right there.
SHOOTER: C'mon, let's get
outta here!
Wait, wait.
I think it stopped.
MADDIE: Alden?
Say "hello" to the guy
who's gonna buy me
out of this place.
♪ ♪
ZED: Alden.
JO: No doubt, Zed's crew
is behind this.
The fact that he used Maddie
as his alibi is just his way
of twistin' the knife.
- Why steal my car?
- Send a message.
- Sorry you got caught
in our crossfire.
- How am I supposed to catch
a crime boss and I don't
even have a deputy?
Well, between this and the robbery
he's probably got what he wants.
He's headed back to the city.
- And if he's not? - I got you.
I'll talk to Maddie, make sure
she doesn't sell him the diner.
Then, I'll look tomorrow make
sure he's not hanging around.
DANTE: I appreciate that.
If you want my two cents
he mentioned Johnny Prattler,
which means Johnny's involved.
Definitely knows how
to steal a car
and shoot a gun.
He once sold out his mother just
to avoid a night in jail.
He might be willing
to turn on Zed.
Yeah.
♪ ♪
Thanks for doing that.
I'll let you know how
things go with Johnny.
No sign of Zed.
- I'd be surprised
if he stuck around.
- What's even more frustrating
is we've been tailing Johnny for
the last six hours and
he hasn't so much as loitered.
Does littering count
as a parole violation?
Works for me.
[SIGHS]
Are we even following
the right guy?
JO: He's a Prattler.
He's bound to break the law
sooner or later.
Well, hopefully it's sooner
because I'm getting hangry.
Depending how things go
maybe we could...
try that bistro later tonight?
You mean like,
after we get off shift?
[WHISTLING]
Hey...
My faith in humanity
may have just been restored.
Well, you not only
let me down Johnny,
but also the Boy
Scouts of America.
What did I do now?
Last I checked stealing
a truck is against the law.
Yeah, well last time I checked
you can't steal your own truck.
Look at what I got.
[GASP] It's the keys!
It's registered in his name.
What a coincidence that
you two just showed up
at the right time.
Is it me or does it feel like
we're getting played?
Maybe Johnny's smarter
than we thought.
We're dumber.
The alarm at the
station is going off.
[ALARM BLARING]
♪ [SUSPICIOUS] ♪
[ALARM]
JO: Clear.
♪ ♪
[METAL DETECTOR ALARM]
Calvin!
Later gator!
You gotta be kiddin' me!
You can't arrest me,
you ain't a sheriff no more.
I don't have to be sheriff;
I can make a citizen's arrest.
Yeah okay, well then I'm arresting
you for assault. Yeah, that's right.
You and I have the same
amount of power.
[PHONE RINGING]
You're nobody just like me.
Hello?
Yeah, I'll be right there.
Get out of jail free.
DANTE: Weapons, computers...
everything of value seems
to be accounted for.
What about the evidence
cabinets?
DANTE: It wasn't tampered with.
Well, whoever it was must've
got spooked by the alarm.
REPORTER: While Maksville
suffers the brunt of a crime
wave, this ex-deputy seems
ill-prepared for.
And at this time unfortunately
we're not sure who's responsible
for breaking into the
location that presumably
should be the most secure in
the entire county.
Well, I suppose it's good that
I'm, uh, running unopposed
because I don't think that I
would vote for me right now.
Hey, we'll figure this out.
...belonged to interim Sheriff
Hill who...
Not having a deputy,
I could really use your help.
I really wish I could,
but I can't.
...can I get a comment about
how eventful it's
been since you've taken office?
Anything?
NAT: Appreciate you letting me
crash while I get settled.
ALDEN: Of course.
Something smells good.
You can cook?
Family recipe. I think my
grandpa picked it up in prison.
Did you eat?
-  I have
but I wouldn't say no to
a small bowl of that.
Oh just so you know, me and
Skooter are
going fishing tomorrow so if
you head out,
make sure you lock up.
- Got it.
You worried about the new guy
next door? Seemed intense.
What? The Miller place sold?
Yeah, the uh...
new owner came by.
He asked about you actually.
♪ [TENSE MUSIC] ♪
He said he wanted to speak with
you
about his family's
business dealings.
[BOWL SLIDES]
Save this for me.
♪ [TENSE MUSIC] ♪
[FOOTSTEPS]
[COCKS RIFLE]
[THUD]
Ah!
Rucker, stop roughhousing and
invite in our guest.
Checkmate.
I can't tell if you're with the
welcome wagon,
or you're here to rob me.
Lucky you're holding that gun.
Well, now I'm not.
RUCKER: Nice try... trick me into
hitting you... arrest me for assault.
As someone recently pointed out,
I'm retired.
I'm a nobody just like you.
I believe the man is
giving you his blessing.
Nah, I'm too classy to hit a
senior citizen.
[THUDDING, PUNCHING]
RUCKER: Ah! My other eye!
You know, I can't quite figure
out what your game is.
My game?
I'm playing chess while you're
playing checkers?
I ain't playing anything.
Like I said, I'm retired. I'm
just a nobody.
That didn't stop you
back in Atlanta.
Move in next door so I have to
keep
looking over my shoulder, huh?
Not a nice feeling when someone
comes into your space uninvited.
You just enjoy your space as
much as you can right now
because I got a feeling pretty
soon you're gonna be
residing in an eight by ten
cell.
I wouldn't be so sure.
Witnesses have a bad habit of
not showing up to my
trial dates.
Speaking of dates...
don't you have a daughter
about my age?
You come anywhere near Ember,
you're gonna wish you hadn't.
♪ [TENSE MUSIC] ♪
What's a nobody like you
gonna do about it?
You know what I noticed
when I first got here?
Nothing.
No helicopters.
No surveillance teams.
No FBI.
Back in the city, Feds are
everywhere I look, whereas here
all I gotta worry about is
some sheriff who's still
wet behind the ears.
I can do whatever I want so I've
decided to try my hand at being
a big fish in a small pond.
And it's all thanks to you.
I bet you're starting to wish
you still had a badge, huh?
♪ [TENSE MUSIC] ♪
All right.
Let him go, Granddad's gotta
make his tee time.
[LAUGHS]
♪ [TENSE MUSIC] ♪
[CHUCKLES]
You sure about this?
- You can't tell Maddie.
[PICKS UP BADGE]
♪ [TENSE MUSIC] ♪
Considering his obsession with
chess,
I think we can assume that he's
got more moves planned.
Well I'm sure he didn't factor you
getting back into the game into his plan.
ALDEN: I think we should tail
him. I'll keep an eye on him
from my place and you guys take
up a position
down the road in case he moves.
Well, first I gotta head
downtown.
There was a report of a mugging.
- Yeah.
And I was thinking I'd
talk to Crystal Dalton again.
- Yeah?
- Zed's always been especially
fond of his mom.
I have an idea how we might
capture his queen.
CRYSTAL: I don't understand
how this situation got to this.
Zed told me that he offered you
a fair deal.
It wasn't a deal,
it was an ultimatum...
either I go on the take or my
father takes a bullet
to the back of the head.
Well...
at least now I understand
why Rick lied.
Lied?
About seeing Zed shoot
his Daddy.
Mrs. Dalton, my father's
telling the truth.
Well, Zed swears he had nothing
to do with it.
It's funny I...
[SIGHS]
well I have a history of coming
to my father's rescue.
And Zed has a reputation of
running to you when he
needs help...
like that time he didn't get
into the college of his choice
and you wanted to help arrange
for my Dad to dig up dirt
on the Dean of Admissions.
[SIGHS]
And when blackmail didn't work,
you had him drive the Dean
out into the woods and dig his
own shallow grave at
gunpoint which, not
surprisingly, did the trick.
If I didn't know better,
I'd say you were trying
to blackmail me!
I'm merely pointing out you're
more invested
than you'd realized.
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACH]
I'm sorry, I didn't realize
you had company.
That's fine, darling.
Can I get you anything?
No, we're good.
Fine.
[FOOTSTEPS]
CRYSTAL:
What is it that you want?
Convince Zed to return to
Atlanta and stories like that
won't come up during my
father's deposition.
I have a counteroffer.
Convince your Dad that
he's getting old,
like Saul was getting old.
Old people forget things.
Why would he agree to that?
Forgive and forget.
Your Daddy forgets what he saw,
and I'll see to it that his
debts are forgiven.
And that Zed never does business
anywhere near your county again.
Mrs. Dalton, I can't let
a man get away with murder.
♪ [TENSE MUSIC] ♪
By the end, my husband was
a shell of the man I married.
He was angry and depressed.
And it was only going
to get worse.
If I can live with what Zed did,
you should be able to as well.
♪ [TENSE MUSIC] ♪
[KICKS]
Hyah!
[KICKS AGAIN]
Are you in position yet?
No, I'm still downtown.
Look I've been here an hour,
I don't know what's going on.
There's been 3 break-ins and
2 robberies; I'm in over my head
here.
Well it can't be Zed and his
guys, they're still here.
Are you able to come down
and give me a hand?
I'd rather stay with Zed.
[KICKS]
Hyah!
DANTE: Alden look,
I could really use your help.
I'll be right there.
[GLASS SHATTERS,
CAR ALARM SOUNDS]
♪ [TENSE MUSIC] ♪
ALDEN: All I can figure is that
Zed's trying to keep you busy.
DANTE: Well, it's working.
ALDEN: Yeah. Calvin!
DANTE: Who authorized you to
put those up?
CALVIN: Why do I gotta tell you?
ALDEN: Cause putting those up on
private property is vandalism.
Heh. Great picture.
Johnny said he give me 20
bucks if I
hung 'em around town.
Can I go now?
CALVIN: Lucky for you,
I ain't old enough to vote.
Between Tom's experience and my
bad press-
[SCOFFS] There's a reason
Tom's a former deputy.
♪ [TENSE MUSIC] ♪
Look, I always knew that
Tom was dirty,
but I never had any evidence.
Once I got some,
I forced him to resign.
So if Zed's backing Tom then
that would explain why Zed's
busing in all those people to
drive in the crime rate.
Yeah, they stay here a month,
they can vote!
He couldn't flip Jo so he's
coming after me.
Here... the thing he doesn't
know is that you got
the dirt on Tom even
before the campaign starts.
And where do I keep this dirt?
[DRAWER SLIDING]
Everything's gone.
You didn't change the locks
after Tom left?
We changed the ones outside,
but not everything in here.
So the reason for the break-in
was the evidence against Tom.
ALDEN: He's smarter
than I thought.
Hey, something's come up.
Where are you?
JO: I'm heading for
the safe-house.
I need to check on Dad.
ALDEN: Hey look, this sounds
dramatic coming outta my mouth
but make sure you're not
being followed.
More here than meets the eye.
JO: Way ahead of you.
♪ [TENSE MUSIC] ♪
I'm not convinced she
can control Zed.
It's worth the gamble.
Gambling's what got us into
this mess in the first place.
I get out of debt entirely,
and you get rid of Zed.
It's the easy choice.
Yeah, I agree.
I'm just not sure it's
the right choice.
You've come to my rescue more
times than I can count.
Just once,
I want to come to yours.
[DOOR OPENS]
How was fishing?
- It was fine.
I mean we didn't catch much but-
Please stop.
Skooter was here for lunch.
I guess I gotta work
on my alibi.
Please tell me you're
having an affair.
I was doing a little
detective work.
Okay, let me understand this.
You gave up a paycheck
to become a full-time volunteer?
A volunteer? No.
I'm actually back in a official capacity.
- What?!
As a special deputy but just
until I take care of Zed.
There is always gonna be
another Zed.
It's my fault he's here.
Once I put him away, I'll lose
the badge for good.
The badge is irrelevant.
You can't stop being who you
are; you shouldn't have to.
But I can't keep worrying about
whether you're gonna come home.
[FOOTSTEPS RETREATING]
♪ [TENSE MUSIC] ♪
[SAFE HOUSE DOOR OPENS, CLOSES]
[FOOTSTEPS]
EMBER:
Give her the night to cool off,
show up in the morning with
flowers and be ready to grovel.
I'm not sure I can do that.
You don't know how to grovel?
- I was married for years.
I can grovel with the best of
'em.
I'm just not sure I can win her
back while I'm still on the job.
Maddie may be right about it not
mattering.
I'm not sure I can just
turn it off.
But you can maybe tone it down.
I mean I'm sure there was an
adjustment period after Vietnam.
Well there would have been if
I hadn't signed up at the
police academy the week
I got back.
Uh yeah, there was an adjustment
period when
I came back from Afghanistan.
I think I missed both like the
chaos and the routine...
the feeling of what it's like to
serve others, you know?
Being a sheriff is my routine,
my chaos, and my service
all wrapped up in one.
I sure ain't gonna get that
lying on the couch watching TV.
But you could, you know, find a
new passion
like I found at the V.A.
I'm so glad that's worked
out for you.
EMBER: Thanks.
But Dad, if this Zed guy is
worth losing
your relationship over then you
better finish
what you started with him.
10-4.
Hey, I love you.
I love you too.
Bye-bye.
♪ [TENSE MUSIC] ♪
He's got a copy of "The Art of
War" on his desk.
It's all marked up.
It's his playbook.
You can read books on that
gizmo, can't you?
Yeah. Well this is the newest
one too.
They have like different
apps that you can-
Uh, you know I got a little
homework to do, thanks.
Heh.
Yeah.
♪ [TENSE MUSIC] ♪
All warfare is based on
deception.
- Appear weak when we're strong.
- Right.
Except we're anything but.
ALDEN: Zed's had us playing
defense the whole time.
He wouldn't expect us to go
on the offense.
[ALDEN CLICKS HIS TEETH]
Look man, I don't know anything
else other than what
I told you and Alden yesterday.
Well I'm not here to get any
information,
I'm here to give it;
and this time
I'd appreciate it if you didn't
keep it to yourself.
That store that got robbed,
they're getting a shipment
of diamonds in
to replace what they lost.
How do you know this?
JOHNNY: Trust me,
there ain't nothing that happens
in this county
without me knowing about it.
- Okay, we'll look into it.
JOHNNY: Yeah, see
that's the thing... they're uh...
putting in some kind
of fancy new high-tech security
system tomorrow so it's kind of
one of those...
now or never scenarios.
♪ [TENSE MUSIC] ♪
Alright, same as last time,
boys. In and out.
♪ [TENSE MUSIC] ♪
You know the drill.
Open it!
ZED: Interesting.
ALDEN: Hope you don't mind
me letting myself in.
ZED: Mi casa,
Special Deputy Rockwell.
I believe you two are
acquainted.
- Alden.
- Tom.
I guess you forgot about
our deal...
that one where you find a new
vocation and I decide not to let
the citizens know about your
low-life behavior.
Hope you have evidence to
support such
serious accusations.
- Not a lick but I do have this:
I have decided to come out of
retirement,
and run for my old position.
As a new homeowner, I reckon
I can count on your vote.
I'm afraid the recent uptick in
crime has me thinking that the
county could benefit from
some new blood.
Well you see that crime wave is
already on its way down.
Matter of fact, we just arrested
a bunch of criminals
right outside the local motel.
We didn't even have to catch 'em
in the act because they all
had outstanding warrants.
We just shipped 'em back
to Atlanta.
That's the thing about crime,
you never know when it's
gonna strike again.
Actually sometimes you do.
Let's go! Open it!
What's so funny?
Surprise.
[COCKS GUN]
It's okay, Rini.
♪ [TENSE MUSIC] ♪
[POLICE SIREN SQUAWKS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
DANTE: Out of the car!
[TIRES SQUEAL, CRASHES]
[AIRBAG DEPLOYS]
DANTE: Seriously?
I have no control over what my
employees do in their free time.
You're gonna have to find
some new men.
Pawns,
they're meant to be sacrificed.
The game isn't over until
you capture the king.
ALDEN: I don't play checkers
or chess,
I'm a poker man.
I think you just got bluffed.
Ciao.
♪ [TENSE MUSIC] ♪
[DIALING]
[DOOR OPENS]
[FOOTSTEPS]
JOHNNY: Uh, where is
Sheriff Hill?
Oh, he asked me to
speak with you.
Uh-uh. Don't take this
personally but I really
prefer to speak with
Sheriff Hill!
Are you intimidated by women in positions of power, Johnny?
- No.
Have you ever looked up
"Prattler" in the dictionary?
[SCOFFS]
[DICTIONARY THUDS]
"Prattler," it's a noun meaning
someone who talks constantly.
JOHNNY: Aw, come on.
That's fitting considering
your reputation
as a bit of a Chatty Kathy.
Ha-Ha.
Unh-uh.
But today, Johnny, that can keep
you out of prison.
No, no, no, no, no.
See if I...
if I roll on Zed...
I'm dead.
You just sent his crew
into a trap.
I'm pretty sure you're off his
Christmas card list.
Look, I'm sorry for what
happened but I reckon I did
the wrong thing
for the right reasons.
Look, it wasn't your fault.
It wasn't fair of me
to force you to retire.
Nah, you didn't force me
to do anything.
If it weren't for me,
wouldn't you still be sheriff?
Maybe but I've come to terms
with that decision.
I know that you are running
for re-election.
Well let me explain about that-
MADDIE: You know what?
I don't have time for this
conversation right now.
It's dinner rush.
I'm needed inside.
Let me come back
after you close.
I don't think that's
a good idea.
I'd really rather you didn't.
♪ [MELANCHOLY MUSIC] ♪
[SIGHS]
Johnny refuses to testify.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Zed's reputation has
him spooked but at least we
threw a wrench in his plans by
arresting his crew.
Speaking of plans, do you think
that Alden will stick to his...
dropping out of the election
a day before?
Why wouldn't he?
- I don't know,
I just think that
he regrets retiring.
Well maybe but he wouldn't
do that to you.
Smells good. DANTE: I
was meaning to ask you...
whatever happened with that
Keto thing?
Oh, I gave that up a few months
into the job
along with exercising, sleeping,
and pretty much
any semblance of a social life.
I'm glad I know what
to look forward to.
Hopefully you'll have a better
time balancing
it out than I did.
Maybe we can balance
each other out.
♪ [SOFT MUSIC] ♪
I mean I do realize that it
could be really awkward if
things don't go well but you
hated Alden the first couple
months that you were
here and now look.
Are you asking me out?
Yes, I am officially
asking you out.
Plans tonight?
You're looking at it.
It's perfect!
I can't think of a more fitting
first date than lukewarm
takeout at the station with a
Prattler twenty feet away.
Yeah.
Cheers!
♪ [TENSE MUSIC] ♪
[LIGHTER CLICKS OPEN]
[MADDIE TALKS TO HERSELF]
Okay, tickets.
Keys.
[MADDIE JANGLES KEYS]
Lights.
[MADDIE CLICKS LIGHTS OFF]
Ugh! Come on, Maddie,
you're forgetting something.
What are you forgetting?
Oh yeah, oh yeah!
The jukebox,
jukebox, jukebox, jukebox.
MAN: Hurry up, we're supposed
to catch her
while she's still in there!
[GLASS BREAKING]
[FLAMES CRACKLING]
[SPRAYING FIRE EXTINGUISHER]
[MADDIE COUGHING]
[FIRE ENGINE SIREN WAILS]
DISPATCHER: Guys, listen up.
We've got a single flag
with one civilian inside.
It's the rear access.
Rear access.
[FIRE ENGINE SIREN WAILS]
[FIREMEN CHATTERING]
[ENGINE QUICKLY STOPS]
- Is she okay?
- She's fine.
Was it a kitchen fire, what?
No, it was arson.
Someone threw
a Molotov cocktail through the
window and Maddie...
wait, no! Alden!
JO: Alden, wait!
[ENGINE ROARS]
[TRUCK SCREECHES TO A STOP]
[DOOR OPENS, CLOSES]
[ENGINE SLOWS TO A STOP]
[DOOR OPENS]
Howdy, neighbor!
DANTE: Alden, stop!
[PUNCH]
Alden!
[PUNCH, ZED GROANS]
This isn't the way to get him.
I'm glad you're here sheriff
because...
I want to press charges...
I was here in my home...
minding my own business when
your... deputy attacked me.
The way I see it,
you threw the first punch.
You take this thing to court,
I think...
they'll take my word against
yours. ZED: I guess we'll just
have to take this to the court
of public opinion
after I give the local news
the footage from my security
cameras,
and my colleague's cell phone.
MAN: Already sent it.
ALDEN: You know what?
You go ahead and charge me.
It was worth it.
- Was it?
Yeah.
- Because under election bylaws,
you're not permitted to run for
sheriff with a criminal charge
hanging over your head.
I guess your re-election plans
just went up in smoke,
pardon the pun.
Come on, come on, come on.
Y'all have a nice day!
♪ [TENSE MUSIC] ♪
Alden, I'm gonna have to
take your badge.
- This is just what he wants.
- I don't have a choice.
You gonna charge me?
If I don't, Tom Marshall's gonna
think I'm playing favorites.
Have you considered you might be
in over your head?
Yeah.
My career could be dead on
arrival all because you couldn't
accept that yours was over.
- Meaning what?
Alden, part of you wanted this.
You're right.
[SHOVES BADGE INTO
DANTE'S HAND]
I'm done playing by the rules.
[FOOTSTEPS]
[RIFLE CLICKING]
Zed's gonna pay for this,
I promise.
[RIFLE CLICKING]
You mean when you arrest him.
I turned in my badge.
[FLAMES CRACKLING]
Whatever you're thinking about
doing right now,
it is not worth it.
I got no choice.
Of course you do.
You said it yourself:
I am who I am.
I go after guys like Zed.
That's what I've always done.
That's what I'm gonna do now.
[FOOTSTEPS]
[TRUCK DOOR OPENS, CLOSES]
[RIFLE CLICKS]
[GUNSHOT]
[CAMERA FIZZLES OUT]
[FOOTSTEPS]
I'm here to press assault
charges against Alden.
♪ [TENSE MUSIC] ♪
That's fine,
I'll take your statement.
But after that, I'm gonna want
to ask you some questions
about an arson.
♪ [TENSE MUSIC] ♪
ZED: I don't know what I'll have
to offer but...
I'm happy to oblige.
[KNOCKS] Rick, pack up. We're moving locations.
- What's the matter?
There was an incident that Zed
may be involved in.
Did something happen to Joanne?
- No one's been hurt,
we're just being cautious but we
gotta move now.
[SAFEHOUSE DOOR OPENS]
♪ [TENSE MUSIC] ♪
[GUNSHOT]
- Whoa!
- Oh! Oh!
♪ [TENSE MUSIC] ♪
[DOOR OPENS, CLOSES]
[FOOTSTEPS]
ALDEN: You just got back from
pressing charges, huh?
- We're unarmed.
- I realize that.
Even you ain't stupid enough to
take guns to a police station.
[COCKS RIFLE]
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Think about it, Alden.
You kill me,
you destroy your legacy.
Well if I don't,
you're gonna destroy it anyway.
♪ [TENSE MUSIC] ♪
You can't do this,
you're a lawman.
I used to be.
[COCKS RIFLE AGAIN]
DANTE: Alden,
put the gun down.
ALDEN: How'd you find me?
JO: Nat called us,
he was worried about you.
Think about what this
will do to Maddie...
and Ember.
They need you.
I need you.
♪ [TENSE MUSIC] ♪
Your lucky day.
[EXCLAIMS]
Whoo!
I got everything on camera.
I expect him to be charged.
DANTE: He will be.
Never in my wildest dreams did I
think about
sending you to prison.
You did a better job of
punishing
yourself than I ever could have.
JO: You're gonna get a call from
your lawyer.
My father recanted his story;
the FBI are dropping their
charges.
Go back to Atlanta.
ZED: Thank you but
like I told Alden...
I like it here.
I think I'll stick around.
Oh!
[GASPING]
[SHOOTER SPEEDS AWAY]
Rick, can you hear me?
[RICK PANTING]
The jacket stopped the bullet.
RICK: I wanted to take your
offer from the start,
but you...
you know Joanne.
I wish you had come
to me from the first.
It was a mistake.
Well I'm glad you're here now.
I just want to take your offer
and have everything go away.
Oh well that offer
is off the table.
No!
Crystal, I need your help.
Zed sent someone to kill me.
Oh no, it wasn't Zed, darlin'.
♪ [TENSE MUSIC] ♪
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACH]
CRYSTAL: So are we good now?
ZED: Yes, ma'am.
Everything's back on track.
CRYSTAL: Good.
ZED: Okay.
CRYSTAL: I love you.
ZED: I'll call you later, mama.
♪ [TENSE MUSIC] ♪
Get this, my mama put the hit
out on Rick which he somehow
survives and the first thing he
does when he gets out is
show up at her front door to see
if she can help!
[ENGINE ROARS]
♪ [TENSE MUSIC] ♪
See ya, cowboy!
This is interesting.
[ZED CELL PHONE VIBRATES]
Alden, I sincerely hope I'm not
your one phone call.
ALDEN: Zed, I reckon this game's
gone on long enough.
I'm willing to offer you a draw.
And why, after your pathetic
display earlier,
would I accept that?
Because you got played, Zed.
I figured once you thought
I was done,
you'd let your guard down and
get sloppy; I was right.
You know what I think?
I think you're sober now,
and you're trying to save face.
Check under that table.
Just because the FBI's not
listening to your calls
doesn't mean nobody is.
Nice one, Alden.
You almost had me.
Try the little table next to
you.
When I broke in to plant the
bug,
I also installed a camera.
[WHOOSHING SOUND]
You having trouble
with that thing?
NAT: You do realize I broke the
law way less
before you had me go
straight, right? [DOOR OPENS]
You just got back from
pressing charges, huh?
All warfare is based
on deception.
Once we are able to attack,
we must seem unable.
Saying you broke in leaves me
doubtful
you obtained the proper warrant
and without it,
nothing you may have
is admissible.
You might be right if I hadn't
turned in my badge.
As a deputy,
that'd be against the law.
But as a criminal informant,
it makes it legal.
I'm willing to take my chances.
Think about your mom.
What's she gonna think of her
darling baby boy once she
realizes he has implicated her
in conspiracy to commit murder?
Mama puts a hit out on Rick.
♪ [TENSE MUSIC] ♪
So you're offering a draw?
- With a few stipulations.
First, a million dollars in cash
to replace the diner.
That's way more than the
asking price.
Next, you pick up Rick at your
mother's place,
and deliver him to me tonight.
That it?
Last of all...
I want you to leave my county
and never set foot here again.
Sounds more like a win
than a draw.
Suit yourself.
I win, you lose.
Take it or leave it.
♪ [TENSE MUSIC] ♪
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
[VAN'S ENGINE SLOWS TO A STOP]
♪ [TENSE MUSIC] ♪
[VAN'S DOOR CLOSES]
Don't move.
ALDEN: I thought you said
alone and unarmed.
[VAN'S DOOR CLOSES]
[FOOTSTEPS]
All your years on the job,
how is it you never learned to
never trust a criminal?
ALDEN: Where's Rick?
ZED: Back of the van.
So I gotta trust you on that?
I see your predicament there.
Truth is... I was worried this
was another one of your traps.
Look, all I want is that money.
And to pretend I never met you.
Give me the video and we can go
our separate ways.
[CATCHES VIDEO]
How am I supposed to know this
is the only copy?
I guess you're gonna
have to trust me.
[SCOFFS]
The thing is...
I learned to never trust
the word of a lawman.
[COCKS GUN]
-  Okay.
You should have seen it
coming, Alden.
♪ [TENSE MUSIC] ♪
[GUN CLICKS EMPTY]
ALDEN: Actually, I did.
Shoot him!
[OTHER GUN CLICKS EMPTY]
The book says "subdue your
enemy without fighting."
[WHOOSHING SOUND]
You having trouble with
that thing?
NAT: You do realize I broke the
law way less before
you had me go straight, right?
ALDEN: Like I said,
you guys wouldn't take your
weapons
to a police station.
- You're right...
I left my backup in my jeep.
[BULLETS NOT FIRING CORRECTLY]
About that...
he might have been too smart to
testify but Johnny
loves to play with firearms.
JO: Nice work, Johnny.
And now we have you on an
attempted murder charge.
You see, you were 100% correct.
You actually did
walk into another trap.
I think this is what you
call checkmate.
Not quite.
Scarlett!
[VAN'S DOOR OPENS]
♪ [TENSE MUSIC] ♪
Just for your information,
she came with her own weapon.
♪ [TENSE MUSIC] ♪
[FIRING AUTOMATIC RIFLE]
[PAUSING TO RELOAD]
♪ [TENSE MUSIC] ♪
JO: Put it on the ground,
nice and easy.
DANTE: You good?
JO: All clear.
Get the bag!
[RAPID FOOTSTEPS]
[GUN SLIDING]
I'll get Zed.
[RAPID FOOTSTEPS]
[EXHALES]
JO: Let me see those hands.
Slowly.
♪ [TENSE MUSIC] ♪
[RAPID FOOTSTEPS]
[PUNCHING, FIGHTING]
[PUNCH]
[RAPID FOOTSTEPS,
TACKLING HIM]
You should've joined the
football team
instead of the chess team.
♪ [TENSE MUSIC] ♪
ALDEN: Zed!
You ain't got a bulldozer tucked
away in here somewhere, do ya?
[FIGHTING]
[GRUNTING]
Looks like we're in one of those
last man standing situations.
ALDEN: I reckon.
[KICKING]
[GRUNTING]
Are you gonna fight like a man,
or are you gonna keep
pulling that crap?
♪ [TENSE MUSIC] ♪
[KICK, THUD]
[FIGHTING, GRUNTING]
[PUNCHING]
[THUD]
[KICKING, THUD]
[PUNCHING]
[JO WHIMPERING]
[KICKING]
[ALDEN PANTING]
[FIGHTING]
[PUNCHING]
Come on, old man.
[KICKING]
[JO WHIMPERING, CHOKING]
[THUD]
[JO COUGHING]
RICK: Come on, honey. I got ya.
JO: [WHISPERS] Thanks, Dad.
ZED: Just so you know, I could
have waited until Maddie was
gone before I set that fire.
[LIGHTER CLICKS OPEN]
But I made sure she was
still there.
Yah!
[ELBOWING]
[PUNCHING]
[PUNCHING, GRUNTING]
You wanted to be a big fish
in a small pond?
Well you picked the wrong pond.
[HEAD-BUTT, THUD]
♪ [TRIUMPHANT MUSIC] ♪
I am retired.
[EXHALES]
[ALDEN SINGS, PLAYS GUITAR]
♪ WAY OUT HERE ♪
♪ IN THE HILLS
OF NORTH GEORGIA ♪
♪ THE HOMETOWN FOLK,
THEY'RE GONNA TREAT YOU FINE ♪
[POPS CORK, CHEERS]
Yeah! Ladies first.
♪ DO WHAT'S RIGHT, THEY GOT
NO ILL WILL TOWARDS YA ♪
♪ ♪
♪ BUT STAY AWAY
FROM THE COUNTY LINE ♪
♪ ♪
♪ AT 17,
I RAN AWAY FROM MY MAMA ♪
♪ A COUNTRY GIRL CAN DRIVE ME
OUTTA MY MIND ♪
- Ha-ha! Cheers!
- Cheers!
♪ ♪
♪ HEAD OUT IN THE HILLS EVERY
EVENING THAT SUMMER ♪
♪ TORE MY HEART
ON THE COUNTY LINE ♪
♪ UM-HMM ♪
♪ MY DADDY WAS JUST
A POOR DIRT FARMER ♪
♪ HE FED HIS FAMILY
COOKING UP 'SHINE ♪
♪ LOCAL LAW... ♪
ALDEN: It seems like not that
long ago that
I gave a little speech
down at the diner and uh...
I'm sure you guys
have noticed that I've been
having a little difficulty
with the transition
to civilian life.
[SKOOTER SILENTLY MOUTHS]
I didn't know that.
Ember reassures me that
eventually I'll find something
that will ignite my passion
again but it's been hard.
I've tried some of the
leisure things like
drinking a case of beer
in a week.
All that did was put
on 5 pounds.
And golf?
Skooter you can have my sticks.
SKOOTER: Really?
ALDEN: I can't use 'em!
Well, gentleman's game is not
meant for everybody. [CHUCKLES]
After awhile I started to worry
that maybe I would
never find anything and um...
then it dawned on me that kinda
like Dorothy in the Wizard of Oz
that what I was searching for,
I could find right in
my own backyard.
So I'm gonna ask y'all to step
inside.
Nat here has been
cooking up a storm.
I got to discuss a little
personal business
with Miss Maddie here.
♪ [ROMANTIC MUSIC] ♪
I know that I've been
a bit of a trial lately,
that I've been hard
to deal with.
But I also know I can do better.
♪ [ROMANTIC MUSIC] ♪
I love you.
Short story long...
Will... will you marry me?
In a word...
Yes.
Yes, yes!
- Will you help me up?
- Yes!
[BOTH LAUGH]
Oh!
[ALDEN SINGS, PLAYS GUITAR]
♪ ON THE COUNTY LINE, UM-HMM ♪
MADDIE: I love you.
♪ [ALDEN ENDS GUITAR SONG] ♪
Whew!
♪ ♪