(MultiCom jingle)
(car horns honking)
(whistle blowing)
(upbeat salsa music)
- [Voiceover] Today, one
of every three New Yorkers
is foreign born and 90,000
documented immigrants
enter the city each year.
It is the strengths of
their hopes and aspirations
that fuels the energy of
today's New York City.
New York City is actually five cities:
Brooklyn, Manhattan,
Queens, The Bronx,
and Staten Island.
So why not travel around
the world in five burroughs?
All any explorer needs is a subway token
to cross the Atlantic, the Indian Ocean,
the Caribbean Sea.
Sample the local cuisine,
purchase traditional crafts
from a street vendor,
remember, have fun.
(speaking in foreign language)
- [Woman] Oh, shut up!
- [Man] Calm down.
- [Woman] No, No.
- [Man] Take a deep breath.
Let it go.
- [Woman] Come on, you
were going to leave me
in that club, all by myself, like--
- [Man] Stop, stop.
Just stop.
- [Woman] 5:00 in the morning.
- [Man] Hey!
- [Woman] Don't walk away from me.
- [Man] Sylvie, I can't
keep bailing you out.
- [Sylvie] What?
You just lent it to me yesterday.
I'm gonna pay you back.
- [Man] Why don't you go home?
Just get some sleep.
- [Sylvie] I'm not afraid to be alone.
Taxi!
I don't need you.
I don't need anybody.
Asshole!
Wooster between Broome and Spring.
Can you turn on the air?
- [Driver] It's on.
- Here.
- [Driver] Don't like musk?
- Yeah, caio!
(speaking in foreign language)
(chuckles)
Fuck him.
I don't need his help.
- [Driver] Excuse me?
- [Sylvie] Nothing.
- [Driver] You are in
the film business, huh?
Movies?
- No.
Why, do I look like I am?
- [Driver] Yes.
- Are you?
- [Driver] No.
No, no, no, not me.
My brother is.
Vikram Raj.
Big movie star in India.
- [Sylvie] Really?
- [Driver] Vikram Raj!
You've heard of him, no?
- [Sylvie] No.
- [Driver] Millions of fans.
Millions.
(carnatic music)
(singing in foreign language)
- I just wanna see if it still runs.
(carnatic music)
(humming)
- [Sylvie] Why are we stopping?
- Um, Wooster, between Broome and Spring?
- Oh.
(mumbling)
Oh sh, I can't find my money.
Please, if you write down your address,
I promise I'll mail it to you.
- I don't know.
- [Sylvie] No really, please,
this is really not like me.
Please.
Staten Island, okay.
Thank you, Vikram.
- [Driver] No, Bipin, Bipin Raj.
- [Sylvie] Bipin, thank you, Bipin.
- [Bipin] Thank you.
- [Slyvie] Goodnight.
- [Bipin] Goodnight.
- [Sylvie] Bum, bum.
Fuck.
(dog growling)
Oh, hello.
(groovy music)
- [Voiceover] Welcome
to CBS News Radio 88,
Traffic and Weather Together.
- [Voiceover] Steve, you wanna get
under the air conditioners.
Here's Neil Bush, Chopper 88.
- [Voiceover] Good morning for us,
it's clear now but it's gonna get hot.
We'll check with Greg Allen
at the CBS Weather Center.
- [Voiceover] The WCBS
guaranteed high for today night.
(fan droning)
(door creaking)
(speaking in foreign language)
(bed creaking)
- When will he leave?
I'd like to sleep in my
own bed just one night
- I told you.
It is a great honor to
have him as our guest.
- He's not the Maharaja.
(laughs)
And I expect occasionally
he'll do for himself.
- He isn't accustomed to living this way.
- [Vikram] Chandra,
bring me a glass of water.
- All night long, I'm gonna kill him.
- Shh ...
- (yawns) Let it run
so that there's no lead in the tap.
(groans)
(fan drones)
Now close the door.
We must keep the cool air
so I can sleep well.
Ah ...
(serene flute music)
(train rattling)
(train conductor drowned
by train rattling)
(door slams)
(distant television echoes)
(speaking in foreign language)
- Fuck!
I'm sick of your shit.
You said you'd do the dishes.
I worked until 5:30 this morning.
Jesus Josif.
I'm cleaning up after people all night,
all fucking night!
I'm sorry.
- [Voiceover] For today is 97 degrees.
That gives you some leeway there.
That means it could go as high as 102.
If you combine that with the high levels
of humidity this afternoon,
you're talking about a
heat index of 110 degrees.
That is dangerously hot
for New York.
(upbeat salsa music)
- Shit!
- Shh ...
Do you have to make so much noise?
- Gimme kiss.
- Do you really have to go?
- Well, I have to get to
the office and my wife,
you know, she--
- Do not mention her in my house.
Don't.
- Why, why?
- No more kisses until
you get me my dress.
The pageant is tomorrow.
I can't believe you still
haven't gotten it yet.
- We already talked about this.
Don't worry baby.
I told you, tonight.
(knocking at door)
- [Voiceover] Marisol?
I'm going down to open up the bake shop.
Make sure your father gets dressed.
(window squeaking)
- We'll party, tonight.
(speaking in foreign language)
(upbeat music)
- Papa?
- Don't tell anybody.
Go to sleep.
(speaking in foreign language)
(alarm beeping)
(moaning)
(telephone ringing)
- [Woman] Oh come on, baby, please.
- It might be important.
Hello?
- Get your Romanian ass out of bed.
Today is the day, compa.
- Who's that?
- [Man] It's Ramon.
I'm up.
- [Ramon] You got the money?
- [Man] Now remember, no money
until we see cigarettes, okay?
- [Ramon] Why, what's the problem?
- [Man] 'Cause that's the
way import export works.
- [Ramon] When are we gonna do this?
Where's it at?
- Okay, I gotta go.
- [Ramon] We gotta hand
shake on this to work.
- [Man] All we gotta do is show up.
Gonna be beautiful.
- [Ramon] I'm trusting
you, we got a lot on this.
- [Man] Ramon,
it's gonna be beautiful, you hear me?
- It better be beautiful.
See you at the store then, alright?
(speaking in foreign language)
(upbeat music)
- What are you looking for?
Matches?
There's no money in there.
We owe $400 for rent,
$75 to Mrs. Silesquin,
$25 to Constantine for plumbing.
- Come on baby, I'll pay you back tonight.
I promise.
- Your promise just don't gamble.
God, Josif.
- It's not gambling.
Not gambling, business.
Import export.
That's what I do now, you know that.
What are you gonna complain about, Elena,
when I buy us a house
with air conditioning
and a hot tub?
- What happened to the air conditioning
you promised me last month?
That's what I thought.
Big talk.
- Oh, I see.
If I don't make money,
I don't desire, right?
Right?
Forget it, you're not listening.
I don't even know why I talk to you.
- I don't?
You don't!
- No, you don't, you don't.
- [Elena] You don't!
(singing in foreign language)
(mellow music)
(jewelry box chimes)
(door slamming)
Josif.
- [Josif] Get dressed up tonight.
I'm gonna take you somewhere special.
- [Elena] Don't get
blood on your good suit!
(melancholy music)
(singing in foreign language)
(telephone ringing)
- [Voiceover] Hello,
you've reached the home
of Mia Mundo Design
and (si-li-op-ta)
Your message is important
to me, thank you.
(beeps)
- Sylvie, Sylvie pick up the phone.
Okay, I'm sorry we fought at the club,
but you have my keys.
I don't want to call a locksmith.
Look,
don't take your shit out on me.
Pick up.
Sylvie.
Sylvie, Sylvie pick up the phone.
You hear me, pick up the phone.
(beeps)
(keys jingling)
(singing in foreign language)
(doorbell ringing)
Sylvie!
Hey!
I need my keys!
(doorbell beeping)
Sylvie!
- [Woman] What?
(banging at door)
- Come on, I know you're in there.
(laughs)
Sylvie, I need my keys.
Please open the door.
(laughs)
I know you hear me.
- Oh, shit!
- Shit.
Listen, I'm not going to
call a fucking locksmith,
understand?
(speaking in foreign language)
(mellow music)
- [Woman] You better not go fussing around
with that china cabinet.
- Just making some coffee.
You want some?
- So.
Now the coffee's in the china cabinet?
- Oh no, woman.
Just checkin' to see if it's secure.
You know them rob coaster last week?
Them take everything.
But this here cabinet secure.
Strong.
Go on to bed now.
Everything's cool.
Just let me sit in the car!
- No!
- Look, what good is all this cheap china?
We never ate off it,
but a Cadillac!
- It's my granny's china
and I want it back!
- When hell freezes over!
- Crazy man.
(footsteps stomping)
- Oh lord, it's hot!
- [Man] Where's the glaze, Errol?
- At the store, right there, sir.
- Stop rubbin' our car man.
You're gonna ruin the finish.
- Heh, let him wash it.
She won't let him drive it.
- What you talk about?
I drive this car.
- When?
You've never driven that car.
- I drive it here, right?
Right, right?
- Come on, no!
So long as you ...
- Cadillac.
- Back home, the man was
happy with his scooter.
He'll take that car
and make him a miracle.
- Brenda, I don't understand
how you let him sell your china
and buy that old stink car.
- I let him?
No.
The man sneak.
For us he say.
I don't drive.
Maggie,
Granny trusted me with the family china.
Only precious thing she ever owned,
40 years of cutting sugar cane.
- Brenda, I know, I know.
You don't have to tell me.
- But I got the key.
- Sinclair, where are you?
Crazy man, move your
backside from the car!
Move it now, man!
Move it!
All I ask is you don't touch the car.
Don't touch the car.
When you get your own car,
you can touch it like a big fat woman.
- Eh, eh, eh, why your neck's showing man?
Give yourself a ride.
- No problem--
- Move the, move man!
- Start facing that woman.
Why you let her treat you like so, eh?
They don't know about
the five finger solution.
Pop!
- [Errol] Watch your mouth now,
before I slap them big lips off your face.
You never treat a woman so.
- That's why she driving you,
instead of you driving that car.
- You watching that vehicle man?
- Close, and you know why?
I'm gonna embarrass you
in front of your woman.
- Let me go now, let me go now.
Oh yeah!
- Boys, boys, this car
got us fight, okay now?
- You crazy.
- Yeah, crazy.
Don't touch the car!
- Please!
- Rodney's cousin's friend
looking for cars, eh?
He's seen the Cadillac.
He say it's a real good price.
He give me his card.
He tell me give it to you.
Take.
Do.
- Errol.
Errol.
Come with pass, having a party tonight.
There's gonna be lots of women there, boy.
Look.
I promise myself I
wouldn't miss this party.
Why don't we go there
in style.
Style, man.
- You're right.
We drive.
- Style.
- I'll teach she a lesson.
Brenda!
- Hates it.
- Oh, I better go.
Big mess.
I'll see you.
- See you, girl.
- Whoo!
- Hey, baby.
- How are we doin'?
(cars honking)
- Bye, Maggie.
- Not like her, she trouble.
- Go on, tell her.
- I got something I wanna tell you.
- Yes?
- I'm goin' to the store.
- What?
- Me I drive it nowhere.
Good wheels about this car.
(food sizzling)
- This heat is unbearable.
It reminds me of when
Far Cry from Sadaam,
which I made for the great Ipram,
premiered at the Cairo film festival.
I was outside of the old Plaza Hotel,
chatting with Al Pacino.
Suddenly, we found ourselves
besieged by an enormous crowd.
Fortunately,
the concierge appeared
and shouted in Arabic,
"Make way for the star!"
I looked back,
and saw poor Al Pacino
struggling to maneuver
through the impossible crowd.
I pulled him through that surging crowd.
It was many years ago, of course.
He said,
"Thank you, my friend,
"Vikram Raj,
"thank you."
He said, "If there's
anything I can do for you,
"please do call me."
- [Older Boy] Why don't you call him?
- Bala.
- Al Pacino is on location, he is filming.
I've spoken to his secretary.
Don't worry.
Soon your uncle will return
to the silver screen.
- You've changed your mind?
You don't want fried eggs?
- My yolk has bled.
- The yolk is loose,
exactly as you like it.
- If you see no difference,
I'll have yours.
- Where are you going?
- [Bala] Outside.
- [Chandra] Okay, take your brother.
- I don't wanna go.
I'm still, I, I'm sorry.
- You need to ween that boy.
- [Chandra] Don't slam the--
(door slams)
(door squeaks)
(video game melody)
(electronic blasts)
- [Little Boy] I wanna play with this, no.
- [Voiceover] The North American bison
relies on an acute sense of smell
for detecting danger.
Sight and hearing also
play an important role.
- Chandra, tea.
- I asked you not to yell.
The water's on.
- [Voiceover] For one or more days
during the dry season.
- Put up the volume.
- [Little Boy] Mommy says no.
Remember, rule number one:
Never let a woman tell you what to do.
Put up the volume.
Put it up!
(screams)
- Now what have you done to him?
- I'm not getting what I need.
- [Chandra] Then go to a hotel.
I've been on my feet all week,
(phone rings)
caring for sick people.
This is supposed to be my day off.
(phone ringing)
- [Voiceover] A kind of thick wet clay.
- Stop it, son, stop it.
(baby crying)
- [Voiceover] On occasion bison will--
- Your tea.
- [Voiceover] Roam into populated areas.
While they are not particular.
- [Girl On Right] What, excuse
me, the new Miss Colita,
Miss Marisol Hidalgo.
Ah, please.
- [Marisol] Goodbye Brooklyn Boulevard.
Goodbye 147th Street.
- [Girl On Right] Oh no,
what, like who you tell us.
- Don't you know my man with the fat cash,
the real cash is settin' me up with this?
He's hookin' me up.
You know, I almost let him go
when I found out he was married.
- What do you mean he's married?
- Well, come on, you
know I like to eat out.
Steak, lobster.
I ain't even lookin' for love.
- Marisol!
Marisol, get in here!
You're not Miss Colita yet!
- Eh!
- [Marisol] Miss Colita.
- So, I'll do it for you later.
Alright?
It's really, really cute.
It's small pussy.
Tell Mama I said hi.
- Yeah.
(speaking in foreign language)
(phone ringing)
- [Marisol] Hey baby, what's up?
- I can't talk long, I'm in the office.
Can you hold on a sec?
Suzy, can you have Mr.
Hutton hold, please?
The phones are ringing off the hook.
- Just wanted to remind
you about the dress.
It's in Soho.
- I know.
I know, Soho.
- Don't work tonight, okay?
I love you, bye.
- Is he married?
Where's your father?
(radio announcer speaking
in foreign language)
(melancholy music)
(train rumbling)
(singing in foreign language)
- God, it's hot, it's supposed to be 100.
(speaking in foreign language)
- Fuckin' polyester is what.
Come on, put it away.
I don't wanna see it.
- What's wrong, it's gold.
- It's a small chain.
Show it to Bowman.
(knocking)
- Let's see what you got, Iscovescu.
- I want $75 on the Mets.
- [Bowman] Are you crazy, the Mets?
- Yeah, New York fuckin' Mets.
- It's a big overlay.
Eight and a half?
Two and a half.
- That watch is worth $500 dollars.
- Yeah?
Where'd you get it?
It's too hot for bullshit, god you.
I'll give you $50 on the Mets.
- $50?
Okay.
Don't scratch it up.
I'll be back for it.
(siren blaring)
(melancholy music)
(comical melancholy music)
(groans)
Shit!
(bell rings)
- Oh ho, ho!
What have we here?
And a minute early.
These are very fresh pork chops.
You're in for a treat.
(speaking in foreign language)
Don't worry, take it.
- I can pay, and I will pay.
Please, can you hold this for me?
- No, no.
Josif will drop it off on his way.
No discussion.
(speaking in foreign language)
- She never has the money.
She's a direct descendant
of Stefan Cel Mare.
- [Josif] Oh, Stefan Cel Mare.
- [Both] Ooh!
- No (speaking in foreign
language) in this shop,
(speaking in foreign language).
Put this on the shelf in the meat locker.
(speaking in foreign language)
(knocking on door)
- Aye, sir?
Aye, sir?
(groans)
(coughs)
If you keep the door closed,
the rest of the house won't get cool.
- This house needs a
bigger air conditioner.
- You have company.
(upbeat music)
- Bala, if you don't mind.
Find Simon and play with him.
(singing in foreign language)
(speaking in foreign language)
(music echoes in distance)
- Glad to see you all.
Welcome.
(upbeat music)
(laughing)
(singing in foreign language)
(doorbell rings)
- [Vikram] Chandra?
(upbeat music)
(doorbell ringing)
(speaking in foreign language)
- [Voiceover] It's a
scorching hot day in Queens,
as right-hander Dave Malicki takes the--
- Yes, man I'm tellin' ya.
I'm tellin' ya man, yes!
- [Voiceover] Six game losing street.
(car bass drowns out radio)
Looking very solid indeed,
a 3.14 ERA for the first
half of this season.
(slaps)
(dominoes rattle)
(car bass booms)
(lock clicks)
(car engine starting)
(air conditioning fan blowing)
♫ You can dance like no other woman
♫ Here
♫ In this world
♫ You got rhythm in your heart
♫ And you got fire in your soul
♫ Our ancestors dance for rain
♫ While some dance to be free
♫ So woman you're the greatest dancer
♫ The world will ever see
(banging)
♫ Woman dance
(woman drowned out by radio)
♫ Let me dance, dance, dance
- What?
♫ Black woman dance
(woman drowned out by radio)
- What?
- Your lights are on.
- [Voiceover] And a grapple to
short could be a double play.
The flip to second, Jordan goes--
(singing in foreign language)
- [Voiceover] Play ends the inning.
We've got one hit, no runs--
(banging)
(singing in foreign language)
- Is that the guy?
- Guys!
Our case is an embarrassment.
- We got it, Mr. Krug.
We got it.
(door squeaks)
(car honking in distance)
- Hello, boys.
We're give tonight.
The cigarettes will be in the truck.
Park across the mall at 5:00,
Jersey plates, understand?
Now Boris, asking to ask
you to see the money.
So we can do business
with civilized people.
- No.
No money 'til we see cigarettes.
That's the way it is.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, that's right.
Tell Mr. Boris that
we'll be there at 5:00,
like we agreed, all business up.
- No fuckups.
Okay, fuckups?
- What was that?
I thought we were doin'
business with Boris.
- This whole thing makes me nervous.
- Oh, come on, Ramon, stop.
It's gonna be beautiful, okay?
- [Ramon] Shit.
(door squeaks and slams)
(door squeaks)
- [Josif] Stelu, my friend.
- Josif.
- How are you?
(speaking in foreign language)
- How are you.
- I'm in a pinch, though.
Listen, I hate to ask you,
do you think I could have the money,
my wife lent your wife yesterday?
- Oh, Josif.
We just borrow yesterday.
It's my daughter's communion.
- That's right.
- Hey, have a drink, huh?
- No.
- Huh?
- I'm okay, congratulations.
- Okay, kiddo?
- Yeah.
- Huh?
(speaking in foreign language)
Okay.
- Be good.
- Fuck!
- Ah ...
(mellow music)
I'm reminded of the time
we were shooting ...
- He fled India because
he couldn't find a part.
- You don't know that.
- Has he looked in the mirror?
Does he know how difficult it is here?
- Mr. Al Pacino may call him.
- He will?
- [Vikram] For my
contributions to the Indian
Chandra?
Scotch!
- I'll get it.
- [Vikram] Al Pacino.
- [Ladies] Al Pacino?
- [Vikram] We were waiting for a taxi cab,
on a miserable afternoon.
We found ourselves--
- Bipin, he is taking over our home.
It's either him or me.
I'll take the children and
go to a motel or something.
- Chandra, let's not fight this weekend.
You were so delighted when he first came.
- Yes, but I had no idea
that he was going to
treat us like his next champas.
I bend backwards too,
'cause then all he does is, "Chandra!"
He say "Chandra!"
I don't have to take this nonsense.
(cries)
- [Vikram] Chandra?
It seems we have finished the nuts.
- There is nothing left to eat.
The house is empty.
You've eaten it clean.
- Bipin, do you let her
talk to you like this?
- I'll go to the corner.
- No!
(speaking in foreign language)
I'll go.
I need some fresh air.
(singing in foreign language)
- Sorry, Vikram.
This isn't like her.
- [Little Boy] No.
- Yes, hello.
Yes, hello, this is Sylvie Otti.
I am the designer who called the ...
Yes.
Yes, no I would like to speak
with Mrs. Bruckham.
Oh, no listen, I've left 20 messages.
I've started ...
Hello?
(phone beeps)
Listen, I don't appreciate
you hanging up on me.
And I don't like your
tone of voice, you hear?
Asshole.
(sighs)
(mellow music)
Hello?
(speaking in foreign language)
(bubble wrap pops)
- But her thighs are huge.
Jello.
What?
Yeah, um, I better go.
Yeah, bye.
Don't start with me.
I shouldn't even be here today.
- Was that him?
(door slams)
(upbeat music)
(hoarsely speaking in foreign language)
- The two sides of a coin;
both shine pretty,
but only one side
will bring you luck.
(singing in foreign language)
Wear this white string
around your finger,
for it bounds your desires.
It's there as a reminder
of what you truly desire.
- [Voiceover] Now the
2-1 pitch on the way.
Wild pitch into the dirt, bouncing away.
Here come Jeffrey Sis--
- Why you so edgy?
You got money on this game?
Wait a minute.
Oh, no.
- What are you, my wife?
- Tell me you don't got
the money on this game.
Oh, Christ, Jesus!
The fucking Russians will kill us!
They'll kill us!
- [Josif] Russians, Russians, Russians.
- We'll be dead!
Dead mother fuckers!
Dead, dead, dead, man!
- [Josif] What's a matter?
- [Ramon] Promise me!
- Ramon, you look like an old man.
Would you calm down?
It's gonna be fine.
Do you trust me?
- Tell me the truth.
- Elena's pregnant.
- [Ramon] What?
- She's pregnant.
- [Ramon] Really?
- I found her pregnancy
test kit in the freezer.
(speaking in foreign language)
(somber music)
- Small taste of heaven.
Ranch-style Tudor,
1.3 acre lot, central air,
and fully automated sprinkler system.
It's a nice house.
- It's mine.
It's gonna happen.
- [Mr. Krug] Guys, we got customers.
(door slams)
(laughing)
(phone busy signal beeping)
(singing in foreign language)
- Damn.
- Chandra, how nice to see you.
What'll it be today?
- Cocktail nuts.
- You look tired.
- I've worked all week.
On my feet most of the day.
I was looking forward to a quiet weekend,
but my home's full of people.
- Having a party, didn't invite us?
- [Chandra] I wasn't invited.
- $8.25, dear.
Are you okay?
Chandra, please, take this.
- Thank you.
- [Clerk] And tell him I'm a big fan,
of Far Cry from Sadaam.
(birds chirping)
(crying)
(somber music)
(cars honking)
(laughing)
- Don't touch the car!
Go home!
Don't make me come get you!
(laughing)
(chanting in foreign language)
(funky music)
- Ah ...
Down, sweetie.
Ow, you're hurting me.
- Have I told you how much I love you?
- Not since last month
when you had me go down to
your job to lie for you.
- Ooo, well, I do.
- That tickles.
- Oh, are you up to something?
- Why do I have to be up to something
to tell my wife that I love her?
- Hmm ...
I know you.
- I'm feeling romantic today.
- Hmm ...
- When I come in and I
see you lying there all
sexy and thing.
And I think to myself,
"Good god you have a sexy woman."
And lets the boys have a kiss.
- Yes.
(moaning)
- Are you goin' someplace tonight?
- No, why?
- Sweets,
there's a rooftop party downtown.
- Go on.
Yeah, that might be nice.
- I know.
Me and the boys, wanna drive.
- Boys?
- Where you goin' woman?
- Get off me, man.
- But, don't do it.
- You talk all sweet to me,
and me take that and get
all wet between the legs,
and now!
- Don't raise your voice.
- I will!
- The neighbors will hear.
- [Brenda] My mother say,
"Be careful of that one.
"He's liable to go soft in the head."
- Who you callin'?
Woman, give me that phone!
Give me that phone!
(busy signal beeps)
Give me that!
- You want the phone?
You better run!
You better run, man!
- [Errol] Watch one day,
one day that woman, she gonna have kids.
(all kids talking and laughing)
- [Voiceover] I'm telling you.
You have to feel for this Mets squad.
They're in the middle of a losing streak,
and just can't seem to
win for losing these days.
It seems the heart has just
gone right out of them.
- [Mr. Krug] Hey, Romo?
(speaking in foreign language)
Come on.
- [Voiceover] And he
no chance in the world.
Alright, that's the
fourth walk of the game
by Dave Malicki.
Struggling a little bit with
his control as we can see.
Now the Phillies have runners to corners,
with no men down,
and up comes Greg Jeffries.
We'll recall he used to
be a Met some time back,
a rather contentious stay
at the New York team.
The pinch to Greg Jeffries,
a slider low and away.
One ball--
- Two dollars.
- [Voiceover] the count to Mr. Jeffries.
Usually falls behind on Jeffries,
two balls one strike.
Jeffries waiting on the 2-0 pitch.
- [Mr. Krug] Hotter than hell today.
You can fry an egg on the sidewalk.
- [Voiceover] And it's in
the dirt, bouncing away.
Here comes Jordan to score,
and he does.
And on a wild pitch,
the Phillies go up five nothing.
Nationwide,
the conversation's of
the deadliest death heat.
For all your insurance needs--
- Can you picture me that
age, still working here?
I'd kill myself.
- All these years hacking pork.
What's he got to show for it?
- [Voiceover] Having thrown
though several innings
straight here on a hot
and very humid Saturday afternoon.
(melancholy music)
- I hear what you're saying, sweetie,
but understand my scheduling needs.
I have to draw the line somewhere.
(shouting in distance)
Frank!
I can't hear myself.
What the hell is going on out there?
- I'm only trying to get
an appointment, Fernando.
Get out of my way.
Are you crazy?
- I'll talk to later, bye bye, sweetie.
- Frank!
Let her go.
- I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
- What's going on here?
- Mrs. Bruckham, I've been
trying to get an appointment
for a month, and I'm really--
- So you just barge in?
I hope you won't be too
upset if I call security.
Do I know you?
- Yes, we've met.
- Oh my god, yes!
Little Sylvie all grown up, oh!
You look splendid!
I should have recognized your temperament.
How is your mom?
Did you see her fantastic
collection on your way in?
Sit, sit!
I apologize.
If I had only known.
Sylvie, oh Sylvie, you've
got Frank all worked up.
I'll probably have to give
him the rest of the day off.
Oh, is that your book, Sylvie?
How adorable.
A designer following in
your mother's footsteps.
Why didn't you mention a name?
I would have seen you toot sweet.
- Here I take the feminine on the inside,
and then throw it with a masculine edge.
- Do you know I was your
mother's fitting model?
A perfect size eight.
- Instead on this other page,
I make a more body conscious
silhouette that can--
- It's a wretched business, fashion.
My advice to you, sweetie:
run!
- No, please hang on to it.
- No, no, you'll need it.
It'll probably get lost in all this chaos.
- Mrs. Bruckham, I really--
- [Frank] The lead from DK on one.
- Yeah.
Yeah, listen, sweetie,
we've been all over that.
Hold on.
Sylvie,
Yuki Shimamura will be
in town until tomorrow.
She's a buyer for one of the biggest
department stores in Tokyo.
She'll be an important contact for you.
Take her to dinner tonight.
Don't let her pay, sweetie.
Frank will set it up on your way out.
Bye bye darling.
Kisses to mama.
Uh huh.
(mellow music)
- [Chandra] What's the matter?
- Nothing, it was just
getting too hot inside.
- So now he's thrown you
out of your own home.
- It's a beautiful day.
- It's 100 degrees.
I'm not going to stand for this.
He hasn't set foot outside of this house!
- Please don't do this.
(party-goers chattering)
(singing in foreign language)
- Please out!
I want you to leave, please.
It's nothing personal.
(record scratches)
Out!
(bottles breaking)
- Poom!
Poom, poom, poom,
poom, poom,
poom, poom.
- [Voiceover] A fly ball deep to left.
It's up there, it's on its way, gone!
A homerun into the kiddie park.
- What are you doing?
- They're fuckin' losing.
What are you doing?
- It's a loan, I'll pay
him back before he notices.
- [Ramon] Are you crazy, no!
You're gonna mess everything up!
Are you crazy, man?
No!
- You wanna tell that to Boris.
Do you?
- Hey, what's goin' on here?
What is it, half a day today?
- Miss Patreski called,
she says she needs another chop.
- Put it in the meat
locker with the other.
And remember, Joe.
Remember.
Drop it off on your way home, huh?
(singing in foreign language)
- I've been locked out
of my Benz all morning.
Where are my keys?
(keys jingling)
(smacking)
Stop, they will come out.
Stop.
(sighs)
- Bye the way--
- No, Sylvie.
I'm broke, flat out.
- You don't think I can pay it back?
Look, I have to meet this Japanese buyer,
a very important buyer.
- I would be impressed if that was true.
- Fuck you, it is true.
Please, I don't wanna blow it.
- I can't keep bailing you out.
Why don't you ask your mom?
- Ouch.
I'm asking you.
- I'm still angry at you.
- What?
- Oh, come on, baby.
Come on, get over it.
♫ I don't ♫
- Take the pack.
- No, I'm quitting.
- Again?
♫ And when I sing
♫ And you ♫
- Whadda ya do to me?
Come here!
Thief!
Thief, theif!
Help!
Get him, Errol!
- I got him!
- [Brenda] Get him!
- Did you get it?
- No, that woman's strong.
- You didn't get it?
- Ma, did you see that?
You see that?
- My god!
- You got my money?
- Money, for what?
Running fast?
Screaming?
No, I don't have your money!
Go on now!
Go on!
Go on before I make it for real.
God, the key, get the key!
Brenda!
You alright, honey?
- Yes.
- Why?
- Thank you, baby.
- Good thing I was here.
- Yes, it is.
- Why them young kids today, man?
- Thank you, baby.
Oh, god, you saw it didn't you?
You saw it.
Oh god, thank goodness.
(mellow music)
- And did you see that girl?
I better go, really.
- But really, (mumbles).
(dramatic music)
(moaning)
(dishes clanking)
- You tell him, Bipin Raj.
Tell him.
- [Voiceover] Kanu Chuahan
and Rajsun Entertainment present
Rangeele Dilwale!
- Look at this.
Ridiculous, these stadium concerts.
In my day it was much more intimate,
respectable.
It's rubbish.
Where's the talent?
(speaking in foreign language)
- Something on your mind, brother?
- I know.
I know.
- It's Chandra.
She, she feels--
- You are a very lucky
man, very lucky man.
- Me?
A delivery driver with a
tiny house on Staten Island.
(speaking in foreign language)
- I remember the first role you ever had.
Cho-tu and the little brother.
You were only on the
screen for a few moments,
but we applauded so loud and long,
we missed the rest of the film.
(laughing)
- How do you remember that?
You were so young when I made that film.
- I remember everything you did.
Everything.
- Okay, tell me this.
What ever happened to that
blue cap I gave you, hmm?
I thought you'd never take it off.
I began to wonder if you
had any hair beneath it.
- I don't remember.
- Ma don't know.
- Yep,
she remembered everything.
- Yeah.
I'll talk to Chandra.
We'll work something out.
(phone ringing)
- Ridgewood Pork Store, Albani speaking.
Ah, Leny, how are you?
Ah, you're goin' out?
That's great.
Josif, it's Leny,
she wants to know what to wear tonight.
- Tell her my favorite.
- [Mr. Krug] He says to wear his favorite.
(laughs)
Okay bye, Leny.
- What?
- Nothing.
(phone rings)
- Hello?
- [Brenda] Full Service Limo--
- I've been expecting your call!
- [Brenda] Full Service Limo?
- Shh, shh, shh!
It's him!
Al!
- Chandra!
It's Al Pacino!
- [Brenda] My friend gave me your card.
- Yes, yes!
It is wonderful to hear your voice.
Oh boy, oh yes.
How have you been, Al?
- Is this 555-0162?
- That is correct, Al.
I'm anxious to hear all
about your proposition.
- Oh, well.
It's a gold Cadillac,
1970, extremely good shape,
low mileage.
- It sounds terrific!
When may I see it?
Tonight?
Perfect.
Thank you, Al.
He has a script, he wants me to read it.
It sounds very interesting.
- A script!
I'm so excited for you.
- Damn.
- Please.
I think I must get ...
- I'll get it.
(footsteps running away)
- My example ...
I'm sorry if I--
- Don't.
Don't.
- [Bipin] Quick Chandra!
We don't want Mr. Al Pacino to wait!
(footsteps running away)
- [Chandra] Unbelievable!
- [Bipin] Al Pacino, Mr.
Al Pacino rang this house!
(mellow music)
- I know what you done.
- What I do?
Alright.
I'll sell the car if that's what you want.
- I want an air conditioner.
I want my granny's china back.
I want to go out to a dinner
and a movie occasionally.
I want to trust the man I married.
(bike bell ringing)
- Errol, what time you going?
Errol?
What, we driving?
- [Bipin] Chandra, where's my keys?
I have 10 minutes to catch the ferry.
(melancholy music)
- [Ramon] Come on, Joe, let's go.
- Ugh!
I can't wear nothing nice in this place.
- It was stuck pretty good.
- Jesus, look out, look out.
Here, hold this.
I'll be right back.
Come on, man, let's go.
(mellow music)
- [Voiceover] Ah, man he took it!
(chattering)
(screams)
- Hello?
Yes, can I order an
iced cappuccino, please?
With sugar, yes.
No, no, no, no, no, with no sugar.
Actually, um, yeah, with sugar.
Oh, fuck it, you decide.
Hmm, yes.
Can I pay by check?
It's Sylvie, right next door.
You know that ...
Oh, come on.
Can I speak with Carlo?
He always accepts my checks.
Okay.
Carlo?
Si, ciao, it's Sylvie, hey baby.
Yes, it's just about, yes.
Just this time.
Come on, yes, I promise.
Yes.
Okay.
Thank you.
(phone beeps)
(kids chattering)
(city drones)
- What?
- Where's Mrs. Pacshesku' chop?
- No, forget it, I got the money.
- I'll meet you there.
- I got the money, man.
Forget the old lady.
(car honks)
Hurry up!
(mellow music)
- [Voiceover] God, I can't believe it.
In all my years, a 15 inning marathon,
full of some of the most bizarre twists.
If you're just tuning in,
well, it's been a long time
since we've been able to say it.
Today's been nothing short of a miracle
by the New York Mets.
(screaming)
Yes, yes!
(thumps)
(door rattles)
Albani!
(thumping)
Oh my god.
(tugboat horn blows)
(ferry engine drones)
(melancholy music)
- [Ramon] Where's the truck?
- Where's the money?
- Where's the truck?
- Man, we should wait for Josif.
I don't know about this.
Ow.
Why'd you do that?
(speaking in foreign language)
(groaning)
Come on, man.
- What the fuck?
- [Ramon] Mrs. Petrescu's chop!
(elevated train roars)
Oh, shit.
(police siren echoes)
No!
No, don't!
Joe!
(speaking in foreign language)
- [Voiceover] Air conditioning
working in this studio?
- [Voiceover] Call maintenance.
- [Voiceover] Hot weather
has a lot of people
hot under the collar.
Details on last night's ugly bar fight
on Staten Island in just a moment.
- [Voiceover] Right now, hazy--
(car honking)
- You wanna fight?
What you drivin' 20 miles an hour for?
Won't you get on the shoulder?
- Don't start.
- Your drawers are showing.
- You're stupid.
- Don't start!
I'll leave you out on the corner
with your backside on the subway.
- Call me when you get settled.
- Of course.
- I'll bring your things over later.
- [Vikram] You don't have to.
- Let me know when you start working.
I'll come by the set.
- Of course.
Bring Chandra and the kids too.
(horns honking)
- I'm blocking traffic.
I better go.
(melancholy music)
(moans)
(muttering)
- Mother fucker!
- [Voiceover] For the time
being, what we have to worry
about after this day of
record-breaking heat,
are the thunderstorms
which are approaching.
The National Weather Service
has put out a severe--
(phone rings)
These thunderstorms could
bring drenching rainfall,
deadly cloud-to-ground
lightning, as well as--
(music box jingle)
- Take this off.
- No, no, no, no, don't touch that.
- Oh no, you messin' with Los Santos?
- Yeah, so?
- Oh no, don't look but there goes
last year's Miss Colita.
- Where?
- Oh, that's Martha?
Somebody told me she was married in Miami.
- [Voiceover] They lied.
(speaking in foreign language)
(laughs)
Junior, por que you don't
find me sexy no more, huh?
- Shit, you know what
happened to Junior's father?
He got fucked with big time, big time!
- No, (speaking in foreign language)
(doorbell buzzes)
(speaking in foreign language)
What do you want?
- Mio Mundo Design?
- I can't hear you, who are you?
- [Ramon] Mio Mundo?
- Yes, that's me.
It's closed.
- Please, I gotta pick it up tonight.
It's just a dress for Hidalgo.
- Hidalgo?
You were supposed to come last week!
You really fucked me up, come in.
Voila.
- This is it?
- Beautiful, huh?
This silk, flowers,
they're very, very dear.
They're silk. (sighs)
And,
how are you planning to pay for it?
- Here's $20.
Will you take that as a down payment?
And I'll pay you the rest tomorrow?
- Is this a joke?
Are you joking with me?
That's all I got.
And my driver's license.
You can hold it, if you want,
until I can scrape together
the rest of the money.
Please, I'm begging you.
- This is a $1000 dollar dress!
- A $1000 dollars?
Maybe you can pull off some
of those expensive flowers.
How much would that save me?
- Look, absolutely not!
- Come on, I just wanted ...
Work with me, baby!
- Work with you my ass.
(speaking in foreign language)
I'm having a very bad day, for real.
- How bad?
Ugh!
- Bad.
Smoke?
- Thanks.
- Do you want a piece of ice,
for your face?
- Nah, I'm alright.
(sighs)
- You know, the fucking
material is imported.
Ah, it's hand-dyed.
It took me two times
to achieve that color.
It's fabulous color, don't you think?
- Do you like pork?
- Huh?
- Bacon, sausage, chops.
I'll pay you in pork,
all the pork you can eat for a year.
- Are you making fun of me?
- No.
It's, it's, it's ...
nice.
Really.
- Really?
(scoffs)
- I tell you what.
You give me those $20
dollars and the subway token.
- I need the token.
- Alright, then I'll hang onto the dress,
until you bring me the rest of the money,
and I need it tonight.
I'll make it $500.
(phone rings)
- Hello?
- Elena, wheres's Josif?
- He took my mother's watch
and he went to went to Atlantic City.
- Atlantic City?
You think?
That fuck!
Excuse me, um ...
When he gets home, tell
him I need to speak to him.
Alright?
- He doesn't have home anymore.
- Yes, officer.
It was stolen from my driveway.
Yes.
See, he's a scrawny man.
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
Beady eyes.
And there be two others,
three other with him.
(mellow music)
- I want a suite with a view.
- Do you have a reservation, sir?
- No.
- Well, you're in luck.
We just had a cancellation.
How would you like to pay for this?
- Credit card.
I hope the suite is very big,
and the finest suite you have.
- Thank you, Mr. Raj.
- You have recognized me?
- Oh, I'm sorry, sir,
your name is on the card.
- Oh.
- I'll come out to the Bronx.
Don't go out.
Stay there 'til I get there, alright?
Promise.
Say it.
Yo!
(doorbell rings)
- Yes, bedroom.
(clears throat)
Thank you.
Oh.
(laughs)
I don't have any small change.
Sorry.
Oh, wait here.
Take it.
It's nothing.
- [Voiceover] Unit 14--
- Stars here are fucked with her.
- Chill.
- What did we do, drive too slow?
- Know why them do this?
'Cause we Carribean men,
tryin' to have a good time.
- Keep your hands on the car now.
- Who's Errol, boys?
- [Female Officer] Hands back on the car.
- Is this your car?
- It's he wife's car.
- Don't start.
My car.
- Errol, cool yourself now, man.
- Got us out here like fuckin' criminals.
What we do?
- Look, you're lucky.
Everything's in order.
Turn the music down and keep it above 20.
You were drivin' too slow.
Have a nice day.
- That's it?
No apology?
- Let it just go, man.
- No, I want an apology.
- Let it go, man.
You're getting our mood down.
- Stop me and don't give me an apology.
Hold me now, hold me.
- Easy, Errol.
- Come on.
- Ah, room service?
Yes.
Yes, this is the imperial suite.
Yes, Vikram Raj speaking.
I would like to order
a little bit of dinner.
What is my pleasure, yes.
I'll tell you my pleasure.
A bottle of your white whine pule pusef,
on ice of course, of course.
The garden salad, the escargot, yes.
Dressing on the side.
What is the soup of the day?
Oh yes, yes.
Please bring me that too.
And the chicken,
the chicken breast,
but the garden greens, yes.
But, pesto, pesto, no, no, no.
No pesto-esto.
Uh, duck comfit, yeah,
bring me two of those.
Good, good.
The souffle?
Good idea, very good.
And the food cart, yes, yes.
And a bottle of your best champagne.
Dom Perignon.
Okay.
(restaurant chattering)
- Yuki.
Yuki.
- Oh, sorry.
I couldn't find the restaurant.
Very nervous there.
I go to every one in city.
I'm so tired of having to say nice things.
Very nice colors, very nice lines.
Like, like, like.
No talk of fashion please.
Just only fun.
I am starving, let's get a table.
Waiter!
- Can you hold this pictures?
Thank you very much.
(melancholy music)
(bottle bonks)
- Right here is good.
(upbeat music)
- Call it $15.
- I'll be right back.
- Hey!
Hey!
Come back!
Come here, ch.
(coughs)
Bastard!
(doorbell rings)
- Hold on a minute.
Ah, excellent!
Please bring it in.
Good.
(door slams)
- Wanna beer?
- Can you get the money?
- Not this week, compa.
Rent.
Took my lady out a couple of times.
Gotta do it, man.
It ain't like it used to be,
when all you had to do
was tell a lady she's fine
and get that coochie.
Look it.
Don't tell me you're strung out.
What?
- I promised Marisol I'd buy this dress
for the Miss Colita pageant.
What's I gonna say when
when she asked me, no?
She thinks I'm some loaded, married,
fat cat riding a cash pony.
Married?
I had say something.
How do I look I ain't
got a crib of my own?
- Get your own place then, man.
- Working at Ridgewood Pork Store?
Fuck!
- That's some sick shit, compa.
You better find yourself some church.
- Fuck you!
When's the last time you went to church?
- Last Sunday, baby.
I was on my knees, full of
the holy spirit and shit.
- I don't wanna hear it.
(speaking in foreign language)
- Oh, shit.
Is it good?
- Good?
It's unbelievable, man.
She puts off fresh garlic, green peppers,
she sprinkle some of that cilantro on it.
(speaking in foreign language)
- $500 dollars ...
That's a lot of money, bro.
- It's a designer's dress from Soho.
Ugly as sin.
- Has she seen it?
- [Ramon] No.
- Oh,
then we ain't got no problem, bro.
I'm gonna hook you up.
Yo, there's a warehouse,
not too far from here.
Designers clothes, bro.
I got myself a pair of
Perry Ellis slacks slammin'.
All we gotta do is get the night watchman
a bottle of Bacardi, and boom,
You get your girl a
beautiful designer dress.
- You mean steal?
(upbeat music)
- My boyfriend, he's an asshole.
He really is an asshole.
- Oh, I'm sorry.
(laughs)
- It's my fault for having such
poor judgement in every aspect of my life.
You know, to quote my mother.
- I'd like very much to meet your mother.
Very great creator.
- Mmm.
- She lives in Vienna, yes?
- Yeah, she lives in
(speaking in foreign language)
many ways of the world.
I don't wanna talk about her.
I don't, I don't.
I don't like it when people look at me
when I say my name.
(laughs)
- Sorry,
I understand.
- Do you?
Okay, let's ...
Let's finish it.
Come on.
- Oh girl, so good,
you're looking wa-seen!
Don't be nervous.
- Is it too much?
- No, no, you Queen of Sheba,
and I Cleopatra myself, eh?
Ha ha!
You won't even think about
Errol and he nonsense.
- Errol who?
- Stupid.
- Maggie, I no longer have a husband.
- To the end of misery and couture!
- To relaxation, and to you.
- War without pain.
- Is everything alright here?
I'll leave this here when you're done.
Thank you very much, mm-hmm.
- I too ...
Nature calls.
I'll be right back.
(upbeat music)
- Hold on, baby.
Hey, you got Bacardi, right?
- Don Rico, three dollars cheaper.
What's the difference?
- One, it says Don Rico and
it doesn't says Bacardi.
- What are you doin', man?
- Takin' it back!
- You know what?
Let's get outta here.
And I'll meet you outside,
because I see a friend at the bar.
I'm gonna go and say hello.
- I will wait for you.
- No, no, no.
I'll be just a second.
Really.
- Okay.
(background chattering)
(plate rattles)
- [Voiceover] Hey, lady,
you can't go through here.
- Yuki?
Yuki.
Yuki!
Come.
- [Yuki] I didn't see you.
- No, no, I came out of the side door.
Let's go, taxi!
- Hey!
(speaking in foreign language)
- Hey, hey!
- How are you dude?
- This fucking heat is killing me.
- Yeah, it's a bitch, bro.
- Checkin' in, 'cause I'm off the books.
It ain't with it, is he?
- Hey man, I was just in the neighborhood,
figured I'd drop by and say,
hello!
(laughing)
- I've given up, man.
Shit, I thought you knew.
I'm in recovery.
I'm sober, hombre.
- What?
- Just jokin'.
- Oh, man, you had me goin', dude!
- I had you goin'!
- Bacardi!
- Yeah. (laughing)
- Ha ha!
- Whoo!
- Fuckin' thing is pushin' in my liver,
but I'm dyin' to use it.
- Come on, man.
- Yeah!
(laughing)
- Are you ready?
- [All] Yeah!
- Time to party?
- Start off!
(upbeat carnival music)
- [Voiceover] Errol, come
on, Errol, come on now.
- [Errol] This is called
a backsplash here.
Yes, yes.
Lock it up, lock it up, lock it up.
♫ One day
♫ Jungle one day
- [Voiceover] Yes.
- [Errol] It hook?
Alright.
- [Voiceover] Very good, very good.
- [Errol] You sure this is a legal park?
- [Sinclaire] It's Saturday night,
you can park anywhere.
- [Errol] Here we go.
Watch me now.
- [Voiceover] Ow!
- [Voiceover] Gettin' our groove, guys.
(yelling and laughing)
- It is the Great Maxine.
- Maxine!
Very style.
- Garcon!
(electronic dance music)
(kisses smacks)
(laughing)
♫ Jungle
♫ Jungle ♫
(electronic dance music)
- Hey, look,
that nice guy I met.
Don't ask Maxine.
- I ...
It's getting sort of late.
I don't want you to get
the wrong impression.
You know, I'm not usually like that.
I'm actually a hard working,
innovative designer.
- (laughs) No clothing!
Waves.
San des, he gave me two of these.
He says it make me feel good.
- No, Yuki, don't.
No, no, don't take both.
No.
Dude.
(laughs)
- Let's dance!
♫ Jungle, jungle
♫ Jungle
♫ Jungle, jungle ♫
- Can we start to get on with the night?
♫ That's right 'cause I made you look
(bass echoes)
- No, back off.
I told you I'm waiting for a phone.
It's an urgency.
(phone rings)
- Boris?
Oh, thank god.
No what?
I haven't asked you anything yet.
Shut up, just shut up and listen to me.
It's an emergency.
What?
Okay, let's go.
- You're drunk.
- I'm not.
I had a little wine at dinner,
a couple of martinis.
That's all, I swear.
- Well then, why did you get me down here?
- Because--
- I thought you were in trouble.
- You're stoned.
- No.
- Yes, you are.
- Say hello to my
important Japanese contact.
- [Manuel] What the
hell did you do to her?
- I didn't do anything.
It was her idea to come here.
I didn't give her the pills.
I fucked up.
- [Manuel] Fuck, what did she take?
- [Sylvie] I don't know.
- [Manuel] Let's go, I'm
late for party in Brooklyn.
- [Slyvie] No, we gotta help her.
- [Manuel] Who's we?
- Ha ha ha!
- [Manuel] She is really fucked up.
Come on, let's take her out the back.
- Ha ha ha!
Then I hit this guy with a nightstick,
but he don't go down.
I waive it!
- No, no! (laughing)
- I seen this shit,
kung fu movie, ha ha ha.
I was gonna fuck him up!
Then my back went out!
(laughing hysterically)
(loud footsteps)
- You hear that?
- No, I didn't hear nothin', man.
Hey, hey, you're doin'.
Put that away, bro.
- Yeah.
Yeah.
- Yo.
- Yeah.
(snoring)
- Yo.
(grunting)
- Yeah.
(screaming)
(upbeat music)
(radio static drowns speaker)
(trains rattles)
(mellow elevator music)
- Oh ...
I forgot my purse at the club.
I forgot my portfolio!
- [Manuel] Come on, Sylvie, let's go.
- Mmm...
Mmm,
mmm.
- [Man In Black] Do I get any?
(laughing)
- Aren't there enough
chairs in this place?
Why can't you sit on a chair, huh?
- You know Mami, I think I
hear Papi calling for you.
- So do I.
- Oh.
(giggling)
- She's fine!
You dog. (growls)
(speaking in foreign language)
- It's good, right?
- What's she doin' messin' with you?
- I'm a businessman,
Import export.
- Yo, what are you doin'?
You live here?
- No.
- Chill, man.
- Don't walk away.
I'm talking to you.
You don't desert me.
- Hey, baby, you look fantastic.
- This dress doesn't fit me.
And it has a label in it.
Made in Taiwan.
Made in Taiwan, Ramon?
Made in Taiwan?
- It's smokin'!
- Right, Vic.
- Oh, I'm into it.
- How can you do this to me?
Did you get this off a bargain rack?
- Let me explain.
- No, I don't wanna hear it.
How can you do this fucking shit to me?
- Hey, I don't like it
when you use that language.
You sound common.
- Fuck that, you made me look common.
- No, no, no, no, no, it looks good.
- [Marisol] What happened to my dress?
- [Ramon] You don't know what
I did to get you that dress.
- [Voiceover] C-train to Coney Island.
Next stop Dekalb Avenue, Brooklyn.
- Look that Italian lady wanted
me to pay her $500 dollars
for that dress.
I don't got that kinda money.
- What do you mean?
- Okay, look.
It is not exactly how I told you.
You see,
I was robbed, baby.
- Ooo!
Are you tryin' to play me, Ramon?
Like one of those project women?
'Cause if you are,
you can take your sorry
ass outta my sights.
- You know, you are some piece of work,
you know that?
You know, fuck you, if
your pageant is all that.
I busted my ass for you,
and you want me to go?
You really want me to go?
(door handle clicks)
(door closes)
(sighs)
Let's go, man.
♫ Work for me it's lots
of work to do be done
♫ He gots another problem
♫ Got to go talk to people
♫ He need to solve the problem ♫
- Ah ...
Errol, share!
- Have another round!
- Patience, man.
♫ Eh eh he
♫ Walk away walk away
- I'm not buying you any drinks tonight.
- Oh.
Ooo.
Oh, like that.
- Errol!
- Hey, man.
- Your wife here.
- Brenda?
- Yes, man.
- Here?
Your wife and your boys.
- Nah.
- I'm the one telling you, man.
Your wife here, man!
- Brenda?
- Yeah, man, I tell ya.
- She's not here.
- Hey there, cowboy.
♫ I don't sa-lish off in the voice ♫
- Brenda?
Do I let go?
Nah!
♫ Ah
♫ Ah ha ha
♫ Drop you waist drop your waist
♫ Drop you waist drop your waist ♫
- Brenda?
- Errol!
Eh, Errol!
♫ Rock me baba ♫
(metal door rattles)
- [Voiceover] That fucking
slime, Messershmitt.
(laughing)
- Ah!
You're a good man, Danny Krug.
It's good.
It's good, ah ...
(sighing)
(upbeat music)
- Stetson!
Edward, music!
Action!
Hey!
(singing in foreign language)
(doorbell rings)
- Al?
Al!
- Please, you're keeping me up.
I have a early flight.
(door slams)
- Errol!
- Brenda!
Get your hand outta my pocket!
- No, give it!
- Get you hand outta my pocket, woman!
Come on!
Give it, gimme that!
- This it.
- Give me my keys!
Gimme the keys.
♫ Longer longer longer longer
♫ Bring the chant now
♫ Oh ho ho
♫ Cranky moods are cranky
♫ Angry moods are ♫
(muffled chatter)
(singing in foreign language)
(laughing)
♫ That's why'em I said
♫ Jump on jump jump jump
♫ Fall down jump jump jump
♫ Jump on jump jump jump ♫
(laughing)
- Let's get some more beers!
- Yeah!
- It's still early.
Forget about her.
- Yeah.
I got that serious love mojo.
- Anything I can do?
- If I had back all the hours
I spent crying over men,
I'd be on vacation right now.
- He doesn't love me, mami.
- I love Marisol Hidalgo!
- This guy.
- I love the way she smells.
I love the way she speaks.
I love the way she, she,
she yells at me, man.
Yo, bro.
I even love the way she tears.
- Oh.
The fuck you goin'?
Ramon?
I'm gonna take you back
to your mom's, man.
♫ Jump on jump jump jump
- [Manuel] Jump, jump, jump
I wanna jump, jump, jump,
and a jump, jump--
- [Sylvie] Manuel!
- [Manuel] Jump, jump--
- Manuel!
♫ Jump and jump jump jump
♫ Fall I'm gonna jump jump jump ♫
- Manuel!
♫ Was I in myself
♫ Jump and jump jump jump
♫ Fall down jump jump jump
♫ I'm gonna jump jump jump
♫ Fall down jump jump jump ♫
- Sylvie, come down from there!
- You don't know how to dance.
You know that?
♫ I am feelin' sweet
♫ Told ya I am feelin' nice ♫
- You don't even fuck good.
Hey white boy.
Look at him.
You can't dance.
- You are very slow paquita, come down.
- No.
- [Manuel] Okay, I'm coming up.
Don't come up.
♫ Are you feelin' the feelin's
♫ All by-a myself
♫ By-a by-a
♫ Buh-by-a myself ♫
- Hmm.
- [Mami] He's not right for you, honey.
I mean, what kind of man is that?
Climbs in, in our windows.
- [Marisol] I love him.
- Oh, now you love him?
- Ow!
- Sorry.
That better?
- Get on.
- [Ramon] No.
- Get on!
- There are no fucking
(speaking in foreign language)!
Your mother's stupid!
(moped engine rumbles away)
- I'm sorry.
- You're sorry?
And now everything's supposed to be okay?
- No, I know, I don't mean it like that.
- Errol, look at us.
You got us runnin' in circles.
If that car means so much to you,
then you can eat in, live in it,
shit in it, for all I care.
- But Brenda.
- I'm goin'.
- Brenda, it's late.
At least let me drive you home.
The last time I drive this car,
so help me god.
- [Voiceover] After
mistakenly locking himself
inside a freezer for hours at his job,
Josif Iscovescu was happy to be alive.
(speaking in foreign language)
The Romanian family was still traumatized
as we arrived on the scene.
How do you feel?
- Beautiful.
- [Voiceover] His only
company inside the freezer
was the radio.
And it was a coincidence
that his boss Albani Krug,
and a nearby shop owner
returned to the store.
- I f-forgot something,
so I came to look for it,
and I heard
noise, singing in the meat locker,
and I opened the meat locker,
and Josif was frozen stiff.
- [Voiceover] How does it feel,
to have helped save his life?
- (stammers) It feels good, yeah.
It's good.
- This is the freezer
where he was locked in for six hours.
On the floor, a pork chop was found,
as well as cash.
- I think it fell outta his pocket.
- So, how ironic,
on the hottest day of the year,
he nearly freezes to death.
In the Ridgewood section of Queens,
Dominic Carter,
New York One.
(thunders cracks)
- It's finished.
I'll put on coffee.
(speaking in foreign language)
(mellow music)
- It's beautiful.
(psychic girl's voice
growling in foreign language)
(thunder cracks)
(raindrops splattering)
- We used to have fun.
- Yeah.
- It's not fun anymore.
- No.
No.
- I'm goin' home.
- Take care of yourself.
- You are a sneaky man.
I love you.
- I love you, sweetie.
Tomorrow, I promise I'm gonna sell the car
and get back your china.
Do you hear me now?
Lord have mercy!
- All this trouble and look what we got!
- My car!
Oh ...
I'm gonna kill them guys for tellin' me
this is a good place to park.
(crying)
(phone ringing)
- Go.
- Mari?
(sighs)
(rain pouring down)
- Bipin?
Who is it?
(rain pouring down)
- Marisol!
Marisol!
- Ramon?
(melancholy music)
- Marisol!
(telephone operator drowned by rain storm)
(melancholy music)
(keys jingling)
(ring clinking away)
(melancholy music)
♫ Yes, man
♫ Watch it
♫ Useless time is a needless time
♫ Useless time hold the mix
♫ It's time for the ultimate
♫ One time
♫ Jam
♫ No we can't stop this jam
♫ Hey hey hey hey hey hey
♫ Oh heck
♫ Right here in this young we be havin'
♫ Why fight why fight
♫ Inside of this young we be havin'
♫ It's time for action jump now
♫ Let's have the breakdown jump now
♫ So we have our mission jump now
♫ A serious mission
♫ It's time that you feel it pipes of it
♫ The ultimate party
♫ It's time that you feel the heart of it
♫ So come soldier prepare to mash down it
♫ The ultimate party
♫ A good solid when is the weapon
♫ It's junction time
♫ On ya matey
♫ This the way we
♫ Grab the bumps and stop
♫ Push back
♫ On ya matey
♫ This the way we
♫ Grab the bumps and stop
♫ Uh huh
♫ Lord no mercy
♫ Eh heh
♫ No we can't stop this jam
♫ No room on the floor we be havin'
♫ Why fight why fight
♫ While it's true the door we be havin'
♫ Jump in the rhythm
♫ Jump now
♫ For this is not prison
♫ The home of our Guinness
♫ Jump now
♫ To complete the business
♫ Heh heh
♫ It's time that you feel it pipes of it
♫ The ultimate party
♫ It's time that you feel the ultimate
♫ So come soldier prepare to mash down it
♫ The ultimate party
♫ A good solid when is the weapon
♫ On ya matey
♫ This the way we
♫ Grab the bumps and stop
♫ Push back
♫ On ya matey
♫ This the way we
♫ Grab the bumps and stop
♫ On ya matey
♫ This the way we
♫ Grab the bumps and stop
♫ Push back
♫ On ya matey
♫ This the way we
♫ Grab the bumps and ♫
(reggae scatting)
(singing in foreign language)
♫ It's time that you feel it name of it
♫ The ultimate party
♫ It's time that you feel the ultimate
♫ So come soldier prepare to mash down it
♫ The ultimate party
♫ A good solid when is the weapon
♫ On ya matey
♫ This the way we
♫ Grab the bumps and stop
♫ Push back
♫ On ya matey
♫ This the way we
♫ Grab the junction time
♫ On ya matey
♫ This the way we
♫ Grab the bumps and stop
♫ Push back
♫ On ya matey
♫ This the way we
♫ Grab the bumps and lord have mercy
(reggae scatting)
♫ The ultimate party
♫ Feel the groove
♫ The ultimate party ♫
(serene music)
(MultiCom jingle)