[music playing]
MAN (ON PA): Lockdown
tonight has been delayed one
half hour to 9:00
for Cell Block C.
C Block innmates
will have dinner
one half hour earlier at 8:00.
Mr. Jacobs, call
Central, please.
Officer Jacobs, call Central.
The lockdown tonight
will be delayed.
Three years in this dump.
I can hardly remember the
last time I played the sax.
[sax music playing]
Ah!
Thank you.
That's all for tonight, folks.
Hope you had a good time.
Drive safe.
Good night.
Richardson.
[beeping]
Mr. McElroy, I
do hope you're not
going to give me any bad news.
You know how much it
upsets Mr. Fisher.
Don't worry.
Tell Fisher I have
the merchandise.
Good.
And the other business, the gal?
Yeah, well, our
friend in Oakland
couldn't take care
of the leading lady.
This is very
disheartening, Mr. McElroy,
but we'll deal with that later.
Right now, we're waiting
for you and the merchandise.
You have 30 minutes.
There's one small problem.
I'll have to call you back.
Oh, he's hung up.
What do you think?
Oh, God.
It was beautiful.
- I'm glad you liked it.
I wouldn't want you
to endorse something
you didn't believe in.
"Endorse?"
It's called "Lisa's Dreams."
Oh, baby!
Mwah!
Mwah.
[inaudible]
I'll be back in a minute.
I just gotta change.
Bye.
OK.
So when do I get one of those?
Honey, they don't make
'em like that anymore.
Great, thanks.
Sax-man.
Mackie, I don't believe it.
I remember when that
thing was bigger than you.
Upon a time, it was.
Hey!
It's been a long time.
How the hell are you?
I'm good.
You're looking at one of the
busiest real estate brokers
in the Bay Area.
If you're so busy,
what are you doing in LA?
Hey, I came to catch your act.
Shit Bullshit.
You haven't seen
me play for years.
Yeah, right.
Mike, I got about 30
minutes to make a very
important business meeting.
This guy's a real
stickler for time.
Anyway, it turns out I meet
this girl on the way down here.
This chick is a real lush.
We must have hit every
bar on the coast.
Right now, she's in the back
of my car, totally crocked.
I can't pitch up at the
meeting with this chick.
Can you give me a ride?
Sure, but what about the girl?
Hey, she's outlived
her usefulness to me.
Now I remember what it
was about you I didn't like.
OK, you ready to go?
Yeah, just let me get a
ride home for my girlfriend.
MACKIE: Your girlfriend?
Anyone I know?
No, thank God.
Well, you know what they say.
Once they've had Mack,
they never can go back.
I gotta make a call.
Sweetheart, an old
buddy stopped by tonight.
I gotta give him
a ride somewhere.
Now?
I couldn't get out of it.
OK.
Could you give
her a ride home?
I would hurry up if
I were you, Mackie.
Let's not upset Mr. Fisher.
Richardson?
Richardson!
Everything OK?
Yeah, fine.
Who's Richardson?
Oh, he's a pain in the ass.
Let's go.
Sir?
So I'm sick of his fuckups.
It's about time we got--
it's about time we got
rid of Mr. McElroy.
I just gotta get some
stuff out of my car.
Looks like the car.
Fuck, man.
Mackie, you're not gonna
leave her like that.
Come on, man.
As soon as I take
care of business,
I'll come back for her, OK?
So where are we headed?
Down Malibu.
God, this is so beautiful.
I remember I did some of my best
fucking in these hills here.
Yeah, I got a good chance
at a record contract.
If it comes through,
Lisa and I are
getting a house, right here.
[unzips]
[deeply sniffs]
I think we got a homicide.
You secure the crime scene.
I'm going after the car.
[siren wailing]
Control, this is [inaudible] 4.
I'm in pursuit.
187.
Suspects heading westbound
for [inaudible] Canyon
of a white, late model Mustang.
Mike, I gotta take a leak.
Pull over.
[radio chatter]
10-4, control.
OK.
[siren wailing]
The suspect's
vehicle [inaudible]..
Fuck!
It's the cops, man!
Fuck it, drive!
Come on!
Mackie, what are you doing?
Come on, move it!
This is crazy.
Shut the fuck up,
Michael, and just drive.
What the hell's going on?
Come on!
Fucking drive, man!
Who's in command
at the road block?
CONTROL: Detective Marsh.
I'm patching you through to him.
Stand by.
- Roger.
- Marsh here.
Go ahead.
Over.
OFFICER (ON RADIO): Are
you ready to intercept?
Yeah, ready and waiting.
What the fuck was that?
I knew it, man.
I'd lay it 8-1
it's that asshole.
Richardson.
Well, I think we should
get the fuck out of here.
Start the bloody car.
Come on, move!
Let's go, man, faster!
Control, be advised.
We're almost at the road block.
Come on, put the
gun down, Mackie!
Shut the fuck up Michael.
- ETA is 20 seconds.
- Come on, Mackie.
This is nuts!
Come on!
Shut the fuck up!
Michael, I'll blow
your fucking head off.
10 seconds, Control.
Move it!
He's no stopping!
Get off the road!
[gunfire]
Hands on the wheel!
JUDGE: In consideration
of your clean record,
I sentence you, Michael Keller,
to five years in state prison
with the possibility of
parole in three years.
Take him away.
Looks like you're
history, killer.
You're out of here.
Let's go.
OK, let's see.
Michael Keller, number 3724891.
Manslaughter, huh?
A cop.
Well, well.
Who'd you suck off
to get out early?
Your mother.
Hey, just cool it.
Let's get him out
of here, all right?
You better hope I never
see you on the outside.
Hear me, cop killer?
You know, this
is really funny.
I-- I thought I had so much
that I wanted to say to you,
but I can't seem to
think of anything.
You don't know
how hard it's been
for me, not being able to
see you the past few years.
I mean, not that I didn't
understand your reasons
for making me stay away.
Because I did.
It was just hard, you know?
Michael.
Michael, please talk to me.
- What do you want me to say?
- I don't know.
Say anything.
Say whatever you want.
Just talk to me!
You want me tell
you how wonderful
it was living in Disneyland?
Shall I tell you about that?
Sorry.
I didn't mean to press you.
But I understand.
You can't understand.
You're wrong, Michael.
I do understand!
I understand your pain
completely, because I've had
to live with that same pain.
It's like every day I've
been in prison just like you.
Now we're free.
We're free to start over.
Michael, for both of us.
That is, if you still want me.
[badly playing saxophone]
[playing saxophone]
You know, when I saw
you, all those old feelings
started pouring back into me.
Guess all this time
I've been setting
myself up to play the victim.
That's why I stopped you
from coming to see me.
But when I was walking around,
I realized the only way that's
going to happen is if I let it.
I have a choice to be
whatever I allow myself to be.
And I choose to be happy.
And the only way I'm happy
is when I'm with you.
That's very good.
Police, open up.
Everybody stay where you are.
Get dressed.
I got some people downtown
who wanna see the show too.
Read 'em their rights.
Why don't you pigs
mind your own business?
We're only giving the
people what they want!
Tyrone, Tyrone.
I've been wanting your
ass for a long time.
He's going to love this.
I hope so.
Now, look, guys.
If you could play that
way tonight, [laughter]
I'd be a happy man.
That sounds real good.
Hey.
I don't believe my eyes!
If it ain't the real
sax-man in the flesh.
Wow.
How you doing, Mike?
Fine.
How are you doing, Frank?
[inaudible] Hey, guys.
I want you to meet one of
the hottest sax players
in this town, Mike Keller.
Hi, Mike.
How are you, guys?
Hey, Mike.
I heard about your misfortune.
Must've been a real drag, eh?
Yeah, it was a bad deal.
Listen, Frank, I need a gig.
Could you use me?
Absolutely, man.
Wow.
And how's the chops holding up?
Better than ever.
You want me to prove it to you?
Hey, you don't have
to audition for me, man.
I know your word.
God knows we've played
enough gigs together.
Yeah.
I'll tell you what to do.
Be here tonight about 10:00.
Then we'll give it a go.
Everything goes well, I'll
speak money with management, OK?
I appreciate it.
A friend of ours has been
waiting a long time for you
to hit the streets again, pal.
He wants you to know he
just hasn't forgotten how
bad you and Mackie fucked up.
He wants his money back.
What the fuck are
you talking about?
I don't know anything
about any money!
I told you he was
gonna need some coaxing.
Let me have him for two minutes.
I'll help his memory.
No, that won't be necessary.
You better watch
my partner, pal.
He's fucking crazy.
Right!
So do yourself a favor, huh?
No more games.
Otherwise, next time, I might
not be able to hold him back.
Look, our friend,
he's a businessman.
When he lays out half a
million for something,
he expects delivery.
When he don't get
what he expects,
it's only natural he
should want his money back.
But to show you he's not
completely unreasonable,
you have 48 hours to
come up with the bread.
OK?
We'll be in touch real soon.
Give him the tape.
For your viewing pleasure.
Goes great with popcorn.
Enjoy the show.
MAN (ON TAPE): By now, I'm sure
you've got a good understanding
of the situation.
Oh my God.
MAN (ON TAPE): So I see
no need to go on about it.
It's simple.
You give us the money, and we'll
give you your girlfriend, Lisa.
What money?
MAN (ON TAPE): So be smart.
Don't fuck with me.
Because if you do,
you're gonna force
me to make your girlfriend
into a moving picture star.
Shit!
MACKIE: I just gotta get
some stuff out of my car.
MIKE: What the hell
was in the briefcase?
Money?
No, he was carrying
porno flicks.
[gunfire]
Where the hell could a
half million dollars go?
REPORTER: Early today, Detective
Marsh led officers of the LAPD
in the apprehension
of long suspected
pornographers operating
from this 29th Street motel.
Detective Marsh, was the raid
the success you had hoped?
Yes, we've made some
important arrests,
and we're hoping they'll lead
to further information and more
arrests.
REPORTER: Does that
mean the ringleaders
were not among those who
were apprehended today?
Well, we have Tyrone
Richardson in custody,
but we're considering the
possibility that Richardson
may be part of a bigger outfit.
REPORTER: In the meantime,
Tyrone Richardson and company
are in custody.
And channel 3 News will be
watching that story closely.
From South Central Los
Angeles, I'm Sheila Hall.
MACKIE: Richardson!
Everything OK?
Yeah, fine.
Who's Richardson?
Oh, he's a pain in the ass.
SONG: I was trying to
live my life alone,
refusing to believe that
love could make me whole.
Still, it seems no matter how
I hide, something in my heart
won't be denied.
It's the lonely love that
turns the world this way,
changing night to day
when I lose my way.
It's the lonely love
takes away the pain
and brings me home again.
It's the only love.
Mike, I gotta take a leak.
Pull over.
OFFICER: Guess who
made bail this morning.
Richardson.
Already, huh?
Yeah, he's being
processed right now.
Any instructions?
I think his boss
got the message.
Next time I speak,
maybe he'll listen.
Put Stoke and
Haber on the watch.
They know the routine.
Got it.
Does that feel
familiar, you rat's ass?
You tell your boss
I got his money,
but he's gonna have to
play the game my way.
What's his name?
Fuck off.
I said, what's his name?
Fisher, Jack Fisher!
You give this to Jack, and
you tell him what I said.
You got it?
I got it.
So where is he?
Hey, this is where the note
says to meet him, all right?
Sir!
Thank you very much.
That's for you.
I see your boyfriend
has a sense of humor.
It seems like you and I will
be taking a little ride.
You two stay behind.
Richardson?
Well, surprise, surprise.
I knew your boss
wouldn't have the balls
to come see me himself.
Well, he's a very busy man.
Get moving there.
I assume you have the money?
Well, then, there's no problem.
No!
No, stop it!
[screaming]
[knocking on door]
Sergeant Philip Keller, US MC.
I'm Michael,
Phil's baby brother.
Sure you are.
What the fuck happened to you?
I need some help.
Well, get your
ass in here, boy.
On the double!
So is it OK if Jennifer
comes over tonight?
No.
No, it is not OK.
I am sick of that bitch
hanging around here.
The answer is no.
Why?
What's she ever done to you?
Because I said no!
Marissa, you are
beginning to piss me off.
Why don't you go shopping?
But I just got
back from shopping!
Then just go, will you?
I need a break.
Will you just go?
Do you understand that?
Go.
- All right.
But we're going to
Maxwell's tonight, right?
I can't tonight.
Something just came up.
I need to work.
Aw, Jack, you promised
you'd take me out.
How am I ever gonna show off
all those beautiful clothes
you 'buy me if you
never take me anywhere?
What, are you
deaf or something?
Look, take Jennifer, will you?
Just-- will you just--
I don't give a fuck.
Just go.
Jackie.
You're so Jackie Jackie, Jackie.
Yeah.
Well, you take this.
And you just go.
You're so good to me.
I'll never ever leave you.
- You're welcome.
You what?
No.
Nobody ever leaves
Jack Fisher, baby.
No.
Yes.
[beeping]
Do you know what this is?
Do yo?
It's your death warrant.
[unzips]
Isn't that [inaudible]
Apparently,
your boyfriend didn't give a
shit whether you lived or died.
And now he's dead.
I'm stuck with you, aren't I?
Agh!
Do you like movies?
I hope you do.
Because I got a new
one the other day.
I would like your opinion on it.
We can watch it together.
And then we can get
to know each other.
[sobbing]
[screaming]
[laughter]
Harry, if anything happens to
her, I don't know what I'll do.
Well, don't you
worry about that.
We'll take care of that.
Well, you know, I don't
think there's a day goes by I
don't think about your brother.
We were real close, you know?
I mean, I can honestly say
I think he's about the only
real friend I ever had.
You were in every
one of his letters.
Man, he used to
crack me up, you know.
We were almost on
that plane home.
Four more miles.
Four more stinking miles is
all I had left on this tour.
I had this crazy notion that
I wanted to drive, you know?
And-- as I--
you know, I really don't
wanna talk about this shit.
I really don't.
Besides, we got some business
to take care of, anyway.
Well, this looks
like a good spot.
For what?
For finding out what
these guys are up to.
Then I'm going.
No, you're not.
If we both get caught,
where does that leave Lisa?
What if something happens?
No buts!
If we're gonna do this thing,
we're gonna do it right.
Now, I understand
you're worried,
but you've got to trust me, OK?
I know what I'm doing.
OK.
All right.
[inaudible] It's a really
great [inaudible] downstairs.
Give me a lift.
Be careful.
Always am.
Well, almost always.
What you reading, Einstein?
I've told you before,
Willie, not to call me that.
Oh, so sorry!
[chuckling]
If your nose wasn't
always stuck in a book,
it might have saved
you a night in jail.
[chuckling]
I think now would be an
appropriate time to warn
you of my mood, William.
- Oh, look at me.
I'm shaking.
Willie, just cool it.
No, I'm getting
tired of taking
orders from this Oxford faggot.
All he ever does is fuck up!
Hey.
What am I running here?
A day nursery, you
fucking idiots, huh?
Huh?
Big John, go get the car.
I've got some unfinished
business for him to sign.
And you two, you two stay
here and watch the girl.
Don't mess up.
Did you see her?
She's up there, all right.
Where are you going?
I'm going to get
her out of here!
No, you're not!
What are you, crazy?
You think these guys
are messing around, huh?
Do you?
You think this is
some kind of game?
Gonna be dark soon.
So why don't we go back to the
shop and think this thing over?
You're sure you don't
wanna go to the police?
I'm not going to the police!
I'm gonna this by myself.
OK, Michael.
OK.
Hey, Chuck.
Where's my sandwich?
I'm starving here?
CHUCK: Relax, Willie.
It's coming.
WILLIAM: Yeah, when, next week?
MARSH (ON RADIO): 1 Mary 12.
This is Marsh.
Do you read.
Over?
Here we go.
You deal with him, Stokey.
He makes me nervous.
Pussy.
Mary 12 here.
Over.
MARSH (ON RADIO): How's
it going over there?
Yeah, everything's quiet, sir.
MARSH (ON RADIO):
Well, I hope you
packed a lunch, because you're
gonna be there for a while.
How long is "a while?"
Until I say so.
That's how long!
Something's going on over there,
and I wanna know what it is!
I shouldn't have to
remind you of what
the consequences
will be if anything
goes wrong with this project.
One slip-up.
and we all go down.
And if that happens, I
will rip your heart out.
That goes for your partner too.
Do you read me, Detective Stoke?
Yeah, I read you.
It's starting to get a little
out of hand, wouldn't you say?
[knocking on door]
[groaning]
Help me, help me, help me!
What the hell happened?
Help!
Don't even think about it.
Should have worn
your bib, Clyde.
Turn around.
What the fuck is this?
Where is she?
Where's who?
You've got five seconds
to tell me where she's at.
It's behind those mirrors.
How do I get in?
Getting
There's a code number
he punches into the phone,
but I don't know what it is!
I swear to God, I
don't know what it is!
You girls having fun?
Fuck you!
You two all right in there?
Yeah.
Watch out, Harry!
Harry.
Get out of here.
Get the hell out of here!
I don't like this.
Something's wrong.
Yeah, who the
hell are those guys?
I don't know.
Better check this out.
This is the key to
the house out back.
OK, now what?
You wait here.
I'm gonna make a phone call.
This whole scene is
starting to get fucked up.
Yes?
It's me.
I have to speak to
Fisher right now.
Fisher, the girl escaped.
She's with her boyfriend.
Marsh doesn't know anything yet.
Forget about your boss.
You get those two back
for me, and I'll make
it more than worth your while.
Do you understand what
I'm trying to say?
Yes.
FISHER (ON PHONE): Good.
That's very good.
Will you make me a line?
[sobbing]
Must be one of Fisher's men.
God!
Listen to me.
Honey, you've got to
get a hold of yourself.
I'll call Harry.
[phone ringing]
Yeah.
Now, listen, just calm down.
Are you two all right?
All right, now listen to me.
I got a small cabin
up at Turtle Creek.
It's about four hours
north of the city.
I'll meet you out back.
And just be careful.
1 Mary 12, this is Marsh.
Over.
Come in.
1 Mary 12, come in.
Over.
Where are those clowns?
Fisher, it happened so fast!
[moaning]
[sobbing]
Oh, oh.
Marissa.
I swear I shall go shopping
for those bastards for you.
Oh, fuck.
If they had any hopes
of calling the police,
they can't now.
Not with a dead
policeman on their hands.
The logical assumption
would be that they're
seeking a place to hide.
The question is, where?
The answer to that question
is sitting over there.
When he tells me
what I want to know,
I'm gonna cut his balls off.
I think that would be
unwise at this time, Jack.
Not only could he be useful in
helping us locate Mr. Keller
and his friends, but he
might make an excellent decoy
when comes the time
for us to learn
the nature of their defenses.
Mr. Keller has proven
himself quite resourceful.
And I'd hate to see
any of your men,
myself included,
get hurt needlessly.
Yeah.
Yeah, you could be right.
You call Lou.
And you tell Lou that
he owes me a favor.
And you tell him that I want
four of his best men, now.
It's time that our
Detective Haber
showed us want we want to know.
Isn't it, soldier?
Yeah, right.
There was something
you wanted to tell me?
Oh, yeah.
We still haven't been able
to contact Stoke and Haber.
Any suggestions?
Well, let's aggravate Fisher,
and see if he can help us out.
Look, you tear
this place apart.
I want some answers.
How you doing, Sammy?
Fill it up, would you?
[music playing]
Harry.
How you doing, Mel?
What the hell are you
doing here this time of year?
Bass don't run for
another two months.
You know that.
I know.
I just had to get out
of the city for a while.
Yeah.
Mind ringing this up for me?
Sure.
Let's see.
Well, fill 'em up.
Oh, God.
Sick son of a bitch!
Put out an APB now.
I want this animal.
Yes, sir.
Tom, there's something wrong.
How do you mean?
I don't know.
You just seemed preoccupied.
That's all.
What's bugging you?
- Oh, I don't know.
I don't know.
I guess it's just tougher to
deal with scenes like this.
Come on.
We got work to do.
Thanks, Harry.
Man, this place is great.
Just the bare essentials.
Hey, Harry.
- Yeah, Mike.
You think he's coming here?
Let me tell you something.
If that guy was a rat,
he'd find food at a Weight
Watchers convention.
Now, let's get cracking!
Come on!
What is he up to?
I have no idea,
but I trust him.
Hey, Harry, what's that for?
It's kind of oatmeal.
It helps the gasoline
stick to your ribs.
I could really
get used to this.
I always had
something a little bit
more tropical in mind.
Sounds good.
I always kind of fantasized
I'd have my own nightclub.
Mhm.
Nothing too fancy.
Just a place where
I could play my sax.
Maybe a little recording
studio next door.
Now, wait a minute.
Your fantasy's getting
awfully expensive now.
And then if we had the money--
I mean, if you're
gonna dream, dream big.
Yeah.
Jack, what makes you so
sure they went this way?
Hurry up with
that line, will you?
Big John, pull over.
Get Lou's men to get
rid of the bodies.
Tell 'em to tidy up.
Jesus, Harry.
This place is starting
to look like Fort Knox.
What are the lights for?
The garden party.
Yo, hey, hey!
Where do you think you're going?
First, I'm gonna
go to the head.
Then I'm gonna get
me something to eat.
OK?
Is that OK with you?
Well, you won't mind if
I tag along, then, right?
Fucking asshole.
[giggling]
It's pretty wild, what Fisher
did to Freddie and Chuck, huh?
Guess this city's out
one car, huh, Haber?
Hope they don't raise my taxes.
Yeah.
[giggling]
That's why I
hang with Big John.
The man is my idol.
He's too smart to get
in a position like that.
He made me smart too!
Now we're just like Kareem
Abdul Jabbar and Magic Johnson.
[snaps fingers]
Hey, let a guy
shit in peace, man.
We're unstoppable, man!
[flushing]
Shit.
Yeah.
Bet that's a
load off your mind.
You're fucking right, it is.
[giggling]
[sniffing]
Jack, don't you ever
get enough of that stuff?
Richardson, you're
beginning to piss me off.
What'll it be, sir?
I-- I'm sorry, sir.
$5 for you.
Your change, sir.
Thank you.
And what'll it be for you, sir?
Hurry up!
Yeah, it's good news.
We just got a call from
a Mel's Trading Post
on highway 40 in Morgan.
Seems like a guy came into
his store 10 minutes ago
and hands him a note stating
that he is Officer Haber.
The note goes on
to say that he's
being held against his will.
From the description of the
cars they were driving in,
it sounds like it
could be Fisher.
We're running a plate
check right now.
Did he say where
they're headed?
North on 40.
Get me a helicopter
and some men.
We're going up.
And get me a fix on
the exact location.
I'm not gonna stay in there.
It's gonna be the safest
place in these woods
in a short while.
Listen, Harry.
I appreciate the
thought and everything.
He's right.
Look, I'm not
gonna stay in there.
I wanna be with you.
I wanna help you.
You know, it's up
to you, of course.
But I already got one
woman's death on my hands.
I really don't want hers too.
I promise you,
I'm coming back.
What are those?
These are very
special shells, Michael.
What are they for?
They're gonna help
us harvest our garden.
Well, now we get to test
your theory, Mr. Richardson.
Where's Haber?
Get me Haber.
Haber.
Well, my friend,
now you prove to me
that I didn't make a
mistake when I put you
and that lame partner
of yours on the payroll.
Why me?
I was just following orders.
Yes, don't you
think I know that?
I know that.
It's just, Haber, that
there comes are time when,
in every man's
life, when he's got
to start earning
the fucking money
that I believe that
I'm beginning to waste.
But I'm just asking you
to go up to that house,
knock on the door, and
you see if anybody's in.
And how the fuck am I
supposed to do that, Jack?
[chuckling]
You're a policeman,
aren't you?
Do what a fucking
policeman does!
Oh, don't worry.
Like a policeman, I'm not
gonna ask you to do it alone.
Oh no.
I'll send somebody with you.
They can-- they can hold
your little pink hand.
Isn't there a better
way to do this, Jack?
I mean, couldn't we--
I didn't seem to be
getting through to you, do I?
You see, Haber,
I'm not asking you.
I'm telling you.
You go up there.
Or I'm gonna fucking put
an end to your career
right here and now.
Move!
You move!
[click]
Now.
Wait, I'm a police officer!
Officer Haber, Officer
Mann, Officer Ruben.
We'd like to speak to you
about a man named Fisher.
Far enough!
May we come in?
You can come forward, but
those two stay where they are.
[gunfire]
Help!
Help me!
Well, it appears we have
underestimate Mr. Keller again.
Shut up.
Keller, just give us
the money, and we'll go!
Just like the original deal!
Yeah, was rape part
of the original deal?
Just call that
a fringe benefit!
No extra charge
for that, soldier.
I'm sick of playing
with those assholes.
[gunfire]
I'll get the others.
Let's go.
We've lost.
I think we should
pull back and regroup.
What are doing?
Turning chicken, right?
I knew you were
nothing but a pussy.
I'd much rather be alive.
[laughter]
I'd much rather be
alive, wouldn't you?
If you wanna regroup,
then fucking regroup!
Richardson!
You think you're smart.
but you're not.
What?
You're not smart.
You of all people should
know that you can't leave me.
Oh, Jack.
[gunfire]
Does anybody
else want to leave?
Hm?
Jack, Jack.
Look, I was thinking.
If-- if we could put
those lights out,
it'll be a little easier
for us to get around.
Shit!
Now what?
I don't know, Michael.
I guess we think like bats.
Something's moving out there.
John, look out!
Come on, John!
No.
John, please.
Get up!
No!
Motherfuckers!
[yelling]
Little prick!
Hey, Harry.
Do you like the beach?
What the fuck are you
talking about, Michael?
I was just wondering.
Ow!
I smell gas.
Yeah.
Shit, it's on fire!
Michael!
Whoa!
I finally get to meet
the great musician.
Let her go, Fisher.
She's got nothing
to do with this!
Oh, on the contrary, she has
everything to do with this.
You see, when I have
finished with you,
she's gonna be covering
for the Marissa.
I no longer have.
I can get the money.
This is-- this is not
about money anymore!
This-- this-- this
is about family.
See, you took my family from me.
Now you've-- you've got to pay.
Hey, dip brain!
Lisa, come on!
Michael!
Down there!
[screaming]
It's the last body, sir.
Is there anything else you
want us to do before we go?
Tom?
Huh?
What did you say?
Is there anything you want
us to check on before we leave?
No, I guess not.
[coughing]
Aw man, I sure used to
love this fucking place.
[laughter]
Here we are.
Thank God.
How about some breakfast?
How about some fried eggs?
What do you think?
[laughter]
Sounds great.
Oh, God.
Oh, Harry.
So much for "home
sweet home," huh?
And what is this?
It's called "money."
How's the Caribbean sound?
Great.
Michael!
Are you serious?
Remember that boat
we talked about?
Yeah.
We're getting it.
Hey, this is Fisher's money.
We earned it.
It's our money.
Wrong.
It's my money.
Ah, who the hell is this?
Hand it over.
Chief Detective Thomas Marsh.
You forgot to add,
formerly of the LAPD.
Thanks to you, this
money is my ticket out.
I can just see
the headlines now.
Chief of detectives linked to
gangland figure in graft probe.
Not to mention accomplice
to how many murders, huh?
Ah, yes, yes.
Well, unfortunately, money
rather than duty calls.
After all, this is
America, is it not?
Yeah, now you know why
they call 'em "pigs."
You, pass me that money.
Easy now, cowboy.
Nice and easy.
That's very funny.
Well, it was nice meeting you.
Harry!
MICHAEL (VOICEOVER):
Well, I knew it would take
a miracle to bring Harry back.
And that's just what happened.
You know the old saying,
"old soldiers never die.
They just go to the dogs."
On the beach, that is.
Who says revenge isn't sweet?
[chuckling]
SONG: I was trying to
live my life alone.
Refusing to believe that
love could make me whole.
Still, it seems no
matter how I hide,
there's something in my
heart won't be denied.
It's the lonely love that
turns the world this way.
Changing night to day
when I lose my way.
It's the lonely love
that takes away the pain
and brings me home again.
It's the only love.
It's the lonely love that
turns the world this way.
Changing night to day
when I lose my way.
It's the lonely love
that breaks away the pain
and brings me home again.
It's the only love.