>> Welcome back, motherfuckers.
I am the supreme originator.
The number-one innovator.
And I am sick and tired of you
motherfucking player haters.
It's been a long God damn time,
but I am back.
Yes, I am back on the scene.
Now sit down and relax
and screw your wig on tight.
Now get ready to take a trip
with me.
Yes, me, the bad ass Dolemite.
[ Explosion ]
[ Shouting ]
Keep it real.
[ R&B music plays ]
There he is!
Pull over.
I get give points for this
motherfucker.
>> He's thinking he's sweet,
look at him.
>> We work for Mr. Green
and you know God damn well
you never put the money in.
Turn the money in and in return
you'll get our shit.
This is only a lesson.
Hey, look, I'm going to go
to the bathroom.
I'll be right back.
Peace.
>> What you doin', man?
>> I'm having a good time.
>> You goin' to be dancing
with my girl now?
>> It's a free country.
I'll dance with whoever
I want to.
>> Oh, you hard?
>> Yeah, whatever you want
to call it.
>> Oh, you hard?
>> Yeah.
>> You hard?
[ Gunshots ]
[ Police siren ]
>> Look at his big, soft ass.
I could smoke that mark
right now.
>> Ain't no point.
>> Shit, there is to me.
I don't know 'bout y'all.
>> What the fuck y'all
waiting on then?
Let's do this.
[ Gunshots ]
[ Tires squeal ]
>> Yeah, they on their way.
Yeah, Tritty the only
one scrapped.
>> Let them punks in.
>> Come in.
What can I do for you?
>> Ah, Boo.
You remember me, don't you?
>> I remember everybody, Money.
What did you come in here for?
>> For my money, man.
You owe us a little fatty.
What's happening?
>> There you go, pal.
>> What the fuck is this?
Where's the rest of my money,
man?
You owe me a lot more than this,
homie, what's up?
>> That's it, pal.
Take it and get the fuck out.
Oh, and by the way,
leave your strap at the desk.
You're fired.
>> Fired?
What you mean, nigga?
>> You talkin' about Tritty?
It ain't, Blue, man.
Where the fuck is the money,
man?
People like me gotta pay bills
and shit, dawg.
>> When I ask you
to take somebody out,
I don't mean you showcasing
a driveby.
It makes me look bad.
>> The motherfucker is dead,
ain't he?
The job is done.
>> But now you've got 5-O
breathing down my neck, fool.
Now take your shit
and get the fuck out.
I got things to do.
>> Oh, no, no.
This conversation
ain't over, Blue.
Me and you,
we have things to talk about.
Oh, yeah, a lot more to talk
about.
I'll be seeing you, Blue.
All of y'all.
I'm keeping my strap, nigga.
I don't ever leave without my
strap.
See you later, Blue.
>> Think quick, Blue.
We'll pop your ass over there.
>> Bye.
Dennis, Jackson follow them.
I think they just had
a bad accident.
>> [ Laughing ]
Got you, boss.
>> And they didn't survive.
>> We gotta find more work,
baby.
>> Chump change. Come on, man.
Shoot or raise, boy.
>> What you waitin' on, man?
>> Shoot it. You think anyone...
>> Yeah, shut up, nigga.
[ Arguing ]
>> Give me the dice.
>> ...my cards, man.
>> Shit, man.
Lay some more money down on the
street.
>> Shoot it, man, shoot it.
>> Break yourself.
>> Yo, Trigger.
Yo, Trigger!
>> What the fuck you want,
nigga?
You better break up outta here
before I smack you, fool.
>> Come here.
>> Can't you see I'm busy?
>> I've got a message from Blue.
>> Who?
[ Automatic gunfire ]
>> It's me, your sister Janice.
Well, I had to call.
We need you here.
Things are bad.
>> How bad are they, honey?
>> Baggy pants wearing
stupid fools, they bringing
the neighborhood down.
Settin' a terrible example
for the young people.
>> Well, what do you want me
to do, honey, about it?
What about the police?
>> Oh, no, the police
have their hands full.
>> My boys have been
wanting to come to the States
for a good while.
I'm going to give them
a vacation.
>> Oh, you will?
>> Yes.
>> Ah.
>> We'll be on the next flight.
>> Okay, I'll see you
when you get here.
>> It's now time to give,
praise the Lord.
The more you give,
the more you shall receive.
Praise the Lord.
>> I have what I'll give!
>> George, sit your ass down.
One hundred dollars?
I'll bless you when we get home.
Praise the Lord.
>> Amen.
>> Good afternoon,
ladies and gentlemen.
This is your captain speaking.
Welcome to the United States.
On the behalf of African
Airlines and the entire crew,
we'd like to thank you
for flying with us.
Have a pleasant stay here
in Los Angeles, California.
>> What up, Reverend?
Holy shit, you really scared
the hell out of me.
Oh, forgive me, Lord.
Uh, how can I help you
gentlemen today?
>> We didn't mean to scare you,
but what you can do for us
is relieve yourself
of that case.
>> That's the church offerings.
The Lord wouldn't want you
to do this, my sons.
>> Give up the case,
you phony ass nigga.
Besides, I ain't gonna
tell the Lord if you ain't.
Let's roll, homes.
>> Oh, Lord.
>> Hey, sucka.
Move this bitch out of my way!
>> Give the case back!
>> Back my ass.
Now you move this fucker
or I'll blow it up.
>> Give the case back!
[ Electric shocks ]
>> Oh, shit!
Oh, shit!
>> God damn.
>> What's going on?
What's going on, man?
>> Ask Marvin Gaye,
motherfucker.
>> Oh, shit.
>> Forget about the case, man.
Let's go!
>> My case!
Thank you, Lord!
>> You're welcome, Reverend.
[ Laughing ]
[ Doorbell ]
>> Cal, would you get that,
please?
Thank you, baby.
>> Miss Janice,
there's someone here to see you.
>> Ah!
Hey, baby!
Thanks for coming to my place!
This is what I was
talking about, look.
We do after school
sessions here.
We do all kinds of classes.
>> This is just what I need.
[ Shouting ]
>> Oh, how do you like your
chauffeur?
>> I got what I like
and I like what I see and I want
to thank you for bringing her
because you know what I like,
baby.
>> All right, let me show you
around.
Everybody, remember me
speaking of my brother?
Well, here he is, Dolemite!
>> Thank you.
Sisters and brothers,
my sister called me
all the way from Africa
to come here to help you
all take the community back
from the thugs, cutthroats,
and gangbangers.
I brought my two sons with me
and they are specialists
in martial arts training.
They will teach you
how to defend yourself,
but I don't want you to use
the art in the wrong way.
When we teach you this art,
it is not for you
to go out here and pick fights.
So I got something to show you.
So brothers and sisters,
I want you all to watch this.
So if I can do all of that
at my age,
I know you all can do it better.
So keep it real.
>> Girls, your Uncle Dolemite
is here.
I asked him to come here.
Something has happened and...
I'll just let him tell you.
>> Girls, your mother asked me
to come here.
She asked me
to come here for a reason.
Because when the streets
were bad twenty-five years ago,
before you all were born,
I always straightened it out.
She said, "Brother, come."
So I am back to see
that young ladies like you
all will be able
to walk the streets in peace.
>> Why do you have to go?
How come you can't just leave it
to the police?
>> The police is the last ones
to take care of situations
like this.
>> Please Uncle Dolemite,
please promise us
you'll come back safe.
>> Dolemite knows
not everything.
>> Promise me!
>> I promise with every breath
in my body, I promise.
I promise.
I'm looking for Officer Blakely.
By the way, is he still working
in your department?
Downtown?
Undercover?
Captain, did I understand
you to say he was
working undercover?
Well, thank you.
Thank you very much.
[ Punches landing ]
>> Yo, where you going with my
radio, you piece of shit?
I'm talking to you.
I said where you going
with my radio?
I said stop!
[ Gunshot ]
>> Sounds like you guys
havin' a bad day.
>> Bad day?
Give me the fucking radio,
you old piece of shit.
>> You want this radio?
>> Yeah, I want your fucking
radio.
>> Shoot him!
Shoot him, shoot him!
>> What the hell is goin' on?
And what is your name anyway,
man?
>> Who wants to know?
>> I want to know who you are
and what is going on down here.
Any man that can
shoot like you...
You remind me of that Chicago
detective named Two-Gun Pete.
>> Well, for your information
they call me Blakely.
>> Blakely!
God damn!
Blakely, Blakely, Blakely!
I've been looking
for your ass all over town.
>> Who are you?
>> I am Dolemite,
the bad Dolemite.
>> I should've known,
all that African shit on.
>> Let me take you home with me
so you can chat with us
and get out of them funky
ass clothes.
>> Those are some of the
pictures I want you to look
at.
>> Now, if you gentlemen
would like anything else,
I'll be right inside.
>> Thank you, sister.
>> And I want to thank you
for letting me squat here last
night, Dolemite.
I feel much better.
>> You look better, brother.
You even smell better.
But I can't understand
you being down here in this
funky ass skid row alley.
>> Well, you know the old
saying, if you want something
done, you've got to do it
yourself.
>> I'm sure you can find
somebody that can do this
instead of you, brother.
>> Nobody gonna do that shit,
Dolemite, nobody but me.
I know how to do it and you know
I know how to do it.
That's why I do it.
>> It's a dirty job,
but if anybody can do it,
I believe you can.
>> You know it, too.
I better get out of here.
I've got things to take care of.
>> One minute.
Take them funky ass clothes with
you.
>> Same old Dolemite.
>> Oh, my Lord.
How can a man be so lucky?
Look at you!
Take a little bit off
the top, baby.
Come here.
Oh.
Damn, White, did you call
before you come over?
>> Yeah, Blue.
I was just driving past.
Thought I'd drop by.
Hey, where's your daddy?
>> He's in the back.
Why?
>> I thought I'd just run
something by him.
>> Well, run it by me first
and I'll tell him.
>> Hold it.
I thought I saw Mr. White
come through.
Now, give me a break.
>> Later, White.
>> Mr. White,
would you like to have a drink?
>> Nah, I'm still on duty,
but I'll have
some of that candy over there.
>> Mr. White, you don't
want none of that candy.
There's no telling what Blue
and those girls got mixed with
that candy.
An apple a day
keep the doctor away.
Have an apple, Mr. White.
>> I like apples.
Hey, what I wanted to tell you
was you've got big trouble
coming your way.
>> What kind of trouble?
>> Yeah, there's this dude
in town that calls himself
Dolemite.
>> Dolemite?
>> Yeah.
>> Mr. White, that's old news.
I know Dolemite.
Didn't you bring more news than
that?
>> Mr. J.L. Al Green.
>> That's me.
>> Yeah.
I'm a cop,
and I'm a nosey cop, secondly.
You know he's aiming
to shut you down?
>> Where'd you get that news
from?
>> You remember that by-the-book
cop, Blakely?
He's got a big mouth, if you get
my drift.
>> I get your drift, Mr. White.
Take this money and drift
your cop ass on out of here.
>> I'll see you later,
alligator.
[ Chuckles ]
>> See you later, Mr. White.
Blue!
Get in here!
>> What's up, Pop?
>> Dolemite! Dolemite!
Get Dolemite!
>> Consider it done.
>> Hold it!
Don't kill him.
Don't even harm him.
Dolemite is mine.
Bring him to me.
Now get Dolemite.
Get out of here!
>> All right, come on.
You heard him. Let's move. Move!
>> Dolemite. Dolemite.
Dolemite.
>> Hello, darling.
>> That's Dolemite!
>> The Dolemite?
>> Every day and every week.
I noticed you running past
my car
and you look simply marvelous.
>> Thank you.
>> Did you know I was a doctor?
>> A doctor?
>> Sex philosophy.
[ Girls gasp ]
>> I do have a PhD.
>> A PhD?
>> A pretty hard dick, baby.
>> Step around to the back,
girls.
Yes, that's it.
You don't have to pull 'em all
the way off, just pull 'em down.
Ladies, this is your first class
and you're getting
a stand up in it class.
Stand up in it, baby.
That's what I'm doing.
Stand up in this motherfucker.
Oh, this class is right.
When I'm finished with the
black, I'm going to jump on the
white.
[ Moaning ]
[ R&B music plays ]
>> * So I can stand up in it
* Stand up in it
>> Stand up in it.
Stand up in it.
>> You know he can't do it.
>> I bet you he has a small
peepee.
>> What's taking him so long,
anyway?
I have to go.
>> Girls?
I'm going to make love
not too slow and not too fast.
like I did in the past.
You're some beautiful ladies
and stolen out of sight.
I want you to get ready to go
on this trip with bad,
bad Dolemite.
>> Oh, I can't wait.
>> Oh, Dolemite!
Dolemite!
>> Oh, Dolemite,
what did you do to us?
I've never been made love
to like that before.
>> Yeah, how can a man
your age make love like that?
>> I may be too damn old
to cut the mustard.
Oh, baby, but I can god damn
sure lick out the jar.
Oh, my.
>> [ Giggles ]
>> Oh, shoot.
Dolemite, you dropped...
What's this?
Hey, girl?
>> Hmm?
>> This guy was using Viagra.
>> Now you know he was sure
using something.
>> But I thought he was real.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> Harder. Come on, kick harder.
>> It's Blakely.
You didn't call him back.
He says it's important.
>> Oh, I forgot all about
that Blakely.
My bag, man.
Blakely, where you at?
Daphne's on Manchester?
I'll be over there
in about a half hour.
Janice?
>> Hmm?
>> I'll be home after a while.
>> Okay.
>> Well, Dolemite,
it's just about time I want you
to meet my friend Marsha here.
>> Nice to meet you, Marsha.
>> You know those guys
that are looking for you
that I was telling you about,
the Mega Pointers?
>> The Mega Point guys, those
cats that was in the alley
talking that Mega Point shit?
>> That's right.
Well, you know who's behind this
is Elmo Green.
Willy Green's brother.
>> Willy Green.
>> That Willy Green.
>> So they're our problem.
Blakely, you know we're going
to have to stop them.
>> You know it's not going to be
that easy.
>> I will rain on their parade
so hard, they will think
it's judgment day.
Now watch this.
[ Electricity zapping ]
[ Shouting ]
>> What the hell did you do to
me?
[ Chortles ]
Damn.
>> Get out the car, get out!
>> Who are you guys
and who do you want?
>> Oh, I like the bread you got.
I know you got some cheddar.
Look at how this cat's dressed.
>> Dolemite, what do we do now?
>> Dole-who?
What did you call him? Dole-who?
>> Dolemite, motherfucker.
>> Dolemite, we got every boy
in the hood looking for you.
We'd get big Mega Points
for you man.
>> I oughta take this gun
and make you eat it,
motherfucker.
>> Fifty-five on this one,
right here.
>> [ Laughs ]
>> Good job, Jackson.
So I finally get to see
the so-called badass Dolemite.
>> In living color.
Dolemite is my name
and fucking up motherfuckers
is still my game.
>> Watch your mouth, tough guy.
Sit down.
I'll be outside.
>> You've got the nerve
to show your face in my town
after what you've done
to my brother?
>> You know Willy Green was
a martial arts fighter and good?
When I got hold of him
I made damn sure
it was a fair fight.
>> Fair fight my ass.
Yes, you were the executor.
This time, I guarantee you you
are going to be executed.
Executed!
[ Laughs slowly ]
It's a pleasure having you here,
Mr. Dolemite.
A little celebration,
I would say.
That's what my brother
would say.
>> Why you no business, barn,
junk-yard son of a bitch!
You better celebrate now
because when I get loose
you'll be celebrating with him.
>> Now that wasn't very nice,
Mr. Dolemite.
You show some respect
to my father.
>> Back up motherfucker!
>> That's okay, son.
Those words you'll live to eat,
my friend.
You and your entire family
are going to pay for it all.
Blue!
>> Yeah?
>> Go down to the club,
there's a dancer
and a rapper down.
I want you to check them out.
Dennis, get this motherfucker
out of here!
He makes me sick!
Put him in the basement!
>> I want you to try
some of that wicked shit
now so I can put a bullet up
your so-called witchcraft ass.
>> Up your mammy's crap,
motherfucker!
>> [ Laughs ]
Come on.
>> Captain?
>> Did I tell you the joke
last week about the fly man and
the...
>> Yeah, you told me.
>> I'll tell you another one.
>> Officer Blakely?
>> Yes, can I help you?
>> Dolemite's been kidnapped.
>> Who are you?
>> I'm Dolemite's chauffeur,
Angela.
>> You mean, as pretty as you
are, they kidnapped him and left
you? Right.
>> Motherfucker, listen to me.
Dolemite's been kidnapped.
>> Look girl, you better
not be kidding with me.
Anybody call me a motherfucker
has got to be serious.
So where did they take him?
>> I don't know.
>> Put the gun away, Johnson.
Okay, Angela, get in the car
and we'll talk about it. Okay?
Come on.
So, you don't know
where they took him?
>> No.
>> Well, you know we've got
to run this by Janice first.
All right?
OK, let's go, Johnson.
>> I knew something like
this was going to happen.
What are we going to do?
>> You're not going
to do anything.
You're going to stay put.
I'm going to pickup
a few of my boys
and we'll be back at your house
in about twenty minutes, okay?
All right, stay cool. Let's go.
>> They've got my brother.
They've got my brother, oh, God.
[ Chatter ]
>> That's what I'm talking
about.
All right everybody,
let me have your attention.
Nuthead, Spencer, Martin,
and Brick, step to the front.
My daddy told me
to reward you all.
These four men
are to be congratulated
for the capture of Dolemite!
Let's hear it for them!
That's right!
Yes.
Y'all give it up!
That's what I'm talking about!
You know that.
>> I would like to say to each
and every one of you,
give these four men
on the East Side a thunderous
round of applause again.
[ Applause ]
And while you're at it,
give yourself a round of
applause.
>> All right!
>> I have one more small job.
I am so happy I have captured
Mr. Dolemite, but I want you
to give me your three best men.
I want his entire family.
I want to have fun
with the entire Dolemite family.
Can you handle that?
>> Mm, mm, mm.
All right, everybody else
out, enjoy yourself.
>> While you funky motherfuckers
sitting up there playing cards
and I'm hungry as hell.
Get me some food!
>> Ah, you're so bad, Dolemite.
I didn't know you ate food.
>> Ain't that a bitch.
If I wasn't tied up,
I'd hang these hush puppies up
your motherfucking ass.
>> Jackson, go get him
a hamburger.
>> Son of a bitch,
don't you go out and get me
no God damn hamburger.
Bring me a steak sandwich!
>> Okay, is that it?
>> No, no, bring him a soda.
And bring me a steak sandwich
and a milkshake.
>> You got it.
>> Oh, well, thank God.
>> Sorry I'm late.
>> Well, what took you so long?
>> I had to pick up the A-Team.
This is Mitch,
that's Crazy Johnson there.
>> Yeah, hello.
>> Geez, Johnson.
>> Well, what's up with
the A-Team?
>> Well, they were here.
They went on over to Charlie
Blue's without you.
>> Ah, well I'm sorry
about that, but in the meantime
we're going to get your brother.
You might get a call from a guy.
We don't want you to go.
You stay here, and you give me a
call.
>> Okay.
>> Okay, let's go.
>> Come on, Johnson.
>> Let's go, Johnson.
>> You're paranoid.
>> Be careful.
>> Here's your food, man.
Oh, by the way,
those girls are here.
>> Oh, they fine, huh?
>> Oh, yeah.
Tell the emcee
to put them up right away.
>> Okay, I'll be upstairs.
>> All right, if you're so
damn hungry, well,
here's your last supper.
Anything for the executor
before he is executed.
>> Motherfucker, wash your nasty
ass funky hands.
Your hands smell
like womp pussy.
>> So you don't want this, huh?
>> Get that shit away from me.
>> I'll tell you what,
it's this or nothing.
[ Coughing ]
>> Get me a drink of water,
motherfucker. Get me some water!
>> Now you want some water, huh?
>> Get some water, man!
>> I'll get you some damn water.
[ Coughing continues ]
>> Yo, yo, yo, pull over.
That's it right there.
>> How the hell you know
where she live at?
>> What's up with that, homes?
How the fuck you know where she
at?
>> Man, what does it matter?
We're here, ain't we?
>> Yeah, we're here.
Nolan, you come with me.
>> Wait, wait, wait.
What if she don't open the door,
then what, homes?
>> We'll break it the fuck down.
>> Nah, y'all both chill.
I got a better idea.
>> What?
You got some trick shit?
You know something I don't know?
>> Yeah, something like that.
>> Something like that?
You better not fuck this up.
He fucking better hurry up,
I know that.
I don't know about this boy.
>> What the fuck is up
with that, homes?
>> I don't know.
We'll see, though.
We will see.
>> My brother!
Who done it?
>> Well, I'll be damned.
Ain't that a bitch?
She let him in.
>> The fuck?
>> Man, come on, man.
What the fuck
is he doing in there?
Fucking her?
>> I don't know.
What the fuck is taking him
so long, homes?
>> If this shit ain't right,
we kill his ass.
[ Janice Sobbing ]
>> He's fucking got her.
He got her, homes.
We're gonna get paid.
Well, I'll be damned.
>> Oh, my God.
Oh, God.
>> All right, homes, take her
through the back, all right?
>> Nah, take her through
the side so nobody sees her.
>> Where are we going to go?
>> Why is he in her ear?
>> You know why?
Because he wants
her pussy, homes!
>> Play along with me.
>> He's a fucking horny
bastard, homes.
>> Yeah.
>> Everything is going
to be all right.
>> Oh, God.
[ Snoring ]
>> God damn, son. What is this?
Hey! Wake your ass up!
Is this what I'm paying you for?
>> I'm awake. I'm awake.
>> Mr. Dolemite,
we have your sister
and my people
are looking for your boys.
As soon as I find them,
I got a little show
for you to see.
After that, it's going to be you
and me.
Tighten that shit up, please!
>> [ Shouts ]
[ Electricity zapping]
>> Now, that's witchcraft
for you, motherfucker!
>> Please welcome to the stage
the very lovely,
the very sassy Bitter Honey.
[ Applause ]
>> Right now,
you know what I'm saying.
>> Nolan! What's up, man?
Where the stuff at?
We need this.
>> She's back there somewhere.
>> Yo, come on. Come on, man.
>> She ain't in here.
Nolan!
Come on man, what is --
>> All right, fellas, I'm a cop.
Put your guns down, turn around,
and put your hands on that wall.
>> I knew your bitch ass
was a cop.
>> It don't have to be like
this, fellas, just turn around,
put your guns down,
put your hands on the wall.
>> Didn't think this shit
was going to happen, did you?
>> You put it down, homes.
There's two of us,
only one of you.
We'll blast your ass,
motherfucker.
[ Empty gun clicks ]
[ Gunshots ]
>> Bitter Honey.
[ Cheering ]
>> Jaz?
Jaz, come on out, it's okay.
>> Oh, my God.
What happened here?
What's all that shooting?
>> I'll tell you later.
>> Are they dead?
>> All right, it's time, now
it's time to introduce the
winner of the third annual Elmo
Green Talent Show and Fish Fry.
To do the honors, please welcome
to the stage Mr. Elmo Green
and Blue.
Come on, give it up!
[ Loud Applause ]
>> Good evening,
ladies and gentlemen.
Welcome to Charlie Blue's.
At this particular time,
we'd like to call the winners
to the bandstand --
Taste of Honey.
Beautiful young ladies,
give them another round of
applause.
Ladies? Ladies?
At this particular time,
I'd like to present you
with five thousand dollars.
You are the winner!
>> Give it to your mammy,
motherfucker!
Come on down!
>> You ruined everything,
motherfucker!
Get him!
[ Electricity zapping ]
[ Thunder ]
[ Police siren ]
It's the cops!
Let's go!
Come on!
>> I want to tell you one thing,
you tell Elmo Green every time
there's a fight,
I'm going to win it.
I'll fuck up a motherfucker
every fifteen minutes!
>> Hello.
Reggie, Mitch.
Where's Johnson?
>> Here he comes.
>> Look what just came in.
>> Oh, not again.
God damn.
Look at that.
>> That's harsh.
>> Look at that, Nolan.
God damn, look at that.
Same old thing.
Do you know whose work that is?
>> Yeah, that's Blue.
>> That's right.
>> Gotta be Blue's boys.
>> Speaking of work,
I wonder what's working
with Jaz nowadays,
you know, Dolemite's sister.
>> Yeah, how is
Dolemite's sister, Nolan?
>> Watch it.
Speaking of her, man,
I will never forget the look
on her face when I told her
I was an undercover cop.
>> Come on, Nolan, tell the
truth. You have a thing for her,
don't you?
>> Man, you mean to tell me you
trying to make it
with Dolemite's sister?
>> No, man, come on.
I mean, she's nice.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> Yeah, that's all.
>> But, I...I...
>> Got one for her, right?
>> Right, a little.
>> A little or a lot?
>> Hey, what about these bad
dudes Dolemite
wants you to get for him?
>> Oh, that's all set.
They'll be in tomorrow.
>> Oh, can we do us
a little bettin'?
>> I don't mind.
>> Sure, I bet on Dolemite.
>> And you, Reggie?
>> Who else? Dolemite.
You betting on one
of Blue's boys?
>> Betting?
Who said anything about betting?
>> [ Chuckles]
Get out of here, Nolan.
Go to work.
>> Lover boy.
>> I still think
he's stuck on Jaz.
>> It's true.
>> Okay, let's get out of here
and go to work y'all.
>> Hello?
Oh...
It's Elmo Green.
>> Elmo Green?
>> He wants to speak to you.
>> I want to talk to him, too.
Elmo Green, are you still
running, motherfucker?
What's up now?
>> Mr. Dolemite,
you're a very smart man.
I have a deal that
might interest the both of us.
Would you like to hear it?
>> I want to hear it if it's
getting rid of your funky ass.
>> That works both ways pal.
>> I'm waiting.
Let's both you and I stage a
fight.
Your people against my people.
>> Yes, motherfucker,
it is time for a showdown.
When I see you, all hell
is going to break lose
because we are going
to whoop your ass to Sunday
and be waiting for you
on Monday motherfucker.
Now, where is the place?
>> Ballser Park tomorrow
at high noon.
>> We'll be there and I want
to let you know one thing,
if you want to get some ass
you got to bring some ass
and that's what we're ready
and waiting for,
is to kick your
motherfucking ass Elmo Green.
>> I want your ass deader
than a doorknob, Mr. Dolemite.
>> Brothers and sisters,
I just got off the phone
with Elmo Green and he claims
when he claims
when he meets me again,
it will be
the fight of the century.
I say to you all, we got
to look over our shoulders
because I am here to tell you
that he will never beat me
with the mystical powers
that I have learned in Africa.
Peanut?
>> Yeah, boss, right here.
>> The remedy that I got
will energize your body
and make you powerful
and strong.
[ Barnyard sounds ]
[ Mechanical whirring ]
I'm over here.
I'm over here, motherfucker.
[ Dog barking ]
Here.
Right here. Here.
[ Echoing ] Here!
Did you all see
just what happened?
This stuff stimulates you
and gives you the strength
and power that you need
to beat Elmo Green.
I call it Voodoo Juice.
>> I'm not going to drink that.
That looks like blood.
>> We got to take it
because we need everything
to make it work.
So let's get ready and go.
We're wasting time.
Is this Ballser Park?
It is?
Well, I hope Elmo Green
don't flake out
and don't show up.
Son...
[ Mumbles ]
You know I've fought all over
the world.
I've kicked asses until my feet
were raw in Panama,
cut up in Connecticut,
had to fight a war in Warsaw.
I can take care of myself.
Look at all of these people
who showed up.
I'm going to give them a battle
that they'll always remember.
A battle of the centuries,
the bad Dolemite and Elmo Green.
>> Well, son, this is it.
After twenty-five years,
this old bitch is back.
I see you got things
half way together.
It's going to be a nice
afternoon.
Dolemite, I'm just sick of the
name, Dolemite.
>> Oh, I think he's here.
Yes.
[ National anthem plays ]
>> Good evening, everyone.
Welcome to the fight
of the century.
We've got Elmo Green's crew
over here, we've got
Dolemite's crew over here.
We do promise
a spectacular fight,
but first, would you believe --
wait a minute, man,
I'm not fighting.
It will all be over soon.
>> Look at that bad, bad Mit Su!
>> Mit Su! Kick ass, Mit Su!
>> Nice one!
Ass kick!
>> Don't say ass kick, son.
Kick ass! Kick ass!
>> What is this?
They're kicking their ass
kicked out there.
Where'd you get them?
Without guns, they ain't shit.
>> Don't worry about it, dad,
we got more people coming.
>> Well, you need to show me
some, before I see it.
Yeah, yeah, much, much better.
That other one, man.
>> From what I can see now,
this could be very bad.
>> That's my kind
of girl, there.
>> Yeah, another Dole-bitch
down!
>> Where'd you get that girl?
I never saw her.
Where'd you get her?
>> Oh!
>> Kick his ass, come on!
>> Show me what you can do.
>> Yeah!
[ Cheering ]
>> Okay, ladies and gentlemen,
it's been a great fight so far,
but I'm about to take
on the second set of fighters.
>> Okay, son, it's time
to get this shit on the way,
wipe this slate clean.
Let me out of here.
Got the nerve to come
in a limousine.
>> I want his ass!
I want to kick his ass
from Genesis to Revelation!
Let me out of this vehicle!
Let me out!
>> Ass kick.
>> I want you, baby.
I want that motherfucker, bad!
Elmo Green,
you dirty motherfucker,
your ass belong to me.
If I can pick up that rock
that killed the giant Goliath,
and whoop Nero's ass for
setting Rome on fire,
your ass is mine, motherfucker!
>> Talk is cheap and grass
is free, now Mr. Dolemite,
it's time for you to see me.
>> [ Whooping ]
>> Get out of here.
I won't be long.
>> Dolemite, Dolemite, Dolemite!
>> I'm sick of this
old motherfucker.
If this motherfucker
is going to fight like he talks,
I might have a job on my hands.
The last time I saw
this motherfucker,
he was running!
I'm talking about you,
son of a bitch.
You can run,
but you damn sure can't hide.
>> All right, Mr. Dolemite,
it's on.
Come on, motherfucker.
>> How do you like that?
Come on!
You want to play, motherfucker?
>> Kick him! Kick him!
>> He's got electric
shooting out of him!
>> Die, motherfucker!
I'm going to tell you all,
when this motherfucker comes to,
I want you to get his ass
out of town!
All the rest
of you sons of bitches,
when Dolemite comes through,
I want you to bow down,
motherfuckers, bow down!
[ Whooping ]
>> Hey, come on. Get off!
>> Get in there. Get in there.
>> Hello?
Oh, Dolemite, what's up?
Oh, you need a massage, right?
I know just the place to send
you, to a girl named Asia.
She's a good friend of mine.
I'll call you with the
information when I get to
office.
All right, buddy.
>> [ Scatting ]
>> Hello, Mr. Dolemite.
I want you to sit back and relax
because I'm going
to make you feel real good.
>> That's just what I need.
You know, I had to whoop
a motherfucker's ass today.
>> Mr. Dolemite, fighting again?
>> Yes, that's why my body
is all tensed up.
You know,
life has a lot of pictures,
but right now, I see bras.
But I think my body needs
a good, soothing
relaxing massage.
>> Yes, and that's just
what you're going to get.
>> [ Moaning ]
Oh, baby, that feels good.
Oh, do it like a nice girl
should.
Oh, back to the left,
back to the right.
Scratch it, baby, with all your
might.
Scratch it, scratch it, scratch
it!
Oh, that feels good, baby.
>> Turn over.
>> Oh, baby.
Wow!
Oh, don't go, baby.
Don't hide them.
Let me look again.
Let me see it one more time.
Just one more time.
>> Only if you're a good
little boy.
>> Baby, I promise.
I promise!
[ Whooping ]
>> [ Moans ]
Oh, Dolemite!
[ Moaning loudly ]
Mr. Dolemite, you're so good,
but I'm not surprised.
>> Yes.
Dolemite is amazing at
making love.
to beautiful women like you.
It's my number one thing.
Wow!
>> I've already called somebody.
I don't know if they'll get here
tomorrow, but I need to --
[ Knocking ]
Call me on another phone.
Don't call on this line.
>> Elmo!
>> What's happening?
>> How are you doing, man?
Long time no see.
Man, I just learned
about you guys.
How'd you get in from Chicago
so quick? I'm glad to see you.
>> Can we help you?
>> You know for me to call you,
I've got problems,
I've got big problems.
After twenty-five years,
he's back.
Yesterday,
in front of all of my people,
he embarrassed me.
>> What's the problem?
>> He knows all kind of shit.
Trick shit -- karate.
He's like a cat with nine lives.
I want him dead.
I want him dead! Do you hear me?
Dead, dead, dead!
>> What's his name?
What's his name?
>> Dolemite!
>> Dolemite?
>> I want him dead.
>> Can you handle that?
>> It's not a problem.
I know just who to call.
>> Good, then maybe I can rest.
It's good you guys came.
[ Indistinct chatter ]
>> Excuse me, ladies and
gentlemen!
I'd like to present at this time
our district attorney.
Give her our applause, please.
>> Thank you for joining us
today and making a presentation
to one of citizens that has done
so very much for our community.
So, without any further delay,
I will present to you our mayor
to make this presentation.
>> Mr. Dolemite it is
my pleasure and honor
to thank you
for what you have done
for our children
and cleaning up the streets.
We would like to present you
the key to our city
and not only to our city,
but the key to our hearts.
Mr. Dolemite!
>> Thank you, to the mayor
and all the distinguished
people,
I want to thank you so very much
for the key to city
and I would like to thank
the beautiful district attorney
for coming out,
and my very dear friend
that's been with me for many
years, lieutenant Blakely.
And I'd like to say to my son
here that come with me
all the way from Africa
to help me curb the streets
from all the thugs
and cutthroats.
My other son who was with me
and was hurt in a little fight
the other night,
but we are still standing.
And I'd like to say that
when my sister called me
and asked me to come home
to help, I couldn't do anything
else but get here as quick as I
could.
Thank you very much.
I want to thank the lovely DA
for coming out.
Thank you, baby.
>> Blue?
>> What's up?
>> That was your daddy
on the phone.
He's real concerned
about these Chicago guys.
>> No, no, no. No, no, no.
You just tell Mr. Green
not to worry about a thing.
Just make sure we get this
Dolemite character here.
>> No problem, guarantee it.
>> Good.
>> Tell Mr. Green,
now he can rest.
[ Chuckles ]
>> Yo, boy, let's get cracking.
Take it up a notch.
[ Loud knocking ]
>> Blakely?
Blakely?
Where are you, man?
Amigo?
Have you seen Blakely?
>> No.
>> I'll be God damned.
Blakely didn't give me
another wrong address.
I need to get the hell
out of here.
And who are y'all, anyway?
What the fuck do you want?
All right, the fight is on!
[ Shouting ]
Did I hurt you?
>> Shit!
[ Electricity zapping ]
[ Shouting ]
>> Come on, come on!
You want to dance?
Oh!
[ Laughing ]
[ Whooping ]
>> Dolemite?
Kiss your nuts goodbye,
because your ass belongs to me.
>> Why, you little tide
strumpet, midget-looking
motherfucker.
You better come up
with more punch than that.
Bow down, motherfucker,
bow down!
>> Bow down?
I'll never bow down to no man.
>> I've got something
for your ass.
[ Electricity zapping ]
>> What have you done
to me Dolemite?
>> I made you just what you are,
a bitch.
Bitch, I said bow down!
>> You didn't have to go there,
Dolemite.
You didn't have to go that
far.
>> Bitch, I said bow down.
I've turned motherfuckers
into monkeys, cats,
and elephants.
Now get up!
Switch bitch!
Switch on this!
[ Laughing ]
>> Kelon, we're here
to meet with the Bishop.
He's the one who hired those
guys from Chicago that Dolemite
just fucked over all of 'em.
He fucked up
the whole operation.
He killed my brother
ten years ago.
This son of a bitch
is getting my nerves.
He's driving me crazy.
I've got to do something.
Bishop!
Look at me!
Two weeks time,
I've aged twenty years.
I am tired! I am tired!
You've got to do somebody!
>> Dolemite?
>> Yes, Dolemite!
>> He can't be that damn lucky.
He must have a horseshoe
in his ass.
We've got to get him!
I need my damn money
to hold this fucker up.
I've got to get him!
>> What you gonna do?
>> Black Chin Ho!
Boy if you see him,
he'd make a rottweiler bow down.
>> That sounds like what I need.
Get it on.
>> God damn Elmo Green!
Come out!
Come out, you ratty,
dodging motherfuckers!
Take that motherfucker!
[ Shouting ]
Come on, you rat-tooth-eating
motherfucker!
Take that motherfucker!
Bow down, motherfucker,
bow down!
Bow down!
Down, motherfucker, down!
Die!
RIP!
Rest in peace, motherfucker!
A black-ass Chinaman.
Chin Ho,
wearing that black and red.
I'm going to put my foot upside
of your motherfucking head.
Easy, easy, motherfucker.
You're a gusto son of a bitch.
Now, I want you to bow down!
Bow down!
Nice landing.
Get up, motherfucker,
so I can knock you back
down, you clown.
Chin Ho, I have the power.
It's time for you to die,
Chin Ho.
[ R&B music playing ]
Get up, bitch!
Rook and crooks,
cakes and rakes,
show me what you can do
with these motherfucking snakes.
>> [ Screaming ]
>> You rat-tooth motherfucker!
This is my final message for
that motherfucking Elmo Green!
I am determined to survive
the explosion!
[ R&B playing ]
Whoo, what you gonna do?
This is for you!
[ Screaming ]
Oh, shit!
Oh, a fat girl!
You may go to the head
of the class.
My brand-new film,
it's called
"The Dolemite Explosion."
I have been chosen
to survive the explosion.
* Put me in the midst
* I'm the bad, bad Dolemite
[ Screaming ]
[ Quivering ]
[ R&B music playing ]
I'm leaving this motherfucker.
God damn, shit.