(uplifting orchestral music)
(dramatic jazzy synthesizer music)
(suspense music)
(gunshots)
- File number 13352.
Submitting Agent C. Nelson.
Confidential.
The principles referred to in this report
are listed as Barry Rengler and Tim Gates.
Both top students at the
St. Louis Police Academy,
they were subsequently dismissed for
failing to answer a variety of charges.
In order to best understand the events
culminating in last night's
shootout in downtown
Los Angeles, it's necessary
to go back five days.
(seagulls squawking)
(dramatic flute music)
(police radio chatter)
(car pulls in and brakes)
- Whoa!
(phone beeps)
- Hola.
- Yo, what do you say, your pizza's
here, where do I bring it?
- What?
You got the wrong number,
I didn't order a pizza.
- I don't think so!
You Tim Gates?
- Yeah, I'm Tim Gates.
I'm telling you, I did not order a pizza.
- That's too bad, my friend, 'cause I
got a beautiful pepperoni and green pepper
Deluxer Pizza pizzas, now
you know what they say.
- What the hell are you talking about?
- Antonio's knows pizza
like nobody's business!
- (laughs) I'll be a son of a bitch!
- Hey buddy, how you doing?
- What the hell are you doing?
- I'm at 414 Clayton
Street, St. Louis, Missouri,
I'm at the phone booth behind
Antonio's, and it's raining!
- Oh come on, are you still in
that dump above the restaurant?
- Well I'm waiting for my ship to come in.
- Is that why you're calling?
- Actually no, I'm coming out to LA.
- I don't believe it.
- You'll believe it when you see
the whites of my beady little eyes.
Hey listen, you're the one
who told me to come visit.
Now do I need a place to stay?
Hello?
The silence is deafening.
Listen, it's no big deal,
don't worry about it,
it's only a couple of
days, I'll get a motel.
- No no no, look, I
just haven't seen you in
a long time, I just wasn't expecting this.
- Well I'll tell you the truth, I didn't
really expect to call,
but listen, I really
don't wanna put you out,
don't worry about it.
- Hey look, you know what?
You're staying with me.
All right?
Not a problem.
So when's your flight coming?
- Friday, 10:23 AM.
- Okay great, you know what?
Dress casual because the
weather here is spectacular.
- Oh damn it!
I was hoping it would rain.
(laughs) All right, I'll see you Friday.
- Yeah, I'll see you then.
- Hey Tim, listen, I'm really
looking forward to seeing you.
- Yeah, me too.
Me too.
- All right, I'll see you later.
(phone hangs up)
(dramatic jazzy music)
(airplane landing)
You look good.
- Not as good as you.
What do you do besides run,
are you lifting tall buildings?
- (laughs) Nah, I just run.
Usually from the landlord.
- All right, well no landlords this week,
okay, because you're on vacation in
Southern California and I
am your neo-native guide.
- I am all yours, you lead me, my friend.
- Hey, you know what, I could get into
some serious trouble if
anybody saw me talking
to a guy from St. Louis,
you know that right?
- Why?
- What do you mean?
Come on, the Rams, the
erstwhile Los Angeles Rams?
- I didn't get them to move
to St. Louis, are you crazy?
- Have you gone to a game yet?
- No, I can't get a ticket.
- All right, well you can get one
from me 'cause I'm all connected, okay?
- Really?
- My agency, sure.
- That would be great, that
would be great, thank you.
So how's Anita?
- Over.
Done.
- Really?
- Yeah, a long time ago.
- You're kidding me, I'm sorry.
- You ready for this?
No, don't worry about it, she moved to
Chicago with Carlin
Pardowski, can you imagine?
- What?
- I'm not kidding you.
- That fat putz?
- Uh-huh.
- Oh man.
Hey, how's Leon?
- Oh, my old man, he's the same,
he's living about 40 minutes away,
he's drinking cheap beer and cheaper wine.
I see him about every couple of years.
Works best for both of us, hey, let me
tell you, what do you think, huh?
- This is yours?
- You like?
- Like it?
This is beautiful.
Must've set you back
what, like 70, $80,000?
- I think this was 82-5, but who's
counting, I had a very good year.
- I guess so.
- Hey.
- What?
- You drive.
- Oh come on.
- Yeah, come on, we'll
do a little sightseeing,
it's all right, we'll settle
you in later, go ahead.
- Man!
Oh this is gonna be sweet.
All right, where to?
(car revs)
- Are you kidding, we're
in Southern California.
Hit it.
(tires screech)
- Woo hoo hoo!
(upbeat keyboard music)
You know, I can't believe I haven't
come out here before, I must be nuts.
- I'm telling you, you are nuts.
You could've called me anytime.
- Yeah, you know, but I just wasn't
ready to deal with what
happened yet, you know.
- Oh my God, you take things so hard.
You know, you should've done
like me, you say screw it.
You move on, there's no percentage
in carrying things with you.
- Yeah, well you know me,
I take things personally.
- Yeah, I know, I understand.
Look, it's been a few years, getting the
bitterness out of my
system, but I gotta tell
you something, that money
makes it a lot easier.
- (laughs) So let me ask you a question,
is this pretty much what you do all day,
or do you actually work for you money?
- This is it, I'm my own boss, you know?
If I want a day off, I'm the
only asshole I gotta speak to.
- I tell you, this is paradise.
- Isn't it?
- So what is it that you do?
- I take other people's
money, I invest it.
So if they make money, they share some
of it with me, the more I make
them, the more I make for myself.
- Simple.
Well not really, so what are you doing?
- Sell videos.
- Oh, like a distribution company.
- No, I manage a video
store on Clayton and Widen.
- (laughs) Come on,
Barry, are you serious?
You of all people?
I thought you'd be flying high by now.
- Well I kinda had my wings clipped.
- Oh come on, that happened to both of us.
I mean you can't dwell
on the past anymore.
I thought you'd go back to
law enforcement or something.
- I tried, believe me.
More places and people
than I can remember.
- And?
So?
- So I'm getting too old to be a rookie.
- Oh come on man, you know what?
I'm gonna introduce you to some people,
you're gonna make some connections,
you're gonna find something right here.
- I don't know Tim, I'm a
St. Louis guy, you know?
- (laughs) Come on, don't give
me that Midwestern hayseed crap.
Come on, it's time to get your life back
into gear, that's what
you came here for right?
- No!
No, I came out here for a vacation.
- Oh please.
You could've gone on vacation anywhere.
We haven't seen each other in five years.
You came here to put the past where it
belongs, behind you, and
get on with your life.
Am I right?
- Is it that obvious?
- Yeah it's that obvious,
(mumbles) with the
white, pasty face you're wearing.
(laughter)
I'll tell you something.
Two days out here in California,
man, you're gonna be a different man.
They're not even gonna
recognize who Barry Rengler was.
Trust me on this, pally.
I know of what I speak.
(synthesizer funk music)
(car door opens)
(shuffling)
- You live here?
- Yeah.
- You kidding me?
Oh my God.
- Huh?
- This should be in a movie.
- It was!
You remember the party scene
in that Tom Cruise picture?
This was this.
- Are you kidding me?
- No.
- This is not real.
- You know, a friend of mine in a studio
mentioned it to a
location scout, next thing
I know they're paying me big money
to bring gorgeous women here, I thought
I died, I thought I went to Heaven.
I met three actresses in that day alone.
- Hey man.
- Deano, baby, hey!
You hard at work, you making me money?
- That's right.
- Good.
Dean Kessman, this is Barry Rengler.
- Hey.
- Dean is my personal techno geek, huh?
- Nice to meet you man.
- My pleasure.
- Hey listen, you know what?
Why don't you take that
bedroom on the left upstairs.
- Okay.
- Get unpacked, get yourself comfortable.
- Hey Dean, nice to meet you.
- Likewise.
- All right, give it to me straight, doc.
- Well I reseated all
the drive connections,
ran a diagnostic on a D-RAM, you had some
kind of conflict that was
corrupting the encoding
every time she tried to run the Bin-X.
(Tim snores mockingly)
- Is my computer working or not?
- Like she was out of the box.
- Oh baby, Michelangelo's
a chump compared to you.
Hey, one last thing, very important.
My online files, are they secure?
Because I hadn't changed my password
before the damn thing crashed.
- They're fine.
- Yes!
Thanks.
- Fighting broke out
overnight between rival
factions along the Israeli-Syrian border.
- Hey, what are you doing?
- I lost my wallet.
- Oh, man.
Well take it easy.
Where'd you have it last?
- If I knew that, it
wouldn't be lost would it?
- This is true.
- So unbelievable, I have all my
money in there, my ID, everything.
- All right, look, don't go crazy,
just try to think, think, where was it?
- I had it with me when
I got on the plane.
Pretty sure I had it when I got off
the plane in LA and when I met you.
- You know what?
LAX.
Pickpockets.
- Oh great, this is great,
now what am I gonna do?
You know how long it's gonna take me
to get all that stuff reissued?
Especially from Missouri.
- You know what, don't
even worry about it, okay?
I'll cover you while
you're here for your trip.
- No, no, no, no!
- No, I'm serious, look, I got the cash,
it's not a big deal, you're here anyway.
You just pay me when
you get your stuff back.
- You see, I hate this, I hate being
a pain in the ass right off the bat.
- You're a pain in the ass whether
you have your wallet or
not, what's the deal?
Come on, we're friends, I haven't seen you
in a long time, let me take care of you.
- You know what, I'll
make some phone calls
and try to get the stuff replaced.
- Oh wait a minute, hang on.
You know what, just leave that
'till the morning, it's no big deal.
Come on, we're going out tonight.
I want you to put on your best threads.
- Well these are my best threads.
- (laughs) This is it?
Oh my God, maybe you'll create
a new look, Midwestern funk.
- Yeah, I doubt it.
- All right, let me help you out.
Nah nah nah.
That's it.
There we go, okay.
All right, that way so you
don't embarrass yourself.
- I'm not gonna embarrass myself.
- Well so you don't embarrass me.
- (laughs) Where we going?
(upbeat synthesizer music)
(hip hop music)
(crowd chatter)
- Here, I'm giving you
my credit card all right?
- Why?
- It would look pretty stupid if
I have to keep giving you money
all night like you're my kid brother.
- Aw come on Tim, I can't (mumbles).
- Oh God, come on, here, look,
just take some cash, okay?
Have some cash, I want you to have it,
use it in case of an emergency, all right?
Listen, Vic's the owner, anything you
want, just put it on my account.
- You know the owner?
- Yeah, actually we're partners.
- In what?
- Come on buddy, what's the matter,
you getting a little slow or what?
- Wait a minute, you
mean you own this place?
- Yeah, I got a little piece.
It's an investment, I got
tight with Vic, hey Vic!
- Hey Timmy!
- Tim!
- Baby!
(smooching)
- Hey, baby.
How are you?
- Now this must be your
cousin from Milwaukee.
- He's actually a very old friend of mine.
Cat, Bar, Bar, Cat.
- Actually St. Louis, nice to meet you.
- Hey, you've come a long
way from St. Louis, Louis.
That's an old song, in
case you don't know.
- Oh I know.
- So what's up, are you
just visiting or what?
- Yeah, I'm just visiting.
- Well you've come to the right place.
If you want, I'll show you around.
- Oh come on, it's okay.
- I'm just being friends with the tourist!
- Thank you Cat, see you
later Cat, maybe later!
Hey, is Syd around?
- She's in the back.
- Well send her out, will you?
- All right, bye Louis.
- Be careful of that one, she's a tornado.
- Really?
That's the point isn't it?
- Well I guess it can be.
Hey there you are.
Syd Deshaye, Barry Rengler, he's a
very dear old friend of mine.
- Why didn't you call me?
Joe Millston waited until after 3, Tim.
- (laughs) Syd handles
the PR for the club,
I guess I missed a meeting or something.
- A meeting we've been trying to
schedule for a month,
why didn't you call me?
- Come on Syd, take it easy, he's an
old friend, he came to town, I picked
him up, we've just been
visiting, all right?
- You could've called.
- Look, I...
- Wrangler, huh?
Just rode in today.
- Actually it's Rengler, R-E.
- Ah.
How you liking paradise so far, cowboy?
- Well I'll tell you the truth,
I could get used to this.
- Don't do that, it's not a good idea.
Out here you never wanna
take anything at face value.
Just remember that.
- And what, where are you going?
- I've got work to do.
Nice meeting you, cowboy.
- Oh come on now.
Look, I gotta go...
You know what I mean?
I'll be back in a minute, all right?
(hip hop music)
(crowd chatter)
- Are you Tim?
- Excuse me?
- It's my first night,
I was told that this
was the owner's table, so you must be Tim.
- Actually I'm a friend of Tim's.
- Okay.
If you're not Tim, then who is?
- Tim is.
(chuckles)
- Great.
- I'll point him out to
you when I see him, okay?
- Thanks.
Would you like a drink anyway?
- Yeah, can I get scotch and
soda with a splash please?
You know what, he's right there.
- Wow, he has a bit of
a temper doesn't he?
- I don't think that's any
of our business, do you?
- Brooke, Brooke Ashton.
- Hi.
- I'm trying it out for a
while, getting used to it.
What do you think, do you like it?
I thought I needed something
more professional sounding.
Because I'm an actress, but I bet you
already figured that
out because of my name.
Brooke Ashton.
I mean Mildred, what the hell
am I supposed to do with that?
- Hey, how about getting
the man his drink?
- Excuse me.
(Vic laughs)
- You don't need to
rescue me, she was cute.
- That's what you think.
I interviewed her for the job.
If you don't stop her, you'll get her
entire life story and no booze.
(laughter)
Vic Pennington.
- Hey, Barry Rengler, nice to meet you.
It's a nice place you got here, Vic.
- You a friend of Tim's?
- Yeah, from St. Louis,
I'm out here just visiting.
- Well if you need anything,
anything at all, just holler.
You're a friend of Tim Gates,
you got carte Blanche here.
- Thank you, I appreciate that.
- Look, we're out of here all right?
- What?
I just ordered a drink.
- Look, you wanna have a drink, stay here,
that's fine, okay, but
I'm leaving all right?
- It was nice meeting you, Vic.
- He'll cool off, just give him a minute.
- Hey.
Hey man, I don't know what
happened, but whatever it was...
- It's no big deal, okay, it's not
your fault, Syd just went off again.
It's no big deal.
- Was she...
- I just said it's no big deal, okay?
- (mumbles).
- Once you jump in the sack with a broad,
don't ever expect to work with them again.
Why don't I learn that?
You know what, I'm sorry, it's just...
- It's cool, forget about it.
- Syd pushes me to a point of distraction.
- Yeah, I could eat.
- All right, you know what, if we were
back home, 2 AM, where would we go?
- Fitz's, right?
- Fitz's, come on.
- Burgers, fries, right?
(laughter)
Kitchen sauce?
- Yup, absolutely.
- Oh my God, I can taste the
grease, I mean I dream of it.
- It's gone.
- What?
- Gone.
Fitz died, they tore it down.
They put in one of those giant...
You know, those giant drugstore chains.
- Oh my God, that breaks my heart.
- Well there's a lot back
home you wouldn't recognize.
- Jesus.
(laughs) Do you remember that thing that
we used to do that would
drive the girls crazy?
Huh?
- Oh God, you know I forgot about that?
- Come on man, for old time sake,
come on, do it one more time.
- Are you crazy?
- Yeah, come on, give it to me one time.
- (sighs) All right.
(clears throat)
(Barry As Tim) Barbie.
(laughter)
(Normal Voice) Hang on, wait.
(Barry as Tim) Barbie, it's Tim.
(laughter)
Listen honey, can we go out Friday night?
Listen, Barry's the one that suggested
I call you, he knows about this.
(laughter)
- Oh man.
Oh God, I miss those days.
I'm glad you're here.
- Me too.
- All right, man.
(car revs)
(dramatic orchestral music)
Boo!
Rise and shine, campers!
It's gonna be a beautiful
day in the north woods, huh?
Hey, listen, I hate to be a rude host,
but I'm gonna have to
take care of a little
bit of business for the next couple days.
- Oh, okay, I'll be fine.
- Well I mean it's not quite that simple,
I'm gonna be gone for three days.
- Really?
- Yeah, I got this client
on Catalina Island.
I made him a deal that
I would charter a boat,
I'd motor over, take
him for a little diving,
a little snorkeling,
and a lot of drinking.
- Tough assignment.
Want me to go instead?
- I would love you to,
I mean like I really
wanna pretend to be this guy's best friend
for three days just to lock up an account.
- Ugly job, but somebody's
gotta do it I guess, right?
- You know, I know you don't
believe what I do is work.
- I don't believe it's work.
- Come on man, it is,
it is, but irregardless,
you're gonna be stuck here
alone for the next three days.
- I'll be fine.
- All right, I just wanna give
you a little something, here.
- No no no, come on, no!
- Take it, take it, come
on, live it up, all right?
That's what it's here for, it's here
to enjoy and, you know, protect yourself.
(Barry laughs)
If there's anything else you
need just call Vic, okay?
He'll get it for you.
- Hey, what about Syd?
I can take care of her if you want.
- Please, trust me, stay away from Syd.
She's a nightmare, okay?
- I wasn't asking for that reason.
- Yeah, I'm sure you weren't.
Are you okay with this?
- With this, with this house, the beach?
Beautiful girls, the credit
cards, the car of cars?
- Oh yeah, the car.
(keys jingle)
Here you are.
- There's a car.
- Have a good time, all right?
- Have a good trip.
Thanks, man.
(upbeat jazzy music)
(mumbles).
(car revs)
(funky synthesizer music)
(phone rings)
(answering machine beeps)
- Hola, go ahead at the beep.
Leave the number and I'll get back.
(answering machine beeps)
- Call me, I've got a
client ready to deal.
We're talking 3.5 mill,
can you cover that?
Let me know, this guy's for real.
- Vic, yeah hey, it's me.
Listen, I forgot to mention I'm
gonna be gone for a few days, okay?
Probably getting a couple
of calls, maybe some
visits from some deals
that are still pending.
- Hey now, don't be
putting me into the middle.
- (laughs) Don't worry about it, listen,
I swear to God it's okay, all right?
Just stalling a couple of guys,
you know what I mean, some cashflow stuff.
All right?
Just tell them I'm out and I'll
call them as soon as I'm back in.
- Okay.
- Yeah, oh Vic, hey listen.
You remember that buddy of
mine that was from St. Louis?
You met him the other night.
- Barry?
- Yeah, yeah yeah yeah, that's him.
Listen man, I'd really appreciate it if
you just let him have
whatever he wants, okay?
I'll cover it.
Yeah, whatever he needs.
Whatever he orders.
That's it, just put it on my ticket okay?
- Got it.
Have a good trip.
- Thanks.
Bye.
- Tim's leaving town?
- You didn't know?
- When is he leaving?
- I don't know exactly, he didn't say.
Just that he'd be away for
a few days on business.
- Business my ass, I wonder
who she is this time.
- Hey Syd, honey, I don't
ask and neither should you.
That way madness lies.
- What did he want from you?
- Give messages if anybody calls him.
And he wants me to give
an open tab to his friend.
- The cowboy from St. Louis?
- Yup.
You know this guy?
- He's an old friend of Tim's.
I guess they have a history.
- Well I gotta get to work.
- What?
- You know Tim's friend?
Not his usual type, is he?
Or yours.
- You know what, he's an old friend.
I guess they have some catching up to do.
- I don't think so.
You know, I saw the way Tim was looking at
him when he brought him
in here the other day.
He wouldn't take that guy to the
supermarket if there
wasn't a deposit on him.
- You know something Cat, I don't
know what goes on in Tim's head.
I just know that I work
here, just like you.
So let's drop it okay?
- Okay.
(gentle jazzy music)
(car revs)
(honking)
Hey, Louis!
- Hey, Cat right?
- That's right, good memory.
So what's up?
Where's your buddy Tim?
- Away on business.
- Awww, and you're filling in
for him while he's gone huh?
Doing a fine job too.
- Just doing a little shopping.
- Uh-huh, I can see.
(laughs)
- So how long you been
working at the club?
- A couple months.
- Like it?
- Yeah, it's a job for now.
- Let me guess, you're an actress
and being a waitress in the meantime
until the right role comes along, right?
- Well you know, it's
like the big guy said.
Whole world's a stage, Louis.
Everything's just another part.
Even waitressing.
What counts is how you play it.
So you and Tim go way back?
- Far enough.
- You don't exactly strike
me as Butch and Sundance.
Come on, I'm curious, hence my name.
- Well you know what happened
because of curiosity don't you?
- I know, I can't help it, it's my nature.
So you and Gates?
- Well we were good friends
once, a long time ago.
- Uh-huh, I sense melodrama, I'm hooked.
- No no no, now it's your turn.
- (sighs) All right.
- All right.
What's the deal with Tim and Syd?
- Well in this case, what you don't
know just might save
your cute little butt.
- Well I'll keep that in mind.
- All right.
Hey, do you wanna buy me lunch?
- Yeah, okay.
- Okay.
I'm so sorry, I forgot I
can't, I don't have time.
- Oh.
- How about a rain check then?
- Fine.
- All right.
Cool, next time.
- Oh, and Louis?
Any friend of Tim's is a friend of mine.
- I'll keep that in mind too.
- You do that.
- Bye.
- Bye, Louis.
(gentle flute music)
(car lock beeps)
- Hey Tim!
Yo, man.
Whoa man, sorry, I thought you were Tim.
- I borrowed some of his clothes.
- That's right, you don't look too
close you guys could be like brothers.
- You think?
- Absolutely, two of a kind.
Hey listen, my shop's just a few blocks
down so I wanted to drop this off for him.
- Yeah okay.
He's out of town on business, when he
gets back I'll tell him you stopped by.
- He left you in charge of the home front?
- Something like that.
- So while the cat's
away, you're the mouse.
(Barry laughs)
Cool.
(glass shatters)
- You lousy son of a bitch!
- What the hell?
- Oh my God, I am so sorry.
- It's okay, I'm okay.
- No no, I thought you were Tim.
- He's (mumbles) what are you doing?
- Well I saw you from behind,
I saw that jacket and I...
- Well I borrowed it from Tim,
I thought it would be okay.
- No, it is, it's just
I gave Tim this jacket.
- Don't worry about it, I'm fine.
More importantly, what did Tim do to you
to make you wanna throw something at him?
- I planned on doing worse than that.
- (laughs) Well I'll
take your word for it.
- I'm sorry, you know
what, I don't wanna get
you caught in the middle
of all of this stuff.
- You didn't answer my question.
- Oh right, right, what did Tim do.
Well let's see, what didn't he do?
Your friend's a real son of a
bitch in case you didn't know.
- Is this a scorned woman talking,
or is this a business associate talking?
- No, no, this is a human being talking.
Somebody who is sick and tired of
being treated like a stray dog.
You know, petted, fed,
loved, then ignored,
kicked around and finally
locked out of the house.
You getting the picture?
- Well he's gone for a couple of days,
went to Catalina, rented a boat, said he
had to lock down an account or something.
- And you believed him.
- Why wouldn't I?
Hey, you don't have to go,
I'm not gonna call the cops on you.
- Oh thank you, but I have
work to do back at the club.
- You want me to tell him you stopped by?
- You know, if you wanna tell Tim
something you can tell him he's a bastard.
You can tell him that we've reached the
proverbial end of the road, he and I.
You can tell him adios.
You can tell him to crap out and die.
I'm just getting warmed up.
- Will do.
(loud explosions)
(beeping)
- Trucker strike, (mumbles)
scheduled to resume tomorrow.
Meanwhile, here in Southern California,
a mysterious explosion has rocked
the waters off of Catalina Island.
Chuck Williams has more
from Marina Del Ray.
- Well the search continues for survivors,
but so far none have been found.
Coast Guard authorities say it would be
something of a miracle were anyone
to be rescued now, but they'll
keep searching until all hope is gone.
And, they admitted, they may never
know what caused this explosion.
This is Chuck Williams reporting
live from Marina Del Ray for KLAAY News.
(ominous orchestral music)
(phone rings)
- Marina Charter, this is Gordy.
- Yeah, hi, I'm interested in a boat
you have for rent named Papa's Joy.
- That craft's not available,
can I help you with something else?
- Well I'll tell you, I'm
really kinda interested in
that one, my friend told
me it was a great boat.
- Sorry, I got others though.
- Well is it just out, or
is it unavailable, or what?
- Who is this please?
(phone rings)
- Yeah.
- Hey, that you?
Your voice sounds a little off.
- Sorry, I caught a cold.
- Drink a lot of juices.
- Yeah, right, thanks.
- The deal's on, 3.5
in your account today.
Usual percentage.
- I'm not so sure.
- Oh come on champ, you can do it.
- Well I wouldn't expect too much.
- Only perfection as always.
I'll be in touch.
(hip hop music)
(crowd chatter)
- Hello, handsome.
How about that rain check?
- Not right now, Cat.
- Come on, I'm just trying to
spice up your dull Midwestern life.
- Well my dull Midwestern life
doesn't need any spicing, I need
to speak with Syd, have you seen her?
- I know that you're trying to look
like Tim and dress like Tim and all that,
but seriously, what has
she got that's so special?
- You know what, give me
another chance, next time
I'll give you my
undivided attention, okay?
Hey Vic!
Vic!
Excuse me.
- Why don't you get a friggin'
handicap space pal, you're in my spot!
- I'm sorry, I just need one second, Vic!
- Oh is that so?
How about if I just shove one of
these bar stools down your throat?
- You know what, I don't want
any trouble, my friend, okay?
- Oh, you don't want any trouble?
- Vic!
- Well how about I blow your stupid
brains all over this nice clean bar?
- Come on, take it easy, man.
Take it easy.
- What the hell, where's my gun?
- That's enough pal, time to head home.
- Sorry about that, man.
You looking for Tim?
- No, Syd.
- Hey, I'm right here, cowboy.
- Can we talk in private?
- Yeah, sure.
- Oh, uh...
You might wanna hold onto that,
that guy might want it back.
- How did you do that?
Wow, that was quite a trick up in here.
Did you learn that in the academy?
- So you do know about me and Tim.
- I've heard stories, but the way Tim
tells it, you would've made quite a cop.
- That's something we'll never know.
I have to ask you a question.
How much do you really
know about Tim's work?
- Enough, why?
- What is it?
Is it drugs?
- Get to the point, Barry.
- Tim was supposed to rent
a boat and go to Catalina?
- Yeah, whatever, yeah, yeah.
- Well I think somebody killed him.
It was reported in the news that a
boat out of Marina Del Ray blew up off the
coast of Catalina and
there were no survivors.
- That's crazy, I mean come on,
there's a zillion boats that go
off the coast of Catalina every day,
what makes you think this was Tim's boat?
- Have you heard from him?
- Well no, I haven't heard from him,
but that's normal, I don't hear
from him for days and it's normal.
- Yeah, well somebody called the house
and said that the money was put into
Tim's account and that the deal was on.
He thought I was Tim.
What's the deal?
- Tim can't be dead, Barry.
- I'm not saying he is dead.
The Coast Guard won't tell me anything,
but when I was at his house the other day
I found information on chartering boats
and I think it's the same boat.
- Okay.
What do you want from me?
Tim and I...
- Whatever your relationship with
Tim is, I really don't care.
If the boat that exploded was his,
then somebody killed my friend.
- I don't know anything.
You don't believe me do you?
Barry, I really wish I did,
but I don't know anything.
- I gotta go.
- I'll walk you out.
Where are you going?
- I'm gonna go back to the house, get some
sleep, and try to figure all this out.
- Okay, but do you feel
like taking a walk?
I mean you've borrowed
everything else, you might
as well take a stroll
with his ex-girlfriend.
- Sure.
- Okay.
So tell me about you
and Tim in the academy.
- He never told you?
- No, he did, I just
wanna hear your version.
- 16 kilos of heroin disappeared from the
evidence lockup the
week we were (mumbles).
I didn't do it, but I
didn't have an alibi.
They suspected Tim and they squeezed me to
testify against him, but
I refused to do that.
So to get rid of the smell, they just
swept everything and
everybody under the carpet.
- Well at least you didn't let
them turn you into a snitch.
- Yeah, real noble.
Now I sell videos for a living.
- Why can't you just go to
another town, another police force?
- Can't do that because something like
that goes on your
permanent record, and once
it's on your record,
no one will touch you.
Funny thing is my father was a cop.
I always wanted to be just like him.
That's corny, isn't it?
- No.
Not at all.
- All right, enough about me.
What's in the bag?
- This?
This is how I unwind.
(circus melody organ music)
(laughs) Are you impressed?
- Very.
- Oh yeah?
Why don't you come and join me?
Come make a fool of yourself.
- No, no no no no no, I've made a
fool of myself enough in my life.
No, come on, go on.
- All right.
Well I was Dean's List at UCLA, Poly-Sci.
My dad was in politics in Washington
he wanted me to join him there.
Then I met Tim.
- Well he has a way of
changing life paths doesn't he?
- Yeah, he does.
He got me an apartment and he got me
a job at Vic's and, I don't know, he has
a way of coming into your life and...
Putting you off balance, you know?
Well anyway, one day I woke up and
I realized that my life was so hooked into
Tim's that I didn't have
one of my own anymore.
And I wondered if I could start over.
I didn't know if I had enough
raw materials to do that.
So are you gonna call
the cops about the boat?
- No, not right away.
I mean if Tim was on that boat they
would've contacted one of us by now.
And besides, you have to be missing
48 hours before they'll even talk to you.
- So you'll call me if
anything turns up right?
- Yes.
- You sure you don't wanna come out here?
(Syd laughs)
- Okay, well get out of here then.
- All right.
- Okay.
- Goodnight.
- Hey!
This was nice, cowboy.
(circus melody organ music)
(police siren wails)
- Hey Tim, you're home!
Jesus man, you had me worried,
I thought you'd bought it.
Hey...
(loud smack)
(dramatic sting)
(Barry groans)
(punching and kicking)
(phone rings)
Hello?
- Still no Tim, huh?
- How did you know I wasn't him?
- Tim always answers the phone in Spanish.
You know, hola.
Signals the party on the
other end that it's him.
- I'll try to remember that.
- You know, I was thinking
I had done the rudest thing.
I told somebody to call me and
then I didn't give him my number,
so I figured would
cowboy be smart enough to
go through that entire
house to find my number?
Probably not, so here I am ready
to give you my number so you don't
think I was yanking your chain.
Are you ready?
- No, listen Syd, somebody broke in here.
- Are you okay?
- (groans) Yeah.
I surprised the guy and he took off.
Course he hung around
long enough to introduce
my ribs to my spine, but nothing serious.
- Oh my God, is anything missing?
- Well I really haven't
had a chance to check.
- Did you call the cops this time?
- No, I'm a little worried to call them.
I mean the burglar can
certainly come up with
a better excuse than I
could for being here.
At least he could...
(uplifting jingle)
He could prove who he is.
- What are you talking about?
- I lost my wallet the
first day I got here.
My ID, cash.
Everything.
Other than the clothes on my back,
everything that I've been using is Tim's.
That might look a little
strange to the cops.
- Yeah, especially if he washes up
off the shore of Catalina tomorrow.
Nice vacation.
- Hey listen, I gotta put
this place back together.
- Okay.
Well get some sleep, cowboy.
Maybe you'll wake up tomorrow and
find out this is all just a bad dream.
- At this rate I'm lucky if I wake up.
- Another beautiful day in paradise.
- All right.
- Goodnight, cowboy.
- Bye.
(Syd hangs up)
Hey!
Hey...
Shit, I forgot to get the number.
Oh what a headache.
(gentle jazz and wind chime music)
- 555-3319.
But I'm not there right now.
(kissing)
(waves crashing)
- Morning.
- Good morning.
- Don't forget to roll over.
- (giggles) I won't.
(kissing)
Wake me at noon, okay?
- Okay.
(shuffling)
(kitchen appliance whirring)
(paper crinkling)
(ominous music)
(shuffling)
Hey.
What are you doing?
- Oh, making coffee.
Tim was a drug dealer.
Now he's a dead drug dealer.
- Tim wasn't a drug dealer.
- "Investment banker" you
call it what you want.
He didn't push on street corners,
but he was definitely involved.
- You have no idea.
- Yeah, I have an idea.
See, Tim moved money, he brokered deals.
My hunch is he did it all on the phone,
this way there'd be no personal contact.
- Go on.
- Mr. A's got money to spend.
Tim finds Mr. B who's got
drugs or whatever to sell.
Money gets put into Tim's account,
they transfer good, money passes, Tim gets
a percentage, no fuss, no muss, he's out.
- Wow, you're a lot
smarter than Tim thought.
- Only thing is I don't know
what the hell his latest deal is.
- Something weird?
- Yeah, somebody broke in here and
trashed the place looking for something.
Our boy was not on good
terms with these people.
I don't know who he was involved with
or what he was up to, but it doesn't
take a lot to figure out that it had
something to do with that boat blowing up.
- So what are you gonna do?
- They still think I'm Tim.
- And they'll still think you're
Tim when they blow your head off.
Listen to me cowboy, get
out now while you can.
That's the best advice
you'll ever get from me.
- And what happens to you?
- Forget about me, okay?
Because if you go through with
this deal they're going to kill you.
You're a nice guy.
Don't follow in Tim's footsteps.
- So you think he's dead.
- After what you told me at the
club that was my first thought, yes.
Then I realized that I had to
start thinking about myself.
- So you're involved in this?
- I was involved, but I'm not anymore.
- If I were you, I'd go to the feds.
I mean you have enough
information, they'll just
let you, they'd let you
walk, they love you.
- Wait a second, you are
suggesting that I become a snitch?
I can't do that.
I can't trust anybody.
- Is that why you slept with me?
- No.
I slept with you because I wanted to.
This is crazy, cowboy, don't do it.
- You gonna help me or not?
- All right, if you are determined
to do this, this is my advice.
I would lay low for a couple
of days, get the cash,
dish it out, and then
get the hell out of town.
You don't owe them anything,
they're not gonna come after you.
Maybe I can get out of here too.
- Is that what you want?
- I'll see you at the club.
- Okay.
(dramatic flute music)
(hip hop music)
(crowd chatter)
Hey, Vic!
- Hey, Tim's friend, how's it going?
- Well I'm not so sure.
Things have been a little strange
since Tim left on business.
- Yeah?
Well he told me to give
you whatever you needed.
So what do you need?
- You heard from him?
- Not since he left.
That's not unusual.
Hey man, look, let me
talk to you in a minute.
- All right.
- Hey Tim.
- Barry.
Tim's friend, remember?
- Oh, yeah, I forgot.
So where is he anyway?
I haven't got the chance to meet him.
- He's away on business.
How about a drink?
- I'm sorry, I can't.
I'm on duty.
- For me.
- I'm so dumb sometimes.
- (laughs) Don't worry about it.
Scotch, rocks...
- With a splash, I remember now.
- Very good.
Hey, how's the acting?
- I have an audition.
- Good for you, for what?
- Video I think.
Anyway, there's not a lot of
words, so I should be okay.
- (laughs) Well good luck.
- You're not supposed to say good luck.
You're supposed to say break a leg,
I mean why anyone would wanna see
someone break someone's leg is...
- Brooke.
- Thank you.
(jazzy hip hop music)
- Hey cowboy.
- Hey.
- You sure look at home.
- How you doing since last night?
- Oh I'm doing good.
- Good.
- I get off at 2.
- I'll be here.
(jazzy hip hop music)
(crowd chatter)
Hey Vic, listen, I think that Tim, I think
he was involved in a boating accident.
- You wanna explain what the
hell you're talking about?
- Did you see on the news where
that boat blew up off Catalina?
I think that's the boat
that Tim chartered.
I think somebody killed him.
You guys were partners right?
- We're partners only in this club.
I sold him a piece of the action.
- But you knew what deals he was into.
Drugs maybe?
- Everybody's got their own opinions.
I keep mine to myself.
Maybe you oughta do the same.
- Yeah, well somebody broke into
his house while I was in it.
- Maybe you oughta just pack
up and go back to St. Louis.
- Maybe.
- Well hey man, I don't know
anything, so I can't help you.
- Look, Vic, if you hear anything, or if
anything occurs to you, will you call me?
Hey, Tim said if I needed anything right?
- I'll think about it.
- Thank you.
(gentle synthesizer music)
(Syd giggles)
Does this seem a little strange to you?
- What are you talking about?
- You know, me and you in Tim's bed.
- Oh you're more provincial
than I thought, cowboy.
I told you Tim and I are no longer.
Would it mean anything less if
we did it on the kitchen floor?
- It might be more fun, but...
- Oh no.
- Depending on what tools you got.
(laughter)
Why don't we go to your
house once in a while?
- Sure, sure, whenever you'd like.
- How was he?
- You did not just ask me that question.
- What's the big deal?
- That is so stupid.
- No it's not.
- Why do men always have to...
Who am I here with right now, huh?
You.
Isn't that enough?
(increasingly tense flute music)
(shuffling)
(phone rings)
- Who the hell's this at 4 o'clock?
- You know what, this
might be the last time
for you to make this
deal, do you wanna do it?
- Yeah.
(ominous music)
- (Barry As Tim) Hola.
- Where you been, you
didn't answer last night.
- I'm sick, what's up?
- You wanna do business?
- What do you want?
- You tell me, amigo.
I got if you got.
- I got.
3.5
- I can cover it.
- How soon?
- You in a hurry?
- The opposite.
I need time.
- Time I don't got.
- It came up unexpected.
I wasn't sure I could do it.
- Then why didn't you call?
- Having a problem with my computer.
How soon?
- Two days.
- Three.
- You know, some days I
wish I was a lettuce picker.
Okay, put it in the account.
- I told you, I got a
problem with my computer.
(Seller laughs)
It's not that funny.
- You live by the computer,
you die by the computer.
Me, I'm a little old fashioned.
I don't like to use anything I
don't understand how it works.
- Well I can't get the money
until I get things working again.
- Sometimes I worry about you, man.
- I need more time.
- You try anything funny,
you know what happens.
(Barry hangs up)
- Well that was very impressive.
How'd you learn to do
that with your voice?
- (Normal Voice) Well...
Me and Tim used to mess
with girls' heads, we used
to make believe we were each
other, drive them crazy.
- Oh, how charming.
Well congratulations, you're now a dealer.
- Drugs?
- Merchandise.
That's the way Tim liked it.
It didn't matter what got traded.
I'd stick to that point of view.
- The point of no return, huh?
- Yeah, I'd say so, I mean if you
backed out now you might make a
whole lot of people really mad.
- I need to get the money.
I know that it's in Tim's computer,
but I can't access without the password.
When it's time to make this
deal, what the hell do I do?
- Call Dean, he'll know what to do.
- And what if he doesn't?
- Then it was nice knowing you, cowboy.
(dogs barking)
- Dean?
Hey.
- Oh hey, man.
- I got a question for you.
- Shoot.
- The other day you dropped off
some software programs for Tim.
- Yeah, I promised to
clean them up for him.
- Do you know what was on them?
- Spreadsheets.
Online banking stuff.
I set up his whole system.
I set up his PC, he gives me stock tips.
- You think you could
retrieve his password?
- Highly illegal.
- Listen, you gotta
trust me on this, okay?
- Yeah, why's that?
- Remember the other day
when that, on the news,
that boat exploded off
Catalina, you remember that?
- Yeah, what about it?
- Tim was on that boat.
I think Tim is dead and I
think somebody killed him.
- Whoa.
I don't want no part of this.
- Look, I need to find out
who killed Tim and why,
but I can't do that unless
I get into his files.
- Go to the cops.
- No, not yet.
Look, you can stand by me, you can look
over my shoulder and see that I won't
take a friggin' dime, okay, but I have to
know what he was up to so I can maybe
help him, or at least
find out who killed him.
- Maybe somebody did kill him.
Maybe they'd be after us next.
- All I'm asking is is it possible?
- It's there, on the hard drive somewhere.
The key is figuring out how to expose it.
- Like a needle in a haystack.
- Not that bad.
We'll use the power of the processor
to help us find the needle.
I can't believe I'm saying this.
Let me clean this stuff
up and I'll go with you.
- All right, cool, thanks.
(tense jazzy music)
Anything?
- Nothing yet, but not to worry.
(typing)
(phone rings)
- (Barry As Tim) Hola
- That you?
I thought you were still away.
- I'm back, what's up?
- Your buddy was in here.
Said he thought you were dead,
something about a boat blowing up.
What the hell's going on, Tim?
- I don't know, he's a little wacky.
Forget about him, why'd you call?
- Told me you were stalling
on some payments, right?
Guy was in here looking for you.
- Really?
- If I had to bet, I'd say this
guys was used to collecting debts.
- What did you tell him?
- Nothing.
But Timmy, if I was you
I'd stay on my toes.
This guy looks like he may eat
small children for breakfast.
- All right Vic, thanks.
- Sure thing.
- I'll get back to you later.
Oh, Vic.
My friend Barry Rengler.
- You still want me to
give him an open tab?
Think the guy's a little too
nosy if you want my opinion.
- He's a good friend of mine,
you give him whatever he needs.
- Whatever you want.
- Thanks, bye.
(Barry hangs up)
(dramatic jazzy music)
- What do you want?
Get the hell out.
- Leon.
- I'm not buying nothing.
And I'm not signing nothing.
- Come on, you don't remember me?
- No.
Should I?
Who the hell are you?
- Leon, it's Barry Rengler.
- Jesus.
It's been a long time.
- I know, since you left St. Louis.
You heard from Tim recently?
- I told him I don't have room
for all that stuff he's keeping here.
Not a friggin' storage locker.
You come all the way out to LA to
have to come to me to find him?
- Not exactly.
I've been with him.
Matter of fact, I'm staying at his place.
Only thing is he had to go out of town
on business and I was wondering if...
- Hasn't he given you
enough trouble already?
- Come on Leon, that was a long time ago.
It wasn't his fault.
The academy made scapegoats of all of us.
- You were always a smart kid.
Smarter than him.
Well I thought.
Maybe not.
- Leon...
There's a good possibility Tim is dead.
He rented a boat and was going to
Catalina and there was an explosion.
- Accident?
- Maybe.
Maybe not.
I'm not sure.
- Figures.
All the crap he was into.
Wallow in the mud, you
make enemies with the pigs.
- Just wondering if there
was anything you've heard.
- No.
- That's it?
- What do you want?
You want me to fall apart?
- Is there anything you
need, anything I can get you?
- Nothing you can get me.
- Well if you do hear anything,
I'd appreciate a phone call.
I'll be at his place.
(dramatic flute music)
- Excuse me.
You live here?
- What can I do for you?
- You know someone by the
name of Barry Rengler?
R-E-N-G-L-E-R, Rengler.
- Barry Rengler?
- Yeah, do you know him?
- Yeah.
- Well he was involved
in a boat explosion.
- The one that I saw in the news?
- Yeah, the charter operator said
he was the one who took out the boat.
- How'd you end up here?
- Mr. Renger's from St. Louis, and the
record shows that there was a phone call
made from here last week to the
Missouri DMV requesting a reissue of his
driver's license, how well
did you know Mr. Rengler?
- You ask me that like
you think he's dead.
- Well I'm afraid that
he probably is, Mister...
- Gates, Tim Gates.
I knew him very well, he
was a good friend of mine.
- Yeah, well Mr. Gates,
I'm afraid it's very
likely that you friend
died in that explosion.
Now anything you can do to help
us out would be greatly appreciated.
- Well he came here to visit.
He's got some stuff in the
house if you wanna check it out.
You know something, he told me that
he lost his wallet, but I never
really thought anything of it.
- Well that's another
odd fact because we found
a wallet in the debris
after the explosion.
- You found his wallet?
- Yeah, that's how we identified
him as the person who paid for the boat.
- He told me he lost it.
- So then I assume you know
nothing about any of this.
- No, nothing.
- Well you call me at this
number if anything comes up.
- Yeah, sure.
- Thanks very much.
- You're welcome.
- Okay.
(dramatic trumpet music)
(toilet flushes)
(dramatic sting)
- Sense of tension in the air.
Don't you think?
All right, here's the thing.
I know there's a young lady
asleep in the next room.
I would hate to wake her.
You agree?
I think you do.
Because if she wakes up,
I'll have to kill her.
I know you don't want that, right?
(muffled grunting)
Do we have an agreement?
(dramatic sting)
(glass shatters)
I think you know why I'm here.
(mumbles).
You've been holding onto cash that
belongs to someone else, haven't you?
Okay, I understand you're concerned
about not making any noise.
The least you could do is
nod, I mean just to be polite.
Good.
There's a growing concern gnawing at
my clients, Mr. Gates, that's perhaps
you do not intend on ever paying them.
They're worried that because you normally
deal with sedate
professionals, that you feel
that you can do this
with a sense of impunity.
He has asked me to impress upon you
the extent to which that (mumbles) is
an error and that he expects his
money within a matters of hours.
It's actually good that
you're so uncommunicative
because I'm not here to discuss the
relative points of the issue, I'm simply
here to deliver a message through
the impressive use of multimedia tools.
Such as this one.
(cranking)
(Barry groaning)
(coughing)
That was your ear drum.
A little bit further and you wouldn't
be hearing at all on that side.
Fortunately, God in His infinite
redundancy has given
you another over here.
So if I ever decide to come
back, you're not totally deaf.
I'm glad we could have this talk.
I've enjoyed it immensely.
I look forward to our next visit.
(dramatic sting)
- God you're a mess.
- What?
- I said I think I'm
falling in love with you.
Get out now cowboy, please.
This isn't high school anymore.
- What about me and you?
- You're not much good to me dead.
Go home, let the dust settle,
you know how to get in touch with me.
- Can't do that.
- God you're as bad as he is, why not?
- 'Cause a guy just tried
to shove a pencil in my ear!
This is personal now.
- It's stupid, why do I always have to get
myself involved with
guys like you and Tim?
- I've got to find out exactly what Tim
was up to and how I fit into all this.
I don't wanna spend the next
five years of my life wondering.
- That's what this is all about isn't it?
- Partly.
- That happened a long time ago Barry,
it's not worth getting dead over.
- He used my name to rent that boat.
I didn't lose my wallet, he stole it.
Then he switched the pictures
on the driver's license.
He was skimming.
God knows how much, but
he owed somebody big time.
And he decided to let me
take the punishment for him.
It's an old familiar trait of his.
I forgot how much it pisses me off.
- Okay, say that they killed
Tim on the boat right?
Why would they be coming after you now?
- I haven't figured that out yet.
What were the return in his investments?
- He'd give out 90, take 10 as a fee.
- 10%?
So three and a half million
dollars, he'd make 350,000.
Wow.
- That's the way Tim
liked it, work a couple of
weekends, then take the
rest of the year off.
He thought it was a nice lifestyle.
- Who wouldn't?
Unless you get blown
into a million pieces.
- I'm gonna ask you one more time, okay?
Let's start over again,
let's leave this place,
let's go someplace together,
take me to St. Louis.
- Syd, what you're
looking for doesn't exist.
There's no house with a white picket fence
and two and a half kids, golden retriever,
I mean aren't you the one who told me
don't take anything
out here at face value?
- All I know is that Tim is dead
and I don't wanna lose you too.
- It's one final deal.
- One final deal that's
gonna get you killed,
why the hell would you wanna do that?
- Because for the past five years
I've watch my life go down the toilet.
If I don't put the past behind
me now, I'm never gonna do it.
(dramatic trumpet music)
- What can I do?
(door opens)
- Back again?
- Yeah.
- I told you I don't hear from him.
- I talked to the authorities.
As far as they're concerned
it wasn't Tim on the boat.
Can I come in?
(door closes)
You said Tim wanted to move
some things out, what things?
(Leon sighs)
Hey come on, Leon, talk to me.
Leon!
- Come in about a week ago, put a
bunch of stuff here in the extra bedroom.
Clothes, supplies.
Boxes full of stuff.
- He told me that he
hadn't seen you in years.
- Hadn't.
'Till he come over to
store all that stuff here.
I told him I didn't want it here, but he
said it would only be
for a couple of days.
Can I get you a beer?
- No thank you, he stole my wallet
and he used it to charter that boat.
Then he switched the pictures and
pretended to me and I'd
be mistaken for him.
- What do you want from me?
- He owed somebody a lot of money, Leon.
He tried to get away, but he
couldn't make it, they were onto him.
- You still haven't answered my question.
What is it you want from me?
- I wanna know what
happened back in St. Louis.
- His mother used to say you
two boys were just like brothers.
- No, we were never like brothers.
Not Tim.
He used me to cover his tracks because
he knew that I would be
the last guy to tell.
He used me, didn't he?
- You were the top recruit in that class.
He could never be what he knew you were.
He figured if you were under suspicion
he'd confuse their investigation.
Throw them off the trail.
And he was right.
- And nobody said a word.
Just left me hanging,
swinging in the breeze.
- Oh I tried.
But his mother, she was gonna
protect him no matter what.
You didn't matter, I didn't matter.
It was only Tim.
Why now?
After all these years, what difference
could it make to you now?
- Because history's
about to repeat itself.
I'll tell you what Leon, I really don't
feel like being dragged along this time.
I'll see you.
(door opens and closes)
(janitor vacuuming)
- What's the problem, Louis?
Look like you're trying
to drown something.
- Vacation's almost over.
- That's too bad.
I'm gonna miss you, Louis.
Things have gotten a lot more
interesting since you come to town.
- Thanks.
- Hey.
- What are you doing?
What's this?
- That's your ticket to St. Louis.
- What are you talking about?
- I used Tim's credit card.
For once in my life I'm gonna take
advantage of the
opportunities presented to me.
- I don't understand.
- This is what you wanted, isn't it?
The picket fence, the whole nine yards?
Here's your chance.
(phone rings)
(Barry as Tim) Hola.
- Who is this, Barry?
- (Normal Voice) Yeah,
hey, did you get in?
- Oh yeah, that part was easy, but you're
not gonna believe what I
found once I logged on.
- Don't tell me over the
phone, I'll be right there.
- This stuff's gonna blow you away.
- Okay.
That was Dean, he's got Tim's password.
This whole thing's gonna
be over by tomorrow, okay?
I want you to go home, pack,
and I'll meet you there.
- Barry, don't go to Tim's house, okay?
Forget about me, forget about the deal,
forget about everything and
just get out while you can, okay?
- It's gonna be okay.
All right?
Don't worry about it.
(dramatic jazzy music)
Hey, hey how's the...
(computer beeping)
Oh God.
(doors slam open)
What the hell?
Hey.
(groaning)
(scuffling)
- I didn't think we'd see each other again
so soon, but I guess
circumstances have changed.
My orders have changed.
I thought I'd let you know
that before I carry them out.
(Barry grunts)
I wouldn't do this unless it was
necessary so you'll forgive me.
(sounds of struggle)
I can't believe you did that!
Where do you think you're gonna go?
(loud smack)
I can keep doing this as long as you like.
(Barry groans)
I should thank you, I
was getting complacent.
A little bored with the
job, you know what I mean?
(strong punch)
(Barry groans)
Nothing like an asshole to get
the ol' juices flowing again.
I'd like to keep visiting like
this, but it's time to play.
(handcuffs snapping)
(mumbles).
(gunshots)
(loud thud)
(Barry breathing)
(dramatic flute music)
(apartment intercom buzzes)
- Who is it?
- It's Barry, open up.
(apartment door buzzes)
Dean is dead.
I was supposed to be next.
What's going on?
- Barry, please...
- I just killed a man, goddammit,
now what the hell is going on?
- Barry, I told you to get out
of this and you would not listen.
- He cleaned out his entire account!
- Barry, please...
- You've been lying to me haven't you?
From this beginning this has all been
a lie, it's all been a setup, am I right?
He's been using me to rip them off.
Jesus Christ I don't get
this, I don't get it,
they killed him once, they
blew him up in the boat.
Why, why...
- I'm impressed!
(chuckles) You know?
You figured it out.
I really wasn't sure that
you would, but you did.
I gotta say it's been
entertaining as hell.
- You son of a bitch.
- I know, I know, yeah, it's me.
Hey listen, you called, you were the one
that said you wanted to
come to sunny LA, okay?
- Is that when all this started?
- Sure.
Look, I wanted to get out of the business.
I couldn't figure out how.
Then your call comes, and as
they say, the penny began to drop.
- So this has all been an act right?
- Come on, I could always
count on you in a pinch!
As a matter of fact, Bar, I always
know exactly what you're gonna do.
You know what, that's
your fatal flaw, Bar.
You're just too goddamn predictable!
- So all that crap about you and him
being finished, that was just a lie right?
- Oh, her?
She's a hell of an actress.
I'm telling you, huh?
She missed her calling, right?
(kisses Syd) Hollywood, babe.
That's her ticket.
You wanna know something?
She made me nervous as
hell because I actually
thought she was starting
to fall in love with you.
- Just out of curiosity,
who hired the hitman?
- Come on, that was them!
I took the money, they got pissed!
These guys play rough,
especially if you rip them off.
But I knew that going in.
See, this is the beauty of it, the guy
who thought that you were me, he was just
trying to scare you so
you'd give the money back.
But I gave him a little more, so he
did a little something extra for me.
He didn't care!
I mean they're all in it for the
money, he was so easy to buy.
- He's not doing anything now.
I killed him with your gun.
- You did?
That's beautiful, that's beautiful!
I mean what, the one under the table?
(laughs)
Oh man, I mean you could imagine how
surprised I was to see
you show up here right?
I mean because let's face
it, this was a great plan.
It had everybody thinking that you're me.
Then I got Barry out on the boat, in the
explosion, chaos ensues,
everyone's running
around like rats in a maze, gives me
perfect time to do a nice clean
little departure with Syd here.
The only thing I didn't
figure on, the only
thing, is I thought you'd be dead by now.
I really thought that that guy
would've done his job, but as they
say, you just can't get good help.
Anyway, listen, the time is ticking.
I think it's time that we get moving.
- Where are we going?
- We?
No no no no, there is no we.
Syd and I are gonna take all that money,
12 million in case you're interested,
and we're gonna go down to South America.
And just so you know, dear friend
of my heart, you're staying right here.
- Tim, no!
(gunshot)
(Syd groans)
(strong punch)
(suspenseful music)
(gunshot)
- Come on, Barry!
Hey, come out come out wherever you are!
She took a bullet for you,
you stupid son of a bitch!
How do you think that
makes me feel, huh Barry?
You think I'm gonna let you walk away now?
Man, I had this all worked out to a T!
You screwed it up!
I mean my woman falls in
love with you, and then
you kill my hitman, I mean
what the hell is that?
Can't you get anything right?
(sounds of struggle)
(suspense music)
(gunshots)
- That's enough, Barry!
That's enough.
You don't wanna kill him.
- Good work, Agent Nelson.
- Aren't you forgetting something?
- Three people are dead, Catherine.
All deals are off.
- You can't do that.
This wasn't his fault, he did
everything we asked and then some.
Sir, we went to him, we
enlisted his help, we owe him!
We can't go back on that now.
- Hey Cat, I didn't know you were back.
I have the budget documents you requested.
- Hey Paula, yeah, I
got back this morning.
How have you been?
- I'm fine, I'm just trying to put
up with the ol' grizzly bear here.
- You two mind?
You can swap stories later.
Right now, Paula, Agent Nelson's gonna
dictate a letter to you that...
I will then sign.
You can word it anyway you
want, we'll make it official.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
(cars honking)
- There you go.
Past is off the books.
It never happened.
(Barry sighs)
- You know, when one of your friends
at the agency came to see me in St. Louis,
he told me what a big target Tim Gates was
and how my past with him helped them
get him and his whole operation.
- You had given up on yourself.
- I just didn't think it was possible
to erase the past, I didn't believe it.
- Well believe it.
What happened at the
academy no longer exists.
(dramatic trumpet music)
- Five years, I dreamed about this.
I thought this was what I wanted, but...
Now I'm not so sure.
- You know, what happened to
Syd wasn't your fault, Barry.
If you still plan to be a cop, you have
to know that it's never going to be easy.
It's never going to be clean.
People get killed.
That's right, you know
that now you can apply
to any law enforcement
agency in the country.
They would be proud to have you.
Of course you could do a lot
worse than join us with us.
- Are you offering me a spot?
- (laughs) I can't exactly
offer, but I'd back that idea.
- You think we'd made a good team?
- (laughs) Louis, I think could be
the beginning of a beautiful friendship.
- It's Barry.
(laughter)
(dramatic jazzy synthesizer music)
(uplifting orchestral music)