- Okay.
Where are you?
All right.
Shit.
Don't come any closer.
This will burn you.
Who's there?
Shit, no!
No, no, no, no, no.
Listen.
I'm sorry.
I won't tell anyone.
Please.
Just let me go home.
Hello, if anyone can hear me,
my name's Keith Barren.
I work at Brooke's
Hardware Store.
There's something terrible here.
I tried to figure it out.
Stay away!
Stay away from me!
You have to fight them.
You have to-
Oh, shit.
No, no, no, no!
♪ A Brooke's day is
a great day ♪
♪ That's our phrase we
love to say ♪
♪ Come on in, why
don't you stay? ♪
♪ And say a Brooke's day
is a great day ♪
♪ In our store you'll
find a lot ♪
♪ Up and down the aisles ♪
♪ You're sure to spot ♪
♪ A friendly smile
who's sure to say ♪
♪ That a Brooke's day
is a great day ♪
♪ Every day ♪
♪ Because work is always
welcome here ♪
♪ And Silvio is our puppeteer ♪
♪ A Brooke's day is
a great day ♪
♪ We know you'll love our
starting pay ♪
♪ Because a Brooke's day
is a great day ♪
♪ Today ♪
- ♪ A Brooke's day
is a good day ♪
♪ A Brooke's day is
a great day ♪
♪ A Brooke's day is a good day ♪
- Gene.
- Yes, sir.
- Just got this resume
in, can you look it over?
- Sam Coleman?
Doesn't look like he has
much experience.
Oh, but he does have his
high school GPA here.
- Hire him.
I don't give a shit who he is.
It's better he doesn't have any
experience, no expectations.
We just need somebody
for Black Friday.
- Sir, maybe we
should look around.
- Sam Coleman.
Hire him.
- All right, boss man.
Will do.
♪ A Brooke's day is
a great day ♪
- It's okay, it's okay.
You can do this.
Here we go.
Hello?
I was wondering if you guys
have any job openings available?
One panini, no tomato.
- Oh no, no, I said,
are you guys hiring?
I actually have my
resume right here.
- Sir, this is a drive-through.
If you want an application,
you can come in.
- Never mind, I'll take
a burger, no cheese.
I'm lactose intolerant.
- Thank you, your total
will be at the window.
- It's okay, it's okay.
- Hello?
- Sam Coleman?
- Yeah, that's me.
- Gene, Brooke's Hardware Store.
- Oh, hello.
- Listen.
We loved your resume.
How would you like to start,
well, today?
- Yeah!
Yes, yes, yes, yes!
Hey!
Yeah!
Shoot.
Oh, hello, mom?
I got a job.
Can you believe it?
Yeah, Brooke's Hardware.
What?
Mom?
Hello?
Mom, can you hear me?
Mom, you there?
You there?
Hello?
- Sam.
I'm impressed, you
made good time.
Gene Knibbs here.
I assume you remember me?
- Yeah, yes, of course.
- Follow me.
So back here are our offices.
This is where we handle
clerical, accounting,
human resources, you name it.
Now it's a big place.
So don't get lost on your
first day, okay?
You ready?
- Yeah.
- All right.
Meet me at the end of the
hall, in the break room.
Come on, lots to go over.
Now, before I give you the tour,
you need to watch this
quick training video.
I think you'll get a
kick out of it.
- Welcome
to Brooke's Hardware.
- Hi, I'm Tim.
- And I'm Karen.
- And it's your first
day working here at...
- Brooke's!
- That's Tim.
- And as Silvio Brooke
says on page 32.
- Watch, watch, watch.
- A Brooke's day is
a great day.
- When in doubt, get
your handbook out.
- I love it!
There you have it.
Think you can do this, you
think you got what it takes?
- Definitely, sir.
- I know you got what it takes.
Anyways.
On with the tour.
The back stock area,
the lumber section,
cleaning supplies, paint
department, accessories,
plumbing department, more paint,
more cleaning, and
more plumbing.
And back where we started,
gardening.
I think you know this place.
And here's the power grid.
It controls all the
lighting in the store.
Don't go messing around
with this thing, okay?
It can give you some
real trouble.
All right Sammy boy, you'll
learn a lot more on the job.
So, let's head up to the
registers and get you trained...
Brian?
- Gene.
The warehouse lights
are completely broken.
Nobody's allowed in there
until we get that fixed, okay?
- Sure thing, boss man.
Oh, Brian.
I'd like you to meet
Sam Coleman.
This is the kid who's gonna
get you through Black Friday.
- Hello, I'm, I'm Sam.
- Yeah, hi.
I gotta get back to work.
Nobody allowed the warehouse,
got it?
- Got it.
That is our owner and
general manager.
The big cheese.
The head honcho.
Don't worry about him, he
gets into moods sometimes.
- Okay.
I'll remember that.
- Well, let's get you set up
for your first day of work,
shall we?
Come on.
All time off requests
must be submitted
a minimum of a month in advance.
Come on, chop chop.
Unless, of course, you're sick.
Brooke's doesn't tolerate
any illness in the workplace.
So.
- Aye aye, Captain.
- Oh, I almost forgot.
Your very own Brooke's
employee vest.
Looks good.
You're a Brooke's man now.
And last but not least,
your name tag.
- Oh, um...
I, um...
- Something wrong?
- No, it's perfect.
- Of course it is.
Looks good.
Your box cutter and
your walkie talkie
will be up with the register.
Those are two things you don't
want to go anywhere without.
- Okay, sounds great.
I, I won't forget.
- And remember, a Brooke's
day is a great day.
- Oh Sam, this is Sarah.
She's gonna be
training you today.
Sarah, Sam.
- Hello.
- Hi, nice to meet you.
- So are you excited for
your first day?
- Well.
A Brooke's day is a great day,
right?
- Huh, the boy already
knows his stuff.
You're gonna fit in great.
I'll leave you to it,
and like you said, Sam.
- A Brooke's day is a great day?
- You're absolutely right it is,
buddy.
- Okay.
As far as the register goes,
it's pretty self-explanatory.
You'll learn everything
through practice.
But here's your three
step lesson.
- I'm listening.
- Pay very close attention.
Scan the item.
- Okay.
- Take the customer's money.
- And give them their change.
- Okay.
- Easy peasy.
Okay, you hold down
the fort here.
I have to go work on an order,
and Brian isn't giving me
any extra time.
- Wait, wait.
- Yeah?
- Aren't you supposed
to finish training me?
- Do you need me to go over
those three steps again?
- No, I just.
- You'll be fine.
As long as you can keep
your eyes open,
this job is a piece of cake.
Anybody can do it.
- Okay.
- Look, channel two is
a direct line to me.
Call me if you have any
questions, okay?
- Okay, cool.
I got this.
- You're gonna kill it, dude.
- Thanks, Sarah.
Hello, welcome
to Brooke's.
Hey, how's it going today?
Hey, you guys need any
help finding anything?
Welcome to Brooke's.
Hey, how's it going?
Hey Sarah.
Just testing my walkie,
but is this all I have
to do all day?
Are there ever customers?
Hey, Sam.
Yeah, honestly,
this place only stays open
'cause of Black Friday.
Other days, it's a
piece of cake.
Easiest job in the world.
Well, I'm actually headed
out for the day,
so I'll see you later.
Nice meeting you, Sam.
- It was nice to meet you too,
Sarah.
- See you, Sam.
- Piece of cake.
- Hey Sam.
End of the first shift already?
- Yes, sir.
- Sarah said you absolutely
killed it on the register today.
I'm so proud.
- Thank you.
I really, really
enjoyed it actually.
- Well, can I count on you to
be back here tomorrow then?
- Yeah.
Yeah, I'll see you then.
- Yes, you will, Sam.
Yes, you will.
- Goodnight, sir.
- Have a good night.
- Yeah!
- Good morning, sir.
- Good morning, Sam.
The registers are waiting.
- $1.25 is your change.
Have a good day.
Oh, and remember a Brooke's
day is a great day.
- Thanks man.
- You're welcome.
Hello.
Nice to meet you, sir.
- What is that thing?
- Oh, the sticker?
I don't know, it's
just a sticker.
I'm Sam by the way.
- Bill.
- So, how long
you been working here?
- Too long, dude.
You in school?
- Yeah, I'm in
community college.
Hoping to get in medical
school eventually.
- Dude, medical school?
Doctor Sam, huh?
- Yeah.
I guess so.
- Well, Doctor Sam,
maybe you can save me
from this job.
It's killing me.
Wanna help me burn it down?
- What?
- Kidding.
Geez Sam,
But come on.
What if we did, right?
It's boring as hell around
here, and kind of creepy too.
What are you doing wasting
your time here?
- I don't know.
I don't think a job like
this is such a bad choice.
I'm having such a tough
time with school,
and I'm getting the
hang of things
pretty quickly around here.
- Hey, I'm not complaining.
At least there's finally another
normal person around here.
- Yeah.
- ♪ A Brooke's
day is a great day. ♪
♪ A Brooke's day is a great day.♪
Good night, Gene.
Gene?
Sir?
- Sorry.
I was just spacing out there.
Long day.
- Okay.
No worries.
- Have a good night, son.
- Good night, Gene.
- Hey Sam, just wanted to
say I'm feeling great today.
Excited to see you back
in action again.
- Thank you so much, sir.
- Good luck out there.
You're gonna kill it.
Put it there.
There you go.
Oh, head to the back stock area.
Brooke's is waiting.
- Hello?
Sarah?
Hello?
- Boo!
Gotcha.
- Yeah, okay.
You got me.
- All right, let's get to work.
Come on.
- Hey Sarah, what do we do
when something's out of stock?
Sarah?
Oh!
Here we go.
- Aha!
Oh.
Brian.
It's you.
Nice to see you again.
Listen,
I am so, so sorry.
Sarah had pulled this
prank on me earlier and I,
I was just trying to get
her back 'cause.
It's really hard to explain.
Just, I've just been getting
used to the store and I,
I know there's no room for
messing around and, and, and,
and I know it was just a joke,
and it will never ever
happen again because,
a Brooke's day is a-
- We need you in the gardening
section the rest of the day.
- Yes sir, of course, sir.
I'm on it.
- Hey. Hey!
Follow me.
- Yes, sir.
Of course, sir.
Welcome to Brooke's.
Can I help you?
Sir?
Hello?
Is there anything I can
do to help you?
Sir?
Sir.
Can, can, can you hear me?
Can I help?
- Hello sir, Sam has
to take his break now.
Have a wonderful Brooke's day.
- What the heck was that?
- Dude, I should have told you
about that creepy customer.
I can't believe Brian put
you on gardening all alone.
- You've, you've seen
that guy before?
- He's been hanging around
that section a lot recently.
Just staring at the fertilizer.
I told you, Sam, this
place gives me the creeps.
If you ever see him again,
just don't go near him, okay?
- I won't, I won't.
- Are you sure you're all right?
- Yeah.
Yeah, I'm just, just a
little shaken.
Just a little shaken.
Shake their hand, look
'em in the eye, help them.
Welcome to Brooke's.
Huh?
Hey, uh, Sarah,
do you know where a janitor's
closet is or something?
There's a spill or, I
don't know what it is.
Something creepy.
Yeah.
Don't bother.
Sorry.
Nevermind.
Think I found it.
"Property of Keith"?
"This place is weird."
"Gonna write entries
about what I see."
"-Keith."
"Brian yelled at me again."
"I should quit."
"I was gonna file a
report on Brian."
"He offered me a raise
to ignore it,"
"I don't know what to do."
"I can't take it anymore."
"I finally submitted a
report, no response."
"Customer repeatedly
harassing Michelle,"
"and no help again... Brian."
"Don't trust management."
"They're part of it."
"Something horrible
in this store."
"I have to find out what it is."
What's happening?
"Finally going to find out
what's happening in this store."
Last message.
Look at this place.
- Yeah, this is weird, Sam.
- Just...
Just look at what I found.
- What?
What is it?
Sam?
- Well, those are old
Brooke's handbooks
from like the '70s or something.
I don't know, but,
I found this in between one.
- Oh, shit.
- Look, dated 7-19-19.
I feel watched.
Something horrible
in this store.
I have to find out what it is.
What?
- Holy shit.
It's Keith.
- Keith?
- He worked
here before you started.
I thought he must have quit
or got fired or something.
I never really found out
what happened.
- What do you mean?
- I don't know.
He just didn't show up one day.
It was weird.
- Did you ask anybody
what happened?
- No.
Sam, I don't know.
People come and go here
all the time.
I usually just keep to myself.
- Do you remember what
day Keith left?
- I don't know.
Some time in October?
- October 3rd?
"Finally going to find out
what's happening in this store."
October 3rd.
No more messages after that.
So now, it makes me wonder like,
like...
- What happened to Keith?
So, Keith goes
to investigate something
and then just doesn't
show up the next day?
I didn't know him that well,
but like...
- I mean, there has to
be an explanation, right?
Who do we ask?
- Dude?
We don't ask anybody.
What if this is some
sort of conspiracy
or black market organ
operation or something?
- Well how, how do we
find out for sure?
- I know Gene keeps
employee records
in a cabinet in his office,
but that's,
that's too risky.
we can't do that.
- Yeah.
- But what if we did?
What if we did?
- Break time.
- Go, go, go.
You stand watch, I'll look.
- Okay. Okay.
Which one is it?
- It's here somewhere, I
promise. No...
No...
- Hey look, it's mine!
- Dude, keep watch.
- Right, right, sorry, sorry.
No...
No.
- Oh, Keith, here we go.
- Sarah, hurry up, I
can hear Gene, let's go.
- Sam.
- What is it? Say it quick,
come on.
It's empty.
- What?
What do you mean, it's empty?
- It's empty.
- Oh...
Shoot.
- He can't hear us.
Trust me.
- All right.
Okay.
That's what Keith meant in
those messages.
They're hiding something.
- Yeah, this is getting scary.
- There's some sort of
conspiracy here.
Just like you said,
Keith was on to something,
and then something
happened to him.
- There's definitely
something going on here.
- I feel like Gene wouldn't just
throw something away
like that by accident.
- No, dude, did you even
read those messages?
This wasn't an accident.
I'm telling you this
place is creepy.
- Yeah well, what do we do?
What do we do?
- Brian keeps secret files in
the closet near his office.
He doesn't think I'm watching.
- Did he just?
- Finally, this job
gets interesting.
- Sarah?
When can we go look into this?
I need to know what's in there,
over.
- Hey doc.
- You don't have to say "over."
- And sorry, I'm on
register all shift.
- Yeah.
Okay.
Right.
No you're not.
You're not alone.
Brian keeps secret files
in the closet near his office.
Dang it!
- What the hell do you
think you're doing?
- I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
- Who's out in the gardening
section right now, huh?
- What?
You're telling me that you
left your section unattended
in the middle of your shift?
- I, I, I was-
Managers only.
Do you remember what I told you?
Do you understand English?
- Yes sir, of course.
- I thought you wanted to
keep this job kid, huh?
I guess you wanna lose it now?
- No, no, not at all.
- Then get your head out
of the clouds.
Stop snooping around
back here like a creep.
And get the fuck back to work.
Okay?
- Sam?
There you are.
- Hey.
- What's wrong, dude?
- Sarah, I'm so sorry.
I went and checked it out,
the closet,
but Brian caught me and,
it was bad.
- Man, why did you
go without me?
- I, I don't know.
I'm just not good at anything.
I'm just... not good
at anything.
- Hey.
- What the hell
am I supposed to do, Sarah?
What am I supposed to do?
- Sam.
- What the hell am I
supposed to do?
- Look at me.
- Hey, look at me.
What do you think you should do?
- Oh.
Yeah,
I think I should talk to Gene
and try to figure things out.
- See, I think that's perfect.
Look, anything outside
of the store,
that's what should really
matter to you.
Okay?
- Yeah.
You're right.
- Look doc, I gotta
get home now,
but let me know how it
goes with Gene.
Okay?
- Yeah.
- Hey, it's gonna be okay.
Don't let this job become
your life, man.
Okay?
- Yeah.
Thanks, Sarah.
- Goodnight, Doctor Sam.
- Gene?
- Sam, to what do I owe
the pleasure?
- Can I talk to you
about something?
- Yes, of course, anything,
come in.
Sit down.
This is about what happened
between you and Brian, right?
- Yeah.
- I heard everything, Sam.
I am so, so sorry.
Nobody deserves to get
yelled at like that,
that's uncalled for.
- I know.
I guess what I'm
trying to say is,
trying to say is
I'm not so sure I'm cut
out to work here anymore.
- Just, just a second.
Sam,
allow me to let you in on
a little secret.
This store, it's teetering
on the edge of bankruptcy.
Yeah, we were hit hard
with the rise
of those big online players,
but you know the one thing
that our competitors don't have,
Sam?
It's the people, the
customer service.
Now with Black Friday
just around the corner,
we're gonna need the best
possible people on our team,
the best.
And you have really
shown promise.
- Thank you, sir.
- Yeah.
Sam, have you ever considered
working here full-time?
- Oh, I-
- I really think that
for your future,
a full-time path, now
that's a smart option.
You know, this here is
a solid career.
You would be on the path
to management.
Let's be honest.
If we want this store to
succeed and grow,
we are gonna need people
like Sam Coleman
in the Brooke's family.
Huh?
For the culture, the
commitment, and for the cause.
Right?!
- Yeah!
- Yeah.
Yeah!
- Yeah!
- Well, there's no rush
on your answer,
but if you want the position,
it's yours.
You, my friend, would
be great at it.
Just let me know by
Black Friday.
Sam, we will make sure
that Brian learns to
respect you, man.
- Wow, thank you.
Thank you so much, Gene,
seriously.
Thank you so much.
I promise I'll have an
answer for you very soon.
- I know you will, Sam, I know.
- Thanks, Gene.
- Are you writing an
order for this section?
- Yeah, I am.
- Okay.
Sam, dude.
How did it go with Gene?
- Oh.
Actually,
actually Sarah,
I think I'm probably gonna
start working here full-time.
- Wait, what?
Sam, you're in school.
You're gonna save lives,
remember?
Doctor Sam?
- No, no, it'll be fine.
I'm pretty sure I'll be able
to work around my schedule.
It's gonna be-
- Wait, no.
Sam?
Did you listen to
anything I said to you?
Come on Sam, are you crazy?
Do you really wanna
get stuck here
working full-time?
You deserve better.
Don't get sucked into
this full-time bullshit.
- Look, I just gotta start
fighting for myself, okay?
I know I can do this.
Gene even said I'm on
track to be management.
- Oh my god.
Are you serious?
- What?
Don't you work here full-time?
Why is it so bad?
- I work here full-time
because I have to.
- Well, Sarah.
Maybe I won't end up like you.
- All right, dude.
Whatever, enjoy the nightmare.
- Look, Sarah.
I'm really sorry for earlier,
but I know this is a
great opportunity
and I just hope we can be cool.
Are we?
Are we cool?
- Don't take this promotion,
Sam.
- Are you serious?
- I'm just looking out
for you here.
- I'm apologizing to you.
I just told you this is a,
this is a great
opportunity for me.
- Sam, do you really
wanna work in this place,
where employees and their
files just go missing?
- Yeah, I do.
- No you don't, Sam.
You have a Brooke's sticker
on your personality square.
You don't know what you want.
- Do you, Sarah?
- Sam, I told you, I told you,
and before-
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, shh.
Let's let's take it down
a few notches, Sarah, huh?
- This is pathetic.
I'm going home.
- Everything alright man?
- Yeah, everything's okay, Gene.
But I wanted to let you know.
- Yeah?
That I gladly accept your
offer to work here full-time.
- Yes, oh my goodness
this is wonderful.
Absolutely wonderful.
That's the right choice Sam.
I am so happy.
We are so happy to have you
in our full-time family, huh?
- Yes, great, wonderful.
So happy for you.
At least if you don't
end up miserable like me,
you'll end up a missing
person, like Keith.
- What do you mean a
missing person?
- Nothing, nothing.
She means nothing by that.
- No, I don't mean nothing.
Keith was on to you guys, Gene.
He knew something bad was
happening here,
and you got rid of him.
- This is a huge
misunderstanding.
Follow me.
Come in. Sam,
shut the door.
I'm telling you, this is
a huge misunderstanding.
I'm sorry.
Look here.
Let's see.
Yep, there it is.
His file is right here.
- What the hell?
- I'm gonna be honest
with you guys.
Keith had a nasty accident
during a shift.
He fell off a ladder and he
got roughed up pretty good.
You wanna read it?
Everything's here.
- What the hell, but?
No, his journal and
the messages.
- No, we took care of it and
he's fine now, I promise.
- No, no, no.
What about if you let us
contact Keith-
- You know I can't give out
information like that, Sarah,
but everything's here.
- No, none of this
was here before.
- What do you mean?
- No, no, no, no, no, no.
- What do you mean Sarah?
- Sam and I snuck into
your office Gene,
and there was no file
here on Keith.
- Don't drag Sam into this.
- What?
But Sam, you found the
room, and his messages.
We both wanted to find out
what happened to Keith.
And there was no file here.
- Sweetheart, documents
take time to process.
Look, this is all a
misunderstanding, I promise.
- Sam, back me up here.
- I, I, I, I don't know.
- This is pathetic.
- I'm sorry, Sarah,
but sneaking into my
office like that.
That's against the handbook.
I'm gonna have to submit
a report to Brian.
Any objection, Sam?
- No.
- Go ahead.
Write your fucking report.
I'm going home.
Good night, Sam.
- I'm sorry you had a deal
with that, Sam.
Mind taking this report
over to Brian?
Then you can head home.
- I will.
- Glad to have you in our
full-time family, Sam.
Have a good night.
- Don't come back!
- Sarah, I-
Bill?
Are you working register today?
- What?
- Where's Sarah?
- She ain't nowhere.
- What?
What do you mean?
- She got fired, kid.
She got fired, okay?
I heard Brian yelling
at her over the phone.
- What?
Are you serious?
What'd he say?
- I don't know. I
couldn't hear exactly.
Something like, "don't
ever come back!"
You know, firing words.
- So she's, she's not here.
- She ain't here.
Brian!
- I'll be right back, Bill.
- Yes?
What is it?
- Do you think we can talk?
- Come in.
What do you need?
- Yeah, so.
- What do you need, Sam?
- Yeah, so I know you're
really busy and everything.
Anyways, I, I really
wanted to ask you about...
About Sarah.
- She broke the rules,
which are in place for a reason.
- That isn't fair, Brian.
She has, she has to-
- Not fair?
What the hell does that mean,
not fair?
A day working into full-time,
and you're trying to
tell me how to do my job?
- I'm sorry.
- Oh, you're sorry?
I give you a place in my store
and you confront me in
my own fucking office.
- I, I'm not confronting
you, I'm just, I'm just,
I'm just trying-
- I'm just, I'm just, I'm
just, I'm just, shut up!
Listen, we need you here
on Black Friday.
All right? I'm gonna be
bringing in some temps
to help out for the day,
but we need full-timers
who know what's going on
if we're gonna pull through.
And if you can't
understand the basic rules,
that's going to be a
problem, for everybody.
- No, it won't be a problem.
- Good.
You're back on gardening
the rest of the day.
- I'm on it, sir.
- Go!
- Sarah?
I know you're not even
here right now,
but I'm gonna figure
this thing out,
once and for all.
Over and out.
Hey Bill?
- What?
- If you distract Brian and
get him out of his office,
no questions asked.
I'll give you five bucks.
- Ten.
- Seven.
- Six.
- Okay.
- You got a deal.
Come on.
Brian, Brian, Brian, get
out, get out here now!
- What, what?
- There's a thief, there's
a thief in the store!
- Where?
- Front of the store.
- Come on, follow me!
- Go!
- Come on!
Brian keeps secret files
in a closet near his office
- Jeez.
- Okay.
Okay, okay.
"Employee incident."
"Harassed by customer,"
"threatened a lawsuit,
fired immediately."
No, no, no, no, "False
report filed."
Oh no, no, no, no, no.
Brian covered it up.
Accident covered up.
Bernard.
"Box baler crushed arm,
false report filed."
Brian...
No no no no no.
Oh my God.
No.
Keith.
No!
No, no, no, no, no.
Brian...
- I'm so sorry, Brian.
You know, I've got bad eyes.
I had no idea it was Gene.
I'll wear my glasses next time.
- October 3rd.
- October 3rd...
What the hell?
What the hell is going on?
You have to fight them.
You have to fight them!
- I will.
- Hey,
it's Sarah.
Sorry I missed your call.
Leave a message, or whatever.
Bye.
- Hey Sarah,
wanted to try you again.
I,
I just found out some
stuff about Brooke's,
and I wanted to let you know I,
I,
I just wanted to tell you,
that Brian covered up so
much corruption.
So many people were hurt
and nobody knows about it,
but I'm never gonna let this
happen to anyone ever again.
And you know what?
I'm gonna do whatever it
takes to take Brooke's down.
So yeah.
I have a plan for Black Friday,
and Brooke's won't survive it.
Gene?
- Mm-hmm.
- Have you noticed Brian today?
Just listen.
And, and the employee
handbook says,
you can't work if you're sick.
I know you know that.
- I'll go and talk to him.
- Yes, what is it?
- I've noticed that
you've been pretty sick
recently.
You can't come in for Black
Friday when you're sick.
It's against the rules.
- I don't care if I'm
on death's door,
I will be here on Black Friday.
- Hey!
- Don't get involved, kid!
- No, no, listen to me!
If you're really sick,
it's gonna be hard for
you to run the store
and manage everybody.
What if,
what if I take on the
responsibilities of team leader?
Just for the day.
- I think that's a
great compromise.
- Can you do it?
- I will.
- Okay.
- I'll see you on Friday, early.
- Of course.
- Sam,
I'm proud of you.
- Black Friday,
here we come.
- Good morning,
everyone.
Thank you for coming
in early today.
As you know,
today is the most important
day of the year for Brooke's.
This day can make or break us.
So let's make it make us, okay?
I'll be frank.
We need to make $15,000 today
in order to pull through.
It'll be close,
but I'm very confident that
we can make it with hard work.
So, thank you again to our temps
for coming in to help us today.
We have a fantastic a team,
and I know that we will succeed.
We have to succeed.
We have to.
- All right team, Brian's a
bit under the weather today.
So I've chosen Sam Coleman
as team leader,
and I couldn't be more proud.
If he tells you to do
something, you do it.
No questions asked, huh?
You got this, Sam, come on.
- Here we go.
Bill, Mandy, you two will
be on the floor
restocking as necessary.
Gene will be on the floor
keeping customers happy.
Ben, you'll be restocking too.
Vincent, you'll start
out on register.
Brian will be in the back,
supervising,
keeping everything on track.
And I am team leader,
rotating between
stations as necessary.
- Any questions?
That's what I like to hear.
Everybody, hands in the middle.
Brooke's on three, one, two,
three.
Brooke's!
- Brain, how's it going?
Are we close to our quota?
- Yeah we're almost there,
but we have to keep hustling.
Stay focused.
We close in an hour.
This is the time that
counts the most.
We have to pull through.
Now, get back in there, go.
- I'm on it, sir.
Here we go.
- Hey Vincent.
- Yeah?
- I think you got this.
So I'm gonna go help
out in the back.
- What, are you sure?
Okay, okay, I got this.
- You got this.
- What?
- Bill, you're doing
a great job.
- Thank you.
- In fact, Bill, actually,
you're doing such a good job,
Um.
Brian told me to let you
know that if you wanted to,
you can take off and
go home early.
- I was wrong about you kid.
I know what you're doing.
Good luck.
See you later!
- Hey, so I can take
over for you now, Mandy.
Why don't you head home?
- Don't you guys need help here?
Like?
- We have a very capable crew,
and you'll be compensated
for your whole shift,
so uh, don't even
worry about it.
- Oh, okay.
Bye.
- Hey Bill, wait for me.
- What?
- Uh yeah, they're gone.
I, I don't know what to do.
- Are you joking around,
are you joking with me?
- Hello?
- Oh, I'm so sorry.
Excuse me, I have to run.
- I'm gonna be
all alone here?
- No, actually you
can head home.
You're gonna get compensated
for the whole day.
- Oh, okay.
Cool, cool.
- Hey Vincent, go ahead
and take off for the day.
You've earned it.
We're gonna compensate you
for your whole shift anyway,
so don't worry about it.
- Okay, okay.
- Sam, what in Brooke's
name is happening?
- I don't know, the temps
all left on me.
- What?
- Everybody's gone.
What do I do?
- Uh uh uh, let me do it.
Let me do it. Let me do it.
Over here everybody, over here.
I can help you.
- What's the hold up?
- Gene, are you all right?
- We can't do this.
- What?
- There's too many people,
what the hell do we do?
- I think I have an idea.
- Well, quit standing
there and do it.
- Excuse me, ladies
and gentlemen.
Ladies and gentlemen,
please listen up.
I'd like to announce that,
um, all further purchases
will be full price.
- That's not true!
- Discounted! It's all
still discounted!
Please!
- I'm sorry! I don't
make the rules!
- No, no, no, no, no!
That's not true!
- Don't listen to him!
- What the hell?
- Oh my God.
- I'm gonna take my break now.
Ladies and gentlemen,
Brooke's will be
closing promptly.
No more purchases will
be made today.
Please head towards your
nearest exist.
And remember, a Brooke's
day is a great day.
- I did it, Keith.
One thing left.
Yes, what is it?
- Hey Brian, can we
talk real quick?
Uh, um,
How's, um...
how's everything going?
- Fine.
Why do you ask?
- No reason just, just
wanted to say,
just wanted to say something.
- Okay?
- Um.
- Keith, what?
I don't have all day.
- You can't keep doing this.
- What?
What are you talking about?
No, no, no, Keith. No!
What the hell are you doing?
- I'm sorry, Brian.
- Let me outta here.
- I know you're doing
something terrible.
I know there's something
bad going on here.
- Keith, open this door,
right now.
- I can't let you keep
getting away with it.
- You do not know what
you're doing.
You have no idea
what's going on.
- I'm going to find out what
you've been hiding, Brian.
I'm going to find proof.
- No, no, no, no, no.
Keith, don't walk away!
No, please, come back!
Keith, Keith, please!
I can't protect you.
Keith, I can't. Come back,
Keith.
No! Keith, come back, please!
I can't protect you!
Oh my God, no, no.
Shit, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Keith, no, no, no, no.
Please come back, turn around.
Keith, please God,
please turn around.
Do not go in there.
Shit, no, no!
Keith, no, no, no, Keith!
Turn around, Keith.
No, no.
I'm sorry.
What did you do?
What the fuck did you do?
I know about everything, Brian.
- What did you do?
- It's over.
I found all, all,
all the shit you've
been covering up.
I took your keys right
from under you.
- You little bastard.
- I went into that closet.
I found the files.
I found the boxes with the files
you've been covering up,
asshole.
Yeah, you better run, asshole.
No, stop, I'm serious, man.
I'm gonna turn you in Brian.
I know about Keith.
I know what's in this store.
- You do?
- Yeah.
Corruption, cover-ups, evil.
- Oh sweet Jesus.
I cannot believe how
stupid I was
to trust you on Black Friday.
- I know about Keith.
I found his journal.
I have his death
certificate right here.
He died working here, Brian,
and I won't let him die in vain.
You covered it up, evil
piece of shit!
You care more about making money
than the lives of
your employees.
- You've never been more wrong
in your entire fucking life,
kid.
- Oh, just calm down.
- Oh, I failed, I failed.
It's done.
The money's gonna be gone soon.
The store's about to
be bankrupt,
and I have nothing,
nothing left to feed you.
Help me,
for I don't know what to do.
- The only thing that I've done
for the last 20 miserable
years of my life
is to work to keep
this place alive.
You could live 10 lifetimes
and not comprehend
the lengths that I've gone to.
- No, no, I know exactly
what's happening asshole-
- No, you don't!
- Talk to me.
Tell me what to do.
Where are you?
I've given you everything,
I've always been there for you.
I need your help, please
tell me, what can I do?
- I have been trying
to protect you,
to keep anything from
happening to you, to any of us.
- Really?
Is that why you fired Sarah?
- I fired her to keep her safe.
Listen to me.
I kept those documents to
figure this out
and to keep people safe.
All those people,
everyone who got hurt,
they all asked questions.
That's why they were
punished, but not by me.
Michelle, Ernesto, Bernard.
They were starting to
figure it all out,
but Keith came the closest.
So if Sarah would've come back
after uncovering that shit,
they would've killed her too.
- Bullshit, this is you, Brian.
This is all you!
- Shut the fuck up and
listen to me.
We don't have much time.
If you'd like to share your
experience with us,
find our friendly Brooke's
general manager, Gene Knibbs,
Gene?
Hello?
Gene!
Gene.
No more games.
You know that the boss man will
never surrender.
So now, after all this time,
you have our blessing,
to take care of it.
- Yes.
- Please.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Yes, I will.
Yes.
I will.
- Yes!
I can?
I may?
- Yes, you may.
- I will.
I will.
- Your hard work is paying off.
No more sitting in the shadows.
Let us out this cage.
Let us out of this prison.
And then,
we will be free.
- Oh yes.
Then we will be free.
- Yes!
Do it. Do it.
♪ A Brooke's day is
a great day ♪
- Come on, we have to
do something.
They feed off this place.
We have to keep them here.
Without this store,
they get out of their
cage, into the world.
It's our responsibility to
keep them here.
- Who?
What are you talking about?
- You can't run from it.
Here.
- Who?
- Take these, take 'em.
Sam, take them.
He trusts you.
Sam, it's your responsibility.
I've done this for as
long as I can.
Listen closer than you've ever
listened to anything before.
You have to keep feeding them.
Sam, feed them.
- Brian? Who?
- Sam, you have to keep
feeding them.
Sam.
Gene,
wait.
Listen to me.
Sam, don't let them out!
Don't let them out!
No!
Lock the doors!
Keep the doors locked!
Sam!
- ♪ A Brooke's day is a
great day, woo hoo hoo! ♪
It's show time!
- Sir.
Please.
You have to get out.
Something, something
horrible is happening.
You, you have to get out.
Just, just go.
Sir, please, please.
You have to, you have
to come with me.
We can get somewhere safe.
- Do you like him?
The closest we could get
to human so far.
We're so proud of what
we've created.
Do you like him?
- No. No. You ki-
- You have no idea
the power that they
could give us.
This is the first one that
could actually blend in,
the first of many.
- No, you killed-
you killed-
- Show him.
- No,
no, stop!
- It's okay, Sam.
- Stop, I'm serious, man.
- Don't take another step!
- You'll never have to
worry again, Sam.
- Stop.
- I always knew you'd choose us,
Sam.
- Please, stop.
- No, no, no, no, no, no.
- I'm sorry!
A Brooke's day,
is a great day.
No! No!
No!
- No, Sam, no!
- What the fuck?
- No,
no, no!
Stop it, no!
- What the fuck!?
What the fuck?
Look at what you've done!
- What the fuck?
- What have you done?
Why, Sam?
Oh.
- Help me!
Now!
Sam,
you will be punished for this.
Sam, get back here.
Get back here, Sam!
No, no. Don't
touch the light.
Don't touch it.
Stay back.
Do you know how hard
we've worked?
- What the fuck?
- Do you?
- This is what we had before,
but then you went and
killed the customer.
He was the most evolved
body we made in 40 years.
- What are you?
Where did you come from?
- Sam.
You should know by now,
this store is home to
countless souls,
damned to hell,
souls that would otherwise
be trapped forever.
Don't you feel it?
When I got this job, a voice,
it came to me and
offered me a deal.
If I helped them create bodies,
in exchange I would
share their power.
In exchange, I would live
forever with purpose.
Brian kept us here for so long.
Thought he could stop us.
We weren't strong enough
yet, but it was inevitable.
Eventually we would be able
to walk out of the store
and claim whatever we wanted
as our own.
- Are you gonna eat me?
- Sam, no, if you work
with us, if you help us,
then your future is set.
If we want this army to
succeed and grow,
we're gonna need people like
Sam Coleman on our side,
for the culture, the
commitment, and for the cause.
- Why are you letting them
do this to you?
- They are mine.
Don't be like Brian, Sam.
When you let them in, they
take away all your fear,
all the doubt, it'll
be gone Sam.
You'll live a life of
peace and purpose.
Just be a good employee, Sam.
It's the easiest way for you.
Just, just give me Brian's keys,
and I'll know you're with me.
- If I give you the keys,
will I really be okay?
- It's okay.
Just put them in my hands.
You'll never have to
worry again, son.
Sam?
Sam.
- No.
No!
- It didn't have to go this way,
kid.
- I'm not letting you-
- You were never cut
out for this job, kid.
- Shit, shit.
Oh my god.
- Hey,
it's Sarah.
Sorry, I missed your call.
Leave a message or whatever,
bye.
- Sarah.
I,
I, uh,
Hey, um,
I,
I'm pretty sure I'm gonna
die right about now.
Yeah.
So, uh, I wanted to
say some stuff.
Sarah,
I am really so, so sorry.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry I was so scared,
and,
and I'm sorry it got in the
way of standing up for you.
You were the best thing
about this place.
And,
now, I'm gonna die.
Yeah.
I'm gonna die.
No.
I'm gonna try and fight
my way out of this.
Because,
compared to this,
the real world doesn't
sound so scary.
You were right.
This job really sucks.
Fuck you!
♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ I'm not gonna take
this anymore ♪
♪ 'Cause I found the strength ♪
♪ I never had before ♪
♪ Same old game, but this time ♪
♪ I'm changing the ending ♪
♪ Same old story, but now
I'm gonna win ♪
♪ I've seen enough ♪
♪ I think it's time to let
some chaos in ♪
♪ I'm not gonna do
this anymore ♪
♪ I'm standin' up and
walkin' out the door ♪
♪ 'Cause you play
around with fire ♪
♪ You end up getting burned ♪
Brooke's is the home
of all things hardware.
We've got deals on everything
from planks to pipes to paint.
Not satisfied with your product?
No problem!
'Cause here at Brooke's
Hardware Store.
Service matters most.
♪ I'm not gonna do this
shit no more ♪
♪ I've seen enough, I've seen
enough, I've seen enough ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ I've seen enough! ♪
Sam Coleman,
motherfucker!
- No!
No!
Please! No!
- I'm sorry Brian.
No, no, no! Shoot, shoot!
Shoot! Don't go outside!
No!
Sarah!
- Sam, what the hell
is going on?
- Sarah.
Gene,
Gene was and, and I...
Keith.
Keith was right.
Keith was right!
And now you're here and,
and you saved me.
You saved everybody.
Sarah!
- Sam!
What the fuck
is that?
- Yeah, um,
so, uh...
- My God Sam, the things you
get up to when I'm not around.
- Yeah.
- I knew there was some
creepy shit in this place.
- You want to help
me burn it down?
Sarah?
- Yeah?
- I'm glad you're here.
- I'm glad I am too,
Doctor Sam.
So,
what do we do now?
- Whatever we want.
Burn, baby, burn!
- They got 'em.
♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ I'm not gonna take
this anymore ♪
♪ 'Cause I found the strength ♪
♪ I never had before ♪
♪ Same old game, but this time ♪
♪ I'm changing the ending ♪
♪ Same old story, but now
I'm gonna win ♪
♪ I've seen enough ♪
♪ I think it's time to let
some chaos in ♪
♪ I'm not gonna do
this anymore ♪
♪ I'm standin' up and
walkin' out the door ♪
♪ 'Cause you play
around with fire ♪
♪ You end up getting burned ♪
♪ I'm not gonna do this
shit no more ♪
♪ I've seen enough,
I've seen enough ♪
♪ I've seen enough ♪♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ I've seen enough ♪