LOOK.
WE'RE GONNA GO SMOKE.
WANT TO COME?
UM, NO, THANKS.
WE'LL BE BACK.
SHE'S PROBABLY
JUST IN THE CAR.
YOU'RE AN ASSHOLE, MIKE,
I SWEAR TO GOD.
LISTEN, I DIDN'T
SAY ANYTHING.
NOTHING HAPPENED.
SHE JUST GOT MAD.
- OH, SHE GOT MAD? GOT?
- YEAH, GOT.
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO THINK OF SOMETHING
TO SAY TO HER. YOU'RE APOLOGIZING.
- FINE, WHATEVER.
- YOU GUYS...
IT'S NICE TO KNOW THAT
THERE ARE OTHERS OUT HERE
WHO HAVE HAD THE SAME
KINDS OF EXPERIENCES,
WHO'VE BEEN THROUGH
THE SAME KIND OF FEELINGS.
IT CAN BE VERY HARD
TO RELATE TO PEOPLE
ABOUT A SUICIDE
IN THE FAMILY.
SOMETIMES YOU JUST NEED
TO TALK TO PEOPLE
WHO UNDERSTAND.
THERE ARE SOME FEELINGS
THAT A LOT OF PEOPLE,
EVEN YOUR
VERY BEST FRIENDS,
ARE NOT GONNA BE ABLE
TO RELATE TO.
WELL,
WE WERE SUPPOSED TO HAVE A
COUPLE OF NEW PEOPLE HERE TODAY,
BUT IT LOOKS LIKE A COUPLE
OF THEM COULDN'T QUITE MAKE IT.
SO WE ONLY HAVE ONE...
ONE NEW LINK
IN OUR CHAIN.
WHAT WE USUALLY DO
WHEN WE HAVE A NEW MEMBER
IS A SELF-INTRODUCTORY
TYPE OF THING.
OKAY.
WHENEVER YOU'RE READY.
UM...
MY NAME IS ANGELA.
HI, ANGELA.
Angela:
AND...
I GUESS
THE REASON I'M HERE
IS BECAUSE...
HI.
ARE YOU BRIAN?
YEAH.
CONTINUE.
YOU ALWAYS HAVE TO
TAKE THE BUS?
WHAT?
OH, NO.
I DO IT SOMETIMES
TO SAVE MONEY ON GAS.
OH.
I USED TO ALWAYS HAVE TO
TAKE THE BUS WHEN I WAS LITTLE.
I HATED IT.
IT MADE ME REALLY
ANXIOUS, YOU KNOW?
I FELT LIKE I WAS
GONNA MISS MY STOP.
I ALWAYS GOT NERVOUS THAT
I WAS GONNA MISS MY STOP.
IT'S REALLY STRESSFUL.
BUT IT'S ONE OF THOSE
IT'S-THE-LEAST-I-CAN-DO
SORT OF THINGS, YOU KNOW...
RIDING THE BUS,
THAT IS.
WHY WERE YOU LATE?
MISSED THE BUS.
NO, YOU DIDN'T.
I JUST WAS, I GUESS.
MY NAME IS BRIAN.
I KNEW THAT ALREADY.
OH, YEAH.
YOU'RE ANGELA.
I KNEW THAT ALREADY ALSO.
WHO WAS IT?
MY DAD.
YOU?
MY MOM.
I'M SORRY.
WELL, GOOD LUCK
ON THE BUS, ANGELA.
DON'T GET LOST, OKAY?
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
I GUESS I'll SEE YOU NEXT TIME?
I'M PROBABLY NOT GOING
BACK AGAIN IF I CAN HELP IT.
YEAH, I DON'T WANT TO
EITHER.
REALLY?
NO.
- WELL...
- I MEAN, I GUESS.
I DON'T KNOW, I HAVEN'T
REALLY THOUGHT ABOUT IT.
WELL, DO YOU WANT TO TALK ABOUT
OUR SORROWS ELSEWHERE THEN?
LIKE WHERE?
LIKE ONLINE?
NO, DEFINITELY
NOT ONLINE.
WELL, NOT LIKE A DATE,
RIGHT?
JUST OUT.
ARE YOU SEEING SOMEONE?
NO. ARE YOU?
I PROBABLY WOULDN'T BE
ASKING YOU IF I WERE, RIGHT?
- HEY, BRENT.
- MORNING, ANGELA.
HOW'S THE SECURITY
BUSINESS?
SORRY TO HEAR
ABOUT YOUR MOTHER.
THANKS FOR HELPING US OUT, IAN.
THAT'S REALLY GREAT OF YOU.
ANGELA, HI.
HI, MR. LOPES. I DIDN'T KNOW IF
YOU HAD CLASS OR SOMETHING.
NO, I'M JUST HERE
FOR YOU.
OH, I DIDN'T KNOW
I WAS SO SPECIAL.
NO, I MEAN
I SCHEDULED THIS
MEETING WITH YOU
BECAUSE I NEED
TO KNOW
WHAT'S GOING ON
WITH YOU.
I KNOW.
I'M TRYING TO GET...
DO YOU WORK?
NO, I DON'T.
JUST TO BE HONEST
WITH YOU, ANGELA,
YOU'RE NOT GONNA PASS
THIS CLASS
THE WAY
THINGS ARE GOING.
IT'S NOT THE QUALITY
OF YOUR WORK.
YOU'RE NOT TOO STUPID
FOR THIS CLASS.
IT'S JUST THAT
YOU DON'T
TURN ANYTHING IN.
AT THE SAME TIME,
I CAN'T CUT YOU ANY SLACK
BECAUSE YOU HAVEN'T
GIVEN ME A REASON
TO CUT YOU ANY SLACK,
YOU KNOW?
I... I DON'T KNOW.
I KNOW, I KNOW.
IT'S JUST...
MY GOD.
UM...
MY MOTHER DIED
REALLY RECENTLY.
UM...
SHE WASN'T OLD
OR ANYTHING.
SHE...
KILLED HERSELF.
AND, YOU KNOW, MY DAD'S,
LIKE, NOT IN MY LIFE.
WE'RE SORT OF
NOT ON SPEAKING TERMS.
I'M SORRY.
IT'S OKAY.
I CAN SYMPATHIZE.
I LOST MY DAUGHTER BETH
RECENTLY.
SHE HAD TONSILLITIS,
YOU KNOW, WHICH USUALLY
ISN'T VERY SERIOUS,
BUT THINGS JUST KIND OF...
THEY WENT WRONG.
AND SHE... SHE LEFT US.
AND SHE WAS NINE...
NINE YEARS OLD.
IT WAS REALLY HARD.
I'M SO SORRY.
SO I CAN UNDERS...
I UNDERSTAND.
I UNDERSTAND HOW IT CAN BE
REALLY REALLY HARD.
WELL...
I'M GLAD YOU TOLD ME
WHAT'S GOING ON
WITH YOU, OKAY?
I GUESS I CAN CUT YOU
A LITTLE SLACK NOW.
COME HERE.
- BAD?
- NO, IT'S ANNOYING.
- WHAT DID YOU GET?
- B-MINUS,
WHICH IS SO STUPID.
I HATE THAT GUY.
IF I HAD TO FIND
A NEW ROOMMATE,
I WOULD NEVER PUT UP
ONE OF THESE ADS.
THEY'RE SO WEIRD.
AREN'T THEY WEIRD, ANGE?
UM, I WOULD NEVER
ANSWER ONE.
I DON'T THINK
THEY'RE WEIRD.
WELL, THE REASON WHY YOU WOULDN'T
ANSWER ONE IS 'CAUSE THEY'RE SO WEIRD.
I GUESS.
PEOPLE PUT SOME
CRAZY STUFF UP HERE.
OH MY GOD.
WHAT?
YOUR MESSAGE.
I THOUGHT YOU
ALREADY GOT THAT.
NO.
I KNOW.
IT'S SO SAD.
GOD, WHEN DID
THIS HAPPEN?
A COUPLE OF DAYS AGO
AT THE BEACH.
IT'S HARD TO TELL WITH
KATHERINE, THOUGH, YOU KNOW?
HEY.
HOW WAS WORK?
FUCKING AMAZING.
HOW WAS SITTING ALONE
IN THE APARTMENT?
ACTUALLY, YOU KNOW
WHAT I DID TODAY?
I BOUGHT CIGARETTES
AND WENT TO THE BANK.
DID YOU ROB THE BANK?
NO.
PITY.
I'M GONNA GO CHANGE.
YOU GOT SOMETHING TODAY.
THERE'S NO ADDRESS ON IT.
SOMEONE MUST HAVE, LIKE,
DROPPED IT OFF OR SOMETHING.
I JUST HEARD.
I JUST CAN'T BELIEVE
SHE WOULD DO
SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
OH, HONEY,
WHAT IS IT?
HAPPENS ALL THE TIME,
YOU KNOW...
THERE'S STATISTICS...
EVERYWHERE.
I KNOW.
MORE PEOPLE KILL THEMSELVES
THAN EACH OTHER.
THERE'S MORE SUICIDES
THAN HOMICIDES.
YOU KNOW WHAT THAT
MEANS, ANGELA?
YOU CAN'T BE ALONE.
YOU'RE SAFER LIVING
WITH A COMPLETE STRANGER
THAN WITH YOURSELF.
YOU CAN'T RUN
FROM YOURSELF, THOUGH.
YOU CAN'T ESCAPE IT.
ANGELA, WHAT'S GOING ON?
I'M SORRY, GARRETT...
I MEAN, MR. LOPES.
I CAN'T REALLY STAY, BUT I
JUST WANTED TO STOP BY.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I JUST... I DON'T THINK I'M
GONNA BE ABLE TO GET MY...
I MEAN, MAYBE,
BUT I DON'T THINK
THAT I'M GONNA BE
ABLE TO GET
YOUR INTRO PARAGRAPH
IN ON TIME.
THINGS ARE HAPPENING.
WELL, THANK YOU FOR
LETTING ME KNOW, ANGELA.
SURE, YEAH.
I MEAN, I'll JUST TRY
AND EMAIL IT TO YOU WHEN I
GET A CHANCE OR SOMETHING...
SOON, I MEAN.
JUST GET IT TO ME
WHEN YOU CAN.
THANKS.
I NEVER KNOW IF WE'RE SUPPOSED TO
WAIT FOR THE CHECK OR GO UP TO THE FRONT.
I THOUGHT YOU'D NEVER
BEEN HERE BEFORE.
OH, WELL, YEAH. BUT I MEAN
AT PLACES LIKE THIS, I GUESS.
I DON'T KNOW.
CHECK, PLEASE.
WHAT?
YOU GO ON LOTS OF DATES,
DON'T YOU?
YOU DON'T?
WELL, NO.
LET'S JUST SAY
FOR THE SAKE OF,
I DON'T KNOW...
SAY THAT...
OKAY, LET'S SAY...
THAT YOU WERE
ON A DATE RIGHT NOW.
- RIGHT THIS MOMENT?
- RIGHT THIS MOMENT.
- WITH YOU?
- WITH ME
OR ANYONE.
IT DOESN'T MATTER.
OKAY.
WHAT WOULD YOU DO
RIGHT NOW?
WELL, HMM.
I WOULD PROBABLY TRY
TO GET TO KNOW YOU
OR HER,
SO I MIGHT ASK,
I DON'T KNOW...
- WHAT'S YOUR FAVORITE...?
- CHINESE.
I THOUGHT
IT WASN'T YOU.
WHAT'S YOURS?
ITALIAN.
WELL, THEY HAD PASTA.
I DON'T LIKE PASTA.
BUT YOUR FAVORITE
FOOD'S ITALIAN?
THAT'S WEIRD.
NO, THAT'S AN INTERESTING
FACT ABOUT ME...
A FACT THAT MIGHT
MAKE YOU THINK
THAT I AM A UNIQUE
AND INTERESTING PERSON.
AND YOU ARE
THE ONLY PERSON HERE
THAT KNOWS THAT ABOUT ME
AT THIS VERY MOMENT.
AND THAT IS WHAT'S GONNA
MAKE YOU LIKE ME.
OKAY, YOUR TURN.
OKAY.
UM, LET'S SEE...
OH, MY MOM AND I
USED TO SEND
MESSAGES IN A BOTTLE,
LIKE, ALL THE TIME.
WHAT WERE THE MESSAGES?
I DON'T KNOW.
I DON'T REMEMBER.
I WISH I DID.
DID YOU PUT YOUR
CONTACT INFORMATION ON THEM?
SHUT UP.
YOU'RE MAKING FUN
OF MY INTERESTING FACT.
DO YOU STILL DO IT...
I MEAN, SEND A MESSAGE?
NO, AFTER MY MOM DIED
I JUST GOT SO MAD AT HER
THAT I NEVER WENT BACK
TO THE BEACH.
IT'S LIKE IT CHEATED ME
OR SOMETHING, YOU KNOW?
MAYBE IF YOU
FORGAVE HER...
I DON'T WANT TO.
YOU SHOULD.
IT'S BETTER.
HOW DID IT HAPPEN?
CAN I ASK THAT?
SHE SLIT HER THROAT.
OH MY GOD. WOW.
YEAH, I KNOW.
IN THE KITCHEN.
I FOUND HER.
I'M SORRY.
WHAT ABOUT YOUR DAD?
HE PUT HIS HEAD
IN THE OVEN.
I DIDN'T THINK
PEOPLE REALLY DID THAT.
ME NEITHER.
DID SHE LEAVE A NOTE?
NO.
DOESN'T MAKE ANY SENSE,
YOU KNOW.
DOCTORS ARE SUPPOSED
TO HELP PEOPLE.
MY DAD WAS A DOCTOR
AT HUNTER GENERAL.
SAME WITH MY MOM.
MAYBE THEY KNEW EACH OTHER.
- THERE MUST BE SOMETHING OFF, YOU KNOW?
- WHAT?
THEY DID IT AT THE SAME TIME,
BOTH DOCTORS.
I DON'T KNOW.
IT'S THE HOSPITAL.
THAT PLACE MUST HAVE
DONE SOMETHING TO THEM.
- MAYBE IF WE WENT...
- NO NO.
YEAH, LET'S GO TO THE HOSPITAL.
MAYBE WE CAN FIND SOMETHING OUT.
I CAN'T GO THERE.
I CAN'T GO TO THE PLACES
WHERE SHE'S BEEN.
I CAN'T TOUCH THE THINGS
THAT SHE'S TOUCHED.
I CAN'T.
IF I TELL YOU
SOMETHING,
DO YOU PROMISE
NOT TO TELL ANYONE?
WHO WOULD I TELL?
SERIOUSLY.
OF COURSE.
I MEAN, IT'S NOT
A BIG DEAL.
IT'S JUST...
WHAT?
I MEAN, SERIOUSLY,
IT'S PROBABLY NOTHING.
WELL, YOU SHOULD
TELL ME.
YOU KNOW, I'M NOT
GONNA TELL YOU
BECAUSE IF I TOLD YOU
THEN I'M MAKING IT A BIG DEAL.
AND IF I DON'T TELL YOU
IT'S LIKE IT NEVER HAPPENED.
SO JUST FORGET IT.
YOU SHOULD TELL ME.
NO.
FINE. DON'T.
YOU CAN'T DO THAT,
YOU KNOW.
WHAT?
SAY SOMETHING PROVOCATIVE
AND THEN NOT TELL ME.
PROVOCATIVE?
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN.
WHAT IF I TELL YOU SOMETHING?
THEN WILL YOU TELL ME?
I GUESS SO.
WHAT?
I GOT...
I GOT THIS TAPE.
OF YOUR DAD?
- YEAH.
- ME TOO, OF MY MOM.
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
- I DON'T KNOW,
BUT WHY WOULD SOMEBODY
VIDEOTAPE OUR PARENTS?
WHY WOULD SOMEBODY
DO THAT?
I DON'T KNOW.
ANGELA, I THINK...
I THINK MAYBE
MY DAD DIDN'T...
LIKE, MAYBE
SOMEBODY ELSE DID.
WHAT?
COME ON, LIKE
SOMEBODY KILLED HIM?
IT JUST DOESN'T MAKE
SENSE TO ME ANY OTHER WAY.
I GUESS I'M JUST
CONFUSED, YOU KNOW?
I DON'T KNOW.
MAYBE...
MAYBE SOMEBODY'S
TRYING TO HELP US.
LISTEN, WE'RE GONNA BE
FINE, OKAY?
I'M GLAD YOU'RE HERE.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
I JUST SAID THAT.
I'M NOT REALLY USED TO
THIS SORT OF THING.
YOU'RE DOING FINE.
THANKS.
I SHOULD GO.
OKAY, I'M GONNA GO.
I GET OFF WORK AT 7:00.
I'll COME OVER.
YEAH, OKAY.
LOCK THE DOOR, OKAY?
- SHUT UP.
- I'll SEE YOU TOMORROW.
OKAY, BYE.
Brent: YOU KNOW. ARE YOU HAPPY?
SURE.
"I'M OUT BOWLING
WITH THE BUDDIES, BABY."
WHEN DID YOU PLAN
ON TELLING ME ALL THIS?
SHUT UP, LISA.
I DON'T HAVE TO TELL YOU
EVERY FUCKING THING
THAT I DO.
YOU KNOW, YOU BORE ME!
YOU KNOW WHAT?
WHY DON'T YOU GET OFF
YOUR FUCKING HIGH HORSE?
IT'S JUST
A FUCKING HOBBY.
SURE, LIKE IT'S
SO HARD TO BELIEVE
THAT I MIGHT WANT TO KNOW WHAT
MY HUSBAND DOES IN HIS SPARE TIME.
ARE YOU HAPPY?
YOU'RE DOING THIS
TO MY LIFE.
SHUT UP, LISA.
YOU SHUT UP.
YOU FUCKING SHUT
YOUR HOLE. SHUT UP.
I JUST DON'T FEEL
SAFE HERE BY MYSELF.
BABE, I KNOW.
I KNOW YOU DON'T.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
EVERYTHING IS
GONNA BE FINE, OKAY?
I'll STAY HERE
UNTIL BRIAN GETS HOME.
AND WE'LL JUST WATCH A MOVIE
AND PAINT OUR NAILS.
AND I'll MAKE DINNER, OKAY?
AND YOU'LL NEVER EVER EVER
HAVE TO BE ALONE AGAIN, OKAY?
MY WIFE AND I WANT TO GET
BACK THERE AS SOON AS WE CAN.
IT'S THE MOST BEAUTIFUL
CITY YOU'VE EVER SEEN.
IS IT?
IT'S JUST GORGEOUS.
ARE YOU BACK IN SCHOOL
NOW, BRIAN?
EXCUSE ME?
- ARE YOU IN SCHOOL?
- NO.
I DON'T KNOW. I GUESS I JUST REALLY
HAVEN'T BEEN THINKING ABOUT IT
TOO MUCH RECENTLY,
YOU KNOW?
DO YOU KNOW
WHAT YOU WANT TO DO?
I WANT TO DRIVE A TAXI.
YEAH?
A TAXI?
I KNOW A GUY
WHO DRIVES A TAXI.
I CAN GIVE YOU
HIS NUMBER.
YEAH, THAT WOULD BE
REALLY GREAT.
DEFINITELY GIVE ME
HIS NUMBER.
YOU GOT IT.
YOU LEFT YOUR PHONE
HERE YESTERDAY.
DO YOU HAVE IT NOW?
YEAH, IT'S ON THE TABLE.
WHERE WAS IT?
IN THE KITCHEN.
OH, YEAH.
I REMEMBER LEAVING IT
ON THE COUNTER.
THAT IS, LIKE, THE THIRD TIME
I'VE HAD TO REPLACE THIS THING.
THANKS FOR FINDING IT.
NO PROBLEM.
ALL RIGHT,
I'M TAKING OFF.
OH. YOU GOT
A HOT DATE?
SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
I HAVE TO CATCH THE BUS.
I'll SEE YOU TOMORROW, OKAY?
ARE YOU SURE?
BRIAN IS GONNA BE HERE
IN, LIKE, A MINUTE. I'll BE FINE.
REALLY?
YES, REALLY.
BRIT, YOU'VE BEEN
REALLY GREAT.
OH...
OH, AND I'M REALLY SORRY
ABOUT ALL THIS.
PLEASE DON'T STAY
YOU'RE SORRY.
YOU'RE MY FRIEND.
YOU DON'T NEED TO SAY SORRY.
OKAY.
PROMISE ME YOU WON'T SAY
SORRY TO ME AGAIN.
BRIT, HE'S GONNA BE HERE
ANY MINUTE.
I DON'T WANT YOU
TO MEET HIM YET.
ARE YOU TRYING
TO REPLACE ME?
OF COURSE NOT.
- OKAY, BYE.
- BYE.
BYE BYE BYE BYE.
HI.
I DIDN'T SEE THIS
THE FIRST TIME.
IT WAS ON MINE TOO.
THE SAME EXACT THING?
YEAH.
SO THAT'S YOUR DAD?
ARE YOU MAD AT ME
FOR SOME REASON?
- BABE.
- NO.
WHAT IS GOING ON?
I HATE THIS.
I'M TERRIFIED.
MY LIFE IS TERRIFYING.
THIS IS NOT A GOOD TIME
FOR ME TO BE ALONE.
YOU'RE NOT.
I KNOW.
WHAT'S WRONG?
IAN COMMITTED SUICIDE
LAST NIGHT.
I DON'T THINK
HE DID IT.
WHAT DID THEY SAY?
HE SUFFOCATED HIMSELF
IN THE CAR.
IT WASN'T EVEN
HIS HOUSE.
GOD, THIS
FUCKING SUCKS.
I THINK I KNOW
WHO TOOK THE PICTURE.
HE USUALLY COMES BACK FROM
WORK RIGHT BEFORE I GO TO SCHOOL.
HE'S A SECURITY GUARD.
WHAT ABOUT HIS WIFE?
JUST ABOUT TO LEAVE.
OKAY, SO HOW LONG
DO WE HAVE?
AT LEAST 15 MINUTES.
I DON'T KNOW
IF I CAN DO THIS.
WE HAVE TO DO THIS, OKAY?
THERE'S NO BETTER TIME.
I THINK THEY HAVE A KEY
AROUND HERE SOMEWHERE.
HEY, PUT THAT DOWN.
WHAT ARE WE DOING HERE?
WHAT ELSE CAN WE DO?
OH, YOU'RE SO ANNOYING.
YOU'RE ANNOYING.
WHAT ARE YOU...?
- WHATEVER.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- I WAS JUST TRYING TO DISTRACT HIM OR SOMETHING.
I JUST CAME BY TO TELL YOU
THAT I DON'T THINK
I CAN COME BACK TO YOUR
CLASS RIGHT NOW.
OKAY.
- WHAT HAPPENED.
- I TOLD HIM.
I SHOULDN'T HAVE TOLD HIM.
HE DIDN'T BELIEVE ME.
ANGELA, OF COURSE HE DIDN'T.
NO ONE WILL.
I THOUGHT HE WOULD.
SWEETIE, LET'S GO
TO YOUR HOUSE, OKAY?
I REALLY DON'T WANT TO
GO BACK THERE RIGHT NOW.
COULD WE PLEASE
JUST GO TO YOURS?
OF COURSE.
IT'S OKAY.
WE'RE GONNA GET
THROUGH THIS, OKAY?
PLEASE NO.
I CAN'T.
WE WENT INTO HIS HOUSE.
WE CAN'T GO TO THE POLICE.
IAN WOULDN'T KILL HIMSELF.
- MAYBE HE DID.
- NO.
BRIAN.
- I TOOK ONE OF THE TAPES.
- BRIAN.
IT HAS TO BE HIM, ANGELA.
I HAD TO BE SURE.
- Angela: WHY WOULD HE...?
- HEY, GUYS.
HEY, GRAHAM.
HEY, ANGEY.
OH, SORRY.
HEY, GRAHAM.
WAIT A SECOND.
HOW...
DID I INTRODUCE
YOU GUYS?
WHAT?
YEAH, THE OTHER DAY
SHE WAS OVER.
NO, I WASN'T.
MAYBE IT WAS
SOMEONE ELSE.
Angela: I GUESS I JUST
FIGURED WE HAD MET
'CAUSE I'D SEEN YOU SO MANY
TIMES WALK IN AND OUT OF...
I GUESS THAT'S
YOUR ROOM?
YEAH, THAT'S MY ROOM.
HOW DID YOU KNOW
HER NAME?
YOU MUST HAVE TOLD ME.
NO, I DIDN'T.
MAYBE SHE JUST LOOKS LIKE AN
ANGELA. I DON'T FUCKING KNOW.
YEAH, BUT YOU
CALLED ME ANGEY.
IT'S A FUCKING
NICKNAME.
YOU KNOW WHAT, GRAHAM?
I'M SORRY, MAN,
CAN YOU GET OUT
OF HERE, PLEASE?
ALL RIGHT.
JESUS.
SEE YOU SOON,
ANGELIQUE.
HELLO.
HEY, I'M AT YOUR HOUSE.
HUH-UH.
I WAS ON MY WAY TO MY MOM'S
AND I WANTED TO STOP HERE
AND SEE YOU FIRST.
IT WAS OPEN.
YEAH.
WHERE ARE YOU AT?
OH, OF COURSE.
BE SAFE, ANGE.
HELLO?
I CAN'T HEAR ANYMORE.
ANGE, IF YOU'RE
SAYING SOMETHING,
I CAN'T HEAR ANYMORE.
I'M HANGING UP.
BYE.
SHE WAS AT MY HOUSE.
INSIDE?
YEAH.
LOOK AT THIS.
THIS IS THE TAPE
I PULLED FROM HIS HOUSE.
HELP ME.
HELP. HELP.
HELP.
WHAT?
WHAT WHAT?
NO.
OKAY.
LISTEN...
YOU WANT A GRANOLA BAR?
IS IT LATE?
IS GRAHAM HOME?
I DON'T KNOW.
HIS DOOR IS ALWAYS CLOSED.
WHAT?
I DON'T THINK
I WANT TO GO IN.
WHAT'S UP?
I JUST
DON'T WANT TO.
THEN WHY ARE WE HERE,
ANGELA?
I DON'T KNOW, BUT I
DON'T WANT TO GO IN.
WHY?
I HAVEN'T BEEN HERE
SINCE THE BURIAL.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
- I'M STILL MAD AT HER.
- SO?
I'M NOT READY
TO FORGIVE HER.
YOU HAVE TO.
I DON'T HAVE TO.
WHY DO I HAVE TO?
I DON'T WANT TO,
SO WHY DO I HAVE TO?
SHE MADE A COMMITMENT
TO HER LIFE WHEN SHE HAD ME,
WHICH SHE COMPLETELY IGNORED
WHEN SHE LEFT ME.
YOUR DAD LEFT TOO,
DIDN'T HE?
YEAH, WELL,
I DON'T NEED HIM, OKAY?
MAYBE SHE DIDN'T NEED
TO LIVE ANYMORE,
BUT I NEEDED HER TOO.
AND SHE SHOULD HAVE BEEN
THINKING ABOUT THAT.
AND SHE JUST LEFT ME.
WHATEVER, ANGELA.
IT DOESN'T MATTER ANYMORE, OKAY?
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO, HUH?
ARE YOU JUST GONNA
STAY MAD AT HER FOREVER?
WHEN PEOPLE ASK YOU
YOU'RE JUST GONNA SAY,
"MY MOM DIED.
I'VE NEVER BEEN TO HER GRAVE"?
WHY DO YOU CARE
WHAT I DO?
BECAUSE APPARENTLY
THERE'S SOMETHING BETWEEN US.
HEY, I KNOW
WHAT'S GOING ON
WITH YOU.
I'VE BEEN THERE.
I'M CURRENTLY THERE.
I'M GONNA BE
BOLD HERE, ANGELA,
AND I'M GONNA SAY
THAT SOMEONE KILLED MY DAD.
I BELIEVE THAT.
AND YOU CAN EITHER
TAKE THINGS
THE WAY YOU HAVE BEEN
ALL THIS TIME
AND STAY STUCK IN THIS...
I DON'T KNOW WHAT IT IS...
RUT, I GUESS.
OR YOU CAN
AT THE VERY LEAST ADMIT
THAT THERE'S SOMETHING ELSE
GOING ON HERE.
SOMEONE HATES US.
I DON'T KNOW,
MAYBE YOU CAN ASK HER
FOR AN APOLOGY.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
MY MOM'S THIS WAY.
ARE YOU GONNA
BE OKAY?
ARE YOU?
I'll SEE YOU SOON.
BRIAN!
- I GOT A...
- I GOT A TAPE.
IT'S OKAY, COME ON.
WE'RE GONNA BE FINE.
COME ON, IT'S OKAY.
COME ON, WE'LL BE FINE.
COME ON, WE'VE GOT TO GET
BACK TO THE CAR. COME ON.
- I'M COMING.
- WE'LL BE FINE, OKAY?
WE'VE GOT TO GET BACK
TO THE CAR. DON'T WORRY.
WE'LL BE FINE, OKAY?
COME ON, LET'S GO.
LET'S GO.
I'M COMING.
WE'LL BE FINE. WE'VE GOT TO
GET BACK TO THE CAR, COME ON.
WE'LL BE FINE.
COME ON, LET'S GO.
LET'S GO, COME ON.
LET'S GO. COME ON, BABY.
LET'S GO. WE'VE GOT
TO GET BACK TO THE CAR.
- IT'S FINE. WE'LL BE FINE.
- HE'S GONNA KILL US.
WE GOTTA KEEP ON DRIVING
FOR A WHILE, OKAY?
WHAT DOES HE WANT?
WHAT THE FUCK DOES HE WANT?
WHY DOES HE HATE US?
WHY DID HE KILL MY MOM?
I HAVE TO CALL HER AGAIN.
I HAVE TO CALL BRIT.
HEY, BRIT.
BRIT?
IT WASN'T BRIT.
WHAT IS IT?
A CAR.
IS IT HIS?
THE HEADLIGHTS
ARE OFF.
DON'T.
IT'S NOT THAT DARK.
IT'S DARK.
IT'S OKAY.
HE'S GONE.
WHAT THE FUCK WAS THAT?
- I DON'T KNOW. JESUS.
- SOMETHING IN YOUR TRUNK?
NO.
I DON'T KNOW, MAYBE.
FUCK.
OH, GOD.
JESUS CHRIST.
WE HAVE TO STOP.
WHAT IS THAT?
I THINK YOUR TIRE BLEW.
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
WE NEED TO KEEP ON
DRIVING, OKAY?
BUT THE SPARE'S
UNDER HIM.
IS THIS THE ONE?
I THINK SO.
IT'S WEIRD.
IT HASN'T BEEN THAT LONG.
I THINK WE SHOULD GO.
WHERE CAN WE GO?
FIND SOMEONE.
AND TELL THEM THAT WE HAVE
MY DEAD NEIGHBOR
IN THE TRUNK
WITH A GUN?
IF WE GET BACK ON THE ROAD,
HE'LL KILLS US.
WE'RE NOT ANY SAFER
IF WE STAY HERE.
YEAH, BUT...
IF I LEAVE IT'S LIKE I NEVER
FORGAVE HER FOR DYING.
I CAN'T DO THAT.
OKAY.
THE MOON'S BIG TONIGHT.
I CAN'T TELL
IF IT'S FULL.
I NEVER CAN.
I THINK IT IS.
IT'S USUALLY FOGGY. YOU CAN'T
SEE THE MOON MOST NIGHTS.
YOU CAME HERE AT NIGHT?
WE WENT ALL THE TIME.
EVEN NOW...
I JUST WANT YOU
TO KNOW
THAT I'M GLAD
I MET YOU.
I'M GLAD
I MET YOU TOO.
- ANGELA.
- MM?
IT'S MORNING.
LET'S GO.
BUT I'M SO COMFORTABLE.
COME ON, LET'S GO.
HER NAME WAS BETH.
DON'T BOTHER
SCREAMING, OKAY?
BECAUSE NO ONE'S GONNA
HEAR YOU...
NO NEIGHBORS.
YOU HAVE NO RIGHT
TO BE CRYING.
SORRY.
SHUT UP!
SEE, THAT'S THE THING...
NO ONE EVER
APOLOGIZED TO ME,
NOT ONCE.
SO WHAT DO I OWE YOU?
HMM? WHAT?
WHAT DO I OWE YOU?
I OWE YOU NOTHING.
I OWE YOU HELL.
THEY TOOK IT ALL.
THEY TOOK
EVERYTHING I LOVED.
IT WAS TONSILLITIS.
TONSILLITIS.
CAN YOU FUCKING
BELIEVE THAT?
IT'S NOT EVEN
A REAL DISEASE.
I'M SORRY.
SHUT UP!
IT DIDN'T HAPPEN TO ME.
IT HAPPENED TO HER.
THAT'S BETH.
MY LIFE WAS DESTROYED
BECAUSE OF TWO FUCKING PEOPLE.
- I'M SORRY.
- SHUT UP.
SHUT UP. SHUT UP.
SHUT UP.
SEE, THAT'S WHY
I DID IT THIS WAY...
TO KEEP YOU SAFE,
YOU KNOW,
SO NOBODY WOULD EVER KNOW.
THEY WOULD JUST HAVE TO GUESS
AND MAKE UP LITTLE STORIES
ABOUT WHY THEIR CHILDREN
OR THEIR PARENTS
HATED THEIR LIVES.
WE DIDN'T DO
ANYTHING TO YOU.
AND WHAT DID
MY DAUGHTER DO?
YOU ARE TOO STUPID
FOR THIS CLASS.
IT'S NOT ABOUT
WHAT YOU DID.
IT'S ABOUT WHAT
YOUR PARENTS DID.
THEY DESTROYED
MY DAUGHTER'S LIFE.
AND NOW I'M GONNA
DESTROY YOURS.
NO. NO.
I'VE TAKEN
EVERYONE YOU LOVE.
AND NOW I'M GONNA
TAKE YOU.
NO.
IT SHOULD HAVE BEEN
A NORMAL PROCEDURE,
ANGELA.
SO COULDN'T YOUR PARENTS
HAVE DONE THEIR JOBS?
NO, IT WASN'T
THEIR FAULT.
IT WAS AN ACCIDENT.
MAYBE IT WAS WORSE
THAN WHAT THEY THOUGHT.
NO NO NO NO.
YOUR PARENTS...
THEY KILLED HER.
THEY DESTROYED
MY FAMILY.
MY LIFE, ANGELA...
MY LIFE, MY LIFE.
YOU GET ONE.
MY LIFE!
WHAT WOULD YOU
HAVE ME DO?
- YOUR FAMILY OWES ME THIS.
- NO NO.
YOU OWE ME THIS.
NO NO.
NO.
BABY GIRL,
LISTEN TO ME.
JUST LISTEN TO DADDY,
PLEASE.
PLEASE LISTEN TO ME.
LISTEN TO ME.
- LISTEN TO ME.
ANGELA!
YOU COULD JOIN HER.
WHAT?
SEE HER AGAIN.
WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
TAKE YOUR LIFE
AND SEE HER RIGHT NOW.
I KNOW HOW YOU FEEL.
AND I KNOW YOU DON'T BLAME
ME, BUT I HATE MY LIFE TOO.
I KNOW WHAT IT'S LIKE
TO FEEL ALONE.
YOU COULD SEE BETH
RIGHT NOW.
I KNOW.
I'll TAKE YOU FIRST.
WHAT DID YOU WRITE?
MY CONTACT INFORMATION.
SO WHAT DO WE DO?
I DON'T KNOW.
DO YOU, LIKE,
THROW IT IN?
YOU JUST LEAVE IT
IN THE WAVES.
LET'S THROW IT.
YOU WANT TO THROW IT?
AREN'T YOU GONNA
WATCH IT?
WE DON'T
WATCH IT.