(machinery clacking and whirring)
(whooshing electronic effects over ominous ambient tones)
(expressive, vaguely ominous piano and orchestral music)
(birds chirping)
- Hey.
- Finally, a chance to talk, just the girls.
- (snickers) Where are they?
- Where do you think, in the garage.
(chuckles) Don never gets tired of showing off.
This week, it's his new BMW.
- I knew it, you know?
- What?
- I just knew that you and Don would end up
in some ridiculously beautiful place like this.
- Oh, it's not that great.
- Yeah, you're breakin' my heart.
I could really get used to this.
- Oh, so it's time for the grass is always greener thing.
You're the one with the great marriage
and the two beautiful kids.
- Yeah, and the mortgage, two car payments,
and a stack of bills that never gets any smaller.
But look at you, you're incredible!
- (scoffs) Oh, please!
- When's the last time you had a worry?
- I worry.
- Oh, what about?
What am I gonna do if the maid doesn't show up?
- (laughs) No!
I, I have problems.
- Name one.
- Don.
- Don?
- Yeah, I mean he's great and everything, most of the time,
but, um, there's this little thing that,
well, it's not so little actually.
When he was playing baseball,
women would come out of the woodwork.
I mean, it was unbelievable, at hotels, in bars,
you wouldn't have believed it.
And then, all of the mail he got!
Christ, it was unbelievable.
These women would send him these sleazy Polaroids
of themselves with, like,
their boobs hangin' out and crotch shots,
and I would find this crap around the house,
you know, and just throw it out, but, it was gross!
Don's glory days, playing America's game.
- He's retired now, what's the problem?
- The problem is he got used to it.
Oh, hi, honey!
Hey, have you been in the garage this whole time?
- Yeah, Donnie was just showing me his new toy.
- Oh!
- Well, we should get going, huh, it's late, right?
- Late, c'mon, it's still early!
I know you still want a beer.
- Uh, sure, why not?
- Well, I guess I'll call Joanie and tell her we'll be late.
Again (scoffs).
(woman chuckling over ominous electronic music)
- [Don] There we go.
- Ah, thank you.
- You know it.
Man, I hate that shit.
- Hate what?
- The old lady, the way she barks at ya.
She treats you like you're a little kid or something,
like she's your mother, I don't get it.
- Eh, she wasn't really barking at me.
- She was barkin'.
- Well, sometimes, you gotta listen to what they say,
you know, it just comes with the territory.
You get used to it.
- No way, pal, some things I definitely do not get used to.
Eh, fuck it, c'mon, cheers, go!
(quietly tense and ominous orchestral music and piano)
(Don gasps)
(Tim coughing)
C'mon, c'mon, c'mon! (Tim gagging and laughing)
- [Tim] Hey, hey, hey, easy!
- (laughs) I can't take it!
- A long time!
- Check the rates unless you don't got it.
- Oh, that feels so good!
- Hey, take a lesson! - Don't stop!
- OK. (Wendy laughs)
- It's so hot out, let's go for a swim.
- Sounds great, go get your suit on.
- Yeah!
- You talkin' to me?
- No, I don't think so (scoffs).
- Why not?
- Well, it's late.
- C'mon, I'll open a bottle of champagne,
we'll all get loaded.
- Oh, that sounds great--
- Well, we didn't bring our suits.
- Look, we're practically family.
I'll let you in on a little secret,
I've seen her naked before.
- Great, thanks. (group chuckling)
- Well, I didn't tell you,
but Joanie's gotta be home by five.
She's got another gig, so I really should get going.
- C'mon, you sure?
- Yeah, she's right, we should get goin',
but thanks for the drinks. - C'mon, c'mon!
- [Wendy] We'll see you next time.
- Next time, all right. - Dude, you're killin' me!
- It's fine, let 'em go, honey.
(Don sighs)
(footsteps clacking)
- (sighs) I forgot the keys.
- Hurry up.
(distant traffic humming)
(quietly tense and mysterious electronic music)
(mysterious and tense electronic music with vocal choir)
(distant traffic whooshing)
(car horn beeps)
(mysterious and tense electronic music)
(distant traffic whooshing)
(car horn honking)
(tense and mysterious electronic music)
(distant traffic humming)
(car horn honking)
- What's wrong with you?
- Nothing.
- Nothing?
Well, you got this look on your face, I mean, acting like--
- Like what?
- Forget it.
- Did you see how much they drank?
- No, I didn't see how much they drank,
but I'm sure you did.
- She had five or six glasses of wine.
He had 10 beers in a matter of, what, two hours?
I think he has a problem.
- Wendy, it's the weekend for Christ's sake.
They're just havin' a little fun!
- Fun, I think they were totally inappropriate.
Can we go now?
(engine rumbling)
(rhythmic, mysterious electronic music with vocal choir)
- Tired?
- Yeah, a little.
- You know, you are so beautiful.
- Thanks, honey.
It's late, huh?
- Well, it's Friday.
We can sleep in (scoffs).
- Don't!
- (sighs) What's wrong with you?
- What, what'd I do?
- It's always something, isn't it?
It's either too late or the kids'll hear.
(expressive orchestral music)
(paper crinkling)
- Hey.
I'm sorry, Tim.
- It's nothing, just forget about it.
- I know you must think I'm a bitch sometimes, Tim, but
I worry about things.
I mean, I worry about everything, actually.
(Tim sighs)
- No, I don't think you're a bitch.
I worry, too.
- Come back to bed before long (chuckles).
I love you.
(lips smacking over expressive orchestral music)
- I love you, too.
- I'm sorry.
(expressive orchestral music and piano)
(expressive saxophone over pleasant ambient music)
(tennis ball clacking)
- Little out of shape there.
Looks like you're gettin' flabby.
- I got news for ya.
I've never been in shape.
- It only gets harder.
(Don grunts)
(Tim sighs)
Yes, that's what I'm talkin' about!
- Phew!
(Tim gasping over vaguely ominous electronic music)
All right, oh!
(Tim sighing heavily)
All right, so tell me, what's the secret?
- The secret, to what?
- A perfect life, man, the American Dream.
Seems like you've been living it.
- Yeah, I guess maybe I am.
- Well, it's obvious you've been
the big man for a long time.
- You know, sometimes I feel like that guy on late night TV.
You know, a shmuck that started out with nothing.
Now, he's got all the boats and women.
What the hell's his name?
- I have no idea who you're talking about.
- Tommy Vu, that's it.
Well, man, I got a couple of businesses,
some women, a beautiful blonde wife.
Maybe I should be on TV. (towel thwacking)
- Why not, you got everything else.
- Yep, come on, let's get outta here.
(Tim sighs)
(birds cawing over muffled chatter)
- Remember back in high school,
when you were a jock, big man on campus.
I remember all the girls used to pray
that you'd come walking down the hallway and look at them.
- You think so, huh?
- I know, I know so, I remember, Donnie.
Then what happens after high school?
You get drafted by the Baltimore Orioles.
- What, you think that's cool, minor league baseball?
I was fuckin' my ass over every bush league town there is,
like Bakersfield and Fresno, for what?
Two years later, I blow out my knee.
It ain't glamorous, Tim.
- But that blown-out knee got you a couple of hundred grand.
- Yes, and the end of a dream.
What's your point, I mean, were you jealous?
- No, I'm not jealous, I'm just saying
that you've had it easy, that's all.
- Right, but you have a kid.
- Donnie, I am busting my ass
just to try to keep my head above water.
- Well, you know what your problem is?
- No, I don't know what my problem is.
All right, tell me.
- You really wanna know?
- Yeah, I really wanna know!
- [Don] You play by the rules.
- [Tim] And there's a problem with that?
- When I traveled around the country, man,
I met a lotta guys like you, good guys.
Good guys with big dreams,
but you know what, they're like a buncha Boy Scouts.
You play by the rules.
I felt sorry for those guys.
You wanna know why?
Because at the end of the day, they had nothin'.
- You try raisin' two kids in LA these days, Donnie.
It's tough out there, man.
- [Don] Oh, come on, man, it's just an excuse.
It's tough everywhere!
- [Tim] All right, so what are you drivin' at?
- Come on.
You know, in everything, I can see the possibilities, right?
I have the money, I have the fancy cars.
Let me tell you something, Tim.
That's power, my friend, that is absolute power,
and it feels good, it feels real good.
- But we all can't be so lucky, Donnie.
- Luck's got nothin' to do with it, buddy,
and if you think it does, you're in big trouble.
Wanna know what success is?
- What?
- Not havin' to worry about the bullshit.
- Well, it sounds like a bunch
of Tony Robbins bullshit to me.
- See, there's your problem.
You're gonna end up like one of these bankers,
shuffling papers all day.
You get home, you give your wife a kiss,
she starts bitchin' at ya because your kid
didn't take the dog for a walk and it shit on the floor.
- Don't worry about me, Donnie.
- I care about ya, Tim.
I'm not worried, I just don't wanna see you
end up on some barstool,
talkin' over old war stories some day, that's all.
- Don't worry, Donnie, that's not me.
- I hope not, I really do.
(Tim sighs)
(engine revving over rhythmic electro rock music)
(engine rumbling over rhythmic electro rock music)
(rhythmic electro rock music)
(muffled chatter)
- Oh, man, whoa!
- [Don] Nice, huh?
- Nice ain't the word, good!
- Hey, c'mere, check this out.
More with that came from.
- Hey, you got padded walls?
(rhythmic electro rock music)
How, how do you do it?
- Gotta take a chance.
(Tim sighs)
Come on.
Come on!
- Tim, getcha anything?
- Yes, definitely, water.
- Come on, how 'bout a beer? (Tim sighs)
- A beer, are you kiddin' me, after that game?
- Hey, suit yourself, suit yourself.
(ice rattling in glass)
Did you think about what I said?
- Yeah, Donnie, but, you know, that's a lot to digest.
- (scoffs) You could do it, you could have all this.
- (sighs) I don't know, man. (birds chirping)
- See, that's your problem, Tim.
- What's the problem?
- You don't know.
You have to have confidence, man, you have to have a vision.
Just think about it (clears throat).
- Hey, you guys!
Hey, Tim, I didn't know you were comin' over.
- Yeah, Donnie and I just played a couple of sets.
- Oh, you did, who won?
- Well, I, no, he won.
- (laughs) Well, don't be such a stranger.
(footsteps clacking)
(mysterious, vaguely ominous orchestral music and piano)
- You like?
- Huh?
- Kim.
- Yeah, she, she looks good, Donnie, yeah.
- You know, um, (Tim clears his throat)
she likes to play.
- She what?
- (scoffs) She likes to play.
- That's great, Donnie, you know, that's good,
but I don't think that's any of my business.
- Yeah, I guess you're right, it's none of your business.
(mysterious, vaguely ominous piano and orchestral music)
C'mere for a second, I got somethin' I wanna show ya.
Clean, huh?
- Beautiful, fuckn' A, I'm in love (chuckles).
- Picked it up about a month ago.
(birds chirping)
Practically stole it, guess who I bought it from?
- Who?
- Ed McMahon.
- (scoffs) From The Tonight Show?
- Yep, Johnny Boy.
- [Tim] Come on, you're kiddin' me, right?
- No.
Why would I kid about somethin' like that, Tim?
I mean, if I was gonna lie to ya, Tim, don'tcha think
I'd come up with something better than Ed McMahon?
- I'm sorry, man, I didn't mean nothin' by it.
(distant traffic humming)
- Hey. (keys rattling)
Take 'em.
- What?
- Come on, take it for a ride!
- Nah, I-I couldn't take it. (tense orchestral music)
- Tim, I'm tellin' ya, it's yours for the weekend.
Come on, take Wendy, I don't know,
for a ride to the beach or--
- I couldn't take this, I just, I--
- Take the car!
- I don't know what to say, Donnie, it's--
- Don't say anything, Jesus Christ!
Will ya take the keys, have some fun for a change?
- All right, all right, all right, I'll take 'em,
but I owe you one.
(pleasant and expressive piano)
- Don't hurt yourself.
(birds chirping over dramatic, vaguely ominous piano)
Hey, Tim, put the key in, turn it, drive away.
- Yeah, yeah, I know, I know.
(birds chirping)
(dramatic, vaguely ominous piano)
(door rattling)
(rhythmic and dramatic rock music with expressive guitar)
- [Don] So how'd it feel
to open up that Beemer and just let it rip?
- It felt really cool, it was so great, man.
- [Don] Yeah, I know it.
- You know, and I felt like I was in control!
- That's what I wanna hear.
- Yeah, thank you so much, it was so cool.
- Hey, don't mention it.
I mean, we've been friends for, what, 20 years or something?
- 23, actually, class of '74,
although if I remember correctly,
we didn't really exactly hang out in the same circles.
- Eh, that's not what matters, I mean,
what matters is that we've known each other for a long time,
right, that's what makes good friends.
- Yeah, I know, I mean,
who would've thought it after all these years,
Don White and Tim Marsh hangin' out together again?
- You guys hidin' out here again?
- Hey, we're just doin' boy talk.
Nothin' you ladies would be interested in.
- Oh, oh no?
- Well, we're interested in a lot of things.
- You guys wouldn't have been talkin'
about women, now would ya?
- Us, women, what makes you say that?
- Because I know what men like.
- And that would be?
(birds chirping)
- Hey, take a lesson!
(slap thwacking)
(Tim chuckles)
(lips smacking)
- (chuckles) Sorry, I hope you don't mind.
It's just that sometimes, he is so irresistible.
- [Tim] No, I don't mind.
- So, did you bring your swimsuits?
- I brought mine.
- Oh, good, Tim, did you bring yours?
- (groans) I forgot.
- [Wendy And Kim] Tim!
- I don't know what I was thinkin'.
- Well, you don't need it anyway, let's just go in!
- No, no, that's, that's OK, you know what?
I'm just gonna take a little walk.
I'm feeling a little light-headed.
- OK, whatever.
- I'll go change.
- OK.
- [Don] Jesus, cleared them out pretty quick (scoffs).
(footsteps clacking over ominous piano and orchestral music)
(Tim scoffs)
(lips smacking over chirping birds)
(Wendy clears her throat)
(both women chuckling)
- Sorry, I didn't know you were, um--
- No, don't worry, you're not the first person to see us.
(women chuckle)
- Yeah, half the people in Mulholland
have seen us messin' around in this pool.
- I didn't see anything, really.
- No, honey, don't worry about it.
- Hey, I'm gonna go grab a bottle of Dom.
- Good idea.
- How's the water?
- It's good, you look great!
- Oh, please, I'd trade bodies with you anyday.
- What are you, kidding me?
You have a fantastic figure.
- Yeah, right, after two kids, you tell me then.
(both women laughing)
- Nice.
- Yeah, water's a lil, little nippy.
(vaguely ominous piano and guitar)
(knocking on door)
- What's happening?
- Hey, uh, just takin' a little break, that's all.
(door rattling)
Admiring the little shrine you built yourself down here.
- Those were some good ol' days, man!
- Yeah, seems like so long ago, though, huh.
- Yeah, it sure does. (Tim sighs)
Hey, now, you could still have a good time tonight.
- Yeah?
- Yeah, picture this.
The girls get drunk, right?
Out of nowhere, Wendy rips off her bikini.
- Are you shittin' me?
- Swear to God.
- She, fucker.
- Just jackin' your chain, bro.
You liked cruising around in that Beemer today, didn't you?
- Come on, who wouldn't?
- Yeah, you know, I have a whole lot of other toys
we could play with.
- What d'ya have in mind?
- You know what I have in mind, the big one.
The only one that counts.
- Which one is that?
- You know which one that is.
- No, I don't know which one.
- So tell me, Tim, what toy of mine
do you want more than anything in the world?
Be honest.
- C'mon, I've, I've already driven your Beemer.
What are you gonna do now, gimme the whole house (chuckles)?
- Mm, no.
- Now, look, you're confusing me here, just...
- I'm talking about Kim.
- Kim?
Come on, you're high, man!
- Well, well, maybe a little,
but I'm serious, man.
- Look, don't go startin' that again.
- You know, that's bullshit, man.
I see you lookin' at her.
- If I did, I didn't mean it.
I didn't mean anything by it, OK?
Look, if, if you're mad at me, I apologize.
I mean, I was drinking and shit, and I (sighs), oh, man.
Did I, did I, look,
did I make a fool out of myself up there or what?
- Tim, uh, I'm not mad.
She's yours.
- She's mine?
(scoffs) D-Donnie, this isn't makin' much sense.
- It makes perfect sense to me.
- No, it doesn't!
- You know, that's what I was talkin' about.
Being able to take a chance,
break a couple of rules once in a while.
You remember the talk we had the other day?
- Yeah, I remember our little talk.
What does it have to do with Kim?
- Everything!
You don't get it, do you?
- Look, look, Donnie, you're going too fast.
Just slow down a minute here, all right?
- You know, I like you, man, I like you a lot,
but you scare the shit outta me.
I mean, you're like a mouse!
You live in this little hole or something, I-I don't know.
You poke your head out, but you don't,
but you won't come out.
It's like you're afraid some cat's out there
that's just gonna rip your ass off
when you stick it out there.
I don't get that, how can you live that way?
I mean, you're never gonna come out of your hole.
- This is too much, Donnie.
- (scoffs) Too much, huh?
- Yeah, I can't sleep with Kim.
- Why not?
- Why not, eh, you're shitting me, right?
She's your wife, for Christ's sake!
Doesn't that bother you?
I mean, and not to mention the fact that I'm married.
I got two kids, I'm just supposed to throw
13 years of marriage out the window?
- I'm sorry, Tim, I, I just don't see it that way.
- No, well you should see it that way.
I mean, people don't just go around
offering their wives to other men.
(Don laughs)
(chuckles) Oh, no (laughs)!
Is this another one of your pranks?
- (gasping) N-no.
Tim, Kim and I, you know, we, we sort of see things
a little bit differently than other people.
I mean, if there's something we like, feels good, we do it.
We play by our rules, not theirs.
I mean, it's not like we're, you know,
waiting for, uh, the neighbors to invite us
to their Christmas dinners, if you know what I mean.
- (sighs) Donnie, she's your wife.
- Man, you don't get it, do you?
You remember those poor slobs
I told you about the other day?
How they ended up with nothing,
well that's right where you're headed, pal.
- Fuck you.
- Look, Tim, don't get me wrong, I love you, man.
It just scares the shit outta me
to think of you becoming like one of those guys.
You need to take a risk, Tim,
and it's time to get off the pot.
- And just throw 13 years of marriage right out the window?
- That doesn't have to happen.
- Donnie, that is the first thing that happens!
- It's not about gettin' caught,
it's about breakin' the rules, do you understand that?
It's about doin' something for yourself.
When was the last time you did something for yourself?
- That is the problem with you, Donnie, OK?
It's, it's always about you.
You don't understand, you've never learned
that there are consequences to your actions.
- (scoffs) OK, you know what,
obviously I've hit a raw nerve.
- You're damn right you did.
I mean, look, I may not have as much as you and Kim,
but I'm happy.
- So (feet thudding on floor)
still friends?
- Yeah, oh yeah, we're still buddies.
- Cool, head's up!
(sighs) I guess I'll go outside
and check on our little friends.
(baseball thwacking on bat)
(footsteps thunking)
(drawer rattling)
- What?
- [Don] Nothing.
- You think you're real funny, don't you?
- The hell's buggin' you?
- You don't even know, do you?
That's really the sad part, Don.
- No, all I know is I threw one damn good party tonight,
and you're all over my ass, I mean, I, I don't get it.
- [Kim] (laughs) One damn good party?
You practically slobbered all over Wendy!
- Honey, you're dreamin'.
- You like her, don't you?
- What the hell's that supposed to mean?
- [Kim] Admit it, you like her
and you can't control yourself!
- (scoffs) You know what, I'm outta here.
- [Kim] Where are you going?
- Watching TV.
- [Kim] I'm not through talking to you yet.
- Yeah, well, I've heard it all before.
- (sighs) Yeah, well, obviously it didn't sink in,
'cause you're still thinking with your dick!
- Yeah, and, um, you're still lovin' it.
- (scoffs) Oh, don't fuck with me, Don.
- Fine.
- You're afraid of me, aren't you?
A big tough guy like you, and you're afraid of me!
- Yeah, that's it, I'm petrified.
- [Kim] (laughs) I know, I can tell.
- Why do you think I'm afraid of you, Kim?
- Because I know what makes you tick,
and that scares you to death, doesn't it?
- You worry too much, baby.
- (sighs) Don't even try to fool me, Don, it won't work.
(footsteps thudding)
(Tim sighs)
(muffled chatter)
(expressive guitar and piano)
(footsteps clacking)
(knocking on door)
- Mr. Marsh?
(clears throat) Tim?
Tim?
- Oh, I'm sorry, Sharon, I didn't see you.
- Do you need me?
- What?
- (scoffs) Are you gonna need me this afternoon?
I'd like to leave early, I'm not feeling well.
- Uh, no, no, no, I don't need you.
- So it's fine for me to leave at three?
- Yeah, that's fine.
- Thanks. (papers rustling)
Have a nice weekend.
- You, too, Sharon.
(papers rustling and thwacking)
(muffled chatter)
(traffic humming)
- Boo!
- Oh, Jesus Christ, you scared me, Jimmy.
- Well, I'm sorry, Tim,
I guess I shouldn't go around scaring people like that.
- Nah, it's not your fault, Jimmy.
I'm just a little jumpy.
- Well, today's Friday, you know what that means, weekend!
Any plans?
- Huh?
- You plannin' on takin' the little lady anyplace special?
- No, probably just gonna rest and relax a little bit.
- (sighs) I'm takin' the wife to the Hollywood Bowl!
Jeez, do I love that place.
I mean, I'll do it up right, you know?
I mean, uh, uh, a little wine, a little cheese,
uh, maybe some good deli sandwiches.
- Really?
- Yeah, Mel Torme is playing.
(Jimmy warbles a tune)
(Jimmy laughs)
Oh, yeah, Betty and I just love him (sighs).
50 bucks for the tickets.
I mean, that's 50 bucks per ticket.
You ever seen him?
- No, I haven't.
- (groans) The man is something else, The Velvet Fog.
I mean, the guy has still got it!
- Sounds like quite an evening, Jimmy.
- Hey, Tim, you have a nice weekend, kay?
- Yeah, you, too.
(Jimmy crooning a tune)
(toy rattling to ground)
(door rattling)
- [Wendy] Is that you?
- [Tim] Yeah.
(Tim sighs)
- [Wendy] Dinner's almost ready.
- OK, I'm gonna go wash up.
- Want more wine?
- No, I'm fine.
- What's the matter, honey, you seem a little edgy tonight.
- Nothing's wrong, why?
- I don't know, you seem a little preoccupied.
- I'm just tired (groans),
work gets me down sometimes, that's all (sighs).
It's awfully quiet in here tonight, where are the kids?
- Oh, they had a very busy day and fell asleep
while they were watching cartoons (snickers).
It's me, isn't it?
I know with my new job and the kids
and everything around the house,
I haven't been paying any attention to you.
- No, honey, there's nothing wrong with you.
- I know, I mean (scoffs), I try,
but (sighs), it just doesn't seem
like we're having any fun anymore, honey.
You know, sometimes we go to sleep without even talking.
(scoffs) I worry about us.
- Don't worry.
- It's my fault, it's my fault
that we're not making love anymore, but I'm gonna change it.
- Oh, it's not your fault (sighs).
- God, you are so tight right there.
- Mm, yeah, that feels good.
- By the way, Don called.
- What'd he call about?
- Um, a party tonight, something about a new car dealership.
- What time?
- Eh, nine o'clock.
You know, we don't have to go.
(lips smacking over expressive piano)
Mm, remember when we used to just stay in the house
and do this for days and never come out (giggles)?
- (lips smacking) I miss that.
- Me, too, we don't have to go out, you know?
(lips smacking)
- No, I have to go.
It's Donnie's big night, you know?
He's been talking about this deal for months.
- OK, well, make an appropriate excuse
for me, would you (laughs)?
- Like, uh, you're not feeling well?
- That's good (laughs).
(lips smacking)
- I love you.
- I love you, too.
(lips smacking over expressive guitar and piano)
(expressive guitar and piano)
(lips smacking over passionate moaning)
- [Ashley] Daddy, can I have a drink of water?
- Your turn (giggles). - My turn.
- (lips smacking) I'll be right there, Ashley (groans)!
- [Ashley] When?
- In a minute (chuckles).
(lips smacking)
- You better get your butt up there
or she's gonna be sleeping in our bed tonight.
- (lips smacking) I know.
(lips smacking)
- I'll wait for you.
- OK (lips smacking).
Coming, Ashley (grunts)!
(shower hissing)
(vaguely ominous orchestral music and guitar)
(footsteps clacking)
- I'm not sure what happened, but I'll look into it
for you if you want me to, you liking the party?
- Oh, it's, uh--
- Hey!
- Hey, hey, thanks for stoppin' by.
Hey, Tim, thanks for comin'.
- Congratulations, Don.
- Hey, save it till after the dealership
lasts at least a year, all right?
- Come on, Donnie, it's you, you're gonna do great!
- Eh, you're right, yeah, one sec.
Hey, where's your drink?
- That's my next stop.
- [Don] Go for it, talk to ya in a few.
- You got it.
(muffled chatter)
Hi, Kim!
- How are you? (footsteps clacking)
Oh, woo-woo-woo-woo (laughs)!
Mm, good to see you, thanks for coming!
- I wouldn't have missed this for anything,
and you look (rolls tongue), you look great!
- (laughs) Well, thanks, so where's Wendy?
- Oh, she wasn't feeling very good, so, um,
I'm kind of on my own tonight.
- Oh, well, maybe next time.
Shoot, oh my gosh, new shoes.
- [Tim] Mm-hmm.
- Well, and I have been drinking since seven,
so you'll have to bear with me.
- I guess I got a little catching up to do then, huh?
- Yeah-yeah, go catch up, and I'm gonna go,
uh, boss around the help.
(footsteps clacking over muffled chatter)
- The way I see it, there are no limits, I mean none.
We got LA, we got the Valley,
we got Orange County, there is no reason,
I mean no reason why we shouldn't move
at least 2000 units a month, at least.
We're gonna own this town, you guys stick with me.
I'll be back in a second.
(expressive soft rock music)
Phew (sighs)!
Man, this is one helluva party, huh, damn!
(Don sighs)
You're mad at me?
- No, I am not mad at you.
- I can tell.
Because of what I said the other night?
- Look, forget it, I don't even remember
what we were talkin' about.
- Look, man, I just brought all that stuff up about Kim,
I was just tryin' to help, that's all.
- Look, it's water under the bridge, OK, forget it.
- Boy (sighs), I don't know, she still likes ya.
- Look, I'm married, Donnie.
- (scoffs) So, hey.
You know, I was thinking about what you said the other day
about, uh, gettin' caught.
I don't know, man, I just,
I don't think it has to happen like that.
- It always happens like that.
- Oh, man.
Damn, look at her.
Damn, she's hot!
(Don scoffs)
I mean, you like her, don'tcha?
- Yes, she's very pretty.
- That's right, very beautiful,
and you could be with her tonight.
Nobody, man, would ever know.
- The bullshit never stops, does it?
- Man, you just, look,
you just do her in the middle of the night!
I mean, you've done that with your wife, right?
You're loaded, she's drunk, half asleep.
Look, you don't, doesn't matter who you're bangin',
just as long as you're bangin', right (chuckles)?
Could be you, that could be you.
Shit, man, you could sleep with Kim tonight.
She'd probably just think it was me anyway.
You know, man, you haven't changed a bit.
I mean, Christ, you're still afraid of gettin' caught!
- (sighs) I am not afraid of getting caught, Donnie.
- You are afraid of getting caught.
You're afraid of anything that's the least bit different.
- Look, why don't you just leave this alone.
- You're blowin' it, man, big time!
- Yeah, I'm blowin' it, and you know what?
You're drunk, and this is startin' to sound
like some bad night from the '60s.
- Whatever, just don't come moaning to me
asking about the Great American Dream,
because I am the Great American Dream.
(Don sighs)
(muffled chatter and laughing over pleasant soft rock music)
- Ah!
(footsteps thunking)
(muffled chatter over pleasant soft rock music)
- Oh!
Thank you (laughs).
- Tim, are you having fun yet?
- I'm having a great time, this is a great party.
- Oh, good, I'm so glad!
You know, I'm really glad you and Don
kept up after all these years.
I think you'll be good for him.
- I don't think Donnie needs much help.
- Oh, yes he does (chuckles).
Besides, you're different.
- What do you mean?
- Oh, I mean from Don and all of his friends,
you're, you're quiet and you don't brag all the time.
(laughs) I like that in a man.
(both chuckling)
- Well, Donnie's got a lot to brag about.
- Well, he thinks he does anyway (chuckles).
But why are we talkin' about Don?
- I don't know!
- You must get sick of it, Don this, Don that.
Everyone's always talkin' about him,
and here I am making a fool out of myself talking about--
- [Both] Don (laughing).
- So, um, ya'll have two kids.
- Yeah, yeah, Ashley is six and,
and Ricky's four.
- Ricky's four, wow, (gasps) how sweet!
- Yeah, he's four all right.
Oh (laughs)! (Tim chuckles)
Well, Don and I don't have any kids, obviously,
but I'm thinkin', I'm thinkin' we might.
I don't know, we haven't been married that long.
How long have we been married?
Oh, it's just been over a year.
- Let me tell you, kids change everything (chuckles).
- That's what I've heard.
(Kim sighs)
- (snickers) What?
- Ah, I was just thinking.
- About?
- About you.
- About me?
- Yeah, I was just thinking
what it would've been like if I met you before I met Don.
(Tim scoffs)
- Mrs. White, you have a phone call.
- Oh, OK, I'll be right there.
(pleasant soft rock music with expressive saxophone)
I'll see you later.
(muffled chatter over pleasant soft rock music)
(footsteps clacking)
Now, uh, now my husband's having this party, though,
and it's, like, drivin' me crazy.
(laughs) I know, I know, you should see some of his friends.
Oh, there's this one guy, though, who's really cute.
(footsteps clacking)
(ice rattling in glass)
I'll call you back.
(phone rattling)
(door rattling)
Tim, come in, come on over and have a seat.
- How are ya?
- I'm good, I'm glad you came in here.
You know, um, I'm a little drunk (snickers),
but, uh, I think you're really cute.
- Uh, thank you. (Kim laughing)
- You seem like a really sweet guy.
(lips smacking)
(door creaking)
(slap cracking)
(Tim groans)
- I'm sorry.
- Really, I, I just, I--
- Just don't.
(ice rattling in glass)
- So what you guys have to realize
is it doesn't just happen, you've gotta make it happen.
You gotta get out there and, hey, buddy, how's it goin'?
- Good, Donnie, good, hey, good party, man.
- Ah, thanks, thanks, look,
we're goin' down to the Century Club for a nightcap.
Come with us.
- Nah, nah, I'm a little tired,
and had a couple of drinks, I gotta drive, so.
- Come on, just one!
- Nah, I think I'm just gonna call it a night, Donnie.
All right, thanks, good party, you guys take care.
- Just one!
Well, so anyway.
(crickets chirping over ominous orchestral music)
(engine rumbling over ominous orchestral music)
(ominous, vaguely eerie orchestral music)
(phone ringing)
- Hello?
- [Kim] Are you coming over?
- What do you mean?
- [Kim] To finish what you started.
(ominous, vaguely eerie orchestral music)
- I think you have the wrong number.
(phone rattling)
(ominous, vaguely eerie orchestral music)
(faucet hissing)
(ominous and eerie orchestral music)
(tense cymbal accent)
(door creaking)
(eerie orchestral music with tense percussion accents)
(eerie and tense orchestral music and piano)
(door rattling)
(eerie and tense orchestral music)
(rhythmic and expressive orchestral music)
(expressive guitar and orchestral music)
(blower whirring)
(birds chirping over rumbling engine)
(muffled birds chirping)
(phone ringing)
- Mm, let it ring, it's early.
- (sighs) I can't sleep, I'll get it.
Hello, yeah.
No, no problem, no, I wasn't sleeping.
What, you're kidding! (sheets rustling)
Oh, Jesus Christ, yeah, yeah, I'll be right over.
- Who was it? (tense orchestral music)
What's the matter, what happened?
- It was Donnie, there's been an accident.
- Is he OK?
- It's Kim.
- Is she all right?
- [Tim] I don't know.
- Well, what did Don say?
- He said something bad happened to Kim.
(sighs) I'm gonna go over there.
(ominous and tense orchestral music)
(camera shutter snapping over ominous orchestral music)
(ominous orchestral music with eerie strings)
- [Jack] Whatta you got?
- Looks like her old man found her,
uh, at around six o'clock in the morning.
The actual 911 call came in at, uh, 6:17.
Someone must've slashed her throat
and beat the hell out of her with some sort of club.
What a mess.
- Who is she?
- Uh, she is a Kimberly White, 27 years old.
Uh, we haven't checked everything out,
but it doesn't look like we're seeing any forced entry here,
and the security company has no report
of the alarm being triggered.
- Well, where's he?
- He's in the kitchen right now talkin' to Wilshire.
He's pretty shaken up.
- Kay, I'm gonna take a look around,
then go talk to him.
- OK, Lutack, let's go check out the perimeter.
(dramatic orchestral music)
- So you found your wife?
- (sighs) Yeah.
- About what time was that?
- (sighs) Six, 6:15, I, I don't know.
- [Jack] Is that your usual time getting home?
- No.
No, actually I took some sales reps
out for a celebration last night.
- Sales reps?
- Yeah, I own a car dealership.
We, uh, had a little party here,
and then afterwards, went out for a few drinks.
- Well, I'll have to get their names before I leave today.
You can leave them with the sergeant.
Your wife, uh, she stayed at home?
- Yeah.
She said she was tired, and just wanted to go
up into the bed, go to bed.
- And you found her when you got home?
- Yeah.
- I'm sorry.
Did you touch anything in the room, anything around the bed?
- Probably, I, I saw her laying there on the bed,
and I raced over to the phone, I called 911.
I'm sure I did touch something.
- Is there an alarm in the house?
- Yeah.
- Well, our guys report no sign of forced entry
and Westec doesn't have any calls for a break-in.
- Maybe she just forgot to put it on.
- What time was it you said
you took your sales reps out last night?
- I don't know, it had to be around one o'clock.
The party was ending here, we went out for a nightcap, damn!
- And nothing's missing?
- I don't know, I (sighs), I don't think so.
- How long were you married?
- About two years.
- Did your wife have any enemies that you know about?
Old jealous boyfriend--
- No, no, nothin' like that.
- Well, I really appreciate you
taking the time out to talk to me.
Call me, whatever time of night,
if you wanna talk about anything, call.
- [Don] Sure.
(Don sighs)
(traffic humming over tense and dramatic orchestral music)
(engine rumbles to a stop)
- [Tim] Donnie, what's goin' on, where's Kim?
What happened?
- It's bad, man.
I got home last night about 5:30,
(sniveling) there was blood everywhere.
Somebody beat the shit outta Kim.
(ominous and tense orchestral music)
I, I didn't know what to do (panting).
Christ, why did I go out last night, man,
I should've just fuckin' stayed here!
(panting) God!
- Donnie, I was here.
I was with Kim last night.
(Don panting)
- What?
- I am so sorry, Donnie.
- What are saying?
Son of a bitch, you killed her!
- [Tim] No, no, I didn't hurt her!
- Don't you lie to me, you killed my angel!
- Donnie, I made love to her, I didn't kill her.
I would never hurt Kim.
You were the one who kept talkin' about it!
You told me to do it, I mean, you told me to sleep with her!
- What (gasping)?
You were here last night!
(both panting over dramatic orchestral music)
Whoa, no, they're gonna think you did it!
What, Christ, man, what are we gonna tell the cops?
What are you gonna tell 'em, they're never gonna believe us!
- Donnie, you gotta, you gotta tell 'em the truth!
- The truth?
Ah, oh (gasping)!
- Look, Donnie,
what I did last night was stupid.
I would never hurt Kim. (Don gasping)
I would never hurt Kim!
(both gasping over dramatic orchestral music)
- Hey, did you talk to the husband yet?
- Yeah.
He was, uh, gone from one in the morning until he found her.
- Read it.
The lab recovered semen from vaginal tissues.
- So?
- So the husband says he leaves at one with his buddies.
He comes home at six, he finds her dead.
When does he do her?
- Are you kidding me (scoffs)?
(scoffs) It was a party, he takes her upstairs
to the bedroom, slips her dress off,
mumbles something dirty in her ear,
and they do the nasty while the party's going on.
It happens all the time.
- I don't think so.
- Oh, so you're an expert on marriage now?
- Listen, wise guy, the lab said that the semen
had been there less than three hours,
meaning it couldn't be the husband's.
- Well, that's just an estimate.
There's no way to pinpoint that.
- You know what I'm thinkin'?
(scoffs) I'm thinkin' there was someone else.
Someone between the time he left
and the time he finds her dead.
- Test out the theory.
- Meaning what?
- Meaning check it out, bring Mr. White downtown,
make he pee in a Dixie cup.
And then, if the semen doesn't match, you've got a lead.
Otherwise, you're just blowin' smoke.
- There's not enough probable cause for that.
- Hey, ask him.
If he's got nothin' to hide, he'll consent.
- OK, I'll see ya later.
- So you didn't tell 'em?
- I couldn't!
- Why not?
- And say what?
By the way, Lieutenant, when I left the party,
my best friend slept with my wife,
and then I came home and found her dead?
- You said you were gonna tell 'em the truth, Donnie.
- [Don] I did.
- Don,
hi.
- [Don] Hi.
- How ya doin', honey?
- I'm all right, thanks.
- Call me if you need anything, OK?
- Yeah.
(footsteps clacking)
So how much does she know?
- Nothing.
I'm not gonna blow my marriage
over a one night stand, Donnie.
- She's gonna find out sooner or later.
(sighs) Oh, man, I gotta get outta here.
- I mean, Donnie, what do I do?
- Look, you can't go to the cops.
If you tell 'em that you and Kim were together that night,
they're never gonna believe it, man.
They're gonna think you did it.
You gotta keep your mouth shut
and pray like hell they catch the guy.
- (sighs) And that's it?
- That's it. (Tim sighs)
Hey, come on, just stay tough, all right?
Just, right? - Yeah.
(Tim sighs heavily)
(footsteps thudding over muffled chatter)
- [Officer] Lieutenant Matthews?
- Yeah.
- [Officer] We got your results.
- Thanks.
(footsteps thudding over muffled chatter)
(paper crinkling)
- So, it doesn't match?
- Nope, you were right.
- (snickers) Incredible.
- Shit just keeps getting deeper and deeper.
We know that the that night Kim White died, she had sex.
The lab found three ccs of semen.
Only problem, it wasn't her husband's.
- So he had a secret lover.
I mean, that's what I've been saying all along!
- So the second guy's the one that cut her?
- Well, look, Don White volunteered to give the sample.
He was totally cooperative.
I'm beginning to think he's in the clear.
- Oh, you think so?
- Well, why not?
I mean, he didn't object to the semen testing,
and he certainly didn't act suspicious.
You find the guy who did her, you find the guy who cut her.
- No, I'm thinkin' just the opposite.
You find the guy that didn't do her,
and you found the guy that cut her.
- You mean her husband?
- Well think about it,
she's got a boyfriend, someone she sees regular.
The husband goes out with his pals,
she calls the boyfriend over for a quickie.
He comes over, they fool around,
and as the boyfriend's leaving, the husband sees him.
He flies into a rage.
- So why not just pull another OJ and,
and, uh, kill the boyfriend or kill them both.
- Nah, this is a rage killing, he was mad at her.
- So there's someone out there who knows a whole lot
about what happened prior to the murder.
- Yep, and he's probably afraid to come forward.
(Liz sighs)
What was the time of death?
- Between five and six.
- And what time did the husband leave the club?
- (sighs) Somewhere around five,
but they were in Century City.
That's like 10 minutes through the hills.
- He had time to do her.
And we know that the guy who was screwin' her
had time to do her (sighs).
- Man, now what are we gonna do?
- [Jack] So things were fine?
- I've told you guys.
We had a good marriage.
Sure, we had our problems.
- Look, this isn't easy, but I need to ask.
Is your wife having an affair?
- That's ridiculous.
- You're sure?
- Absolutely, Kim loved me.
- There was no one else?
- You know, you got one helluva nerve
comin' in here and crappin' all over my wife's reputation.
- (scoffs) Look, I don't care what your wife
did or didn't do, I'm here to solve a murder.
- Yeah, well, it looks like you're goin' about it
in a pretty half-assed way.
- You live in a big fantasy world here, don't you, Don?
With the big pool, the fancy cars, the parties.
- I live well, what's your point?
- Your wife was seeing someone, we know that for a fact.
- There's physical evidence, Mr. White.
- It's garbage.
- Garbage (scoffs)?
I hate to rain on your parade, pal,
but the night your wife died,
she died full of semen, and you know what?
It wasn't yours.
- We've done all the tests.
Do you, um, have any idea who she was seeing?
- I don't know.
- Think harder.
- I said I don't know.
(Don clears his throat)
(chair rattling on floor)
You know your way out.
(blower humming over ominous orchestral music)
- How you doin'?
- Well, good.
- Pretty hot out today, huh?
- That's when I start real earning.
- You work out here on, uh, Saturdays?
- Oh, yes, every day I work.
Lots of property to take care of.
- Yeah, what time do you usually start?
- When the sun comes up, uh, five, six in the morning.
- Yeah, did you get that.
- Yeah.
- Um, do you remember anything unusual about last Saturday?
- Saturday?
- [Jack] The day when all the police came.
- No, nothing, I just remember the police.
- Any unusual noises, no screams, anything at all?
- No, nothing like that.
- How 'bout any, uh, strange vehicles you hadn't seen
in the neighborhood or in the driveway next door?
- Um, yeah, there was a blue utility vehicle
parked in the driveway when I first got to the house,
then I went inside to get my tools,
and then it was gone.
- Did you see who was driving?
- No, I'm sorry, I was inside.
- Huh, eh, you know what kind of car Mr. White,
your next door neighbor, drives?
- Oh, sure, everybody knows his Porsche.
It's a real nice car.
- Yeah, you didn't happen to see it
around that Saturday, did ya?
- No, not the Porsche, just that blue utility vehicle.
- OK, well, hey, you've been a big help.
Thanks a lot.
- OK.
- [Jack] Try to stay cool.
- Heh, thank you (chuckles).
- Nice, thank you.
(dramatic orchestral music)
(engine rumbles to life)
(engine rumbling over dramatic orchestral music and piano)
(ominous and eerie orchestral music)
(traffic humming)
- [Jack] You don't own a utility vehicle, do ya?
- No.
- But you do own a car dealership?
- I sell foreign cars, I don't sell trucks.
- Do you know a friend of your wife
who drives one of these utility vehicles?
- Tim.
- Tim?
- [Don] Tim Marsh.
- Who is he?
- He's just an old friend from high school.
- What's he do?
- He is an accountant.
- Did he know your wife?
- Of course, came over all the time.
They were good friends.
- How good, lovers maybe?
- (scoffs) No.
- Was he at the party that night?
- Yes, yes, he was at the party.
- Did he go with you to the Century Club after the party?
- Nope, he went home.
- With his wife?
- She didn't come to the party, no.
- Look, I'm gonna ask you this once.
Is your wife having an affair with Tim Marsh?
- (scoffs) No.
(water bubbling over chirping birds)
- Hi.
- Morning!
(birds chirping)
- I thought I heard you leave with the kids.
- I did, dropped 'em off at school.
Had a parent-teacher conference, came back, ate breakfast,
all before you even opened your eyes.
- I need to talk.
- Sure, is something wrong?
- It's about Kim and everything that's happened
the last few days.
- Yeah, I know.
God, poor Don, I feel so bad for him.
It must be hard.
I mean, you always hear about these things
happening to other people,
and then when it happens to somebody close to you,
it just, I now just realized how lucky we are.
- It's still hard to believe.
- You look tired, honey.
- I am so sorry.
- It's not your fault.
- Dammit!
- What is it, what's the matter?
(Tim sighs heavily)
- I was with her.
- With who, what are you talking about?
- Kim.
I was with her the night she died.
- Uh, what do you mean, with?
- I slept with her.
- You slept with her.
- Kim, I slept with Kim.
- With Kim, you slept with Kim White?
- I am so sorry.
- Oh, you're sorry?
Is that supposed to make it all better now,
that you're sorry?
God, Tim, you're pathetic!
What's the matter with you?
You stupid bastard! (slap thwacking)
Get out of my house!
- I'm sorry, I didn't mean it!
I never wanted to hurt you!
- Well, good, then you should've thought about that
before you cheated on me and slept with someone!
- I made a mistake!
(gasps) I never loved her, I loved you!
You, you need to know that!
- Loved me, is that why you slept with my friend?
Because you love me?
How many times, Tim, once, twice, what?
- Is was one time, I was drunk.
Can't you forgive me?
- 13 years of marriage, Tim, and our kids,
what am I supposed to tell them now?
Huh, Daddy fucked someone, but he's sorry now,
and he loves us!
Fuck you!
- Honey (panting), you're my life!
You're all I got (panting)!
I can't go on without you!
- Get out of my sight.
- Oh, Wendy--
- Get out, you're making me sick!
- God, what did I do?
- Get out!
- Wendy?
- Get out.
(Wendy whimpering)
(traffic humming)
- [Liz] So you went home after the party?
- That's right.
- About what time was that?
- Around one.
- Your wife was asleep when you got home, wasn't she?
- Yeah.
- It's not good, my friend.
- DMV says you drive a '93 utility vehicle.
- That's right.
- [Liz] And you're a friend of Don White's?
- Yes, I've known Donnie since high school.
- And his wife?
- I knew Kim.
- How well?
- She was married to my best friend.
- You know, there's a little something tellin' me
that you knew her real well.
- What do you mean?
- Well, I got a little voice inside me that says
that you liked her so well that you wanted to screw her.
- That's crazy, I told you,
she was married to my best friend!
- Hey, it happens all the time.
- You don't have any evidence.
- Mm, we have an eyewitness.
He saw your car there the morning of the murder.
- I suggest you start telling the truth.
I've got enough right now to get a court order
to get a little sample of that precious little sperm,
and if it matches, I'm gonna nail your ass to the wall.
- Jesus Christ (sighs)!
- What happened?
- We had sex that night,
me and Kim, it was the first time.
- And you got excited and you wanted more,
so she said no and you hit her.
- No, that's not what happened.
- OK.
Tell me what it was like then.
- (sighs) We were flirting at the party.
We were drunk and,
after I went home, she called and she said
she was leaving the back door open
and that I should come over.
- She was a good-looking woman.
I can understand.
- So you went over.
- I was nervous, and I felt guilty, but Donnie,
I mean, he's the one who arranged it.
- Arranged what?
- He's the one who said I should sleep with his wife.
He said, he was playing all these weird mind games with me.
- He said that you should sleep with his wife?
- I know it sounds bizarre, but it's the truth.
He wanted me to take more risks,
he said my life was boring.
- So he wanted you to sleep with his wife?
Hell, man, I've got friends who think I'm timid,
but they don't let me go fucking their wife, though.
- He dared me to.
He let me use his cars,
let me use his house,
and he offered me Kim.
(dramatic piano and orchestral music)
I didn't kill her.
- You'll have to do better than that.
(tense and ominous orchestral music)
(Jack sighs)
- So, what do you think?
- I think he's full of shit.
Take him downtown, get a statement.
I'm gonna go get a warrant and tear this place apart.
(dramatic and ominous orchestral music)
(door rattling)
(distant traffic whooshing over ominous orchestral music)
- Hey, Lieutenant?
Lieutenant, I think we got something here.
- What do you got?
- I don't know, it looks like a club or something
wedged in there pretty tight.
Doesn't look like it belongs.
You want me to pull this out?
- Yeah.
(dramatic and ominous piano and orchestral music)
(increasingly ominous and tense orchestration)
Jesus Christ, let's go, inside.
- Sir?
- We got our man. (tense orchestral accent)
Gimme your hand, let's go.
You have the right to remain silent.
Anything you say can and will be used
against you in a court of law.
(dramatic and ominous orchestral music)
- They matched.
Lab found Marsh's prints on the bat.
- So we have the murder weapon and an eyewitness.
Son of a bitch is gonna fry.
What's bothering you?
(dramatic piano and orchestral music)
- Nothing.
- Aw, come on, I know you're thinking something there.
- Just a couple things bugging me.
- Like what?
- Don White, he took out
a life insurance policy on his wife.
- [Jack] So?
- It was three months before the murder.
- You got anything more?
- Just bothers me, that's all.
- Well, hey, I mean lots of people
take life insurance out on their spouses.
- It's for two million bucks, Jack.
- Hey, the Whites had the money, so why not?
Besides, it's a slam dunk, am I missing something?
- I don't know.
- Look, we've got the murder weapon with his fingerprints,
we have his semen, and he's admitted to banging her.
So what am I missing?
- Right.
Nothing.
- There's something still bothering you.
- No.
- No, you sure?
- Yep.
- Well, let's go get somethin' to eat.
Come on.
(dramatic and ominous orchestral music)
(birds chirping)
(knocking on door)
- Hi, I'm not interrupting anything, am I?
- No, not at all, come on in.
- Thanks.
(sighs) Everything's gonna be fine.
- Are you OK?
- Yeah, I'm holdin' up.
Oh.
(door rattling)
(rhythmic, vaguely unsettling electronic music)
(tense orchestral accent)
(traffic humming)
- [Jack] What's up?
- [Liz] Nothin'.
- [Jack] Come on, I've been a cop for 17 years,
I know when something's bothering you.
- [Liz] It's the Marsh case.
- [Jack] What about it?
- Just, I just can't get it out of my system.
I mean, like the murder weapon.
Why not destroy it, why bury it in your backyard?
- Who knows, Marsh wasn't a brain surgeon.
(traffic humming)
You got anything new?
- Yeah, I talked with the insurance agent.
He sold the Whites their life insurance policy.
He said they were having all sorts of financial problems.
- Like what?
- Everything, the house in the hills
is mortgaged to the hilt,
the car dealerships are running huge losses.
(scoffs) Mr. Donald White was living a lie.
- Doesn't look good, but it doesn't prove anything.
Hell, lots of people in this town live on plastic.
- Yeah, but there's something else.
- What?
- Well, I went up to Soledad last week.
Just wanted to talk to Tim Marsh.
He told me the strangest thing.
He said his wife had dropped the kids off
at his mother's three weeks ago.
She said she needed a few day's rest.
(scoffs) Guess what?
She hasn't been seen or heard from since.
She's just disappeared.
- You're shitting me.
- No.
(traffic humming over tense orchestral music)
(dramatic, vaguely unsettling orchestral music)
(rhythmic percussion)
(eerie strings over rhythmic and murky ambient music)