Mustafar.
From its fiery depths I rose
just as my new castle rises
as the ultimate testimony
to the awesome power of the dark side!
So... What do you think?
A little on the nose
is what I think.
I mean, you can say evil fortress
on the hill without saying it, you know?
Look at this place,
you could really
use something, anything...
A chair, perhaps.
Anywho, no time to sit around.
We've got a galaxy to conquer.
-Master!
-Gah! Who is that? Who are you?
Vaneé is but the humble servant
to Darth Vader, Lord of the Sith.
I've prepared your bath, master.
Conquer now, tubby time later. Let's go.
- But my castle...
- Fine.
You. Darth Hideous.
Keep an eye on the place.
It would be
Vaneé's honor to serve...
What are you, the last five guys
in the galaxy to get the news?
The First Order is destroyed.
The war is over. You lost! Go home!
Okay, suit yourself.
I'm not scared of these bucketheads!
Watch this!
Like taking candy
from a baby porg.
Now let's go home!
Don't be such a worry wampa! I got this.
Okay, still got this.
I just need to make an emergency landing
on that bright red lava planet.
I got this, I got this,
I got this.
See? Told ya, I got this.
We'll just call for help and...
Comm's dead. Hmm.
Okay, no biggie.
Come on. Let's go find some help.
I was not showing off!
That TIE got off a lucky shot!
Oh, I bet we can find help there!
Okay, you can stay here alone...
In these dark, creepy woods.
That's what I thought.
What is this place?
-Hello? Excuse me?
-Gah!
Don't sneak up on a guy
like that, will you?
I got a condition, you know?
Oh, sorry. What are you buildin' here?
Castle Vader!
The galaxy's first all-inclusive,
Sith-inspired luxury theme resort.
A place for fun-lovin', free-spending
families from across the galaxy
to finally indulge
in their inner dark side!
What do you think?
You're building a hotel.
-In Darth Vader's old castle.
-Mmm-hmm.
No offense, but that sounds
like a really bad idea, Mr... um...
Graballa! The Hutt!
Legendary entrepreneur?
Real estate tycoon?
Um...
Cousin of the late Jabba,
may he rest in peace.
And you are who exactly?
Poe Dameron.
Poe Dameron!
The fearless pilot
who destroyed Starkiller Base
and led the Resistance on Exegol?
I mean,
a lot of folks helped... But, uh, yes.
It is an honor, General.
Please, allow me to give you a tour.
Raam, Baash...
Help the gentleman with his luggage.
Oh, no, no, that's not my lugg... Okay.
We've been working around the clock
and I've spared no expense.
Castle Vader is gonna be class
all the way.
Lava fountain. We got one.
So... My X-wing took some damage
back there and...
And wait'll you see the lobby!
General, are you familiar
with the term, "celebrity endorsement"?
A stranger enters.
Could they finally be the one
to fulfill the Prophecy of Mustafar?
A fearless pilot arrives
with the strength to unlock
the treasures of my master's castle?
Perhaps...
The troopers set the mood
the second you walk in.
And I got 'em all.
Storm, shore, scout, snow, death...
Even my own creation, the skelo-trooper.
Feel the power of the dark side...
Of the dark side... Of the dark side...
Of the dark side...
Ow! I'll show you a dark side!
Um, excuse me, Mr. The Hutt?
I might be able to fix it.
I highly doubt that.
All right, go ahead, kid.
So, what do you say? Ready to be
Castle Vader's official S-Poe-ksman?
You see what I did with your name there?
I put the Poe in spokesman!
Feel the power of the dark side...
at the Empire Emporium! Now open.
-Oh, you've got skills, kid.
-Thank you, sir, I...
Hey! You... You're...
Hi. Poe Dameron. What's your name?
I'm Dean! I can't believe
I'm meeting the Poe Dameron!
You're the best pilot in the galaxy!
Oh, I don't know about "best."
Maybe top three. Or two.
You're pretty good with those tools.
I could use some help fixing my X-wing.
Me, fix your X-wing? I'd be honored!
I wanna be a pilot too someday,
and you know...
The grown-ups are talking.
So, it looks like we each
have something the other wants.
So I'll make you a deal.
You record a holovid for Castle Vader,
and I'll have the kid fix your X-wing.
After my X-wing is running.
You're not the first Hutt I've dealt with.
-Come on, kid.
-No!
The fearless pilot mustn't leave.
Vaneé! What've I told you
about sneaking up on people?
Sorry. He came with the place.
Sort of a creepy caretaker.
Emphasis on "creepy." Just ignore him.
Hmm...
- Uh, that's kinda tough.
- Hmm...
Okay, Vaneé.
We've talked about sniffing the guests.
Boys...
But Vaneé has something
to show the brave pilot.
Some other time. We're kind of in a rush.
NI-L8, show them.
Behold, The Helmet of Ren!
Did you say Ren? As in Kylo?
This helmet belonged
to the one who helped create him.
Would you like to hear its tale?
The man said he's in a rush!
Tell me.
This is the tale of a powerful warrior
who longed for more...
Excellent, Ben.
This is such
a waste of time, Uncle Luke.
I'm so much stronger than all of them.
Patience. There are no shortcuts
to becoming a Jedi.
How is this lame rock-stacking
gonna make me a great Jedi?
I sense your frustration, nephew.
Really? Wow!
Did you use the Force to sense that?
He'll be fine, R2.
He just has more to learn.
Master Skywalker! I think I did it!
Oh! Ow!
Every time with you, Cozler!
- "No shortcuts to becoming a Jedi."
- Hey!
How long did he train on Dagobah?
Like, 20 minutes?
The Knights of Ren are coming!
Be afraid! Be very afraid!
Knights of Ren, feast on their fear!
Take all that you want!
See you around, kid. Let's roll!
Join us, Ben.
Solo... Join us, Ben.
Don't listen to him, Ben.
Stay out of it, Skywalker!
Power is yours for the taking, Solo.
We're doing dream sequences now?
Sorry to interrupt, son,
Mom and I were wondering
if you're coming homing for dinner...
Chewie made your favorite.
Roast Tip-Yip in Bantha sauce.
Join us, Ben.
Stay on the path, Ben.
Solo...
Solo... Solo... Solo.
You aren't Jedi. Are you Sith?
The Knights of Ren live by our own code.
Use our power to take what we want.
You have skills.
Yet you follow that fossil Skywalker
when you could have so much more.
You could be one of us.
Or are you afraid?
Yeah!
Not in those old rags.
The Knights of Ren
have a reputation to keep.
Really? Not again.
Would you please...
Could you just... This isn't funny.
You got the knight fever, Ben!
Yeah! Play that kloo horn!
- He's so good.
- You're moving like a real champ.
Whoo!
That was so fun! I am in!
No, no, no.
There's still the initiation.
Uh... Wasn't the beach dancing
the initiation?
My uncle's lightsaber. How did you get...
I told you. We take what we want.
Now, take what you want.
To create a Knight of Ren
requires destruction.
Destroy what Skywalker has built
and you will be free.
No... I don't know.
Don't waste
your time with him, Ren.
The kid's a total Kylo.
Kylo?
Yeah, Kylo. Small. Weak. Scared.
Kylo... Kylo... Kylo... Kylo...
I'm not scared! I'm not a Kylo!
Then take what you want.
What I want is for you to leave me alone!
Wrong choice, kid.
Knights of Ren, destroy the Temple!
Destroy the Temple.
Yeah!
Ow!
Power was yours for the taking.
But you're too scared... Kylo.
Keep calling me that.
I'm starting to like it!
Rock stacking. Go figure.
Ben?
-Ben!
-No, Uncle Luke. Call me...
Kylo.
And that night was Kylo Ren's
first step on his path to power!
And how did that work out for him?
What was even the point of that story?
To scare us?
It worked!
No.
To remind you that there is much
to be taken by those unafraid to take it.
Sith artifacts
lie beyond this door.
The Prophecy of Mustafar
foretells the arrival of a fearless
stranger with the strength to open it.
Perhaps, a brave pilot
who has fought many battles?
Sounds like my cue.
What about your X-wing?
If there's even a small chance
Vaneé is telling the truth,
there's no way I'm letting a Hutt
get his slimy hands on Sith artifacts.
Come on. Give me a hand.
Yes... Follow Vaneé!
Much to see. Much to find...
Come on!
Monster!
Would you bantha brains focus?
I mean, look at all this space!
We can add a business center and a gym!
You said you want to be a pilot.
So, how'd you wind up
on Graballa's clean-up detail?
You saving for a ship or something?
For my family. My mom was a mechanic.
We had a shop on Arkanis.
Had a shop? What happened?
The First Order accused her of helping
the Resistance and destroyed it.
People got scared
and wouldn't hire her anymore.
- So now it's all on you.
- Yeah.
I'm afraid if I lose this job,
my family has nothing.
Hey, I get it.
I had a tough childhood, too.
But it's a big galaxy.
You can't let fear get to you. Look at me.
We got room for luxury suites!
Was not.
The ancient lightsaber repository.
We're looking for something very special.
The Saber of Scardont.
Said to be a Sith lightsaber
of unusual power.
How dare you!
Ooh! This must be priceless!
What the... Dean! Fix it!
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
That's a Sith lightsaber, kid.
I wouldn't mess with it.
I told you, I can't lose this job.
While the boy toils,
would any of you care to hear
the Tale of the Saber of Scardont?
Why do I have the feeling
no matter what we say, you're gonna...
-It is a tale of two monstrosities.
-And there it is...
Was that lightning... Inside?
Left for dead
by a Jedi named Obi-Wan Kenobi,
Darth Maul nonetheless survived.
And made his way to a clan
of witches known as the Nightsisters.
Now, you shall rise! Rise!
But of course, Mother.
Ow!
Uh-oh.
Rise!
Ah, so close.
- Now... Rise!
- Rise!
Rise!
Hang on. A guy gets cut in half, lives,
and gets put back together
by a bunch of witches.
Is anybody buying this?
Oh, tell us more!
Yeah, does he take the legs off to sleep?
But Maul was not the only one
who returned after being left for dead.
A loyal student of Count Dooku
once known as Qymaen jai Sheelal,
but reborn as General Grievous.
-You clumsy fool!
-Excuse me?
Kidding.
General Grievous, we are receiving
a transmission from Lord Sidious.
How may I be of service, my lord?
There is an ancient Sith Saber located
on the sixth moon in the Scardont system.
You will find it and bring it to me.
And be warned,
the Saber of Scardont's power is so great,
anyone who attempts to wield it
will be driven mad.
I shall not fail.
Oh, no!
Really scraping
the bottom of the barrel
with General Wheezius there.
You know, back in the day,
I had Darth Maul.
You know, before he "came apart."
I have returned, my master.
No!
Hey, hey! Well, look at you.
You're... You're alive.
Oh, and look you've got legs...
A whole bunch of legs.
- Yes. So, many legs.
- No, no, no. Turn... Turn left.
-I... No!
-My left.
One, two, three, four, five, six.
I will retrieve the Saber of Scardont
so that I may once again
stand by your side.
Oh, you heard that.
Though the journey was difficult,
Grievous would not yield.
The Saber of Scardont's
power is so great,
anyone who attempts to wield it
will be driven mad.
Ah, a rival to bring
the saber to Lord Sidious.
The power.
Too bad it can't be split in half, Maul.
Unlike you!
At least I can wield the Force.
Force spin! Force leap!
I'm taking it to Sidious!
- It's mine! Let go!
- You let go!
You let go! Coochy coochy coo...
Cut that out!
I will destroy you!
Power is mine!
Force flip!
Come on, I just got these!
I've destroyed Jedi.
A half-Sith is no match for me!
- What?
- It appears you are un-armed!
And without a leg to stand on.
Hmm, perhaps you need a cough drop!
That's not funny!
Warm up the oil bath!
So, did you find it?
Ooh! Give me, give me, give me!
Uh, what's with the eyes?
The blade is mine! All...
Oh, you know, uh, funny thing,
it must have been damaged in the fight.
Oh, too bad. Pushity push!
Goodbye!
Ow!
There it is.
I can't believe he broke it.
Apprentices. Am I right?
Defeated, but not destroyed,
Darth Maul gained
a valuable insight into his feeling...
I got it.
Whoa...
So strong.
Uh, Dean? You okay?
Maybe you wanna stop staring
into the scary saber?
As Vaneé was saying,
Darth Maul gained a valuable insight.
Power comes
not from serving others, but...
From serving yourself.
Very good, boy.
Now, see where the saber leads you.
Uh, what is that?
Perhaps Vaneé placed his hopes
on the wrong pilot.
Perhaps.
Follow me, everyone.
I got a bad feeling...
It's still worth mentioning.
The first Temple of Mustafar.
Built generations ago.
A repository of ancient lore!
Lore schmore.
I mean,
this stuff must be worth a fortune.
Pack it up, boys.
Hey!
All treasure is the property
of Graballa the Hutt Enterprises, LLC.
Graballa, we need to talk.
Let me guess, Dameron, now,
you want the spokesman gig, right?
-Too late!
-No. This Sith stuff.
Do you have any idea how dangerous it is?
I'm a Hutt.
The only thing I fear is poor cash flow.
- Power.
- Here, boy.
- Freedom is yours.
- Save your mother.
- Take what you desire.
- Fear no more.
- This is yours.
- What do you desire?
Whoa!
Yes! The boy has found it.
Found what?
This has the power
to make any dream come true.
That little triangle
makes wishes come true.
Oh, please.
Nothing in the galaxy can do that.
A Wookiee's Paw can.
Oh, the child knows of the Wookiee's Paw?
The pilots who came to my mom's shop
would tell stories.
I've heard those stories, too.
-They're made-up.
-Are they?
Submitted for your approval.
The tale of a boy in search of more.
Of a better life. Much like you.
Uh, the droid
on the South Ridge broke down.
Again. Useless.
Luke, I want you to go to Mos Espa
and get a new one.
But, Uncle Owen,
I was going to Tosche Station to drop off
my application for the Academy.
You get your head out of the stars.
Harvest is coming up
and we're short-handed. Now go.
I'll show him.
I will be a pilot one day
and get off this dust ball planet.
You look like you want
to get off this dust ball planet.
I got something that might help.
-What is that?
-The Wookiee's Paw.
Make a wish
and your dream instantly comes true.
I wish I was off this rock.
Hey! You look like
you want to get off this rock.
You should join the Imperial Academy.
Really?
And as he wished,
the Wookiee's Paw
took Skywalker off of Tatooine.
Yet, he still wasn't satisfied.
Ow!
I can't see a thing in this helmet.
I wish I was a pilot.
Sir, what should I do
with this extra pilot gear?
Give it to him.
He looks too short to be
a stormtrooper anyway.
I'm a pilot!
Everything Skywalker wanted,
he got.
Yet, he still wanted more.
Patrol duty.
I wish I had the chance
to show everyone how great I can be.
Lord Vader's
squadron is under Rebel ambush.
All fighters assist.
It's about time.
Hmm?
Not so fast, Rebel scum. Eat proton.
You. Pilot.
That maneuver,
what do you call it?
The 180 Reverse Proton Move.
Most impressive.
What's your name?
Luke Skywalker, sir.
Skywalker?
I knew a Skywalker once.
- Um, Lord Vader?
- Huh? Oh, yeah. Right.
You are sensitive with the Force.
You remind me of... A young me.
I will train you.
Whoa! I only wish I could be
as powerful as you.
Then come with me.
Actually, I wish to be
more powerful than you.
Your eyes can deceive you.
Don't trust them.
I can still see.
Firm touch.
Focus. Focus.
It tickles.
More like this.
Try again.
For luck.
You have mastered
the dark side of the Force.
Yet, I sense you are still unsatisfied.
I want more.
I wish I could fight the rebellion
and become the most famous pilot
in the galaxy!
The Death Star is under attack!
Vader, scramble your men.
- All wings report in.
- Red Two standing by.
Red Ten standing by, Princess Leia.
Red Five standing by.
Good to have you, General Kenobi.
And thank you for rescuing me earlier.
No, thank you for rescuing me
from that trash compactor, Your Highness.
I wasn't sure I'd make it
off the Death Star alive.
Lock S-foils in attack position.
I'm making my run. Cover me!
Enemy fighters coming our way.
Like Beggar's Canyon back home!
I'm hit! I can't stay with you!
Get clear, Obi-Wan.
You can't do any more good back there.
- I'm on the leader!
- No, I am!
Oh, no! He's trying the...
One-eighty Reverse Proton maneuver!
Oh, yeah!
I don't think so, fly boy!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
-Oh!
-No!
You're going to be
the most famous pilot in the galaxy.
Yes!
For blowing up the Death Star!
No.
Is that really what happened?
No, it's not.
You're saying Luke Skywalker
did not blow up the Death Star?
Well, yeah, but not like that.
Just as the Wookiee's Paw
gave Skywalker all that he wanted,
this holocron will grant
whatever you desire.
No! That story is a warning.
Be careful what you wish for!
I know what you want.
For your family to be safe.
Open this and never fear for them again.
No, don't do it!
Not with your hands. With your heart.
You said this makes dreams come true!
It does make dreams come true.
Mine!
Long has Vaneé waited for this.
I thought you were the one
to make it happen.
But little did I know,
it was the boy I needed.
One who is strong with the Force.
I'm strong with the Force?
Oh, my whole life I was weak.
Pitiful. Afraid to seize power.
Like in the Mask of Ren story.
Always toiling for others.
Like Darth Maul.
Now Vaneé has all he desires.
Like the Wookiee's Paw!
Those stories were for him!
Okay, really, like you had it figured out?
For a generation,
the galaxy feared my master!
Now it shall fear... Me.
Yeah, you and what army?
Yeah, some army. One droid.
Roger, roger. Roger. Roger.
These fools have served
their purpose.
NI-L8, annihilate them.
As you command.
- Oh!
- Destroy...
NI-L8, "annihilate."
Should have put that together sooner.
Swarming killer droids
and you focus on the wordplay? Run!
We gotta grab that holocron!
It's the source of his power.
-How?
-We'll do it the old-fashioned way.
Whoa! Nice shot!
Grab it, kid!
Master, are you all right?
Without the holocron,
my power will not hold! Get them!
Destroy...
In here.
Whew!
Roger, roger, roger, roger, roger.
I think I lost 'em.
Mama! That's a big one.
My dreams are crumbling around me.
Here's B-14961138815...
- Took you long enough!
- Here's...
Destroy, roger. Destroy, roger.
Destroy. Destroy.
Destroy. Destroy...
Vaneé's right behind us.
-What do we do now?
-I have an idea.
Where is my holocron?
I find
your lack of souvenirs disturbing...
Disturbing. Disturbing...
Destroy.
We gotta get to the ship
and get that holocron
as far away from Vaneé as possible.
This way!
-It's all my fault.
-Kid.
I fixed that lightsaber.
I opened the holocron.
All because I was scared.
Everyone gets scared, kid.
You don't.
Well, no, but, you know,
sometimes the adrenaline gets going...
I'm scared right now.
You can't control fear.
But you can choose what to do with it.
Because without fear,
you can't have courage.
Destroy. Destroy. Destroy.
BB-8! What are you doing?
Now let's get outta here.
Oh, we never fixed it!
Way to go, Dameron!
Always having to prove how brave you are!
-Poe...
-Pulling that move in the X-wing!
-Poe?
-Opening that stupid door.
Poe!
I got this.
May the Force be with you.
-I'll buy us time.
-How?
I have no idea!
Destroy. Roger. Destroy.
Roger. Destroy. Roger. Destroy...
The energy of the dark side
is slipping away.
Where is the holocron?
Ah!
Blast! Missed!
Roger. Roger. Roger.
Ro-Ro-Roger.
They're wrecking my place! We gotta fight!
Hide me!
I could get used to this.
Yes, destroy him!
Come on, come on.
Got you right where I want you.
Destroy. Destroy.
Destroy. Destroy. Destroy...
Yeah! This is so fu...
Whoa!
Dean!
My holocron.
I got this.
Nice flyin', kid.
Master is gone!
The Emperor is gone!
Finally, the galaxy shall fear me!
I'm not scared.
Okay, maybe a little.
Hey!
Give me the holocron
and I will spare your friend's life.
No! Fly away! He's getting weaker!
Soon he'll be nothing. Whoa!
You don't have that kind of time.
The choice is yours, boy.
Whoa!
All right!
Although, this reminds me
of the story of the Wookie's Paw.
And how is that?
Careful what you wish for!
No!
Ow.
Cut it a little close there,
don't you think?
Still, it was a gutsy move. How'd you...
Like you said,
without fear you can't have courage.
-Thank you, Poe.
-Oh! Don't get all mushy on me, kid.
Aw! Is the brave Poe Dameron
afraid of a little mushiness?
Terrified.
Oh!
My hotel. My beautiful hotel.
Ah! You! Look what you did!
You have any idea
what this'll cost for me to fix?
You're not fixing anything.
You're leaving.
And don't even think
about taking those Sith artifacts.
I'm not scared of you, Dameron.
Okay, fine, I am. Let's go, boys.
That means you, too, kid. Come on.
-No.
-No?
I'll never work for you again.
See? That's what greed gets you, Graballa.
Nothing.
Yeah, you're right.
I really learned my lesson.
Gotta start small!
Like a bed and breakfast!
Come on, boys! We're gonna be rich.
-Ooh, breakfast!
-Breakfast!
I just realized. My wish came true.
What? You actually wished
on that Sith holocron?
Of course not.
But I have been wishing to quit
pretty much from the day
I started working for Graballa.
Well, then I guess you're out of a job.
What're you going to do now?
I don't know.
I saw how you handled that X-wing.
We always need pilots.
Really? Thank you, Poe.
And you should meet my friend, Rey.
She knows a little about the Force.
So you were scared back there?
Nah, I just said that
to make you feel better.
I wasn't scared.
Was not!
Master, forgive me.
I have failed you!