[Captioning sponsored by
Hallmark Cards
and CBS]
I liked how when they sang
"Everything got really smooth."
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
Hold on.
Dianne, I got
an extra one.
Can you save it
so I can give it to Julia?
Oh, yeah. Good idea.
She'll like that.
Yeah.
Let's get a cab.
Oh.
Evening.
Hi.
Hi. You free?
Yes, ma'am.
( horn blares, tires squeal )
Amy!
MAN ( over radio):
Aphrodite, Aphrodite.
This is the marine operator
for Captain Mark McCune.
McCune aboard the Aphrodite.
I've got the emergency room
at San Francisco
County Hospital.
They're asking if you know
a Dianne Parker.
Taxi!
MARK:
Hello? Excuse me.
Hello?
Hello.
Hi.
Hi. I'm looking
for Parker.
Oh, it's Dianne. Dianne Parker.
Can I help you?
Uh, yeah. You have a playhouse
for my brother, Dr. McCune.
Oh, yeah.
So just tell David
to call me.
I'll come by his office
and put it together for him.
What's wrong with now?
I'll help you.
Then you can say thanks;
I'll say, "Forget about it.
Have dinner with me
on my yacht."
You'll say,
"Sure. Why not?"
See? I give you the easy part.
I say, "Sure. Why not?"
You don't even know me.
I know you're strong
and you work hard
and you're not afraid
to get your clothes dirty.
You're not dating my brother,
are you?
No. we're friends.
He can chaperone
if you're scared.
( knock on door )
Sailor boy's unloading
the playhouse.
Okay.
That girl's come, too.
Dianne's here?
MARK:
It's very simple.
Watch me. Watch me.
Like this, all right?
Wait, wait, wait.
Then fold it back.
Come on. Come on.
Keep up with the master.
Here, use a clean one.
No. No do-overs.
Just fold it
back like this.
Where did you learn
how to do this?
Some old guy
in a Chinese
opium den.
You've been to China?
I've been everywhere.
Ooh, Tales from the sea.
Take him with a grain of salt,
please.
MARK:
All right.
Miss Piggot, my
seventh-grade art
teacher had me
stay after school
and make 50 of these.
It was my punishment.
For what?
You don't want to know.
You won't like me anymore.
Who says I like you now?
Come on. You tell me.
He was too busy
running for student
council president.
He doesn't remember.
Treasurer.
I was running for treasurer.
Well, I was running for my life.
You got sauce on your chin.
Thanks.
There you go.
( tittering )
MARK:
Thank you.
Sure.
( laughs )
MARK:
That's Orion.
Canis Major.
Taurus.
My mother, she painted them
on her bedroom ceiling.
You never talk
about her.
Nothing to talk about.
( crickets chirping )
( sighs )
It took two years.
I hated the hospital.
I... stopped going.
David, he was,
he was the hero.
He held her hand.
You were 12.
No, he kept asking me
to come with him.
Said she wanted to see me.
Say good-bye.
I don't beat
myself up about it.
Mothers aren't
supposed to die.
You had every right
to be angry.
She understood.
She knew you loved her.
How do you do that?
Make me feel like
you've known me
all my life?
Maybe we're soul mates.
You make
everything perfect.
I mean it.
I need you.
I love you.
( car horn honking )
David! David!
She said yes!
We're getting married!
Come on.
Say something, David.
Say something.
Congratulations.
He's jealous.
No. No, that's great.
I didn't...
Congratulations.
Thank you.
That's wonderful.
Mmm... mmm!
Oh, everyone in the world
is jealous of me right now.
Good morning,
Mr. Fisherman.
Mrs. Fisherman.
Oh, don't get lost
out there, okay?
I can't get lost.
What do you think
the stars are for?
God never figured
we'd invent a compass.
If you need directions,
just follow the stars.
Besides, I'll always
come home to you.
Me and the kids?
Kids?
Well, one, for starters.
Woo!
Come here!
Oh!
( laughing )
Wow!
This... mmm!
Hi.
Hi. You seen my mom?
She's over in the stacks.
What are you
doing here?
( whispering )
What?
No!
( laughing )
Oh, my!
You're lucky you're over
morning sickness.
So did you have morning
sickness with me?
Morning, afternoon
and evening.
You must be
having a boy.
Old wives tale.
You going to eat this?
No. I think you are.
Well...
how much weight
did you gain?
Oh, when you start running
after Mark Jr
it'll melt right off you.
No. If we have a boy
we're naming
him after Dad.
You are?
Mm-hmm.
Well, thank you, sweetheart.
He'd like that.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean
to make you sad.
Oh, no.
I was just remembering
when you were born.
I held you in my arms
and suddenly this wave
of terror came over me.
( chuckles )
Here I was holding
this complete stranger.
How much should I feed you?
What if you wouldn't
stop crying?
Uh, suppose you hated me?
Your dad came over to me
and he said... bless his heart...
"Hannah, give her to me."
And suddenly I knew
I didn't want to let you go.
You were mine.
We have a lot of books
about motherhood at the library
but none of them can prepare you
for that moment...
when you give your heart
to your child.
( gasps )
Oh!
( laughs )
What is it?
He kicked.
What?
Oh, my!
I think he's going
to be a football player.
Just now. That was
the first kick.
Well, maybe
soccer, at least.
( laughing )
Please, don't cry,
okay?
It's going
to be okay.
We'll figure it out.
It'll be okay.
It's not going
to be okay.
( crying )
Okay.
Listen...
Dianne, we'll...
we'll have a baby.
We'll have lots
of babies.
Just not now.
I want this baby.
Did you not understand
what Dr. Ellis was saying?
I don't care.
A baby who can't
walk or talk.
A baby who's
going to die.
Listen to me.
Dianne...
I can't deal with this.
Hey.
Genetic abnormalities.
Neurological damage.
Here, you went
to med school.
Did you take
a second test?
You're looking
at it.
Sorry.
How's Dianne?
She wants to have this baby.
You have to help me.
Explain it to her.
Tell her that it's
not fair to the baby.
This is between you and her.
You're a doctor.
She'll listen to you.
Mark, I cannot tell someone
to terminate a pregnancy.
Forget your hypocritical oaths
and ethics.
What if this was your baby?
Come on, David, be honest.
I don't know.
You know what you would do.
Anybody home?
Mark?
Dianne?
Mark's not here.
He left last night.
He'll be back.
He's scared.
I'm scared, too.
He showed me
the test results.
I made some calls.
The spine and the nervous system
are damaged.
There's fluid in the brain.
Your baby won't walk
or have normal speech.
If the heart and lungs
don't develop
they won't support
the body's growth.
This research expert
I spoke to said
he's seen cases like this
survive up to six years.
Don't tell me
not to have her.
I won't.
I mean, that's not
why I'm here.
She'll probably need
to undergo some surgery.
She'll need good care.
I'll be her doctor
if you want.
Will she be in pain?
I'll help you.
I'll help you take care of her
if you want to do this.
Mark!
Dianne!
Grab my hand!
Mark!
Dianne!
( voice echoing ):
Help!
( child crying )
Julia, I'm coming.
I'm coming.
What is it, sweetie?
Oh, what is it?
Does it hurt?
Do you have a cramp?
Do you want me to rub it?
You want me
to rub your tummy?
Oh, shh, shh.
I know, I know.
Did you have a bad dream?
Oh, I know, I know.
( clock chimes three times )
Is Julia all right?
Oh, yeah, she's fine.
Sweetheart,
you look terrible.
Go back to bed.
You're sick?
No. I just had
a bad dream.
Maybe Julia
had one, too.
I hate when
she's scared.
I don't know
how to tell her
it's just a dream.
Oh, she knows.
I dreamt about Mark.
He was drowning;
I couldn't save him.
Good.
Forgive us our trespasses, Mom.
I forgave that
louse years ago.
I'm not the one
having nightmares.
You can't help what you dream.
Forgive and you'll forget.
Five years is a long time
to hold out hope
for an ex-husband.
Or carry a grudge.
Or both.
Six. Six years
in August.
Yeah, but who's counting?
Not Mark.
He still sends you
a check every month.
Yeah, but that's
because he knows
I'm going to send it right back.
It's his conscience cleaner.
It's his opening gambit
and you keep
the conversation going.
Why don't you
just rip it up
instead of mailing it
back to him?
You're right.
Next time I will.
( toy piano tinkling )
JULIA:
Ma...
DIANNE:
I think Grandma has one
of these somewhere.
We haven't seen it
in a while, have we?
That's red...
and maybe that one's...
that's more
brown than red.
And orange.
Ma...
What's she got?
Nothing.
We're just here
for a checkup.
What have you got?
Nothing.
I feed the fish
and take out the bloaters
for Martha.
She freaks out
if there's any bloaters.
There always are.
There we go. Good.
Heart sounds good.
Lungs, too.
Good.
Get out.
I have
sick people waiting.
Hear that? He's
kicking us out.
We're too healthy.
I didn't say
you looked healthy.
Don't even
start with me,
Uncle David.
We're having
a good day.
Looks like
you need a break.
You look tired.
It's your
fluorescent
lighting.
Say "hasta la
bye-bye,
Uncle David."
Seriously, Dianne.
Seriously, stop.
Look, I moved in
with my mom.
She's retiring
just to be
with Julia.
We're fine.
( sighs )
Didn't mean
to bite your head off.
I have that effect on women.
Good-bye, sweetie.
Da...
Okay.
Thank you.
All right?
Mm-hmm.
Okay, let's see
what we have here.
Oh, Julia, you won't believe
there's starfish in here.
Can I get you one?
Okay, I've got one.
Ooh, look at that.
Gosh, look at that.
Look at the feet.
Kind of drippy.
Cool.
All the little tentacles.
That's where
it sucks in...
Dianne!
Hey!
Starfish.
Okay.
Hey, you
want a ride?
I can walk home.
Anybody who cleans
out that tank
deserves a ride.
Come on.
Got any plans
for the summer?
Mrs. Sobel says
I need a summer job.
I told her
I'd feed your fish
but she said
that wasn't enough.
Who's Mrs. Sobel?
The case worker.
I hate her.
Ever think about
being a mother's helper?
You like kids?
Well, that depends.
You can't just
"like kids."
They're all different.
No one ever says,
"So, do you like adults?"
Touche.
What does that mean?
It means you win.
You got me.
It's a fencing term.
It's French.
Well.
( train whistle blowing )
Is someone home?
My mom is.
( rock music playing )
And boyfriend Bud.
Thanks for the ride.
Okay. See ya.
"Farewell, cow,
and farewell, cat
"rabbit, tiger,
sullen rat.
"To our children
we shall say
"how we walked
the Milky Way.
"You whose journeys
now begin
"if you reach
a lovely inn
"if a rabbit
makes your bed
"if two dragons
bake your bread
"rest a little
for my sake
and give my love
to William Blake."
That's a good
story, huh?
( door opens )
Did you ask David
to dinner?
Oh, I forgot.
Dianne.
What? I forgot.
I'll call him.
No, Mom, please.
Do you want me to stop
having nightmares?
David reminds me
of Mark.
Every time.
Apples and oranges.
Something about
his voice... it's...
David's voice
is much deeper.
It's exactly the same.
All right, I will...
( sighs )
I could use a little help here.
( dog yelping and whining )
BUDDY:
Stop whining,
you worthless mutt!
( yelping and whining continue)
Come here!
All right, that's it!
That's it!
Get in there!
You let him out.
What did I tell you, Amy?
I'm sorry.
I thought he needed exercise.
If you want a dog
to obey
first you got to break him.
Do you hear me?!
( whining
and yelping )
The whole neighborhood
can hear you.
Hey, Amy Beth.
Where'd you put
my cigarettes?
You told me not to buy you any,
remember?
You wanted to quit.
( laughs )
I'll go.
We're out of hot sauce, anyway.
Oh, cookie face
don't be gloomy.
Buddy's fun.
He doesn't like me.
Don't be silly.
He loves you.
And don't be mad.
Go to bed... you got
school tomorrow.
School's out
for the summer.
It's over.
You had moving up ceremony?
Oh, I wanted to come.
Why didn't you tell me?
I did.
No, you didn't.
You did? Did you?
It wasn't anything.
It was just a stupid assembly.
It doesn't matter.
I'm not mad.
Oh... hug me.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry.
( electronic whirring )
( car horn honks )
( car doors opening )
David.
Hey.
Hi.
Uh... Dianne,
this is Amy Williams.
I know Amy.
You fish out the bloaters
for Martha, right?
Right.
Amy's looking
for a summer job.
Oh, that's great...
did you check the bulletin board
at the rec center?
Actually, I told her
you were looking for
a mother's helper.
Oh.
Where's Julia?
She's sleeping.
Would you like some lemonade?
Let me give you a hand.
You can have
your lemonade
and then you can
get on your horse, cowboy.
I told you, I don't
need help with Julia.
Especially not
from a 12-year-old.
She's a good kid.
She's having some
trouble at home.
She remembered Julia.
She wanted to come.
Why? So she can tell
her friends at school?
I remember her, you know,
from the waiting room.
Well, Julia seems to like her.
She's awake.
They're having a little chat.
You like my watch?
It was my dad's.
It was being fixed
at the jewelers
the day his ship went down.
It glows in the dark, see?
Ma...
It's okay...
she's making lemonade.
She'll be right back.
It's a guy's watch,
but I don't care.
I've had it
six years now.
It's waterproof...
I even wear it in the shower.
Hear it?
JULIA:
Mee...
You want to wear it
while I'm here?
Oh, be careful.
It's too big... it might
fall off and break.
Oh... look at your
little wrists.
Your mom's right.
You can buy her
a kid's watch
at the drugstore
with different color straps.
Yeah, I've seen those.
Ba...
They don't have blue.
Yellow, red or green.
( whispering ):
Get yellow.
Can I push her chair out?
Okay.
Here comes the bump.
( both laughing )
Did you like that?
Did your stomach
flip up?
Want to do it
again? Okay.
Whoo! Was that fun?
She really likes that.
Yeah.
( seagulls crying )
Mee...
That's my name...
don't wear it out.
Do you want to
trade hats? Here.
Oh, you look pretty.
Here.
You like that?
Do I look good?
"Mee" is "Amy"?
Uh-huh.
Girls at school trade
clothes all the time.
I don't trade with
anybody, though.
Do you like school?
It's okay. I like math.
Mmm.
Do you go to dances?
Ugh. Boys in my
grade can't dance.
Now, my dad was
a good dancer.
He drowned when I was six.
My dad died when I was 17.
It hurts in my chest
when I think about him.
Does it hurt in your chest?
Big-time.
Him and my mom won a dance
contest together once.
We had a picture of it,
but my mom took it down.
Yeah. Sometimes
it's hard to look
at old photographs, you know?
Is that why you don't have
any of Julia's dad?
Did he drown?
No. He just doesn't
live with us anymore.
Thanks.
You should get some
pictures for Julia.
So she knows what
he looks like.
Hmm.
Sometimes I can't remember
my dad's face
and it scares me.
'Cause I'm going to grow up
and look different
and he won't know me in heaven.
And what if I don't
recognize him?
Mmm. So, got a boyfriend?
No.
Lucky. My mom's got one.
He thinks he can sing.
( laughs )
Julia and Amy
traded hats.
Amy says all
the girls at school
trade clothes
with their friends.
Julia has a friend.
Talked to Martha.
David's got the flu.
My reading group's
coming over.
Otherwise I'd deliver
this myself.
Well, Ma, he doesn't
need your soup.
Dianne...
Trust me, I'm sure
the Single Mother
Brigade is on duty.
I'm sure he's
drowning in soup.
And brownies
and hand-knitted socks.
Do you remember
his address
or should I write
it down for you?
David?
( coughing )
Dianne?
( yells )
( laughing ):
Oh, I'm sorry.
You scared me.
Uh, the door
was unlocked
so I let myself in.
She'd kill me
if I came back with it.
What? With what?
Oh, the chicken soup.
Martha said you came home
with the flu.
Go back to sleep.
Oh, and, um...
these are your glasses.
I took them off.
So, it's on the stove.
The soup.
Thank you.
What is it?
Don't ever send me
to his house again.
Sorry.
This is your temporary card.
Just sign the back.
Now you can
check out a book.
I think Julia
wants one, too.
Absolutely.
Julia, you should have
a library card, too.
Will you sign your name?
Amy's going to help you
sign your name.
J...
BOTH:
U-L-I-A.
Julia.
Look.
Now you have a library
card just like Amy.
Let me take that for you.
There you go.
See?
Mom...
Mom, got you a book
with my own card.
Oh... baby...
I've got one of my headaches...
a really bad one.
Sorry.
Look... Agatha Christie.
Hannah says she's
really famous.
She's written a
million mysteries.
And Hannah's read
every one, I bet.
Oh... oh,
don't do that.
You can't sleep...
it's afternoon.
Get up. Get dressed.
Oh! Ooh...
Mom?
It was all my fault.
( Julia crying )
( gasping )
( quietly ):
Amy, I'm here.
Okay...
Come on, David,
pick up.
Please pick up.
She seems stable.
You can call me in the
morning if you want.
This was a bad one.
It was like she couldn't
catch her breath
you know, like
she'd been running.
Her lungs are small,
you know that.
She's growing,
and they're not.
I used to pray
for her to grow.
When she was born,
she was so tiny.
I was afraid to touch her
after the surgery, you know?
I just knew I was hurting her
every time I picked her up.
I remember talking
out loud to myself...
shouting, really...
usually at Mark.
Now I just... want her
to stay the same size
and not grow an inch.
What about Mark?
I don't think
about Mark anymore.
I'm sorry I made you
come out in the rain.
( thunder rumbling in distance)
Don't be afraid
to call me again tonight.
Okay, thanks.
And try to get
some sleep yourself.
All right. Good night.
Okay.
Julia wants
her Christmas rabbit
but I can't find it.
Her Christmas rabbit?
You gave it to her.
With the red top hat
and the bell.
Wha... That was
three years ago.
Well, she wants it.
Oh, my, I think it got lost
in between hospital visits.
Okay, I'll tell her.
Did you tell her
about the rabbit?
No. I didn't even remember
that rabbit until she
mentioned the top hat.
Someone must
have mentioned it.
Keep the tiger there.
You like the doggy?
Want to keep him
here with you?
Let's do a rhythm strip.
We did one
two weeks ago.
Yeah, I know.
That little click
every ten heartbeats or so
seems a little more
frequent now.
It might mean nothing
but I'm going to do a strip
and send it to Kaplan
see if he wants
to do an echo.
It may be nothing,
believe me.
I... am an old woman
kind of guy.
I check the locks
on every door.
David, tell me the truth.
The truth is the same
as it's always been.
She's surprised us too often
for me and Kaplan
to have a timetable.
I know that's hard.
( rhythmic beeps )
Good.
Maaaa.
Here you go.
Mmm, thanks.
Hmm.
( sighs contentedly )
Amy left this on my desk
at the library.
"I learned a word,
it's "serendipity.
"When you say it,
it sounds skippity.
"Light and airy,
just by chance
a breeze that makes
the flowers dance."
"Skippity."
It's nice, huh?
I like that.
Hmm...
Amy is what I imagine
Julia would be like.
Smart... messy and awkward,
you know?
Full of questions.
( sighs )
I had so many plans
when I got married.
You sound like your life has
been folded up and put away.
But it's not over.
The carnival opened
in Blair County.
You know, Amy's never been.
We should take the girls.
Oh, it's two hours away.
Thursday's my last day
at the library.
We could go Friday afternoon
and avoid the traffic.
All right.
I know you made us
promise no fuss
but this doesn't
feel right.
Well, you'll
get your chance
at the Book Lovers Ball.
You can make as many
speeches as you want.
I'll play the fool
for a big donation.
You'll play the guest
of honor and like it.
Aw. Well, we'll see.
( chuckling )
Goodbye, Mrs. Parker.
We'll miss you.
Yeah.
( sniffles )
DIANNE AND AMY:
Go, Hannah! Go, Hannah!
Go! Go!
Go, Hannah!
Go, Hannah! Go, Hannah!
Go! Go!
Go, Hannah!
Whoo!
Congratulations.
Oh, thank you.
Happy new life.
Good job.
( laughing )
Thank you, sweetie.
Oh, thank you.
Mmm...
Oh, ah!
I was feeling a little sorry
for myself before, but not now.
Oh. Well, remember what
you told me at graduation?
"Marvels of the
universe lie ahead."
Here you go.
Mmm... yum.
Here, Julia.
She like it?
Yeah.
That was
her favorite.
A rabbit.
Oh, no.
Oh. A pig.
A pig.
( snorting )
Hi.
Hello.
Julia wants to go
on the Ferris wheel.
Can I take her?
Why don't you
and Hannah go.
Julia and I will stay
down here and wave
But Julia's the one
who wants to go.
I won't go without her;
It wouldn't be fair.
They strap them in;
it's safe.
Why don't you just take Amy.
Honest, Dianne,
I'm not making it up.
She said she wanted to go.
Well, it's just that it's...
it's awfully high, Amy.
She might get scared.
No, not if Amy's with her.
All right, we'll all go.
No, let her go with Amy.
Let her go with her friend.
( kids screaming )
How pretty.
( laughing )
Hey, guys!
Ahh!
( laughing )
Ah!
( laughs )
Oh!
Look, I did it!
Thank you.
Whoa!
Dianne!
What? What? What?
What's wrong?
Okay, I got you.
I got you.
What's happening?
Dianne, hold
down her tongue.
Get away. I know
what I'm doing.
She's bleeding!
It's her lip.
Mom, call an ambulance.
I got you, sweetie.
Julia...
I got you.
It's okay.
It's all right.
( phone rings )
( answering machine clicks )
Hi. This is David McCune.
I'm not here right now,
but you can leave a message.
( beep )
David, it's Hannah.
We have a problem with Julia.
Woman ( over PA):
Dr. Gelber. Dr. Gelber.
As soon as she's stable,
I want to transfer her to Mercy.
They don't know her here.
Hillcrest is
a good hospital.
I know. It's just...
I'm sure they're thinking,
"What's the point?"
They're taking good
care of her, Dianne.
The nurse asked me
if I want to speak
to social services
about a hospice.
I told her
Julia lives at home.
Thank God, you've
never played me
like a martyred mom
with a "special" kid.
David:
We'll see how she is
in the morning, okay?
Amy thinks
this was her fault.
Can you please
tell her it wasn't?
She took Julia
on the Ferris wheel.
The two of them?
Oh, if you'd seen her;
heard her when she got
to the top, she...
So excited.
My wild thing.
You're not afraid,
are you?
You'll try anything.
Bet you could see everything
from up there.
DAVID:
I'll talk to Goodman.
He'll probably adjust her meds.
And you just keep on going,
okay?
Keep on loving her.
Put it on there.
You got it?
Good job.
Like that, Julia?
AMY:
That's cool,
Julia.
Good job.
What do you think?
Uh.
DIANNE:
No?
( sighs )
You need something
for the Book Lovers Ball.
Let's find you a dress.
I don't need
to go to that.
Yes, you do.
Hannah's the guest of honor.
How about this? Come on.
Let's see.
No, don't look at the tag.
It's a birthday present.
It's too much money
for a birthday present.
Besides, it's not
even my birthday.
I got my first
dress-up dress here.
( laughs )
I did, when my mother took me
to San Francisco
to see The Sound of Music.
Every summer, we'd go,
we'd leave my dad at home
and we'd go see a musical,
just the two of us.
We'd stay in a hotel,
and we'd get room service
and we'd go to the evening
performance for grownups.
I remember those
trips to the city.
Your little overnight bag.
Now, there is a picture
of you somewhere
in a red raincoat, standing
in front of the theater.
You should take Amy
to San Francisco
just for the night
to the theater.
Amy is not my daughter.
Oh, here, sweetie,
let me...
No, Mom.
One on each side.
You don't want to look
like a little schoolgirl.
Just give it to me.
I like the way
Dianne does it.
This way looks good, too.
Oh, wear it however you want.
I've got a headache.
Buddy's going
to take you.
( doorbell rings )
I asked Dianne to pick me up.
Hi. How are you?
Hi. Good. Thank you.
I think it could
be lots of fun.
There's plenty
for them to do there.
They could go
to the theater, museums.
Why, it's just
for the weekend.
Amy's never been
to San Francisco.
What about Julia?
Oh, Julia
stays with me.
HANNAH:
You know, Dianne's
never spent a night
away from that child
in six years.
It's not just Amy
I'm thinking about.
She won't do it.
Well...
I'll talk to her.
Good.
Mmm.
You lost?
Um...
What are you
doing back here?
Uh, just... inhaling.
( inhales )
I see.
I love the way
libraries smell.
When I was little,
my mom used to bring me here
and I thought all the books
belonged to her.
My dad built these shelves.
( sighs )
I wish he could be here tonight.
You look nice.
Thank you. You, too.
Thanks.
These are pretty.
Oh, they were
your grandmother's.
Mark gave them to me.
Ah, yes. That's why
they would seem familiar.
( laughs )
Let's dance.
( giggling )
BUDDY:
I cannot believe this!
TESS:
I-I had to pay the rent...
BUDDY:
No, no, no,
it's not okay.
You told me you
were going to
give me the money
and now there's
no money.
I-I'm not saying
it's okay.
I'm just saying I don't know
where to get the money from
because it's already
gone out, that's all.
It's already
gone out.
You told me I was
going to be able
to get this amp.
I have a gig
tomorrow night!
We'll try and figure it out
as soon as I get the next...
"Try and figure..."?
What do you
want me to do?
What do you want me
to say?
I want you to give
me the money
that you told me you
were going to give me!
Okay, okay, okay!
Just shut up
and stop this!
( slapping )
( Tess screams and gasps )
I'm outta here!
( Tess sobs )
( door slams )
( sobbing continues )
( van drives away )
( dog yelping and whining )
Knock it off!
( dog quiets )
Where's your mother?
She's sleeping.
She said she's
tired and she just
wants to sleep.
Did you have
breakfast?
Get out of my way.
No.
( dog yelping )
Shut up!
I said shut up!
Buddy...
Go get me
one of your pillowcases.
Buddy, you can't.
You can't.
He's just a puppy.
He can still learn.
I swear I'll never
touch him again.
Go get me
a pillowcase!
No.
Amy!
( horn honking )
( horn honks )
( brakes squeal )
No... no... no...
Ow! Ow!
( sobbing )
Get in there!
( whimpering )
Now, you leave him
in there.
( sobbing )
Okay, get out.
You can walk from here.
Say "Thank you, Buddy."
Thank you, Buddy.
Oh, no, no,
no, no, no.
I said you can walk.
He's going for
a little swim.
No!
Hey!
Ow...
( yelping )
( yelping louder )
No... no... no...!
Buddy, Buddy, no!
Buddy, please...
Get off of me.
Please don't!
Get out of here.
Buddy...
I told you, a dog
who won't train
isn't worth jack.
No!
( yelping )
Amy Williams.
I'm her mother.
Where is she?
Was she admitted
in the last hour?
Yes. They said she was here.
Amy... Williams.
She's fine.
Are you sure?
I just saw her.
She made it to
shore with the dog.
( relieved gasps )
Where is she?
I want to see her.
You got a cigarette?
Tess, listen...
they arrested Buddy.
What?
Come here.
You have got to get
into a treatment
center... now.
This is it, Tess.
Child Services
has issued an order of
protection against you.
Mommy?
Wha...? Baby...
Oh, honey.
Oh... oh...
Say good night
to Julia.
And don't
wake her up.
You got to keep it
nice and quiet.
Amy...
Do you want some hot chocolate?
Come on.
When I was a kid,
I used to sleep out
here in the summer.
I'd lie on my back and
try to count the stars.
You can't;
there's too many.
Do you believe
in Heaven, Dianne?
Absolutely.
I think my dad can see me
from Heaven.
And I know he helped me
get to shore today.
I know he did.
I wish he could come back.
So do I.
Julia misses her dad.
She's never met him.
His boat could sink.
He could drown,
just like my dad
then it would be too late.
Oh...
( sniffling )
Hey, it's clearing. Look.
( gasps )
Did you see that?
Yeah. Did you make a wish?
Yeah. Did you?
Yeah.
( weary sigh )
TESS:
You want to take her
to San Francisco?
Yeah. To see a play.
I said she couldn't go
without your permission.
Taking her places,
buying her clothes...
I'm grateful to you.
You don't need to be.
I like Amy very much.
She thinks you
hung the moon.
( chuckles )
You're going
to be okay, Tess.
After Ryan died,
I... couldn't sleep.
Pills didn't work.
I drink so I can
sleep, that's all.
I'm not very good
at being alone.
Mom!
Hi.
When you're better, I
can come home, right?
I'm your mother.
We belong together.
AMY:
Love you.
( horn blaring )
Amy!
( monitor beeping )
Dianne?
Dianne.
Would you like to
see your daughter?
Not now.
( pager beeping )
( groaning )
( monitor beeping )
Dianne.
NURSE ( on P.A. ):
Code Blue, E.R. Two.
( woman screaming )
( yelling )
( alarm beeping )
DOCTOR:
Losing her!
( monitor beeps steadily )
( respirator pumping )
Done with that?
Thanks for
the call.
Seems like old times.
Not really.
I meant when Mom
was in the hospital.
I know what
you meant.
What are you
doing here, Mark?
The hospital
got in touch with me.
Well... you don't
need to stick around.
Dianne's not your
responsibility.
Order something else.
I'm buying.
Just coffee.
I thought you'd
be married by now,
have a couple of kids.
Seeing anyone?
20 patients a day,
on the average.
Here's one of them.
She's my niece.
It's recent.
Taken about
a month ago.
Keep it.
She's your daughter...
doesn't that mean
anything to you?
I send a check
every month.
It's not like
I'm a deadbeat dad.
Now what?
You going to pay
for her funeral?
Yeah. A few months,
at the most.
Makes me sick,
all of it.
Six years wasted.
You know, Dianne takes her
to the beach sometimes.
They sing together.
Julia laughs when
you tickle her.
She's got a great laugh.
You missed out, brother.
You can call it a waste, if that
makes you feel better about it.
Put that back
in your wallet, huh?
You tell everyone
that Dianne's your wife,
or is it a private game?
Whoa! Hey!
Knock it off!
Sorry.
Dr. McCune?
What is it?
Dianne Parker's awake.
She's asking for you.
Great.
Where's David?
What?
Where is David?
He's not here yet.
Amy?
She's okay.
I'm not lying to you.
You want me to
get the nurse?
You're here.
Yeah. You had my business card
in your bag.
I'm sorry.
You can go.
What? You kidding?
You hate hospitals.
I'm not going
to lose you again.
Am I dying?
No.
Not on my watch.
TESS:
My little girl was hit by a car.
She's okay.
A drunk driver.
You say trust in
your higher power.
Why should I
trust something
that sends a storm
to drown Ryan
or a car to hit
my little girl?
If God wants to
teach me a lesson
why doesn't he send a
drunk driver to hit me?
I mean, that's fair
but Amy's just
a little girl.
She's never, ever
done anything bad.
If there is some master plan,
I don't see it.
I'd like to, 'cause
whatever it is
it's got to be better
than what I've been doing.
AMY:
I'm not going back.
Not until you do.
You can tell Julia
I'm all right.
I don't want her to be scared.
Hannah's there.
You understand her
better than anybody.
She trusts you.
I can't leave
until you're okay.
( sobbing )
Amy.
It's my fault.
We came here
because of me.
Everybody gets hurt
I don't take good
care of Julia.
Look what happened
at the carnival.
I didn't take good care
of my mom, either.
I hurt people.
I hurt everybody.
Oh, Amy, no.
It's okay.
Listen...
sometimes I feel
just the way you said.
'Cause I can't
fix something,
it's my fault.
I'm a doctor... I'm supposed
to make everything okay.
But I can't.
We can't, Amy.
We can't stop...
taxis from jumping the curb
or boats from sinking.
We just do
what we can
and try not
to blame ourselves
or anybody else,
that's it.
I made Julia have a
seizure at the carnival.
Julia's had seizures before
It isn't anything you did.
This has been the best summer
of her life, Amy.
Come here.
Do you know what
it's meant to me
for Julia to have a friend?
I don't think
I can tell you.
Not in words.
Your mother wants
to get better because of you.
Don't you see, it's just
the opposite of what you think.
You're so good...
for everyone.
Can you do something for me?
It's important.
Go back.
Tell Julia I love her
and I'm coming home.
Okay?
Thank you.
I went to three
different places.
No one had lilacs.
I guess this isn't
a good time to talk.
There's nothing
to talk about.
You still had my
card in your handbag.
I gave that to you
when we went dancing
on the pier
six years ago.
It's an evening bag.
I never use it.
Don't turn this into something.
You know, I was docking
when the hospital called.
Docking here in San Francisco,
a cab ride away.
What are the odds on that?
I'm tired.
We're meant to
be together.
We're getting
a second chance.
Dianne...
I'm not going
to leave this time.
All right?
I appreciate it.
Thanks.
Okay. I've arranged
for an ambulance
to take Dianne to the
hospital in Hawthorne
as soon as she's
ready to be moved.
She can have the
knee surgery there
maybe by Friday.
I'll stay here with her.
You can go back.
Uh...
Look, I never stopped
thinking about her
not one day.
Things could
have been different.
Now they are.
Dianne wants you to stay?
Ask her.
TESS:
I've had enough therapy.
I want to go home.
Amy's coming back.
She's got her arm
in a cast.
She's going to need help
getting dressed.
You're not ready.
You need more time, Tess.
I want it to be me.
I want to be the one
to help her, not somebody else.
The important thing now
is to help yourself
and to get better.
Helping Amy would
help me get better.
I want to think
about somebody else.
When I think
about myself
I don't want
to get better.
I don't get how people
can forgive themselves.
I don't understand how
to say life is not so bad
when it is.
You're going to feel
pain sometimes, Tess
but you can handle that.
No one's happy all the time.
It's what you do with it.
I want to go home.
I'll feel better
once I know you're there.
I'll leave tonight,
if you want.
Mark says he'll
stay around
until they
transfer you.
Unless you don't
want him here.
I can have Greenwald
restrict your visitors.
No.
I need to forgive him.
For my sake as much
as for Julia's.
You still love him?
I'm sorry.
None of my business.
I need time.
That's all I can think about
right now is time.
Julia has so little left.
He doesn't know that.
I haven't told him.
I don't know, David.
It's hard to think right now.
He never took off
his wedding band.
Here, baby, just...
just take it.
I'll see you at
Hawthorne, okay?
Bye.
There she is!
Julia!
Hi! Hi, sweetie.
Oh...
How's my girl?
You look good.
I missed you so much.
How's Amy?
She's doing fine.
David's watching her.
Here, give me that.
Do I tell you I'd
be lost without you
or do you know it?
I think you'd manage.
Dianne, I have a lot
of respect for you...
as a person,
as a woman.
And not just because
you're my daughter.
Mom...
Mark was in
San Francisco.
I know.
David told me.
He wants to come back.
He wants to get
married again.
Well, whatever
you decide
you'll be doing
the right thing.
I want to know
what you think.
That you deserve
to be happy
and no one can
define that for you.
I never really forgave him.
I can now.
He's changed now.
He's... he's older.
I'm older, too.
I'm not expecting it to be
exactly the way it
was, you know.
I mean, a lot's happened
in six years.
To you it has.
I wish I were certain.
I was so certain
when we got married.
Mark's sure.
He says we're meant
to be together.
Mmm.
Is that his wedding ring?
He never stopped wearing it.
He made me take it.
No one's ever made you
do anything.
It's not too late for Julia
to know her father...
that's what I keep thinking.
( knocking )
Who do you have to know
to get a shave
around here?
Come on in.
Hey.
Hi.
I'll leave the key for you
on the kitchen table.
Thanks.
It's your house, too.
Yeah, I don't see
bunking at her mother's.
Put a good word in for me
with Hannah, I'd appreciate it.
How's Dianne?
Been to see her?
She's got enough visitors
without me hanging around.
If you hurry up, I'll
take you to the hospital.
Uh, I'll get a cab.
Wish me luck.
Good luck.
Hey, you know,
I've been thinking
Dianne and I should
move up to Portland.
Get a really fresh start.
I got enough money
to put down on a place...
nothing grand.
You know Seaside?
Just north of Rockaway Beach.
I brought some pictures.
Oh, it looks like
you got company.
Hey.
You want to stay in
the chair for a while?
Yeah, thanks.
All right, no dancing.
You weren't here.
I thought I got stood up.
I was in X ray.
I'm sorry.
Someone should
have told you.
Nah, I didn't ask.
Hey, look,
let's get out of here.
I can't propose
sitting next to a bedpan.
Mark, uh...
Yes, I can.
( sighs )
Marry me.
Please.
Are you sure?
Yes. I love you.
I never stopped missing you.
You know, I hate that we lost
these six years
and I want to make
them up somehow.
I don't think they were lost...
I lived them.
You're right, you're right.
It's not starting over,
it's starting now.
Everything's a first, okay?
'Kay.
I knew right
when I saw it.
Isn't that a great
old farm house?
Yeah.
Just an hour
north of Portland.
It's great, but we can't
take Julie to a farmhouse
in the middle of nowhere.
All her doctors are here.
I meant in
the spring.
It'll be good for
you... afterwards.
After she dies?
Is that what you mean?
Move after she dies?
That's the plan?
Look... David told me
that she's only got
a few months left.
Dianne...
If David told you
she had ten years left
would you be here
right now?
Be honest with me.
No, you be honest.
Would you do it again
knowing the kind of
life she's had...
with doctors and surgery?
You don't know anything
about her life.
She has a friend.
They tell secrets
and share ice cream
and sing songs.
She's dying.
She's not even
six years old
and she's dying.
Now, what was the point?
Look, we're going to
have kids... healthy kids.
We're going to have
a real family.
Do you even know
what that is?
Or do you mean
a "perfect" family
where no one's ever sick
or angry or sad
or in pain?
Six years, Mark...
you've never even
touched your daughter...
never even seen her.
Oh, what are we
talking about?
I love you, and that's
all that matters now.
Where were you?
What were you doing, Mark,
when I was up all night crying
because I was too tired
to fall asleep?
Where were you when
I was changing diapers
or going to the grocery store
or taking walks
on the beach?
Where were you?!
I'm... I'm here now.
Six years...
for six years I have been
apologizing for you in my head
trying to understand
trying to make excuses
and... now I understand.
Understand what?
Julia is my daughter.
She is...
part of who I am
and who I have become.
I don't know you.
And you sure don't know me.
I want you
to leave us alone.
Don't come back.
Hi.
Hey.
Hannah, can I ask
you a question?
Sure.
It's about Julia's dad.
Oh.
I thought he was coming
to see her.
Things didn't work out.
Why not?
Well, I don't have an answer
to that question...
not a simple one,
that's for sure.
But we don't always choose
the right people to love.
Poets deceive us...
talk about the feeling
and things
we say to each other...
and those things
are important...
but in the end,
it all comes down
to how much we're willing
to give of ourselves.
Like Romeo and Juliet
dying for each other.
Well, I don't know
if killing yourself
in a crypt before you check
your girlfriend for a pulse
is an act of love
but it makes
for a good story.
Love isn't always
so dramatic...
but it is an adventure.
( kissing sounds )
( chuckling )
I just spoke
to Tess Williams.
She's coming home tomorrow.
Oh, good.
Where's Amy?
Oh, she rode her
bike into town.
Oh.
You think Tess knows
the Dewey decimal system?
I bet she could learn.
Mmm.
Why, are you going
to get her a job?
Well, I can try.
David and I
were talking about it.
He thinks
he may know a doctor
who needs a receptionist.
How is David?
Well, I invited him to dinner
but he took a rain check.
You know
he's selling his house?
Where's he going to live?
I saw his sign
on my way back from the market.
Hmm.
Well, maybe he's getting
a bigger place.
Is he seeing anybody?
Don't ask me.
Ask him.
Oh, stop avoiding him,
Di, it's silly.
He cares about you.
He always has.
I know, and I didn't
treat him very well.
I carried a torch for Mark
and David got tired
of being patient.
Why do you think
he's not coming to dinner?
Well, maybe because
I invited him, not you.
Or maybe it's because
he's seeing somebody.
No...
it's just better
that I stay away from him.
All I ever gave David
was a hard time.
Tomorrow's another day,
Scarlett.
She blew her chance.
Amy!
She's here.
Mom!
Oh, Amy!
I missed you so much.
Oh!
Let me look at you.
You look great.
A lot better than
I used to, right?
I feel better, too.
I'm not perfect,
you know.
You don't go in
and come out
and that's it.
I've got
to go to meetings
and... and get
lots of exercise
and I've got
to eat right.
Can't sit around
and get sad.
I got to get a job.
Oh, Amy, I almost lost you.
I'm so sorry.
Would you forgive me?
Mom, I can
exercise with you.
We'll go on walks
and I'll jog
if you want.
That would be great.
I would love that.
You and me,
we're going to make it
right?
Right.
And we can talk about Dad.
I'm a lot braver now.
I'm going home
with my mom now
but I'll be back
to play, okay?
Not in the morning,
because school's starting.
But after school,
sometimes
if I don't have
too much homework.
And every Sunday
with my mom for pancakes.
Mee...
Bye.
Well, it's just you
and me now, kiddo.
But you know what?
We're still going to have fun,
just like we always have.
We'll swim
and we'll take our walks
and we'll sing
and we'll read stories...
Maybe we'll pick out some new
wallpaper for your room, hmm?
I wouldn't trade one minute
we've had together.
Not for all the tea in China.
Do you know how much tea
there is in China?
Oh.
You make my days,
you know that?
Yeah, she knows.
She wants you to know
she says thank you for her life.
She's glad
you're her mom.
She's glad she's here.
She wouldn't
trade you, either.
She loves you, Dianne.
Oh, Amy...
thank you.
Thank you.
Thought I'd
find you here.
Hi.
How are you?
I haven't
seen you lately.
Hannah's been
bringing Julia by.
Oh, yeah. I didn't want
to drive 'cause my knee...
Ah, yes. I talked
to Dr. Lawry,
He's pretty happy
with your progress.
Well, as long
as he's happy...
Do you have a minute?
Or an hour, really?
I made an offer on a house.
I need someone's
excellent opinion.
Sure.
Do you mind?
Yeah, no. No.
Wow.
It's great.
Nice door... oh...
Well, that's easy to fix.
There's good light.
You could do floor-to-ceiling
bookshelves right here.
Yes.
I could...
I could do that.
You could
take these doors off.
You know,
have open shelves?
Or I can make you new ones.
I like the ones
in Hannah's kitchen.
My dad did those.
This is what sold me...
this room here.
It could be a bedroom.
It's two steps
from the kitchen.
It's got an outside door
right there.
It's connected
to the bathroom.
It would
save your back.
My back?
Yeah, if this
were Julia's room.
You wouldn't have to carry her
up and down the stairs.
I've seen you
at your mother's house.
You probably go up and down,
like, a dozen times a day.
Not a very romantic proposal,
is it?
Marry me
and eliminate lower back pain.
It's not how
I was going to say it.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to, uh...
I thought it was too late.
I thought I missed my chance.
I love you.
I want to marry you
I want
to adopt Julia
and I want to live
in this house together.
As a family.
That's what I... I want.
That and bookshelves.
What about you?
That's what
I've always wanted.
Why has it taken me
so long to see it?
Hey, guys!
Hi.
Welcome.
Thanks.
Hi, Julia.
Hi, Hannah.
Hey, Martha.
Hi.
Glad you got here.
Yeah, you've been
waiting for her.
Listen, can you stay
with her for a second?
I want to help Dianne,
if I can find here.
Oh, there you are.
I think everyone's here.
Hey, look.
There she is.
Hello.
Good to see you.
MAN:
Over here. Picture.
Everybody's looking
this way now.
And... smile.
[Captioning sponsored by
CBS
and HALLMARK CARDS
Captioned by
The Caption Center
WGBH Educational Foundation]