Lucky life isn't one long
string of horrors.
And there are moments of peace
and pleasure as I lie
in between the blows.
I can't believe
they lost the photos.
It was so rude of them.
Maybe it's better.
This way it won't affect
how you remember.
Did you pray this morning?
Yes.
What did you pray for?
I can't tell you.
It won't come true.
That's not how it works.
Did you pray for me?
-Yes.
What did you pray?
I can't tell you.
Yes, you can.
Why are your feet always
so cold?
My lizard, my lively writher,
may your limbs never wither.
Know who wrote that?
No.
I was dreaming
about Jason last night.
About when we first went down
to the beach house.
I can see us
talking to each other,
but I can't remember any of
the words we talked about.
You mean in the dream,
or in reality?
Both.
Oh.
I really think this thing
with Jason is affecting you.
Mm-hmm.
You're peeling.
Let me put some lotion
on your face.
I'll get the, um --
It's sunny for a while.
And there's only
a very few showers
on the last day.
Great.
How long does it take us
to get there?
10 hours if I drive.
But if Alex drives, then 8.
I don't want to drive.
What did you say?
Do you want me to pack
your sleeping pills?
No.
-Are you sure?
-Yeah.
-What you thinking about?
-It's a long trip.
Is it okay to wish that we're
the only two people going down?
Jason wants to see you.
He wants to see you, too.
We should call Alex and tell him
not to come pick us up.
Are you joking?
I'm gonna get dressed.
-Hi.
-Hello.
-May I see I.D., please?
-Yes.
I'm 30.
They sell wine.
Yeah? Let me see.
-Looks like shit.
-Yep. Fits in with the spirit.
-Ready to go?
-Yeah.
I'm sure they're right.
They're -- They've told him
it's an aggressive tumor.
And they've told him it's
about extending his life,
about -- about quality of life
at this point.
-How long of a time
do you think that gives him?
Karen?!
Do you still see it?!
It's -- it's way gone.
Come on back.
We do this all the time.
Yeah, I don't think
we should do anything special
or talk about it.
If he wants us to talk about
it, we should talk about it.
But if he wants to ignore it
on this trip,
then we should
respect that, too.
You know, it's probably the
last time we'll have together.
Last week he told me
that he thinks
he's going to be healed by God.
Really?
But if that's what he needs
to believe to feel better,
then...that's fine.
He's got some hard months ahead.
Let's go.
Actually, I do like it better
in terms
of just kind of being on it
and not seeing traffic
rushing at you.
-That's true.
-And being able to actually see
a bridge while
you're on a bridge.
Ah, so you can see water
on both sides.
That's true.
-Hey, yeah.
-Yeah, water on both sides.
Wait, why
aren't you buckled up?
If I'm gonna die by
going off of a bridge...
-I agree.
-...my seatbelt...
I don't want to have it on,
because what if we drowning
and then I can't get out?
-I'd be right there.
-Who will save you all?
Me. I will save you.
-No, 'cause you...
-Are the pyramids concrete?
The pyramids are definitely
not made out of concrete.
Oh, yeah.
Who invented the concrete?
-The Romans. No, the Romans.
-Oh, the Chinese got gunpowder.
-Yes.
-The Romans got concrete.
What about the aqueducts?
Those are concrete.
-That's the Romans.
-But I'm saying, I'm --
I'm on your side.
-I know.
I used to want to build these.
Uh, giant bridges
across ocean?
Well, large or small,
any of them.
It's -- just before.
That just didn't work out so
you decided to become a writer?
No, I decided...
No, yeah. It didn't work out.
Trigonometry was not --
well, no, calculus was harder.
Trig was okay.
But I just stopped.
Yeah, put on your seatbelt.
But I didn't do the last one!
Why do I have to have
a seatbelt on now?
I was just going along
with Alex.
How about if I do this?
That's... Oh.
Oh, so you get decapitated.
Now it's on my back.
I can't find the keys.
You don't need them.
Jason's already in.
You got that stuff?
Yeah, I'll take --
I'll take the groceries.
-Hey, there.
-Hey, you!
-You look beautiful.
-Thank you.
-You got the keys?
-Hey!
You look good.
Thanks. I feel good.
Yeah.
God's doing a whole lot.
With that whole thing.
Yeah.
Thanks for your prayers.
Sure.
What's your, uh, what's your dad
got you up to lately?
Papayas.
That's one of the better ones.
That's good.
Yeah. Yeah. Uh-huh.
-What is that until...
-He's growing papaya trees
in the backyard.
Mm-hmm.
-Of course. Of course.
-Yeah. It's good times.
I'm glad you're here.
It's good to see the two of you.
You're, uh, together.
It's beautiful.
It really is.
Oh, it's warm.
Is it plugged in?
And this is hot.
Uh, let me turn it on.
Is this mine?
I almost hit --
I almost hit...
It's disgusting!
...hit one of those birds
coming over the bridge.
-Oh.
-Yeah.
I was like swerving,
I almost went over the bridge.
That was -- that --
that's nothing.
You got to hear this.
It's almost --
it's almost too gross
to tell at a restaurant, but...
We're done.
We're done. Go on.
Two -- two years ago,
I was in, uh,
in Nevada with a friend
from medical school, right?
And we were late,
and we were sort of driving
through the desert at, like,
must have been around midnight.
Maybe even a bit later.
And, you know,
the desert cools down at night.
So the --
the desert's real cold,
but the road traps the heat.
So the -- the road's
the warm place.
So all the hares come
from the desert and they --
they lie down in the road.
And so you're driving through
and your headlights...
-Uh-oh!
-All you see is, like,
all these bunny rabbits
all across the road.
You know, like...
You know, you can see, like,
50 at any one moment.
Flying through, and --
and you have two choices.
Either -- either you --
you drive at, like,
20 miles an hour
and honk the horn
and put on your bright lights,
or you just...
-Which any...
-...or you just -- just go.
And we -- we were
in a bit of a rush.
Massacre!
You didn't even honk
your horn?
Well, would it have
done any good?
They had places to go!
-Oh.
I ran over
a humongous cat once.
-Thank you.
-That was --
That was definitely...
He was here.
-Yeah. You can't...
-It was just as sad.
It was sadder.
Oh, I'm sorry.
What do you guys
want to do tomorrow?
-Hmm.
-Um...
Why don't we go to
the Wright memorial?
-Okay.
-No.
What do you guys
want to do tomorrow?
-No.
-Have you ever done it?
No, and let's
keep it that way.
I've been in an airplane.
Good enough.
You haven't been
in a bronze airplane
that's stuck to the ground.
That's true. I --
I've never gone there.
You know something
I've never done,
is, uh, see the sun rise
at the beach.
Oh.
You mean, not here on
the Outer Banks.
-No, I mean ever. Anywhere.
-Oh.
-Really?
-We have to do that.
We'll do that.
-Yeah.
And it gets us until,
when, 8:00.
We're done with that.
We still have the whole day.
Yeah, but you only get one...
Let's watch this
and go with...
No! We want to go to Ocracoke!
We want to go to Ocracoke.
-Okay.
-Yeah, yeah.
-Sounds good.
-All right.
Say it again?
Ocracoke.
That's a plant.
So I'm always
the last one to hear.
The book.
What's going on?
Yeah, um...
Well, I sent --
I sent off the manuscript
to several agents.
And, uh, I ended up choosing one
who I'm fairly comfortable with.
Um, and so we signed --
we signed up.
-Yeah?
-Yeah.
-That's great.
-Yeah, uh...
-Fantastic.
-It feels a lot better
than it did a couple weeks ago,
when --
when we didn't have it.
Um, we've been kind of feeling
the crunch
with the post-wedding bills.
Um...
So it's -- it's nice.
Yeah.
-Congratulations!
-Thanks. Thank you.
-You deserve it.
-Thanks.
-It's high tide this year.
There's hardly any beach.
The family in the A-frame
had to move out.
Yeah?
They're gonna knock it down.
Are they at least rebuilding?
-So what'd you talk about?
-Not much.
Do you know
where my toothbrush is?
You put it in the bathroom.
I heard Jason talking
to himself.
"The one thing in life."
"Wherever I go now, I lie down
on my own bed of straw
and bury my face
in my own pillow."
"I can stop in any city
I want to
and pull the stiff blanket up
to my chin."
"It's easy now.
Walking up a flight
of carpeted stairs
and down a hall,
past the painted fire doors."
"It's easy bumping my knees
on a rickety table
and bending down
to a tiny sink."
"There is a sweetness
buried in my mind."
"There is water
with a small cave behind it.
There is a mouth
speaking Greek."
"It is what I keep to myself.
What I return to.
The one thing
that no one else wanted."
I don't think I get it.
You do?
Let's go to sleep.
Hit the light.
Yes. Yes.
Yes. Yes, God.
Bless the lord, oh, bless.
Bless the lord.
And all that is within you,
bless his holy name.
Yes.
Bless the lord, oh, my soul,
forget not all his benefits,
forget not
all his benefits.
Who forgives all my sins,
heals all my diseases,
redeems my life
from the pit.
Alex has definitely...
changed a lot more this year.
I was thinking that, too.
He seems different
from how it...
-Yeah.
I mean, even his clothing
is slightly less pressed.
It is.
I think that's a good way
to describe him:
-...less pressed.
-Less pressed.
Probably a little bit
to do with,
you know, you and Karen.
Just like seeing the two
of you guys get married.
I think it's affected all of us.
Especially at the wedding,
you know?
It's just beautiful, and so...
I think he's sort of looked
at his life a little bit.
I think we all did.
I think it was also maybe you.
I don't really talk to, uh,
well, the old crowd, you know?
I just can't really talk
to everybody right now.
Yeah.
I'm so sick of,
like, people calling me
because they think it's the last
time they're gonna talk to me.
What is that?
It's like they're defeated.
I just don't have time for that.
Yeah.
Earth's crammed with heaven
and every common bush
afire with God.
But only he who sees,
takes off his shoes.
Where'd you learn that?
You.
I learned it from you.
Salt is the only thing
that lasts on this island.
It gets into the hair,
into the eyes,
into the clothes,
into the wood, into the metal.
Everything is going
to disappear here but the salt.
I like to think of myself
turned to salt
and all that
I love turned to salt.
I like to think of coating
whatever is left
with my own tongue and fingers.
I like to think of floating
again in my first home...
...still remembering
the warm rock
and its slow destruction...
...still remembering
the first conversion
to blood and the forcing
of the sea
into those cramped vessels.
Man, it's getting windy.
-Beautiful waves, though.
-Mm-hmm.
We should go swim in there.
Oh, I got the key.
This light -- do you think
this light's out?
Did that work last night?
It just takes a while.
Here, I'll --
I'll try this one.
Huh. This switch
doesn't work either.
Does that one?
Hmm.
Where's the fusebox
in this house?
It's, um...
I bet it's over
by the bedroom.
-Yeah. No, it's in the kitchen.
-Let me get a flashlight.
Right.
-It's romantic.
-There you go.
Because we want to get
the scent out of all of them.
Oh, I can't get
a flame on mine.
Got to go to the source.
Come on.
I don't know if this counts
as a ghost story,
but, uh...
my father actually
told me a story one time.
And he -- he -- he --
and he's not the kind of guy
who makes stuff up,
I mean, ever.
He, you know. He never
exaggerates for anything.
Um, but he told me once,
when they were still
living in Kingston
in this really big apartment
complex,
um, before it got rough,
you know, uh,
real communal environment.
And, uh, he and this girl
were really tight.
And I'd heard him mention before
that she had
actually been killed,
really bad situation.
At that time, that didn't --
didn't really happen very much.
Um, his parents went to be
with the family.
And I guess they were
making arrangements.
And he came back to the, uh,
apartment complex alone.
And, uh...
yeah, he swears on this.
The girl that was killed,
his friend,
um, he saw her figure
in the courtyard,
saw her dancing circles,
just dancing.
And he just stood there,
watching.
And he never says
anything like that.
And, uh...
I just can't imagine
he would make that up.
-This feels so good.
-Yeah?
Yeah, get back in shape.
Yeah, if you want to get back
in shape,
then I'm not sure
running's the right thing.
It's a start.
You know what I mean?
Yeah, but, you know,
why don't you choose something
that you're actually gonna do?
You know, just go for a walk.
5 times a week, 30 minutes
a day, that's all you need.
-I mean...
I just really feel good.
I'm gonna get serious.
What are you doing?
-I run.
Are you really gonna do it?
-Yeah.
I'll see how I feel.
-I -- I have never seen you
run before my whole life.
Used to make fun of me
when I went out
with my running shoes
back in college.
And now you're telling me
you want to go for a run.
-That's 'cause
you wore spandex.
I'm not gonna run far.
You know what I mean?
I just want to...
I -- I just want to get moving.
I hate sitting inside.
I want to get moving.
-Yeah, let's go out.
You want to go running today?
-Cool.
-Hey, good morning,
sleepy head.
-Good morning.
Would you sirs
like any more coffee?
-No thanks. I'm all set.
-I'm good.
-Okay.
-So you still think
that bed's too soft?
-Yeah.
I don't like it that much.
Hurts my back a little.
Let's go out there on the deck.
-Don't even!
I made you a present.
-No, he doesn't trust me.
-No!
-I wasn't gonna
do anything to you.
I was just gonna give it to you.
-Whoa!
-Come on!
-Come on, man!
-Who lives
in this castle, anyway?
-We do.
-We do?
-I've brought topiaries.
-Oh, man.
What's this right here, Jason?
-Uh...this...
is an amphitheater.
-Oh!
-That's cool, actually.
-Yeah, and I'm gonna put
some tiers in here.
-Uh-huh.
-For the seating.
And I'm trying
to make the stage.
So the actors...
-That's nice.
-And the players will be here.
-I can make the people
for your stage.
Look, look!
Little grass people.
-The people are us.
We live in this city.
-It's us.
-I'm also building
a sports arena.
We can't have two sports
arenas in one castle.
-No, that's a theater.
-This is for...
-Oh, it's for theater.
-Yeah.
-So we can do all that gladiator
stuff over here.
-Yeah, no gladiator stuff here.
-Okay.
-This is only....
-That's good to know.
-I would love to live
in this city back then. Nice.
-Yeah. I bet it would b--
it would be real nice
until there's a siege.
Half your family
gets killed by war. And then...
-I've got -- I've got walls up.
-Okay.
But then the other half
of your family dies
from plague and pestilence.
I think most people
don't know that.
That actually cities,
you know, wasn't that
they were constantly under siege
and that everyone died in war.
They actually didn't really
fight that often in the cities.
And, you know, some generations,
it's, like,
60% of people died
in the plague.
Or even just dysentery. That was
a common household thing,
to lose two
or three kids to dysentery.
Now, these are just -- they're
just diseases of progress.
Everyone moves to the cities.
Suddenly, they have work.
They have enough food.
And then the plague hits.
-I'm gonna take a shower.
Hi.
-Wait.
-What?
-Wait. I think they're back.
-Hmm.
-It's not them.
-Okay, good.
-I think this goes, like...
Watch your head.
...this.
And this fits in this.
And two planks in between them.
Maybe these. Right?
-These go on the bottom?
-Yeah.
-Right.
-I think...
See, they go in between here.
Yeah.
Something like that.
-Mm-hmm.
Just push, uh,
just steady push a little.
Thanks.
That's fine.
That's -- that's steady enough.
-Do you know what this is for?
-Yes, I do.
-It's for --
it's for our little peanut.
-Yes.
-And he will sleep there
every night until it's 18.
That's okay.
-Just put your side.
And I'll do this side.
-But there's something that
might need to be fixed
before we finish the middle.
-What?
-I think that corner.
-What about it?
-It's not in.
-Yeah, I know, but...
-It's best to use corners.
-You're right.
-Whoa!
-Shit.
-I don't think
that's the next piece.
-It goes right here.
-Yeah, but...
-I'm just looking
to see how it works.
-Okay.
-This...
Hmm. Okay.
-The manual says
to do these pieces first.
-I know that.
That's fine.
-You know,
I can do this myself.
I -- I don't mind.
I -- I want to do it.
-You want to do this yourself?
-Yeah, I don't want
to do it this --
the style that you're doing it.
I want it to go slow
and enjoy it.
-You -- you want...
-So it's fine. I'll do it.
-I just... Okay.
Um, I don't think you can,
all the way through right now.
-Well, that doesn't show
a lot of faith in me.
-Okay. I'll watch --
I'll watch you do this bit.
Would you like me to hold that
for you while you do the thing
that you know
you're supposed to do?
-Yeah, now, get the other one.
Oop! Sorry.
Okay.
Now get me some of these.
-I could help you,
but I'm holding this
because you told me
to hold this.
-It's not those.
Can we please just do this
without fighting?
-Yes, I have no problem
doing it without fighting.
I just want to do it.
-Just be a little gentler.
-Fine.
-That's okay.
-You're gonna
rub your knuckles.
-Go slow. Hold on.
Let's go like this.
-Our little person will be
a very good swimmer.
You dressed up?
-Yeah, I -- I thought
I would look nice tonight.
-What time are they coming?
-Around 7:00.
And so I'm feeling guilty about
finding someone else attractive.
And then I realize it is Mark.
And I'm awful.
-Oh, my God.
-But I was really excited.
I was like, "Yay,
he's still really hot and sexy!"
But this has happened to me
numerous times, actually.
-It was getting so bad
that I --
we go out to dinner,
saying she's --
if she saw a pregnant woman,
she'd start to cry.
And we couldn't --
we couldn't even finish dinner.
-Oh, no.
-And it happens,
you know, several times.
-S-so you just stayed home.
-Yeah.
-Oh, man.
-It was depressing.
-Thank God it worked out.
-It did.
I mean, you know, we -- we...
My friend told me
about a place in --
in Iceland.
I, uh, what was it called?
In vitro clinic.
-Why Iceland?
-They have, uh,
supposedly,
a wonderful in vitro clinic.
I -- I'm not familiar
with the ins and outs of...
-So if it hadn't all
worked out,
you'd be up in some,
like, snowy fertility clinic?
-Yeah.
-Oh, my God.
Well, so are you ready
for everything to change?
-Am I ready?
-Ready to actually
gonna have --
actually have to wake up
in the morning.
-Yeah.
-Can't sleep till noon.
-Yeah. I sleep --
I don't sleep till noon.
I sleep till, like, 10:00.
That's my normal. But...
-Yeah?
-I-It will.
It'll be different.
I'm -- I like just writing,
thinking about the next story,
um, going to this --
this wonderful café nearby.
Um, I get a lot done, I think.
-Yeah.
-Other writers are there.
It's just a really
comfortable place.
I spend most of my day there.
-I don't remember the last time
when I sat down to drink
a cup of coffee.
Just not a doctor's life.
Man.
Yeah, I'm jealous.
I hope someday I have the chance
to slow down a bit more.
-Yeah.
I hope so, too.
-I -- I suddenly just wanted all
the things that we talked about,
like, this full life
that we had planned.
And I was worried
that I was gonna leave him.
And I -- I don't know.
It was --
it was really weird.
-Yeah, something changes
when you have
someone to live for, I think.
-Yeah, I mean, the --
the -- the reason
I don't want to die young
is, uh,
because I don't want her
to marry another guy.
Um, I -- I -- I know she could
do better than me.
And, uh, I just, uh,
don't want her to realize that.
-I thought you just didn't want
her to have sex
with anyone else.
-That's exactly
what I'm talking about.
Even -- even --
even the thought of that, uh,
drives me crazy, you know.
-Sam's ready for more wine.
-We've just started.
-He's always ready.
-I can't wait
to have wine again.
-I'm sorry.
-Soon, very soon.
All right.
This is from Yo and Kyoko.
-Please.
-Oh, what is this?
Is that a squid?
-Um...
-Uh...
-Looks like a mushroom.
No, no, no.
-Is it a blanket or one
of those little snuggly things?
-It's a blanket.
-Oh, it's beautiful!
-I like the color.
-Yeah.
Does that mean
we're gonna have a boy?
-It doesn't matter.
-Or...
-They can have
any color they want.
-An androgynous girl?
-Or androgynous boy is fine.
-Let's see what it is.
Oh, it's a flying heart!
-Aw.
-That's very sweet.
-That's better than squid.
-Yeah.
-I kind of like squid, too.
I'll settle for the heart.
-That's very nice.
Oh, that's great. It reminds me
of a children's book.
-Thank you.
-Sure.
-Kind of illustration.
Thank you.
-It cost us $2,000.
-$2,000?
I'll have to give you something.
-All righty.
This is from you guys.
Do you want to pull
the other side of the bow?
-Yes. I'm folding. But yes.
-Okay. I won't wait for you.
-I'm sorry.
-Okay.
It's one of these.
-It's stuck.
-Yeah.
-It's something that's silver.
-Who's it from?
-It's from Alex and Lillian.
-Oh.
Tempting.
-Ooh, it -- it makes noises.
-Wow.
Oh, wow.
Isn't that beautiful?
-This is your selection,
Lillian? I assume?
-I had nothing to do with it.
It was Alex.
-Wow.
-Really?
-Way to go, doc.
-Wow, good choice. Pretty.
-Mm-hmm.
-Thanks, guys.
-Congratulations, both of you.
-Thank you, guys,
very much for coming.
-Sure.
-Of course.
-It means a lot.
Is the smoke getting to you?
Sorry.
I was just thinking
that I, um...
...I don't even remember
Jason's face anymore.
Hey.
You know what
I was reading today?
I saw that there are
numerous cases of malaria
outbreaks along
the eastern coast.
They found several down
in Hatteras, in Jersey.
It's really weird.
We'll have to uptake
our gin and tonic.
That way, uh...
What's up?
How was your day?
-What the hell's going on?
What's up?
What's going on?
It's all right.
It's okay.
-This morning, I --
I found blood in my underwear.
-What?
How much blood?
-Let me see it.
We need to go to the hospital.
-I'm sorry.
-We need to go to the hospital.
-I just need a minute.
I just need to pull myself
together a little bit.
-Mm-hmm.
-Should we transfer
to the C at Jay Street?
-No, I think we can take a cab.
I made it with cardamom.
-Thank you.
-"I am sick of the spirit
of Lindbergh over everything."
-Can -- can we skip it tonight?
-I'd like to go back
to the beach house soon.
-Yeah. I'd like that.
The last time
we were there was with Jason.
Do you remember?
He died so soon after that trip.
-Hey.
-Hi.
-Welcome to the studio.
-Thank you.
-These are beautiful.
Thanks so much.
It's all made right here.
-How much?
-Um, $18.95.
And that comes with the scroll
that I think you were reading.
-Yeah.
-Do you make a lot of them?
-I do.
Uh, they're very popular,
very popular, about 75 a week.
-Hey.
-I want to get this one.
-Oh, great. Terrific.
Let me get you the scroll, too.
-Okay. Is that the, uh,
one from the wall?
-Yeah, it comes with that.
It's kind of fun.
Why don't I wrap
that up for you?
-Okay.
Hey, I really appreciate
the, uh, the article.
-Oh, thank you.
-Yeah.
-Yeah. Um, that's what I had
to go through.
-I'm, uh, I'm actually
gonna be starting chemo
in a couple weeks, 2 1/2 weeks.
-I know where you're at.
Got to be strong.
And you're not alone, you know.
Oh, so you stay strong, okay?
I'll be praying for you.
-Thank you.
-Are you here relaxing
before you...
-Mm-hmm.
-Well, good.
-Well, I'm just hanging out
with my friends.
-Good.
-Um, we come --
we come here every year, so...
-Great.
-That's $20.23.
-♪ You know, I think
they're always best ♪
♪ Playin' my bones ♪
-♪ Like xylophones ♪
-♪ Playin' my bones ♪
♪ Like xylophones ♪
Here it comes.
This is gonna be
the time to shine.
-Oh.
-♪ Come right in ♪
-♪ My luminary fairy ♪
-♪ I am -- ♪
-♪ A charlatan ♪
-♪ Terry query ♪
Do it again. Do it again.
-All right.
♪ Come right in ♪
-♪ My luminary fairy ♪
-Mm.
-Aw, sh-- I messed up.
-And...
-♪ Come right in ♪
-"Dear waves,
what will you do
for me this year?"
"Will you drown out my scream?"
"Will you let me rise
through the fog?"
Will you fill me
with that old salt feeling?"
-So how long are you
gonna cook the corn?
-20 minutes, 20 minutes
and a stick of butter.
-No, no, no, no.
That's disgusting.
It'll be really, really mushy.
-I don't want...
I like this place and...
-Great. But, yeah, you --
you like it
'cause your aunt's put
the money into it.
That's why.
-I don't know if I need
to put the kind of money
that she's been putting into it.
And I just think
I have a simpler vision
of what this place is.
-A romantic vision
of living in,
uh, this artist's paradise then?
-Yeah.
-Well, I'll come visit...
...for a week a year.
But I wouldn't want to
live down here. That's for sure.
-I wouldn't want to live here
permanently or anything
like that.
But I'd like to have it.
I'd really like having a place
like this to go to.
And I like, you know...
I mean, you're right.
It's romantic. But I think
that that -- that's a positive.
You know, living out in an area
where, obviously,
it seems like it could kind of
almost collapse, um...
...and maybe not buying
insurance, something.
I don't anything about these --
these insurance quibbles.
But I kind of would like
to kind of have a place
where you don't have that.
-It sounds romantic until
the day the hurricane comes
and knocks it over.
-Right.
Well, as long as I wasn't inside
of it, maybe that would be okay.
-But then it's gone.
-Right.
-It's the same rule
as the corn?
-Yeah.
You know, I think
you're a pretty good cook.
-Dinner's ready.
-If you found a live one,
like, there was --
there was, like,
a rule, you throw it back.
I guess that's what you're
doing. You're not gonna eat it.
-A rule -- a rule of humanity?
-You would...
No, there was all these people,
like, gathering around
because they would
see this lady that I saw.
And then they -- they would
see us with the conch shells.
And they'd be like,
"Oh, what's going on here?"
And then they would, like,
sort of hang around,
like, look what we were doing.
And every time the tide would,
like, roll back,
we'd all,
like, scoot towards the shore.
He was, like, it was
a little vicious, you know.
If you saw one,
you would dive for it.
I'm serious.
It was intense.
This young couple came by.
They looked like they're from,
you know, New York or something.
They're all trendy.
And he was, like,
asking me questions.
And I'm like, "Yeah,"
giving 'em short answers.
You know what I mean?
-"Get out of my sight."
-'Cause, you know,
you see, like,
one every, like, few minutes.
So, yeah, I got, like, four.
I wanted to get
some more, though.
The beautiful ones were the ones
that were still living.
Anytime I saw one with, like,
purple hue and white,
I'd reach for it and grab it.
But then you'd see the --
the meaty flesh inside.
And you're like, "Okay."
So you throw it back
as far as you can.
And, um, all the --
the darker-colored ones
are the ones I ended up with.
But they're still
really beautiful.
It's neat.
I'm glad it happened today.
You need some more of this.
Last drop.
-Oh. You know, so, actually,
I had something
I want to tell you guys.
Guess now is the time.
So, just before I left New York,
I went out and bought a ring.
I'm gonna ask Lillian
to marry me next week.
-Wow.
-All right!
-That's great.
-Hope she says yes.
-Of course she's gonna say yes.
I knew he had something...
-Mm.
-Something brewing since
the weekend began.
-When did you decide this?
-What do you mean?
When --
when did I buy the ring?
-No. When did you decide
that you wanted to get married?
-I mean, I've been thinking
about it probably
since the moment I met her.
Somehow, it just, uh,
it felt right.
-Mm-hmm.
-Felt right.
I'm a doctor now.
Now, I...
Somehow I always thought that
I had to get the career
nailed down first
and then, you know,
when I was 40,
think about wife and family.
But -- but now that
I have Lillian,
I just feel like, you know,
I can't imagine
doing it without her.
Yeah.
-Does she know it's coming?
-I mean, of course she does.
-All right. Here we go.
-All right. Come on.
Come on, USA.
-Get back, Whitney.
-Come on.
-Get away! G--
-Here.
-Get away! Get away!
-Yay!
-Watch.
-Take cover.
-I like that.
I like what's
happening right now.
-I'm disappointed.
You're just disappointed?
-It's not over!
-Just smoke.
-That's good.
-That's just
very disappointing.
-All right.
I'm getting the next one.
-Get outta there.
-Whoa! Something's...
-Ah, see, that's cool.
-I like that.
-Aw.
-It's like the last one.
-No, it's better.
-That's the Georgia Peach?
-That was definitely better.
-I guess it's a little better.
-I kind of wish this
one did stop for a second.
-Gonna go up.
-I want this one to stop.
-Whoa!
-I am able to zero in
on these days
with more clarity now
so that not one detail is lost,
as if the clarity
illuminated the pain,
as if the pain decreased
where the clarity took over,
as if the clarity were taking
the place of the pain.
♪ Great is thy faithfulness ♪
♪ Morning by morning ♪
♪ New mercies I see ♪
♪ Whatever I have needed... ♪
♪ Great is thy faithfulness ♪
♪ Glory is mine ♪
-Actually, if it rains
next year,
that's when
you should be fishing.
Show the locals what's up.
-Fish in the middle of the lake
while it's raining?
-I mean, go bayside,
you know?
Like that one spot
that we found at sunset?
I'd love to build something,
too, you know, something small,
maybe where no one else
will find it.
But we know where it is,
above the paths.
-We could go down to the --
the Kill Devil Path,
down to the trees,
that bike path.
-Yeah.
-That's pretty isolated.
-Many moons. Okay.
-Oh, come on.
Got to think.
What does the woman want?
She's definitely...
Oh, come on.
I think she'd love it.
I don't know about Lillian
diving off the coast of,
-...you know, New Zealand.
-Oh, I think...
Well, maybe not New Zealand,
but, like, Thailand maybe.
Dude, this is what
I'm talking about,
going the other direction.
All right.
It's time to pack.
"But he, the rain god,
is sobbing uncontrollably.
Sick drops are coming
from his eyes.
And he is gasping.
And, finally,
his arms alone are moving.
And he is in the center
of a huge circle on his hands
and knees, pounding the earth.
Dry gasps are coming
from his throat
and a trickle of thin water
from his mouth...
...while, all around him,
violets are springing up
in the dirty cinders
and giant thistles
and strings of chicory
and daisies to pay him
for his tears,
to pay the old god
for his tears...
...apart from everything else,
to pay him for his tears."
When we were singing tonight
and looking out
into the ocean...
...I've never felt
as empty as that.
-Is everyone smiling?
-Yes.
Okay, here we go.
Two, three...
-Okay.
-Yeah!
-All right, all right!
Let's do it.
Let's go right here.
One more!
I'm gonna get one more.
With just Mark and Karen.
-Okay. Okay.
-And you kind of -- yeah.
Smile big.
One, two, three!
-A lucky life is like this.
-That's great.
Lucky there is
an ocean to come to.
Lucky you can judge yourself
in this water.
Lucky the waves are cold enough
to wash out the meanness.
Lucky you can be purified
over and over again.
Lucky there is the same
cleanliness for everyone.
Lucky life is like that.
Lucky life.
Oh lucky life.
Oh lucky, lucky life.
Lucky life.