Your call has been forwarded to
an automatic voice message system
At the tone please record your message.
- Hey, got your message.
Is everything okay?
I'm coming over.
- Jesse what...
- Don't come any fucking closer
- Okay
Okay, I...I just wanna talk
- You don't understand okay. Uhm...I'm...
I am confused
I've been having these feelings but...
but I know know that it's a sin
and that it's wrong
but, look, you gotta promise
not to tell anyone, okay?
- Where are you parents?
- What?
- Where are your parents?
- What the fuck does that matter?
They probably told the whole
goddamn church about me
- He did hit you again?
- It was my fault
-  No Jesse, it' s not your fault
- I deserved it
- My dad, he can help
- Don't you get it
He's already signed me up
for his correctional therapy
- What?...What therapy?
- You should know golden boy
I'm gonna pop to the fucking pious
He's gonna fix me with his Jesus powers
- Look Jesse, you're drunk,
you're not thinking straight
It's going to be okay,
I can tell
- But you can't
I'm a freak
- Don't!
- Listen, just listen
- No, it's gonna be okay.
I'm calling someone for help
- No...I love you
Don't hit me
- No Jesse,
I love you for you