(synthetic crescendo)
(robot shit cranking)
(cinematic riser)
(thunder clappin')
(double serious music)
(wet shit pourin')
(thunder rollin')
(double serious music)
(thunder crack-a-lacking)
- Stone cold sober.
- Yet another hashtag, times up.
- Let's peace,
Before the Wet Shit gets us too.
(sick AF rock music)
(techno building)
(peeps chitty-chatting)
(dramatic ass rock music)
- Yo, welcome home, CHAI-T!
- It's JTRO. JTRO's BACK!
- CHAI-T.
- JTRO, MAN! JTRO!
- Hey lady, how ya doing?
It's good to see you.
- What sup?
What sup?
- Oh my God, CHAI-T.
- Namaste, 'n Shit.
(Alarm pops off)
- RAGE and RENINJ, come from the sky, yo.
- [Crowd Bro] From up above.
- From the Gods of the sky and shit.
But RENINJ is our God.
Ya heard?
- (crowd together) YEUH!
- Feel that shit. Believe that shit.
- (crowd together) I Believe
it. Got it inside of me!
- Good, now let that
shit into your hearts.
(Big ass chest pounds)
- The wet shit's coming, y'all.
[Crowd] Fuckin' Wet Shit!
- So, knees down and pray up, ninjas.
- [Crowd Bro] Let's go.
- We got you RENINJ.
(whispers) We got you.
(Crowd resumes Chitty-Chats)
(Rager music rages)
(crowd cheering)
- Ima be up on that wall!
(laughing)
- Sup?
- How's it Looking out
there, any survivors?
(Spooky Ass Choir shit)
Let's hope tomorrow goes
like it's supposed to.
(Double Serious Fist Pounds)
(Lightning Claps 'n Shit)
(Thunder says what up)
(Dopest AF training music of all timez)
(FP Peeps Chant Grunting
in unison 'n shit)
(Dopest AF training music
of all timez CONTINUES)
(GONG BITCH)
(Group Grunt Chanting Intensifies, yo!)
(Captain Pigtails Approves)
(Sound FX Overload for tripple
serious Character intro shit)
(Group Chant grunting returns)
(Dopest AF training music
of all timez #KILLING IT)
(Group Chant Grunting goes BIG)
(Dopest AF training music
of all timez CONTINUES)
- Mother fucker.
- Goin' somewhere?
- Yeah, duh.
- Don't you duh, me, young lady.
Where do ya think you're going?
- Where evz, B-F-D
I'm 18.
I'm a sheila, now.
I do what I want.
- Do you have any idea
what could happen to you out there?
- Don't give an eff.
I'm 18, I'm ready to
become a Beat-Beat Massa.
Just like you and MUM-CHAI.
- Oh and it's that easy?
You just turn 18
and become a Beat-Beat Massa.
Just like that?
- I don't know.
You tick with me.
- Yeah, I'm tick with you.
Don't you care what would happen,
if you just split town
without telling anybody?
What that would do to your mum?
- I care.
- Well caring silently,
doesn't mean shit, CHAI-TRO.
Look, I don't care
how much booshit you got goin' on either.
Okay. 'cause we all does.
If you don't tell peeps that you care,
they just assume you don't.
Your mum is very sensitive
and tonight it's very important to her.
You understand me?
- I know.
- Good.
'sides if you skipped town,
who's gonna teach you
how to Beat-Beat, huh?
- You're gonna train me?
- I'll think about.
Come on, run along,
finish your chores from UNCLE-DC
I'll see you, tonight.
- Thanks DAD-TRO.
- H-B-D yo.
(Smooth AF music and Thunder 'n Shit)
(CHAI-TRO knocking)
- Yo, Unc.
Knock, knock, yo.
What the fuck is that booshit?
- Some top seek shit,
I found on one of my old adventures N-B-D.
- Word.
Mum said ya had something for me,
to pick up for the party.
- Awh yeuh.
(Rummages Through Shit)
- What's this?
- None of your bees wax, girl.
(Prezzie Jingles and Jangles)
- No peekin', neither.
Or your mum will slit my ass.
You heard?
- Yeah, yeah.
(thunder BLASTS yo)
- It's a'ight.
That shit's far off.
- Uncle DC,
why is RENINJ mugging us off like this?
- Well, sometimes the gods,
they just blind to our pain
and deaf to our sorrows.
Yo.
Sometimes, they just testing us,
tryin' to push our asses, ya know?
Prophecies told of a flood,
to wipe us off the world's ass and shit,
but some other prophecies rapped about
something that could stop all that bull.
- Like what?
- Once upon a someday,
a Beat-Beat Massa
with ancient ass blood would rise up.
Some SHE-RO of time,
who would Beat-Beat shit so fast,
that she would move
time with her feet, yo.
Makin' time her bitch and shit.
Ya know stories, yo.
I'm just here, on the ground,
livin' that real shit.
- I feel you.
- You take good care of that shit.
- For true.
- H-B-D, yo.
See you tonight and shit.
- Lates.
(Happy ass music)
(thunder roaring)
(Burfday music)
(yipping and yelling 'n shit)
- What does it take
to get a fucking drink around here?
- Welcome to CHAI-TRO's
little Soiree De La T'wa.
Eighteen and shit, y'all heard?
Legal A-F.
- This fucking bullshit again?
You know How many times have I been coming
to this God damn bar?
Guess who throws a birthday for me?
Who's fucking buyin' me a drink?
- Its getting hot in here,
especially in the South.
Little moisture in the south...
- I'm just worried about her.
- Whether you like it or not,
she's a RENINJ.
We can't keep her in
our joey pouches forevz.
- I know.
But you know what day it is
and we've spent a really long time
preparing for tonight.
- Yeah, I know all this,
blah, blah, blah shite.
You've got to let her go, JTRO.
- I know.
But CHAI.
What the fuck comes after tonight?
What the fuck happens after this?
- We check-a-do. Togethz.
Hey, calm-a-do.
- [Drunk] Yeah-Hooo.
- Awe, Omega Awks.
P-D-Fuckin' A.
- Oh, you got your Prezzie.
- Is that what this shit is?
- Obvi. Tear them wraps.
- Oh. What the jangle?
Is this what I think it is?
- Hundo P, grade A,
beat-beat ninjawa bracelet.
- A thousand generations of CHAI's live on
within that bracelet.
- My mumzies gave it to
me when I was of age-ies
and now I gives it to youse.
- For Reals?
Can I try it on?
- Yeah. I mean, that's the idea, right?
(music gets all magical AF)
- Can I have a mummy-do with little CHAI?
- Yeah, of course.
- Some Sheila's were very special
back in the wastes, CHAI-TRO.
When they came of ageies,
they were touched by RENINJ
and they became ninjawas.
- Ninja what-a-s?
- Ninjawas, they were my peeps.
And yours too.
- Oh yeah, I 'member?
Wasn't you they queen?
- Yas.
But thanks to your Papa-do,
we found our homezies
and we became one with the FP.
- That's so fucking tight.
- Watch your mouth.
- Sorry MUM-CHAI.
I just wish I could do something tight,
like you and daddy-do.
- You will.
On a ninjawas 18th BD.
She becomes a warrior
and her Beat-Beat training begins.
- For reals?
- For reals, H-B-D my CHAI-TRO.
- I L U V you, MUM-CHAI!
- I L U V youse.
The mostest.
- Oh, Training? For beat-beat?
How about butt-butt?
Kiss my butt-butt, you fuckers.
I should be running this God damn town.
- (trip serious electronic music)
- Yo JTRO. It's time.
- I know.
- What's the haps?
- There's somethin' we got to show you.
- What sorta somethin'.
(music implies serious shit is comin')
(thunder roaring)
- I thought y'all closed the mines,
'cause the FP went green.
- Nah, he closed the mines
after we found this shit.
(big ass epic sci-fi reveal swell)
- What the H E dubba L?
- The ancients called
it the remix revelation.
It came to our world a
whole bunch of 365s ago.
- You can read all that shit?
- I speak quack Baby-TRO.
BFD
- All right.
The remix revelation brought
Beat-Beat to our world
and started all them beat-wars.
After all that bull ended,
this shit got lost A-F to legend.
Until now.
- Yeah, yeah.
I heard all about them beat-wars before.
Some ancient civilization
from the way backs, that got lost to time,
Called like...
Quactopia or....
- CHAI-Quacktica.
Exacts.
- So.
What does this thing do, hey?
(explosion)
- [Game Announcer] Three.
Two.
One.
Remix.
(big time travel noises 'n shit)
(time travel noises turn up to 11 'n shit)
(remix revelation blastin' at full power)
(time rewinding sounds)
(chill music)
(beat-off alarm sounding)
- [Game Announcer]
Mission launch, good luck.
(screaming)
(BOOM YO!)
(beat-off alarm sounding)
- Awe, give me a minute.
That was my first time
getting launched out
of a fucking beat-cannon.
Awh, my back.
- DAD-TRO?
- Wait, what?
Dad, why the fuck are you calling me dad?
- Are you going deaf or something?
You heard me.
It's me, your effin' daughter.
- What the fuck?
- I know, what the fuck?
- Watch your mouth.
How old are you?
- Eighteen and change.
- Yeah, how much change?
- A couple of HRS's.
What about you J-POPS?
- Eighteen and a bunch of change.
- It aint about how much change you got,
it's about how you spend it.
- Okay, look, I can't
even with you, right now.
You were a baby two days ago.
- Whoa, this is hevs.
- Yeah, what's going on, here?
Spit it out.
- I think I just remixed through time.
- What?
- I was just in one time
and now I'm in this time.
- Excuse me?
- You and Uncle DC,
just found this
old ancient ass beat-beat machine.
In the mines called like,
the remix revelation or whatevs.
- The remix-a-what-a?
- I don't know.
- Oh, this is just perfect.
Figuring out time travel, really
isn't something I wanted to
fucking have to deal with today.
Wait a second.
I recognize that bracelet.
- Oh TLDR,
where's mum?
(explosion)
- Oh shit!
(gasps)
BOOM YO!
(beat-off alarm sounding)
- You okay?
- Fresh Plus
Wait, is this your first time
getting shot out of a beat-cannon?
- What do you think?
- Wow, you catch an attitude quick.
- Jesus.
- Who's this?
- Oh, this is our uh,
this is our daughter
from the future, apparently.
- What?
- Yeah.
(obvious tension builds)
- Okay, this is a way to O-T-T for me.
- [Game Announcer] Three.
Two.
One.
Escape.
(undrunks roaring with thirst)
- What the cone-head?
- We have to skip-o, now.
(undrunks roaring with thirst)
- Look, we'll explain on the way.
Let's go.
(undrunks roaring with thirst)
- [Jim Scary] How it do BAKO Deadlands.
This is your boy, Jim Scary.
- And it's your boy,
Tom Softy, coming at you
live from the drift zone.
- Welcome to another dipstickin'
edition of Escape From BAKO.
Bounty hunters from all up
across the wastes
cash in on captured beat-beaters
and toss them over to
BAKO for Re-Hab-ilitation
(dope ass level select music)
- [Jim Scary] Three vicious rounds
of out running, undrunk prisoners of old.
Who will reach the Comet Of Dawn
in the center of BAKO,
knee deep in the Quatro-Cano
and win their mo' suckin' freedum?
Who it gonna be tonight?
The CHAI-TROS vs. AK-47
and the bro-bot of legend,
himself with a cracking new rig,
L Dubba E.
- Yo! Check this shit out, Dr. Bitch!
- Let's go fucking L I V.
(classic running away music)
(for real ass storm noises)
- What the hell are we out here
doing all this for?
- I don't know.
Ask your mum.
She's the one that thought
getting tossed in here
with a bunch of Beat-Beat bounty hunters
was such a great idea.
- Oh excuse me.
L Dubba E's just trying to
raise the beat-beat god,
who wants to 1-8-7 Earf
and start round two of
The beat-wars.
- Yeah, trying.
How about we wait until he actually
fucking does something, first?
- Unlike you, when shit gets hot,
I don't wait for it get hotter.
- Jesus, come on.
- Yo Rents! Fuckin' Refresh-ify,
we've got bigger probs.
(undrunks roaring with thirst)
- (both together) Watch you mouth.
- They look hungry.
- They're not hungry, they're thirsty.
- What?
- Nevermind.
Doesn't matter.
- We're almost at the first barrier.
(storm noises gettin' serious)
Time to turn on the gas.
- My gas is turned on.
What the F?
- Look, your mum's in a mood right now.
Okay.
Just jump on.
- What?
- Just jump on my God damn back,
so we can outrun these fuckers
in the booze storm. Okay?
- Oh fuck!
- Yeah, oh fuck, now get on, now.
- Hold your breath, we're going in.
(big storm whoosh energy)
("we can do it" action music)
- We're not gonna make it.
- We're gonna make it.
- We'll you're not gonna
make it, unless you zip it
and hold your God damn breath, young lady.
Hold on.
(music intensifies vibe
that "we can do it")
(undrunks roaring with thirst)
(music triumphantly lets
us know "we did it")
- Did we lose them?
- Yeah, for now.
- Obviously you ain't taking this,
saving the world shit as hundo-P as me.
- Oh, I'm taking it hundo-P,
but I'm also taking,
saving our time-traveling daughter's life,
pretty seriously too.
I've got a lot of shit
on my plate, right now.
- Well, if that was our daughter
she wouldn't need saving.
She'd be a CHAI.
- Okay, here we go.
- Yeah, here we go.
It's my fucking 18th Bday
and you twos just tossed me through time
and did fuck-all to prepare me
for any of this shit.
- Wait, today's your 18th bday?
- Duh.
- Come on CHAI
She's got your mum's bracelet.
She looks just like you, do the math.
- Fine,
H-B-D my CHAI-TRO.
But youse a Sheila, now.
It's time to calm those
chin waggy chin chats.
And we're going to get you,
some beat-weppies.
- [ Game Announcer] Wow. Beat-Knucks.
- Wow!
What are these?
- Beat-knucks.
- Huh?
- First time out of the FP, huh?
- You know poten-ch?
- Well beat-offs come in all sorts
of different flavors out here.
- I know this might be a bit cringe but,
I don't know how to use any of these.
- Something tells me,
you're about to find out pretty fast.
(undrunks roar with thirst)
- We best beat-feet.
We're falling behind.
- Mum's the boss.
Let's roll.
(tracker beeping)
- JTRO and crew just rolled
past the red barrier. Ha!
- I don't give a fuck.
Well, that's gonna complicate shit.
- Maybe if I was a bitch, you
calling my ass a bitch, bitch?
- No.
- Yo don't be salt talkin' my ass, buster.
Y'all wanna enter the drop zone again.
I'm fucking right here, homie.
It's all day. Eryday!
- No.
That's not what I'm saying.
All I'm trying to say is,
if we wanna roll out now is the time
because the people who are
trying to stop our asses
are basically here.
- Y'all wanna take back the a FP
or get your ass 1-8-7'd,
like last time, huh?!
- Well, as I remember you
didn't fare well either.
- Booshit.
Who found your ass out here?
Dusted that shit off and
got you back in the ring?
Ninja? Me, my ass.
Now I'm taking charge, homeboy.
- If you're so tough.
Why did it take you so
long to take back the FP?
- Shit, I got bigger ducks to fry, honky.
Just sit back and watch the show, Q-tip.
Chop, chop doctor bitch.
(bad guy music rises the tension)
(dope ass level select music returns)
- If you're both here,
who the F-U-K is watching
little me back home?
- Your babysitter, Uncle DC.
- Wait, you mean all them times,
you had me chill with Uncle DC,
when I was little me,
you were off doing cool shit, like this?
- I don't know, this is the first time
we've left little you with him.
- Okay, you both need to
zippy dip it, right now.
We've got bigger ducks to pluck.
- Does we?
(scurry ass monster noise)
Prepare to beat-off.
(undrunks screaming)
- They're coming.
- What's coming?
(undrunks moaning with thirst)
- Undrunks.
- Undrunks?
- Aint dead, Aint alive
Certainly aint drunk.
- Sober Peeps. Turned into foul,
beastly versions of their former selves.
From once there is, no redrunkening.
- W-T-F.
Youse rents nevs tells me shit.
(undrunks roar with thirst)
- [Jim Scary] How it do BAKO Deadlands.
- Welcome to Escape from
BAKO - Round 2. The Beat-Bop.
- [Jim Scary] Where contesties must bop
their way to the streets
of beautiful downtown BAKO.
- That's right Jim,
we got our top contesties
entering the round now
the CHAI-TROS.
- Well, Tom, they're still
getting their asses
burned by L Dub and AK-47.
Hopefully, they catch up
before they catch a dirt nap.
- I'll drink to that.
- Three.
Two.
One.
Beat-Bop.
(undrunks roaring with thirst)
- All right time to stay alive.
(dopest training montage
music of all timez RETURNS!)
- [Game Announcer] Bapp! Bapp! Bapp!
Bap 'n the box!
Trip Dope!
Quad Dope!
Dopezilla!
- Holy effing S.
- [Game Announcer] TL-DR!
Konkie Dong!
Woolloomooloohoo!
Queen killer!
Quack Slap!
Knock-knock!
Open up the door!
It's real!
Mates rates!
Hot Knucks!
King killer!
Thwack!
Sik thwack!
Thwack to the future!
Getting thwacky with it!
- Your punchies are slow AF.
- My punches aint slow.
I'm just actually looking
at where I am swinging 'em.
- Less chatties, more punchies.
- [Game Announcer] Surf's up!
Too long!
Didn't read!
Tell it to!
My knucks!
- Push-a-do! Forward!
(music continues to be dope)
- Bad guys 12 oc.
- Yo, four way stop, bitch.
- [Game Announcer] Run tell that!
- Cinco de Mayo.
May 5th 'n shit.
- Two plus two, bitch.
- [Game Announcer] Four way stop!
Cranberry juicer!
Lick my nine.
- Yo, these mother fucker's are thirsty.
We gotta go.
Dirt nap. Dirt nap. Dirt nap. Dirt nap.
Lights out, Doctor bitch!
- S-O-Mother-F'in - B!
After them.
Who the F-U-K is they?
- TTYL
(music continues to be dope)
- Open wide.
Sand ninja.
Yo, cheese!
(undrunks howl)
- Fuck!
- Lick my nine! Woo!
- Yo rents, we gotta split!
(undrunks howl with thirst)
- [JTRO] Come on hurry up.
We'll lose these fuckers
in the booze storm.
(booze storm intensifies)
- Yo!
Run ninjas, run!
(big reveal riser)
- Y'allz ready for dis?
- Huh?
(BOOM YO!)
(dope level select music returns)
- [JTRO] Oh perfect, making first contact
with some new race of whatever
the fuck these things are,
really isn't gonna help us catch up
with AK and L Dub right now.
- [CHAI-T] This aint first contact.
We're just going through immigraties,
while they chin wag us up and down.
Shouldn't be long.
- Okay.
Time out.
What the chocolate F is going on here?
I've been remixing through time,
like all fucking day,
trotting through whatever the hells,
while you two were doing
whatever the something.
I really need like a "previously on" here
to fill in some gaps, hey.
- Listen well and have a tink.
I won't spin this twice.
- Lay it on me.
Give me the hot goss.
- Legend chats of a fierce warrior
from the Diamondies in the sky,
known as Beat-Massa X.
(fuckin' sik snyth guitar music)
It was he, who brought beat-beat
to the duck peeps of Earf.
Allowing him to do
what he did to so many worlds before.
Hook the peeps on the Quatro
until they couldn't live withouts it.
Enslaving them with the fear of getting
flipped straight edge again,
on the spot for, without no booze,
these ducks could sort
their shit out no longer.
And they would become undrunk.
The Beat-Massa descended upon them
with his unstoppable army of L Black Ds
and 1-8-7'd the known duck world,
in what we now know as the Beat-Wars.
(fuck this music just got sik)
And when the land was sucked dry,
of all her fossil boozes,
the Beat-Massa began the cycle anew.
The wet shit swept across the land.
1-8-7'ing and all the peeps.
But 9-1-1-ing Mother Earf,
bringing them fossil boozes back
for the new race of enslaved peeps
to mine for him all over again.
- All right, so like way TLDR.
But what's important, right now,
is that we need to stop L Dubba E
before we wakes that
B-M-X son of a bitch up
and starts this cycle all over again.
- Hold up.
How can L Dubba E do all this shit?
Wasn't he just some broke
ass busta from the FP?
- Look CHAI-TRO,
L Dub is a left over
weapon from the Beat-Wars.
He is the last of the L Black Ds
and it is up to us to stop him,
before he can start this
shit all over again.
- Wait, trip what?
(knocking on the cage)
- [The Sequel] Go time ninjas.
(BOOM Yo!)
No one lives in BAKO 'cuz they want to.
We like a train.
We just go where them rails take us, yo.
Farm Massa De Falt's got a
deal to slap on yo asses with.
- Deal?
- Have y'all evz even
been beat-off before?
- Once or twice.
- Us peeps?
Shoot.
We's but a simple clan of Brewsk-zs.
Booze farming on the reg and shit.
- You grow booze, here?
- Liquid grass up in here.
None of that fossil booze booshit.
Renewable AF yo!
- Cool.
- Grand Massa De Falt
I present you with CHAI-T and fam.
Yeah.
- Jesus.
- Resume chorezes Z2
- Fucking wake up.
Got to work
Go to bed
- Yousse is NITRO's youngling, yes?
He was our guestie once.
As youse is now.
- Far out.
- You are looking to D-U-N
this ancient ass evil?
This L-E-E of the L black D's,
but in order to reach his ass,
y'allz must voyage deep into the purple
and upon his 1-8-7.
Y'allz will roll up
upon the Comet Of Dawn,
and pray to him for escape from Bako.
- Cool.
- Now open your drums.
'Cause I gots a request of y'allz.
The use of the forbidden fossil boozies
from the twinkies must end.
- Respect. But what the hell
do you want us to do about it?
- The Comet Of Dawn is
poisoning our Earf Mama.
You must finally D-U-N the comet,
once and forevz.
- How?
- We will 1-8-7 Dawn
and help bring balance back to the wastes.
- Many thanks CHAI-T, my old friendy-do
allow us some H-R-S's to prepare
Y'allz's transport into the purple.
- Many thanks Farm Massa.
Need to have some meditates
and sort some shit out.
You stay close and be ready.
(thunder rumbling)
- You wanna go get a drink or what?
- Lates.
(rockin' bad guy music)
(lightening crackling)
(beat-pod engine revs)
(bro-bot hydraulics)
(beat-beat arrows bopping)
(intense beat-beat)
- Can't see shit in this storm.
- Get used to it, homie.
I'm gonna spread this darkness worldwide.
For my Massa.
- What?
- It's how my peeps do.
Bro-bot shit. My Massa
made me in his image.
During them Beat-Wars, dumb shit.
- I got priors.
- L-E-A, L-E-B, L-E-C.
Do the math sucka.
- L-E-D?
- Shit, that nothin' ass use-ta?
He use-ta to run Dawn's Liquor, in the FP.
He use-ta to run all kinds
of shit. Like his cock sucka.
- And what happened to him?
- ME, motha fucka!
My ass!
Y'all keep beatin' it, homie.
(bad guy music gets double serious)
(beat-beat intensifies)
(mystical contemplation music)
- [CHAI-TRO] Not bad, hey.
- [JTRO] Yeah. You can't really
tell the difference, huh.
- [CHAI-TRO] What up
with you and MUMMY-CHAI?
- [JTRO] What do you mean?
- She's all P-Oed A-F, what'd you do?
- That's adult shit.
- Mmmmm. I'm 18 and I've
remixed through time,
I adult AF.
- Did I ever tell you about your birth?
Like, you know, the future me?
- Nah.
- Well,
When you were born, it wasn't just you.
You had a brother, CHAI-TRO.
- Twinsies?
- Yeah, kinda.
Um, you know due to
some health politics he,
Yeah, he didn't make it.
Ever since then, uh,
you know your mum and I hasn't
really been quite the same.
You know, she's strong, she got over it.
I dunno,  I guess, I just,
never really knew how.
And uh,
you know, she's a CHAI,
and they don't really
care much about boys so.
You know, I probably said some shit.
Probably didn't handle things
as well as I probably could have.
I guess now she's pissed off at me because
She thinks that, all I care
about, is about somebody
who's already gone.
And not about her, who's still here.
- Did you ever tell her any of this shit?
- Yeah, I mean I tried.
She's like some fuckin' magical being,
okay, I'm just some dude from the FP.
I mean what am I supposed to say?
I don't know what's going on in her head.
- All right, rewind.
Take two, yo.
When's the last time
you told her you L-U-V'd her?
Caring silently doesn't mean shit, dad.
I don't care how much booshit,
you got goin' on.
We all does.
But if you don't tell peeps you care,
they assume you don't.
- Who told you that?
- You did.
- How were your mom and I in the future?
- Factor fifty.
To power these beat-poddies,
you gotta be able to beat-beat, right?
- Yeah, I mean that's generally
how things work out here.
- You've never even let me beat-off
before in my time.
I don't even know how.
- Really?
- Maybe we never taught you
how to beat-off and your time because...
- We already did.
We knew, that in order to save the world,
things had to happen,
exactly as they once did.
- And how do we know that?
- I lits just thought of it.
But we have to Omega enforce it,
from here on out.
- So is beat-pod ready, then?
- Ready, steady and burning hot.
- All right.
Let's go to work.
(bomb electronic music swells)
(guitar synth music up in here)
- [Game Announcer] Beat-pod boot-up
sequence activated.
(beat-computer beeping)
- [CHAI-TRO What do I do, first?
- [JTRO] You just hop on.
- [CHAI-TRO] That's it?
- That's how I learned.
(beat-computer beeping)
- [Game Announcer] Beat-Pod coordinates.
Coordinating.
Coordinated.
- There's a lot of ancient
CHAI-blood in you CHAI-TRO.
From both our sides.
Y'all ready for this?
Let's beat first and think later.
- [Game Announcer ] Three.
Two.
One.
Beat-Beat.
(beat-pod engines ignites)
(incoming creep mode alarm)
- Somethin's comin' up fast.
Double fast.
(incoming creep mode alarm)
- White Chocolate.
- What do we do?
- Yo! Stop slow riding, like a bitch.
Move this bolt bucket, cracka.
- It's a little tough to
do all this by myself.
There's two pads for a reason.
- Fuck it!
Take the wheel, cranberry juice.
Let me show you
how a mo-suckin' stallion gets this done.
- Okay.
- Franken-ninja up in here.
Yo, hot potato.
I'm ghost-beatin' , ninja.
(beat-pod engine blasts-off)
- [Jim Scary] Welcome to Escape From Bako.
Round three.
Finally, some fuckin' beat-pods.
Contesties must race their way through
the never-ending storm of
twisted booze mountains
towards the final goal
at the home of the Comment Of Dawn,
The Quatro-cano.
- It's been a long time
since we seen a round three, Jim.
Ole NITRO was the last beater we saw
with that kind of gas, Tom?
- Yeah, fuck it, I'm here for
it. Fuck it, I'm here for it!
(dope level select music)
(typical beat-pod chase music)
- Yo, tippy toes.
This is how a real ninja beat-off.
(laughing)
(beat-pod revving)
Check this shit out!
I'm an Omega Gangsta.
Youse an Omega Bitch.
Boom BreXit motha bitch.
How do you like that shit?
I aint even breakin' a sweat.
- Ram the fucker.
- Straight up the hooey, hooey?
- Yeah, of course, right
up the hooey, hooey.
(beat-pod accelerating)
- Yo, Panduh Express! Take a left.
- What through the canyon?
- It's a short cut.
- Yeah, a shortcut to
gettin' fuckin' Green-lit.
- Do it, saltine.
- [Game Announcer] Omega speed mode.
- Click it or ticket.
(Beat-Pod revving)
- [Game Announcer] Target escaping.
More gassies.
- We need more gassies.
Beat them feet.
- All right, CHAI-TRO dance with your mind
not your feet.
Do you understand me?
- What the fuck does that mean?
- Anticipate what's coming.
Look forward, not back.
If you spend your whole
life looking at yesterday,
you're never gonna have a tomorrow.
Yesterday is a 1-8-7.
Tomorrow is where winning is dun.
D-U-N.
I used to be mad about everything,
about what I've lost and
how I've been wronged.
But if I never lost BTRO or B-L-T,
I never would have met your mother,
and I would of never had you.
Everything happens
how its supposed to happen, CHAI-TRO.
Sometimes if life takes a shit on you,
you just gotta wait for it to wipe its ass
and flush first before you give up on it.
You dig?
- I dig.
I'm digging.
(beat-beating intensifies)
(Beat-Pods revving)
- We can't change the past,
But we can always change tomorrow.
CHAI-TRO. Don't run from the past.
Learn from it.
Use it's ass.
You got this.
You take everything,
one beat at a time, CHAI-TRO.
Nothing past that matters.
Do not fear the pads.
You make the pads fear you.
(beat-pods revving)
- [Game Announcer] Queen killer.
Whoa! She-RO Mode!
Incoming Four-way stop.
- Low bridge.
- What the fuck does that mean?
- Beat down.
(beat-pads beatin'-off like mad)
Down Ninj!
Creepers still be creeping.
- So that did nothing.
You got anymore bright
ideas back there, pal?
- Check this shit out.
(Beat-Pods revving)
(music continues to be dope AF)
- High bridge.
- What the fuck is up
with you and bridges all of a sudden, huh?
Does that mean up?
- Duh.
- DUH!
- Awh! Jesus Christ!
(beat-pod breaking the sound barrier)
- [Game Announcer] Yo! Speed up, chumps.
- So, yeah, none of this is working.
Yo, what are you doing?
- Break check.
- Full bridge.
- Awh shit!
- [Game Announcer] Lates.
(shit powers down)
(coughing)
Is everyone okay?
- I thinky, dink.
- Samesies.
(alarm sounding)
- Oh that mother fu-
I am not a happy chappy.
- Me neither.
(BOOM Yo!)
- JTRO.
- Stay back.
This knuckle dragger's my fight.
I should have 1-8-7'd him years ago.
This one's on me.
- You don't have to do this alone.
- I'm not alone.
We're a team, right?
Different team members
have different skills.
You're the brains, and I'm the noise.
Now, go take care of our Sheila
until shit quiets down.
And then end this.
- JTRO.
I'm sorry about JR-TRO
- I miss him too, but I miss you more.
I L-U-V you CHAI, always and forevz.
- I L-U-V youse too.
G'Day TRO.
- G'Day CHAI.
We got this.
(BOOM Yo!)
(epic end movie choir music 'n shit)
(L Dubba E chanting)
- (clears throat)
- Yo! What the fuck is
you doin' up in here,
white chocolate?
I'm summoning my massa.
- I'm gonna give you two guesses
but you're only gonna need one.
- What the fuck just
sniffed outta yo slit hole?
Take a look around, homeboy.
- I'm sick of listening to you breathe.
- You want to take it
outside, doctor bitch?
- We are outside.
- Shut yo jap flap.
Let's bapp bapp bapp.
- All right, so do I punch
first or do you punch first?
I'm getting confused.
- (screeching)
(FIGHT music)
- [Game Announcer] Combo buster!
Yo kick it!
Bap City!
- Yo don't be trying
that Ninj-FU with my ass, chumpzilla.
- [Game Announcer] Wow! Omega knucks!
Forkliff!
1-8-7!
L Dub wins!
- We from different worlds, homie.
Yo. Knock the chocolate out of
this meat popsicle, I'm busy as shit.
(L Dubba E Chanting)
D-U-N! Nothin' but net!
- Okay, I might have my issues,
but look who you're
fucking working for, here.
You think this mother fucker is gonna
live up to anything he says?
What's he even promising you?
He's in this for himself, that's it.
And you fucking know it.
Look, I'm sorry dude,
but you do not have to do this.
The FP doesn't have to
be my town or your town.
We're fucking adults, now.
It can be our town, God damn it.
(Emotionally persuasive music)
You don't have to be some
lonely sand-ninj out here,
just huffin' to do God
knows what to survive.
You can come back.
You have a home.
You have a family.
- This is some dumb ass shit.
Y'all listen to yourselves.
- That mother fucker, killed our brother.
- I don't give a fuck.
- He'll kill you,
he'll kill everyone
if we don't stop him.
Come on ATRO.
- Hermanos?
- Just a couple of assholes
who look like each other.
(L Dubba E chanting)
- Hot potato, bitch.
- [Game Announcer] Eight way stop.
- Eeny, meeny, miny, ho,
catch a ninja by its chode
my dick told me
to pick the very choice one and,
open wide cranberry juice.
Time to suck my brick mother fuck-
- [Game Announcer] Nut buster!
(L Dubba E screaming)
- This is where you fall down.
Some mother fuckers are always trying
to Beat-Beat up hill.
(L Dubba E screaming like a chump)
(explosion - DUH)
- Holy shit.
- Yeah, that's honestly
not how I thought that
was gonna go at all.
Awh fuck, I'll take it.
- Dadzies!
Uncle-ATRO?
What the Unc is you doing here?
- Am I supposed to know who this kid is?
- Yeah, that's uh, that's your niece.
- Oh. Hola
- Uh its YOLA
- Where's L Dub?
- No body, no trial.
- Is it done?
Did we winsies?
(mysterious music mystifies)
- It's up to you now, CHAI-TRO.
You have to finish this.
- Mom?
- It'll be chill.
A great power brews within you,
from the blood of our ancients.
Only you can 1-8-7 the comet.
It's what our ancesties did,
to free worlds.
Back when we came from the twinkies.
- Dad?
- It's like ridin' a bike.
- I L-U-V youse.
- We L-U-V youse.
The mostest.
- HBD kiddo.
- Lates rents.
- Lates yo.
- Nice meeting you.
- Some Sheilas were very special
back in the wastes CHAI-TRO.
When they came of ageies,
they were touched by RENINJ,
And they became ninjawas.
A thousand generations of CHAIs live on
in that bracelet.
- Just wish I could do something tight,
Like you and daddy do.
- You will.
On a ninjawa's 18th BD,
she becomes a warrior.
And her Beat-Beat training begins.
(unexplainable magic shit intensifies)
(time fast forward)
(Remix Revelation cools down)
(music is all mysterious 'n shit)
- Oh thank RENINJ.
- We never knew if we'd see you again,
after we sent you through the remix.
- I told you, what happ'd, happ'd.
You can't change the past.
- But we can change tomorrow.
- What is the actual F-U-K
are you guys rappin' about?
- Are you ready?
- For what?
(ominous music implies
shit's about to get ill)
(thunder roaring)
- The wet shit comes in every awakening.
- Rewind.
What's awakening?
(thunder crashing)
- Beat-Massa X.
- The final battle for earf has begun, yo.
(thunder crashing)
- Jesus laweez-Us.
(intense imminent cliffhanger music)
(End credits banger vaguely
hinting at the plot of FP4)
(PS - Keep watching
until after the credits)
(Oh shit there's another scene?!)
(Spooky bad guy music 'n shit)
- Yo.
Let's finish what you started, pops.
Quack!
(BOOM Yo!)