Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
MOMMY.
I'M TIRED OF CAMPING.
CAN WE GO HOME NOW?
[MOM SIGHS]
MOMMY, I'M TIRED OF CAMPING.
COME ON!
- WES.
- CAN WE GO HOME?
MOM: WHAT, BABY?
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
WES: I WANT TO GO HOME
AND I'M HOT,
AND I'M TIRED OF CAMPING.
MOM: YOU... YOU USED TO LIKE
CAMPING WITH DADDY.
WHAT'S WRONG?
WES: I KNOW,
BUT WE DIDN'T CAMP THIS LONG.
OH. YOU'RE REALLY SAD, HUH?
WES: I'M HOT,
AND I WANT TO GO HOME.
MOM: COME ON.
IT'S NOT THAT BAD.
WHERE'S MY SMILE, HUH?
♪ COME ON, BABY,
LET'S GET GOING ♪
♪ GET THOSE APPLE TREES
A-GROWING ♪
♪ THERE'S A LOT OF WORK
OUT THERE TO DO ♪
♪ OH, THERE'S A LOT
OF WORK TO DO ♪
♪ BOOP, BOOP ♪
IT'S TOO HOT
FOR HUGGING, MAMA.
YEAH, FAIR POINT.
I MISS DADDY.
I WISH HE WAS HERE.
OH, I KNOW, BABY,
BUT DADDY'S HERE.
DADDY'S ALWAYS WITH US.
HE'S ALL AROUND US
BECAUSE HE'S AN ANGEL.
YOU DON'T BELIEVE ME, HUH?
OK. LET ME SHOW YOU SOMETHING.
HAVE I EVER TOLD YOU
ABOUT ANGEL WISHES?
WES: ANGELS GRANT WISHES?
MOM: MM-HMM. THEY SURE DO,
AND YOU KNOW WHO'S
THE BEST ANGEL WISHER GRANTER?
- WHO?
- YOUR DADDY.
YOU WANT ME TO SHOW YOU
HOW TO MAKE A ANGEL WISH?
- MM-HMM.
- YEAH? OK. WATCH.
SO THIS IS WHAT WE DO.
WE TAKE DADDY'S RING,
AND THEN WE GIVE IT A KISS.
AND THEN I SAY, "SAM,"
OR YOU WOULD SAY, "DADDY,"
SO THEN I SAY, "SAM, I WISH...
"THAT WES WOULD GIVE ME
THE BIGGEST SMILE EVER."
HA HA! SEE? I TOLD YOU IT WORKS.
WES: LET'S SEE IF HE CAN
GRANT MY WISH.
MOM: OK.
DADDY, I WISH FOR A FAN.
MOM: YOU ARE
THE SILLIEST LITTLE GIRL.
WES: WELL, I AIN'T KIDDING.
MOM: I KNOW YOU'RE NOT KIDDING.
I KNOW, BABY.
MMM. YOU'RE SO MUCH
LIKE YOUR DADDY.
YOU KNOW THAT?
SO MUCH LIKE YOUR DAD.
WHAT TIME IS IT?
WHERE'S MY PHONE?
- DO YOU KNOW WHERE MY PHONE IS?
- MM-HMM.
I'LL GO GET IT.
MOM: OK. PLEASE.
THANK YOU.
IT'S DEAD.
WES, WHY IS MY PHONE DEAD?
I PLAYED GAMES ON IT LAST NIGHT.
MOM: WE DON'T KNOW
WHAT TIME IT IS!
WE'RE GONNA BE LATE.
GO GET READY, OK?
WES: CAN I PICK OUT OUR OUTFIT?
MOM: YEAH, GO AHEAD.
[SIGHS]
WHAT'S THAT?
THIS IS YOURS,
THIS IS MINE, OUR OUTFITS.
THAT'S MINE?
I'M WEARING THAT TODAY?
YEAH, YOU'RE WEARING THIS.
OK.
NOW I'M GONNA GO BRUSH MY TEETH.
MOM: OK. YOU DO THAT.
WES: LOVE YOU!
MOM: LOVE YOU, TOO!
YOU SURE THAT'S
WHAT WE'RE WEARING?
WES: YES!
THAT GIRL.
NYLA, CHRISTINA, BECKY.
GREAT. SO JUST ONE MORE,
AND THEN WE GET OUR APARTMENT.
I'M GONNA DO THIS, SAM.
WE GOT IT.
WE GOT IT, WE GOT IT, WE GOT IT.
OK, WES.
I GOT YOUR SANDWICH.
PUT IT IN YOUR BAG,
AND REMEMBER,
THIS IS OUR LITTLE SECRET,
RIGHT, CAMPING?
WES: MM-HMM.
DO YOU PROMISE THAT THIS
IS OUR LAST DAY OF CAMPING?
MOM: I PROMISE. OK? ALL RIGHT.
SO LET'S GO SEE MS. CYNTHIA.
YOU READY?
- MM-HMM.
- ALL RIGHT. LET'S GO.
[WOO & THE CLOUDS' "CONSTANCE"
PLAYING]
♪ SEE BEAUTY A NEW ♪
♪ BUILD FOR TWO ♪
♪ AS ONE IN-TUNE ♪
[DOG BARKING]
♪ INFINITUDE ♪
WES: MOMMY, I'M HOT.
WHY DO WE ALWAYS HAVE TO WALK?
MOM: WE'RE ALMOST THERE, WES.
WES: DO YOU PROMISE
WE'RE GOING HOME TODAY?
MOM: LISTEN. I HAVE
A SURPRISE FOR YOU.
- REALLY?
- MM-HMM.
WE'RE GOING TO GET A NEW HOUSE.
- HA HA! REALLY?
- DO YOU LIKE THAT?
- MM-HMM.
- YOU WANT TO GO TO A NEW HOUSE?
- YEAH!
- ALL RIGHT, BUT YOU GOT TO
KEEP IT A SECRET.
- OK.
- CAN'T TELL ANYBODY.
I WON'T.
SHOW ME THAT YOU PROMISE.
ALL RIGHT.
BOTH: PROMISE!
MOM: ALL RIGHT, MY BABY.
OK. SO QUIT ALL
THE COMPLAINING, ALL RIGHT?
WES: YEAH.
COME ON. COME ON, COME ON.
MOM: OK, GIRL. COME ON, COME ON.
HEY! I WAS EXPECTING YOU GUYS
ABOUT A HOUR AGO.
MOM: I KNOW.
CYNTHIA: GETTING WORRIED.
I'M SORRY.
WE HAD A REALLY LONG WALK.
CYNTHIA: HOW ARE YOU, LOVE?
- HOT.
- HOT? COME ON IN. COOL DOWN.
- OK!
- WHOA, WHOA, WHOA, WHOA!
- WHAT?
- WHERE'S MY KISS, MY HUG?
MMM. OK. SO I'M GONNA BE
BACK AT 5:00, OK?
AND THEN CAN WE SLEEP INSIDE?
MOM: YES, OF COURSE WE CAN
SLEEP INSIDE.
SHE'S KIDDING BECAUSE
WE ALWAYS SLEEP INSIDE.
DON'T WE?
WHAT'S GOING... WHAT'S UP
WITH BEAR-BEAR?
WES: NO, NO, NO, NO, NO!
MOM: OH, MY GOD.
THIS IS DISGUST...
- NO!
- THIS IS DISGUSTING, WES.
NO. I'M TAKING HIM
TO GET WASHED.
GO INSIDE. GO INSIDE.
WES: PROMISE TO TAKE
CARE OF HIM.
MOM: I WILL TAKE CARE OF HIM.
Y'ALL HAVE FUN.
WES: COME ON.
MOM: SEE YOU!
WES: BYE!
BYE!
SO, HON, I'VE BEEN MEANING
TO TALK TO YOU.
YEAH. HOW WAS YOUR COOKING CLASS
THAT YOU HAD?
CYNTHIA: OH, THAT WAS GOOD.
THANK YOU.
YEAH? WHAT'D YOU COOK,
SOME SOUFFLÉS OR SOMETHING?
YEAH, HONEY. WE MADE SOME PASTA
FROM SCRATCH,
BUT I JUST WANTED TO TALK
TO YOU ABOUT, YOU KNOW.
- UH-HUH.
- IT'S BEEN A FEW WEEKS
THAT I'VE BEEN WATCHING WES,
AND, UM...
YEAH.
WE DISCUSSED SOME PAYMENT,
AND STILL, YOU KNOW, NOTHING.
I KNOW, I KNOW.
I'M WORKING ON IT.
I HAVE SO MANY CLIENTS,
AND THINGS ARE GONNA WORK OUT,
AND I...
CYNTHIA: THAT'S GOOD.
MOM: YEAH.
I GOT, LIKE, TWO TODAY,
AND THEN I'M GONNA CALL
A FEW TOMORROW,
AND IT'S ALL LINING UP,
SO DON'T WORRY.
I'M GONNA GET IT FOR YOU, OK?
CYNTHIA: OK. I MEAN, YOU KNOW
I ALWAYS GOT YOUR BACK,
AND I KNOW IT HASN'T BEEN LONG
SINCE SAM,
BUT THINGS ARE ROUGH
FOR A LOT OF US RIGHT NOW.
- YEAH.
- BUT IT'S HARD.
IT'S HARD OUT HERE FOR ME, TOO.
- YEAH, I KNOW.
- SO LET'S WORK THIS OUT, OK?
CAN I LEAVE THESE HERE?
- YEAH. GO AHEAD.
- OK. THANKS.
CYNTHIA: I HAVE ERRANDS TO RUN,
SO BE BACK AT 5:00.
- AT 5:00.
- DON'T PLAY.
- I DON'T PLAY.
- ALL RIGHT, GIRL.
♪ I'LL BE HERE ♪
- ALL RIGHT. SEE YOU. THANK YOU.
- BYE. BE SAFE.
MOM: TODAY'S GONNA BE
A GOOD DAY.
CYNTHIA: BRING IN MY MONEY.
MOM: YEAH!
MAN: AAH!
[THE ALKAHOLIKS'
"DAAAM" PLAYING]
TASH: ♪ KICK YOUR DOPEST RHYME,
I'LL BREAK IT UP LIKE 3RD BASS ♪
♪ I'M FROM THE CREW THAT
SETS IT OFF ♪
♪ BY SPRAYING BEER
IN YOUR FACE ♪
♪ SO THE 94 TO THEM
I POUR MY NIGGAS THAT REMEMBER ♪
♪ MEANS I'M STEPPIN'
TO THE MIC ♪
♪ WITH LYRICS COLDER
THAN DECEMBER, BRR! ♪
♪ THE LIQUIDATOR
WITH THE HARDCORE DEMEANOR'S ♪
♪ BUSTIN' OUT THE PERPETRATORS,
I SEE THROUGH THEM LIKE A ZIMA ♪
♪ SO I'M NEVER CAUGHT BETWEEN
A HARD PLACE AND A ROCK ♪
♪ 'CAUSE I KILL RHYME BANDITS
BAREHANDED LIKE MR. SPOCK ♪
♪ I TOLD CHIEF NOT TO START
NO BEEF ♪
♪ HE TRIED TO SHOOT ME
WITH HIS GUN ♪
♪ I CAUGHT THE BULLET
WITH MY TEETH ♪
♪ 'CAUSE I'M STRONGER
THAN THE BULL ♪
♪ THAT'S ON THE SCHLITZ
MALT LIQUOR ♪
♪ HITTIN' UP YOUR CITES
WITH THE ALKAHOLIK STICKER ♪
♪ 'CAUSE I FEEL LIKE
BUSTIN' LOOSE ♪
♪ IT'S THE WICKED PAIN INFLICTOR
WITH THE MICKEY'S DEUCE DEUCE ♪
♪ DROPPIN' RHYMES LIKE A BOULDER
ON THE 21 AND OLDER ♪
♪ THAT'S YOUR MAMMA
WITH MY PICTURE TATTOOED ♪
♪ ON HER SHOULDER ♪
♪ SO RAP ARTISTS,
"GET READY TO RUMBLE!" ♪
♪ 'CAUSE I GOT LYRICS
UP MY SLEEVE ♪
♪ THAT SLAM HARDER
THAN MUTUMBO ♪
♪ I HEARD YOUR DEMO TAPE ♪
♪ THAT SHIT WAS FAKER
THAN A SCAM ♪
♪ WHILE I BE DROPPIN' SHIT
THAT MAKE YOU SAY ♪
♪ ALKAHOLIKS GOT THE BEATS
THAT'LL MAKE YOU SAY DAAAM ♪
♪ THE ALKAHOLIKS GOT THE FREAKS
♪ THE ALKAHOLIKS GOT THE FLOW ♪
THAT'LL MAKE YOU SAY DAAAM ♪
♪ THE ALKAHOLIKS GOT THE HOS
♪ THE ALKAHOLIKS GOT THE BEATS
THAT'LL MAKE YOU SAY DAAAM ♪
♪ THE ALKAHOLIKS GOT THE FREAKS
♪ THE ALKAHOLIKS GOT THE FLOW
THAT'LL MAKE YOU SAY DAAAM ♪
♪ THE ALKAHOLIKS GOT THE HOS
- ♪ IT'S LIKE THIS ♪
- ♪ YEAH ♪
- ♪ IT LIKE THAT ♪
- ♪ DAAAM ♪
- ♪ IT'S LIKE THIS ♪
- ♪ UH-HUH ♪
- ♪ DAAAM ♪
- ♪ BUST RHYMES ♪
♪ LIKE THAT, WORD UP,
ALKAHOLIKS ♪
♪ DAAAM ♪
- ♪ X TO THE Z XZIBIT ♪
- ♪ YEAH ♪
- ♪ IN THE MOTHERFUCKING PLACE ♪
♪ DAAAM ♪
♪ LET ME SHOUT IT OUT ONCE,
ONCE, ONCE ♪
♪ DAAAM ♪
♪ TO MY NIGGA KING TEE
YOU DON'T STOP ♪
♪ TO MY NIGGA DIAMOND D
♪ TO MY NIGGA DJ POOH
YOU DON'T STOP ♪
MOM: SO YOU STILL TALKING
TO THAT GUY LARRY?
WOMAN: YEAH. I MEAN... GIRL,
IT'S A BIT OF AN ENTANGLEMENT.
HA! DID YOU JUST SAY,
"ENTANGLEMENT"?
YOU ARE SO LIKE THAT.
YOU ARE SO STUPID.
SO WHAT'S UP? WHAT'S THAT MEAN?
HE, LIKE, PUTTING IT DOWN
OR SOMETHING?
WOMAN: I MEAN, HE DO
A LITTLE THING OR TWO.
HA HA HA!
BUT SO IS KAREEM.
MOM: WAIT A SECOND.
NOT KAREEM FROM THE SWAP MEET?
SWAP MEET KAREEM?
THE DUDE WE MET LAST WEEK
AT THE SWAP MEET?
- YOU KNOW.
- SWAP MEET KAREEM?
YES, SWAP MEET KAREEM, YES.
YOU KNOW HIM.
MOM: NO!
♪ MMM, KAREEM, KAREEM,
MAKING YOU SCREAM ♪
♪ KAREEM, KAREEM ♪
♪ MAKING YOU CREAM ♪
- EW!
- HA HA HA!
WOMAN: YOU ARE SO NASTY. EW.
MOM: I KNOW.
IT WAS NASTY WHEN I SAID IT.
WOMAN: HA HA!
MOM: ALL RIGHT, GIRL.
YOU ARE ALL DONE.
- HERE'S YOUR CLIP.
- THANK YOU.
ALL RIGHT. SO IT'S GONNA BE
150 FOR THE HAIR
AND THEN 100 FOR THIS, OK?
- OK.
- ALL RIGHT.
PLEASE HURRY, OK, BECAUSE
I GOT SOMEWHERE TO BE.
WOMAN: I GOT YOU, I GOT YOU.
MOM: TELL YOUR MOM
I SAID HI.
WOMAN: OK. I WILL.
YOU KNOW SHE LOVE YOU.
I LOVE HER, TOO.
NYLA, HURRY UP.
I GOT TO GO!
YOU GOT IT?
WHAT'S THAT LOOK FOR, NYLA?
NYLA: DUDE.
MOM: NO, NO.
EVERY TIME YOU SAY, "DUDE,"
IT'S SOME BULLSHIT.
WHAT IS IT, NYLA?
OK. LOOK. CHECK.
SO... SO I WENT IN THE HOUSE.
THE HOUSE LOOK
ALL SPICK AND SPAN.
I WAS LIKE, "OH, OK. LOOK,
YOU KNOW, MOM'S CLEANED UP,"
SO I GO TO GO LOOK
FOR THE MONEY,
AND THEN I THINK SHE MUST
HAVE PUT IT SOMEWHERE
BECAUSE SHE CLEANED UP,
SO I ASKED HER.
I'M LIKE, "YO. YOU KNOW,
WHERE'S THE MONEY?"
SHE SAID, THAT, YOU KNOW,
SHE MOVED IT
TO THE PHONE BILL COMPANY,
AND SHE PAID THE PHONE BILL
WITH MY MONEY, DUDE.
- NYLA.
- DUDE.
NYLA.
NYLA: I DIDN'T KNOW
SHE WAS GONNA DO IT, DUDE.
NYLA, IT DOESN'T MATTER.
I NEEDED THAT MONEY.
I HAVE TO GO MAKE
A SECURITY DEPOSIT
ON A PLACE RIGHT NOW.
- OH, SHIT.
- I GOT TO GET A PLACE, OK?
NYLA: CAN YOU GIVE IT
TO THEM LATER?
- I MEAN, I GOT YOU.
- NYLA, NYLA,
IT'S NOT ABOUT GIVING
IT TO THEM LATER.
THAT'S NOT HOW IT WORKS.
I GOT TO GET A PLACE.
I GOT A BABY, NYLA.
THAT'S NOT COOL!
LOOK. I SKATED ALL THE WAY
OVER HERE TO DO YOUR HAIR.
- I KEPT MY WORD TO YOU...
- OK.
AND I EXPECT YOU TO KEEP
YOUR WORD TO ME.
- WHAT AM I SUPPOSED TO DO?
- MY BAD.
CAN YOU BORROW IT
FROM SOMEONE ELSE
AND THEN PAY THEM BACK LATER
OR SOMETHING?
PSS. I MEAN...
MOM: OH, MY GOD.
OH, MY GOD, NYLA.
NYLA: I MEAN, YOU KNOW
I'M GOOD FOR IT.
MY STIMULUS HIT ON THE 12th.
- NEXT WEEK, I GOT YOU.
- YOUR STIMULUS?
- I'LL EVEN GIVE YOU INTEREST.
I DON'T CARE
ABOUT YOUR INTEREST.
- I KNOW, DUDE.
- SHIT IS NOT FUNNY.
NYLA: I DIDN'T KNOW
SHE WAS GONNA DO THIS, DANNY.
IT DOESN'T MATTER
ABOUT YOUR MAMA, NYLA.
IT DOESN'T MATTER.
IT'S ABOUT YOU,
BUT IT'S COOL, IT'S COOL,
IT'S COOL, IT'S COOL.
NYLA: BUT, DANNY, YOU KNOW
I'M GOOD FOR IT.
DANNY: I DON'T CARE, NYLA.
IT'S COOL, DUDE! IT'S COOL!
NYLA: YOU KNOW I GOT YOU!
DANNY, I GOT YOU. I GOT
YOU WITH INTEREST NEXT WEEK.
- LIKE, DON'T EVEN TRIP.
- WHATEVER, NYLA.
NYLA: YOU KNOW I'M GOOD FOR IT.
DANG, MOM!
[WOO & THE CLOUDS'
"WINTER SOLSTICE" PLAYING]
♪ IGNORE THE SIGNS ♪
WOMAN: DANNY?
DANNY, IS THAT YOU?
DANNY: OH, SHIT.
- HI.
- IS THAT YOU, GIRL?
WOMAN: OH, MY GOD. HOW ARE YOU?
DANNY: YEAH, I'M FINE, YOU KNOW.
THANKS FOR ASKING.
I'M GOOD, WE'RE GOOD.
EVERYTHING'S... YEAH.
WOMAN: IT'S BEEN A WHILE
SINCE THE MEMORIAL,
SO, YOU KNOW, I MIGHT
WANT TO CALL YOU.
DANNY: I, YOU KNOW...
I JUST REALLY HAVE TO GO.
- ARE YOU SURE?
- YEAH.
WELL, HOW'S WES?
I MEAN, I GOT TO KNOW
HOW THAT CUTE, LITTLE GIRL IS.
WES IS GOOD.
SHE'S DOING HER SCHOOLING,
- AND EVERYTHING'S, LIKE...
- THAT'S GOOD. YEAH?
DANNY: BUT I'M GONNA...
I'M JUST GONNA...
AND SHE'S DOING OK?
YOU KNOW, SAM WAS SUCH
A GOOD GUY,
AND I KNOW HOW DEVASTATING
THAT LOSS MUST BE.
I MEAN, MY SISTER'S HUSBAND'S
CO-WORKER JUST DIED,
AND THAT'S BEEN AWFUL.
DANNY: YEAH. YOU KNOW,
I REALLY GOT TO GO,
THOUGH, CHARLOTTE.
LIKE, I... I... I DON'T WANT
TO BE RUDE,
BUT I, LIKE...
OH, BUT, DANNY, BEFORE YOU GO,
I HAVE TO TELL YOU
ONE THING THAT'S BEEN
REALLY HELPFUL FOR ME
IS THAT WE GOT A LITTLE PUPPY,
AND IT'S ONLY $350 TO ADOPT.
- REALLY?
- YEAH.
- THAT'S GREAT.
- AND IT'S REALLY HELPFUL
FOR YOUR MENTAL HEALTH.
OH, OK. YEAH, YOU KNOW,
I DO THINK WES WOULD
LIKE A DOG,
BUT, LIKE, RIGHT NOW,
IT'S NOT THE TIME.
I REALLY WOULD LOVE TO TALK,
BUT I GOT TO GO.
- I HAVE, LIKE...
- BUT YOU'RE GONNA CALL ME,
THOUGH, RIGHT?
- I AM, GIRL.
- AND I'LL CALL YOU,
AND WE'LL CATCH UP.
ALWAYS. YOU KNOW, WE ALWAYS
NEED TO...
I'M JUST GONNA SCOOT BY YOU
REAL QUICK.
I'M GONNA SCOOT RIGHT BY. OK.
THANK YOU!
CHARLOTTE: BYE, GIRL.
HI. WANT TO SIGN UP
TO ADOPT A DOG?
MAN: NO.
CHARLOTTE: NO? YOU SURE? OK.
ALL RIGHT. THANK YOU.
MR. YU, IT'S DANNY.
I HAVE THE MONEY, MR. YU.
HEY. I HAVE THE MONEY.
- OH. HEY, DANNY.
- HI.
UH, KEEP THE DISTANCE,
KEEP THE DISTANCE.
I JUST WENT TO THE DMV.
IT WAS A CISSPOOL.
DANNY: OH, YOU MEAN CESSPOOL.
YES. CESSPOOL.
WHEN DO YOU THINK
WE CAN MOVE IN?
YOU THINK I COULD GET
THE KEYS RIGHT NOW?
UH, I MEAN, YOU CAN GET
IT RIGHT NOW.
LET ME FINISH COUNTING.
IT'S NOT ENOUGH.
I KNOW IT'S A LITTLE SHORT.
IT'S ACTUALLY, UH, $200 SHORT.
DANNY: THE THING IS THAT
I JUST CAME FROM A CLIENT,
AND I WAS SUPPOSED TO HAVE
THAT MONEY,
AND SHE SHORTED ME,
BUT I'M GONNA GET IT SOON.
HOW SOON?
NEXT WEEK?
[YU SIGHS]
I CAN'T DO NEXT WEEK.
OH, COME ON, PLEASE.
I... I REALLY NEED THIS PLACE.
I HAVE A LITTLE GIRL.
I'M TRYING.
I... I KNOW THAT I CAN GET IT.
IT'S JUST $200, MR. YU.
DANNY, HERE'S THE THING.
THERE ARE ALREADY PEOPLE
WAITING FOR THIS UNIT,
AND I'VE ALREADY REDUCED
THE RENT FOR YOU.
I DIDN'T REDUCE IT FOR THEM,
BUT IT'S NOT MY PROPERTY.
I DON'T OWN THIS PLACE.
I HAVE A BOSS TO REPORT TO.
MR. YU, PLEASE.
THERE'S GOT TO BE SOMETHING.
I KNOW I CAN GET THIS MONEY.
IT'S ONLY $200.
[YU SIGHS]
ALL RIGHT. OK.
WELL, LET'S DO THIS.
I'LL TELL MY BOSS
THAT I WENT TO THE DMV,
SO I DIDN'T GET TO
SEE YOU TODAY, OK?
I'LL KEEP THE UNIT FOR YOU
FOR ONE MORE DAY.
BUT YOU HAVE TO GET THE $200
TO ME BY TONIGHT.
DANNY: YEAH? OK, OK.
OH, MY GOD!
THANK YOU, MR. YU!
THANK YOU SO MUCH!
YU: IT'S ACTUALLY PRONOUNCED
"YEW."
DANNY: "YEW."
YU: NO, IT'S "YEW."
DANNY: "YEWW."
YU: UH, IT'S OK.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
YEAH. DON'T WORRY
ABOUT IT.
JUST GET THE MONEY.
DANNY: I JUST HAVE ONE MORE
HAIR APPOINTMENT,
AND I'M LATE,
BUT I'LL BE BACK TONIGHT.
YU: YEAH.
DANNY: BYE!
CHRISTINA!
CHRISTINA, WAIT!
WAIT, WAIT, WAIT!
I'M HERE. I CAN DO IT,
I CAN DO IT, I CAN DO IT!
WAIT. I'M HERE.
WE CAN STILL DO IT.
IT'S ONLY, LIKE, TWO BRAIDS.
COME ON. JUST LET ME...
SO, WHAT, YOU JUST GONNA...
YOU IGNORING ME?
CHRISTINA: I TOLD YOU
A THOUSAND TIMES I HAD TO GO.
DANNY: LOOK. I'M NOT THAT LATE.
IT'S, LIKE, 10 MINUTES.
CHRISTINA: I CALLED YOU
SO MANY TIMES TO LET YOU KNOW
THAT WE HAD TO GO.
DANNY: BUT MY PHONE IS DEAD.
I'M SORRY.
I'M HERE NOW. LET ME JUST BRAID
YOUR HAIR, PLEASE.
YOU'RE THE ONE THAT INSISTED
ON THIS APPOINTMENT.
DANNY: BUT I'M HERE.
WE'RE WASTING TIME. JUST...
[CAR STARTS]
CHRISTINA, LOOK.
NO, NO, NO, NO.
I REALLY NEED THE MONEY.
PLEASE JUST LET ME BRAID IT.
CHRISTINA: ARE YOU SERIOUSLY
ON MY CAR?
- YEAH.
- GIRL, COME ON.
- PLEASE.
- GIRL, IF YOU NEEDED THIS MONEY,
YOU WOULD HAVE BEEN
HERE ON TIME.
IT'S ONLY GONNA TAKE,
LIKE, 10 MINUTES.
I AM NOT THE ONE.
GET OFF OF MY CAR.
GET OFF MY CAR!
I MEAN, JUST ONE BRAID?
- GIRL!
- OK. ALL RIGHT.
CHRISTINA: AND YOU'RE BEING
RIDICULOUS.
DANNY: I MEAN, WELL, WHEN
CAN WE DO IT THEN?
CHRISTINA:
MAYBE NEXT WEEK, DANNY.
I GOT TO GO.
LIKE, NEXT WEEK WHEN, THOUGH?
WHEN? LIKE, TUESDAY?
CHRISTINA: SURE, DANNY.
HEY. IS THERE SOMEWHERE
I COULD CHARGE MY PHONE?
CHRISTINA: FRONT DOOR, DANNY.
FUCK.
I DON'T KNOW, BEAR-BEAR.
[GIGGLING]
[SIGHS]
[CHIMES]
HEY, MICHAEL.
HEY. IT'S DANNY.
HEY. YEAH. UH, I WAS
JUST CALLING TO SEE
IF YOU NEEDED YOU HAIR BRAIDED
LIKE I DID THE LAST TIME
WITH THOSE EXACTS.
OK. GOOD, BECAUSE I'M
AVAILABLE TODAY.
YEAH. NEXT MONTH IS COOL.
WAIT. WHO BRAIDED YOUR HAIR?
YOUR SISTER?
DUDE, SHE CANNOT BRAID.
MAN, CALL ME BECAUSE
I KNOW IT'S LOOSE.
IT'S ABOUT TO GET
ALL FUZZY AND STUFF.
I'M ON SPEAKER?
YEAH. NO. TELL HER I DIDN'T
MEAN NOTHING BY THAT.
FUUUUU....
MAN: MAN, COME ON, LeBRON.
PASS THE BALL.
SHOULDN'T HAVE GOT RID
OF LONZO, MAN, AND INGRAM.
[SIGHS]
IT'S CRAZY.
- HEY. WHAT UP, LAMAR?
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
YOU WAS SUPPOSED TO BE HERE
30 MINUTES AGO.
LAMAR: I KNOW, MAN.
GOT IN AN ARGUMENT WITH MY GIRL.
BARBER: WHAT, YOU AIN'T PUTTING
IT DOWN NO MORE?
TSS. YEAH, RIGHT.
NAW, MAN. UH, SHE GOT ME
THIS NEW JOB,
BUT I GOT TO CUT MY HAIR.
BARBER: OH. HA HA HA!
SEE? THAT'S WHERE YOU MESSED UP.
NEVER LET A WOMAN
GET YOU A JOB.
SHE'LL HOLD IT OVER YOUR HEAD
THE ENTIRE RELATIONSHIP.
YEAH. I'M STARTING TO SEE THAT.
I MEAN, UNLESS YOU GOT
A JOB OPENING.
BARBER: AW, MAN. NAW, MAN.
WE PACKED LIKE SARDINES
UP IN HERE.
LAMAR: YEAH. YEAH. I SEE THAT.
- I GOT YOU. SORRY.
- WHOO! WAIT, WAIT.
BARBER: BRO, WHAT ARE YOU
JUMPING FOR?
LAMAR: WAIT. THAT WAS
TOO SOON, MAN.
BARBER: ISN'T THAT WHAT YOU
SAT DOWN IN THE CHAIR FOR?
LAMAR: YEAH, BUT DAMN.
IT'S... OOH!
OK. HEY, WHOA, WHOA, WHOA.
OK. WHOA. ALL RIGHT.
HOW ABOUT WE JUST
START OFF SLOW?
WE START WITH THE FACIAL HAIR,
AND THEN WE WORK OUR WAY UP.
BARBER: HOW YOU GONNA TELL ME
HOW TO CUT YOUR HAIR, MAN?
- I'M JUST...
- THESE PLAITS WENT OUT
WITH "MENACE II SOCIETY" IN '92.
DANNY: HI. UM, THE SIGN
OUTSIDE SAID THAT YOU BUY GOLD.
BARBER: ARE YOU THE POLICE?
POLICE DON'T LOOK
LIKE THAT, MAN.
BARBER: ALL RIGHT. HEY.
MAKE YOUR MIND UP, MAN.
I'M CHOPPING THAT OFF
WHEN I GET BACK.
WHAT CAN I HELP YOU WITH?
I WANTED TO KNOW HOW MUCH
I COULD GET FOR THIS CHAIN.
CAN YOU HELP ME?
WHAT ABOUT THIS GOLD RING?
OH, NO, NO.
THAT'S NOT FOR SALE.
HOW MUCH FOR THE CHAIN?
I CAN'T GIVE YOU MUCH
OF ANYTHING FOR THIS.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN? IT'S GOLD.
BARBER: I DON'T KNOW
WHO LIED TO YOU,
BUT THIS AIN'T GOLD.
I SEEN PEOPLE MAKE
BETTER THINGS IN PRISON.
OH, OK. NO. THAT IS REAL GOLD,
ABSOLUTELY 100% REAL GOLD.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT KIND
OF HUSTLE YOU HAVE HERE,
BUT YOU COULD GIVE ME
SOMETHING FOR IT.
BARBER: I'M SORRY. I APOLOGIZE.
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA. HOLD ON.
THAT I CAN GIVE YOU
SOME MONEY FOR.
NO. THIS IS A FAMILY HEIRLOOM.
I'M GIVING IT TO MY DAUGHTER,
AND SHE KNOWS I'M
GIVING IT TO HER,
SO THAT'S DEFINITELY NOT
HAPPENING.
BARBER: LIKE I JUST SAID,
WHAT ABOUT THE THAT GOLD RING?
THAT'LL EASILY GO FOR $300
RIGHT NOW, BIG FACES.
300?
OHH.
UM...
THIS... WAS MY HUSBAND'S RING.
NO. ARE YOU SURE YOU CAN'T
GIVE ME ANYTHING FOR THIS,
LIKE, ANYTHING?
WHAT DO YOU WANT ME TO DO?
I'LL GIVE YOU 5.00.
GIVE ME $10.
BARBER: I CAN'T. I'M SORRY.
TELL YOU WHAT. YOU CAME IN HERE
LOOKING ALL GOOD
ON THEM SEXY-ASS SKATES.
I'LL GIVE YOU 7.00
AS LONG AS YOU SKATE OUT SLOW
JUST THE WAY YOU CAME IN.
JUST GIVE ME THE $7.00, PLEASE.
AND THAT'S ONLY
BECAUSE YOU'RE CUTE.
DANNY: ALL RIGHT.
THANK YOU.
I'LL BE HERE UNTIL 8:30
IF YOU WANT TO
COME BACK BY WITH THAT RING.
DANNY: UH, 8:30?
BARBER: BEFORE 8:30.
DANNY: UM, I'M NOT SELLING
THE RING,
BUT I MIGHT COME BACK
WITH SOME OTHER STUFF, OK?
- I'LL BE HERE.
- ALL RIGHT.
THANK YOU.
MAKE SURE YOU BRING THEM SKATES.
ALL RIGHT, MAN.
YOUR SCARY ASS READY?
[CLIPPERS BUZZING]
LAMAR: AGH! I CAN'T DO IT, MAN.
I CAN'T DO IT.
I CAN'T DO IT. I CAN'T DO IT.
FUCK THAT JOB.
BARBER: HEY. YOU WANT TO GET
IN CORPORATE AMERICA,
YOU GOT TO CHOP, CHOP.
LAMAR: HEY, LOOK, MAN.
I'D RATHER SLING
SOME DING-A-LING, ALL RIGHT?
I'M OUT. PEACE.
BARBER: HEY.
DO THE RIGHT THING, MAN.
[CHIMES]
UM, EXCUSE ME.
- YEAH?
- WHERE ARE MY WONTONS?
WONTONS. HOLD UP ONE SECOND.
- IS THIS 13032?
- YEAH.
NO. THERE'S NO WONTONS
ON THIS ORDER.
HEH. THAT'S NOT POSSIBLE.
I ALWAYS ORDER WONTONS.
NOT ON HERE,
BUT MAYBE IF YOU CHECK THE APP,
- YOU CAN CALL AND...
- WHY DON'T YOU CHECK?
DANNY: YEAH. I DID.
I JUST... THAT'S WHAT I'M SAYING.
I JUST DID.
DO YOU EVEN KNOW
HOW TO CHECK YOUR PHONE?
YEAH. UM... MA'AM, JUST
PLEASE JUST CHECK YOUR APP
AND CALL THEM, SO...
WOMAN: MAYBE YOU DROPPED THEM
WHILE YOU WERE SKATING.
DANNY: YEAH. THAT'S NOT
REALLY POSSIBLE.
IS THERE A SUPERVISOR
I CAN TALK TO?
WHAT? MY... I'M... THERE'S...
IT'S POSTPALS.
I'M... I'M THE SUPERVISOR.
WOMAN: WHATEVER.
YOU'RE GETTING ONE STAR.
WHAT THE?
WHAT THE? I DIDN'T EVEN...
DID SHE JUST KAREN ME?
I CAN... SUCH BULLSHIT.
POSTPALS.
DANNY?
JACOB.
I THOUGHT YOU LIVED
IN NORTH HOLLYWOOD.
I DID, BUT M-MY ABUELITA PASSED
AND LEFT ME HER PLACE.
OH, MAN.
I'M SORRY TO HEAR THAT.
I MEAN, AT LEAST SHE
LEFT YOU SOMETHING, RIGHT?
YEAH, THE HOUSE
AND ALL THE BILLS.
HEH HEH HEH.
HEH.
WELL, UM, I GOT A LOT
OF THINGS...
JACOB: WAIT, DANNY.
HOW ARE YOU, YOU AND WES?
I MISSED YOU GUYS.
I HAVEN'T SEEN YOU IN MONTHS.
- YEAH.
- YOU GUYS OK?
MM-HMM. WE'RE MANAGING.
EVERYTHING'S COOL.
WE'RE FINE.
JACOB: YOU KNOW IF YOU
NEED ANYTHING,
YOU AND WES, I'M HERE.
SAM WAS A HELL
OF A FRIEND TO ME,
AND I JUST WANT TO LET YOU
KNOW THAT I'M HERE FOR YOU TWO.
- THANK YOU.
- WAIT. HOLD ON, DANNY.
I'M GONNA... OH.
CALL ME.
COOL. ALL RIGHT.
- COOL.
- CALL ME.
[WOO & THE CLOUDS'
"BRAND NEW DAY" PLAYING]
[SCAT SINGING]
♪ BRAND NEW DAY ♪
♪ HEY ♪
♪ BRAND NEW DAY-AY-AY-AY ♪
♪ SUN ON MY FACE, HEY ♪
♪ CAME A LONG WAY ♪
♪ HEY ♪
♪ FREQUENCY ♪
♪ SOCIETY ♪
♪ ANXIETY ♪
♪ BRAND NEW DAY, HEY ♪
♪ CHANGE ♪
[CELL PHONE CHIMES]
♪ SAY ALL RIGHT,
GONNA BE ALL RIGHT ♪
♪ I CAME A LONG WAY ♪
♪ CHANGE ♪
♪ LOOK ON MY FACE ♪
♪ I BEEN A LONG WAY,
CHANGE ♪
[CELL PHONE CHIMES]
♪ BEEN A LONG WAY ♪
♪ CHANGE ♪
♪ STAY ALL RIGHT ♪
♪ TOOK A LONG WAY,
CAME A LONG WAY ♪
♪ CHANGE ♪
♪ LOOK AT MY FACE,
CAME A LONG WAY ♪
♪ CHANGE ♪
♪ SMILE ON MY FACE ♪
♪ LOOK AT MY FEET,
PAID MY WAY ♪
♪ CAME A LONG WAY ♪
DANNY: THANK YOU.
[HORN HONKS]
OH, MY GOD!
GOD!
[BEEP]
[BEEP, BEEP]
WOMAN: DANNY! DANNY!
DANNY, YOU HEARD ME
CALLING YOU, GIRL?
DANNY: OH, BROOKLYNN.
BROOKLYNN: YOUR LITTLE CRAZY ASS
STILL SKATING.
DANNY: OH, MY GOD.
BROOKLYNN: YOU BETTER GET IT.
- HA HA HA!
- HEH HEH.
IT'S BEEN... GIRL, DON'T
FALL ROLLING OVER HERE TO ME.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
HOW YOU DOING?
I'M GOOD, YOU KNOW.
UM, I'M COOL.
BROOKLYNN: ALL RIGHT.
YOU KNOW, I'M JUST TRYING
TO GET SOME WORK
AND DOING PEOPLE'S HAIR
ON THEIR PORCHES,
BUT I CAN'T... I'M TRYING
TO FIND SOMEONE TODAY.
EEK.
HOW YOUR MAMA DOING?
I MEAN, SHE'S COOL.
SHE MOVED.
SHE'S OUT OF STATE NOW,
SO IT'S JUST ME AND WES.
AW. HOW'S SHE?
WES IS GOOD.
SHE'S...
SHE'S GETTING REALLY BIG,
AND SHE'S IN SCHOOL...
WELL, NOT...
YOU KNOW, THEY'RE ONLINE,
BUT SHE'S OVER AT CYNTHIA'S.
- DO YOU REMEMBER CYNTHIA?
- YEAH, YEAH.
YEAH, SO CYNTHIA'S BEEN COOL
IN HELPING ME WITH HER,
AND, YOU KNOW, WE'RE FINE.
SPEAKING OF WHICH,
I WANTED TO APOLOGIZE
FOR NOT MAKING IT
TO SAM'S MEMORIAL.
I JUST CAN'T DO STUFF LIKE THAT.
YEAH. I MEAN, IT'S HARD...
IT'S HARD TO GO
TO THOSE THINGS.
I DON'T... I DON'T BLAME YOU.
NOBODY LIKES MEMORIALS.
I DON'T THINK I'VE EVER
SEEN YOU AT A MEMORIAL.
I COULDN'T TELL YOU
THE LAST TIME
I'VE BEEN TO ONE,
BUT JUST KNOW IT WASN'T
ANYTHING PERSONAL.
I WAS THERE WITH YOU IN SPIRIT.
YEAH.
WHAT YOU ABOUT TO DO?
I GOT TO WAIT FOR MY CLOTHES.
GIRL, LOOK. YOU AIN'T
WAITING FOR NOTHING.
THEM DRYERS AIN'T WORKING.
ALL THIS STUFF WET,
AND MY ARMS ABOUT TO FALL OFF.
COME WITH ME REAL QUICK.
ALL RIGHT,
BUT I GOT TO GET BACK.
- IT'S OK. COME ON.
- DON'T KEEP ME, BROOKLYNN.
I KNOW HOW YOU ARE.
BROOKLYNN: IT'S ALL RIGHT,
BUT WE ALWAYS HAVE FUN.
DANNY: I HOPE
MY DRYER'S WORKING.
BROOKLYNN: I SEEN YOU OUT HERE
ON YOUR LITTLE SKATES
AND YOUR BIKER PANTS.
DANNY: YOU KNOW, WESLEY
PICKED THIS OUT.
BROOKLYNN: I'M SURE SHE DID.
SHE TRYING TO FIND HER
A NEW DADDY.
- HA HA HA!
- GIRL, TAKE ONE OF THESE ARMS.
THIS SHIT HEAVY AS HELL.
OK.
- GOD, THIS IS HEAVY.
- I TOLD YOU.
BECAUSE THEY ALL WET.
DAMN DRYERS.
DANNY: WES... SHE REALLY
LOVES SCIENCE NOW AND MATH.
THAT'S HER THING.
BROOKLYNN: OH, THAT'S
SO AWESOME.
WE NEED SOME MORE YOUNG
FEMALE SCIENTISTS IN THE WORLD.
DANNY: YEAH. THAT'S WHAT
SHE WANTS TO BE.
BROOKLYNN: I LOVE IT.
GIRLS ROCK.
HOW ARE YOUR KIDS?
OH, CHILD, STILL
DRIVING ME CRAZY,
BUT, YOU KNOW, WE STILL
GOT TO TAKE CARE OF THEM, RIGHT?
DANNY: YEAH, THAT'S TRUE.
BROOKLYNN: OH, GOODNESS.
YOU DON'T WANT TO
TAKE THEM SKATES OFF?
NO, BROOKLYNN.
I TOLD YOU I GOT TO GO.
BROOKLYNN: YOUR LITTLE
SKATING ASS.
AHH. WELL, BEFORE YOU
LEAVE, THOUGH,
I GOT SOME GOOD NEWS.
- YOU DO?
- YES, GIRL!
WHAT IS IT?
WE ARE LEAVING
PACOIMA GARDENS, GIRL.
NO FREAKING WAY.
YOU BEEN HERE FOREVER.
- I KNOW.
- SO THEN WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
- CALABASAS!
- CALABASAS?!
- SO EXCITED!
- OH, WE BIG TIME NOW, HUH?
- YES, YES, YES.
- SO, WHAT? HOW YOU DOING THAT?
YOU GOT A NEW JOB
OR SOMETHING?
BROOKLYNN: HA HA! NOPE!
SOMETHING EVEN BETTER.
A NEW MAN!
HIS NAME IS CHAD. HA HA HA!
YOU'RE DATING SOMEONE
NAMED CHAD?
OK. HIS NAME'S NOT
ACTUALLY CHAD.
IT'S MICHAEL,
BUT I CALL HIM CHAD
BECAUSE HE'S AN ACCOUNTANT.
IT SOUNDS RIGHT, RIGHT?
- YOU ARE SO STUPID.
- HA HA HA!
- I CANNOT...
- OH, MY GOODNESS!
SO HOW LONG HAVE YOU
AND CHAD... MICHAEL BEEN DATING?
BROOKLYNN: IT'S BEEN
A COUPLE WEEKS.
- YEAH.
- SO WAIT.
YOU'VE BEEN SEEING HIM
FOR TWO WEEKS,
AND NOW YOU'RE MOVING IN
WITH THE KIDS?
GIRL, IT'S BECAUSE
I GOT THE GOOD-GOOD.
- HA HA HA!
- YOU ARE...
YOU ARE TOO MUCH FOR ME.
BUT ALL SILLINESS ASIDE,
I KNOW IT HASN'T BEEN
THAT LONG
SINCE SAM HAS BEEN GONE,
BUT I HAVE TO ASK.
YOU THINK ONE DAY
YOU MIGHT EVER THINK
ABOUT GETTING OUT HERE,
DATING AGAIN MAYBE?
NO. I JUST... NO.
I'M FINE, YOU KNOW?
I ONLY ASK BECAUSE... HEH...
CHAD GOT HIM
SOME RICH FRIENDS, BABY.
NO. I'M FINE, THANK YOU.
BROOKLYNN: I MEAN,
BUT REALLY, ARE YOU, DANNY?
YOU'RE BEAUTIFUL.
YOU GOT ALL OF THIS.
YOU OUT HERE DOING HAIR
ON PORCHES?
YOU NEED TO HAVE YOU
A RICH MAN TAKING CARE OF YOU
AND PAYING YOUR BILLS.
FIRST OF ALL,
I LIKE DOING HAIR.
YOU KNOW THAT,
SO I'LL ALWAYS DO HAIR,
MONEY OR NOT,
BUT SECONDLY, I GOT MONEY.
YOU KNOW, LIKE, SAM,
HE LEFT US
THIS INSURANCE POLICY,
AND IT WAS
A BIG INSURANCE POLICY,
AND SO, LIKE, ME AND WES,
WE GONNA BE... PFFT.
I WOULDN'T TELL NOBODY,
BUT WE GONNA BE REAL GOOD,
SO, LIKE, I'M HAPPY, YOU KNOW?
- REALLY?
- UH-HUH.
- GIRL!
- YEAH!
WHAT?! YES! OH, MY GOD!
WE ABOUT TO BOTH BE RICH!
♪ AYYY! DRINKING TEA
WITH OUR PINKIES UP ♪
I LOVE IT, I LOVE IT!
OOH, GIRL.
I KNOW EXACTLY
WHAT WE SHOULD DO.
I KNOW
EXACTLY WHAT WE SHOULD DO.
WAIT HERE.
I GOT SOMETHING PERFECT.
- DON'T MOVE.
- BROOKLYNN.
DON'T GO NOWHERE.
HOLD ON, HOLD ON.
I WISH WE WERE SET UP.
BROOKLYNN!
BROOKLYNN: I'M COMING.
DON'T LEAVE.
OK. OOH!
I'M SO EXCITED YOU HERE.
IT'S BEEN SO LONG
SINCE WE KICKED IT.
- OK. THIS IS ALL YOU, BOO.
- OH, NO, NO.
NO, NO, NO, NO. I CAN'T.
BROOKLYNN: WHEN WAS THE LAST
TIME WE BEEN ABLE TO KICK IT?
I CAN'T, B. I GOT TO GO BACK
TO THE LAUNDROMAT.
I GOT TO DO POSTPALS.
I'M ON ROLLER SKATES.
I CAN'T BE DOING THAT.
BROOKLYNN: DANNY, YOU BEEN
SKATING HIGH FOR YEARS.
I AIN'T TRYING TO HEAR
THAT MESS.
LOOK AT YOU.
THAT'S WHY YOU GRINNING.
WE BOTH RICH, BITCH.
ONE PUFF.
I GOT ONE FOR ME, TOO.
COME ON. YAY!
- ONE PUFF.
- THAT'S IT.
JUST MAKE IT BIG.
♪ MMM, MMM, MMM ♪
OK. LET ME LIGHT IT FOR YOU.
UNH! GOT YOU!
YOU GONNA MISS ME
WHEN YOU GONE.
YOU GONNA BE LIKE, "DAMN.
"B ALL THE WAY
OUT IN CALABASAS
WITH THE GOOD WEED."
THAT'S OK. WE'LL SEND A UBER
TO COME GET YOU.
[VOICE DISTORTED]
TAKE A BIGGER PUFF
THAN THAT, DANNY.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
[NORMAL VOICE]
WHOO! TODAY WAS SO GOOD!
I HAD MY GIRL, WE GOT HIGH!
WE BOTH RICH!
MAN, I COULDN'T HAVE ASKED
FOR NOTHING BETTER.
I'M NOT OK, B.
- I'M NOT FINE, DUDE.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
I'M NOT OK.
GIRL, YOU ALL RIGHT.
YOU JUST HAD ONE LITTLE PUFF.
YOU GONNA COME DOWN IN A SECOND.
IT'S ALL GOOD.
NO, MAN. I'M NOT OK.
I'M NOT FINE.
I DON'T HAVE... I'M NOT
RICH, DUDE.
I DON'T HAVE THAT INSURANCE.
THERE'S NO INSURANCE.
- I LIED.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
I THOUGHT SAM TOOK CARE
OF EVERYTHING FOR YOU GUYS.
YOU WERE SET FOR LIFE.
SAM DIDN'T TAKE CARE
OF ANYTHING, B, LIKE NOTHING.
NOTHING. HE DIDN'T
EXPECT TO DIE,
SO HE DIDN'T DO SHIT.
SO WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
WE LIVE IN A TENT
ON THE SIDE OF A ROAD.
WAIT. YOU...
YOU AND WES ARE WHAT?!
WE'RE LIVING IN A TENT, MAN.
WELL, WHAT DO YOU MEAN
YOU'RE LIVING IN A TENT?
WE IN A TENT.
THAT'S WHERE WE LIVE.
LIKE, I DON'T HAVE A PLACE.
COME ON, DANNY.
WHAT'S GOING ON, GIRL?
OHH, MAN. I DON'T HAVE SHIT, B.
I DON'T HAVE SHIT.
LIKE, I DON'T HAVE...
I DON'T HAVE A CAR,
I DON'T HAVE FOOD,
I DON'T HAVE A HOME.
I DON'T HAVE A HUSBAND.
HE'S GONE. HE'S GONE, B.
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO, DANNY?
I DON'T KNOW.
I DON'T KNOW, MAN.
I JUST, LIKE...
I TRY EVERYTHING.
I'VE BEEN POSTPALING.
IT DOESN'T WORK WELL,
AND THEN I'VE BEEN
BRAIDING HAIR,
BUT ALL I NEED IS $200.
GIRL, YOU BETTER SELL THEM RINGS
IF ALL YOU NEED IS $200.
- THESE?
- YES, THOSE.
I CAN'T SELL THESE RINGS.
- MAN, NO. THIS IS A HEIRLOOM.
- A HEIRLOOM?
THIS IS, LIKE, SUPPOSED
TO GO TO WES.
GIRL, THOSE ARE TOMATOES.
NO. WES WOULD NOT
WANT YOU IN A TENT
ON THE SIDE OF A ROAD
WITH HIS BABY.
WES IS MY DAUGHTER,
AND SAM WOULDN'T WANT...
OH, MY GOD, GIRL, I'M HIGH.
LISTEN. I CAN'T LET YOU COME
AND STAY HERE BECAUSE WE GOT...
DUDE, IT'S ROOMMATES
AND HELLA KIDS.
I DON'T MOVE IN WITH CHAD
FOR A LITTLE WHILE,
OR ELSE I WOULD JUST TELL YOU
TO COME OUT THERE WITH ME,
AND I SPENT ALL MY DAMN SPARE
MONEY ON THE WEED.
OHH!
I DON'T FEEL GOOD, DUDE.
- OH, DANNY. THE WEED.
- I DON'T FEEL GOOD.
I COMPLETELY FORGOT
ABOUT THE WEED.
YOU WEREN'T IN THE RIGHT MINDSET
FOR WHAT I PUT IN THE WEED.
DANNY: I DON'T FEEL GOOD, B.
I DON'T FEEL GOOD, MAN.
BROOKLYNN: LET ME GET YOU
SOME WATER, GIRL.
WE GONNA GET YOU SOME WATER,
AND WE GONNA...
DANNY: WHAT DID YOU PUT IN IT?
BROOKLYNN: GIRL, LOOK.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT ALL THAT.
- I'MMA GET YOU SOME WATER.
- NO.
- SO YOU CAN DO WHAT YOU...
- I GOT TO GO.
I TOLD YOU...
BROOKLYNN: OH, MY GOD.
I NEED SOME WATER.
DANNY: I GOT TO GO.
BROOKLYNN: OH, GIRL.
BROOKLYNN: BUT WAIT.
WE'RE GONNA GET YOU WATER.
DANNY: I GOT TO GET UP.
BROOKLYNN: THESE MY TOWELS?
DANNY: WHY ARE WE HERE?
BROOKLYNN: DID I NOT
FOLD UP THE TOWELS?
DANNY: HOW DID WE GET HERE?
BROOKLYNN: WHO TOLD US
TO GET ON THE SLIDE?
DANNY: THAT WAS PROBABLY
YOUR IDEA, BROOKLYNN.
BROOKLYNN: I THINK IT WAS.
DANNY: ALL YOUR IDEAS
END UP LIKE THIS, BROOKLYNN.
BROOKLYNN: I HAD ANOTHER IDEA,
THOUGH.
WHAT WAS IT?
DANNY: NO MORE IDEAS.
I GOT TO GO.
BROOKLYNN: WATER.
I NEED TO GET YOU WATER, DANNY.
DANNY: I GOT TO GO.
BROOKLYNN: WATER. OOH.
BROOKLYNN: OK.
OH, MY GOD.
I DON'T THINK I CAN MOVE.
THERE WAS SOMETHING
I WAS SUPPOSED TO BE DOING.
DANNY: BYE, BROOKLYNN.
BYE.
BROOKLYNN: SELL THE RING, DANNY.
WHAT DID I DO WITH MY JOINT?
AAH!
[WOO & THE CLOUDS'
"WASH OVER ME" PLAYING]
MAN: ♪ THE RISING TIDE ♪
♪ THEY WASH OVER ME ♪
♪ EXCUSE MY PRIDE ♪
♪ DON'T KNOW
WHAT CAME OVER ME ♪
♪ I CHOOSE TO HIDE ♪
♪ IMPULSIVELY ♪
♪ DESPITE MY WAYS ♪
♪ YOU WATCH OVER ME ♪
♪ WASH OVER ME ♪
♪ JUST CLEANSE ME, PLEASE ♪
DANNY: AAH!
[BUZZ]
[GRUNTS]
OH, JEEZ.
WHAT?
NO.
OH, SHIT.
OH, MY GOD. OH, MY GOD.
OH, MY GOD!
OHH. EXCUSE ME.
HAVE YOU SEE A GOLD RING?
[SPEAKS SPANISH]
OH, SAM. WHERE IS IT?
EXCUSE ME.
HAVE YOU SEEN A RING,
A GOLD RING?
EXCUSE ME, SIR.
HAVE YOU SEEN A RING?
ANYONE SEEN A RING?
BROOKLYNN!
BROOKLYNN, ARE YOU HOME?
HEY. HEY, BROOKLYNN.
ARE YOU HOME RIGHT NOW?
I'M OUTSIDE.
OH, MAN.
HAVE YOU SEEN A RING?
YOU KNOW, SAM'S RING,
THE GOLD RING.
OH, MAN. I SHOULD HAVE PUT IT
BACK IN MY POUCH.
WHAT WAS I DOING
WEARING THAT THING?
I DON'T KNOW WHERE IT IS.
DO YOU SEE IT ANYWHERE?
ALL RIGHT. ALL RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT. BYE, BYE, BYE.
OH, SHIT.
OH, DAMN IT.
BE HERE. COME ON.
OH, MY GOD.
OH, MAN.
NO!
WHERE IS IT, SAM? WHERE?
WHERE ARE YOU, SAM?
WHERE ARE YOU?!
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
HELLO.
OH, HEY, BABY.
HOW ARE YOU, HONEY?
NO. I'M FINE. I'M FINE.
YOU HAVING A GOOD DAY?
GOOD.
UM, YEAH. I'M ON MY WAY.
I'M COMING.
COULD YOU PUT MS. CYNTHIA
ON THE PHONE?
OK. I LOVE YOU.
HEY. UM, YEAH. I'M, UM...
I'M GONNA BE A LITTLE LATE.
YEAH. I'M SORRY.
LIKE, TWO MORE HOURS.
I KNOW. I'M SORRY, OK?
I JUST NEED TWO MORE HOURS.
JUST TWO, JUST TWO.
I'LL BE THERE.
OK? I'LL BE THERE AT 7:00,
ALL RIGHT? OK.
THANK YOU. THANKS. BYE.
[DANNY AND JACOB LAUGHING]
THAT'S A SECRET.
YOU CAN'T TELL NOBODY.
MAN, I'M TELLING EVERYBODY.
I'M TELLING EVERYBODY.
MM-HMM. ALL RIGHT.
WHOSE TURN IS IT?
- IT'S MY TURN.
- IT'S YOUR TURN.
- OK.
- TWO TRUTHS AND A LIE.
ALL RIGHT.
SAM WAS MY BEST FRIEND.
I REALLY CARE ABOUT YOU AND WES,
AND I REALLY LIKE THIS BEER.
YOU LYING, DUDE.
YOU HATE BEER, JACOB.
I KNOW YOU WENT AND BOUGHT THIS
BECAUSE I WAS COMING,
SO GO AHEAD AND DRINK.
IT'S DELICIOUS, HUH?
CHUG, CHUG, CHUG.
THERE WE GO.
MMM.
- ALL RIGHT. SO IT'S MY TURN.
- YEP.
ALL RIGHT.
OK.
WES IS DOING REALLY WELL
IN SCHOOL,
UH, WE LIVE IN A TENT
ON THE SIDE OF THE ROAD,
AND I'M REALLY HAPPY.
WELL, THAT'S OBVIOUS AND EASY.
YOU LIVING ON THE SIDE
OF THE ROAD IN A TENT.
DRINK.
YOU DRINK.
YOU'RE LIVING ON THE SIDE
OF THE ROAD WITH WES?
DRINK.
DANNY, WHAT THE HELL?
WHY HAVEN'T YOU TOLD ME
WHAT'S GOING ON?
I MEAN... I HAVEN'T TOLD
ANYBODY ANYTHING.
I DON'T... THAT'S WHY YOU
HAVEN'T SEEN ME.
I DON'T WANT ANYONE TO KNOW.
I MEAN, EXCEPT FOR BROOKLYNN,
BUT THAT'S BECAUSE
SHE GOT ME HIGH, SO...
BROOKLYNN? WHY WOULD YOU
TELL BROOKLYNN'S CRAZY ASS?
I RAN INTO HER.
DANNY, WHAT DO YOU NEED?
WELL, I NEED $200.
LIKE, I'M GOOD FOR IT.
I HAVE CLIENTS LINED UP
ALL NEXT WEEK.
IT'S JUST THAT...
I GOT SHORTED TODAY,
AND THAT'S WHY YOU SEE ME
GOING AROUND
DOING POSTPALS AND EVERYTHING
BECAUSE I JUST NEED TO
GET THIS APARTMENT.
I'M SO CLOSE.
WELL, I JUST PAID MY BILLS,
BUT I CAN GIVE YOU 75, 80,
AND... AND WE'LL FIGURE OUT
THE REST IN A FEW DAYS.
I APPRECIATE THAT.
I DO, BUT, UM... IT'S JUST NOT
GONNA WORK
BECAUSE I HAVE TO GIVE HIM
THE MONEY TODAY.
HE'S ONLY HOLDING IT...
FOR ONE MORE DAY.
HE'S BEEN HOLDING IT
FOR A REALLY LONG TIME,
SO I JUST... I DON'T KNOW, MAN.
WELL... WHAT IF YOU AND WES
JUST COME STAY WITH ME?
YOU CAN... BE OFF THE STREET,
AND YOU CAN SAVE
FOR AN APARTMENT,
AND YOU DON'T GOT TO RUSH
AND JUST TAKE ANYTHING.
YOU SERIOUS?
JUST STAY IN MY GRANDMA'S
OLD ROOM.
- THIS ONE HERE?
- YEAH, THAT ONE.
- YOU'RE NOT KIDDING?
- NO.
I WANT YOU... I WANT TO LOOK OUT
FOR YOU AND WES,
SO YOU CAN STAY HERE.
DANNY: OH, MY GOD.
I MEAN... YOU HAVE NO IDEA.
I THOUGHT I WAS GONNA
HAVE TO TELL WES.
YOU KNOW, I'VE BEEN
TELLING HER WE'VE BEEN CAMPING,
SO SHE THINKS
WE'VE BEEN CAMPING,
AND SHE JUST KEEPS SAYING
HOW MUCH SHE WANTS TO GO HOME,
AND I, LIKE...
I CAN'T THANK YOU ENOUGH.
DANNY, COME ON.
I WANT TO LOOK OUT FOR YOU TWO.
- MAN.
- I'M HERE FOR YOU,
BOTH OF YOUSE.
YOU KNOW HOW I FEEL ABOUT YOU.
- THANK YOU.
- ALL THESE YEARS, AND...
I KNOW... HEH... HELL,
I INTRODUCED SAM TO YOU,
AND I SHOULD HAVE NEV...
I SHOULD HAVE
REALLY TOLD YOU HOW I FELT.
OH. YOU DON'T HAVE TO DO
THAT, THOUGH.
- IT'S NOT LIKE THAT,
- DANNY.
DANNY, I WANT YOU.
JACOB, PLEASE DON'T DO THAT.
I TOLD YOU BEFORE
IT'S NOT LIKE THAT.
- IT'S OK. STOP, OK?
- DANNY, SHH.
- STOP!
- OK! OK, OK. I'M SORRY.
DANNY, WHERE YOU GOING?
DANNY: NO, DUDE.
GET OFF OF ME.
WHAT THE FUCK IS WRONG WITH YOU?
[SIGHS]
SHIT.
[WOO & THE CLOUDS'
"WASH OVER ME (REMIX)" PLAYING]
♪ WASH OVER ME ♪
♪ WASH OVER ME, WASH OVER ME ♪
♪ WASH OVER ME, WASH OVER ME
WASH OVER ME ♪
♪ WASH OVER ME ♪
♪ WASH OVER ME, WASH OVER ME ♪
♪ WASH OVER ME, WASH OVER ME
WASH OVER ME ♪
♪ WASH OVER ME ♪
♪ WASH OVER ME, WASH OVER ME ♪
♪ WASH OVER ME, WASH OVER ME
WASH OVER ME ♪
♪ THE RISING TIDE ♪
♪ THEY WASH OVER ME ♪
♪ WASH OVER ME,
WASH OVER ME ♪
♪ WASH OVER ME, WASH OVER ME
♪ EXCUSE MY PRIDE ♪
♪ DON'T KNOW WHAT CAME OVER ME ♪
♪ WASH OVER ME, WASH OVER ME ♪
♪ WASH OVER ME, WASH OVER ME,
WASH OVER ME ♪
♪ I CHOOSE TO HIDE ♪
♪ IMPULSIVELY ♪
♪ WASH OVER ME, WASH OVER ME ♪
♪ WASH OVER ME, WASH OVER ME,
WASH OVER ME ♪
♪ DESPITE MY WAYS ♪
♪ YOU WATCH OVER ME ♪
♪ WASH OVER ME,
WASH OVER ME ♪
♪ WASH OVER ME, WASH OVER ME
HEY, BROOKLYNN.
WHAT'S UP?
NO WAY.
WHAT?! OH, SHIT.
WHERE WAS IT?
IN THE LAUNDRY BASKET?
OH, MY GOD!
OK, OK, OK, OK.
UM, YOU'RE AT HOME, RIGHT?
OK. STAY THERE.
DON'T GO ANYWHERE.
NO. I'M NOT FAR, I'M NOT FAR.
I'M JUST AT THE PARK.
I'M... I'M UP A TREE.
NO, THAT'S NOT A METAPHOR.
I'M REALLY UP A TREE,
SO JUST STAY THERE.
I'M COMING, OK?
ALL RIGHT. ALL RIGHT.
DON'T GO ANYWHERE.
BYE.
OHH. OHH.
BROOKLYNN: WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
WHY WOULD YOU JUST LEAVE THEM
IN MY FRONT YARD LIKE THIS?
THESE AREN'T NEW WASHERS.
HOW AM I SUPPOSED TO GET
WATER IN HERE?
HEY, BROOKLYNN.
BROOKLYNN: SEE, THIS IS WHY
I'M LEAVING.
GOOD-BYE.
DANNY: HEY!
BROOKLYNN: OHH. HEY, GIRL.
- THANKS FOR CALLING ME!
- YES!
YOU GOT IT? WHAT ARE THESE?
APPARENTLY MY NEW WASHERS.
THESE ARE YOUR NEW WASHERS?
GIRL, HELL, NO, THEY AIN'T NEW.
NO. GHETTO-ASS LANDLORD.
THIS WHY I'M LEAVING.
I KNOW YOU KNOW WHAT
I'M THINKING RIGHT NOW.
YOU WENT AND GOT YOUR HAIR DONE?
HOW... YOU WENT AND GOT
IT BRAIDED?
YOU KNOW I COULD HAVE
BRAIDED IT.
I SAT THERE
AND TOLD YOU EVERYTHING,
AND YOU LEFT AND GOT IT BRAIDED,
AND YOU...
I HADN'T SEEN YOU IN AGES.
I DID NOT KNOW YOU WERE
SUPPOSED TO BE HERE TODAY,
AND IN MY DEFENSE,
I DID NOT HAVE THE MONEY.
CHAD PAID FOR IT
BECAUSE, YOU KNOW, HE DON'T WANT
HIS WOMAN OUT IN CALABASAS
LOOKING CRAZY.
THESE EDGES ARE TOO TIGHT.
YOU'RE GONNA BE LOSING
YOUR HAIR.
CHAD... HE GONNA PAY
FOR YOUR REGROW, TOO?
THE SHADE OF IT ALL.
HA HA HA!
WHERE'S THE RING.
WHERE IS IT?
- BAM!
- EEH!
OH, MY GOD!
THANK YOU SO MUCH, BROOKLYNN.
I TOTALLY THOUGHT
I WAS GONNA...
NEVER SEE THIS AGAIN.
YEAH, GIRL. IT WAS CRAZY.
IT WAS STUCK, LIKE,
IN THE...
IN BETWEEN THE WICKER
IN THE LAUNDRY BASKET.
DUDE, YEAH. GOD.
YOU DON'T KNOW HOW MUCH
THIS MEANS TO ME, MAN.
I JUST THOUGHT... TODAY'S
JUST BEEN...
WE'LL HAVE TO TALK OVER DRINKS,
BUT I GOT TO GO GET WES,
AND I'LL TALK TO YOU SOON.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
YOU ABOUT TO GO SELL THAT RING?
NO. LIKE, BROOKLYNN,
I TOLD YOU
HOW MUCH THIS MEANS TO ME.
THIS IS SAM'S RING.
I GOT SOME OTHER THINGS
BACK WHERE I'M STAYING
THAT I COULD PAWN,
AND I'M CERTAIN
I CAN GET, LIKE, 200
OR SOMETHING OFF OF IT
IF I... LISTEN. I GOT THIS.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
I DON'T NEED THAT FACE.
BROOKLYNN: WE FOUND THAT RING
IN THAT BASKET FOR A REASON.
THAT WAS A SIGN FROM SAM.
OK. LISTEN, PASTOR BROOKLYNN.
I GO TO CHURCH ON SUNDAYS.
IT'S MONDAY,
SO I'M GONNA GET THIS DONE.
DON'T YOU WORRY.
I DON'T NEED YOUR PREACHING.
I'LL LET YOU KNOW HOW IT GOES,
AND THANK YOU! MM-WHA!
I'LL TALK TO YOU SOON, OK?
BYE!
BROOKLYNN: THERE SHE GOES,
SKATING OFF AGAIN,
NOT LISTENING AND SHIT.
OHH. I'M GONNA PRAY FOR HER.
NOW WHAT AM I GONNA DO
WITH Y'ALL?
OH, MY GOD.
YOU FUCKER, GIVE ME MY STUFF!
OW!
YOU FUCKER! NO! LET GO!
MAN: GIVE ME THE BAG!
DANNY: NO! STOP!
[BOTH GRUNTING]
MAN: FUCKING BAG!
DANNY: NO!
MAN: FUCKING BITCH!
I'LL HURT YOU!
OK. FUCK. OK.
DANNY: LET GO! LET GO!
MAN: GODDAMN IT.
OH, SHIT.
DANNY: NO! AAH! FUCK!
[GRUNTING]
STOP!
[WHIMPERS]
UNH!
[MAN GRUNTING]
AGH!
FUCK. UGH.
- FUCK YOU.
- NO!
FUCK.
GODDAMN IT!
OH, SHIT.
BROOKLYNN!
BROOKLYNN, BROOKLYNN.
OH, SHIT, GIRL.
WHAT HAPPENED TO YOU?
DO YOU HAVE A WASHCLOTH
OR SOMETHING?
YOU GOT INTO IT
WITH A ICE SKATER, DIDN'T YOU?
THAT DOESN'T EVEN MAKE
ANY SENSE.
BECAUSE I THOUGHT ICE SKATERS
AND ROLLER SKATERS
HAVE BEEF OR SOMETHING.
CAN YOU JUST GIVE ME
A WASHCLOTH?
YELLING AT ME BECAUSE YOU DONE
SKITCHED OUT ON YOUR SKATES?
I DIDN'T SKITCH OUT.
HERE. I GOT A WET ONE
OR A DRY ONE.
- THANK YOU.
- BUT SERIOUSLY,
WHAT HAPPENED?
DANNY: DON'T WORRY
ABOUT IT, MAN.
UGH. MY FEET HURT SO BADLY.
BROOKLYNN: I GUESS SO.
YOU BEEN SKATING AROUND PACOIMA.
OK. SO SERIOUSLY, DID YOU WIN
THE ROLLER DERBY BATTLE?
I'LL TELL YOU SOME OTHER TIME,
BROOKLYNN.
COULD I LEAVE THIS STUFF HERE?
EVER SINCE YOU BEEN HERE,
YOU BEEN ASKING ME TO DO SHIT.
COULD YOU PLEASE HELP ME?
I CAN COME GET IT LATER.
I JUST NEED TO FIGURE OUT
MY NEXT MOVE.
IT'S GONNA HAVE TO BE
LATER, GIRL.
I GOT PLANS. CHAD'S ON HIS WAY
TO COME GET ME.
ALL RIGHT. WELL, IS THERE
ANYTHING IN MY HAIR?
YOU GOT GRASS IN YOUR HAIR
AND STUFF?
WHAT IS... WHAT?
IS THAT GRASS AND TWIGS?
WHAT HAPPENED TO YOU?
ALL RIGHT. IS IT OUT?
BROOKLYNN: WHO DO I NEED
TO CALL?
- OK. IS IT OUT?
- YES.
DO I LOOK OK?
I MEAN, I GUESS.
LEAVE YOU ALONE
FOR A FEW MINUTES,
YOU COMING BACK LOOKING
ALL BEAT UP AND TATTERED.
ALL RIGHT. I'LL BE BACK
A LITTLE BIT LATER.
- I LOOK ALL RIGHT, RIGHT?
- YEAH.
- ALL RIGHT. OK.
- ALL RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT. BYE. THANK YOU.
I'LL BE BACK.
BROOKLYNN: I'MMA PRAY FOR YOU.
DANNY: THANK YOU.
[MUSIC PLAYING ON CAR STEREO]
[MUSIC STOPS]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
MAN: HEY, BEAUTIFUL.
HOW YOU DOING? YOU ALL RIGHT?
YOU A PREACHER?
THIS YOUR CHURCH?
I AIN'T NEVER SEEN A REVEREND
IN SKATES.
AUTOMATED VOICE: INCOMING CALL
FROM SUGAR LIPS.
SO MY CAR'S GOING OFF
BECAUSE THAT'S... HOLD ON.
AUTOMATED VOICE: CALL DECLINED.
MAN: IT'S MESSED UP.
I APOLOGIZE.
IT KEPT BEEPING.
WHAT YOU DOING OUT HERE
IN SKATES?
THEM SKATES? THEM SKATES.
WHAT YOU DOING OUT HERE
SKATING IN THIS NEIGHBORHOOD?
YOU SHOULDN'T EVEN BE
WALKING AROUND HERE,
LET ALONE SKATING, HUH?
YOU MUST GOT SOMEBODY.
BECAUSE IF YOU WAS ON YOUR OWN,
YOU WOULD AT LEAST HAVE A CAR.
ASS LIKE THAT,
YOU'D HAVE A CAR, BOAT,
HELICOPTER, SOMETHING.
YOU DON'T NEED A CAR?
I MEAN, ALL YOU GOT TO DO
IS TALK TO ME.
IT'S COMMUNICATION, YOU KNOW?
QUIET TYPE, HUH?
THAT MEANS SMART.
THAT'S WHAT MY MOTHER SAYS.
SHE SAYS MOST WOMEN
THAT'S REAL QUIET,
IT MEAN THAT THEY REALLY SMART
BECAUSE THEY LISTEN.
THEY ABSORB STUFF LIKE
A SPONGE, YOU KNOW,
AND THAT'S GOOD, YOU KNOW,
BUT YOU OUT HERE SKATING.
THAT'S... SHOULDN'T BE DOING THAT.
YOU SHOULD COME WITH ME.
I GOT A NICE LITTLE PLACE
IN CALABASAS ALL BY MYSELF
WITH GOLDFISH.
- CHAD?
- REAL QUIET.
THEY DON'T TALK A LOT NEITHER.
HEH HEH!
I GOT A CAT, TOO, WITH 3 LEGS.
IT'S A RESCUE.
THAT'S WHAT THEY TOLD ME
I NEEDED TO DO.
I NEEDED TO HAVE A RESCUE PET
IN ORDER TO MAKE ME LOOK GOOD.
IT'S COOL. HE AIN'T FUN
BECAUSE HE CAN'T DO
WHAT OTHER CATS DO,
BUT HE ALL RIGHT.
COME ON. MAKE YOUR NEXT MOVE
YOUR BEST MOVE.
COME WITH ME.
I'LL GET YOU A CAR.
WELL, LOOK HERE.
GET YOU SOME NEW SKATES.
NO? YEAH.
YOU NEED THAT, RIGHT?
HUH? HOW THAT SOUND? NO?
BECAUSE YOU'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
WELL, GOD BLESS YOU.
[REVS ENGINE]
[REVERSE SIGNAL BEEPING]
SKATES DON'T COST THAT MUCH.
THE LORD PROBABLY
GOT YOU ANYWAY.
[KNOCKS ON DOOR]
MOMMY!
HA HA HA! OH, MY GOD!
HEY, LITTLE ONE. YOU OK?
HOW WAS YOUR DAY?
- GOOD!
- YEAH?
- MM-HMM.
- WHAT'D YOU DO?
WHAT DID I DO? LET'S SEE.
I DID SCIENCE,
I PLAYED WITH LUKE,
AND I DID MATH.
YEAH. SHE'S BEEN
PRETTY EXCITED TODAY
ABOUT SOME SURPRISE.
YEAH. WE'RE MOVING
TO A NEW HOUSE!
OH, NO. NO, WE'RE NOT.
WE'RE GET... IT'S A DOLLHOUSE
I'M GETTING HER.
AND A DOLLHOUSE?
CAN WE ALSO GET A FAN?
ALL RIGHT. SO THANK YOU.
YOU'RE WELCOME OF COURSE.
I'LL SEE YOU TOMORROW?
TOMORROW. TOMORROW SOUNDS GOOD.
CYNTHIA: ALL RIGHT.
DANNY: ALL RIGHT. BYE.
WES: BYE! I WANT TO
SHOW YOU MY DOLLHOUSE.
DANNY: ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
I THOUGHT WE WERE SUPPOSED
TO KEEP OUR SECRET SECRET.
WES: OH, YEAH. SORRY.
DANNY: IT'S OUR SECRET.
OH.
WES: MOMMY, WHY ARE WE HERE?
I'M HOT.
BARBER: LOOK WHO'S BACK.
DANNY: YEAH.
BARBER: BROUGHT YOUR MINI-ME.
DANNY: MM-HMM.
BARBER: GOT SOMETHING FOR ME?
- YES, I DO.
- FOLLOW ME.
DANNY: I'LL BE RIGHT WITH YOU.
HAVE A SEAT RIGHT HERE, BABY.
LISTEN.
OK, BABY. I HAVE SOME
BUSINESS TO TAKE CARE OF,
BUT I WAS THINKING BEFORE I GO
WE CAN MAKE
ONE MORE ANGEL WISH.
- OK.
I'LL MAKE MINE FIRST.
OK.
WAS IT A GOOD ONE?
- YEAH.
- YEAH?
BUT HOW DO WE KNOW THAT
ANGELS REALLY GRANT WISHES?
YOU'LL KNOW THAT ANGEL WISHES
WORK THROUGH DADDY
BECAUSE DADDY WILL SHOW YOU.
THAT'S WHAT HE DOES FOR ME.
[WOO & THE CLOUDS' "UPTOWN
IN THE SPRING" PLAYING]
♪ SOON I WILL BE ♪
DANNY: I KNOW YOU MIGHT FEEL
LIKE YOU'RE ALONE SOMETIMES.
YOU MIGHT FEEL THAT
THINGS AREN'T FAIR
OR THAT A PART OF YOU
IS MISSING
AND THAT MAYBE EVEN
DADDY LEFT US...
BUT HE HASN'T.
I PROMISE YOU HE HASN'T...
SINGER: ♪ I SURRENDER
ALL MY STRENGTH ♪
DANNY: BECAUSE HE'S ALL
AROUND US ALWAYS.
SINGER: ♪ LOSING FAITH ♪
DANNY: HE'S IN THE TREES...
SINGER: ♪ FIGHTING
ETERNAL DREAMS ♪
DANNY:
AND LIKE THE ROOTS OF THE TREE,
WE MIGHT NOT SEE THEM...
SINGER: ♪ WITHOUT YOUR HANDS ♪
DANNY: BUT WE KNOW THEY'RE
THERE ALWAYS SUPPORTING US.
SINGER:
♪ I TRY TO HIDE MY FACE ♪
♪ STARTLED BY MY REFLECTION ♪
DANNY: HE'S IN THE AIR.
WES: EVEN IN THE SKY?
DANNY: EVEN IN THE SKY...
SINGER: ♪ WHAT'S STARING ♪
DANNY: AND WHEN THE WIND
WRAPS AROUND YOU,
YOU'LL KNOW THAT THAT'S
DADDY'S EMBRACE,
SO THAT'S HOW I KNOW
ANGEL WISHES WORK
BECAUSE I KNOW...
MY WISH CAME TRUE.
SINGER: ♪ INVITED ME TO FLY ♪
♪ BUT THINK I LOST MY MARBLES ♪
OK. YOU BE GOOD. I GOT TO
GO TAKE CARE OF SOMETHING, OK?
- OK.
- ALL RIGHT. BE GOOD.
HEY, BOBBY.
YOU READY?
CAN I STILL GET 300 FOR THIS?
- AS PROMISED.
- ALL RIGHT.
LET'S DO IT.
BE RIGHT BACK.
SINGER: ♪ WE'LL ALL BE FREE ♪
♪ AS SOON AS I CHOOSE IT ♪
♪ WE'LL ALL BE FREE ♪
♪ WE'LL ALL
BE FREE ♪
♪ WE'LL ALL BE FREE ♪
1...
2...
3.
YOU GOOD?
YEP, I'M GOOD.
SINGER: ♪ AS SOON
AS I CHOOSE IT ♪
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'LL HOLD IT FOR A WEEK
BEFORE I PUT IT OUT.
THANK YOU.
BOBBY: Y'ALL BE SAFE OUT THERE.
SINGER: ♪ AS SOON
AS I CHOOSE IT ♪
DANNY: OK, BABY.
YOU READY TO GO?
WES: MM-HMM.
- ARE YOU HUNGRY?
- YEAH.
YEAH? OK.
- HEY, MOMMY.
- HMM?
WHAT DID YOU WISH FOR?
OH, I WISHED FOR YOU
TO ALWAYS BE SAFE AND HAPPY.
WHAT'D YOU WISH FOR?
- UM... A FAN.
- A FAN.
AGAIN, A FAN? THE SAME THING?
WES: WELL, I'M NOT KIDDING.
IT'S HOT.
DANNY: HMM. I KNOW.
SINGER: ♪ I SURRENDER
ALL MY STRENGTH ♪
♪ I CONFESS I'M LOSING FAITH ♪
♪ FIGHTING ETERNAL DREAMS ♪
♪ I CAN'T DO THIS
WITHOUT YOUR HANDS ♪
♪ SEE, I TRY TO HIDE MY FACE ♪
WES: ME? I BARELY MOVED.
DANNY: JUMP, JUMP.
WES: CAN YOU BEAT THIS?
DANNY: YEAH. HA HA HA!
LET'S GO PLAY. COME ON.
SINGER: ♪ STARING ♪
♪ THE MIRROR STARTED
SHATTERING ♪
WES: SEE? IT'S EASIER
WHEN I DO IT.
I'LL RACE YOU,
AND I'M WALKING!
DANNY, VOICE-OVER: AND I ALSO
KNOW THAT IT'S GONNA BE
ALL RIGHT BECAUSE I HAVE YOU,
AND DADDY LIVES ON THROUGH YOU.
DANNY: WHOO!
WES: I CAN TOUCH THE MOON!
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA!
FUN.
DANNY: ALL RIGHT.
GONNA SET YOU DOWN.
COME GET HIM.
- OOH! CATCH HIM!
- WHOO!
HA HA HA!
SINGER: ♪ AS SOON
AS I CHOOSE IT ♪
♪ WE'LL ALL BE FREE ♪
♪ SOON I WILL BE FREE ♪
HEY, WES, LOOK AT THAT.
SINGER: ♪ AS SOON
AS I CHOOSE IT ♪
♪ WE'LL ALL BE FREE ♪
♪ WE'LL ALL
BE FREE ♪
- BEAUTIFUL.
- RIGHT?
HA HA HA!
[FIREWORKS EXPLODE]
[CRYING]
SINGER: ♪ HEY,
BRAND NEW DAY-AY-AY-AY ♪
♪ SUN ON MY FACE, HEY ♪
♪ CAME A LONG WAY, HEY ♪
♪ FREQUENCY ♪
♪ SOCIETY ♪
♪ ANXIETY ♪
♪ ...HEY ♪
♪ CHANGE ♪
♪ ...CHANGE ♪
♪ SAYIN' ALL RIGHT ♪
♪ ...ALL RIGHT,
I'M GIVIN' ALL RIGHT ♪
♪ CHANGE ♪
♪ BEEN A LONG WAY, CHANGE ♪
♪ MOVIN' MY FEET, I'VE BEEN
PAYING MY WAY, LONG WAY ♪
♪ CHANGE ♪
♪ LONG WAY, KEEPING ALL RIGHT,
CHANGE ♪
♪ ...MY FACE, TAKE A LOOK AT
MY FACE, BEEN A LONG WAY ♪
♪ CHANGE ♪
♪ SMILE ON MY FACE, CHANGE ♪
♪ MOVING MY FEET,
PAYING MY WAY ♪
♪ ...LONG WAY, HEY ♪
[SCAT SINGING]
♪ IT'S A BRAND NEW DAY ♪
♪ HEY ♪
♪ A BRAND NEW DAY-AY-AY-AY ♪
♪ SUN ON MY FACE ♪
♪ HEY ♪
♪ ...IT'S A BRAND-NEW DAY ♪
MAN, RAPPING:
♪ ...WITH A RUNNING GRIN ♪
♪ ...THIS IS FROM A LIE
TO A MAN ♪
♪ BE DOWN FROM THE STREETS
PARALLEL... ♪
♪ IMAGINATION INCREASE
THE MIND ♪
♪ THERE'S PLENTY THERE
BY THE SYSTEM OF DESIGN ♪
♪ IT WAS WRITTEN IN THE SKY,
I WAS BORN TO LEAD ♪
♪ REACH DOWN IN THE EARTH
WITH THE BEST SEEDS ♪
♪ BETTER BELIEVE, WATCH ME ♪
♪ BLESS THE WATER,
SLAY THE DEMON ♪
♪ PREACH THE WISDOM
ACROSS THE GLOBE ♪
♪ TEACH THE KIDS
SOME MAGIC FLOW ♪
♪ START A LIE
WITH MY THIRD EYE ♪
♪ ...MENTION MY COMPREHENSION ♪
♪ RESURRECTION...
INTENTION SO THE ♪
♪ YOUNGER ME KEEP SUFFERING ♪
♪ THERE YOU GO... ♪
[SCAT SINGING]
♪ IT'S A BRAND NEW DAY ♪
♪ HEY ♪
♪ IT'S A BRAND
NEW DAY-AY-AY-AY ♪
♪ SUN ON MY FACE ♪
♪ HEY ♪
♪ ...IT'S A BRAND NEW DAY ♪
♪ HEY, A BRAND NEW
DAY-AY-AY-AY ♪
♪ SUN ON MY FACE ♪
♪ HEY ♪
♪ ...IT'S A BRAND NEW DAY ♪
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull