Old man?
Old man are you awake?
Or are you sleeping?
When I couldn't sleep,
my mom would tell me a story
My favorite was about a wandering man
who was lost
After walking for a long time,
he became tired and hungry.
Without food and water
he thought he would die
and would cry in pain.
Then a rabbit that was passing by
felt sorry for him
and she offered herself as food,
to save his life.
As a thank you,
the man carved the image of the rabbit
on the moon
so that she would be with him...
...forever.
Panties too?
Si.
You looking for work?
- Si.
I've got three
hours, 12 dollars an hour.
- Yeah, all of you guys.
So this whole thing is coming down,
you can see that already came down,
we have to move everything out
and anything metal, copper
or anything shiny basically,
I want you to take that
out and put it here.
Hi my love, how are you?
- Where are you?
What are you doing?
And the kids, how are they?
Do they ask abut me?
How I miss their smiles...
- All this shit still has to,
no, all this shit goes
now, everything has to go.
How is Havana?
Did you get the package I sent you?
The extra money is for you
to buy yourself something beautiful.
I have a new job, it's in an office.
They pay me more than before
but it's a lot of hours and
the work is hard.
But it's okay.
Everything here is extreme.
The weather is either too hot
or too cold; there is no in-between
This place makes me
miss you so much.
I dreamt about you last night.
We were floating on the Almendares River.
40,
that's a little more.
You were looking at me with a strange look,
Thanks man.
and you were silent for a while, but...
Garcias.
He paid us well, didn't he?
He paid us shit.
you start to tell me softly...
I'm still here.
Over and over again.
And you were floating away...
... I swam toward you but the currents
would pull me farther away.
I woke up in a panic, then was relieved because
it was only a dream.
I brought more.
Look over here!
I have so much more to tell you.
In my spare time, I've been
taking care of hurt animals
until they recover.
Is anyone hungry?
Yes.
And the girl?
Some take longer than others, but...
When they are better I let them go.
Eat!
You have to eat!
Does anyone need to use the bathroom?
There is one in particular
She's been with me longer than the rest.
It's a kitten.
She's scared,
but I think you would like her.
It's getting late my love.
I have to go
but I will dream of you.
both of us in the river,
laughing, swimming, and floating
and with your sweet voice
you will say,
I'm still here.
I love you my love.
Don't fuck with me.
How much longer?
He says he almost has all the money.
Then I'll come and get her.
No, that wasn't the deal!
She's been here too long.
She doesn't eat, she doesn't speak!
If something-
- Relax! Calm down!
She's scared, you know how kids are.
She's fine.
Look, keep, taking care of her here.
I'm going to pay you good money.
I'll call you tomorrow!
Are you okay, kitty?
Do you need anything?
Can you hear me?
Are you cold, old man?
Do you like the snow?
I like it.
I saw the snow once.
My mom took me.
She saved up money
and took me to the mountains.
When we got there,
everything
was covered in white snow.
My mommy and me
on top of the snow.
It was beautiful.
A pack of cigarettes.
Do you have to use the bathroom?
What are you writing?
Do you feel like walking around a little bit?
Be careful.
Do you like this place,
or do you miss Mexico?
I hate this place.
Your dad comes next week.
Does that make you happy?
I don't know.
You are lucky, you know that?
When I was born in Cuba, my dad
had already left and I never met him
I don't care now, but I did when
I was your age.
Do you know your dad?
I never met him.
Even though he wasn't in your life,
I know he loves you a lot.
Your dad really loves you.
Look, it's beautiful.
You see, it's easy.
See? Give me another.
Do you like music?
Do you like music, little cat?
This is one of my favorites.
I remember those days
when all the kids from my block
would come out of their houses
and we would would play for hours.
we'd forget about everything and everyone.
It was like
we were in a world
that was only ours.
We would sing.
We would dance.
Until I heard a voice
Cecilia!
calling me because it was time for dinner.
It was my mommy.
- Hello?
Yes?
When, today?
What time?
Okay, she will be ready.
Are you happy you will see your dad?
Si, no?
I don't know.
Let's go.
Don't be afraid.
Remember what I told you.
Your dad loves you a lot.
Hurry up!
We'll be driving for a few hours.
You want to sleep?
Plans have changed,
I have absolutely no idea
where your dad is.
You are going to stay with me.
Are you a mute?
Kids, kids...
What are you looking at?
- Hey.
Hey.
Nothing.
Do you want to use the restroom?
Are you sure?
Stay here, I'll be back.
My Love, I've been thinking about you tonight.
You would like this place.
There is so much to do
and so much to see.
I think you would like my friends.
But I feel lonely.
So lonely.
I think of you to clear my thoughts.
My love, I promise I will bring
you and the kids here soon.
Come closer.
Sing.
Old man.
Are you awake?
Are you sleeping?
Wake up.
Are you there?
How is the snow?
We had to go Old man.
My dad didn't show up.
I don't know where he is.
Did you hear me?
Look outside.
Do you see it?
He is looking for us.
The monster.
He kidnaps little girls.
But don't worry old man,
I'll take care of you.
Always.
I'll be back old man.
Hello.
Are you hungry?
What's your name?
I will call you Pancho.
You don't like it?
I'll call you Panchito.
Nice to meet you, Panchito.
My name's Cecilia
How many did you bring?
Eight.
Eight?
Hey man, you said four or five.
Calm down.
It's more money for us.
What happened to your eye?
Nothing, just an accident.
An accident?
How did it go with the little girl?
I don't know, she ran off.
What do you mean she ran off?
Calm down,
I'm just joking.
Don't play games with me!
It was a joke. It's all right,
she's with her dad.
There's nothing to worry about.
Don't play with me.
Open it.
Hold on.
I need a favor.
What?
A loan.
From me?
Two thousand dollars.
- Have you seen where I live?
- Can you or can you not?
- Of Course I can't, you're crazy.
Come on, get out.
Be careful with your heads.
To the house.
Careful.
This is too many people, you know.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Cecilia.
Ceci!
Is that you papa?
- I can go straight to the left?
Yeah, it'll take you
about four more miles.
Hello, Panchito.
Are you thirtsy?
Do you want some water Panchito?
Here.
Old man,
I have something to tell you.
Today
I saw the savior.
Did you hear that?
-Stay quiet old man!
It won't hear us.
Cecilia.
- What about the rest of them?
- They haven't paid me yet
-What about the loan?
-Do I look like a bank?
-It's only two thousand dollars.
-Only?
-And why do you need so much money?
-Business.
That was last month.
- Can I use the bathroom?
- Yeah.
Yeah, of course, you know the way.
Yeah, no, no, just does some work for me.
Are you through in there?
We gotta go!
On my way!
Old man,
How do you feel?
You look sad.
When I'd get sad,
my mom would tell me a story
about a boy and a tree.
The tree loved the boy so much.
She would give her leaves
and her branches to the boy
So that he would be happy.
But one day,
the boy was not satisfied
and stopped visiting the tree.
When we were in the hotel room
coming here, I started thinking about
everything I was leaving behind
and I started to cry
I was leaving it all for a better life,
but it was sad for me to think
of my friends and family.
I wanted to help my mom and dad,
but I never had any money.
So I had to
look for a better life in a different place.
In a different part of the world.
The tree was so sad.
The boy grew
until he turned into a man.
He'd come back only when
he needed something.
Until one day,
the tree was left with nothing.
- Only a stump was left.
Dried up.
Nothing was left.
Nothing.
Cecilia.
- You won't regret that
you came, asshole.
-We'll split it half and half.
- There's a lot of money in this place.
- And how do you know that?
- I do business with these people.
- Business.
- Last time I was there, i took this.
- They didn't even notice.
Cecilia.
I've been looking for you Cecilia.
Come to me Cecilia.
Why didn't you want to see me?
Why don't you want
to see me, Cecilia?
I don't know you.
The come and meet me
Cecilia. Come in.
They're leaving.
Alright, you ready? Honk twice if someone is coming.
Don't fuck with me.
Hurry up, hurry up.
You are not my papa.
Don't worry old man,
it wasn't him.
You sleep well.
- Wake up asshole! Hurry up!
-What happened?
-Nothing
-What did you get?
- Nothing!
-What you mean nothing!?
-They didn't have shit in there!
- Can I help you?
- Things cost money.
-You understand?
- I'm watching you.
I saw you little girl!
You got that?
- I saw you!
- Gracias.
What happened old man?
Dear Francisco, How are you?
I hope this letter finds you well.
I've been wanting to write you for months,
but there are things I'm still trying
to understand in my life without you.
I've been thinking about
when we first met.
- Two kids in love
- with a passion to change the world.
- Or at least our world in Havana
- But you left.
- You left me, my love.
- Your children,
- and your country.
- Our views of this place
have always been different,
- that never changed.
- But you did
- You left everything that was important to you
- with a promise of something better.
- a better life?
I'll bring you more tomorrow.
Is your life better without me?
Maybe it's like a dream,
- like us floating in the river
- whispering,
- I'm still here.
- At this point, all I have left is the
sound of your voice in my memory.
Cecilia!
Leave without me, Cecilia!
You'll be okay.
Cecilia.
Cecilia!
- You're going to be okay. I'll stay here!
- Mamma?
- Leave my love. They're waiting for you!
Mamma!
- You'll be okay!
Cecilia!
- You'll be okay
I can't wait any longer my love.
- Your boys are almost men now.
- You're just a face in old
photographs to them.
- And now, to me.
- This is not how I imagined things would end,
but our communication is almost like a ghost.
- Pieces of paper,
- broken promises.
- I wish you the best
- with your life, with your love,
- with your dream.
- I say all of this knowing
well that I will miss you,
- in the same way the boys miss you,
- the way Havana misses you.
- Always, with love,
- Claudia