[MUSIC PLAYING]
Please to hold very still.
Nikita, I thought
you were sleeping.
I don't think so.
But I'm sure my comrades will be
very interesting to learn what
you have been up to in here.
And since when
is love a crime?
You are a spy,
a very good one.
There will be a big
reward for your capture.
What's the rush?
You caught me with
my pants down.
You're making
minimum wage, playing
the lottery with the
chance to win toilet paper.
So?
So why don't you let me show
you the power of capitalism?
Capitalism?
Mm-hmm.
Money.
But no tricks.
No.
No tricks.
Just treats.
And it all starts
with an open hand.
Now you're sleeping.
Come in, Agent Tania.
I understand your mission
was a success, as usual.
I believe that the film
turned out very well.
However, it wasn't easy to get.
That's why we put our
best agent on the job.
Mr. Whately, you flatter me.
I mean to.
You all rested now?
Yes, sir.
I am feeling back to
my old self again.
Good.
Agent, I have need of
your services again.
Right here on
top of the desk OK?
Not those services, agent.
Right, sir.
Sorry.
Have you ever heard of
sensible satellite radio?
All music and
talk all the time?
Exactly.
Well, there's one
special channel, 6969,
which is reserved for
international communications
between our organization,
the FBI, CIA, all in code,
of course.
Of course.
BIKINI is represented by
the "Surf's Up Radio Hour."
Most of our
information is filtered
through these channels.
Someone somewhere is
jamming that signal.
We don't think they've
broken our code yet.
They are stopping our
agencies from communicating
with each other,
which is playing
hell with our operations.
I love the "Surf's
Up Radio Hour."
You know, I never
realized that they
were using it for top-secret
communications, though.
That's how we first learned
of your successes in Moscow.
Oh.
I'm impressed.
I need to know who's
jamming our signal.
We have an informant, a
stripper named Patty Mercury.
We think you two should
get on well together.
If she gives you any leads, play
it through, and get back to me
with the results.
I'll tell you what, sir.
I am not going to
take this lying down.
I mean, I won't
let you down, sir.
You never have, agent.
Good luck.
Thanks.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
(SINGING) Baby, I want
to get in your veins.
Baby, you got no one
but yourself to blame.
You can run, but you can't hide.
Welcome to your suicide.
We both know what I'm gonna do.
Your agony is my ecstasy.
And I'll give you
everything you need.
Oh, yeah.
You wanna see what?
A lifetime, a
lifetime of misery.
Your agony is my ecstasy.
Sister, I got
something in store--
I enjoyed your show.
Thanks.
Very sensual.
That's the idea.
ID?
Well, would you look at
that, a real secret agent.
That's right.
So Whately told me that
you had some information
you wanted to share with me.
Sometimes I do
private shows, the kind
I'm sure I don't need to explain
to you, and some of our clients
are very important
people, the kind
that you would never expect.
That's exactly the kind of
man or woman I'm interested in.
Well, not too long
ago, I was entertaining
this very wealthy man
named Randolph Davis.
Right in the middle of a
little, his cell phone rings,
and the guy takes the call.
What?
Anyway, the phone call
sounded extremely suspicious.
I mean, it's not like I could
talk right then or anything,
but I could certainly hear.
So when I got home,
I called the cops,
and they referred
me to Mr. Whately
and your BIKINI organization.
You know, Patty, that
was very patriotic of you.
And Whately asked me to hear you
out, and I believe your story.
I am telling you the truth.
You need to check this guy out.
Can you help me with this?
Sure.
You know, Patty, I really need
Randolph's address and phone
number.
If I gave it to you,
he would have me killed.
Well, I need it now.
Isn't there some other
way you can get it?
Like, the phone book maybe?
Patty, I know that you
want to give it to me.
Don't be afraid.
I need it, and I need it now.
You think someone
killed Patty Mercury
because she was about to talk?
Well, that or she
was about to orgasm.
Interesting.
I read the contents of this
dart analyzed down at the lab,
and it turns out it
contains deadly poison.
I'm not bit surprised.
Deadly in an
Asiatic sort of way.
It's an extract of
the mariposa lupine
plant, which only
grows in the mountains
of the northern Himalayas.
Exotic and dangerous.
Yes.
And it is rarely, if ever,
used on this continent.
Well, that narrows
it down a little.
It narrows it down a lot.
So now what?
We've arranged for you
to meet Mr. Randolph Davis
under the guise of
writing a magazine article
for "The Rob Roy Report."
He expected at 1:00 PM.
I'll let you know
what I find out.
Good luck.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
This entire mountainside
belongs to Davis International.
We could land a helicopter out
there if we really wanted to.
This is quite a spread
for a weekend getaway.
Yes, well, I believe in
indulging in total pleasure.
Therefore, we must prepare for
pleasure in every indulgence.
Can I quote you on that?
I wish you would.
Wine?
I've never been one
to complain, Mr. Davis.
No, no.
Would you like a glass of wine?
Oh.
Yes, please.
Yes, well, I'll be right back.
Please.
OK.
Fay Wong.
Thank you.
You know, you have amazing
views from up here.
Indeed.
We can see all the world up
here, but they can't see us.
I bet you could run
around naked outside
if you wanted to, huh?
Be my guest.
Work first, Mr. Davis.
Yes.
So what is the circulation
of your magazine, exactly?
Oh, it's really
large, I think.
Mm-hmm.
And your target demographic?
People who read.
You're being very
secretive, Tania.
But then again, I like that
in a woman, a little mystery.
Oh.
I don't mean to be
secretive, Mr. Davis.
I mean-- oh, that's going
to be a bitch to get out.
Are you OK?
Fine.
I'm fine.
Did you say I could run
around naked outside?
Absolutely.
You know what?
If you help me get this off,
I will show you a good time.
Can I quote you on that?
Please, I wish you would.
Woo!
Oh, Mr. Davis.
[EXCLAMATIONS]
That's rude.
[LIGHT LAUGHTER]
How are you feeling?
Oh, I'm feeling so good.
I've never quite seem to want
to get out of their clothes
that quickly.
I know.
It's pretty amazing, isn't it?
Yes.
Mr. Davis, what a
view from down here.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Why, Tania, you look
absolutely ghastly.
Thank you, sir.
I'm assuming you hooked
up with Randolph Davis?
I believe I did, and I think
he got the better end of it.
I see.
I think he drugged my wine and
had me perform a few lewd sex
acts on him and the gardener.
Did you come up empty-handed?
Hardly.
Before I took the
nosedive, I did
come across a few
foreign waybill documents
made out to a certain Fay
Wong International Export.
That's very interesting.
Better still, the parts
that are being shipped
are the very kind
that are used in radio
transmitters and satellite
uplinking conduits.
Excellent.
Did you latch onto
anything else?
Well-- ooh.
There was the
gardener, but I don't
remember too much about that.
You've done plenty.
Wong International Exports
is a front for the dreaded
Tong warlord Fay Wong.
Mr. Whately, I really think
that I need to lay down.
For years she's dominated,
killed, and tortured her way
to the top of
Interpol's most wanted
criminal mastermind list.
She shows neither mercy nor
compassion for her victims.
It's rumored she even
stir-fried her dog
and served it for lunch.
She's heartless, cruel, and
she cheats at Texas Hold'em.
No one's actually
seen her in years.
It was rumored
that she was dead.
But I see now she's been
waiting and plotting
in secret to rule the world.
Agent?
Oh.
Yes?
Can I get you
a glass of water?
No, sir.
I'm fine, really.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Exalted one, Mong Lee has
arrived with information
of an urgent nature.
Very well.
Let him enter.
As you command.
Exalted one.
Do you have news for me?
I bring news from
America and Randolph Davis.
And what does he have
to say for himself?
He believes we are
being investigated
by agents of BIKINI.
Your name has been
linked to his,
and I believe it has brought
us some unfortunate exposure.
Indeed.
The girl from BIKINI has
been placed on our trail.
It's only a matter of
time before she discovers
your secret fortress
and leads an Interpol
force straight for us.
And for what purpose?
I haven't done anything wrong.
We are jamming their
radio frequencies
and their intelligence network.
Oh, that.
Who wants to hear the
surf channel, anyway?
Still, it is inconvenient for
them to come here uninvited.
Perhaps you should pay
them a visit in America
to make sure that
that doesn't happen.
By your command.
How else may I be of service?
Kim Chee.
Well, you can start by
checking the air in my tires.
By your command.
Honey, I'm home.
Oh, that's right.
I live alone.
This is as much Chinese
culture as I understand,
chow mein and eggroll.
Ugh.
God, I feel like day-old trash.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Stop.
Does it hurt?
Well, how about this, huh?
Oh, wait.
Wait.
Tania.
Tania, it's me.
It's me.
Whoa, Tania.
Mark Ten.
I should have known.
Only the CIA would
do something as
low as attacking a girl when
she just gets out of the shower.
Hey.
I was only testing your
reflexes to see if they're
as sharp as I remembered.
And?
You still got it, baby.
I should've made
you say uncle.
Now, that would've been funny.
What are you
doing in my bedroom?
Can we continue this
conversation downstairs?
I saw some Chinese
food and I'm starving.
You want my Chinese food?
Yeah,
Man, you CIA guys are cheap.
I used a coupon, though.
Come on.
Oh.
It wasn't that bad.
Ow.
So I ask her again.
I say, you learned
everything you
know about sex from a manual?
She says, yeah.
Emmanuel, my pool boy.
Oh, poor baby.
Maybe you just weren't meant
to settle down and get married.
I guess it is crazy
to think that I could
have replaced a
hot chick like you
with some off-the-rack trim.
You know, if you're trying to
get back into my good graces,
you're not doing so hot.
No, that's not it at all,
although I do sometimes
wish that you and I could
get back together again.
Dream on.
The only hot, wet treat you're
getting tonight is wonton soup.
Well, you obviously didn't
come here for my mu shu pork.
What's on your
beady little mind?
Mm.
Mu shu pork is good.
I know you're working on
the radio jamming operation.
So am I.
Do tell.
Recently, we've
intercepted communications--
threats, dangerous threats
against the Rhinehart family.
Rhinehart family?
Who are they?
They just happen to be the
family who owns Sensible
Satellite Radio,
the ones who provide
all the covert organizations
with their secretly
encoded airwaves.
So part of this program
has been subcontracted out
to a private sector.
And now they're being
pushed around as well.
Precisely.
And further to that,
I've been ordered
to provide protective shelter
for Samantha Rhinehart,
their daughter, who's
been specifically
targeted for kidnap and murder.
And what?
You want her to stay here?
You are one of BIKINI's top
agents, and you are both girls.
Duh.
You are so not getting
back into my good graces.
Come on.
This is important.
[DOORBELL]
There she is.
Just meet her before you
rule this out entirely.
OK, fine.
But you're not getting
into my pants today, Mark.
Please.
Just meet her, say hello.
We'll take it from there.
Hey, Samantha.
Come on in.
Hi, Mark.
Am I early?
No, not at all.
Don't worry about it.
This is Tania.
This is her house.
Hello.
Hi.
I'm Samantha.
Yeah, I know.
Wow.
You know what?
You can just go that way.
OK.
You are so close to getting
into my pants today.
I thought you might like her.
Wow.
There's a lot to lick--
I mean, like.
Hoo.
So tell me about your
problem, Samantha.
Well, lately, I haven't
been having any trouble.
But then the notes
started coming.
You're dead meat, bitch.
And, I'm going to
get you, sucker.
And then the phone calls.
Is your refrigerator running?
Better catch it.
Do you have Prince
Albert in a can?
Better let him out.
Before long, it
felt like someone
was staring at me, watching me.
I could hear every breath
and his burning eyes burning
into my naked flesh.
What?
It's my job to watch her.
It's for her good.
Sure it is.
Please, go on.
The sensation
was the strongest
whenever I took my clothes off.
And I'm a sexaholic, so I take
my clothes off an awful lot.
Really?
Are you having these
strange feelings now?
No, not right now.
I feel pretty safe and secure.
Hm, interesting.
Maybe you should remove
a piece of clothing
and then we'll see how you feel.
OK.
How's that?
I feel like someone's
staring at me.
Is that so?
You know, maybe if
you take the bra off,
we'll see what happens.
OK, if you think it'd help.
Oh, I definitely
think it'll help.
That's really hot.
Yeah.
Now I'm starting to
feel like strange eyes are
burning into me.
Maybe I should take off
the skirt to make sure.
Ooh.
OK.
Yeah, the meter's
really [INAUDIBLE] now.
You said something
about being a sexaholic?
Oh, I can't get enough.
And what does
that mean, exactly?
It means they want to go
down on you both right now.
Oh, I hope you saved
room for dessert.
Oh, I did.
FAY WONG: You're
all having fun now,
thinking in your tiny
minds that you're
far beyond Fay Wong's reach.
Little do you know
that even now,
Mong Lee's plotting the end
to your meaningless lives.
Bask now in your
earthly pleasures,
for soon your torment
will only delight me.
So then it's agreed.
Samantha is going to stay
in your protective custody.
That's right.
Although I don't
know how safe that is.
But at least until the CIA can
assign a new bodyguard for her.
Well, that all
depends on Whately.
But in the meantime,
yes, it's OK
if she camps out at my place.
Good.
But I don't want to get
into an international incident
over this.
We both know that
BIKINI and the CIA
aren't exactly
company bedfellows,
and I don't know how
Whately is going to react.
Really.
I have gone over
all the fine details
and have looked deep into this.
I'm afraid that such
a thing is not possible.
But you haven't
even heard us out yet.
MR. WHATELY: I don't need to.
Tania has a date
with an airplane.
She's on her way to Asia,
and I wouldn't trust
this mission to anyone but her.
No offense to the
CIA, of course.
Noted.
I've already heard about
your little babysitting job.
Tania's destiny lies in the
mountains of northern China.
That will be all.
I'm sorry, Mr. Whately.
No need to apologize.
I understand she
was quite a looker.
Oh, yes, she was.
Have a successful journey.
Report to me when you get back.
Yes, sir.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Hello.
May I help you?
Is the lady of the house in?
No, she's not in right
now, and I'm just the guest.
Perhaps I may interest
you in fine hairbrushes,
hairbrushes for
every type of hair,
fine hairbrushes for
every kind of occasion.
Really?
A traveling brush salesman.
Oh, please, come in.
Well, you know, I've been
brushing my hair every day,
sometimes more, and I thought,
wouldn't it be a super idea
if somebody came up to the door
with a vast variety of brushes
to sell to people.
And here you are.
Please, if just show a
lady fine brushes, perhaps
she find something she like.
I can hardly wait.
MARK TEN: [INAUDIBLE]
protective custody.
TANIA X: I don't want to
get into a [INAUDIBLE]..
Samantha, we're back.
MONG LEE (ON RADIO):
Mong to Empress Fay.
Do you come in?
Hold on.
This is Fay Wong.
I have disabled the
Americans with surprisingly
little difficulty.
What are your instructions?
Do you have Samantha
Rhinehart in your possession?
Oh, that's affirmative.
Excellent.
She will make a
beautiful hostage.
Bring her to me.
What of the others?
Leave them.
The shame of having
been defeated so easily
will send a message
to others who seek
to interfere with my plans.
MONG LEE (ON RADIO):
As you command.
I mean, as you command.
Mong out.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Ooh!
Oh, sorry.
Ooh.
What happened?
I think somebody
Pier sixed me.
Oh my god.
Samantha.
I'll check upstairs.
I'll call Whately.
Samantha, you up here?
Samantha?
Yes, I understand, sir.
I hear you loud and clear.
She's gone.
More bad news.
BIKINI is not going to accept
any responsibility for this
because your bringing her
here was unauthorized.
Now what?
Well, Mr. Whately did say
that it be prudent for us to get
our asses on a plane
to China right now
and save her before
it's too late,
and he gave me the coordinates
to her secret fortress.
So this means you'll help me?
What else can I do?
The fate of the free world
hangs in the balance.
Come on, then.
There's no time to lose.
Let's go.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Exalted one, I bring you the
prisoner, Samantha Rhinehart.
Well done, Mong.
You may leave us now.
What kind of deviltry is this?
A most wicked and
painful one, if you desire.
Please me and I shall
pleasure you back.
Disobey me and, well, you'll
just see my private party room.
My father will
never pay a ransom,
and I have nothing to offer.
I disagree.
I've been watching you
in the mystic smoke
of the ancient ones.
I think you have
plenty to offer.
Kim Chee.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
TANIA X: OK, you're going
to wait for my signal,
and then you're going
to blow them to hell.
Yeah.
Wait a minute.
Blow them to hell?
With what?
Disposable ink
pen rocket launcher.
You're joking.
I thought everybody
was using these now.
No way.
Oh, well.
Just wait here for me, OK?
And hold my purse.
All right.
OK.
Be careful.
Good luck.
What if I push this button?
Oh, boy.
You should've been more
careful with the exalted one.
She has very sensitive
private parts.
Like I would know.
Sheesh
It's a shame you have
to go this way, a pity.
Such a waste.
Yeah, it's a regular
tit and the pendulum.
Edgar Allan Poe
would be so proud.
I don't suppose you'd let
me go for the best piece
ass you ever had, would you?
Nah.
I didn't think so.
Shoot.
Just in time.
That's called a payback.
All right, Samantha.
Come on.
Mark's waiting to
blow this joint.
Blow this joint?
You'll see.
Thank god you guys made it.
I was starting to get hot.
Mong, what has happened?
Blow this joint.
Blow this-- blow this joint.
Not now.
Is that all you
ever think about?
No.
Kaboom.
Give me the ink pen.
Kaboom?
Yeah, kaboom.
Dammit.
[SHOT FIRED]
[EXPLOSION]
Oh.
Well, that's it for her.
My heroes.
Ah.
Come on, guys.
We've got a plane to catch.
And using our customized
disposable pen rocket launcher,
we managed to destroy Fay
Wong's evil empire and all
those in it, which is a
shame because, uh, Kim Chee,
she was pretty tasty.
Excellent work.
And what of Miss Rhinehart?
Returned safe and
sound to her family
without a scratch on the paint.
Well, it seems as if
this cooperative effort
between BIKINI and the CIA went
off quite well, even if it was
unauthorized and unrecognized.
We may have to try it
again in the future,
should the need arise.
So I assume that the
radio waves are back up.
You're correct.
Surf's Up is broadcasting
day and night,
and communications
have never been higher,
all thanks to the two of you.
Hey, did anybody ever figure
out why Fay Wong jammed up
the radio waves to begin with?
Not completely, but
as near as we can tell,
she just hated Jan and Dean.
Oh.
So I guess that's it
for you and me, huh?
I'm sure we'll
hook up again soon
for another exciting adventure.
Yeah?
You think so?
Oh, yeah.
You know, if they know
what's good for them.
I'll get my own TV show.
Cool.
And that way, I can kick ass
and you can be my eye candy.
Really?
Let's go.
What else can I do?
Fate of the free world
hangs in the balance.
Can we continue this
conversation downstairs?
I saw some Chinese
food, and I'm starving.
The sensation
was the strongest
whenever I took my clothes off.
And I'm a sexaholic, so I take
my clothes off an awful lot.
Oh, that.
Who wants to hear the
surf channel, anyway?
You should have been more
careful with the exalted one.
She has very sensitive
private parts.
Deadly in an
Asiatic sort of way.
It's not like I could
talk right then or anything,
but I could certainly hear.
You're being very
secretive, Tania.
But then again, I like that
no woman, a little mystery.
You are a spy,
a very good one.
I've seen your picture on the
"Moscow Most Wanted" TV show.
[MUSIC PLAYING]