(classical violin music)
- Ooh.
Oh hello.
I'm Fredrick Michaels,
and welcome to Found Footage Theater.
- [Director] Um, it's
Tales of Found Footage.
- I know, I was trying to add some class
to this unrefined little film.
May I continue, please?
Thank you.
As I was saying, I'm Fredrick Michaels,
an accomplished thespian,
trained in the classic
Shakespearean theater style,
and you may remember me
from my many performances
on Broadway or at the Royal
Opera House in London.
And now I'm hosting
Tales of Found Footage.
Fuck my life.
Did you know, I've been nominated
for multiple Tony and
Laurence Olivier awards
for my performances, fantastic productions
guided by excellent directors,
not like this fucking
tosser behind the camera.
Oh, you're making yet another
Found Footage horror movie.
Oh, I'm original.
And what's with you young
people and your fascination
for found footage?
Found footage?
I call it low-budget rubbish!
But I digress.
And since I'm being disgustingly underpaid
to host this crap, I'll
give you what you want.
So please, send the kids off to bed,
sit back, relax and turn off the lights.
(classical violin music)
I said turn off the bloody lights!
And prepare yourself as I regale you
with three stories of terror
presented to you in found footage style.
Go, turn it off, change your
channel to something better.
- Do it quickly.
- Fredrick!
- Our first story tonight
comes from something
you young people are also fascinated with,
an online challenge.
Hashtag this challenge,
hashtag that challenge.
It's a bloody pound sign!
And in this tale, two teenage girls
take it upon themselves
to attempt a challenge
that nobody has been able
to complete thus far.
For good reason.
(classical violin music)
I thought you were gonna fade out.
- [Director] Um, the title?
- Oh bloody hell, wretched bastards,
I present to you, Hashtag the Challenge.
- Hi, I'm Delaney.
And I'm Sarah.
- And we are going to be doing
the Hotel Alexandria Challenge.
- It's this super cool
challenge that all the kids
at our school are doing.
- But none of them have completed it.
Not a single one.
And, um.
- Do you know anyone who've done it?
- Yes, yes, Ryan did it.
It's just--
- Ryan did it?
- Yes, that's the thing, that's the thing.
He tried it, and, um,
so he (laughs), he gets there,
and he rides his bike the whole way there.
He sees a shadow in the
window and just leaves.
- Oh my gosh.
- Like, what?
- That's Ryan for you,
right, all big and macho.
- Literally, wait here, let me show you.
Like, it's all in the way he walks.
Like, how he's like big and like (grunts).
I play football and I'm so cool,
and you would think that
he's not afraid of anything.
And he just chickened out
at the first sign of like,
what was that?
He's a big baby.
- [Delaney] Well you only say
that because you like him.
- No, I don't.
- Yes, you do.
- No, I don't, Delaney, that's not fair.
You can't just.
Can you just not tell anyone?
- [Delaney] I won't tell anyone.
- And can we please delete
that outta the final cut?
(laughing)
- [Delaney] Yeah, yeah of course.
- Okay, okay, can we just get back to it?
- [Delaney] Yeah, yeah yeah.
- Let me, hold it.
All right, the Hotel Alexandria.
- Woooo.
- The challenge is you have to make it
all the way up to the fourth floor,
and then all the way down,
and you have to record
the whole thing for proof.
- And it's all like
abandoned, and like haunted.
- Yes, yes, and, do we say anything
about the ghost lady, or is that like?
- Eh, I mean there's like this ghost lady
who supposedly like roams the halls.
- And she died in the hotel.
- Woooooooo.
(laughing)
- But who knows if we'll
run into her or not?
We're recording the whole thing, so
you guys'll find out if you stay tuned.
- Yep.
Is that it?
- Yeah, wish us luck.
- Wooooo, bye.
- Bye.
(laughing)
- [Sarah] It's this one right here.
- Holy shit.
- [Sarah] Oh my God.
- [Delaney] Are you sure
this is the right one?
- [Delaney] This is the place.
Oh my God.
- [Sarah] Delaney, I don't
know if I wanna do this.
- Are you seriously chickening out?
- [Sarah] It's just,
it's late, and I'm like.
- We walked like 15 minutes
to get here, like in the rain.
Are you serious?
- [Sarah] I just like, it's, I don't know,
I'm scared and I feel stupid.
- What about Ryan?
If like he couldn't do it and you do it,
he'll think you're like really cool.
(phone ringing)
- [Sarah] Who's that?
- It's my mom.
- [Sarah] What are you gonna tell her.
- I don't, I'm sleeping
over at your house.
- [Sarah] Wait, no no no no no.
- I'm sleeping over at your house.
I'm sleeping over.
Hey, Mom, hey.
Um, I'm sleeping over
Sarah's tonight, okay?
What are you--
No, I--
Mom, we've talked about this, seriously.
Pick me up, or I'll walk.
Ten.
Okay.
- [Sarah] Man.
- We're gonna do this,
okay, we're gonna be fine.
- Here we go.
- Are you ready?
- Yeah, okay.
- I guess.
- [Delaney] Let's go, let's go, let's go.
- [Sarah] All right, first floor.
Jesus, it's cold.
It's absolutely freezing.
It's like worse than outside.
(footsteps)
This place looks like it's
from the 18 freaking hundreds.
Everything's just old and weird.
- [Delaney] Take a look at that baby.
- [Sarah] Ugh, where are its eyes?
I hate this, I absolutely
freaking hate this.
- [Delaney] Dammit.
- [Sarah] What?
- There's no cellphone service.
- [Sarah] Are you kidding me?
Delaney, we have to go home
if there's no cellphone service.
- We're fine, we're fine, we're fine.
Don't be a baby.
- [Sarah] What do you mean,
what if something happens?
- Stop being a chicken.
We're fine, we're gonna
get through this, okay?
Just, just calm down.
- [Sarah] God, okay.
The clock's stopped.
I don't know why I would
think it would be going, but.
Hey look.
- Yo.
I think this is a phono-graph.
So I think what you do
is you turn the crank
and it plays music on the discs.
- Yeah, like, I've seen them in movies,
just never in real life.
- [Delaney] Well, here it is.
- Kinda cool.
- [Delaney] Hey, try and see if some
of the doors are locked.
- Locked.
That's really stupid,
when you think about it.
Like, think of how easy
it was to get in here.
I mean, the door was practically open.
But then, all of these
doors have to be locked.
I don't know, it's just my opinion, but.
- [Delaney] Yeah.
- Look at the little, I don't know,
it's like the talky holes
at church, in confession.
- [Delaney] Yeah, I get it.
- Forgive me, Father, for I have sinned.
(laughing)
I don't know, this whole place is weird.
- [Delaney] Stand a little
closer to the portrait.
She looks exactly like you.
Like, spot on.
- I don't like this.
That's, I don't.
I don't like that kinda
stuff, can we just keep going?
I think we should keep going.
- [Delaney] Yeah, I'm sorry.
- No, it's fine and I'm
just being stupid, it's.
I just really don't like things like that.
- [Delaney] No, I get it.
- [Sarah] Okay, thank you.
All right.
So far so good.
- [Delaney] Hey, try that door.
See if it's locked.
- Locked.
- [Delaney] Down here then?
- [Sarah] Sure.
- [Delaney] Okay.
- [Sarah] It's so cold.
- [Delaney] It's worse
than the other floor.
How's that even possible?
- [Sarah] Look at this.
That's so weird.
- [Delaney] That's strange.
(door slamming)
Oh my God.
(panicking)
Oh thank God.
- [Delaney] Sarah?
(hard breathing)
- [Sarah] My God.
- [Delaney] Sarah, what are you doing?
- [Sarah] Oh my God.
- [Delaney] Why are you?
- [Sarah] I don't know, I just wanna see.
What the hell?
- [Delaney] Screw this,
Sarah, we're going home.
- What?
- [Delaney] We're going home.
- We, we.
But.
What the f--
- [Delaney] What's happening?
Sarah, we're going home.
- No, no, now you have
think about this rationally.
This is an old abandoned hotel.
The wiring's probably all weird.
It's, the draft from
the door made it swing.
You can't just like, it's, there's
no reason to panic over this.
God, we came all the way here.
We can't just give up now.
We broke into this freaking hotel.
We made it to the second floor.
We, we--
Come on, can we just finish this?
This is stupid just to
freak out over a chandelier.
Please.
- [Delaney] Okay.
We're gonna be okay.
- Yeah.
We're fine, let's just go.
- [Delaney] Let's do this, okay, come on.
Perfect.
- What?
- [Delaney] My phone glitched.
It's been doing that.
- [Sarah] Oh, mine's fine.
- [Delaney] I haven't updated in a while.
That might be what it is.
- Ugh, no more slamming doors.
Yeah, I don't know, that's weird, but
really it's probably just a
bug that you haven't figured.
Oh that is weird.
- [Delaney] Yeah.
- [Sarah] All right.
This is the
third floor.
Second to last.
Okay.
- [Delaney] Each floor is
definitely colder than the last.
- [Sarah] For real.
(hard breathing)
Ugh.
- [Delaney] Sarah, can
we please turn around?
- [Sarah] Oh, yeah, totally.
- [Delaney] Oh, I'm sorry, that was me.
- It's okay.
- [Delaney] After we're
done the fourth floor,
I just wanna go straight down.
- [Sarah] Definitely.
- [Delaney] Just go home.
(floor creaking)
- [Sarah] It's like everything
has a layer of dust over it.
- [Delaney] No kidding.
- You know what?
I have an idea.
Um, okay.
Hey, guys, so we're on
the third floor right now.
- One more floor to go.
- Yeah, and it's creepy as shit, but, um,
we're doing pretty good.
- That door's cracked.
- And we'll, uh, show
you guys what's inside.
Yeah, um.
Okay, okay.
It's really just like a normal room.
- [Sarah] What's in it?
- I don't know, like a bed,
a dresser and a bathroom.
Lamp, chair,
ugly wallpaper.
- What does the wallpaper have on it?
- It's all birds and flowers.
It really looks like a room
in someone's grandmother's house.
I don't know why I thought it
would be scary or something.
Sorry to disappoint.
Um.
Yeah.
(door closing)
- Okay.
- Um, looks creepy, totally harmless.
Um, we're going up to
the fourth floor now,
so keep watching and you'll see it all.
- Bye.
- [Sarah] Last one.
- [Delaney] Let's just get this over with.
- [Sarah] What the hell?
- [Delaney] What's that?
Look.
Nobody mentioned a fifth floor.
- If it's not in the
challenge we're not doing it.
Let's just go and let's just finish this.
- [Delaney] I just wanna go home.
- Me too.
Almost there, though.
Next hallway, come on.
We film this last one for proof,
and then we are out of here.
- [Delaney] You're right.
- [Sarah] Then we did
it, and then we go home.
- [Delaney] Sarah, I,
I think that's enough.
Let's go.
(door slamming)
- Oh my God.
- [Sarah] What the hell?
- [Delaney] Oh my God.
- [Sarah] Was that always like that?
- [Delaney] Sarah, that was not there?
- [Sarah] Well are you sure?
- [Delaney] Don't go near it!
Are you sure it wasn't there?
- [Sarah] Delaney?
Delaney?
(gasping)
- [Deep Voice] It's okay, Sarah.
Everything's fine now.
- Delaney!
(footsteps)
Delaney?
(thumping)
(moaning)
(screaming)
(footsteps)
(panicking)
(door slamming)
(hard breathing)
(crying)
(door pounding)
No, don't, please please stop!
Go away, go away!
(weeping)
Okay, um.
I haven't heard anything in a while,
and I'm gonna try and go down there
and I'm gonna try and find Delaney.
I don't know.
I just thought I'd make this
just to say that this whole thing
was just such a big mistake.
And we were just so stupid and
we didn't know what we were doing.
(crying)
But I have to go down there
and I have to find her because
I don't know, we promised
we wouldn't leave
without her, she's like my sister, I.
I have to.
I just wish we never came here.
And I just wanna go home.
(crying)
(sniffling)
Just God, please let her be okay,
and just let this visit be
okay, and just let us leave.
(crying)
(deep breathing)
Okay.
I'm gonna go now.
(deep breathing)
(door closing)
Shit.
(deep breathing)
Delaney?
(phone ringing)
Oh my God.
(footsteps)
(phone ringing)
Delaney?
(thumping)
(hard breathing)
I don't know.
(phone ringing)
Delaney?
Delaney, is that you?
(door creaking)
(bicycle bell ringing)
(hard breathing)
(footsteps)
- [Delaney] Sarah?
- [Sarah] Delaney?
- [Delaney] Sarah, help me please.
- [Sarah] Delaney, where are you?
Delaney?
- [Delaney] In here.
- [Sarah] Delaney?
- [Deep Voice] Take my hand.
- [Sarah] No, no, no!
(footsteps)
Delaney?
No, no no, no no no, Delaney!
(footsteps)
Delaney, Delaney,
Delaney, no, God, no, no!
(big band music)
♪ Listen to me, honey dear ♪
♪ Something's wrong with you, I fear ♪
- [Deep Voice] Sarah.
♪ It's getting harder to
please you every year ♪
♪ I don't wanna make you blue ♪
- [Sarah] Delaney, please stop!
(muffled singing)
Delaney, no, please please please please.
Please please.
(crying)
♪ If I gave you the moon ♪
Hail Mary, full of Grace,
the Lord is with you.
Blessed art thou among women and blessed
is the fruit of thy womb, Jesus.
Holy Mary, mother of
God, pray for us sinners
now and at the hour of our death, amen.
(soft breathing)
(hard breathing)
(whirring)
(creaking)
(giggling)
- [Deep Voice] Sarah!
- [Sarah] No.
(screaming)
- All right, three, two, one.
It's been over a month
since Delaney Torrance
and Sarah Grady went missing.
Now unfortunately for the Torrance family,
Delaney has yet to be found.
Now after Sarah was discovered
wandering the streets
just days after the
incident, she was little help
to police and didn't have
any details of the events
or even the whereabouts
of her best friend.
But we're gonna get to the bottom of this
and answer those questions for you.
So join me, Whitney
Stone, for an exclusive
first on-camera interview with Sarah Grady
and her family to talk
about the details of that
fateful evening that
the girls went missing.
(door knocking)
(bird calling)
I mean, there's cars in the driveway.
They know we're coming.
All right, let me knock again.
(door knocking)
(bird calling)
Let's just try to go
in, see what's going on.
(door creaking)
Hello, is anybody home?
Sarah?
It's Whitney, is anybody home?
Hello?
Oh my God!
Oh my God, what the fuck,
we have to get outta here!
(screaming)
(grunting)
(thudding)
- Are you serious?
Is this what I'm hosting?
Teenage girls getting possessed
and hacking up their parents?
How deplorable!
What kind of sick individual
thinks up this shit?
Well, honestly.
And what's wrong with
you people for watching?
Is this how you get your
jollies, your rocks off?
Oh, look at me, I'm a horror fan!
I love gore and violence.
Ha.
I'm befuddled.
Don't you want some
refinement in your cinema?
No?
I see.
Well this will make you
happy, you sick fucks.
Our next tale is about an
unlucky-in-love American male
who decides to go the
unconventional route.
Probably because he's
a sick fucking pervert
like the rest of you.
To find the woman of his
dreams from the internet.
I now present you Mail Order Bride.
- [Matt] Hooch, tonight's the big night.
Are you just like so excited?
Tell us what's going on.
- Tonight's the night, tonight
I pick up my new bride.
- [Matt] That's right.
- Ah, I can't wait, it's been months.
It's been, it's here.
- Well, of course, I bet
you're very happy about it.
- Yes, I am, see.
- [Matt] Of course he's happy,
look at him, he's glowing.
- And you, you're happy too, right?
- [Matt] Smiling from ear to ear.
- Of course, it was all your idea?
- [Matt] Well, it was
my idea, but you know.
Listen, it wasn't easy
convincing him, but.
- Do you understand what you got him into?
- [Matt] I absolutely
understand what I got him into.
- I don't think you do.
- [Matt] What are you talking about?
I got him, how gorgeous is this woman?
- Oh very, very.
- This is human trafficking.
- [Matt] Oh come on, human trafficking?
- Seriously, where is she from?
- Romania?
- Romania.
- Yes, what's wrong with that?
- Are you guys serious, Romania?
Have you heard those stories?
Have you seen those documentaries?
My friend, Romanian girl,
pretty much experienced
that through her, firsthand,
they sell those women.
They get your money, they rip you off
and then they treat them very very poorly.
- [Matt] Well quick
disclaimer, I don't watch
any documentary unless
it's on a porn site.
- Oh, God.
Jesus.
(laughing)
This is a very shady business.
There are so many women out there.
You can go out and meet them.
You don't have to spend your money.
- [Matt] He's tried that,
he's been dating for years,
he's done the bar scene, the
dating apps, the dating sites.
Speed dating, remember the
time you did speed dating?
- We all have been.
- [Matt] He's tried that stuff for years,
nothing's worked, he's
not getting any younger.
I mean, come on, how much
longer is he supposed to wait?
- He has time, all right.
- [Matt] He doesn't have that much time.
- Just because it was your
idea, you got him into this
and now somebody's telling you it's
a bad, bad, bad idea, you're
trying to defend yourself.
- [Matt] I'm not trying to defend myself.
I legitimately think it's a good idea.
- You're a very chauvinistic
person, did you know that?
How about if I told you that?
- [Matt] Listen, I, listen.
- You treat women as meat.
Body, face.
- [Matt] See this is
where I'm calling fraud.
Because women treat men as meat,
and women have treated him as meat,
because how many times at a bar,
tell me, how many times
at a bar has a girl
like been flirting with
you, gotten a free drink
outta you and then walked
away with some other dude?
- Oh, it's like almost all the time.
- Look, guys, it happens on both sides.
- [Matt] I'm telling you, women
take advantage of men too.
- Well, okay, I'm not arguing with that.
- [Matt] Okay, thank you.
- It sometimes happens,
but it doesn't mean he should stop trying.
- [Matt] It just happens a lot to him.
That's why we're going down this path.
- No, I don't think so.
Yeah, you know what happens to him also?
He gets persuaded by people like you
to get into this very shady affair.
- [Matt] Is it my fault
I have a better haircut
and he listens to me more?
- Oh, God, goodness gracious.
You know how serious bad guys are behind
that type of businesses?
They sell those women.
You're gonna get ripped off.
- [Matt] He hasn't been sold.
He's been video chatting
with her for months.
Hooch, in all the times
you video chatted with her,
has she seemed under duress,
under slavery at all?
- No, it's all her own doing, all right.
It's a mutual thing.
- You know what, I'm
pretty sure she's gonna,
she's not gonna be there.
And when you go to meet her,
it's gonna be somebody else.
- [Matt] What are you
saying, a guy showing up?
- Well maybe, I don't know.
I don't know, maybe nobody will show up.
- [Matt] Well it's a good
thing I'm going with you then.
- That's right, we can just drive away.
- Yeah, oh, of course you can protect him,
if you know, if some shady
people, I don't know.
- [Matt] Listen, this is a gorgeous girl.
I personally looked at the pictures.
I won't tell you how many times.
But this is a gorgeous girl,
and I'm going with him,
I'm going with him to the airport.
- Good girl, good looking.
- [Matt] Listen, there's no more risk.
- It's very a light, light chance,
slight chance that this girl's gonna be
really good person as she appears to be.
- [Matt] Hooch, I'll check her for weapons
when she gets off the plane.
(laughing)
If you know what I mean.
- Very funny, guys,
you know where I stand.
I don't like the idea.
I think you shouldn't have done that.
You shouldn't have, you
know, gotten him into it.
- [Matt] I'm just saying you
take just as much a chance
meeting a girl at a bar
or a dating service,
or, or whatever, it's
just as much a chance.
- No, and why does he
need to spend his money?
- [Matt] This way, there's a nice little,
he said himself, it's a
nice little mutual situation
where she gets something out of it.
She probably just wants citizenship.
You get something out of
it, you finally get laid.
- Yeah, what about glove?
What about heart and soul, why are we?
(laughing)
- [Matt] What are we, in kindergarten?
Love? Love doesn't, come on.
How much longer is he supposed to wait?
I mean, no offense, he's not
a spring chicken anymore.
- Wow, heart and soul.
- [Matt] How much longer
is he supposed to wait?
It's not a matter of love.
Look, I mean, listen, God willing,
you too fall in love and
live happily ever after.
- Oh yeah, of course, do you believe that?
- [Matt] But let's face the reality.
She's really hot, let's face the reality.
- No, that's a bad idea.
I don't like that.
- [Matt] No, but this might
be his last chance at kids.
- Bail out, unless, you
know, until it's too late.
Please bail out, I beg of you.
- My mind's made up,
it's happening tonight.
- [Matt] He's a big boy, see, no no no,
you can't blame me on
this, it was just my idea.
He's a big boy, this took
months of convincing.
You're a big boy, this was your idea?
- Yes, it was.
- [Matt] Are you good to go?
- Yes.
- [Matt] He's good to go.
- We both know it was your idea.
- [Matt] Yes, I agree to that.
I can't argue.
Yeah, and you convinced
him and now he's sold.
Sweetie, I want you to be happy.
But, this is not the right way to go.
- [Matt] I say getting
laid'll keep you happy
on a regular basis.
(laughing)
- Ahh.
- [Matt] Hooch, we are
like 10 minutes away
from actually picking her up.
How pumped are you now?
I mean, this is it, dude,
this is like the finish line.
- Yeah, I'm very pumped.
I mean, it's like it's finally here.
It's like the last few
days have been just--
Because it was getting so
close, and I'm just like,
okay, it's here, it's here,
all right, all right and now.
- [Matt] Are you nervous, are you nervous,
are you nervous?
- A little bit, of course, sure, you know,
because it's easy when you're
video chatting and stuff.
You know, but once now you're
actually seeing face to face,
it's real, that makes it real.
- [Matt] And flesh to flesh.
- Exactly, it's a lot different than being
on a video chat when she's
like 7,000 miles away.
- [Matt] Not anymore.
- You know, now she's gonna be literally
standing like right next to me.
- [Matt] Now she's like
seven minutes away.
- Yup, about that.
So, yup, yup, pumped, man, excited.
It's happening.
It's happening!
You know, I shoulda listened
to you a long time ago.
You always said, mail order bride, dude.
What is your, I mean.
- [Matt] Dude, do you realize,
I just wanna say something
because like this was like,
this was like a long
time coming, this idea.
So if you'd listened to me,
do you know how much time
and money you would have
saved by just listening?
Listen, this should be a lesson to you
for the rest of your life.
When I say something, just save yourself
the time and trouble.
- Yeah, but you know,
it's so, but hold on,
it's so much, it's--
- [Matt] And listen to me.
- I get it, but it's easy
and a way for you to say it because--
- [Matt] And when this
pays off the way I think
it will, you're gonna be--
- Listen, and you know what?
I'll be saying, oh yeah,
shoulda done it sooner and all.
But you know what, though, it's easier,
it's easier said than
done because, you know,
I'm used to doing things a certain way.
You know, you're always in,
people naturally like have a comfort zone,
and it's not even the, it's just being
in a different environment
and trying something new.
But you're right, you're
right, I mean, yeah.
I mean, yeah you're right.
Of course, you always been nagging me
about it for how long now?
- [Matt] I pulled you
outta your comfort zone
and it's gonna pay off royally.
- I mean, I tried everything else.
I tried, the bar scene is terrible.
Dating apps suck.
It's the same people that
are on there for ages.
The speed dating thing was ridiculous.
I'm like, what the,
what was that all about?
- [Matt] That's what's
great, and now, here it is.
Payoff time.
- Oh, by the way.
Might as well get this outta the way now.
- [Matt] You're taking Viagra?
- No.
- [Matt] Cialis?
- No, when I introduced myself,
I didn't introduce myself to her,
she doesn't know me as Hooch.
She knows me as Rich.
- [Matt] What?
You haven't been Rich in 30 years.
- Well I'm Rich now.
Tonight, I'm, hey.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, pump the brakes.
Hold on a minute, I gotta get this right.
Bullshit.
Wait, so this girl's like
laying down the law already?
- No no no no no no no no.
- [Matt] I want you by your proper name.
- No no no, nope, nope, nope nope nope.
Nothing to do with her.
- [Matt] Did she threaten you like Drago?
- No no, no no no, this was all me.
I did it because I felt, I was thinking,
oh my God, I'm gonna
say Hooch to this girl?
Like, she might, be like, Hooch?
- [Matt] Wait, wait wait.
So she's never heard the name Hooch?
In all the months you've been chatting,
she's never heard the name Hooch.
- Never came up, never came up.
Nope.
- [Matt] Get the fuck outta here.
- Nope, never came up.
- [Matt] Oh, dude, you
know I'm ratting you out?
- Oh, that's fine.
Listen, hold on, when she gets here,
I felt it's obviously gonna come up.
It's a big part of me.
- [Matt] Of course it's gonna come up.
- But I figured tell her my
real name, who I really am,
and then somebody, one of my friends, you,
or somebody else.
- [Matt] It's on your license
plate, for God's sakes?
- Well, I didn't think of that one.
But oh well, oops.
Uh, yeah, all right, so.
Listen, I just felt like by using Rich
it was more, I felt proper, it was all me.
I just felt maybe it was like
being nervous at the time,
maybe I just was overthinking
things a little bit.
- [Matt] Oh, you're
definitely overthinking.
Dude, she's tightening you up.
- No she's not, it's
nothing to do with her.
Nothing at all.
It was about me.
- [Matt] She's bringing about changes,
and I don't like it.
- Listen, it was about me.
I figured once she's here,
I'll tell her I'm Hooch.
- [Matt] Dude, I am
never calling you Rich.
- That's fine, I'm not asking you to.
But, you know, and then
once she's here, she can--
- [Matt] Dude, at your wedding day,
when the priest says, do you, Rich?
I'm gonna be like, it's Hooch.
- Oh and by the way, nice hair.
(laughing)
- [Matt] What the hell does that?
Listen, listen, listen.
Okay, all right, I see what you did there.
A little diversion tactic, that's fine.
- No, nice hair, really, seriously.
- [Matt] Of course it's nice hair, dammit.
Listen, I know this is your girl,
I know this is your
thing, but there's no way
I wasn't gonna, I was gonna go with you
to meet like a hot Euro
and not do my hair.
Listen, I still need to look good.
- Oh no, that, that's, I mean.
- [Matt] I have a fragile ego.
- I mean, listen, I'll let
you have the hair thing,
being I didn't use the Hooch.
- [Matt] Okay.
- So you can have the hair thing.
If you need to rat me out
on the Hooch, you can.
- [Matt] Oh I am.
- I don't care, it's whatever,
but listen, this is finally
happening, we're minutes away.
7,000 miles away is now like, literally--
- [Matt] Seven blocks.
- Yeah, seven, eight blocks
down the street, and that's it.
- [Matt] But wait, wait wait, wait.
I do wanna clear up one
other thing, though.
We still have our arrangement, yes?
- Ohhhh.
Oh, what arrangement now?
Oh, this should be good.
Come on, what's the arrangement
you claim that I'm down with?
- [Matt] The one while
you're having sex with her
I get to watch from your closet.
- Excuse me?
(laughing)
Oh sure, right, okay.
- [Matt] Listen, listen,
just, while you're doing it,
just if you hear a
rattling in your closet,
just tell her to ignore it.
- I'll just tell her that's my friend Matt
getting his hard-on.
- [Matt] Just tell her to ignore it,
and I promise I will
clean up any mess I make.
- What's that big bang in your closet?
Um, nothing, something fell
off the shelf, I don't know.
Oh come on, man, you know what?
That's all I need, right, she's there,
we're getting it on
intimately, passionately,
in private, so she thinks.
- [Matt] And I pop out naked.
- Oh my God, dude, she's
going right back to Romania.
That's what gonna happen.
- [Matt] I'll rent that
big teddy bear costume,
and I'll pop out like that.
- All that money and all those video chats
are all gonna be flushed down the toilet
for your two minutes of
gratification, right.
Seriously, right?
- [Matt] Wait, what makes you think
I can last two minutes?
You tell me she's supposed
to meet you out front?
- [Hooch] Yeah, right over here somewhere.
In front of the terminal.
- [Matt] Is that her?
- [Hooch] Yeah, who's that, what?
- [Matt] Is it her, are you sure?
- [Hooch] Yeah, that's her.
- [Matt] Dude, she brought a friend.
- [Hooch] Whoa.
- [Matt] Dude, she's hot.
- [Hooch] Oh no.
- [Matt] Oh my God, dude, I'm so in.
I am so in.
Look at, oh my God, look at that.
Dude, I'm so in.
Quick, let's get out,
quick, hurry up, hurry up.
(car beeping)
I can't get out quick enough.
(laughing)
- Hello.
- How are you, finally?
- I know.
- Finally, you're here, wow.
- I know, wow.
- And you brought a friend?
- Yes, yes.
- [Matt] Like, is anybody
gonna introduce me,
or am I just like chopped liver?
- I'm Nicoletta, and this is Mihaela.
- [Matt] Matt.
- Oh.
- [Matt] Matt, sorry, say that again?
- Mihaela.
- [Matt] Mihaela, oh my God, oh.
Wow, very good to meet
you too, oh my goodness.
- No, she doesn't speak English.
- [Matt] Oh, no English?
- No.
- All right, even better.
(laughing)
- [Matt] Good, I don't have
to be clever all night.
Oh my God, you guys gotta
be tired and hungry.
- Yes, yes.
- [Matt] Dude, hey, let's
take them to the pub.
Get some dinner and drinks,
absolutely, here it is.
- [Matt] All right, guys, bring it in
to Hooch and Nicoletta.
(glasses clinking)
To a long happy relationship,
it's been a long time coming.
- Ahhhh.
- [Matt] I don't know if
she can hold her liquor.
- Yes I can.
- [Matt] She looks like she
was choking on that one.
- Stop.
(laughing)
- [Matt] So you guys are
finally, finally together,
after like months of anticipation.
Hooch, what are your thoughts, man?
- Oh man, it's amazing, she's here.
- I'm here.
- She's right here.
- [Matt] Look at this.
So now, like, he said that he told you
that his real name is Richard.
- It is.
- [Matt] I know it is,
but at the same time,
his nickname is Hooch, so
now are you gonna start
trying to make me like
call him like Richard now?
Because I don't know if I
can make that adjustment.
- Whatever he wants.
- Look at that, huh, ah, nice.
- [Matt] I believe they
call that a jackpot.
- Cha-ching, yes.
(balls breaking)
- [Matt] Oh, okay, I guess
that's how they shoot in Romania.
So, is it Mi-ha-ella?
Am I saying that right?
Oh, okay, okay cool, I got it right.
Mi-ha-ella, Mi-ha-ella.
If I say it too fast, I screw it up.
Mi-ha-ella, there it goes.
It's like a tongue twister, I can't do it.
Oh my God, so what do you think?
What do you think, do you like it here?
USA, do you like it here?
USA, yes?
Okay, cool, cool, all right.
You like it here, clearly.
How long was your flight?
It was from Romania, how long was that?
Okay, but you're from
Romania, yes, Romania?
Yes, yes, Romania.
Okay, yeah, we're making
a little progress.
Uh, uh.
Ah shit, I don't know what to say.
Oh, what do you think of Rich, Richard?
Do you like Richard?
Richard?
Nicoletta fiance?
Nicoletta, I got you to nod to Nicoletta.
We have word recognition.
Okay, you know what?
I am gonna go get you another drink,
so you just sit there and keep
nodding and smiling, I guess.
All right, I'll see you.
Wow, that went well.
Hooch, don't think too much about it,
just find a shot and go for it.
It's not like you're
gonna embarrass yourself
in front of your new, oh, wait a minute.
Maybe you will.
Oh boy, look at this.
The happy couple.
Hooch is in heaven right now.
He is so happy.
Oh my God, it's like he struck gold.
He just, he couldn't be much happier.
He is in good.
This is awesome, look at this.
All he has do is--
She's like completely locked
in on him, it's great.
He's like so happy.
You know what?
Good for him, good for my boy.
Oh my God, unbelievable.
Oh, he is so getting laid.
All right, Hooch, your bride-to-be,
let's see if she can get a shot in,
anything at this point.
(laughing)
All right, Hooch, you give it a shot.
Can somebody get a ball
in, any ball at all.
At this point, I'll take the eight-ball.
Hooch, Hooch, Hooch, come
with me for a second.
I'll bring him right back, I promise.
I'll bring him right back.
Stop stop stop, stop stop.
Dude, what do you think?
- Oh my God.
Incredible.
More beautiful than even in the photos.
Dude, I'm like wow.
- [Matt] Dude, she's awesome.
She's like perfect.
- Holy man, it is something, just wow.
I just can't believe it took
me so long, man, to just--
I shoulda done this a long time ago.
- [Matt] Dude, what are you
gonna do to that perfect body?
- Oh, that's freaking messed up (laughs).
I mean, I'll keep it in good form, but.
- [Matt] Dude, and the
other one's like hot,
but it's like pulling
teeth talking to her.
- Yeah, she's quiet, yeah.
- [Matt] She doesn't
speak a lick of English.
- She understood something
like, when you mentioned me,
and USA, that's it, nothing else.
- [Matt] That's all I'm getting.
- Yeah, sorry, man.
- [Matt] But I will be getting more later,
I promise you that.
But like, dude, she's
like, dude, I got an idea.
So it's like, you'll have your girl,
we'll go back to your apartment,
I'll hook up with the other one.
And dude, so like halfway
through, we'll switch.
And that way I get to have both.
- We'll what, excuse me?
Hello, um, um, no.
I think one's taken already.
- [Matt] But you see, you see,
you shoulda done this a long time ago.
- Oh no, absolutely.
I mean, I'm like, but I'm stubborn,
and you kept trying to push me and push me
till finally I'm just like, just do it.
Just, just, and I think
it's the best thing
I've ever done in my whole life.
I don't know, I'm just like.
- [Matt] I'm happy for
you, I'm happy for you.
- Absolutely, man, this is it.
It's a new beginning for me.
Finally, what I been
looking for my whole life.
- Good, good for you.
All right, guys, ready?
One,
two, three.
- [All] Romania!
- [Matt] Hooch, you got the keys, right?
- [Hooch] Yes, I do, right here.
- [Matt] Good, that would be bad.
- [Hooch] Ready to roll, of course.
You cannot forget the keys.
(whistling)
Over here.
All righty, come on in.
Watch your step right here.
Be careful right there, watch yourself.
- [Matt] Thank you.
- All righty, right this way.
Down this way.
All righty.
Make yourselves comfortable right here.
Right here will do.
All righty.
Ohhhhh.
- [Matt] Sorry, ladies.
Hooch, let me borrow you
for one sec, one sec.
- All righty.
- [Matt] Sorry.
- I shall return.
- [Matt] We'll be right back, I promise.
- [Hooch] All righty, be right back.
(footsteps)
- [Matt] Dude, come here,
come here, come here.
Dude, dude, dude, you
gotta take the camera
for a little bit.
- Huh, why?
- [Matt] Dude, I wanna hook
up with his Mihaela chick.
- Oh come on, really now?
- [Matt] Dude, I've been
filming all night, man.
Just for a little while.
Plus, plus, plus, dude,
you get to like film her.
You get to film her.
- All right, all right.
- You get to keep the camera on her.
- All right, you sold me.
- [Matt] Good, good.
- [Hooch] You happy now?
- Uh, yes I am.
- [Hooch] So now what do you wanna do?
- Show me your bedroom.
- [Hooch] Hold on, let me just check.
Oh, he's fine.
- I have a surprise for you.
I'll be right back.
(door knocking)
- [Hooch] Come in.
Wow!
- You like what you see?
- [Hooch] Yes, very much.
- I choose it for you.
- [Hooch] I don't even
know what to say, but wow!
- You don't have to say anything.
You know, ever since you choose me,
I've been waiting for this night.
I'm going to make you so happy.
Give you everything you
want, everything you desire.
I'm going to make all of
your dreams come true,
make you never want another
woman again, I guarantee it.
I'm going to do very bad things to you.
I'm going to make you feel
things you never feel before.
You have no idea how
hard it's been to wait.
I want to taste you.
Mmmmm.
(panting)
Mmmm.
Mmmm, oh.
Haaaa.
Haaa.
(slurping)
Haaaa.
- [Hooch] Ow, ow!
What the fuck?
Did you just fucking bite me?
(laughing)
What the fuck?
You did bite me.
- Of course, I'm from Romania (giggles).
- [Hooch] I'm fucking bleeding!
- Actually, Transylvania.
- [Hooch] What?
- Remember when we chatted, I
told you I liked heavy guys?
There's more of you to feed on (laughs).
- [Hooch] You crazy bitch!
Matt?
(hissing)
What?
(laughing)
- Leaving so soon.
- [Hooch] Let me out!
(gasping)
(choking)
- What's the matter, Richard,
you don't want me anymore?
(choking)
(hard breathing)
- How did he taste?
- I finally shut him up,
and he taste like shit.
What about him?
- Not bad, you wanna try him?
- After I drain this one.
Be right back.
- [Hooch] No, please, no.
No.
- Oh, Richard, you Americans
are such easy prey.
You're all the same.
I show you beautiful woman
in provocative outfit
and you are, how do you
say, putty in my hands.
- [Hooch] No, please, no.
- Oh you thought you found
the perfect little Euro bride.
- [Hooch] Please, no, no, please no.
- Shut up already.
At least your friend died silently.
- Shh, no, Miha.
It's okay, Richard, this will hurt.
You can scream.
(biting)
(slurping)
(hard breathing)
(panting)
- I must confess.
I was hoping I was wrong about you people.
But the fact that you're still here
only confirms my suspicions
that you truly are
sick, perverted deviants.
Directors like this twisted
individual hand-feed you
sex and violence, mix it together,
and pass it off as horror.
And you people gorge yourselves on it
as if it's some delectable
buffet at a Sunday brunch.
I truly am disappointed.
What? What does it say?
Make a joke, make a joke about what?
About this short we just watched?
It'll make me feel better.
Surely you jest.
And there's certainly nothing funny
in this utter filth being
presented here tonight.
Your entire film offends
me and my sensibilities.
I believe I will take my leave of you now.
Good day, sir.
- [Director] Um, there's one more story.
- I said, good day, sir.
What, who are you?
Let me pass.
I said step aside, my good man.
Do not test me, dear boy.
I may be a gentleman,
but I'm quite formidable.
What, what are you doing?
No, ahhhhhhhh.
(banging)
Unhand me, you brute.
(soft music)
As I was saying, I'm absolutely delighted,
I'm overjoyed to have the privilege
of introducing the next tale in this utter
masterpiece of a film, send help.
Our final story tonight has
us following the exploits
of three teenage girls as they dabble
in the art of witchcraft in
order to obtain magical powers.
Call the police, call INTERPOL.
So without further ado,
I introduce to you,
The Coven, help me?
- Are you nervous.
- [Kyla] Yeah, a little bit.
- Don't be, it's gonna be fun.
It's a good day.
We have everything we can do.
You know, I've been practicing at home.
Have you?
I told you to.
- [Kyla] Yeah, a little bit, little bit.
- A little?
Come on, oh my gosh, we talked about this
that you, honestly if it's not gonna work,
then it's gonna be on
you because I've been
working really hard (giggles).
So, if something does not go as planned,
you're to blame, sorry, not sorry.
But no, we should be good.
I feel confident, you know.
- [Kyla] Yeah, I think
everything will go good.
- I hope so.
Are you gonna go, sir?
Yes, cool, awesome.
Honestly, I just feel good.
I don't know about you,
I woke up this morning,
I was excited, I just
wanna get it over with so
I can see the outcome
right away, you know?
- [Kyla] Uh-huh.
- I've been reading,
I've been researching and
a lotta people who really care and put
a lot of effort into it
seem to be successful.
So I think I have, so
hopefully, we'll have the same outcome.
- [Kyla] Yeah, I think we have a good shot
of making this happen.
- Me too, I can't wait.
- [Natalie] Look at her.
- Yeah, what's up, bitches?
- Hey.
- Guess what I just found out.
- [Kyla] What?
- My parents aren't gonna
be home next weekend.
- Mine aren't either, that's so weird.
- [Elise] Ooh, we should have a party.
- We could have it at your
house, because you know,
my dad has like those
weird security cameras.
- Oh yeah, damn.
- [Natalie] Oh yeah,
he'd see like one person
and he'd like fly right home.
- [Kyla] Oh yeah, we can't do that.
- [Elise] Well whatever.
Fuck that, we'll have it at mine.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah, I just found out
they're gonna be gone
the whole weekend, so we're good.
- There's no way they'd come
early or anything like that?
- [Elise] No, they have a hotel,
they have everything, they're set.
- [Kyla] Really.
- [Elise] Mm-hmm, they're not coming back.
- Shit, okay.
I will give you money for alcohol,
and I'll help you plan and shit.
- Awesome, yeah, we can all throw down.
- Cool.
All right, well, what about today?
Do you guys feel ready?
- [Elise] I'm super ready,
I've been so excited.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah.
- Good, me too, I couldn't
even sleep last night.
I was like, I know, like, I think it's
a mix of nerves and like excitement.
- [Elise] Yeah, totally.
- I think it's mostly excitement.
I just gotta, you know,
we gotta get it over with.
See what happens.
I just wanna see like what the outcome is.
- [Kyla] Yeah, but this
should be a lotta fun, though.
- I know, but like, I was researching
and I was looking at like
what people who tried,
you know, similar stuff said before,
and there's a lotta mixed stuff.
So I feel like if you're
prepared, you know,
feel good, like I know I do,
I think we should be okay
for the most part, but.
- We're ready, let's make the leap.
Like no more hesitation.
- [Kyla] I know, I just
wanna see results right away.
- [Elise] You can't do it, who can, so.
- [Kyla] Exactly.
We've been thinking about
this for a while now, so.
- And, if something goes
wrong, I'm blaming it on Kyla.
You can't fuck us up, okay?
- [Kyla] I won't, I swear.
- [Natalie] Rachel's been
like so annoying lately.
- [Elise] Yeah, like, she's the worst.
- [Natalie] I don't think
she's really that awful.
- [Elise] I know she's
been really bitchy lately.
- You wouldn't think she's that awful.
You guys were besties back
in your cheerleading days.
- [Natalie] Yep, I knew you
were gonna bring that up.
You're so funny.
Cheerleading.
- Yes, our little Natalie,
preppy cheerleader.
- [Natalie] Shut up.
- [Kyla] Preppy cheerleader.
- [Natalie] Oh my God,
yeah, look at me now.
Look at the difference.
- Oh, I know you got it in you.
Come on, where is it?
- Give me an N.
- N.
- Give me an A.
A.
- Come on, join in,
you're the professional.
- [Natalie] You're the professional bitch.
- What's next week, ballerina?
- [Natalie] You know I'm not coordinated
enough to to that, please.
I have two left feet, you're funny.
Like I said, guys, this
is why I'm a spooky bitch,
because I can't do sports, I can't do any
like, you know, other physical activity,
cheerleading, whatever, so
I guess I'm goth.
You can relate, right?
- Yeah.
- Shit.
- That better not be the only reason.
- [Natalie] Oh my God,
yeah, I'm sure you guys
weren't perfect either.
What'd you do, like
gymnastics or something?
- [Kyla] I wasn't friends
with Rachel, I know that much.
- [Natalie] Oh my God.
- You know who's a weirdo?
- Who?
- Mr. Burkley.
- [Natalie] Oh my God, yes he is.
I really don't like him.
- [Elise] Such a creep.
- Gives me a really bad
vibe, and you wouldn't think
like, by now, like, I
know it's not just us.
I think like a buncha girls
would complain about him.
I don't know how he still has a job.
- [Kyla] Exactly, like the things he says,
like out loud in class, I don't know how
he gets away with it.
- Oh yeah, I bet he drives a white van.
(laughing)
No but don't you wonder like,
that's probably how Sarah
gets her extra credit.
- Probably.
- Yep.
- [Kyla] That's why she
gets such good grades.
- [Elise] She has to suck something
just to not suck at math.
- Ooh, bitch.
You know what, maybe I should
start kissing up to him,
though, because I have a
really bad grade in math.
- [Elise] Yeah I think that's about the
only thing you could do.
(laughter)
- [Kyla] Pretty much.
I don't do any of my
homework in that class.
- Well I like try, you
just like don't do it.
- [Kyla] I just wish he
wasn't like so perverted.
- [Elise] Yeah, I don't
take my orders from a creep.
No thank you.
- I don't take orders from anyone.
- [Kyla] It's so nasty out here today.
- [Natalie] Yep, good thing
we're all wearing black.
It's so unusual for us.
I hate summer.
- [Elise] Exactly, all the
mosquitoes and bugs out here.
- [Kyla] I just wish it
was fall so I could wear
combat boots and leggings
without sweating my ass off.
- [Elise] Wish all the bugs would just go
in their little homes.
Well, I guess it's time set up.
(birds chirping)
- From east to south and north to west,
I call to you, Hecate,
to attend and bless.
To brew my spells and honor you well.
With my hand steadfast, my circle is cast.
Hecate, we are gathered here today
to ask that you shine some of your wisdom,
knowledge and power
upon three young witches
who will be loyal to you.
(birds chirping)
We ask that you lend us a hand
on our guide to witchcraft and help us
lead a successful, powerful
path down this journey.
(birds chirping)
And now we're done, with harm to none.
I inhale the power, at this magical hour.
Stay if you will,
but go if you must.
(birds chirping)
- I don't feel anything.
- Me either.
- Give it a minute please.
- Okay.
(birds chirping)
- I still don't feel anything.
- Do you wanna try reading it?
- I'm good.
- I don't understand,
it's exactly what I wrote
down, word for word.
Why is it not working?
- Did it say how long it normally takes
when you were reading up on it?
- No.
Were you focusing?
- Yeah, I was focused.
- Were you?
- Mm-hmm.
- You're sure?
- Yeah.
- I don't understand.
Fuck.
- [Elise] So, Nat, I'm just like
busting with power over here.
- Same.
- [Elise] It's coming outta
my fingers, yeah, exactly.
- Okay, we get it, I know.
Yeah, I know, but when we try
next time, we should be fine.
I don't know what we did wrong.
I was ready.
- [Elise] I was ready too.
- So was I.
- Are you sure?
Because whoever fucked
up, I know it wasn't me.
- [Elise] How are you
so sure it wasn't you,
Miss Can't Do Anything Wrong?
- That's me.
Well, you know, I've been
researching every night.
I've been doing my morning
rituals, my bedtime rituals.
I've been doing fucking everything,
cleansing baths, like,
what have you been doing?
Partying, drinking, smoking, yeah.
- [Elise] I've been doing stuff,
no, I've been visualizing.
- Oh you've been visualizing, great.
You're something else.
- [Elise] I've been
doing rituals, you know.
- Well, listen, I don't know.
Maybe you just have to fail
the first time and then.
- [Kyla] The first time, second time.
- You shut the fuck up, because
I feel like this is you.
Miss Oh My God I'm Nervous,
I Don't Wanna Do it Yet, no.
Kyla, my money is on you
because you just need a,
oh my God, you both, you know what?
Look at you, you're giggling,
you're taking things not seriously.
- [Elise] You gotta laugh it off.
- Okay, yeah, but not when
you're doing, you know,
a ritual or something.
Maybe if we took this more
seriously, all three of us,
shit woulda been more successful.
So, my money's on one
of you two fucking up.
You laugh at everything,
and you're nervous as fuck,
and I'm fucking ready, so
I know that it's not me.
- [Elise] I'm just having a good time.
I was ready, I know it wasn't me.
- Yeah, well, I'm getting
a little desperate here,
so I'm about to sacrifice a
fucking goat or something.
Because, yeah, I went there, exactly.
So, I don't know, I
just, I feel like shit.
But keep laughing at me,
just kick me while I'm down.
(giggling)
Yeah, oh ho, really fun.
- [Elise] You gotta be
able to laugh it off,
kiddo, come on.
- God, shut up.
You're so annoying, you sound like my mom.
(laughing)
I don't know, maybe round two will work.
I don't know, I guess we
gotta just take a breather,
you know, do some spiritual
like cleansing baths.
Just like relax, I don't know.
Hopefully it'll work out.
- [Elise] Yeah, maybe a bath
will give us all our power.
- Baaa.
I think you need to
fucking take a bath, bitch.
Maybe it'll clean your
attitude up, my God.
- [Elise] You too, Miss
Blaming It on Everybody Else.
- Well, listen, I'm, shit.
Okay, whatever, well
I feel like I didn't--
I don't know, I felt the best
I think out of all of us.
- [Elise] How could you know?
- How could I know, because I put like
my heart and soul into it.
- [Elise] And we didn't?
- No, that's what I'm saying.
- [Elise] Maybe your doubt in the group
is what made it fail.
- Okay, funny, why would
I have reason to doubt
with you two fucking idiots?
But the thing is, like, look at you.
Like I'm fucking hurt, and you guys
are like, oh yeah, next time.
So maybe if you were sad
and you like cared a lot
about it, and you just
put more effort into it,
it would've worked out the first time.
- [Elise] Who doesn't care
a lot about acquiring power?
- [Kyla] Exactly.
- Well, you don't seem
to be too upset about it.
- [Elise] I'm upset, I just
don't show it like you.
I laugh and have a good
time when I'm upset.
- Okay.
Well, I guess we all have our
own way of doing shit, but.
- [Elise] You gotta be a bitchy witchy.
- I guess so.
(laughing)
- Natalie's taking this
really really seriously.
I mean, like,
it's not like we're not
gonna try this again like
next week or something, like,
we're gonna go back, so like,
I just, I don't know why she's
taking this so seriously.
Like, she's probably the one
that messed it up or something.
I don't know.
(door knocking)
- [Mr. Boland] Hey, Honey.
- [Natalie] Good, Mr. Boland, how are you?
- [Mr. Boland] Good, how are you doing?
- I'm doing good.
- Natalie!
- Hello, how are you?
- What are you guys up to?
- Oh, we are going to the
woods, casting spells,
you know, normal stuff.
- Generation Z stuff.
- [Kyla] Dad.
- [Mr. Boland] Just teasing, you guys.
- Are you ready to go?
- Yeah.
- Can I come too?
- No.
- [Mr. Boland] Listen,
not too late today, okay?
- All right, love you.
- No problem.
- [Mr. Boland] Love you too.
- [Kyla] It's even worse
out here than last week.
- [Natalie] Yep, life is disgusting.
- [Kyla] Too many spinny bugs.
Ooh.
Just wish it would cool down already.
- [Natalie] I know.
- [Klya] Maybe we should
waited an extra couple weeks.
- [Natalie] Yeah, I guess so.
(footsteps)
- Kyla.
- Hmm?
(thumping)
- Yo, I don't think I could do this, man.
She's only 18, dude,
she's just our friend.
- [Natalie] I don't wanna
have to do this, either.
I love her just as much as you do,
but you need to relax, okay?
We are not going to get
anything done if you're gonna be
so hysterical the entire time.
Just believe.
You have to trust me on
this, this is the only way
that this can happen, you know that.
- I don't.
- [Natalie] This always works, okay?
- How do you know?
How do you know, you're
reading from a fucking book.
This is not a book anymore.
- [Natalie] Elise, you have to believe me.
You're only gonna freak
her out more, okay?
Please, just relax.
- I don't know if I can do this, man.
- [Kyla] What's going on?
What's happening?
- She's fucking awake.
You can't fucking do this to her, dude.
- Shut the fuck up, you're gonna wake.
Okay, just stop.
You're gonna freak her out, okay?
Here, listen, listen, you hold the camera.
Hold the camera.
Kyla?
We have to tell you something.
- What?
(crying)
- We're going to sacrifice you.
- No no no, untie me.
- I'm so sorry, okay.
Listen.
Elise and I did research,
and this is the only way.
We need a virgin sacrifice,
and you're the only virgin that we know.
- No, no, untie me.
Elise, Elise, please, help me.
Untie me, untie me.
No no no, you're fucking crazy.
- I'm not crazy, okay,
no one's gonna miss you.
We're your friends.
We're you're only friends.
Don't you wanna help us on this?
- What about my sister?
What about my sister, my little sister?
Help me, untie me, untie me.
Untie me, untie me.
- [Natalie] Give me that,
I can't look at her.
- Please, please, help me.
- [Natalie] This is so you don't have
to see it coming, okay?
- Untie me, untie me.
- And so I don't have to
look at you while I do this.
- Untie me, untie me, untie me.
- [Natalie] It's gonna be okay.
- [Elise] Untie me, untie me.
Someone help me out,
please help, please help.
Untie me, untie me, help, help.
Help me, please.
Please please please, no no no no.
- I'm sorry, Kyla.
- [Elise] No no, no no.
- I love you.
I love you, okay?
- [Elise] No no no no.
No no no.
(grunting)
(coughing)
No, help.
- Elise, I need you to
start singing, okay?
People are gonna hear her screaming.
You need to start singing.
Fucking sing now!
♪ Ah, ah, ah ♪
(knife penetrating)
(Elise vocalizing)
(coughing)
(knife penetrating)
- [Natalie] It's almost over now.
(engine revving)
(car door opening)
- [Natalie] It's gonna be okay.
She did a really good thing for us.
And,
you will start to feel it soon.
I promise.
- [Elise] If you say so.
(car door opening)
- [Natalie] Um, bye.
(car door closing)
(footsteps)
- It's never, nothing's
ever gonna the same.
I'm not the same.
I don't.
I just wish I could.
Nothing, nothing to do, there's.
Just have to sit here,
just like I stood there,
doing nothing, nothing.
And just.
I just.
Just wanna go back, and I can't.
I'm such an idiot.
Why did I just,
just stood there.
Just let her,
I just.
What the fuck?
I don't know who I am anymore.
I don't.
It's.
I can't be me anymore, I.
Just want.
(crying)
I can't believe it's real.
Nothing's the s--
Nothing's worth this.
Nothing,
I didn't know, I didn't.
I didn't know
that was gonna be.
I'm just.
Can't stop seeing it.
And that's it, that's
all it's ever gonna be,
just seeing it over and over.
And just not moving, not doing anything.
I can't be me anymore.
I thought they were the best thing
that's ever happened.
It's the worst.
I can't, I don't, I
don't want this, I don't.
(doorbell ringing)
(sighing)
I don't feel.
Like a person.
I don't.
Nothing makes sense any--
I just.
I just wish I could.
I wish I did.
(door slamming)
Who the fuck is that?
Fucking kids.
(door creaking)
(crickets chirping)
(wind blowing)
Fucking kids broke the lock.
(crickets chirping)
(door closing)
(footsteps)
(crickets chirping)
(hard breathing)
The fuck?
- [Kyla] Elise.
(thumping)
(Kyla vocalizing)
(crying)
- Kyla.
Kyla, I'm so sorry.
I didn't mean it, Kyla.
Please, you know I didn't mean it.
I love you so much.
I knew it'd be you that'd
come back, I knew it.
Kyla, please.
I'm so sorry.
It was a mistake.
I knew it was a mistake.
I shoulda stopped her, I'm so sorry.
(crying)
You gotta believe me, I love you so much.
I didn't wanna do it.
(crying)
It was Natalie.
You know it was Natalie.
I shoulda stopped her.
No, oh, oh.
You know it was Natalie.
Please, no (screams).
(deep breathing)
- Okay, so, after collecting
all of my thoughts today,
I really have to say that,
I'm so fucking proud of myself
for being able to do
something that I never
thought that I could do a week ago.
If you told me a week
ago that I was gonna do
what I did today at that ritual,
I would have not believed it.
I really wouldn't have, because
it's almost like all of my doubts
and all of my worries
were just like washed away
before this all happened at the ritual.
And I feel like that was
Hecate's way of telling me,
you know, I've got you,
everything's gonna be okay.
I'm gonna help you get through this.
I want you to succeed.
And, oh my God, it
just, I already feel it.
Like, I already feel this sort of power
just in my veins, and I feel confident,
I feel invincible, I
don't feel like myself,
but in the best way.
I feel like I could get hit
by a fucking truck right now
and I'd be fine.
Oh my God, I just,
I'm proud of myself.
So, with that being said,
I think I'm just gonna do
my normal goodnight ritual,
and then I'll call it a night.
(door closing)
(sighing)
Hello?
And it's probably just the cat.
So, now I'm gonna do my goodnight ritual,
so I will keep you all updated.
Now I lay me down to rest,
I pray that all the world be blessed.
Lady Moon and Sister Star,
watch over me from afar.
Mother Earth is always there
and keeps me safe within her care.
The Lord of Dreams will to me bring,
and when I wake, to greet the day,
Brother Sun will light my way.
What the?
Who ripped out my?
Oh my God.
(hard breathing)
(crying)
(thumping)
(papers rattling)
Oh my God, oh my God, Elise.
Oh my God.
I have to tell Elise,
I have to tell Elise.
I tried to call Elise's
house so many times,
and no one is picking up the phone.
And, I'm starting to
get really freaked out,
and I know, I know that
this isn't possible.
- [Kyla] Natalie.
(gasping)
- No, no, no no no.
Please, please.
Please.
Fuck.
(crying)
No, no no.
Oh my God.
(hard breathing)
Protection spell.
Wait, wait, I have a
protection spell in my book.
What?
What the fuck?
(crying)
No.
(sobbing)
Kyla?
I'm sorry.
(gasping)
(voices whispering)
Oh my God.
(panicking)
(choking)
(crying)
(voices echoing)
- Well, as you can see, I
am free of my constraints.
I have fulfilled my contractual
obligations to be in this chair.
So until next time, that is
if enough of you actually
watch this piece of shit
to warrant a sequel,
I bid you farewell.
I want my money, and
I want to get the fuck
out of here, posthaste!
If you think I'm returning
here for a sequel,
you are sorely mistaken!
I have half a mind to call my attorney
the way I was treated.
(door slamming)
(soft classical music)