Hey!
Hey! Come over here,
I think I've found it!
Come closer.
Do you know what you have found?
I'll tell you my story.
This skull was once my mother's.
These bones were once my family.
The blood our family spilled,
marked the beginning
of the most violent century
the world has ever known.
Mama,
why did they hate us so much?
And why did they hate our friend,
Father Grigori Rasputin?
He was my saviour,
my Merlin, my wizard.
Father Grigori was magic.
Grigori, what do you see?
I see...
a flower.
Grigori,
what do you see?
Love?
What did he say?
It's my turn.
Come closer.
--
He has no magic.
Wait.
You stole Yegorov's horse.
This boy is mad.
What are you raising,
a child or a devil?
Boy,
come here.
Apologise.
Why?
Forgive me.
But let him deny it, father.
Let him deny it.
Yes.
Let him deny it!
It's not true!
God is good
There he is.
They say you are a wizard.
They say you're an imbecile.
Tell me, what do I have
behind my back?
A coin.
A book.
A leaf. A pipe. A rock.
The Archbishop's balls.
I told you he's all dried up.
Plough this row to
that hill by nightfall
or lose your pay.
-
Enough!
Father Grigori said
the holy mother
asked him to help me.
No matter what people
said about him later,
I know better,
because he came to St. Petersburg
and he saved my life.
She became the mother
of God himself.
She carried him in her arms.
She nourished him with her milk.
Who can describe the greatness
of the Virgin Mother of God.
I saw Her.
First the sky was empty,
then silver, then gold.
Her eyes were purple,
and Her skin was ivory,
and She reached out her hand
and blessed me.
Who are you?
Grigori Rasputin,
from Pokrovskoye.
Why are you here?
The mother of God,
she told me to come.
Many have come here claiming
to have seen the virgin.
She touched me...
here.
Some said the bishop was hypnotised.
Some said he had seen the truth.
All of St. Petersburg
was talking about this day.
Bless me.
The Virgin has touched him.
There was little hope for me.
Me, Alexei.
Sovereign heir, Tsarevitch
to the Russian throne.
God help me.
He will.
How much mama prayed
that God would forgive her.
For it was she who carried
my disease in her blood.
Your majesty,
I know of a holy man
who can heal.
What a wretch.
Disgusting.
Alexi.
The man from Siberia is here.
Mama.
Don't be frightened.
Christ is with you,
don't weep anymore,
everything passes.
Why is your heart so heavy?
Do you have faith?
There's no reason to suffer.
The Lord bless his faithful servant
Alexandra Feodorovna.
This is Father Grigori,
from Siberia.
Papa.
He's come to bless Alexei.
The Tsarevitch is sleeping.
My blessings
are powerful.
Just a moment.
He's sleeping, Father.
Grandpa?
Alexei,
this is Father Grigori,
he has come to bless you.
Father, quickly.
How is your leg?
Did you tell him?
It hurts.
Oh now, that's enough.
Derevenko, lead him out.
No more opiates for this boy.
- Take him!
- No, wait.
Do you like to sail?
Yes.
The sea brings comfort.
And the waves...
they talk.
The sun shines on the water
as it gently rises.
You can see the face of God.
You look at the sun...
your soul
forgets everything
as you wake from the dream
of life's worries.
for the joy lights your heart
and your soul sees the wisdom of life
and beauty
indescribable.
Is the pain gone?
Yes.
There now.
Go to sleep.
Sleep.
I'm telling you.
Something to drink?
Madeira, if you have it.
Who told you...
about Tsarevich's leg?
The mother of God.
Her voice blooms like a kiss in my ears,
and then grows till it hurts my body,
and tears at my ears until
I want to cry: enough!
She told me how your boy suffered.
I know his blood is diseased.
I don't know why I was chosen.
I'm just a poor, stupid man.
Pray to her, mama, papa.
God is good.
The Prime Minister.
The French ambassador is here.
Peter.
Oh, I'm sorry, I didn't know.
This is Father Grigori.
Prime Minister Stolypin.
And, thank you so much
for coming, Father.
Downstairs.
The man's drunk as a boiled owl.
Thank you, Father.
I'll call for a motor.
Does a wretch drink wine
with the Empress?
Does a wretch rest his face
in her lap?
How else would he have known
about Alexei's leg?
Gossip.
Hearsay.
You saw him limp from the bed.
He took his pain.
What is it, Nicky?
There has been another bombing.
Stolypin thinks it's the
electrical workers and...
and the way they
want another meeting.
It's a plot to undermine you,
to make you look weak
and start more trouble.
Smile.
I never see you smile.
Do you remember the
little cottage we stayed in
when we visited
your family in Germany?
And the picnics we used to have,
and the songs we sang
under the chestnut tree?
What in the world
made you think of that?
And how those fishermen
splashed us with their oars,
and didn't know who we were.
--
And how we never ever
wanted to leave.
#
#  #
God
blast
the Tsar!
Do you know the saying
from my youth?
"After the last of my flesh
has tormented me
"Lord Jesus Christ do not condemn me,
"therefore."
Do you know it?
Alexei.
Look.
It's a miracle.
Oh.
Papa!
Alexei?
How did this happen?
The Holy Man did it.
I want to show the girls.
Alexei.
Morning, Dr Botkin.
Look! The Holy Man cured me!
It’s all gone. He took it all with him.
- How?
- With magic!
Like Baba Yaga?
Like a good wizard.
Like Jesus Christ.
Meprobamate.
It’s known to slow the flow of blood
in some haemophiliacs.
I started using it last week.
But Alexei was cured last night,
doctor, not last week.
These things often take times.
--I can walk!
Who are you really?
The infinite.
-
Next time your excellency
goes to the palace,
Ask the Tsarina if I might
borrow her crown.
I will see her today.
Grigori Rasputin.
Her Imperial Majesty
The Empress Alexandra Feodorovna
now wishes to see me.
Yes.
Now, call me a liar.
Ah.
I spend days on my knees
to heal my son in minutes.
Do you have faith, mama?
I pray, I...
In your heart, do you have it?
- I try.
- Answer the question.
I don't know.
Then get on your knees and beg. Beg like
a peasant with your knees in the dirt.
- How dare you!
- Like a beggar
or a sneak or a thief.
You are the reason
the little one suffers.
You doubt the divinity of God.
Your prayers mock his name.
Every time the boy screams,
it is your knife in his body.
Mama, God cursed your son.
Only He can cure him.
Do doctors listen to God?
Answer.
- No.
- No, the disease will leave him.
The holy mother promised
but only if you believe in her mercy.
Cherish and then, don't you see
God has sent me.
I'm afraid.
The child isn't helpless
but he can do nothing
in his weakness.
He doesn't need medicine,
he needs a pony, a sled.
We may pray to God
on our knees
but we also pray in joy,
in laughter and in love.
Father...
I have premonitions.
Of what?
Terrible things.
Tell me.
My husband
does not want to rule.
Wait.
Watch.
A miracle is yet to come.
Alexei!
Let him be.
Go.
Father Grigori set me free
with his magic.
I could play with my sisters
and teacher-- in the park again.
For the first time Mama could believe
in me as the next Tsar of Russia.
I had all that I wanted.
What did others have?
No food, no coal.
Some wrap papers on their feet
instead of shoes.
Papa said this is how God
has willed it.
I know that some call Papa,
Nicholas the Bloody
but those were his enemies.
Boo!
Who is that?
I wanted to say goodnight.
Come in.
-
So, how are we?
Good.
Are you going to be
working all night again?
Probably.
Why do you work so hard?
Because I love Russia
and I love her people.
But they don't love
the revolutionaries.
Olga said so.
No.
They killed granddad, Alexei.
And Uncle Serge.
Why don't you give them
what they want?
Because they want the throne...
and God gave that to me and
only God can take it away.
Father Grigori could protect it for us.
Oh, I'll protect it for you, Alexei.
As my father protected it for me.
I promise you.
Mama and Papa were so happy on the day
when they could show me to everyone.
We didn't tell them who
we had to thank for this miracle.
For me?
And what do you know about love?
- Olga's in love.
- I'm not!
- I saw you flirting.
- So do you.
Who is he?
You can tell me.
I'm an avant-garde.
Well, he's a marine guard
on the Standard.
What do we know about this Rasputin?
He has a fondness for
strong Madeira, cheese cake
and gypsy prostitutes.
We don't know if he talks
to God or to the devil.
After 12 years of torture
I have peace.
And what if he were to talk to the press
about Alexei's condition.
That the next Tsar to Russia could bleed to
death by pricking his finger on a rosebush.
Handing the revolutionaries
more ammunition.
Nicky, help me.
I love you.
Father Grigori.
A morsel of bread is
more precious to men
than a mountain of
diamonds and gold, amen.
Amen.
Tatiana, pass the bread.
Perhaps our next tsar
will be called Alexei the Terrible.
You know children,
when Father Grigori made his
pilgrimage to St Petersburg,
he travelled 1,000 miles all over it.
And I walked and walked
and walked, all day.
Sometimes...
3 days without food.
I worked with the labourers
and I prayed by the river,
and I never once
touched my flesh.
But I was young then,
and have since learned
that although the soul
may belong to God
and the flesh belongs to us.
Have you been to
Mount Athos in Greece?
Yes.
It's a simple place,
no gold or silver but
for taking on the life.
When I arrived, I went
for a walk through the woods
and suddenly I heard breathing
through the bushes
I saw two monks,
naked as nature,
one behind the other...
Come with me.
Father, the palace is our home,
I insist you treat it with respect.
When you spit in the country it lands in
the dirt, here it lands on somebody's head.
The Empress likes you
a great deal, in fact...
she has opened her heart.
It is a fragile heart,
it is easily broken.
Without me, the little one will die.
I see more blood.
I have his pain,
you will need me.
I think that that is enough.
I didn't choose to be holy, Papa.
It frightens me through.
You will wait here for an escort.
They came to celebrate
300 years of Romana --.
Our great dynasty
anointed by God.
One day I will be Emperor and
autocrat of all the Russians.
Tsar of Moscow,
Kiev, Vladimir, Kazan, of Poland,
of Siberia, of Georgia.
Grand Duke of Lithuania.
But what I thought
was the beginning,
turned out to be the
beginning of the end.
Make it stop! Make it stop!
It's useless.
Maria, try to find Father Grigori.
Father Grigori!
- Maria, hurry!
- And a real priest.
Lord have mercy.
Christ have mercy.
Grigori?
Grigori Rasputin, wake up.
Father Grigori!
Mama.
Please, help him.
God hear me now,
for the peace and tranquillity
of holy Russia,
for the good of its people,
spare
the life of this child.
For the Greek ---
And the sun shining on the water
See the face of God
in the waves.
Remember the pain
as it leaves your body.
Remember the joy
as it leapt in your heart.
Mama.
Alexei.
Open your eyes.
Oh...
Very impressive.
You'll always fail
because your soul is dead.
I have performed many
autopsies in my time
but I've never located a soul.
How many memories
or emotions have you found?
The future of Russia is in your hands.
The man is a first class hypnotist.
We were in the same room, doctor?
Did we see the same thing?
By hypnotising the boy,
he lowers his blood pressure,
slowing the flow
of the blood itself.
What I saw was a miracle!
The mind is capable
of fantastic things.
The man is soothing,
the boy likes him.
There's nothing more to it than that.
Sir, forgive me,
I think it's about time the people
knew the truth about your son's health.
People are talking.
The papers are making up
all kinds of stories
to explain this man's
presence in the palace.
I don't care, doctor,
he saved my son.
This is his new address.
I want you to post around-the-clock
surveillance and record everything.
And begin immediately.
"The story of my life."
"Although I am a poor man
with no learning.
"I have already performed
great services for the crown."
What services?
The Empress has been under a
great deal of psychological pressure.
So what are you saying?
She's very...
vulnerable.
Father Grigori?
They say you are fool.
I'm a believer.
Princess Marisa Ivanovna.
This is for you.
I forgive you.
Sit.
Why are you here?
- My husband...
- Shht!
What's all this noise?
You think that you love him
and I see that you do
but when night comes and you
climb into bed, he leaves you alone.
Yes.
Yet, someone else
who puts her black hair
on his chest
and listens to his heart
beat in her ear.
- How can you know this?
- And I see a tall man
with the face of an eagle and
a jacket that is covered
in ribbons and gold.
He wants your heart
but he has a wife of his own.
What a web we weave.
What else do you know?
The greatest gift in the world is love.
Only through love
can we enter the gates of heaven.
You understand.
But pride is a sin
and you are so full of pride.
What is the greatest sin of pride?
Chastity.
Repentance is very pleasing to God
but before we can repent
we first have to sin.
What?
God has the answers.
He has the key.
No.
A humble soul is a holy soul.
Humble yourself.
Kiss me.
--means more to me than this.
--
I would cut these wrists,
if it would give you a
single moment of happiness.
Think of God, my angel.
He gave us this pleasure.
I talk to God.
Kiss me
and you kiss Him.
Lay with me and you will lay with Him.
I know you're frightened,
I'm frightened too.
But when we kiss holy things
we should kiss with
the soul and the heart.
As well as the mouth.
Let me kiss you.
God
is love.
Father, bless me!
Father, I'm sick. Make me well.
Father, touch me!
Oh, Father.
Certain ladies,
and I use the term loosely
have arranged a club whereby
they take turns in his bed.
He says it will put them
closer to God.
Princess Marisa Ivanovna,
your own cousin!
People say that Tsarina knows peace
only with her head on his shoulders.
This man is doing more
damage to the dynasty
than a hundred
revolutionaries ever could.
Why do you need him?
If the Tsarevich—
The Tsarevich has nothing
to do with it.
It's all over the city.
I love my country.
And I love of you.
But this man must go.
Enough is enough.
Nicky, don't you see? God is
testing us to see if we are worthy!
Alex, this man is
a danger to Russia!
Oh!
Look... at this.
I'm sorry, Alex.
He is a danger to me and to you
and to Alexei.
Nicky,
you do this and you
are spitting at God.
And God well forgive me.
But I never will!
-
#
Hey.
--
If you won't be decent,
then I have to ask you to leave.
Me?
Yes.
The Empress kisses my hand!
I am her saviour!
And her angel!
I am the Empresses nephew!
Very pretty
but I prefer
women.
Are you saying
you sleep with the Empress?
I am
a great man!
A great.
Big.
Man.
His Majesty will see you now.
I can't be hypnotised,
so don't bother.
Do you realise
what you have done to my family?
All my life I've had nothing.
Now I have too much.
But I never hurt anyone, Papa.
You have hurt me!
Everything I do, I think of God.
I dread to imagine
what He might think of you.
You are ordered to leave
St. Petersburg in 24 hours.
I want to stay here!
There are thieves
all around you, Papa.
They want to rob me of your love!
Did -- come for our country, Papa?
We will all drown in blood.
Oceans of tears, oceans of blood.
Millions will die here.
These are not my words.
Leave, or you'll be arrested.
Death is behind him.
There it is! You see it?
It will have him within a month!
This is enough!
There is more than just God, Papa.
I am nothing and everything
but I have seen the infinite!
I walk with Pan, with Eros,
with Brahma,
with Vishnu, with Isis,
with Ansher and Belial.
Why was I chosen?
I don't know!
But I am Russia!
I have taken your pain!
I have your pain!
--
Alex?
You are not alone.
I love you.
Where is he?
Prime Minister.
Serge.
I apologise your Majesty
but the heir to the Austrian Empire
has been assassinated.
Assassinated?
By a Serb.
In Sarajevo.
The Austrians will
probably invade Serbia.
We cannot be indifferent to
the fate of our Serbian allies.
Make that clear to the Austrians.
But if we threaten the Austrians they
will ask the German Kaiser to threaten us.
Does he really?
He would never agree to go to war
against Russia. Against me.
I shall ask him to
persuade the Austrians
to calm down.
And if he refuses?
I think Your Majesty should put our
forces on the war footing immediately.
I am not prepared to send
hundreds of thousands
of Russian soldiers to their deaths.
It may not come to that.
But your cousin has
long dreamt of war,
now he has an excuse.
That was behind him
just as Father Grigori had said.
What Papa feared the most, happened.
Germany, Mama's own country,
became our enemy.
"Oceans of tears,
"oceans of blood"
Father Grigori said.
We would all drown.
110,000 people killed in
the battle of Tannenberg.
the battle of Tannenberg...
Your Majesty, how can you
take control of the army?
Your only training
is as a cavalry officer.
How can you run both the
army and the government?
All military and political blame
will be aimed directly at you.
Your Majesty,
the unrest in our streets
is as alarming and as dangerous now,
as the problems at the front.
Your Majesty, you must
stay in St Petersburg.
Dear Holy Mother,
I'm so afraid,
please send us Father Grigori.
Papa needs him
and I need him, too.
Father Grigori!
Ohh!
--
-
...hear every word.
If you do not,
have no fear.
God has seen your tears
and heard your prayers.
It doesn't hurt
anymore,
does it?
Watch the pain
go away
like a white turtledove.
There. See it fly out the window?
It's all gone.
Now go to sleep.
My boy,
sleep.
Sleep.
How is he?
Father Grigori has healed him.
- But I thought he was in Siberia.
- Yes.
I spat at God once.
Never again.
I know that all have
desired more of you.
Even the most faithful.
You are the Tsar,
the father of the people.
Do not let the fools triumph.
Do not let them throw
themselves and us
into the abyss.
My precious darling,
I arrived at headquarters
on Tuesday morning.
The situation is worse
than imaginable.
Our men are facing
German machine guns
with sticks in their hands.
They wait for their
fellow soldiers to die
so that they can have a gun.
As to the revolutionaries at home,
I say drown them all.
How I wish Stolypin was still with us.
The Germans have
already struck at Riga,
while others marched
towards Galicia.
My generals and I cannot agree,
unfair to commit our forces.
We could go north, towards Riga,
but it's already winter
and that alone should prevent
the Germans from settling in.
South is vulnerable,
especially Galicia.
Should we move north or south?
Father?
North.
"Father Grigori
"begs you
"to order an advance
"towards Riga."
It was seen in the night.
"This message
"is prompted
"by what he saw
"in the night."
--
Two million Russians have
already died at the front!
With the help of this Siberian madman!
The Tsarina runs our children into ruin!
How much longer
do we allow these bloodthirsty...
to spit in our faces.
Have I done the right thing?
Send me a sign...
please.
Mama!
The Holy Mother won't answer my prayers.
She’s turned Her back on me. Help me!
I'm so scared.
When did you last see Her?
Weeks.
Here's to traitors!
Down with bloody Nicholas!
And the German bitch!
-
--
Do we not as Russians have a duty to...
to shut off our monastery
before she ruins --
dynasty
and all of Russia!
We can no longer stand by
as this man of God
defiles our nation!
If the name of the Tsar
means anything to you!
If you hope to save Russia
from the revolutionaries
who threaten her,
then Grigori Rasputin
must be stopped!
Hear, hear!
--
I'll do anything to stop him.
For my country.
Did you see the vision?
Don't lie.
I saw Her.
She gave me my power.
How else could I have
known about the boy?
Did you see the vision?
I swear!
In your mind or before your eyes?
- It's the same.
- Don't you know the difference?
I saw her, that's all that counts!
Say where you saw her?
Say it!
I'm not mad!
Where did you see her?
It's the same!
Answer!
Here.
But look what I've done for you!
Oh, look indeed.
I saw Her!
She came to me!
I have magic!
From the devil!
Mama,
look at me, please!
Mama!
I...
leave
this
behind
What?
I'm sorry to bother you at this hour,
this is Prince Felix Yusupov.
My wife Irina is very ill and she
asks if you'll come and see her.
No.
Please, Father, I beg you.
I can't.
You won't say no
to the niece of the Tsar?
I will come in 3 days.
But she leaves for Crimea
in the morning.
I'll send a motor.
Father?
Then do it.
How many does he have to eat?
One of these cakes
will kill him instantly.
I'm so glad you could come.
This is my parents domain,
my rooms are in the basement.
Irina is entertaining some friends,
they will --
- I thought she was dying.
- She is, from a headache.
What do you drink?
- Madeira.
- Ah.
We have some from
our very own vineyard.
To Russia.
No.
More wine.
What are you gaping at?
So, where is she?
I'll be right back.
Is he dead?
I can't understand it.
- Did he eat one?
- He ate three!
Pure cyanide.
I swear.
In his wine.
All of it?
Go.
#
Bravo.
I know a brothel that has
only gypsies. We'll go there.
With God in mind
and mankind in the flesh.
I can taste the barrel.
I'm going.
But... Irina is coming.
She's coming, she's coming.
Maybe she flew by and I missed her.
She leaves in the morning,
she'll be gone for 6 months.
Then get me some more Madeira.
It's upstairs.
# Die, die, we're all going to die #
Maybe... he is holy!
It's impossible.
He drank it all?
He's dancing.
Let him go then.
He can't leave this house alive!
#
This cabinet is beautiful.
Can I take it?
He's dead.
Get the bag.
Are you crazy!
Get some air!
--
Shoot him!
Kill him!
The pain.
It's over.
I leave this behind
because I will soon die.
Know that if I am killed
by my brother peasants
then you have nothing to fear.
But if I am murdered by nobles
if your relatives cause my death,
then no one
not you or your children
will remain alive
for more than 2 years.
You will all be killed
by the Russian people.
Your friend,
Grigori.
Yes?
Excuse me, your Majesty,
but they just found the body.
Who did it?
We're holding Vladimir Purishkevich,
vice-president of the Duma.
As well as Prince Felix Yussoupov.
I'm so sorry.
Your own family.
From that day on,
Mama never smiled again.
We buried Father Grigori
in a secret place near the palace.
His murderers were exiled.
Mama said they were
not punished hard enough
for what they had done to us.
They took away
the only friend we had.
-
Please, don't.
Papa said what is given by God
cannot be taken away by man.
Why was God looking away
when Papa had to give up the throne?
-
Go with me.
This way.
-
Pick them up.
We're all going to die.
They killed Aunt Ella,
Uncle Serge, Igor,
Constantine, Oleg.
All our relatives
who could not escape.
The new rulers made us prisoners
in a house in Siberia.
Today it is 18 months
since Father Grigori died.
Mama.
Don't be scared.
I'm not scared, Mama.
Then I won't be.
Trust in God.
I trust you.
I made so many mistakes.
I'm so sorry.
You always love me
more than anyone.
I'll always love you
Sometimes,
you don't know where
to look for answers.
Sometimes,
you don't know what to believe.
Do you remember the chestnut tree?
The fishermen?
With their oars.
And how I never, ever wanted to leave.
Get ready!
In here.
We're going to take your picture.
Why?
There are rumours in Moscow
which say that you are all dead.
All there.
Can we at least have some chairs?
Chairs.
For crimes against Russia,
the Ural Soviet has hereby
sentenced you to death.
Your life is finished.
What?
Sometimes we have to
believe in something.
believe in magic.
Is the pain gone?
Yes.