( indistinct chatter )
GOOD EVENING, MA'AM.
( elevator bell dings )
( indistinct chatter )
HEY, JIMMY RAY, WHAT'S UP,
MAN? YOU GOT SOME SMOKES?
YEAH, I GOT SOME SMOKES.
YOU GOT THE LAUNDRY TRUCK
SET UP FOR ME?
AROUND BACK.
I GOT DANKER RIGHT
IN FRONT OF ME.
NO, ATLANTA.
DID YOU SEE THAT GUY
IN THE CAR, MAN?
MAKE SURE HE DOESN'T
FOLLOW ME.
YEAH, SURE.
YOU GOT IT.
( coughs )
HEY, WHAT'S UP, MAN?
YOU GOT A WARRANT?
I'M TELLIN' YOU GUYS.
I'LL CUT YOU, MAN!
YOU SON OF A--
YOU'RE PICKING ON
THE WRONG GUY.
FBI.
WE'RE COOL. WE'RE COOL.
( chuckles )
( wind whistling )
STUPID SONS OF BITCHES.
( muttering )
AHH!
OHH!
UHH!
YOU SURE THIS'LL WORK?
I TOLD YOU, THEY DESIGNED
THIS NEW SYSTEM FOR QUICK
ACCESS, IN CASE OF EMERGENCIES.
I CUT THIS ALARM,
AND WE ARE HOME FREE.
( beep )
HOW'D IT GO?
JUST LIKE YOU SAID.
HEY.
THIS IS MY BROTHER.
YOU'RE A GENIUS, BOB.
IT WAS SO SIMPLE. WE JUST--
GET IN THE VAN.
DAMN! WE DID IT!
WE REALLY DID IT!
MARCY, I LOVE YOU.
I FEEL SO LUCKY--
ENOUGH OF THAT.
I SAID ENOUGH.
HEY.  JIMMY.
WHAT? YOU NEVER SEEN ANYBODY
KISS YOUR SISTER BEFORE?
I SAID ENOUGH OF THAT.
WHAT? WHAT?
DID YOU FUCK THIS GUY?
DON'T.
WHAT HAPPENED BACK THERE?
JIMMY, DON'T.
JIMMY? I THOUGHT
HIS NAME WAS BOB.
ANSWER ME, GODDAMNIT!
DID YOU FUCK HIM?!
I DID WHAT YOU TOLD ME TO DO.
I MADE HIM FALL IN LOVE
WITH ME.
WHAT?!
YOU'RE NOT MARCY'S BROTHER?
NO.
STOP IT.
NO!!!
AND HER NAME IS NOT MARCY.
STOP IT!
UHH! UHH!
STOP IT! JUST STOP IT!
THIS IS YOUR FAULT.
I TOLD YOU I'D KILL ANYONE
THAT TOUCHED YOU!
( "Marcy" whimpering )
STUPID...
( gears grind )
I'M SORRY, HONEY.
I REALLY AM.
I JUST LOVE YOU SO MUCH.
I CAN'T STAND TO THINK OF
THAT PUNK TOUCHING YOU.
DON'T TURN AWAY FROM ME, HONEY.
PLEASE.
I CAN'T LIVE WITHOUT YOU.
DON'T EVER, EVER LEAVE ME.
PLEASE.
PLEASE...PLEASE DON'T.
STOP IT.
MAKE LOVE TO ME.
OH!
SAY "JIMMY RAY."
JIMMY RAY.
SAY, "JIMMY RAY, I LOVE YOU."
JIMMY RAY, I LOVE YOU.
I LOVE YOU TOO, BABY.
YOU WON'T EVER LEAVE ME.
I LOVE YOU.
FBI Agent: I WENT TO ATLANTA
TO NAIL HIM. I KNEW HE WAS
GOING THERE ON A JOB.
YOU WERE DOWN THERE
ON VACATION.
YOU REPRESENTED YOURSELF IN
AN OFFICIAL CAPACITY.
UNOFFICIALLY.
THAT'S THE WRONG ANSWER.
I READ YOUR REPORT.
IT'S LUNACY. NEXT?
AW, COME ON, JACK.
THE BASTARD'S RICH NOW.
HE'S TURNED THIS STOLEN MONEY
INTO REAL ESTATE; HE'S SO LEGIT
HE EVEN PAYS TAXES!
SO? THE MAN'S A PATRIOT.
HE MIGHT NOT PULL
ANOTHER JOB!
I'VE WAITED 15 MONTHS FOR
ATLANTA. IF I DON'T SMOKE HIM
OUT NOW, I MAY NEVER GET HIM.
YOU'RE TAKING THIS
VERY PERSONALLY.
WHAT'S YOUR OBSESSION
WITH THIS GUY?
ENLIGHTEN ME.
HE'S BEATEN ME TWICE.
HE'S PLAYING WITH ME NOW.
AND I CAN'T PROVE SHIT.
DOES THAT SOUND LIKE SOMEONE
WHO'S OBSESSED?
( both laugh )
OPEN THE DOOR! STEP THROUGH!
EVEN WITH THE AUTHORIZED
RELEASE FROM THE COURTS,
THIS HAS TO BE STRICTLY
VOLUNTARY ON THE PART
OF THE PRISONER.
GEE, YOU THINK HE'LL CHOOSE
TO STAY HERE?
COME ON, MAN.
MAKE THAT GOODBYE MOVE.
IT'S OVER.
( chatter, laughter )
CHECK.
All: OH, YEAH!
( enthused chatter )
WILL YOU DUMB SCHOOLGIRLS
SHUT UP?
( chatter stops )
YOU LEFT YOUR QUEEN
UNPROTECTED.
( laughter )
( chatter )
THAT AIN'T NO WAY
TO TREAT A LADY.
CHECK.
SCOLD HIM! SCOLD HIM!
YOU KNOW, HISTORICALLY,
ALL THE GREAT MILITARY CAMPAIGNS
WERE WON ON PAPER BEFORE
A SHOT WAS EVER FIRED.
NOW, TAKE ROBERT E. LEE,
A MASTER STRATEGIST.
WHO GIVES A SHIT?
YOU IN CHECK, MAN.
IT'S YOUR MOVE.
( laughter )
JUST TRYING TO GIVE YOU
AN EDUCATION, BIGGS.
NOW, FOR HIS VICTORY AT
FREDERICKSBURG, HE HAD
ANTICIPATED HIS OPPONENT'S
EVERY MOVE, SO WAS ABLE TO APPLY
THE APPROPRIATE COUNTERMOVE.
SUCH AS...
CHECKMATE.
( chatter, laughter )
THE KING IS DEAD!
LONG LIVE THE KING!
WHOO-HOO!
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
GRUDGE MATCH, SIR.
( all shouting )
COOL IT, ASSHOLE!
HE STARTED IT!
COME ON!
I'M ALL RIGHT.
HE DIDN'T HURT ME.
( shouting )
THAT'S YOUR MAN. COOPER.
AHHH.
YOUR HIGHNESS.
OR WOULD YOU PREFER
YOUR MAJESTY?
ACTUALLY, WE PREFER
"YOUR ROYAL MAJESTY."
PLEASE, BE SEATED.
HA HA HA HA!
A MAN AFTER MY HEART,
A REGULAR WISE-ASS.
IT'S ONLY BECAUSE I'M SO
HAPPY TO BE HERE.
IF YOU WEREN'T SUCH A HOTHEAD
YOU'D BE OUT OF HERE BY NOW.
IF I WERE DOING TWELVE-TO-TWENTY
FOR ARMED ROBBERY, I WOULDN'T
BE PUNCHING GUARDS AROUND.
I'D SAY YOU'RE GONNA DIE
IN THIS LOVELY LITTLE ROOM.
WELL, I'LL TELL YA,
THE WAY I LOOK AT IT,
WITH GOOD BEHAVIOR
I COULD BE OUT IN THIRTY YEARS.
WELL, I'M YOUR FAIRY
GODMOTHER.
I WOULDN'T SAY THAT
TOO LOUD IN HERE.
THE WARDEN TOLD YOU MY PLAN?
YEAH. YOU WANT ME TO FLY
TO DENVER TO SET UP JIMMY RAY
IN EXCHANGE FOR PAROLE.
WELL, IF YOU DON'T
SCREW IT UP.
YOU'RE THE CLOSEST THING TO
A FRIEND OF JIMMY RAY'S
I COULD FIND.
YOU HAVE ANY TROUBLE CROSSING
AN OLD CELLMATE?
JIMMY RAY IS A PSYCHOPATH.
YOU SAVED HIS LIFE IN HERE.
WHY?
WAIT A MINUTE.
IF SOME GUY WANTS TO TAKE
THE HIGH HARD ONE UP THE
KEISTER, THAT'S FINE WITH ME
SO LONG AS IT'S HIS IDEA.
BUT FIVE-ON-ONE WAS NOT HIS
IDEA; THEY WERE GONNA RAPE HIM
OR KILL HIM.
YOU'RE A MORAL CRUSADER?
NO. NO, I AM WHAT IS KNOWN
AS A FUCKING IDIOT.
BECAUSE A WEEK LATER, THE
LAUNDRY ROOM SOMEHOW CAUGHT
ON FIRE AND SOME FRIENDS OF MINE
GOT BURNED. MAYBE IF I HADN'T--
DO WE HAVE A DEAL?
HERE'S THE SET-UP.
IF YOU CROSS ME AND RUN, I WILL
DEVOTE MY LIFE TO FINDING YOU
AND BLOWING YOUR HEAD OFF.
I'M NOT GONNA RUN, OSCAR.
YOU HAVE MY WORD.
IS THIS KIND OF A PERSONAL
THING WITH YOU AND JIMMY RAY?
JUST DOIN' MY JOB.
UH-HUH. WELL, YOU'RE THE
EXPERT HERE, BUT YOU THINK HE
MIGHT BE SUSPICIOUS WHEN I GREET
HIM WEARING HANDCUFFS?
FUNNY. NOW, THERE'S AN EXTRA
LITTLE WRINKLE HERE.
JIMMY RAY HAS GOT A GIRLFRIEND,
A FORMER DANCER, REAL PRETTY.
MONEY'LL BUY THAT.
NOW LISTEN TO ME.
SHE'S UNBALANCED.
SHE HAD ONE OF THOSE
NIGHTMARE CHILDHOODS.
SHE'S DANGEROUS,
YOU'RE VULNERABLE.
YOU'RE GOING IN THERE
TO GET JIMMY RAY--
JUST CONCENTRATE ON HIM.
YOU FOLLOW?
ONE MORE.
YA FUCKIN' PRICK.
YOU DIRTY DOG.
PUT 'EM ON DOWN, JIMMY.
( approving chatter )
HEY, TAKE IT SLOW, MAN.
YEAH! JIMMY RAY!
OH, YEAH! JIMMY RAY!
MY MAN JIMMY! WHOO!
GO, J.R.
JIMMY RAY!
YOU AIN'T STUPID ENOUGH
TO BE HUSTLING ME, ARE YA?
WHOO.
YOU CALLIN' ME A HUSTLER?
THAT'S RIGHT, ASS-WIPE.
HE AIN'T A HUSTLER.
YOU JUST STINK.
AND WHO THE FUCK ARE YOU?
I'M THE BILLIARDS POLICE.
YOU KNOW, IT'S ALWAYS THE WORST
STICKMEN THAT WILL CALL SOMEONE
A HUSTLER.
I'LL PUT THIS STICK
UP YOUR ASS, MARY JANE.
NO SHIT?  HEY, TINY.
OHH!
UHH!
HEY, DOUG, GIMME THAT BEER.
( choking )
T.C. TEDDY COOPER.
JIMMY RAY.
SON OF A BITCH, HUH?
WHAT ARE YOU  DOING HERE?
AH, I WAS CRUISING AROUND,
STOPPED IN DENVER, THOUGHT
I'D SEE PIKE'S PEAK.
YOU KNOW.
PIKE'S PEAK?
HOW COME THEY LET YOU OUT?
I LET THE WARDEN BLOW ME.
( both laugh )
WELL, I CAN'T SAY I MISSED
YOU, BUT IT SURE IS
GOOD TO SEE YOU.
WHERE YOU STAYIN'?
I'M NOT REALLY STAYING
ANYWHERE.
WELL, YOU ARE NOW.
GONNA TAKE ME HOME ON
MY NEW HARLEY.
I OWN ALL THE LAND
GOING UP TO THE CREEK.
AND ANOTHER 60 ACRES OF WOODS
OVER THERE.
THERE SHE IS.
HOME SWEET HOME.
IMPRESSIVE, HUH?
EVER SINCE I WAS A KID
EATING DIRT FOR BREAKFAST
I ALWAYS KNEW I'D ONE DAY
OWN A PLACE LIKE THIS.
MY PHILOSOPHY: YOU SEE SOMETHING
YOU WANT, TAKE IT. SIMPLE.
HA HA HA HA!
JULIA!
JULIA?
MR. DANKER.
YOU'RE BACK EARLY.
BEN, UH, MEET T.C.
AN OLD BUDDY OF MINE THAT'S
GONNA BE STAYING WITH US
FOR A FEW DAYS.
HOW DO YOU DO.
HOW YA DOIN', BEN?
PUT HIM UP IN THE GUEST
HOUSE, TAKE HIS THINGS.
AND, UH, CAN YOU  PUT OUT
A JACKET AND SHIRT FOR ME?
I'VE GOT TO GO BACK INTO TOWN.
YES, SIR.  WHERE'S JULIA?
ON HER WAY DOWN, SIR.
NOW YOU ARE ABOUT TO SEE WHY
I AM THE LUCKIEST MAN ALIVE.
JULIA.
REMEMBER I TOLD YOU ABOUT T.C.?
HELLO.
JULIA SOMERS,
LOVE OF MY LIFE...
MEET TEDDY COOPER, THE MAN
WHO SAVED MY LIFE.
NOW... WHY DON'T YOU
CUT THE BULLSHIT
AND TELL ME WHY YOU'RE HERE.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
PIKE'S PEAK MY GRANDMA'S ASS.
I THINK WE SHOULD TALK ABOUT
THIS WHEN WE'RE ALONE, OKAY?
NO. JULIA, SHE'S MY
RIGHT EYE, SHE'S MY LEFT ARM,
SHE'S MY HEART AND SOUL.
YOU CAN SAY ANYTHING YOU WANT
IN FRONT OF HER.
YOU STILL WORKIN', JIM?
UH...
NO, I'VE RETIRED NOW.
BUT YOU CAN TRY AND TEMPT ME.
HOW'S HALF A MILLION
IN DIAMONDS SOUND?
DIAMONDS.
WHERE DO I COME IN?
WHY? YOU'RE RETIRED, MAN.
WELL, MAYBE I'LL MAKE
A COMEBACK.
YOU KNOW, MAYBE I'M JUST
MAKING THIS ALL UP, J.R.
Julia: CAN WE CHANGE
THE SUBJECT?
SHH. NOW, DARLIN',
NOT WHEN I'M TALKIN' BUSINESS.
COME ON.
WE'RE NOT TALKING BUSINESS.
ARE WE?
YOU GOT ANYTHING DECENT
TO WEAR?
I FEEL MORE COMFORTABLE
BEING INDECENT.
I'M GOING TO TAKE YOU
TO A CHARITY EVENT
I'M HOSTING TONIGHT.
YOU'LL BE VERY IMPRESSED.
YOU KNOW, I BEEN THINKIN'...
THE WARDEN WASN'T EXACTLY
YOUR TYPE, SO HOW THE HELL
DID YOU GET OUT OF THERE?
DON'T LIE TO ME.
JIMMY RAY,
I RATTED PEOPLE OUT.
THERE WAS GONNA BE A PRISON
BREAK, I WAS THE WARDEN'S MAN.
NOW, I'M NOT PROUD OF IT,
BUT I'M OUT.
HA HA HA HA!
WELL, I'M PROUD OF YOU.
DIDN'T THINK YOU HAD IT IN YOU.
LISTEN, I'VE GOT TO GO
INTO TOWN TODAY.
SO YOU HANG AROUND THE HOUSE,
USE THE POOL, USE THE SAUNA,
USE ANYTHING YOU WANT...
EXCEPT JULIA.
THIS IS YOURS FOR AS LONG
AS YOU WANT TO STAY.
LITTLE ISOLATED, BUT I GUESS
IT BEATS THE SLAMMER, EH?
( knocks ) HI.
HI.
WOULD YOU LIKE TO GO
FOR A RIDE?
ARE YOU ANY GOOD ON A HORSE?
YEAH, I CAN USUALLY
AVOID FALLING OFF.
GOOD.
PUT YOU ON LIGHTNING.
LIGHTNING?
WHOA! WHOA!
YAHHH!
WHOA. WHOA. WHOA.
Julia: COME ON, PEPPER.
OH, SHIT!
WHOA! OOHHH!
OHH...
OH, GOD. YOU OKAY?
YEAH, I'M OKAY.
I USUALLY DON'T FALL
OFF HORSES... BECAUSE
I DON'T USUALLY GET ON 'EM.
( both laugh )
CATHERINE, COOL 'EM OUT,
OKAY?
YES, MISS SOMERS.
YOU'RE THE GIRL FROM
THE Z.Z. TOP VIDEO
DANCING ON THE BEACH, RIGHT?
OH, MY GOSH. ( laughs )
YEAH.
THAT WAS ME.
IT'S HARD TO BELIEVE.
WHY? DON'T YOU LIKE DANCING?
NO. NOT REALLY.
IF YOU'RE THE LEAST BIT
ATTRACTIVE EVERYONE THINKS
THAT YOU'RE REALLY STUPID.
IT'S NOT LIKE I WAS A SERIOUS
DANCER, A BALLERINA OR ANYTHING,
I JUST WANTED TO GET
AWAY FROM HOME.
TRAVELED ALL OVER.
I'VE BEEN TO EUROPE AND
NEW YORK, L.A.
I EVEN DID A COMMERCIAL--
ONCE. HA HA!
HALF THE TIME I WAS SO
SCREWED UP ON DRUGS I DIDN'T
EVEN KNOW WHERE I WAS.
I USED TO WAKE UP AND NOT KNOW
HOW I GOT THERE.
I WAS HIGH FOR YEARS.
THINGS ARE MUCH BETTER NOW,
THOUGH.
WHAT, YOU MEAN SINCE
YOU MET JIMMY RAY?
OH, YEAH.
HE SAVED ME.
EVEN THOUGH HE BEATS YOU?
LOOK, I KNOW JIMMY RAY,
AND I CAN SEE THE BRUISE,
IT'S RIGHT THERE.
HE IS EXCITABLE, THAT'S ALL.
HE CARES ABOUT ME TOO MUCH.
DO YOU BELIEVE IN REINCARNATION?
I'LL BET YOU DO.
YEAH.
I THINK THAT WE COME BACK HERE
MANY TIMES TO LEARN SOMETHING.
WE TRY TO FIND OUR SOUL MATE.
THEY SAY THAT WHEN YOU SEE
YOUR SOUL MATE...
THAT YOU KNOW HIM RIGHT AWAY...
THAT THE MOMENT YOU SEE HIM,
YOU JUST...YOU JUST KNOW.
( sighs )
YOU KNOW, I'M REALLY JUST HERE
TO STEAL SOME DIAMONDS.
( rock music plays )
HEY, I DON'T SUPPOSE THAT
J.R. STANDS FOR "JIMMY RAY."
HELL, I'D NEVER HAVE NOTICED.
MISS SOMERS, YOU'RE LOOKIN'
LOVELY TONIGHT.
JIMMY RAY, GOOD TO SEE YA.
RIGHT OVER HERE.
( rock music continues )
IT WOULD APPEAR YOU'RE PRETTY
POPULAR AROUND HERE, JIMMY RAY.
I'M JUST AN OLD-FASHIONED
AMERICAN CAPITALIST.
I STOLE MONEY,
AND I INVESTED IT.
NOW I'M RESPECTABLE.
I ALWAYS DREAMED OF OWNING
A CLUB LIKE THIS, T.C.
YOU HAVE NO IDEA HOW IT FEELS
TO HAVE ALL YOUR DREAMS
COME TRUE.
THAT RIGHT, SWEETHEART?
DANCE WITH ME, JIMMY.
WITH A PROFESSIONAL?
NO, THANK YOU.
TEDDY.
YOU WANNA DANCE WITH ME?
( Teddy chuckles )
YOU KNOW HOW SOME GUYS
HAVE TWO LEFT FEET?
I GOT THREE.
HE'S BRAGGING. REMEMBER,
I SAW HIM IN THE SHOWER.
HA HA HA!
COME ON, A NAME.
MEDNIKOW JEWELERS,
BERNEL JEWELERS.
OH, YEAH?
MENDIKOW'S?
BERNEL. YOU COULDA GOT
THOSE NAMES STRAIGHT OUT OF
THE TELEPHONE BOOK.
YEAH, BUT WHO SUPPLIES 'EM?
JIMMY, YOU SAID AFTER THE
LAST TIME WE'D QUIT FOREVER.
ANGEL, YOU JUST LISTEN
TO THE MUSIC.
T.C., ARE WE PLAYING
TWENTY QUESTIONS HERE?
I WANT A NAME.
I WON'T RIP YOU OFF.
THIS IS YOUR GIG,
I RESPECT THAT.
WE'LL GO, UH,
WE'LL GO FIFTY-FIFTY.
IF WE CAN'T TRUST EACH OTHER,
WHO CAN?
CRAWSON'S. KANSAS CITY.
WELL?
WELL, IT'S A NAME.
I'LL THINK ABOUT IT.
Man: JIMMY RAY?
I'M BEING SUMMONED.
YOU'LL HAVE TO EXCUSE ME.
DARLIN', YOU LOOK BEAUTIFUL.
DOESN'T SHE LOOK BEAUTIFUL?
( laughs )
Emcee: HELLO.
( taps microphone )
UH, HELLO. GOOD EVENING!
EVERYBODY HAVING
A GOOD TIME TONIGHT?
Crowd: YEAH! ( cheering )
WELL, I CAN CERTAINLY TELL
HE LOVES YOU.
HE SAID HE'D KILL ME IF
I EVER TRIED TO LEAVE.
HE MEANT IT.
Emcee: ...LEADING CITIZENS,
JAMES RAY DANKER, NOT ONLY
FOR GRACIOUSLY HOSTING THIS
FUNDRAISER TONIGHT, BUT ALSO
FOR DONATING THIS GENEROUS
CHECK OF $10,000!
GIVE IT UP FOR
MR. JAMES RAY DANKER!
I BEEN TRYING TO STAY AWAY
FROM TEQUILA.
THANK YOU, THANK YOU.
THANK YOU KINDLY.
GOOD TO SEE Y'ALL HERE TONIGHT,
BECAUSE IF THERE'S ONE THING
I DO BELIEVE IN, IT'S CHARITY.
ALL I WANT TO HEAR IS THE RUSTLE
OF LARGE DOLLAR BILLS AND CHECKS
IN THIS LITTLE OLD HAT OF MINE.
YOU GONNA GIVE?
Crowd: YEAH!
EVERYBODY SAY YEAH?
Crowd: YEAH!!!
WELL, IN THE MEANTIME,
YOU CAN PARTY ON.
BUT ALWAYS REMEMBER,
JIMMY RAY IS WATCHING.
( crowd cheers )
♪ I GOT A LITTLE CHANGE
♪ IN MY POCKET, GOIN'
♪ JINGLE-INGLE-JINGLE
♪ GONNA CALL YOU ON
♪ THE TELEPHONE, BABY
♪ GIVE YOU A RING
♪ BUT EACH TIME WE TALK
♪ I GET THE SAME OLD THING
♪ ALWAYS NO HUGGY, NO KISSY
♪ UNTIL I GET A WEDDING RING
♪ MY HONEY, MY BABY, DON'T PUT
♪ MY LOVE UP ON NO SHELF, SHE
♪ SAID DON'T GIVE ME NO LINES
♪ AND KEEP YOUR HANDS
♪ TO YOURSELF... ♪
Julia: HE LOVES TO
HUMILIATE ME LIKE THIS.
♪ BABY, BABY, BABY, WHY YOU
♪ GONNA TREAT ME THIS WAY
♪ YOU KNOW I'M STILL YOUR
♪ LOVER BOY, I STILL FEEL
♪ THE SAME WAY, I SAID
♪ SHE TOLD ME A STORY... ♪
YOU SURE YOU WON'T
DANCE WITH ME?
IT'S NOT A GOOD IDEA.
♪ MY HONEY, MY BABY
♪ DON'T PUT MY LOVE ON NO SHELF
♪ SHE SAID DON'T HAND ME
♪ NO LINES, AND KEEP
♪ YOUR HANDS TO YOURSELF ♪
♪ OVER HERE
♪ SEE, I WANTED HER REAL BAD
♪ AND I WAS ABOUT TO GIVE IN
♪ AND THAT'S WHEN SHE STARTED
♪ TALKIN' ABOUT TRUE LOVE
♪ STARTED TALKIN' ABOUT SIN
♪ I SAID, HONEY, I'LL LIVE
♪ WITH YOU FOR THE REST
♪ OF MY LIFE, SHE SAID
♪ NO HUGGY, NO KISSY
♪ UNTIL YOU MAKE ME YOUR WIFE
♪ MY HONEY, MY BABY
♪ DON'T PUT MY LOVE ON NO SHELF
♪ SHE SAID, DON'T HAND ME
♪ NO LINES, AND KEEP YOUR HANDS
♪ TO YOURSELF ♪
HEY.
GET OUT OF THE WAY.
YOU OKAY, MR. DANKER?
NO, I'M NOT OKAY.
WHERE IS THAT BITCH?
YOU STUPID SLUT.
BASTARD.
GET IN THE CAR.
DON'T TOUCH ME, JIMMY.
GET IN THE CAR!!!
HEY, TAKE IT EASY, JIM,
COME ON.
JUST STAY OUT OF IT.
THIS IS BULLSHIT.
WHAT IN THE FUCK DID I DO
TO DESERVE THIS?
JIMMY--
HEY. ( laughs sheepishly )
WAS THAT JUST YOU BACK THERE?
I'D FORGOTTEN HOW GOOD YOU WERE.
I APPRECIATE IT.
THANKS.
I GUESS THAT'S ANOTHER ONE
I OWE YOU.
THEN DO THIS JOB WITH ME,
JIMMY BOY. COME ON.
WELL, I BEEN THINKING
ABOUT IT.
I'VE GOTTA GO TO BOULDER
TOMORROW ON BUSINESS.
I THOUGHT MAYBE I'D GO OVER
TO KANSAS CITY AND CHECK
THE PLACE OUT, IF IT'S
ALL RIGHT WITH YOU.
IF YOU DON'T TRUST ME.
NO, IT'S JUST THE WAY I WORK.
IF I LIKE IT, I'LL DO IT.
THERE'S JUST ONE LITTLE THING.
DO YOU FIND JULIA ATTRACTIVE?
AND...
ARE YOU THINKING OF DOING HER,
MAYBE, WHILE I'M AWAY?
HMM?
YEAH, I FIND HER ATTRACTIVE.
WHO WOULDN'T?
BUT I DON'T EVEN THINK ABOUT
SLEEPING WITH MY FRIEND'S
OLD LADY.
IT'S A GOOD ANSWER.
BECAUSE IF YOU HAD DENIED IT,
THEN I'D HAVE KNOWN YOU
WERE SCHEMING ON HER.
I'M SORRY, MAN.
HAVE YOU EVER BEEN IN LOVE
WITH A WOMAN? I MEAN,
SO IT'S DRIVING YOU
OUT OF YOUR MIND?
NO.
WELL, I CAN TELL YOU,
YOU'RE LUCKY.
I TELL YOU, IT'S HELL ON EARTH.
NOW, YOU KNOW I'VE DONE SOME
BAD THINGS IN MY TIME, T.C.
(sarcastic) NO.
BUT I SWEAR...
I THOUGHT GOD HAD FORGIVEN ME
THE DAY HE SENT ME JULIA.
SHE'S THE FIRST WOMAN I'VE EVER
FELT I COULD SETTLE DOWN WITH.
SEE, ALL THIS...
WOULD BE NOTHING WITHOUT HER.
I DO EVERYTHING FOR HER NOW.
IT'S JUST THAT I'VE GOT
TO PROTECT HER.
BECAUSE, YOU KNOW, SHE GETS
A LITTLE CRAZY HERSELF
SOMETIMES.
WHEN...
WHEN SHE TOUCHES ME...
HER SKIN...
HER HAIR, HER HANDS...
SHE READS MY HAND SOMETIMES.
AND YOU KNOW, I COULD SIT
AND JUST WATCH HER HANDS
ALL DAY.
I GUESS WHAT I'M TRYING TO SAY
TO YOU...IS THAT I...
I VALUE OUR FRIENDSHIP,
I REALLY DO.
BUT IF YOU TOUCH HER...
THANKS FOR LISTENING TO ME.
GET SOME REST.
I'LL BE OUT OF HERE
WHEN YOU GET UP IN THE MORNING.
Oscar: ACT LIKE YOU'RE
TAKING A PISS.
( Teddy sighs )
ANOTHER NIGHT ON THE TOWN
WITH JULIA AND JIMMY RAY.
JIMMY RAY IS
A FUCKIN' ASSHOLE.
BUT DOES HE LIKE DIAMONDS?
TOMORROW HE'S GOING TO
KANSAS CITY TO CHECK ON
CRAWSON'S.
PERFECT. OUR MAN THERE
WILL TELL HIM ALL
HE NEEDS TO KNOW--
ACCIDENTLY.
OSCAR, THOSE ROCKS
BETTER BE REAL.
JIMMY RAY KNOWS HIS DIAMONDS.
I DON'T WANT TO GET SHOT IN THE
HEAD WHEN HE OPENS THAT SACK.
UNLESS THEY'RE REAL,
I CAN'T BUST HIM.
WHAT ELSE DID YOU FIND OUT
TODAY? LIKE ON THE HORSE TRAIL,
FOR INSTANCE.
WHY DO I FEEL LIKE
YOU'RE WATCHING ME, OSCAR?
( chuckles )
SHE'S GETTING TO YOU
ALREADY, HUH?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
JULIA.
SHE'S A BLACK WIDOW SPIDER, MAN.
YOU GET CAUGHT IN HER WEB,
SHE'LL EAT YOU UP.
HOW POETIC.
HAVE I PISSED ENOUGH?
DON'T LET YOUR PECKER
FUCK THIS UP.
I'M WARNING YOU.
I'VE PISSED ENOUGH.
YOU KNOW, OSCAR, I DON'T SEE
WHAT'S SO CRAZY ABOUT JULIA.
YOU MEAN EXCEPT FOR ONE
LITTLE MINOR DETAIL--
SHE LIVES WITH JIMMY RAY.
YEAH?
CAN I COME IN?
YES.
HI.
BEN SAID YOU DIDN'T WANT
ANY BREAKFAST, BUT ROSA MADE
FRESH STRAWBERRY PIE.
I THOUGHT YOU MIGHT LIKE SOME.
THAT'S VERY KIND OF YOU.
YOU WANTED TO KISS ME
YESTERDAY.
I DID.
YES, YOU DID.
I WISH THAT YOU HAD.
YOU'RE WITH JIMMY RAY.
( coughs ) I'M JUST A...
IF YOU DON'T FEEL THE SAME
AS ME, THEN JUST TELL ME NOW
AND I'LL FORGET IT.
YOU BETTER GO.
ARE YOU SURE?
WAIT. WAIT. WHAT--
THIS IS NUTS. WHAT AM I DOING?
WHY AM I DOING THIS?
THIS IS CRAZY!
THIS DOESN'T MAKE ANY SENSE!
BECAUSE THIS FEELS RIGHT.
THIS IS HOW IT'S SUPPOSED
TO FEEL.
OH, TEDDY...
I KNEW YOU'D COME.
AND NOW YOU'RE HERE.
UHH! UHH!
NO.
LOOK AT ME.
LOOK AT ME, LOOK AT ME.
NOT LIKE THIS.
JUST FEEL ME.
I'M HERE FOR YOU.
I'M NOT GOING ANYWHERE.
JUST...JUST FEEL ME.
OH, GOD.
JULIA...
SOMETIMES YOU MAKE ME
FEEL CRAZY.
IT'S LIKE I DON'T KNOW
WHO I AM ANYMORE.
YOU KNOW, A LITTLE
NOURISHMENT IS PROBABLY NOT
A BAD IDEA.
( sighs ) MY GOD.
( starts car )
IT WAS STUPIDITY, REALLY.
YOU KNOW, WHEN I WAS A KID
MY OLD MAN DIED, AND SOMETIMES
I THINK HE DIED JUST TO
GET AWAY FROM MY MOTHER.
BUT ANYWAY, WE WERE POOR,
I WAS ALWAYS BROKE, WORKING
MY WAY THROUGH SCHOOL,
AND I WAS JUST SICK OF
EVERYTHING.
SO I GOT AHOLD OF THESE GUYS
FROM THE OLD NEIGHBORHOOD,
AND THEY HAD A PLAN.
AND LIKE AN IDIOT,
I GET DRUNK,
GET A GUN--
IT WASN'T EVEN LOADED--
I MEAN, IT WAS REALLY STUPID.
MUST BE HORRIBLE TO BE
LOCKED AWAY LIKE THAT.
THE FIRST TWO YEARS,
I DON'T KNOW... BUT I STARTED
TO EDUCATE MYSELF.
I SET GOALS.
THE THIRD YEAR I DECIDED
I'D READ ALL THE RUSSIANS--
CRIME AND PUNISHMENT, OF
COURSE, WAR AND PEACE--
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
I'M BORING YOU, RIGHT?
NO.
I DON'T KNOW.
THIS IS HAPPENING SO FAST.
YOU COULD REALLY HURT ME.
I'LL NEVER HURT YOU, JULIA.
YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND.
I DON'T TRUST PEOPLE.
YOU CAN TRUST ME.
YOU CAN.
YOU KNOW, I HAD TOO MUCH
ICE TEA, I THINK.
EXCUSE ME.
YOU STUPID DUMB-ASS
SON OF A BITCH!
OSCAR, YOU GOT THIS GIRL
ALL WRONG, MAN.
I DO? TELL ME.
SHE'S KIND, SHE'S SWEET,
SHE'S THE NICEST GIRL
I EVER MET. SHE JUST HAS
A LITTLE SELF-DESTRUCT GOING,
THAT ALL.
AND YOU WANT TO HELP HER.
YEAH, I'M GONNA TRY.
YOU ASSHOLE! YOU'RE BEING
TAKEN IN BY THE MAYA!
WHAT THE FUCK ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT, MAYA?
WHAT IS THAT?
THAT'S HINDU-- ILLUSION
IN THE SHAPE OF A WOMAN.
SHE AIN'T WHAT SHE
APPEARS TO BE.
AND WHATEVER SHE'S TELLING YOU,
SHE'S NEVER GONNA LEAVE
JIMMY RAY.
MAYBE I JUST TRUST PEOPLE
MORE THAN YOU DO, OSCAR.
OH, MAN.
HAVEN'T YOU FIGURED IT OUT?
THE WOMAN IS A LIAR.
( runs faucet )
YOU REALLY LIKE THIS
CRYSTAL, HUH?
I MEAN, I GIVE YOU
A $20 NECKLACE, AND YOU ACT
LIKE IT'S A DIAMOND.
IT'S WHAT IT MEANS.
I WANT TO GIVE YOU SOMETHING.
NOT THAT. HA HA!
I ONLY WEAR THIS WHEN I'M ALONE.
CLOSE YOUR EYES.
DON'T LAUGH. I MADE IT
WHEN I WAS LITTLE.
PUT OUT YOUR HAND.
OPEN?
YEAH.
WOW! IT'S AN INDIAN NECKLACE,
HUH?
YEAH.
IT'S KIND OF SILLY.
YOU MADE THAT?
DON'T EVER LEAVE ME.
I NEVER WILL.
JULIA?
OH, MY GOD, HE'S BACK.
Jimmy Ray: YOU UPSTAIRS?
JULIA?
YOU'RE BACK.
YEAH.
HEY, YOU'RE WET.
YEAH, I WAS IN THE BATH.
WHERE'D YOU GET THIS?
OH, UH, IT'S A CRYSTAL.
I BOUGHT IT TODAY.
IT'S SUPPOSED TO BE MAGIC.
UH-HUH.
LET'S GO DOWNSTAIRS.
I'LL MAKE YOU A DRINK.
I'VE HAD TOO MUCH TO DRINK.
COME ON.
YOUR SKIN IS THE ONLY
MAGIC I NEED.
COME ON, LET'S GO.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
COME HERE.
THE WINDOW'S OPEN.
YOU'LL GET YOUR DEATH OF COLD.
( laughs nervously )
( door opens )
WAKE UP, BOY.
JIMMY RAY.
WHEN'D YOU GET BACK, MAN?
COUPLE OF HOURS AGO.
LET'S GET SOME LIGHT ON
IN HERE.
NO, COME ON, MY EYES.
WHAT YOU BEEN DOIN'?
NOT MUCH. YOU KNOW, UH...
READING, JUMPED IN YOUR POOL.
SPEND MUCH TIME WITH JULIA?
YEAH. WE DROVE INTO TOWN.
SHE BOUGHT A DRESS.
I GOT SOME BOOKS.
SO TALK TO ME.
GOT AN ASHTRAY?
HERE. USE THIS.
SO? YOU CHECK OUT MY STORY?
IT'S TRUE.
CRAWSON'S TAKE DELIVERY
FROM GALVESTON.
LOOK, MAN, I DON'T GIVE
A FLYING FUCK WHERE
IT COMES FROM.
I JUST GOT OUT OF JAIL.
I AIN'T GOT NO MONEY,
I GOT NO HOME--
IF THIS DOESN'T HAPPEN,
I'M GONNA BE FLIPPIN' BURGERS
FOR FIVE DOLLARS AN HOUR.
SO WHAT DO YOU SAY, YES OR NO?
I'VE JUST BEEN WONDERING...
HOW DID YOU FIND OUT ABOUT THIS?
( chuckles )
THAT MY SECRET, JIMMY BOY.
HEY, LOOK, I'LL TELL YA.
BIG DEAL. A LIFER GAVE IT TO ME.
PART OF MY END GOES TO
HIS OLD LADY.
BUT LOOK, MAN, IT'S GOING DOWN
THE DAY AFTER TOMORROW.
YOU GOTTA TELL ME YES OR NO.
WELL...
IT'S NOT BECAUSE I NEED
THE MONEY...
BUT WHEN ALL IS SAID AND DONE,
DIAMONDS ARE A GIRL'S
BEST FRIEND.
( laughs )
SO...
WHAT'S THE PLAN?
RIGHT THERE.
I CAN'T READ THIS
WITHOUT A LIGHT.
( paper rustling )
I'M IMPRESSED.
LOOK AT THAT.
YOU GOT YOUR MAP, SCHEDULE,
ALL RIGHT THERE.
YOU ALWAYS WERE
A CLEVER BOY, T.C.
THIS IS ONE OF YOUR CHESS GAMES.
LET'S HOPE IT MAKES US
SOME MONEY...PARTNER.
( door opens )
( Jimmy Ray sighs )
YOU AND T.C. HAVE FUN
IN TOWN TODAY?
UH, YEAH, I-I GOT A DRESS,
AND HE WANTED TO GET
SOME BOOKS OR SOMETHING.
WHAT HAPPENED THEN?
WHAT, ARE YOU INTERROGATING
ME OR SOMETHING? IS THAT IT?
NOW, DON'T LIE TO ME.
DON'T YOU LIE TO ME.
DID YOU PULL YOUR LITTLE
PRICK TEASE ACT AGAIN TODAY?
YOU'RE HURTING ME.
I WAS NICE TO HIM
BECAUSE HE'S YOUR FRIEND.
WELL, HE'S LYING TO ME.
LYING?
YEAH.
ABOUT ALL OF THIS.
IT'S...
IT'S TOO EASY.
SUDDENLY HE'S FREE.
THEN HE'S GOT A PLAN.
I DON'T TRUST HIM.
TEDDY?
WHERE DO YOU THINK I MET HIM?
AT A COUNTRY CLUB?
HE'S A CON.
AND WE'D SAY AND WE'D DO
ANYTHING TO SURVIVE.
I KNOW HE'S GOT A HARD-ON
FOR YOU A MILE LONG.
WHAT IS THAT SUPPOSED
TO MEAN?
( chuckles )
IT MEANS HE WANTS
YOUR LITTLE TRIANGLE.
WHAT DO YOU THINK IT MEANS?
CAN'T SAY I BLAME HIM.
CAN'T SAY I BLAME HIM AT ALL.
HE'S BEEN INSIDE SO LONG,
YOU KNOW, HONEY, HE'D FUCK
A RATTLESNAKE NOW IF HE COULD
FIND SOMEONE TO HOLD ITS MOUTH
OPEN LONG ENOUGH.
YOU'RE DISGUSTING,
YOU KNOW THAT?
( chuckles )
HA HA HA!
NOW, GIRL, I WANT YOU, TOMORROW,
TO FIND OUT WHAT HE'S UP TO.
I WANT YOU TO TALK TO HIM.
MY VIBRATION'S TELLING ME
THAT HE'S LYING.
WHAT'S THE MATTER WITH YOU,
HONEY?
DID YOU HURT YOUR BACK?
YEAH, RIDING PEPPER TODAY.
I PULLED SOMETHING.
HEY, YOU SHOULD HAVE TOLD ME.
I'LL BE GENTLE WITH YOU.
HEY.
WHEW. YOU LOOK BEAUTIFUL.
DOESN'T SHE LOOK BEAUTIFUL?
YEAH.
I'VE GOT BAD NEWS
FOR BOTH OF YOU.
WOULDN'T YOU KNOW, I'VE GOT
TO VISIT A TAX LAWYER
THIS AFTERNOON.
SO JULIA, YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO
ENTERTAIN OUR BOY HERE
ALL ALONE ON HIS LAST DAY
BEFORE HE LEAVES US.
SHOW HIM A GOOD TIME.
OKAY?
OKAY.
DON'T LET ME DOWN.
( Jimmy's car starts )
HOW CONVENIENT FOR HIM
TO LEAVE US ALONE.
YOU'RE LEAVING TOMORROW.
WHERE?
TORONTO.
THANK YOU FOR TELLING ME.
YOU'RE COMING WITH ME.
HOW? WHAT ARE WE DOING?
I DON'T KNOW ANYTHING THAT'S
GOING ON HERE.
JULIA, YOU'RE LEAVING THAT
MANIAC AND COMING AWAY
WITH ME TOMORROW.
WHAT ELSE DO YOU NEED TO KNOW?
I REALLY WISH THAT I COULD
BELIEVE THAT YOU WERE
TELLING ME THE TRUTH.
ABOUT WHAT?
ABOUT EVERYTHING.
OKAY, TOMORROW I'M GONNA
LEAVE YOU A MAP OF WHERE
WE'RE GONNA MEET. OKAY?
NOW, YOU KNOW YOU CAN
TRUST ME, JULIA, YOU KNOW--
NO, NO, I DON'T.
I DON'T KNOW THAT.
IF THERE'S SOMETHING THAT I NEED
TO KNOW, YOU HAVE TO TELL ME.
I'M SO CONFUSED. I--
DON'T! DON'T!
DON'T.
I LOVE YOU, JULIA.
I LOVE YOU SO MUCH.
OH...
COME ON.
( car drives away )
ARE YOU SURE YOU WANT
ANOTHER DRINK?
OH YEAH.
OKAY.
MISS, COULD I GET ANOTHER
MARGARITA, PLEASE?
No tequila.
SURE.
WHAT DID YOU JUST
SAY TO HER?
NOTHING, I ORDERED
ANOTHER DRINK.
DO YOU THINK SHE'S CUTE?
WH-WHAT?
WELL, YOU WERE LOOKING
AT HER ASS SO MUCH, I THOUGHT
MAYBE THAT YOU LIKED HER ASS.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING
ABOUT, JULIA?
I WANT TO MAKE LOVE
WITH YOU...NOW.
LET'S GET A MOTEL OR SOMETHING.
I'LL GET THE CHECK.
Waitress: MAY I TAKE
YOUR ORDER?
CAN I GET THE BILL, PLEASE?
EXCUSE ME A MOMENT.
THERE'S TWENTY, OKAY?
NOW, YOU COME BACK.
YEAH, RIGHT.
COME ON, BABE, WAIT UP!
JULIA, COME ON! THE GIRL
WOULDN'T LET GO OFF MY HAND--
DON'T TOUCH ME.
YOU THINK I'M GONNA JUST
STAND THERE AND LET YOU
MAKE A FOOL OUT OF ME?
WHAT'S GOING ON? COME ON.
YOU'RE LIKE EVERY OTHER MAN.
I THOUGHT YOU WERE DIFFERENT!
JULIA, WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
YOU WANT TO HIT ON THAT
LITTLE TRAMP IN FRONT OF ME,
THAT'S FINE! I DON'T CARE!
JULIA, THIS IS CRAZY!
THIS IS NUTS!
DON'T CALL ME NUTS!
GODDAMNIT, THE GIRL GRABBED
MY HAND, SHE WOULDN'T LET GO!
THAT'S ALL THAT HAPPENED!
YES, AND YOU ACTED LIKE
THE SCUM OF THE EARTH!
WHAT DID YOU CALL ME, HUH?
WHAT DID YOU CALL ME?!
THE SCUM OF THE EARTH!
HOW COULD YOU CALL ME THAT,
HUH? WHAT ABOUT JIMMY RAY, HUH?
DON'T HIT ME, OKAY?
JULIA, I'M NOT GONNA HIT YOU.
I'M NOT GONNA HIT YOU.
I LOVE YOU. I JUST DON'T
UNDERSTAND WHAT'S GOING ON
IN YOUR MIND.
JUST LEAVE ME ALONE.
YOU GOT IT?
YOU LEAVE ME...
YOU LEAVE ME ALONE.
I DON'T BELIEVE THIS. JULIA!
HAPPY NOW?
LIE DOWN WITH DOGS
AND GET UP WITH FLEAS.
NOT NOW, OSCAR.
YOU DON'T LIKE THAT CLICHE?
I GOT OTHERS.
ARE YOU GONNA BLOW THIS THING
OVER SOMETHING YOU DON'T
UNDERSTAND? I WARNED YOU.
AND NOW YOU'RE MESSING
WITH MY LIFE.
OSCAR, YOU DON'T KNOW
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE.
THERE'S A REAL DARKNESS
IN YOU, ISN'T THERE?
YOU'RE ATTRACTED TO THE DARK.
I WARNED YOU, BUT HERE YOU ARE--
A BRAINLESS BUG FLYING HAPPILY
INTO THE WEB, BECAUSE YOU...
LIKE IT ON THE DARK SIDE!
YOU ARE CRAZY, OSCAR,
YOU KNOW THAT? YOU ARE SICK.
IF TOMORROW GOES RIGHT,
YOU'RE FREE.
BUT IF YOU FUCK THIS UP
OVER HER...
I WON'T PUT YOU BACK IN JAIL.
YOU UNDERSTAND ME?
JULIA TOLD ME YOU WERE
COMING ON TO HER!
ARE YOU IN LOVE WITH HER?
OHH!
YOU SON OF A BITCH.
I KNEW YOU WERE LYING TO ME!
HA HA HA! BUT I NEVER THOUGHT
IT COULD BE ABOUT JULIA.
AHHH!
YOU KNOW SOMETHING?
WOMEN BEATERS SCARE ME.
GIRLFRIEND GETS A LITTLE
CONFUSED SOMETIMES, HUH?
FUCKIN' ASSHOLE.
FUCKING ASSHOLE.
( chuckles )
SHE'S MINE!
UNDERSTAND? MINE!
REMEMBER THAT, BOY.
JUST REMEMBER THAT. MINE!
( laughs )
SEE YA IN THE MORNIN'.
( door opens )
JULIA, WHAT--
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
TEDDY, JUST HOLD ME, PLEASE.
DO YOU HATE ME? I COULDN'T
LIVE IF YOU HATED ME.
I DON'T HATE YOU,
BUT THIS CANNOT BE SAFE.
DON'T MAKE ME GO.
HE'S ASLEEP. PLEASE, I KNOW
THAT I CAN'T LIVE WITHOUT YOU.
JIMMY TOLD ME THAT YOU JUST
WANTED TO FUCK ME.
JULIA, THAT SON OF A BITCH
HAD A GUN TO MY HEAD
AT THE TIME. COME ON.
OH, MY GOD.
OH, GOD, I COULD HAVE LOST YOU.
(crying) I'M SORRY.
IT'S OKAY.
DO YOU FORGIVE ME?
YEAH, I FORGIVE YOU. YEAH.
YOU DO?
OH, BABE.
COME HERE.
YOU'VE NEVER HAD ANYBODY WHO
LOVED YOU AND CARED FOR YOU
THE WAY I DO, BABY.
YEAH.
BUT I DO.
I REALLY DO.
IT'S SUCH A STRANGE THING
THAT'S GOING ON.
A WEEK AGO I DIDN'T EVEN KNOW
YOU WERE ALIVE, AND NOW I DON'T
THINK I COULD EVER LIVE
WITHOUT YOU.
LET'S JUST RUN AWAY FROM
HERE, LET'S JUST GO.
HE'S ASLEEP, LET'S JUST
GO RIGHT NOW.
I CAN'T.
WHY? YOU DON'T HAVE TO GO
THROUGH WITH THIS ROBBERY.
YES, I HAVE TO.
WHY? I DON'T UNDERSTAND!
SHH! SHH! QUIET!
LISTEN TO ME. YOU WANT TO KNOW
WHY I HAVE TO DO THIS?
BECAUSE THE FBI GOT ME
OUT OF JAIL!
THIS WHOLE ROBBERY
IS A SET-UP!
HE'S GONNA GET BUSTED TOMORROW.
THE FBI WILL WANT ME, TOO.
I DID A TERRIBLE THING.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
I DID A REALLY BAD THING.
DON'T WORRY. YOU AND I
ARE GONNA DISAPPEAR, BABY.
IS IT OSCAR?
HOW DO YOU KNOW OSCAR?
HE'S BEEN AFTER JIMMY RAY
SINCE I MET HIM.
RIGHT. LISTEN,
IT DOESN'T MATTER. NOW, THIS
IS WHAT'S GONNA HAPPEN....
WHERE WERE YOU?
WITH TEDDY.
AND?
AND I FOUND OUT
WHAT YOU WANTED.
YOU CAN'T GO THROUGH WITH THIS,
JIMMY.
HE'S WORKING FOR THE FBI.
THEY'RE GONNA COME
ARREST US TOMORROW.
GOD IN HEAVEN.
I KNEW HE WAS LYING TO ME.
YOU PROMISE ME, JIMMY.
YOU CAN'T GO THROUGH WITH THIS.
YOU GOTTA KEEP ME SAFE.
OH, I'M GONNA GO THROUGH
WITH IT ALL RIGHT, HONEY.
I'M GONNA GO THROUGH WITH IT.
JIMMY, IT'S THE FBI.
YOU THINK I'M SCARED
OF THEM?
( laughs )
WELL DONE.
GOOD WORK.
Jimmy Ray (distant):
YOU FUCKING TOLD ME, MAN.
YOU FUCKIN' LIED TO ME!
YOU DID! KANSAS CITY!
IT'S NOT GOING DOWN THE WAY
I TOLD YOU IT WAS. FORGET IT!
JULIA TOLD ME. YEAH.
T.C. IS WORKING FOR THE FBI.
( Jimmy continues, indistinct )
( door slams in distance )
( gasps )
OH, GOD, TEDDY.
YOU'RE EARLY, MAN.
( chuckles )
LET'S GO.
WHICH DOOR IS IT?
THE TOP OF THE STAIRS.
LOCK UP ALL EXITS.
THEY'RE ON THE ROOF.
Teddy: RIGHT ON TIME.
YOU KNOW WHAT TO DO?
YEAH.
SAM. CAN YOU SEE THEM?
THEY MOVED BEHIND THE TRUCK.
COME ON, BOYS!
WAIT A MINUTE. THIS ISN'T
THE WAY OSCAR HAD IT PLANNED.
SHUT UP! DIAMONDS IN THE BOX?
YEAH.
EVERYBODY MOVE IN NOW!
HANDS THROUGH THE MIRROR
BRACKET. HANDCUFF 'EM.
( starts, revs motorcycle )
GET OSCAR. NOW!
WE GOT JIMMY RAY,
BUT COOPER IS GONE.
AND SO ARE THE DIAMONDS.
SHIT!
GODDAMNIT!
OHH!
THAT'S IT!
SUSPENSION, PENDING
INVESTIGATION.
YOU NEVER LISTEN, OSCAR.
WE TRACED COOPER TO TORONTO,
FENCING SOME OF THE DIAMONDS.
HE'S IN CHINATOWN.
I'LL GET THE SON OF A BITCH,
AND THE DIAMONDS BACK.
( sighs )
( chuckles )
T.C.
♪ ONLY YOU AND YOUR TOUCH
♪ CAN CURE MY
♪ JEALOUS HEART
♪ YOU SAY YOU LOVE ME, I SUPPOSE
♪ BUT THEN YOU--
Ben: EXCUSE ME, MR.DANKER.
THIS GENTLEMAN SAYS
HE'S AN OLD FRIEND OF YOURS.
WELL, WELL, WELL.
WE HAVE COMPANY, DARLIN'.
JULIA SOMERS,
MEET OSCAR PIERCE.
YOU'VE HEARD ME SPEAK OF HIM.
MISS SOMERS.
I'VE ENJOYED YOUR SHAMPOO
COMMERCIAL.
HA HA HA HA!
WELL, OSCAR,
I'D POUR YOU A DRINK...
ONLY I DON'T WANT TO.
NOW, YOU...
AND YOUR F-B-FUCKIN'-I
DECIDED I COULD NOT
BE PROSECUTED.
SO WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
AH...I NEED YOUR HELP.
COOPER'S BEEN TRACED SELLING OFF
SOME OF THE DIAMONDS.
HELP ME GET THEM BACK AND I WILL
FORGET I EVER HEARD OF YOU,
AND YOU CAN SETTLE THINGS WITH
COOPER ANY WAY YOU WANT.
( laughs)
( continues laughing )
ANY WAY I WANT?
OSCAR...
JUST HOW STUPID DO YOU
THINK I AM?
LOOK!
ASS-WIPE...
GETTING THOSE DIAMONDS BACK
IS THE TICKET TO MY LIFE.
NOW, I COULD KILL COOPER TODAY,
BUT IT WON'T GUARANTEE
GETTING THOSE DIAMONDS BACK.
HE'S GOING TO HAVE TO BE LURED
INTO GIVING THEM OVER.
AND YOU...HAVE THE ONLY
THING HE WANTS.
NO.
NO, JIMMY, I WON'T DO THAT.
(laughs) YOU SEE, OSCAR?
YOU SEE...
HOW THIS LITTLE EPISODE
WITH TEDDY COOPER HAS INTERFERED
WITH MY OTHERWISE PERFECT
RELATIONSHIP WITH MS. SOMERS?
NOW, DARLING, OSCAR'S OFFERING
TO FINALLY LEAVE ME ALONE.
AND I'M GONNA GET T.C.
IF IT'S THE LAST THING
I DO ON EARTH.
SO YOU HAVE TWO CHOICES.
YOU EITHER COME TO YOUR SENSES
AND YOU HELP ME, OR YOU GET
THE FUCK OUT OF HERE.
TODAY. ALONE.
NO MONEY. NO CLOTHES.
ALONE.
ONE HUNDRED PERCENT ALONE.
NOW...
...WHAT'S IT GONNA BE?
JULIA?
JULIA.
Teddy: I ONLY RECENTLY
STARTED THINKING ABOUT THESE
THINGS, THE DARKNESS, MAKING
AN EFFORT TO MOVE TOWARDS
THE LIGHT.
I REALLY APPRECIATE OUR
CONVERSATIONS, BUT I HAVEN'T
BEEN COMPLETELY HONEST WITH YOU.
THERE'S SOMETHING I'VE BEEN
AFRAID TO TELL YOU.
I STOLE SOMETHING...
VERY VALUABLE.
BUT I DECIDED I WANT TO RETURN
IT SO I CAN STAY WITH YOU
AND LEARN WITH A CLEAN SLATE.
YOU ARE MAKING PROGRESS.
YOU ARE ALREADY TEACHING
YOURSELF.
TAKE THIS BOOK.
IT WILL HELP YOU.
BY THE WAY, DID I MENTION
THAT I COMMUNICATED WITH MEMBERS
OF THE POLICE UP HERE?
IT SEEMS THEY'RE EXTREMELY
UNDERPAID, SO IT TOOK A BIT
OF MY SAVINGS.
BUT IF ANYTHING GOES WRONG,
MOTHERFUCKER, BEFORE I GET
THOSE DIAMONDS, YOU TWO
WILL BE FOUND LYING FACE DOWN
IN A CHINESE LAUNDRY.
IT WOULD PAIN ME
TO SEE THAT HAPPEN.
( car horn honks )
HE'S BACK.
OKAY, TELL ME AGAIN.
I KNOW WHAT TO DO.
JUST GET THE DIAMONDS.
UNDERSTAND?
THEN HE'S A DEAD MAN.
GO AHEAD AND GET DRESSED.
( Oscar chuckling )
( footsteps )
TEDDY?
IT'S JULIA.
TEDDY, PLEASE LET ME IN.
HOW DID YOU FIND ME HERE,
JULIA? HOW DID YOU FIND ME?!
JIMMY RAY, THROUGH
THE DENVER POLICE.
FUCKIN' NIGHTMARE.
I'M SORRY.
I'M JUST GONNA GO.
JULIA, YOU ARE MY
WORST FUCKIN' NIGHTMARE.
DON'T EVEN TRY TO LIE TO ME,
JULIA. YOU TOLD JIMMY RAY
EVERYTHING. I HEARD YOU.
GIVE ME THIS.
DON'T!
AAH!
YOU FUCKING LIAR!
OSCAR WAS RIGHT ABOUT YOU.
YOU'RE SOME KIND OF
FUCKING DEMON!
DON'T CALL ME THAT!
LISTEN TO ME.
LISTEN TO ME!!!
TEDDY, I LOVE YOU.
TELL ME HOW YOU DO IT, JULIA.
TELL ME HOW YOU DO IT, HUH?!
I LOVED YOU, AND YOU TRIED
TO KILL ME!
NO, I DIDN'T.
YOU DID.
I WAS SCARED.
I WAS AFRAID.
I DIDN'T WANT THE ROBBERY TO
HAPPEN, I TOLD YOU I DIDN'T
WANT THE ROBBERY TO HAPPEN!
AND I THOUGHT YOU WERE
GOING TO ABANDON ME, TEDDY!
PLEASE, I SWEAR TO GOD,
I LOVE YOU!
OH, SAVE YOUR LIES!
I DON'T WANT TO HEAR IT.
LISTEN TO ME.
ALL RIGHT, I'M LISTENING!
TALK TO ME! SAY IT!
HOW DO YOU DO IT?!
I DON'T KNOW.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT I DID.
I'M SORRY. EVERY MOMENT OF EVERY
DAY I THINK ABOUT YOU, AND I
WAKE UP AND I THINK THAT WE
SPENT THE NIGHT TOGETHER AND
THEN I REALIZE YOU'RE NOT THERE.
OH, TEDDY--TEDDY, I'M--
I FEEL LIKE--
( gasping )
I FEEL LIKE I'VE COMMITTED
MURDER.
YOU TRIED.
I--I FEEL LIKE
I MURDERED MYSELF.
I CAN'T DO ANYTHING!
I CAN'T THINK OF ANYTHING
BUT YOU.
YOU'RE EVERYWHERE, EVERY MOMENT,
EVERY MINUTE, EVERY BREATH.
TEDDY, YOU'VE BEEN INSIDE OF ME.
IT DOESN'T GO AWAY.
AND IF I CAN'T BE WITH YOU,
THEN I WANT TO BE DEAD.
WELL, WHAT DO YOU GOT?
PAIR OF EIGHTS.
PAIR OF NINES.
( laughing )
WELL, UH, HE HASN'T
THROWN HER OUT, SO IT MUST
BE WORKING.
I GUESS.
I GOTTA HIT THE CAN.
DO I TRUST YOU,
OR DO I HANDCUFF YOU?
IF I WERE YOU,
I'D HANDCUFF ME.
AHH. HA HA HA!
I THOUGHT WE WERE
GETTING TO BE FRIENDS.
SORRY, OSCAR,
I WANT THE DIAMONDS TOO.
( gunshots )
( shouting in distance )
NO BLOOD.
SEE THAT?
$490,000 IN DIAMONDS.
AND I'M JUST LEAVING IT.
WE SHOULD--WE SHOULD GO.
I'M LEAVING 'EM HERE, JULIA.
'CAUSE YOU'RE TELLING ME THAT
JIMMY RAY'S FOLLOWING YOU,
RIGHT?  WE SHOULD GO.
IS THAT IT? GOTTA GO.
LET'S GO. LET'S JUST GO
RIGHT NOW, OKAY?
( gunshot )
AAHH! OHH!
GOOD WORK, BABE.
( crying )
YOU SET ME UP AGAIN. HA HA!
GET OFF HIM, JULIA.
GET OFF HIM!
NO! NO!!!
NO! OHHH!
YOU DIDN'T BELIEVE ME.
I CAN'T FORGIVE BETRAYAL.
GO TO HELL, JIMMY RAY.
( laughs )
I DON'T BELIEVE IN HELL.
( gunshot )
Julia (sobbing): NO!
THE GAME IS OVER.
( Teddy groans )
TAKE IT EASY.
BETTER GET AN AMBULANCE.
FORGET ABOUT THE AMBULANCE.
GO GET THE CAR. WE'LL TAKE HIM
IN THE CAR. PUT HIM DOWN HERE.
OKAY.  EASY, EASY.
OHH...
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
( grunts, coughs )
I'M SORRY, OSCAR.
NO, MAN, IT'S ME
THAT'S SORRY.
I JUST WANT YOU TO KNOW
I NEVER WANTED JIMMY RAY
TO GET TO YOU.
PLEASE BELIEVE THAT.
YOU KNOW, THAT DARKNESS IN
THE LIGHT--IT'S ALL MY FAULT.
IT'S MY FAULT. MY FAULT.
JUST DON'T TALK ANYMORE.
COME ON.
OKAY, GET HIM UP.
( groaning )
EASY.
GOT HIS LEG?
( siren wails )
I'M GOING WITH YOU.
NO, YOU'RE NOT GOING WITH ME.
TAKE HER TO THE STATION.
TEDDY?
TEDDY, I THOUGHT THAT YOU
WOULDN'T WANT TO BE WITH ME
IF I TOLD YOU THE TRUTH.
COME ON, COME ON.
HEY! EASY.
HERE ARE THE DIAMONDS.
THIS GUYS SAYS HE KNOWS YOU.
YOU WANNA TALK TO HIM?
WELL, I GOT THE DIAMONDS AND
JIMMY RAY TOOK CARE OF TEDDY.
THAT WAS THE DEAL.
DON'T BE SUCH A HYPOCRITE.
COME HERE.
( crying )
SIT DOWN.
YOU'RE FREE TO GO, YOU KNOW.
( continues crying )
YOU KNOW, YOU'RE THE ONE WHO
CAUSED THIS TO HAPPEN.
I DID?
I SENT YOU IN THERE TWO YEARS
AGO TO GET JIMMY RAY.
BUT YOU ENDED UP
LIVING WITH HIM.
HE CARED ABOUT ME.
I CARED ABOUT YOU.
I COULD HAVE PUT YOU IN JAIL
FOR DRUG TRAFFICKING.
BUT I FELT SORRY FOR YOU.
YOU FELT SORRY FOR ME?
DON'T YOU MEAN YOU WERE
OBSESSED WITH ME?
ISN'T THAT WHAT YOU MEAN?
THAT YOU WERE OBSESSED WITH ME
AND YOU COULDN'T STAND IT THAT
I STAYED WITH JIMMY RAY?
I DIDN'T CAUSE THIS.
YOU DID.
HEY...
HAVE A NICE LIFE.
DID YOU HAVE TROUBLE
FINDING IT?
NO. THANK YOU.
HE IS FORTUNATE,
FOR NOW HE IS FREE.
HE IS NO LONGER BOUND BY
THE DARKNESS OF HIS PAST.
I ENVY HIM.
I MISS HIM.
GOODBYE, TEDDY.
YOUR POLICEMAN FRIEND
HAS GIVEN YOU
THE GIFT OF DEATH.
NOW YOU CAN BEGIN A NEW LIFE.
WHAT DO I DO FIRST?
YOU MUST BURY HER.
HERE. NEXT TO YOU.
( thunder rumbles )
( car starts )
♪ DOCTOR, COULD YOU ♪
♪ CHECK MY VISION ♪
♪ TELL ME IF I'M GOING BLIND ♪
♪ TAKE A GOOD LOOK ♪
♪ INSIDE MY HEAD, 'CAUSE ♪
♪ I THINK I'M LOSING MY MIND ♪
♪ NO NEED TO PUT ME UNDER ♪
♪ 'CAUSE I'M ALREADY ♪
♪ UNDER HER SPELL ♪
♪ ONLY THING I STILL WONDER ♪
♪ IS IF I DID IT ♪
♪ ALL BY MYSELF ♪
♪ I REMEMBER HER SAYING ♪
♪ SHE LOVED ME ♪
♪ BUT I MIGHT HAVE BEEN ♪
♪ TALKING IN MY SLEEP ♪
♪ DREAM ♪
♪ I MUST HAVE BEEN ♪
♪ DREAMING ABOUT HER ♪
♪ DREAM ♪
♪ I MUST HAVE BEEN ♪
♪ DREAMING ABOUT HER LOVE ♪
♪ BUT I SAW IT IN ♪
♪ LIVING COLOR ♪
♪ MAN, I COULD HAVE SWORE ♪
♪ IT WAS REAL ♪
♪ WRAPPING HER ARMS ♪
♪ AROUND MY BODY ♪
♪ AND THE WAY THAT ♪
♪ SHE MADE ME FEEL ♪
♪ WAS IT MY IMAGINATION ♪
♪ RUNNING AWAY WITH ME ♪
♪ JUST A BEAUTIFUL INSPIRATION ♪
♪ THAT ONLY A FOOL MIGHT SEE ♪
♪ WELL, I GUESS ♪
♪ I SHOULD HAVE KNOWN BETTER ♪
♪ THAN BELIEVING THAT ♪
♪ IT MIGHT COME TRUE ♪
♪ DREAM ♪
♪ I MUST HAVE BEEN ♪
♪ DREAMING ABOUT HER ♪
♪ DREAM ♪
♪ I MUST HAVE BEEN ♪
♪ DREAMING ABOUT HER LOVE ♪
♪ SWEET LOVE ♪
♪ DREAM ♪
♪ DREAMING ABOUT HER ♪
♪ I MUST HAVE BEEN ♪
♪ DREAMING ABOUT HER LOVE ♪
♪ SWEET LOVE ♪
♪ DREAM ♪
♪ MUST HAVE BEEN DREAMING ♪
♪ DREAM ♪♪