♪ If you do want me,
give me little sugar ♪
♪ If you don't want me,
don't lead me on, girl ♪
♪ But if you need me,
show me that you love me ♪
♪ And when I'm feeling blue,
and I want you ♪
♪ There's just one thing
that you should do ♪
♪ Just gimme
some kinda sign, girl ♪
♪ Oh, my baby
♪ To show me
that you're mine, girl ♪
♪ All right
♪ Just gimme
some kinda sign, girl ♪
♪ Oh, my darlin'
♪ To show me
that you're mine, girl ♪
♪ All right
♪ If you do want me,
give me little sweet talk ♪
♪ And if you don't want me,
don't lead me on, girl ♪
♪ But if you need me,
show me that you love me ♪
♪ And when I'm feeling down,
wearin' a frown ♪
♪ You'll be there
when I look around ♪
♪ Just gimme
some kinda sign, girl ♪
♪ Oh, my baby
♪ To show me
that you're mine, girl ♪
♪ All right
♪ Just gimme
some kinda sign, girl ♪
♪ Oh, my darlin'
♪ To show me
that you're mine, girl ♪
♪ All right
Yeah.
Hey, hey, kids, look there!
My name is Abraham Jacob Lee
and I am my father's son.
My father, Hubert Lee,
served in Korea.
( babies crying )
One day he found a baby
in a ditch.
But the baby died
before he could deliver it
to the orphanage.
( babies crying )
( baby cries )
Well, you look happy.
What do you know
that all the others don't?
ABRAHAM:
The moment he saw
my Korean name
I became his son.
Abraham Jacob Lee.
( baby cries )
So who's that?
Is she afraid I'll take you
and not her?
( baby cries )
I think I know you.
I think you are none other
than Louise Janine Lee.
Abraham Jacob Lee?
Yes, Dad?
Who's your
favorite father?
You are.
Who's your
only father?
You are.
Janine Louise Lee?
Who's your
favorite father?
Daddy, must we?
Who's your favorite
father, Louise?
( "Runaway" plays on radio )
♪ I wonder...
♪ I wah wah wah wah wonder
♪ Why...
♪ Why, why, why, why, why
♪ She ran away
♪ And I wonder...
♪ Where she will stay
♪ My little runaway
♪ Run, run, run, run, runaway
♪ Run, run, run, run,
runaway... ♪
( waves crashing )
Right here.
( Hubert laughs )
ABRAHAM:
This, I knew immediately,
was our journey's end.
A stretch of sand
halfway between Jacksonville
and Saint Augustine.
HUBERT:
This is going to be
just right, don't you think?
ABRAHAM:
Here my father would build
his great wall of life
and it would be exactly
as he saw it in his mind...
big as a dream.
HUBERT:
What's that?
ABRAHAM:
My father studied literature
in college
and to him the world was full
of signs and symbols.
Everything had a meaning.
From the moment my father
first laid eyes on him
Turner Knight
was Death personified.
And since my father
saw himself as life
it was inevitable
that they would be
adversaries.
Bye.
ABRAHAM:
Perhaps other things
were inevitable, too
etched in stone long
before any of us were born.
HUBERT:
Look at him, kids.
He has no idea
what the future has
in store for him...
that Hubert T. Lee and
his great wall of life
are going to put him
in the dark.
Abraham, Louise
your father is
a dramatic man.
Pay him no mind.
Come on.
( mid-tempo rhythm and blues
tune playing )
♪ Oogum, oogum, boogum, boogum
♪ Boogum, now, baby
♪ You're casting your spell
on me ♪
HUBERT:
All right now
here we go,
here we go.
♪ I say
♪ Oogum, oogum, boogum, boogum
♪ Boogum, now, baby
♪ You're casting your spell
on me ♪
♪ You got me doin' funny things
like a clown ♪
♪ Just look at me
ABRAHAM:
My father thought that once
The Flamingo was built
Turner Knight would be forced
to relocate.
Life would send Death packing.
♪ And you wear
that cute miniskirt ♪
♪ With your brother's
sloppy shirt ♪
ABRAHAM:
He was wrong.
I'm glad your mother
didn't live to see this.
MAN:
Come inside, Dad.
♪ Boogum, now, baby
♪ You're casting your spell
on me ♪
♪ I say
♪ Oogum, oogum, boogum, boogum
♪ Boogum, now, baby
♪ You're casting your spell
on me ♪
♪ You got me doin' funny things
like a clown ♪
♪ Just look at me
♪ When you wear
your high-heel boots ♪
♪ With your hip-hugger suit
♪ Huh! It's all right
♪ You're outta sight
♪ And you wear
that cute miniskirt ♪
♪ With your brother's
sloppy shirt ♪
♪ Huh! I admit it
♪ Girl, that I can dig it
♪ And I say
♪ Oogum, oogum, boogum, boogum
♪ Boogum, now, baby
♪ You're casting your spell
on me ♪
♪ I say
♪ Oogum, oogum, boogum, boogum
♪ Boogum, now, baby
♪ You're casting your spell
on me ♪
♪ You got me doing funny things
like a clown ♪
♪ Just look at me
♪ When you wear
your bell-bottom pants ♪
♪ I just stand there
in a trance ♪
♪ Huh! I can't move
♪ You're in the groove
♪ Would you believe,
little girl ♪
♪ That I am crazy 'bout you?
♪ Huh!
♪ Now, go on now
with your bad self... ♪
( truck horn blares )
♪ Ooh, ooh...
Uh-oh.
What?
Death's paying
life a visit.
♪ Ooh, ooh...
♪ Ooh, now, mercy,
mercy on me... ♪
ABRAHAM:
During the year
we built the Flamingo
we didn't formally introduce
ourselves to Turner Knight.
He and my father communicated
only through lawyers.
♪ You got style, girl,
that shore is wild ♪
♪ And wear
that cute trench coat ♪
♪ And you're standing
and posing ♪
♪ You got soul
♪ You got too much soul
♪ And I say
♪ Oogum, oogum, boogum...
KNIGHT::
I beg you to be
reasonable, Mr. Lee.
I'm trying to conduct
a funeral service.
HUBERT:
I thought we agreed
that you were
going to stay
on your side
of the highway
and I was going
to stay on mine.
That's just the point,
Mr. Lee.
Your music
is on my side
of the highway.
HUBERT:
Well, what manner of man
objects to music?
KNIGHT:
I don't object
to music, Mr. Lee,
but I am well aware
you're trying to ruin
my business to drive me out.
♪ When you wear
your bell-bottom pants... ♪
I'm trying to conduct
a funeral service
for the 17-year-old daughter
of the mayor
of Saint Augustine!
How would you like to kneel
in my chapel
beside the casket
of your daughter
and be forced to listen
to "Oogum Boogum"?
( record scratches )
I will never kneel
in your chapel, Mr. Knight.
On this you may
rely implicitly.
EDNA:
Mr. Knight...
Mr. Knight.
( panting )
Mr. Knight...
I fear we have been
very inconsiderate.
Mrs. Lee, believe me
I harbor no ill feeling
for you or your...
Husband.
...family.
Surely, we could come
to some reasonable
accommodation.
Of course, perhaps
you could telephone
our office when you're
having a service.
Thank you, Mrs. Lee.
And we will be installing
individual speaker posts
as soon as possible.
According to whom?
According to me, Hubert.
If you'll excuse me.
Gladly, you're excused.
Hubert, Hubert!
Hubert,
you're a good, decent man.
Act like one.
Oh, Hubert.
What gets into you?
Abraham?
Yes, Dad?
Later on, when you grow up
and find yourself
a good woman...
run like crazy.
Yes, Dad.
♪ Let me in, whee-ooh
♪ Whee-ooh, whee-ooh ♪
♪ Hoop-whee-ooh ♪
♪ I can see them dancin'
♪ The silhouettes on the shade
♪ I hear the music
♪ All the lovers on parade
♪ Open up
♪ I want to come in again
( horn blares )
♪ I thought you were my friend
♪ Pitter-patter of those feet
♪ Movin' and a-groovin'
with that beat ♪
♪ Jumpin' and stompin'
on the floor ♪
♪ Let me in!
♪ Open up!
Oh, oh, my, yes!
You know what this place
is going to be?
ALL:
A gold mine!
That is right.
We ran out of everything.
I'm guessing about 50 or 60 kids
snuck in in car trunks.
Maybe more.
They're sneaking
in the exit, too.
We should hire
someone to guard it.
Mm-hmm.
EDNA:
Hubert, listen.
Louise is right.
We're seriously understaffed
on weekends.
We need two registers going
Fridays and Saturdays.
Popcorn is where
we make our money.
Yeah, Daddy,
you're going to have
to adopt at least
two more kids.
( giggles )
Ooh!
I know what we really need.
Pirate costumes!
Daddy.
( groans )
Yes.
Pirate...
Yeah.
Pirate costumes.
Oh, yes.
( laughs )
Ten, 20...
Come on, Abraham.
Oh, yes... here, hold these.
You got that?
Here.
Huh?
( laughing )
Ha!
You like it?
Yeah.
Ha!
My goodness!
( tires squealing )
Stand back, stand back!
My goodness, are you...?
Come on out of there.
Are you... are you all right?
Yeah.
Now, really,
are you all right?
Yeah.
Are you sure
you're all right, Mr...?
Maws, Pete Maws.
Really?
Yeah.
Hubert T. Lee.
Edna Lee, Abraham Lee,
Louise Janine Lee.
How do you do?
Pleased to meet you.
I'm sorry about
the fence, Mr. Lee.
Not at all, not at all,
don't you worry about that.
That's not important.
This, this your drive-in?
It's not just a
drive-in, Mr. Maws.
You're looking at
the world's largest
movie screen...
conceived, built, and operated
by the Hubert T. Lee family
formerly of North Carolina.
North Carolina?
Mm-hmm.
Where you headed,
Mr. Maws?
I wasn't headed for
your fence, Mrs. Lee.
I'm not exactly sure
where I'm headed.
I was just looking for
a place to park my engine.
Do you possess any
skills, Mr. Maws?
For instance, uh, carpentry?
I can pound a nail,
if that's what you're asking.
Matter of fact, I'm looking
for a job, if you're offering.
Do you believe in
accidents, Mr. Maws?
I believe
I just had one.
I don't... believe
in accidents, that is.
I believe everything
happens for a reason.
And I believe that if you're
not just looking for a job
but also for a new home,
you just found both.
Both?
Mm-hmm.
What do you think about that,
Mr. Abraham?
My dad's
usually right.
Your dad's
always right.
Put her there.
Come on in.
Come on in?
Yeah.
HUBERT:
You're a lucky
man, Pete Maws.
You've escaped the
"Iron Line of Necessity"
and become part of
the "Great Wall of Life."
Directionless just a
few short hours ago
you are now part of
the "Grand Design."
( chuckles )
Well, Mrs. Lee
you have yourself
two beautiful children.
Miss Louise,
I believe, favors you
and Mr. Abraham...
his father.
( Hubert chuckles )
At the risk of appearing nosy
Mr., Mr. Maws,
there's, uh...
well, there's something
about your story
I don't quite understand.
What's that, Mr. Lee?
You retired from the railroad?
Yes, sir.
On the Palm Coast Line,
in Florida?
Yes, sir, started out in linens
and worked my way up
through the dining car.
And I spent the last ten years
in charge of maintenance.
And the Palm Coast gave you
a pension?
The Palm Coast Line is under
the mistaken impression that...
I'm white.
You may have to explain
that one, Mr. Maws.
Well, Mrs. Lee, I was hired
with a bunch of boys
out of Palatka.
And, well, I was
the only one that could write
so I got to fill out
all the forms.
Now, you had to check either
that you were colored
or you were white.
At that time... I must have
been about Mr. Abraham's age...
and, well, I wished I was white.
So when it came down
to my own form
well, guess which one I checked?
Wasn't that a lie?
Yes, that's exactly what
it was, Mr. Abraham.
Big, old white lie.
I mean, as young as I was
I didn't know
that there's some things
that you just can't change
by wishing, you know?
And later on, well,
I felt more ashamed
about the wish than the lie
if you follow
my meaning.
You still look a little young
to retire, hmm?
Well, sir,
that's another lie I told.
Instead of 14, I wrote down
that I was 40 on the form.
Yeah, yeah, Mrs. Lee.
That's true.
You're looking at
a 65-year-old white man.
( laughter )
Are you, are you sure
you're telling us the truth
about all this, Mr. Maws?
Now, would I lie to you?
( chuckling )
Here's to retirement.
ALL:
Yes!
( giggling )
♪ Joyful, joyful,
we adore Thee ♪
♪ God of glory, Lord of love
♪ Hearts unfold
like flowers before Thee ♪
♪ Opening to the sun above
♪ Melt the clouds
of sin and sadness ♪
♪ Drive the dark of doubt away
♪ Giver of immortal gladness
♪ Fill us
with the light of day ♪
PRIEST:
Let us pray.
O Lord, be merciful
to your people.
Fill us with your gifts
and make us always
eager to serve you
in faith
hope and love.
( whispers ):
What's your name?
We ask this through
Christ, our Lord...
Amen.
( giggles )
A reading from the
First Epistle of Paul
to the Corinthians...
I'm Gary.
Gary.
"Now I will show you
the greater way
"which surpasses all others.
"If I speak with human tongues
"and angelic as well,
but do not have love
"I am a noisy gong,
a clanging cymbal.
"If I have the gift of prophesy
"and with full knowledge
comprehend all mysteries
"and have faith great
enough to move mountains
"but do not have love,
I am nothing.
"Love is patient.
"It is never self-seeking.
"Love never fails.
"Prophesies will cease.
"Tongues will be silent.
"Knowledge will pass away.
"In the end
"but three things last:
faith, hope and love.
And the greatest
of these is love."
( bells ringing )
Mrs. Lee, how nice to see you.
Mr. Knight.
LOUISE:
Mother, can I wait for you
across the street?
Close by, Louise.
I don't want to have
to search for you.
Yes, Mother.
I didn't know you were a member
of the parish, Mr. Knight.
Oh, I belong to seven churches
and, and a synagogue.
My vocation requires it.
( chuckles )
Does that make me
a hypocrite,
do you suppose?
Well, that would be
a rather harsh judgment.
Harsh, but perhaps just.
Faith and I have been resolute
strangers since my wife died.
Abraham, go keep
your sister company.
She's got company.
Yes, but I think she
could benefit from yours.
Dad said not to be late.
Go.
Mrs. Lee
I am happy
to run into you.
I've been wanting
to thank you
for intervening
with your husband.
Oh, what you were asking for
was more than reasonable.
Mrs. Lee, might I ask you
why he hates me so?
Oh, now, Hubert doesn't
hate you, Mr. Knight.
He hates...
the idea of you.
Ah, well...
that's reassuring.
( chuckling )
Have you been
down the street?
( indistinct )
Well, I think
it's a great success.
( laughter )
Mother's found an
admirer, Abraham.
Mom loves Dad.
EDNA:
It was kind of you
to give me that advice
about the schools.
KNIGHT:
Oh, I'm happy to
any... anytime.
EDNA:
I do appreciate it.
Bye-bye.
Bye.
Abraham, Louise.
Mr. Knight has suggested
a school for the two of you:
Saint Margaret.
Catholic school?
With nuns and uniforms?
Dad would never allow it.
Uh-huh...
Who's your favorite father?
My favorite father
wouldn't make me go
to Catholic school.
You'll have to take that up
with your favorite mother.
All right, how old
is the earth?
Millions
of years?
And how do we know?
Carbon dating.
Who's the father
of modern science?
Galileo.
And who had Galileo
thrown in prison
for telling the truth?
The Pope.
Where'd your mother
come up with this idea
is what I'd like to know.
All right.
Be careful, now.
Don't grow up now.
Don't you ever grow up now.
( school bell ringing )
( chattering )
Sister.
Mother.
( class murmurs )
MOTHER SUPERIOR:
Today is a special day, class.
( pounds on chalkboard )
Class!
Today it is my pleasure
to introduce to you, not one,
but two new classmates.
Ow!
( laughing )
Their names are
Abraham Jacob Lee
and Louise Janine Lee.
I'm sure you'll want to join me
in welcoming them.
( applause )
You may go to your seats.
GIRL ( whispering ):
I wonder what's wrong with her.
BOY ( whispering ):
I don't know, maybe...
Nice shot.
Thank you, Mother.
Today we are reading
Romeo and Juliet
Act Two, Scene One.
BOY:
Use this one here.
Come on.
You can look on with me.
Thank you.
( whispers ):
Have you read ever read
Romeo and Juliet before?
What scene is this?
Act Two, Scene One.
( both giggle )
LOUISE:
He dropped all this popcorn
and then he dropped
all the money my mother gave me.
Oh, hey, Louise,
you dropped this.
GIRL:
See you later, Grace.
Bye.
( chattering )
Hi.
Your sister's really pretty.
Why was she limping before?
It only happens when
she's really nervous.
You'll probably
never see it again.
Well, it was really nice
the way you took care of her.
The nuns will make her
button her blazer.
They think the sight
of girls' breasts
inspires boys
to evil thoughts.
So, are you Chinese?
Louise and I were
born in Korea.
We were adopted
when we were little.
Do you know
who your parents are?
They're Hubert
and Edna Lee.
No. I mean your real parents.
They are our real parents.
I'm... sorry.
I didn't mean to...
No. That's okay.
We probably shouldn't
even be talking.
My father is Turner Knight,
you know.
I know.
I recognized you.
Guess that makes
you a Capulet.
And you a Montague.
Your top button
has to be fastened.
( school bell ringing )
( laughter )
MAN:
Come on, you guys.
So, what's it like
to live in the world's
largest movie screen?
Pretty normal mostly.
What's it like to live
in a funeral parlor?
Well, it's the same...
pretty normal.
Do you sleep
in a bed or a coffin?
( laughs )
So, since you work in the
Flamingo Drive-in and all...
Yeah.
Are there any
good movies?
No.
No? Not at all?
No. Not at all.
BOY:
...cheerleading class?
LOUISE:
Do you really think I should?
BOY:
Yeah. I definitely think
you should.
BOY:
They could really use
somebody like you.
I don't know.
LOUISE:
There's my dad.
I'll see you later.
BOY #2:
Take care. I'll see you.
Her name's Ashley.
And she's on... she's like...
Oh, that's so sweet.
LOUISE:
Abe. Come on.
Sorry. I-I have to go.
MAN:
So long now.
BOY #2:
Okay, I'll...
MAN:
We've got to get going.
BOY #2:
Okay.
LOUISE:
Hi, Mom.
EDNA:
How was it?
How was your school?
LOUISE:
Fine.
ABRAHAM:
Great.
You got a lot
of homework.
Yes.
No.
I'm glad you brought
your books home, Abe.
I'd like to have a look
through them.
Your father wants to check them
for Papal fallacies.
We've already read
most of them.
Our living room
has more books than
the school library.
HUBERT:
See? What
did tell you?
Maybe a donation
is in order.
You give hand-outs
to everyone else.
Fine with me, Edna.
I'll start making
a list of books
no high school library
should be without.
D.H. Lawrence,
Nabokov, Salinger.
So you make
any new friends?
Yeah.
Yeah?
Who's the young lady, Abe?
Which one?
Forgive me, Father,
for I have sinned.
HUBERT:
Under the elms
just now.
I think her name was Grace.
Grace what?
Hubert.
Edna.
LOUISE:
Yeah, Abraham.
Grace what?
How come you two
are arguing so much lately?
Both:
Who?
( airplane whirring )
Here he comes.
( crowd chatting excitedly )
MAN:
Money. Money.
Watch this.
Watch. Watch.
He said he's going to do
a loop-de-loop.
Isn't that dangerous?
Don't you worry, son.
That is none other than
Judge Lester at the throttle.
He's the best circus pilot
in all of Dixie.
Rule #1 in business, son:
Advertise, advertise, advertise.
Rule Number Two:
Always, always hire the best.
Hey, what's that?
( gasping )
Oh!
Oh! Oh!
Whoo!
( gasps )
( frustrated muttering )
Come on.
Whoa!
Is he okay?
Uh... I think so.
I-I think he made it.
Hey!
You kids
stay away
from there now!
That's not a toy.
It's not exactly a
plane anymore, either.
Yeah. She'll need a little work
before she flies again.
Judge Lester, this
is my son, Abraham,
you remember?
Young man...
you are the spitting
image of your father.
Thanks.
Well, it could have been worse.
How?
You could have been killed.
These children
could have been killed.
( frogs croaking )
Could have been
better, too.
Mr. Lee
maybe this ain't such
a good idea.
Come along. Edna probably
doesn't even remember you.
It's okay. Come
on in. Come in.
Well...
Look what the cat dragged in.
Sweetheart.
( laughs )
Hi. Now, you may
not recall, but
this is Judge Lester.
He's the best stunt
pilot in all of Dixie.
Oh, I remember Judge Lester.
They finally run you out
of North Carolina, Judge.
HUBERT:
And-and this...
is our new projectionist,
Mr. Pete Maws.
Hey, Judge.
Well... an outdoor
cinematic technician.
Whoa!
Is that Miss Louise there?
Why, you're even prettier
than your pictures.
And old honest
Abe there, why
he-he looks like a...
a doctor.
Hey, how about some candy,
you two, huh?
Yeah. Take as
much as you want.
I got connections
with all the candy kings
of North America.
Whoo!
And, uh, Mrs. Lee...
the lady of the house
always deserves a gift
when a guest comes
for a long visit.
A long visit?
Um...
I've invited the judge
to work here at the Flamingo
for a while until he gets
his plane fixed up.
We had a little problem in town
this afternoon.
I know that, Hubert.
It was all over the radio.
You know what they call that,
Judge?
Hmm?
Free publicity.
Yeah.
Well, it's a good thing
we just made a $5,000 donation
to the Policeman's
Benevolent Fund
or you two overgrown adolescents
would be in jail
for public endangerment.
Rule #1 in business,
Abraham:
Always make friends
with the cops.
I thought Rule #1 was:
"Advertise, advertise,
advertise."
Well, Rule #2, then.
Dad, Rule #2
is "Always hire the best."
Okay, then, call it
2A and 2B.
Your father's full of #2,
isn't he?
( laughter )
Would you take
me flying?
EDNA:
Sweetie
the finest stunt pilot
in all
of Dixie just wrecked his plane.
Oh, there's lots of planes
for hire, Mrs. Lee.
I'll be glad to take you up.
Louise, darling, we don't
need to discuss that now.
Oh, Please, Daddy?
We really don't.
Please, Daddy, please.
Louise, no-no sugar.
Mom, please. I want to fly
more than anything.
You have to say yes. Please?
Louise!
Please?
No.
On one condition.
Anything. Anything.
I promise.
The Judge takes me up first
so I know it's safe.
But, Mom, you're scared
of heights.
You won't even go
up on the roof.
Oh, I think I'll be safe enough,
won't I, Judge?
You're a different man up here.
Aren't you, Judge?
Nothing to be afraid of
in the sky, Mrs. Lee.
It's down there
where everything gets messed up.
Up here...
Even I...
don't make you nervous.
Oh, not a bit, Mrs. Lee.
I got you just where I want you.
What do I do?
Yeah, that's good.
You all right?
I'm fine.
( laughing )
Yeah.
Whee!
LOUISE:
Thanks, Mom.
( laughing )
Come on, little lady.
Abraham...
you were really
worried about me,
weren't you?
Here comes our
next aviator.
( Abraham chuckles )
It's gorgeous.
( plane engine starting )
LOUISE:
Bye!
Bye.
SON:
Dad, can you listen?
DAD:
He is going to give us
a practical demonstration
of what I feel safe
in saying
is a pretty exciting
birthday present.
SON:
Dad, we need to talk
about this for a second.
DAD:
I can't hold them
much longer, Ben.
You'd better get out here.
SON:
I'd like to discuss this.
Hey, you're flexing
my face.
Air.
GARY:
Hey, fellas,
that's $3.75.
Oh, come on, man.
Give us a break.
Admission is one and a quarter
times three.
Makes $3.75, fellas.
Ah, man.
BOY:
Come on, fellas.
Let's bug out...
Come on, baby.
ABRAHAM:
Thanks a lot, guys.
Enjoy the show.
This remarkable young man
is going to perform for you...
I think your sister's
in love with me.
Don't you?
No.
Not even a little?
She loves the fact
that you love her.
That's not the same
thing, is it?
She wants to be
an actress.
That way everybody
will love her.
You could be one
of the everybody.
What I want to be
is the only body.
( laughing )
( coins clanking )
All right...
spill it.
What?
Whatever's wrong.
You've been moping
since yesterday.
You regret now
you didn't go flying.
No.
What then?
I wasn't supposed to know
about you and Grace Knight?
Is that it?
How did you find out?
You didn't invent
falling in love, Abraham.
You going to tell Dad?
You're going to.
Why not?
Shall I tell you why not?
You're not going to tell him
because you love him, right?
Because you're crazy
about Grace.
And because telling
your father
would serve no
useful purpose.
Do you like Turner Knight?
Yes, Abraham, I do.
Why do you have to talk to him
every Sunday after church?
I think I just answered
that question.
Were you paying attention?
Abraham, look at me.
Look at me.
Turner Knight
is a lonely man
in need of a friend.
That's all we are though
if that's what's worrying you.
I haven't told your father
about my friendship
with Mr. Knight.
The same reason you haven't
told him about Grace
because no possible good
could come of it.
Keeping a secret...
isn't that the same as a lie?
Abraham...
( sighs )
your father's right.
We shouldn't be sending you
to a Catholic school.
You were born a Jesuit.
( laughs )
Whoa.
Man:
Run. Run.
( can clanking )
HUBERT:
Abraham
Easy.
don't, uh... okay.
Here.
This boy...
he's either
real brave or...
he don't understand
too good.
PETE:
That boy's name
is Abraham.
And he's smart enough
not to drop that crate
in the first place.
You know what
would be extra neat?
Set them babies off
from the top
of the screen.
Too dangerous.
Let's just
go along
as we planned, okay?
Set them off
from the barge.
Just in case
anything happens...
there's an accident
or something
it happens right
over the water.
Now, if something
goes wrong up there
it's over a crowd
of people.
( groans )
Pete's right.
Well, I just don't see
what's going to go wrong,
I guess.
So, exactly who makes
the decisions around here?
I do.
And I like the idea
as much as you do, Judge
but Pete's right.
We're gonna fire the rockets
off the barge, like we planned.
( groans )
Except for the finale.
I don't see where
it'd hurt to shoot
the last four Rebel Dogs
off the roof.
Just when folks think
it's all over
bang, bang, bang!
Bang, bang.
Right in a row.
Right overhead.
Heck, that'd bring down
the house.
( laughing )
It's your house.
Are you ready
for the biggest
fireworks display ever witnessed
in the great state
of Florida, huh?
The line in front
of the snack bar
is going to wind halfway
to Jacksonville, son.
And you'll be glad
to know that I hired
I hired two extra
girls to help.
That way I can emcee things
instead of being stuck
behind the counter.
Uh, uh, Abraham, could...?
Yep...
about the finale...
Yeah, Dad.
I don't see what
where it's necessary
to tell your mother
about what we're planning.
Oh, you mean shooting
the Rebel Dogs off the roof
instead of the barge?
Shh, shh, shh.
Why, thank you.
Here.
You want me
to lie
to Mom?
No.
No, no, not lie.
Just...
Keep a secret?
Exactly. A small secret.
A small, insignificant
little secret.
Isn't a secret
the same as a lie?
I just don't see the point
in worrying her.
Do you?
Hi.
Oh, you-you
like the green?
I prefer the red.
Mm-hmm.
Hello, sugar.
Hot as a biscuit
today, isn't it?
( door closes )
( waves roaring )
( seagulls singing )
What?
It's nothing.
I just hate lying
to my father.
Well... it's not a lie.
You didn't lie to him.
Abraham, I snuck out
of the house.
If I'd asked
for his permission
he would have said no.
Well, they keep secrets,
too, you know?
Who?
My parents.
What are those lights
out on the water?
They're shrimp boats.
They like to
fish at night.
The shrimp are attracted
to the light.
It's all so beautiful.
I'm really glad
we're here.
LOUISE:
Abraham!
Have you
met her?
Met who?
Go, right this minute.
She's in the snack bar.
Hurry!
( loud rock music plays )
♪ Judy in the sky
♪ Hey, that's what you are
♪ A lemonade pie
♪ Hey, got your brand-new car
WOMAN:
Stare much?
♪ Cantaloupe eyes come
jumping tonight ♪
♪ Judy in the sky
( giggles )
Who are you?
WOMAN:
Cat seems to have
got his tongue.
But unless I miss my guess
this is none other
than Abraham Jacob Lee
future heir
to the fortune
of Hubert Lee, our employer.
No one told me he was a mute,
though.
I'm not a mute.
Good.
The one you were admiring
over here
this is Polly.
And the one who scares you...
I'm Alice.
And I forgive you
for admiring her and not me.
♪ Unzipping the strings
in my kite ♪
So, um, what do people call you?
Abraham.
Hmm...
Then I'm going
to call you Jacob.
Aw, I like the way
you blush, Jacob.
♪ Judy in the sky
You know we are going
to be very good friends
you and I.
Did you know that I used to go
to Saint Margaret myself
until I was expelled?
( laughing )
What for?
( giggles )
So what do you think?
Isn't she something?
Oh, she's gorgeous
all right, but...
Gorgeous?
Abe, I'm not talking about
the muffin in the mini.
I'm talking about Alice.
Don't you get it?
She's the
Alice King.
The?
Haven't you heard
the stories
about Alice King
at school?
She's a legend.
She's the one who got caught
dancing in her birthday suit
in the courtyard fountain
during the bishop's visit.
ABRAHAM:
I don't believe it.
It's true, Abraham,
I'm telling you.
( car horn honking )
I don't know.
That's a pretty small fountain.
( both laugh )
( up-tempo soul song plays )
No, no, no, no.
Go to the other side,
other side.
♪ Show me a man out there
who's got a good woman ♪
No, no...
( indistinct shouting )
No, you have to park.
Whoa.
♪ Show me a man
that's got a good woman ♪
( giggles )
( shouting playfully )
Bye-bye.
Bye.
Virgil.
Is it busy out there?
ROD STEIGER:
You take care, you hear?
Uh-huh.
MAN:
Excuse me.
Can I help you?
Two popcorns.
Psst...
MAN:
One with butter,
one without.
Would you like some advice?
Sure, I guess.
Okay, you like
Grace Knight...
right?
Yeah.
Then how come every
time Polly is around
you make a beeline
for her?
When you walk into a room
and there are two girls there
you don't always have to sit
next to the pretty one.
Popcorn.
PETE:
Abraham, Abraham.
listen, there's been
a change of plans.
Now, your dad's gone off
to the barge
to set the
fireworks off now.
He wants you to
find the Judge
and head to the top.
And he said remember your cue!
Got to go.
( Sousa march plays )
Your dad invited me
to come live with you guys
for the rest of the summer.
That's great.
He likes the regular crew
to live here.
He's neat, your dad.
There's the big, green one!
Th-that's our cue.
All right, get back there now.
Come on.
JUDGE LESTER:
There they go.
( cheers )
( groaning ):
What happened here?
It's a dud.
Judge!
Get down!
Hey!
( breaking glass )
Uh-oh.
MAN:
Hurry up!
Daddy!
( coughs )
Damn.
Hold onto your sister.
You all right?
Yeah, we're all right.
( Sousa march stops )
JUDGE LESTER:
Uh-oh.
Oh, man...
Well...
it was the biggest
night in the history
of the Flamingo Drive-In.
Every single space
in that park
had a car sitting in it.
The snack bar broke
the record, right?
Abraham, we made more
money in one night
than we usually do
in a good week.
Subtract the cost of a new roof
for the Knight Funeral Home,
and what did we make?
Well, that's why we have
insurance, sweetheart
because accidents happen.
Oh, I'm sorry, Hubert.
Aren't you the one
that's always saying
there's no such thing
as an accident?
Or was that somebody else?
Turner Knight does
not need to worry.
He'll get his new roof.
That is not the point.
Good grief!
We almost burned
that man's house down.
If it hadn't rained when it did
that's exactly
what we'd be guilty of.
You did a bad
thing, Hubert.
You did it secretly,
because you knew I'd object.
And you!
You kept the secret.
It's not like you don't have
secrets, too, Mother.
I don't know what
you're talking about, Louise.
And do you know what?
Neither do you.
Now, you go upstairs
to your room
and you think about that
for a little while.
Abraham, you are not excused.
Don't you ever expect me
to apologize to Turner Knight.
EDNA:
I've already apologized.
What I want is
for you to quit
this senseless feud,
and leave the poor man alone.
All this is unnecessary, Hubert.
May I be excused?
Yes.
♪ Let's just stay together
♪ If you only know...
Aren't you going to ask me
if I got the job?
Did you get the job?
Yes, Abraham, I did.
You may now congratulate me.
I just don't see why
you need a job.
I don't need one.
I want one.
It was different
when I was teaching
you and your sister.
Now you're in school.
I could use a little help
filling up the days.
I was a teacher before
you came along, you know.
Who's going to
look after Dad?
Well, Abraham, it is true
your father needs more or less
constant supervision.
I guess we'll have
to take turns.
REPORTER:
To repeat this breaking story:
the Reverend Martin Luther King
has been shot and killed
by an assassin's bullet
in Memphis...
Oh, dear.
Witnesses say the shots
were fired from the window
of a building adjacent
to the Lorraine Motel...
♪ Mmm...
Let's give Pete some
privacy, son, okay?
♪ Mmm...
WOMAN:
I think she overdid it
a little bit, don't you?
WOMAN #2:
I completely agree.
GARY:
Great turnout.
WOMAN #2:
The flowers...
She just tries too hard.
How come your dad booked
The Bliss of Mrs. Blossom?
( chuckles )
Mom wanted to see it.
He's still trying to get
back on her good side.
She still hasn't
forgiven him?
Actually, she forgave
him right away.
Then why's he still
being so nice to her?
I don't know.
It's the way they are.
Don't your parents
ever argue?
No, that would require
my dad to speak.
( women laughing )
POLLY:
There you are!
What is it?
They need you
in the ladies' room!
Hurry!
Go! Go!
( knocking )
Read the sign!
ABRAHAM:
It's me, Alice.
Oh!
Come on, come on, come on,
come on, come on...
Louise, go get
your mother!
Okay.
Take over
the ticket office for her!
ABRAHAM:
Is she sick?
Not anymore.
Ooh, she's...
You know what. Why don't you
go out and guard the door?
Don't let anybody in here.
Me, too.
No-no-no, no-no-no.
No! Not you, Jacob Lee.
What?
The door's locked
from the inside.
So?
So, climb.
Come on.
Oh!
( gasps )
The latch is stuck.
Well, you're upside
down, remember.
Try turning it the other way.
( sighing )
Okay, let me down.
ALICE:
Oh, you are kidding me.
Oh, my heavens!
What are we going to do?
I don't know, but it's
going to require...
a Phillips head
screwdriver.
Hi, hi. Um, I'm sorry, the
ladies' room is out of order.
Yeah.
But you can
use the men's.
( giggles )
Mr. Knight has the solution.
Come on.
Come along.
I'll show you what to do.
( siren wailing in distance )
That'll be the police.
I'll go wait for them.
Pete... you go on to bed.
Thank you.
You'll be all right.
Uh-huh.
ABRAHAM:
She looks so lonely.
We shouldn't
have moved her.
No. It was the right thing.
If that lady had been found
on your folks' property
the state would have
closed you down.
Maybe for a week...
or more.
Besides, it's better
if her family
remembers her like this.
Uh, here come
the professionals.
I'm to deliver a message
from my daughter.
She says she misses you.
I miss her, too.
Well, you can come
and visit Grace at our house
anytime you wish.
Evening, Mr. Knight.
Good evening, Randy.
Is she dead?
It would appear.
HUBERT:
I'll decide what we need
or do not need around here.
EDNA:
Listen to me,
Hubert...
Oh, for goodness' sake.
No, I don't care, Edna.
I don't want him here.
I asked him to come,
darling.
He's doing us a favor.
No, I don't want
any favors from him.
I don't want any
favors from him.
Come on.
Edna, I do not believe
that I'm talking
to you right now.
It's all right.
RAYMOND:
Be easier
to just bury her
in the car.
Well, it would.
EDNA:
Morning!
KNIGHT:
Good morning to you.
How are you?
I'm just fine.
Did everything work out
to your satisfaction?
Thank you so much.
You're very welcome.
I'll see you later.
I hope so.
Don't worry, Dad.
We won't be late.
Abraham. Just the man
I was looking for.
I'm kind of late, Dad.
Oh, I think our
helpful neighbor
can wait a minute.
Is this going to be
an everyday thing?
Just till the end of school.
Mom says Mr. Knight
is going to...
going to drive us to school
in the morning
and she's going to bring us
home in the afternoon.
Huh...
Anyway...
feast your eyes on this.
Come here.
Come here, come here, come here.
Come on,
come on,
come on.
Not only is he
the world's largest
freestanding neon cowboy,
you know what else he is?
That's right, Abraham.
He's for sale.
But I like our flamingo.
I'm not talking
about getting rid
of the flamingo.
I don't get it.
What are we going to do
with a cowboy?
Hmm...
♪ One, two, three, four
♪ Sha, la, la-la-la-la,
live for today... ♪
HUBERT:
I happen to own
this piece of land right here.
KNIGHT:
This will not stay
on my property.
( arguing )
LOUISE:
Uh-oh.
♪ Hey, hey, hey
♪ Sha, la, la-la-la-la,
live for today... ♪
HUBERT:
You must think I'm crazy.
MAN 2:
Please yourself.
HUBERT:
Here you go.
Thank you
very, very much.
I appreciate you guys
and getting it done so quickly.
Okay, we'll see you.
All right, nice job.
Okay, thank you.
OFFICER:
Now, Mr. Knight,
is there going to be
any more problem
here today?
Mr. Knight?
No more trouble, Cal,
I can promise you that.
Mr. Knight and I
are going to establish
a peaceable kingdom
right here in the
Sunshine State.
Right, partner?
Hey, whoa!
Back up! Back up!
Come on!
Hey, back off!
Let go!
Hey! Whoa!
Come on, now!
Hey, hey, back off!
Back off!
All right, Hubert...
that does it.
HUBERT:
Do I or do I not have a
perfectly legal right to erect
a sign on
my own property?
You have every legal right,
Hubert.
No one's saying
you don't own the land.
Except for the one tiny acre
Turner's business is on
you own everything
around here.
Oh, so he's "Turner"
now, is he?
And what does
he call you? "Edna"?
Don't change the subject,
Hubert!
You're a rich man
and you're abusing your power.
What's worse,
all you're really proving
is how small you can be.
You're still angry because
Turner Knight came over here
and helped us out
when we needed it.
Oh, Hubert Lee needed
Turner Knight? Ha!
You're moving that cowboy.
When pigs fly, Edna.
Not only are
they going to fly
they're going to fly
first thing tomorrow morning.
When I get home
from school
I expect to see the air
full of flying pigs.
Well, that's just too bad
if he can't take a joke.
( grunts )
I just... ( grunts )
I'm never going
to see Grace again.
( horses whinny )
Sorry about that bump.
MAN:
Are you going to come up here
and help me or not?
MAN 2:
I'm a passenger, not a driver.
Hyah!
( horses whinny )
( laughs )
( electrical buzzing )
Ow! Ow!
( grunts )
Actor:
Hey, grandpa...
( dog barks in distance )
( Edna panting )
You wouldn't think it
but this is much scarier
than flying in a plane.
So, you feel like
talking about it?
What's there to talk about?
We're freaks.
That's what you think?
Mom, we live in a movie screen.
People are laughing at us
and everybody thinks
we're crazy.
Who thinks we're crazy?
Name one person
who thinks we're crazy.
Everybody thinks... Dad's crazy.
Uh-huh.
Why did he do it?
Put the cowboy there?
Like most people
your father's... complicated.
I don't want him
to be complicated
and I don't want him
to be crazy.
Because if he's crazy,
then you're crazy to love him.
Abraham...
your father went halfway around
the world to fight a war...
and every minute he was there,
he was surrounded by death.
A lot of men brought that death
home with them
but not your father.
He brought life...
two lives:
yours and your sister's.
There are times, like this
afternoon with the cowboy
when your father will follow
a notion
that seems a bit nutty, maybe.
And there are times
I would like to wring his neck.
But, sweetie, that's love.
I love your father
and so do you.
Every now and then Hubert Lee
needs to be saved from himself
but that's my job.
You want to make a little wager
what side of the highway
that big ugly cowboy will be on
this time tomorrow?
No.
That's where you're smart.
♪ For goodness' sake,
I got the hippie-hippie shakes ♪
♪ Yeah, I got the shakes
♪ I got
the hippie-hippie shakes ♪
Mm-hmm.
♪ Oh! I can't sit still
♪ With the
hippie-hippie shakes... ♪
Mom, can I fly
again, please?
You'll have to
ask the Judge.
You should go up,
too, sweetie.
Flying gives you
the most astonishing feeling
of... freedom.
It's almost like
you're not really tied
to anything down here.
I like it down here.
I don't want it
to be different.
LESTER:
Whoo!
Hold on, now. Here we go!
So, was it fun?
( sighs )
I just hope
falling in love will be
as exciting as flying...
but I just know it won't.
Abraham, I'd like
to ask your opinion
about something.
Turner Knight wants to put in
a cemetery
in back of his funeral home.
For the last few months,
he's been after me
to sell him a parcel
of our land.
But you don't have
to sell it to him, do you?
Legally, no.
No, but he did do us a favor
with that lady who died
and so now he figures
I owe him.
What does Mom think?
Well, I have
to hand it to him.
He never mentioned
it to your mother.
I think you should
sell him the land.
Yes. Yes, you're
probably right.
But I can't.
Because if I do, he'll stay.
Then again, maybe I'm the one
who should give up.
Give up what?
Well, the Flamingo,
for one thing.
I mean...
more drive-ins
close down every year.
Some people say
there's no future in it
and they-they could be right.
But it's our home.
The best home in the world.
Yeah. That's true.
Dad?
Mom never liked Turner Knight,
you know.
She loves you.
Why?
Haven't you ever wondered why
your mother could love
a man like... like me?
No.
( plane whirring )
Here she comes!
She's coming back.
Of course she is.
When do you think your
husband might be willing
to discontinue his feud?
With Hubert, one... never knows.
He's nothing if not
full of surprises.
Which is...
one of the reasons I love him.
I have a confession
to make...
which shames me.
Your husband has not
hated me more than
I have hated him.
No man should
be so lucky.
I've often wondered,
Mr. Knight...
Would you call me Turner?
If I promise never
to embarrass you again
would you do me that honor?
I've often wondered, Turner
does Grace resemble
her mother?
More and more every day.
She was so...
I have been slow to understand
that for me
there will never be another.
And I take your point, Edna...
that I have been lucky, too.
Very nice.
It's very impressive.
All right, well, let me show you
how this deal works.
Step over here.
Oh, watch the wire.
Oh!
Okay, you got your two buttons.
They're marked #1.
#1.
And #2.
It's foolproof.
When you get
over the drop area,
you press #1.
That releases the
"Banner of the 10,000
Illuminations"
from this hook.
Come here. Let me show you.
Come on.
From this hook right back here.
You all see it?
Hook.
I see it.
Next, you look behind you
to make sure the banner
has been released.
Why?
I'll tell you why.
Because if it is not
released, you won't
ever touch #2.
Why?
I'll tell you why.
Because that will ignite
that son of a gun
too close to your airplane.
So, we're going to drop
a bomb on our audience.
Safer than
dropping a payload of feathers.
Provided you're up
at least 1,300 feet.
Now, I've already arranged
for the fire truck
to be on hand, just in case.
You won't need
no fire truck
as long as you stay
above 1,300 feet.
Yeah, right.
Guarantee you one thing.
Everybody looking up will swear
the sky is raining fire.
HUBERT:
Well, that's what
we want, right?
Something they'll remember
all winter long.
That way they'll come back
when we reopen next spring.
Oh, they'll remember.
Yeah, okay, thank you.
You got it?
Oh, yeah.
HUBERT:
All right.
Sure you got that?
You want to have fun?
Drop that payload
right on top
of that undertaker fellow
you don't like.
He'll think the angels
in all their glory
have come down from heaven
to fetch him on high!
HUBERT:
That would
be something.
You've done
a wonderful job.
I really want
to thank you.
EDNA:
Every now and then
Hubert Lee needs
to be saved from himself.
♪ Oh, the rules
were changed today ♪
♪ Hey! ♪
♪ I have no place to stay
♪ Thinking about the subway
♪ Hey! ♪
♪ The love has gone away
♪ My tears have come and gone
♪ Hey... ♪
♪ Time! ♪
♪ Time... ♪
Mm-hmm.
( snoring )
( movie plays in background )
ABRAHAM:
Hey, Mom!
Hey, Mom,
Alice needs some quarters.
You're just the person
I was looking for.
Abraham, hold on.
I want to talk to you.
She needs them right away.
Yesterday, in fact.
Hey, Mom?
Is everything okay?
Yes, Abraham.
Don't worry so.
Everything's fine.
Girls... order, order!
♪ Tell me again
just like you told me ♪
♪ Is it a dream or can I fly?
♪ Far beyond the far horizon
♪ Where there are
no borderlines... ♪
Girls,
four minutes to intermission.
There appears
to be an epic lack of discipline
in these environs tonight,
Jacob!
So, what are you going to do
in the off-season, Alice?
Well, it's
a sad story, Jacob
but Polly and I
are going
to have to join
the hoochy-koochy show
until the Flamingo
opens up again
in the spring.
Who'd pay to see you,
Alice?
Hey, I've got news
for you, Missy.
Five years from now
after you have made
the transition
to size 18 maternity dresses
they'll still be
chasing after me
Miss Polly-Wolly!
( laughter )
So where's Mom?
Isn't she going to help
with the rush?
Nope, she decided to go up
with the Judge.
She did?
Why?
Um, there was some
sort of problem
with the Banner of the
10,000 Illuminations.
The Judge fixed it.
Fixed it?
Actually, I think
your mother wanted
to make sure
there was no repeat
of the last fireworks
fiasco.
She wanted to make sure
that old fool
dropped his payload
over the ocean
not the funeral home.
Jacob?
♪ Time has come today
...because we have for you
a celestial conflagration
the likes of which we have
never witnessed anywhere.
Hey, Abraham,
ready for the fireworks?
Now, I want y'all to do
a little favor for me now.
I want y'all reaching up toward
the celestial lights.
Yeah, that's right!
Because what we have for you
tonight on this Labor Day
is the Banner of 10,000
Illumination Lights!
Yeah!
( amplified heartbeat )
Now, what's that?
Do you hear that?
I hear something coming...
( labored breathing )
( crowd clamoring )
There she is.
EDNA:
How beautiful it all is.
How incredibly beautiful.
HUBERT:
I hear something coming
so look to the firmament now,
ladies and gentlemen
because I give you...
the universe!
( cheering and applause )
( hammer clicks )
No!
Shh...
( sobbing )
( crowd sobbing )
( thunder rumbling )
I wonder if
I might come in.
( sniffling )
The land for the
cemetery is yours
if you still want it
and if you would allow me
to select her plot.
Yes.
Would you care to...?
Yes. Yes, thank you.
That would...
Thank you.
I don't know how to thank you,
Mr. Knight.
You have
a very, very great skill.
No, it is my sons
you wish to thank.
I could not.
Going to the funeral?
Do you want
to tell me why you knew
what was going to happen
before it did?
No.
Why don't you tell me anyway?
Want to have a little fun?
Drop that payload
Right on top of that
undertaker fella
you don't like.
He'll think the angels
in all their glory
have come down from heaven
to fetch him on high!
That would be
something.
Think about it.
EDNA:
Every now and then
Hubert Lee needs
to be saved from himself.
( heartbeat )
ABRAHAM:
When the judge fixed the wires
he must have spliced them
the wrong way.
When he pushed the button
to release the banner...
I killed her, Alice.
Oh, come here, sweetheart.
It was an accident, Jacob.
Now, you listen
to me, okay?
Listen.
I know that
it doesn't feel like it now
but one day you are going
to forgive yourself, Jacob.
And it won't be because you feel
like you deserve it.
It'll be because you realize
that your mother has
already forgiven you.
She forgave you in advance.
And there's something else
you've been wrong about, Jacob.
You've always thought
of yourself
as your father's son
but you are her son, too.
You have her faith, Jacob.
God forgives you.
Your mother forgives you...
and one day
you will forgive yourself.
Come on.
Your father needs you.
ABRAHAM:
Alice was right, of course.
With my mother gone
my father did need me
far more than I knew.
This will be a fine cemetery,
won't it, Abraham?
And this, right here
will be the finest plot.
But you do see
the problem, though.
I won't put her
in the dark, Abraham.
I can't.
If ever there was a woman
who deserved to see the sun
that woman was your mother.
ABRAHAM:
"Biology," my father always
told me when I was little
"has got nothing to do
with parenthood."
He was right.
No mother was ever more real
than mine.
I was kissed every night
and told that I was loved.
The night Edna Lee
fell from the sky
was the night Hubert T. Lee,
my real father
saw that Death had crossed
the highway, not just to
visit.
And in time,
hope rose from the ashes
of the Flamingo Drive-in
Theater...
for my father, for my sister
and yes, even for me
Abraham Jacob Lee.