[music playing]
[gasping]
[grunting]
[crying]
[gasping]
[screaming]
[music playing]
(SINGING) I want to be happy.
But I won't be happy till
I make you happy too.
Life's really worth living
when we are mirth-giving.
Why can't I give some to you?
When skies are gray and
you say you are blue,
I'll send the sun
smiling through.
I want to be happy.
But I won't be happy till
I make you happy too.
You owe it to yourself.
Bullshit, bullshit.
Oh, my part.
Bullshit.
It's all bullshit, Monica.
This is Hollywood.
Bullshit, bullshit.
JACK: The usual?
Oh, usual's fine.
[horn beeping]
Bullshit.
Oh, my part.
Here.
You owe it to yourself.
[horn beeping]
Mm.
Pure heaven.
Jack, you are a god.
JACK: What are you reading?
William Shakespeare's
"Twelfth Night."
Shakespeare, William--
1564 to 1616.
The guy could write his ass off.
Well, I'm up for
Viola in the Valley.
Is that a good part?
Well, if you took
the trouble to read
the rest of the
characters' roles,
you'd realize that Shakespeare
didn't write any bad parts.
I can barely understand
my own part, Jack.
Give me a break.
I bet you Bette Davis
knows her Shakespeare.
[ringing]
She doesn't have to.
She's already got an Oscar.
Ernie's Pagoda Lounge.
Sorry, we're closed today--
private party.
I don't care who you are.
Open tomorrow.
Hollywood.
Get a load of this.
Real beluga caviar.
Martha Anne is crazy
about it, well,
ever since she heard
Harlow orders it
by the ton from the Caspian
Sea, wherever that is.
You know you can tell
if caviar is any good?
When the eggs are
large and unbroken.
Hey, you know
what to put that on?
Leave it to, doll face.
I trust you, Jack.
Around food-- food
and mixed drinks.
I bet you say that
to all the bartenders.
Mm, I do.
And you can't imagine
how helpful it's been.
[ringing]
MAN: Hey, Martha Anne.
We need you on set.
JACK: Hey Shirl.
Shirl?
Shirley?
SHIRLEY: Not now, Jack.
Here we go again.
[gasping]
MONICA: Oh, did I
serve that lady.
I might not be
delivered to the world
till I had made my
own occasion, my love.
What my estate is?
That's cute, huh?
Yeah.
Don't fucking know
what it even means.
(RUSSIAN ACCENT)
Get me a whiskey,
a ginger ale on the side,
and don't be stingy.
How you doing, Shirley?
How am I doing?
How do I look, Jack?
Like usual.
Like a drowned rat.
What's today?
JACK: Monday.
Oh.
Been up for three days.
Pills?
Mm-hm, and booze and insomnia.
You got a cig?
Be a darling and do that again.
It's hot out there.
Insomnia.
I know what that is.
But what is it?
She doesn't know
what insomnia is, Jack.
It's nothing, honey.
Just a bunch of
sleepless nights.
So?
A person can't be expected
to know everything.
Do you know where Illyria is?
Illyria is an ancient
country on the east coast
of the Adriatic.
Shakespeare's "Twelfth
Night" was in Illyria.
I was in a production
once of "Twelfth Night."
You were in "Twelfth Night?"
What part?
Olivia.
It's a lead, isn't it?
Uh-huh.
Uh, one of the leads, yes.
SHIRLEY: That was back
in my college days
on the plains of Nebraska.
Oh.
Then it wasn't a
professional production.
SHIRLEY: Who does professional
productions of Shakespeare,
huh?
Maybe someone in England.
So, um, what
caused the insomnia?
You remember
that man, Raymond?
Raymond, Raymond--
That I was going out with.
Oh, yeah.
Raymond what's his name?
- French.
Raymond [inaudible].
Dapper.
Distinguished.
Rich.
Good looking.
23rd best-dressed
man in America.
Raymond threw me over
for another woman.
A stand-in?
A stunt woman, part-time,
over at Republic.
Ugh.
I'm sorry.
SHIRLEY: You're sorry.
Heh.
If you're sorry--
Caviar?
Beluga.
MONICA: Yeah, nothing's too good
for Martha Anne on her 30th.
She's 30 years old today, huh?
How nice for her.
MAN: Quiet!
[ringing]
MAN: Stand by for picture!
MAN: Mark it.
Action.
Let's roll a few feet.
Cut.
[ringing]
Get out of that
dress, Martha Anne.
I can't afford to
have it sweated up.
We may need it later.
Wardrobe, change it for
the next setup, will you?
We're ready, Miss Harlow.
How's life on the set, Shirl?
Our set is closed.
We're shooting "Conquest."
[laughing]
Everybody is trying to get
a glimpse of Charles Boyer
as Napoleon.
And Miss Garbo?
Contrary to popular
opinion, Miss Garbo
can be really quite affable.
Sometimes, after hours, off
the set, Miss Gustafsson--
that's her real name--
and I sit around in our
underwear, chewing the fat.
Greta cooks up a batch
of Swedish meatballs.
Jack, Miss Garbo and I have
a very healthy relationship.
I have a healthy
relationship with the woman
I work for, unlike some
people I could mention.
I'm going to pretend
you didn't say that.
You pretend anything you want.
Greta, Miss Garbo with
the bashful Valkyrie.
Mm-hm.
Here, Shirley.
You owe it to yourself.
Jack.
I have such an enormous
debt to myself,
it would take more than a
lifetime to pay it back.
Whiskey can do magic
for lonely people, Shirl.
Whiskey.
Morphine.
[inaudible]
Hi!
[cat call]
Hi.
I'm a stand-in.
I'm OK.
$16.50 every day.
Other girls are on the
street, while I'm a stand-in.
Life is sweet.
Paramount or MGM,
Warner Brothers--
all them pay our wages.
In exchange, we all look
like someone strange.
I'm a stand-in,
that's my game.
I'm not in it for the fame.
Don't call me no glamourpuss.
I'm a stand-in, marvelous.
War in Europe.
PEGGY: War in Spain.
Newsreels.
They give me a pain.
Dust bowl, unemployment too.
Honey, I got things to do.
PEGGY: Wardrobe
wants me in a gown.
Makeup thinks our
hair is too brown.
I'm not in some unwashed mob.
I'm a stand-in.
That's my job.
PEGGY: I'm a stand-in.
I'm true blue.
My profession, [inaudible].
I'm a stand-in.
I got class.
I'm a lady, bet your ass.
I'm a stand-in.
So is my pals.
We are not your average gals.
We're together, thick and thin,
proud to be a genuine stand-in.
Glad to see me, big boy?
JACK: Mm-hm.
That poem still kills me.
PEGGY: God bless you, Jack.
Me and Martha Anne knocked
out that little ditty
over a couple of dozen Gin
Rickeys and some reefer.
I wanted to call it,
Stand-ins Never Die.
Course, she calls it
Fuck this Occupation.
We never could agree.
I brought some comestibles.
Comestibles?
A lot of them.
MONICA: I know what combustibles
are, but what are they?
Food, babe.
Eats.
Vittles.
MONICA: Oh.
Miss Unaware,
that's you, honey.
MONICA: I'm not so unaware.
Aware, even.
Will you look at
these comestibles?
God!
It's [inaudible] Do you
think I'd show up to my best
friend's party empty-handed?
I don't think so.
I'd better put this
all in the kitchen.
OK, well I'll help.
OK, come on.
If you're so smart,
what's a Valkyrie?
Garbo's bashful Valkyrie.
So what is a Valkyrie?
SHIRLEY: In Norse mythology,
she's the maiden of Odin.
She conducts the souls of
dead heroes to Valhalla.
That's the Viking version
of heaven, to you.
A Valkyrie is the
chooser of the slain.
You knew that?
No.
Norse mythology.
Viking heaven.
So Garbo's the
chooser of the slain.
And you have a
healthy relationship
with the chooser of the slain?
I'm in show business, if
that's what you're driving at.
It'll be your life or mine.
And if you're
killed, I'll be free.
And if I'm killed,
it won't matter.
And if we both
die, good riddance.
So?
That was Betty
Davis in "Dangerous."
She won an Oscar for
that performance.
Did she break off a piece
of the gold statuette for you?
A foot, maybe?
I didn't stand in
for all of "Dangerous."
During part of the
shooting, I was
loaned out for another picture.
Loaned out?
You had a teensy weensy walk-on.
"And She Stayed for Breakfast."
Was that the name of it?
She was there in the morning.
She learned from sailors.
Best Actress, 1935.
She did it with her socks on.
When Betty won that
award, I was overjoyed.
Did you hear me?
Best Actress, 1935.
Oh, wasn't that the year that,
uh, Garbo made "Anna Karenina?"
I can't imagine
Miss Garbo's ever
taken home an Academy Award.
I don't imagine she cares.
But you do.
Garbo's gotten
her share of awards.
The New York Film Critics picked
her best feminine performance.
Sounds like a sanitary napkin.
That was for "Anna Karenina."
The New York Film Critics.
Think any of those saps
ever worked in the movies?
Think again, kiddo.
The Academy Awards are voted
by people who make movies--
a jury of your peers.
Maybe the bashful
Valkyrie has no peers.
Garbo will get an Oscar.
And I mean soon.
Do you hear me?
Maybe this year for "Camille."
Nobody with an ounce of
sense thinks that Garbo
will not get an Oscar.
She'll never get one--
not ever.
You're nuts!
Is that so?
SHIRLEY: You're also drunk.
Oh, so now I'm a drunk?
You fucking insomnia dope fiend.
Since when did the
city of Los Angeles
pick you to give drunk tests?
Macadamia nuts?
Came all the way
from Redondo Beach.
SHIRLEY: Practically imported.
Oh thanks, Peg.
I could use a nut right now.
Been eating caviar all day.
Get her.
Whatcha reading, doll?
"Make me a willow
cabin at your gate,
and call upon my soul
within the house.
[inaudible] loyal
cantons of condemned
love, and sing them loud
even in the dead of night.
[inaudible] your name to
the reverberate hills,
and make the babbling gossip
of the air cry out, Olivia!"
Olivia de Havilland?
Who else?
Well, the Parsons must be
the babbling gossip of the air
they're talking about, huh?
Of course.
See?
Shakespeare's not hard when
you have the right references.
Shakespeare, huh?
Knock me over with
a feather duster.
Yeah, it might be kind
of hard, Peg, or haven't
you noticed?
Huh?
Your girth, honey.
I'm talking about your weight.
I'm trying to keep
up with Miss Mae West.
Yeah.
That's what I mean.
It's that Mr. Fields,
that W. C. Fields.
There's talk of co-starring
them in a picture together.
It's made her anxious,
so she puts on weight.
He drinks.
He just got out of a sanitarium.
He came on the set, he
kissed her on the nose,
and he pinched
her on the behind,
and he called her
his little bird mare.
She thinks he's fucking nuts.
It's made her gain.
And you're gaining
right along with her.
That's what I call loyalty.
That's what I
call keeping my job.
MAN: Johnny, get that tent in.
JOHNNY: Yes sir, boss.
Incoming, right in.
[ringing]
[inaudible]
MAN: Coming through.
Martha Anne, the dress!
Fuck you!
It's my birthday!
[humming]
[giggling]
Didn't anyone ever tell you
you should be in Vaudeville?
Yeah, sure.
I was in pictures at the time.
SHIRLEY: But you were
in Vaudeville, weren't
you, little Jackie Turner?
The lively songs
and terpsichore
of little Jackie Turner.
What's terpsichore?
Dancing, kiddo.
Dancing.
Later to be replaced
by the lovely sounds
of sand dance Jack Turner.
Yes.
I was in Vaudeville for
a while there, sure.
You managed
three to about 100.
To about 100.
Did you ever play the palace?
Yeah, I played
the palace, Peggy.
SHIRLEY: In Boise, Idaho.
Anything on the radio?
Been thinking about
dance music all day.
Anything to forget about
little Jackie Turner.
[music playing]
Me?
You.
(ON RADIO) You,
Come on, Shirl.
(ON RADIO) You never
cared for me after I
gave my devotion to you.
You, you gave the air
to me, spurning a love
that was honest and true.
When I met you, I let
you fall into my heart,
just to hurt me, desert
me, and tear me apart.
[ringing]
If that's Raymond,
I haven't been here.
He's always trying to call
me up and beg my forgiveness.
Ernie's Pagoda.
Martha Anne!
It's Martha Anne.
Hey, where are you?
Oh, we're here, just
dancing, me and--
yeah, just the two of us.
Oh, uh, you coming by?
Oh, a drink or two.
I'm thinking about making it
an early one, blue Monday.
Swell, we'll see you
in a jiff, kiddo.
Did I give it away?
Think she had any suspicions?
Did she sound a Hollywood 30.
19.
Don't you just hate her.
No, I don't just hate her.
You do just hate her.
I believe you do just hate her.
SHIRLEY: Oh, you're sounding
like a Betty Davis movie again.
Martha Anne's birthday,
and she sounded so cheerful.
We'll fix that.
You should have
asked her how's
Erwin Reisner, the imminent
Erwin Reisner, the producer,
another lounge lizard.
Erwin Reisner and
Raymond Dubliet are
cut from the same snake skin.
Oh, shit.
Hey!
Do you know anything
about morphine?
Only that I'd like to try it.
Oh, god!
She's whiter than
Robert Taylor's teeth!
Oh, she's on her knees again.
She's been there before.
Ask Raymond Dubliet.
Fuck Raymond Dubliet!
She's back.
So we're in Paris.
It's my first time abroad.
And we check into this very
ritzy hotel, which happens
to be called the Ritz Hotel.
And I fall in love
with the bidet.
So I'm on the bidet, a
genuine French bidet,
with those warm jets of water
spraying their everloving way
upward to my heart--
Beautiful.
I'll say.
Raymond comes back, and I
say, "Raymond, if you really
worship me, you will
buy me something
that I can't get at home.
You will buy me a
genuine French bidet."
And he looks at me,
and he says, "Do
you know what a bidet costs?"
And I say, "Raymond,
if you really love me,
cost would be no object."
And he looks at me again,
and he says, "I got
a suggestion for you, Shirl.
Do handstands in the shower."
PEGGY: Lord Almighty,
you could hurt yourself!
He only took her
there for an abortion.
PEGGY: Sweet Jesus.
I'd never have one.
Oh yeah?
What about that
little trip to Mexico?
PEGGY: Jack, I think
it's time for a Martini.
Monica?
You ever tell anyone that I went
to Paris just for an abortion
again I will rip
every cheaply dyed
hair out of your empty head.
Twat!
Now I'm a twat.
SHIRLEY: Yeah,
now you're a twat!
Look, Shirley, if
this is about Raymond--
What about Raymond?
In case you're
wondering, I never
laid a hand on Raymond Dubliet.
Is that so?
Yeah.
What about Erwin Reisner?
You said he wasn't good
enough to write in your shoot.
Yeah?
So I lay plenty of guys I
wouldn't let write in my shoot.
Now that's an interesting
character trait.
SHIRLEY: Shut up, Jack.
What about Erwin?
For the record, I haven't
laid a hand on Erwin Reisner,
for years.
Other body parts?
I got stopped this
morning for my autograph
at Vine and Melrose.
This very cute traffic
cop said he'd see me
in "I'm No Angel" four times.
You signed
autographs as Mae West?
Four times!
And he saw me twice
in "Klondike Annie."
But I thought enough is enough.
We had cars backed up
half the way to Sunset.
Don't you think that's
a little dishonest?
Dishonest?
Lord, no.
The way I see it, Mae can't be
everywhere, but thanks to me,
she can be in two
places at once.
And the cop?
Did he give you the ticket?
PEGGY: Sweet blood Jesus, no!
He just wanted to gab.
He said, (LOW
VOICE) I'm surprised
you're not in some
big limousine.
I never expected to see Mae West
in overalls driving a Ford V8.
So I said, "Fritz."
His name was Fritz.
Fritz, I donated my limousine
to the Beverly Hills Orphanage
for the day.
And as for these
overalls, they were
a personal gift from the
late Rudolph Valentino.
And he swallowed that?
He said, (LOW VOICE)
you knew Valentino?
I said, intimately.
It was the only way to know him.
So he said, (LOW
VOICE) well, wait
till I tell the little woman.
So I said, you know,
you win, Fritz.
I gotta go make a movie.
And with that, I
drove away, and left
him standing there
at the intersection,
admiring his four
Mae West autographs.
I don't think that
young police officer
will soon forget meeting someone
he believes to be a star.
You, uh, you should
have signed autographs
as Rudolph Valentino.
That would have made his day.
Peggy can't even
spell Valentino.
PEGGY: I can't
even spell Rudolph.
Peg, you have no
sense of yourself,
no sense of who you really are.
JACK: Monica.
No, let me finish.
Sorry.
You completely bury yourself
into an entirely different
woman's identity, a woman
who's carving out her own image
and has forged her
own successful career.
And she can sign
her own autographs.
You ain't Mae West, Peggy.
You never will be.
That traffic cop
thought I was Mae.
I don't see that there
was any harm done.
Not to him, anyway.
Oh.
I know who's stand-in you are.
Takes one to know one, huh?
We're like dogs
of the same breed.
We've got to sniff
each other out.
Hey, how'd you like
to come to a party?
You think I'd fit in?
Right down to the slacks.
Yeah, you're gonna
fit in just fine.
What's today?
Is it Monday?
JACK: Only for 24 hours.
I have a birthday
party to go to Monday.
You're at the party.
This is the party, Shirl.
Good.
I thought I'd miss it.
(SINGING) Tramp, tramp,
tramp, ze boys are marching.
Cheer up, comrades.
They come.
JACK: Hey, Rhonda.
Did you hitch or bus it?
- No.
My new friend drove me
over in her Duesenberg.
It's OK.
I know you didn't mean it.
PEGGY: So much nicer
when you're friends.
RHONDA: Christ, I
could use a drink.
JACK: One Martini coming up.
Jack, you know
what a girl wants.
So where is your
friend in the new Duesy?
Parking.
[music playing]
(SINGING) Oh they [inaudible]
that I couldn't do
with plenty of money and you.
[inaudible] worry, that money
dream, just a [inaudible]
buy a lot of things.
Hi.
I'm Taffy, Taffy Entwistle.
Hi, Taffy.
This is Monica and
Shirley and Miss Peggy.
Welcome.
Oh, thanks.
And the inimitable Jack.
I had a sister named Peg once.
One Hayworth Martini
coming right up.
Her real name was Lillian.
But everybody called her Peg.
Well, mine's Pegine.
What happened to her?
She died.
Oh, I'm sorry.
She's in a better place.
JACK: You do look like Hayworth.
Do I?
Thanks, Jack.
Here.
Anyone that looks as much
like Hayworth as you do
owes it to herself.
I always wanted to
look like somebody.
Are you from back
East like Miss Hayworth?
Me?
I'm from back nowhere,
a little town in Wyoming
called Beach City.
I never could figure out why
they called it that, though.
JACK: No beach?
None.
Maybe they named it after
somebody, a Mr. Beach.
The local newspaper
was called the Sand Flea.
You figure it out.
I can't.
The important thing
is you grew up there.
TAFFY: The important thing is I
grew up to be exactly five feet
7 and 1/2 inches,
the precise height
of one Miss Rita Hayworth.
A million girls
come to Hollywood,
but I was just
right, the right bone
structure, the right coloring.
I saw every one
of her pictures.
I was scared silly the day
that I got on the Greyhound.
Hollywood was like a
place out of a storybook.
Yeah?
What storybook have
you been reading?
A place with a beach, anyhow.
You wouldn't be having fun
with me, now, would you, Jack?
Doll face?
You couldn't pass the physical.
I don't mind being
the butt of a good joke.
I just don't want to
be a laughingstock.
Oh, you're in the
wrong profession, girlie.
TAFFY: I don't feel
that way at all.
I've been here a whole month,
and everyone's been so nice.
May 6, the day that Zeppelin,
the Hindenburg exploded--
If only we could get
the bags of hot air
here in Hollywood to explode.
I know she's Greta
Garbo, but honestly,
does she had to be so negative?
Don't worry about
Shirley, honey.
She's been up since Friday
painting the town bloodshot.
You know what I mean?
JACK: May 6 to June 6--
barely one cycle of
the moon, and you're
driving your very
own Duesenberg.
Barely one menstrual cycle.
MONICA: Yeah, Shirley's periods
last about 29 days a month.
SHIRLEY: Yes, so
don't fuck with her.
MONICA: Some flivver
you got parked outside.
That's not my car.
I borrowed it from props.
From props?
Entwistle' an unusual name.
Is it German?
English.
Like, maybe
Scotch-Irish or Welsh.
Got a little of
all of them in me.
Yeah, I've had a little
of all of them in me, too.
Me, too.
JACK: Monica's known for
her discerning taste in men.
That depends on the man.
TAFFY: A month's
not a long time.
And I managed to land a
job that's a real plum.
Could have happened to any
girl that looked like me.
Anyone who looked like Rita
Hayworth, don't you mean?
Oh wait, Jack.
I'd rather have a tequila.
Make it a triple with a hunk of
lime and a fist full of salt.
You are a regular cowgirl.
Cowboy, you mean.
- Damn mirror's cracked.
- Who gave you that?
Raymond?
I wish.
He didn't give me crap.
Oh, am I shiny?
Yeah.
You know what it is ride
around all day with your tits
strapped down under your
corset and your hair pinned up
on your hat?
Standing in is a breeze compared
to stunt work out in public.
Raymond Dubliet.
JACK: Oh god, no.
Pardon me.
Are you the refined
young lady who
lured away my gentleman friend?
Do you want me to say I am?
Thursday night, Raymond and
I were at the Brown Derby.
He got up to make a phone call.
He was calling you, wasn't he?
I don't recall receiving
a phone call that night.
When he came back
from that phone call,
he was informing me
that he was going
to throw me over for a
horse acrobat at Republic.
Walter Pigeon was
that the next table.
Norma Shearer was
two seats away.
And I don't mean their
fucking stand-ins.
He told me how tall you
were, all about your hair.
He didn't tell me you
were so goddamn pretty.
So goddamn young.
Excuse me.
I'm just going to dash
off to the ladies' room.
Ugh!
RHONDA: Taffy!
Are you OK?
I'm OK.
Just don't plan to
have children with him.
You get back here, Shirley.
I'm gonna twist your tits off.
Waiting for that.
Oh yeah?
Ladies,
- Please--
- No, no, no, Jack.
I just wiped
the floor, please!
Just sit down.
And I'll tear her
vocal cords out.
She'll never speak
baritone again.
Come on. (SINGING)
Who's hopping in a Honda?
She never told
her love, but let
consume it like a worm in the
bud, feed on her damask cheek.
She pined in thought, green
and yellow melancholy.
She sat, like patience on a
monument, smiling at people.
Is this not love indeed?
We men may seem [inaudible].
But indeed, that shows
I'm more than will.
But still, we may
prove much in our vows
but little in our love.
That's Viola's speech
from "Twelfth Night."
Everyone in LA knows
this fucking play.
JACK: It's been
around for centuries.
SHIRLEY: Viola had
a few good lines,
but Olivia was really
the one who could dress.
MONICA: Olivia was the lead.
Even in Nebraska, I had
gowns that could kill.
If you'll excuse me, I
really do need to touch up.
Think I'll do some
touching up, too.
Jack!
MONICA: Shirl, come out.
Shirl, come out.
Get out of here, Monica!
[slam]
MONICA: You're breaking
my fucking heart.
TAFFY: Jack, you
make a fine tequila.
I love the way salt tastes on
the webby part of your hand.
You know, between your
thumb and forefinger?
What do they call them?
The webby part.
Let me see your hand.
You read palms?
I love all that
metaphysical stuff.
Got a Ouija and everything.
Do you believe in reincarnation?
Nah.
This is it.
This is all you're
ever gonna get.
Did you know that men
and women are different?
Hell, I grew up in
Wyoming with animals.
There's no need for
the birds and bees talk
when you're around sheep
and cows and cowboys.
No, I mean the hands.
Oh.
MONICA: See how
the index finger is
longer than the third finger?
TAFFY: You mean the ring finger?
MONICA: Yeah.
For men, it's generally
the other way around.
It is?
The index finger is usually
the same length or even
shorter than the ring finger.
You read that in
Ripley or something.
Naw, it's true.
Does everybody knows this?
I didn't.
Guy named Erwin Reisner
told me about it.
It was this little game
he used to play in bed,
you know, like morning after?
He'd take your hand, and
he'd hold it up to his.
And then he'd show you how
the fingers didn't match up.
It was kind of a
ritual with him.
He'd always do that.
You mean every time
you slept with him?
Hmph, no-- with
different girls.
Erwin Reisner, huh?
Yeah.
Remember that name.
I guess you knew
him pretty well.
No.
I was 18.
Took me right off the
20th Century Limited.
Everything I had read
or heard about Hollywood
was right there, right in
front of me, just waiting.
And before you knew it, we were
playing footsie, and handsie
and everything elsie.
Ain't that just like a man?
Take advantage of a poor,
sweet, innocent young girl?
Oh, I was.
And probably from
a good neighborhood.
Hell's Kitchen, honey.
I wish I were from
someplace glamorous, like you.
10th Avenue and 44th?
That's about as
glamorous as the Argon.
There are no
party decorations--
no balloons, no
streamers, no nothing.
Well, 30's a tricky age
for someone who's standing
in for a 26-year-old actress.
30's a tricky age
for any actress.
32, in fact--
1905.
I saw her passport when
she hopped down to Havana.
That makes her a full six
years older than the fucking
star she's standing in for.
Gosh.
Where's Havana?
Cuba, honey.
Cuba.
Were a gent can fix
his lady's problems.
Oh, that problem.
Yep.
Oh, god!
The sign!
Where the hell is Martha Anne?
Fuck this.
Hey there, blue eyes.
How you doing?
Don't call me blue eyes.
I don't have blue eyes.
Well you ought to, doll.
One of these days, the Swedish
swan is going to need them.
Just two words for you, Shirl.
Techni-- color.
Those two words
don't scare me.
I'm not afraid of Technicolor,
which is one word, by the way.
Hm.
No?
SHIRLEY: No.
So what if I don't have
Greta Garbo's eyes?
Nobody has Garbo's eyes.
Calma started by
projecting red and green.
Technicolor is a
process that suits me.
Those have always been
my colors, red and green.
Stop and go.
Mostly go.
Now our boy Jack here, is
living in little Jackie Turner's
scope, a process developed
at the Palace Theater
in Boise, Idaho, a process
that only Jack sees,
where they take black
and white and turn it
into a blue riddance,
mm, like they did
in "A Midsummer Night's Dream."
What fools these mortals be?
That's why Jack and I
will always be friends,
because he knows about tinting,
and I know about red and green.
So don't call me blue eyes.
They're hazel.
And no.
I'm not afraid of Technicolor.
[ringing]
I'll get it.
Quick, it's Martha Anne!
Help me put these
candles on the cake!
Quickly!
Ernie's Pagoda Lounge.
Oh, it's you.
I can't really talk right now.
The car is fine.
Turn on the radio?
Why?
All right, all right.
PEGGY: OK, for God's
sake, everybody,
please try to be nice to her.
And Shirley, do you
think you could pretend
to be pleased to see her?
Please?
SHIRLEY: I'll be
good, like usual.
MAN (ON RADIO): We
interrupt this program
for a special bulletin.
PEGGY: Happy birthday!
MONICA: Hey glamourpuss!
Martha Anne, happy birthday!
MAN (ON RADIO): --and
one on [inaudible]
--opposite Gable
in "China Seas."
But Kansas City native,
born Harlene Carpenter,
succumbed just before noon
today to a cerebral edema
in Los Angeles's Good
Samaritan Hospital.
With her at her bedside where
her mother, and the actor,
William Powell.
Repeating our
bulletin, Jean Harlow,
the blonde bombshell of the
silver screen, is dead at 26.
I need a drink.
I just worked with her
this morning, you know,
on-- on "Saratoga?"
Violet-- that's
Jean's makeup lady.
Sometimes she does
my makeup, too.
Violet told me that the baby--
that's what Violet calls her--
had a premonition
last week sometime.
Anyhow, Violet was
sponging off her face,
and Harlow looked at
her, and said, "Violet?
I have a feeling
I'm going someplace
and I'm never coming back."
Violet thought she
was talking about Palm
Springs or maybe even Europe.
You ever had a
premonition, Jack?
My premonitions were all
about my Hollywood career.
Never coming back.
That sounds really final.
You think she knew?
TAFFY: I believe it.
I really do.
Who the hell are you?
Taffy.
I'm Taffy.
She's Hayworth's new stand-in.
Another one?
Harlow never shared any
her premonitions with me.
Hell, I don't do her makeup.
All I do is stand in her shadow.
Then I stand in her light.
Then I sit down while
Harlow does her scene.
Martha Anne's my name, honey--
just Martha Anne.
TAFFY: Martha
Anne's a nice name.
You think so, huh?
Well, it's a name straight out
of Lake Charles, Louisiana.
All of us are called by
two names down there.
It's a part of their French
tradition or Napoleonic code
or something.
But--
In my case, it was different.
Three years before I
was born, my father
had already taken
a powder for Panama
or some other
equatorial paradise,
and left mom a pair of twins.
There was a fire.
Nobody knows how it started.
There wasn't anybody
there when it ignited,
except those baby twins.
When rescue workers
found them, they thought
they were burnt rag dolls.
Oh, sweet Jesus.
They were my sisters.
My mother had been out
all night conjuring
me up with some truck driver--
was a produce truck, I think.
And I was born 30
years ago today--
June 7, 1907.
My mother hated me
from that day onward.
Soon as I could walk, she would
drag me through the cemetery,
pull me along by the hand
through the tombstones.
I can still remember how
that soft earth would crunch
beneath my feet,
until we'd arrive
at those two tiny matching
headstones for two baby girls--
Martha and Anne.
My momma would stick my nose
in the soft earth of those two
tiny plots and say, "Martha
Anne, if they hadn't died,
you wouldn't be alive."
Martha Anne?
My momma had christened
me Martha Anne.
She used to force my hand into
the engraving on the tombstones
and make me trace their names.
"If they had lived, you
wouldn't have a soul."
She'd make me pray for their
salvation, a special prayer
she had concocted,
offering up my chance
at heaven in
exchange for theirs,
a prayer for their eternal life.
I had to pray that my soul
would be damned to hell
if it meant heaven
for Martha and Anne.
It was a two-for-one deal.
Momma wasn't sure
God would buy it,
but she kept me
praying for 16 years.
I don't know what to say.
Yes you do.
All of you know it.
It's like you were
born to be a stand-in.
MARTHA ANNE: Jack,
Harlow's dead, but alive
forever in the
memory of her fans,
a legend, the platinum blonde.
Me?
I'm really dead.
If it wasn't for
Erwin, my very own man,
a rotten snake, but all
mine, I really would
think about killing myself.
Oh, God!
I look like death.
I didn't even
realize I was crying.
This one's going to
require major surgery.
Back in a jiff.
JACK: You think Shirley's right?
About what?
About me.
I mean, all that little
Jackie Turner scope.
What do you think?
Maybe there is some
process only I can see.
She hit a nerve.
Yeah-- the one in her arm.
Yes, but in wine
there is truth.
Think that goes for dope, too?
Well, don't they make
truth serum with morphine?
Suppose I do see things
that nobody else can.
Sweet blood Jesus, Jack.
You're supposed to be the
normal one around here.
I'm counting on you to
hold this mess together
until we can all go
home and just forget
this night ever happened.
Jack!
Some party, huh?
Where's Monica?
She went to the valley.
She had a callback
on "Twelfth Night."
Yeah, that's what she said.
You think Monica lied
about her callback?
Oh, maybe.
Why would she lie?
Because she's a fucking
stand-in, that's why.
PEGGY: She doesn't
always talk like one.
Well, no.
No, because Monica fancies
herself as an actress.
She's ashamed of
being a stand-in.
Viola's a swell part.
I played it once, back home
at the Neptune Theater.
Figures.
Say, who was that
call you took from?
The call.
You know the one,
the one where someone
told you to put on the radio?
Nobody.
Nobody?
Nobody just called and told
you to put on the radio?
Could that nobody's name be
Raymond Dubliet, possibly?
Rhonda, please.
Well, you told
me on the way over,
Taffy, that you and
Raymond were through.
And I've never heard of
props sending out Duesenbergs
like they were lipsticks.
And Raymond has an
office on the lot, so--
Come on, Rhonda.
You know me.
Yeah, I think
I'm beginning to.
PEGGY: You're new.
We could use some fresh
blood around here.
We used to have Joan Crawford.
Ugh.
PEGGY: She loved
to needle people.
I'd sit here,
drinking my Martini,
doing my nails peacefully,
and she'd needle me.
Yeah.
Shirl finally threw her down
a flight of stairs, huh Shirl?
Selznick lot, stage eight.
You're an unusual girl.
Am I?
I always wanted to be.
You're not half as
naive as she pretends.
Hey, can I ask you a question?
Shoot, honey.
What's "Saratoga" about?
PEGGY: It's a racetrack
picture from Metro.
Gable and Harlow
and Martha Anne--
maybe they'll try to finish it.
It's not finished?
It's what the town's saying.
TAFFY: Town.
Isn't it a city yet?
Never will be.
OK.
So it's not finished.
Harlow's not available.
What do they do now?
Well, if they have most
of her closeups in the can,
they might be able
to shoot around her.
And if they don't
have all her closeups?
They could shoot
some over-the-shoulder
shots using a double.
What would this
double have to do?
PEGGY: Just stand there and
look like Harlow from the back.
Would she have to
be the same height?
I suppose not,
for those shots.
She could be any height.
And she could dye
her hair or wear a wig,
if it wasn't already platinum.
Honey, no one on
God's green earth
is born with hair
Harlow's color.
What about the long shots?
Those would be harder to fake.
You'd need someone
with Harlow's frame.
Martha Anne can do it.
She's in no shape
to do anything.
She'll recover.
Sweetheart, don't
even think about it.
I'm just gathering
information.
You're five inches too tall.
I could crouch.
Your figure doesn't go
in and out like Harlow's.
It's all curvy like Hayworth's.
Just curious.
Is Martha Anne talented?
She's tried singing,
dancing, acting.
There's no beginning
to that girl's talent.
TAFFY: My father used
to say that birds don't
fly because they have wings.
They have wings
because they fly.
Martha Anne has no wings.
I thought so.
Did you?
Yes.
Instantly.
How perceptive.
You must think I'm awful.
But I see a real
chance for myself--
a real opportunity.
I could be in "Saratoga."
I could be noticed.
No one's ever going
to see me standing in.
I could do that my whole life.
When I die, they wouldn't
even print my obituary.
Who wants to read about an
ex-stunt girl turned stand-in?
But if they put
me in "Saratoga,"
it could lead to something.
I'd be the girl who saved
Harlow's last performance.
I'd be in pictures.
I'd be a movie star
with my own stand-in.
You heard me do Viola's speech.
Maybe-- just maybe,
I've got wings.
I know I'm nothing.
But with God's help,
and a little luck,
I just might rise above
my station and amount
to something.
"Saratoga's"
Martha Anne's job.
And no one's taking her place.
Understand?
[music playing]
It's gonna rain again.
Jack, I-- I need to
tell you something.
You have a confession to make?
How did you know?
Just part of the job, kiddo.
Just part of the job.
TAFFY: Monica didn't go to
the Valley for any call-back.
That call she got had nothing
to do with Shakespeare.
Monica's call came from Metro.
I think it was the director, or
at least one of his assistants.
He wants Monica to test
for Harlow's replacement
in "Saratoga."
[slam]
Why the hell would MGM hire
Monica to stand in for Harlow?
They already have
a Jean Harlow--
Martha Anne.
Platinum blonde, baby
blues, strange ass--
besides, she's under contract.
Come on, Jack.
Let's go inside before
we get drenched.
Get me a whiskey, baby,
ginger ale on the side.
And don't be stingy.
Where's Rhonda?
When Dietrich
calls, Rhonda runs.
Her master's voice.
PEGGY: Are you all right?
I'm fine.
You're the new stand-in.
I remember.
I haven't actually
started yet.
My star's away on vacation.
But as soon as she
gets back, we're going
right into our first film.
You have nice skin,
nice bones, a good height.
You're lucky-- a
lucky little liar!
Excuse me?
Oh, don't get upset.
We're stand-ins.
We can talk to each other.
Have you ever seen Jean Harlow?
TAFFY: Um, "Red Dust," "China
Seas," "Hold Your Man,"
"Wife First," "His
Secretary," all of them.
No, I mean in person.
You mean in real life?
No.
I stood in for her on
all of those pictures,
every one you named.
You know what dead is?
Dead is you can't work anymore.
Jean Harlow can't work anymore!
I'm sorry about Miss Harlow.
Well, that's very
kind of you to say.
You're very young.
I'm 19.
19?
19.
At 19, I was--
Now I'm 30 years old.
You still look 19.
MARTHA ANNE: Shut up!
Just shut the fuck up!
Why did you call me a liar?
Right there is a ladies room.
And in that lovely little
toilet is a window,
a skimpy little screen window.
Let me tell you something, kid.
No one but no one is taking
Harlow's place in "Saratoga--"
not while I'm alive!
Got that?
Look, I'm new.
I'm just starting out.
I don't know anything.
Oh, you're starting
out and I'm ending up?
Is that what you think?
No.
I'm just confused.
Huh.
A stand-in, confused?
You're very beautiful.
I bet you have guys
eating out of your hand.
No, nothing like that.
A boyfriend?
I've only been here a month.
It would take a girl like you
about one hour in this town.
I'm here to work.
I got a man.
He's a perfect bastard.
Look, I know you're upset.
He's good to me
once in a while.
When he got me pregnant he
took me on vacation to Havana.
I'm sorry I said those things
before, about "Saratoga."
And I'm sorry you overheard.
If they're gonna
finish "Saratoga,"
they'll be giving me a ring--
not Monica, not you,
not anyone else.
Me!
(WHISPERING) I'm
sorry I offended you.
I'd like to be friends.
We're stand-ins.
Can't we be friends?
I'll shake your hand.
I'll buy you a drink.
Oh!
Did you know that men
and women are different?
See how your ring finger is
longer than your index finger?
Well, with men, it's
the other way around.
Their index finger is the same
length, or maybe even longer.
You're fucking my boyfriend!
[gunshot]
[gasp]
SHIRLEY: Jesus Christ!
Oh god, no.
SHIRLEY: Oh, my god.
Martha Anne!
Don't give me an
excuse, Shirley.
I never liked you, anyway.
Martha Anne!
MARTHA ANNE: I do
like you, Jack.
But I got another
bullet in here.
Don't make me kill you, too.
Two bullets like
two sleeping babies.
Get against that
wall, all of you!
My mother gave me this gun when
I was 16, still a little girl.
But that's not how
the boys acted.
Momma thought I needed
protection, a Derringer,
a lady-like weapon, two bullets,
enough to do the job, two
sleeping twins, all snug in
their own little chambers,
Martha and Anne, snug in
their own little coffins.
Jean Harlow understood.
I'm going away from here,
and I'm never coming back.
JACK: Martha Anne, don't!
PEGGY: Martha Anne,
please don't do it!
MONICA: I got the part!
No!
[gunshot]
[screaming]
SHIRLEY: Monica!
[inaudible] didn't need me.
Maybe, maybe I'm dead!
JACK: Martha Anne!
PEGGY: Get me the police.
SHIRLEY: Monica.
Hey, is there a cop
named Fritz there?
Gimme that.
Yeah, it's Ernie's.
We got a bar over
on Santa Monica.
Yeah, we need an
ambulance, a Hearse,
a couple of boys from homicide,
and the coroners, as fast
as you can.
Yeah.
Best reading I ever did,
and no one was filming it.
Oh, Martha Anne.
[crying] Ow.
Monica, you're
not going to die.
You just got a shot in the arm.
Ow.
[sirens]
- Oh, I'm sorry.
- Ow.
Ow.
OK, we're getting someone.
She's all right.
[tires squealing]
Yeah Ernie, I
know the lecture.
I know how life is.
Yeah, bad publicity.
I know.
I know murder is
bad for business.
I still say the Pagoda
should stay open.
No, I know how it works.
No, no, no, no.
You talk to him.
If he comes to his
senses, thank him for me.
Ernie, we owe it to ourselves.
OK.
Sure is dead around here.
MONICA: I know.
They suspended work
for one whole minute
in memory of Harlow.
11:00 to 11:01.
Mm.
So tell me what happened.
You should've seen
the look on Erwin's face
when I walked
through his office.
Erwin Reisner?
He didn't believe that
I had the balls to do it.
PEGGY: Neither did I.
So his secretary announced
me like I was royalty,
Eleanor Roosevelt to somebody.
And I looked him right
in the baby blues.
I could read his
smarmy little mind.
(LOW VOICE) What
does this bitch want?
But it came out, "Why
Monica, what a surprise."
So I said, "Don't get up, Erwin.
I just need a tiny
little favor."
So I put on my
best fuck me pout--
you know the one.
I do.
Martha Anne needs a lawyer.
And you know, Erwin runs
with all the big shots.
So he gives me a name.
PEGGY: You got
Martha Anne a lawyer?
[ringing]
Uh-huh.
Well, let me tell you
I spent my morning--
at the morgue.
Sweet Jesus, it's like
a Frigidaire down there.
And the morgue attendant
was wearing a fur coat.
And there she was, Taffy, laying
there like a smoked trout.
They asked me, "Is
this Taffy Entwistle?"
All I could do was just nod.
That's all it took.
She was identified.
And no Raymond Dubliet?
Not at the morgue, not at
the train depot, nowhere--
but he did send two guys
to pick up his Duesenberg.
Guys like that use girls
like us like tissue paper.
[whistle]
Jack!
Jack?
What are you doing here?
Job interview, [inaudible],,
assistant choreographer.
Did you get it?
Ah, this is showbiz, Peg.
I'll believe it
when I'm on the set.
Oh, ah.
Well, I spent the
morning at the morgue.
Oh, I found this.
I found this in Taffy's pocket.
"Variety, September 20, 1932--
the [inaudible] actress
Peg Entwistle, suicide.
Peg Entwistle, legitimate
actress who had slight picture
experience, was found dead in
the hills back of Hollywood
this morning by a pedestrian.
According to the police, she
had evidently jumped off the H
on the Hollywood sign.
With her was found this note--
afraid I am a coward, and
I'm worried for many things.
If only I would have
done this long ago,
I could've saved a lot of pain."
Taffy's sister.
Exactly.
[sigh]
What do you want to do?
Martini.
Let's get a drink!
Leave it to me.
To Taffy and Harlow.
May god welcome them to
the kingdom of heaven,
for eternal bliss,
salvation, and joy.
Hey, Rhonda.
Hey, Peg.
How's Deitrich, Rhonda?
Taffy.
God, I really loved her.
If only I could have been
here, I could have saved her.
You'd be dead.
Yeah, but you
ever meet someone,
and you just love them?
And maybe you have a
relationship, maybe
you don't-- it doesn't matter.
You love them anyway, and
you love them forever.
You hardly knew her.
[cat call]
JACK: Mm, wow.
Make it a Coke, Jack.
PEGGY: She's being
a good girl tonight.
SHIRLEY: Well, I'm
doing it for my health.
RHONDA: Health?
Shirl, your liver
expired with a repeal.
And that lovely set of matched
hypodermics in your purse?
Gone.
That easy?
Hell.
See, first you take
a vial of morphine,
and then you take a
vial of distilled water,
and for every amount of
morphine that you take out,
you replace it with water,
and soon it's all over.
Well, I mean, except for
the retching your guts out
and the not sleeping
for 72 hours.
But I think--
I think more clearly now.
And I see better, too.
And what do you see?
The future, Jack.
Let's get out of here.
You owe it to yourself.
PEGGY: Yeah, Jack.
Come on.
You're gonna get that job.
Come on, Jack.
Well, I'm a stand-in.
I'm OK.
16.50 every day.
Other girls are on the streets.
I'm a stand-in.
Life is sweet.
Paramount or MGM, Warner
Brothers-- all of them.
Come on, Jack!
I'm coming.
By, Ernie's!
They never did have
good Chinese food, anyway.
[music playing]
(SINGING) I want to be
happy, but I won't be happy
till I make you happy too.
Life's really wroth living
when we are mirth-giving.
Why can't I give some to you?
When skies are gray, and
you say you are blue,
I'll send a sun smiling through.
I want to be happy,
but I won't be happy
till I make you happy too.