( cat meows )
This one's unlocked.
( telephone rings )
Willis and Martha can't
come to the phone now.
Please leave a message.
( beep )
Hey, Willis,
it's your wake-up call.
Willis, get up.
Are you listening to me?
Huh?
See you in the bubble.
Yeah, o.k.
( tape rewinding )
( woman's voice )
Willis, I'd tell you
this in person,
but as you say,
I have a fear
of confrontation.
I'm leaving you.
I need to find myself,
and traveling around
the world is the answer.
So I took the $5,000
from your account.
I'll pay you back
when I can.
I hope you're not mad.
Since you're
a psychologist,
you'll understand
this is nothing personal,
just something I have to do.
Goodbye.
( beep )
( car engine starts )
You're late.
So shoot me
and put me out
of my misery.
( click )
Aah!
Heh heh heh heh.
You're crazy.
You know that?
Is that
your professional opinion?
Heh heh heh heh.
You should've
seen your face.
Ha ha ha ha!
Opening one.
This do anything
for anybody?
Lyle?
I was up all night.
Ask Harry.
You weren't up all night.
You snored all night.
O.K., anybody?
Give it up.
Nobody wants
to be here.
Well, maybe that's why
they call it prison.
If you were
a better shrink,
we'd all be
out by now.
Aha! O.K., there's
something right there.
Now, what's
he doing, huh?
Come on, everybody.
He's blaming his problems
on somebody else.
Somebody else put us
in here, Willis.
If you were good,
you'd be on Park Avenue
listening to some
rich bitch's sex life.
Not all therapists
are into money.
Only assholes
don't want money.
You can be happy
without money.
You happy?
You look like shit.
Thank you. Today is
an exception, O.K.?
My girlfriend
moved out on me.
Oh.
Aw!
Ooh!
I can get
her legs broke.
Hey, put that away.
( glass shatters )
Take it easy!
The guy's heart's broke.
I got a theory
about your temper.
You're trying to be tougher
than your brother.
He is.
I met his brother.
He's chicken shit.
Just because
you had college
for four months
doesn't make you
a genius!
Can we talk about
something else,
please?
You going to
pick up that glass?
Here. Tell us
what you see.
O.K.
Well, I see
a bunch of guys
trying to avoid
talking about themselves.
( coughing )
Tricks, you O.K.?
Oh, this cancer's
starting to win.
The doctor said two weeks,
maybe three.
Oh, God, I heard.
There. Just don't
burn down the place.
I want to tell you
a story.
It's about a job
five of us pulled
back in '57.
We ripped off the mob
for $8 1/2 million.
I want you to go get it.
( coughs )
Wait a minute.
You're talking about
stolen money, right?
Willis, it was stolen
even before we took it.
Came from
a casino skim bank.
You know what that is.
Oh...yeah.
I'm the only one alive
who knows where the money is.
You're my best friend.
I want you to go
and get it.
Keep half for yourself
and give half
to Louise Bump.
Here...sweet Louise.
She still writes to me.
Oh, good. Let me
think about it.
Don't think about it.
Do it.
Don't be stuck
in this dead-end job.
Do something real
for once.
Dig down 7 feet
in the basement of a house
in Cherry Hill.
It was new then.
Jack Sausegal's
concrete company
did the neighborhood.
He poured a foundation
over it the same day.
He drew three circles
in a triangle
in the cement.
Dig there.
73...22...
Pleasant Street.
Willis...
this is my last request.
732...4
Oh!
You promised it to me
on our anniversary!
I did not. You're lying!
I did not!
Yes, you did!
I never--
No!
( bells ring )
We'll never finish
our book at this rate.
How can we work
when they're screaming?
Maybe sitting at
our desks would help.
We still need a title.
Maybe something with
the word "sex" in it.
Look at Jessie's house.
What's he saying?
Lydia,
I don't read lips.
Oh, now she's crying.
He's a bastard.
Give me those!
We should be working.
You started this.
Norm and Peedi
are having
cold cereal again.
Talk about boring.
Chews
with his mouth open.
Swallow that, Norm.
My God.
Ouch.
He's going
to murder her.
He's got a chain saw!
I'll call the police.
Call Marty Rollins.
Marty the realtor?
Why him?
( arguing continues )
I'm calling the police.
This spoon is dirty,
Peedi.
I don't think we should
get involved, pumpkin.
Thank you.
Mm-hmm.
Let Jeffrey and Lydia
handle it.
They're probably monitoring
the whole thing anyway.
Aah!
No! No!
Oh, no!
Aah!
You wanted half,
you got your half!
I cut. You choose.
You're a psychopath!
Any man who could destroy
a beautiful piano--
( doorbell chimes )
Albert,
meet the Colangelos--
Jim, Jean,
Jerry,
and Jillian.
So, Jessie
here?
Ha! Hi,
Jess, babe.
We'll start
in the breezeway
and work our way back.
By the way, that is
a rare split piano.
It's going to
the Museum of Modern Art
next month.
I'll show you
a breakfast nook that'll
take your breath away.
Come this way.
That is
a beautiful dress.
I love the color.
It brings out the blue
in your eyes.
Jess, babe?
How could you
use Marty Rollins?
He hasn't
sold a house
in three years!
And he's
a sex fiend.
Some of us are loyal
to our friends.
Besides, he's getting help
for his problem.
No. He's beyond help.
He's a maniac!
Look who's talking.
( electrical buzzing )
Huh?
Aah!
You done
your homework,
Marvin.
Like my mama taught me.
You take care
of Willis Embry?
Uh, that's for sure.
Ohh!
( paper bag rips )
Oh...
Shit!
Aah!
( sirens )
I saw him go upstairs
with his groceries.
I'm sure he was inside.
He was always inside.
Lady, there was
nothing identifiable
in that room.
He was a good neighbor,
never bothered anyone.
That's because he had
a very boring life.
When he sang
in the shower--
What a horrible voice!
That's not grounds
for murder, though.
Ask Norm if I should
up my asking price
to offset the lower
interest rate.
Uh, should Jessie
up her asking price
to offset...
the interest rate?
That'll increase
the value of our
place, muffin.
Tell her yes.
Yes.
How much?
I'll ask him.
Let me talk to him.
Oh, Jess, he just
went to, uh, work.
7-3-2-0, right?
Yeah.
Are you sure?
Yeah, I'm sure.
73-20. Drive in here.
All right.
Now, gentlemen,
I don't remember
asking--huh?
Shut your trap.
How's that tape
working out?
Fine. Just the
thought of exercise
makes me tired.
Oh, now,
you're just depressed.
Things will get better.
Really.
Why doesn't anyone
on that tape sweat?
Maybe it doesn't
photograph well.
How about you?
I just wear
the clothes.
You're making
a mistake!
I got to go.
Let me tell you
something--
Try sh--
P-p-please...
that's a Fabrizzi.
Oh, yeah?
They finished it off.
What do you mean?
The basement.
It's a rumpus room.
They got
a big-screen TV,
jukebox, VCR.
Any good tapes?
Gone with the Wind,
Last Picture Show,
Casablanca--
Casablanca?
Is your version
black and white
or colorized?
I think Ted Turner is
making a big mistake,
don't you?
The floor!
What's on
the floor?
Linoleum. I think
it's Armstrong.
Rip it up. Mmm!
Mmm!
Shut your mouth!
Mmm mff mmm!
Shut up!
Just as soon
shoot you
as look at you.
Is he always
this edgy?
Take a look at this.
I did not think
he'd kill him.
I really have to
talk to him, Lyle.
Hey, I wouldn't
do that.
He's very sensitive
about being
criticized.
He's on medication.
Did you put down
that linoleum?
Mmm mff hmmf...
Ma'am, did you see
three circles
in the cement?
And
a triangle?
Uh-uh.
We can rip up the whole
goddamn floor.
We don't know
anything about--
I can't understand
you, mush mouth.
Speak up.
We don't know anything
about circles.
You liar.
Hey, Marvin,
Marvin, easy.
Now, we can
use them.
Can I talk to you
for a minute?
Marvin,
just look at this--
Thank you.
Don't contradict
me in front
of the hostages.
I didn't.
You know,
it's embarrassing.
I'm about to
bash somebody,
you tell me not to.
It makes me
insecure.
I'm sorry.
Ffm hht mmm mmm...
Shh!
Don't make me look bad
in front of them.
If the mailman notices
they're turning
black and blue,
the cops will be
all over us.
It's not easy...
you know,
having all this
responsibility.
It's not easy.
Now let's go
back in there.
Let's get them
on our side, big fella!
Don't ever hit me
like that.
Out...
touch in.
Half-circles.
Big arms.
Again. Out...
and in.
Half-circles.
Step-touch.
Front again.
To the side.
To the front.
Front again.
To the side.
To the front.
Last time.
( doorbell chimes )
Furnace?
Do I have one?
Yes.
I'm here to fix it.
I didn't know
it was broken.
Did Albert call you?
Uh...
My ex-husband?
No, yes. He--
He called yesterday.
Can I come in?
Basement's that way.
Heel out.
Heel out,
break five...
arms down.
Heel out.
H-hello, Frannie.
Yes. I have a touch
of the flu.
Could you fax me over
anything that you feel
might be important
until I shake this thing?
Thank you.
Have a nice day.
My father
used to say that.
Oh, really?
I hate that.
I'll keep that in mind.
Got to take a pill.
Get me a glass
of water.
( crunch )
Oh.
That was
my last one.
Doesn't matter.
You got to learn
to just say no.
Ha ha ha!
Excuse me.
Could I go
to the bathroom?
No.
I'm comfortable
with that.
Get out of the way.
Yes.
Let's dig,
circles or no circles.
( shovels clang )
Furnace?
Oh, I'm just looking
for the fumes detector.
Look what I found
in your truck.
Who gave you the right
to go into my truck?
Don't you have that
backwards?
I knew you weren't
a repairman. Out!
O.K., all right,
look--
Hey, stay away!
Did Albert
send you here?
I don't even know Albert.
How'd you know
his name?
You just told me
his name.
Look, look,
I can explain this.
You've got one minute
to leave.
O.K., all right, O.K.
I don't know
what your problem is,
but there are circles
somewhere in here
worth a lot of money.
Not this way!
Over there.
O.K., O.K.
And don't come back,
or I'll call the police.
There's money
in this basement.
You have 40 seconds left.
No. Millions.
32. What do you mean,
millions?
Aw, never mind.
19.
Calling the police
will cost you money.
I'll think about
what you said.
I may be
the sanest person
you ever meet,
so don't treat me
like a wacko.
You're a
pathological liar.
Get out!
I'm going.
I'm on my way.
Just take
my word for it.
I'm not pathological.
Ugh!
Uh...
that was three
kyoke coffees
and--and one French roast.
Are you sure
it's decaf?
Otherwise,
I'll be up
all night.
Oh, yeah.
I'm the same way.
Norm has an espresso
and just drops
right off to sleep,
but if I have
one sip of coffee,
it costs me
half the night.
I'm never effective
after a bad night's
sleep.
Uh...huh. Ha ha!
Hey, honey.
You know,
you have your safety on.
Here.
Good.
Not allowed
to have caffeine.
Oh.
Hold it! Stop!
Whoa!
Stop! Stop!
May I...
No, no, no, no!
May I make
a suggestion?
What are you yelling for?
That makes
a terrible racket.
We have the nosiest
neighbors in the state.
He's right.
Lydia will die.
She'll think we're
putting in a sauna,
which means
they'll have
to build a sauna.
My idea is that
I use your lawn mower.
That will help
mask the noise.
So I let you
out of the house?
Do I look stupid?
Well,
then Harry can mow.
Look...
you-- You shut up.
I'm running this,
not you.
Ha ha ha!
Lyle, you mow.
Harry, keep an eye
on these two.
And don't
scare the neighbors.
( Marvin humming )
I would just like to say
you have a lovely home.
A sauna would be
very nice.
( jackhammer drills )
I need lunch money.
Jeffrey gave you $3.25
last night, dear.
Oh, yeah.
Goodbye.
Bye.
Give Jeffrey
a kiss goodbye.
She doesn't have
to do that.
He said
I don't have to.
You do,
and take off
the hat.
I like my hat.
It's awful.
It doesn't do
anything for you.
I'm not taking it off.
Jeffrey.
Yeah.
You are a sweet one.
Swan,
excel.
O.K.
( Jeffrey )
Jessie Lodge
has company.
Why don't you
like Swan?
She thinks
stepfathers are wicked.
I'm obliging her.
She's just too smart
for you.
The Rutledges' shutters
are closed.
Maybe they're
making no-no.
( Jeffrey )
Are you kidding?
They've been married
10 years.
I can't believe
they hired
a gardener.
How did you know, uh,
Marty Rollins' phone number
without looking it up?
I looked it up.
Not the other day,
you didn't.
That was
delicious coffee.
Well, it's all
in having fresh beans.
I could never get
the milk to fluff up
like that.
Well, you have to have
the right espresso machine.
I've got a friend
who used to fence
hot espresso machines.
That must be
exciting work.
Beats 9:00 to 5:00,
I guess.
I should know.
I used to work
in an office.
Really?
An insurance company.
I figured they'd never
miss a few thousand.
They deal with millions,
you know.
I can believe that,
health insurance,
especially.
It really has gotten out
of control, hasn't it?
I majored in sociology
at Bryn Mawr.
I have a million questions
I'd like to ask you.
Be careful!
( barking )
( whistles )
May I ask what it is
that we're looking for?
Dig.
You know...
you should consider
how odd it'll look
to our neighbors
to see a service vehicle
parked overnight
in our driveway.
See, I normally
go off to work
about 7:30
in the morning
and return
by 7:00 at night.
Those are
very long hours.
Yes. A long commute.
We like the location.
The benefits are decent.
Make your point.
My point is this--
Anything screws up,
we're dead meat, right?
So when I see
you gentlemen
being careless,
I sort of take it
personally.
Spit it out!
Our nosy neighbors
are already wondering
about the van,
not to mention
the kitchen shutters,
so if you want the cops
off our backs,
things have
to look normal.
I have to be seen
going to work.
That's impossible.
Not quite.
You take the van
like you finished work
and park
in the commuter lot.
Tomorrow I drive off,
as if to work,
one of you on the floor
with a gun.
We switch vehicles,
drive back in the van,
sneak me
into the garage.
Then you have
the appearance
of business as usual.
May I suggest one thing?
Since Lyle
has already been seen
mowing the lawn,
he should continue
a program
of hedging, trimming,
and pruning.
I can make up a list.
That's a good plan,
but I don't like it.
W-well, I'm comfortable
with that.
This guy's nuts.
Probably doesn't want to do
the yard work himself.
Take it easy!
You dig.
I don't want
to mow the lawn.
Just pretend.
Norm!
Oh, s--
Why are you even
talking to them?
Many of us want things.
We say, "I want
a relationship."
( telephone rings )
Hello.
Don't hang up!
Who is this?
The guy from
your basement.
I feel terrible
about what happened.
Ha ha.
You knew it was
my machine.
I'll get back to you
if you leave a message.
Beep!
I just want
to say I feel badly
about what happened.
I'm the guy
from your basement.
I apologize, and it--
( click )
( dial tone )
Don't get hysterical.
Uh!
Let me go!
Aah!
Oh!
Uh!
Aah!
You are a maniac!
I am not a maniac.
I'm a psychologist.
Aah!
Shh! Shh!
Don't scream.
Mm-mmm.
O.K.?
Mm-hmm.
God!
Did you hear that?
I need ice.
Do you
have some ice?
Aah!
Ooh!
( woman's voice )
Cherry Hill
help line.
If you're
calling from
a touch-tone phone,
press 1 now.
If this
is an emergency,
press 2 now.
If you need
the fire department,
press 6 now.
If you need
the police
department,
press 7 now.
If you call the police,
nobody will get the money.
They stole it
from a mafia skim bank!
Look! Right here!
Right here. Look.
See? Look. That's me. That's me.
( man )
Cherry Hill police.
Uh, sorry.
Wrong number.
Sorry.
Must be
an old picture.
It's nice to sleep
in the same bed again.
Reminds me of before
we were married.
Nobody has to know
about our sleeping
arrangements.
Oh, they're all asleep.
If I could get loose,
we could run for it.
This is a window
of opportunity.
They'd cut you down.
They wouldn't
risk the gunfire.
Those guns have silencers.
Yeah, well--
How do you know?
Harry told me.
"Harry told me."
I'm your husband,
not Harry.
So?
So you listen to me,
not Harry.
( groaning )
I was just wondering
if you use
hollow-tip bullets.
Sure.
( ring )
Hello.
Don't think I don't know
what you're up to.
If you touch my wife again,
I'll kill you.
( dial tone )
I think your husband
just called.
Oh, no!
Oh, no, I shouldn't...
It's O.K., Jillian.
I shouldn't
have done this!
You did
the right thing.
No, I didn't!
Lyle and Harry
had something to do
with your bombing?
If they did,
I'm disappointed.
I thought we were
getting somewhere.
Maybe it's an ex-convict
with some unresolved
feelings about you.
Sounds like you've
had some therapy.
Albert and I
saw a psychiatrist.
Then he ran off
with her.
Sorry. That's bad
for the profession.
You're good for it,
breaking in
with a pickax?
You're very angry,
aren't you?
Sometimes if you talk
through it,
you can feel better.
Look, doctor--
If you are a doctor--
I don't discuss
my shitty marriage
with just anybody.
If you want to repress it,
go ahead.
I'm not. I'm furious,
and I'm expressing it.
Can I get
some more ice for the...
Thanks.
So you want me
to take my house
off the market
because
there's $8 million
in my foundation?
8 1/2.
Well, excuse me
for not trusting
psychiatrists anymore.
I'm a psychologist.
There's a difference.
I know. You're not
as well-trained.
Somebody tries to kill
you, and you say
you're disappointed?
Talk about
not expressing yourself.
Look, I'll give you 10 percent
of the 8 1/2 million.
Ha! 10?
This is my house.
50 of that goes
to that lady in St. Louis.
I could kick you out
and keep it.
I'd tell the police.
Look, look, look.
20 percent.
I'll do all the work.
I want half
of whatever you get.
Half. Yes or no?
Deal, but you do
half the work.
Oh, God! Oh!
I know it's not easy
for you right now,
but, uh,
things will work out.
Whenever Albert
used those words,
I knew he was lying.
Anything else?
No.
Do you want to, uh,
you want
to give her a try?
O.K.
So we're going
on the word
of a convicted felon
called Tricks?
It was his last request.
Oh, well, then...
Just aim for the circle.
Nice swing.
( Jeffrey )
Norm just left
for work.
What was that noise
last night?
I slept through it.
Digging.
What?
Somebody's digging.
Maybe somebody's
burying a body.
Don't be juvenile.
I am a juvenile.
Do you have
your lunch money?
Jeffrey, give her
lunch money.
Swan, give Jeffrey
a kiss goodbye.
The money's
on the dresser.
Actually, the little...
She may be right
about the body.
I heard some screaming
in the night.
Maybe Albert slipped
over there and murdered her
and buried her
in the garden.
Or maybe it was
your friend Marty.
Your corpse looks
pretty healthy to me.
How did you sleep?
Oh, not bad.
I've never slept
tied up before.
No?
Come on.
Pretty good plan, huh?
Move.
* You have a way *
* With your way *
* And I'm waiting *
* For every way **
Do you have to sing?
It makes the work
go faster.
Not for me.
What are you,
a music critic?
You the one who picked out
that astroturf?
Albert did.
Took absolutely no
interest in this house
or anyone in it.
He was the most selfish,
conceited,
and ultimately
dishonest person
I've ever known.
He never even voted.
Huh.
He screwed me.
That's what people
do to each other.
It's an old story.
And I let him.
I put him through
business school.
We were going
to have nine kids,
only he changed
his mind.
He didn't want
any kids.
He didn't even
want a wife.
I see.
So we started going
to see a shrink,
then he
ran off with her.
Yeah. You told me.
This is what believing
in marriage gets you.
You can get shafted
just as easily
when you're single.
A wedding ring
is a "kick me" sign.
You can get kicked
with or without the sign.
Maybe I don't want
an answer.
Maybe I just want
to feel bad, O.K.?
O.K.
It's just hard.
( sobbing )
Oh, don't touch me.
Oh, don't even
think about it!
What? What?
What?
What, are you kidding me?
That was the last thing
on my mind.
A woman gets divorced,
suddenly
it's everybody's job
to make her feel better.
Look, look,
if you don't want to talk,
you just say so.
I don't want to talk.
Fine.
Paper boy!
Hey, get out of there.
I'm collecting.
How much?
7.50.
They're busy. Here.
Thanks.
Whoa! I thought
you said 7.50.
Well,
they usually tip me,
and I don't have
any change.
You
the new gardener?
What if I am?
My parents need one.
I'm booked.
They're competitive.
They'll pay more
than you're getting.
I can't be bought.
They'd never
understand that.
Tell them
to go fuck themselves.
They'll understand that.
Do you think you could
fix this chain?
Sure...
for 10 bucks.
Paper boy!
( doorbell chimes )
Oh...
( horn honks )
Oh!
Come on!
( knock on door )
Mrs. Lodge?
Must be out back.
( Marty )
I think you're going
to love this neighborhood.
It's tres recherche.
( knock on door )
Mrs. Lodge, it's Marty!
I have the Kims here!
( doorbell chimes )
You know what?
We'll come back.
What the hell
is going on
over here?
Settle down.
Ha ha ha!
Lyle's talking
to some kids out there.
He shouldn't be
talking to anybody.
Hey, who asked you?
Yeah, he shouldn't be
talking to anybody
out there.
Harry, go get him.
He started it.
He squealed on me.
He told the teacher
on us.
Break his glasses.
What?
You want to
teach him a lesson?
Break his glasses.
Cut it out!
There are rules to life.
One of the most important
you'll find is--
Nobody likes a squealer.
Now tell him.
He does it again,
you'll hurt him.
Come on!
There's
a philosophical point
I'm trying to make here!
The world is divided into
the doers and the doees.
The doees pay taxes
and generally
get shitted upon.
People look up
to the doers.
I'm a doer!
Lyle,
may I speak with you?
Sure.
There's something
seriously wrong
with you.
Maybe yes...
maybe no.
Jessie, it's me.
What the--
It's Albert.
I don't want him
to see me like this.
O.K.
I'll take care of it.
You might
want to go out
the same way
you came in, pal--
Empty-handed.
This is my house, pal.
These are my clothes.
I wouldn't brag.
Your name Albert?
Yeah. Who are you?
Jessie says you got
your share already.
The rest is hers.
You know that.
Are you the plumber
or just plumbing Jessie?
Hyaaah!
Don't make a move.
I know karate.
That was an antique.
Give me the watch.
It's my goddamn watch!
It was her stereo!
Oh, yeah?
Not here, baby.
Why don't we try the--
Albert, I didn't know
you were here.
Yes.
He was
just leaving.
Damn.
You know what, kids?
You're going to hear
from my lawyer.
Does he know
karate, too?
You certainly
don't waste any time.
Oh, Albert.
Hey, come on.
We'll talk.
Why can't you mind
your own business?
( bell rings )
Quiche is ready.
I'll help you with that.
You dig.
You help her.
Smells good.
It is good.
I mean you.
You must've studied
sociology.
Criminals
have very poor
impulse control.
I'll bet
you're the type
that fantasizes
gangsters
breaking in here
and having their way
with you.
Ohh...
y-y-you're sick.
It's a sick society.
Oh, no.
I don't buy that excuse.
You've got to learn to be
responsible for yourself.
You sound like
my shrink.
Now, come on.
You've got
a lot going for you.
You're good-looking,
you've got
a great body,
an inquisitive mi--
You appreciate
fine food and--
Did you say-- You say--
A good body
or a great body?
Let's serve the quiche.
( classical music plays )
Nice music.
I plopped these tapes on
'cause I hid them
when Albert was
stealing the stereo.
That doesn't mean
that I'd be hiding
things from you.
We're partners.
Did I say anything?
You looked it.
( knock on door )
I didn't know
you had company.
Marty,
this is Will...
Goldberg.
Willie Goldberg.
He's a...
he's an old, uh...
cousin.
He's an old
cousin of mine.
Cousin?
Hello.
I just dropped by to see
if you needed anything.
Got some serious buyers
coming in next week.
( turns TV off )
Come on.
Why did you--
I'm hearing noises.
You're just
imagining it, Marvin.
Go check it out.
It's just the neighbor
trying to diddle
the divorcee.
He won't be long.
Since when
do you use
the word diddle?
Damn.
Jeffrey...
that man drove away
in his van an hour ago.
Aah! Aah!
Marvin!
Aah!
I told you
they had silencers!
My Neiman! My investment!
Your invest--
I never did like
that painting
anyway.
May I speak without
getting shot at?
Marvin, we've got to get you
more medication.
Willis Embry's
right next door.
What do you mean?
You can't see him
from there.
But the papers say--
You can't believe
what you read
in the papers.
You know,
I've had it with you.
You talk and talk--
Ow!
You stay away from me,
Marvin.
I'm not following any man
who can't keep his cool.
Aah!
( glass breaks )
You shouldn't
have done that.
I'm splitting.
You want to walk away
from $8 million?
My ass is more valuable.
If he knew we were here,
he would've busted us.
Not if he knows that
we're sitting on the money.
We don't want your money.
Just don't hurt us anymore.
I'd like to speak
to you outside.
You got anything to say,
say it right here.
I'm getting
very perturbed.
I want to have
a discussion
in confidence.
Is it about me?
It ain't.
How do I know that?
If you're
worried about us
running away, don't.
Cuffs!
Cuffs, cuffs.
You heard him. Quick!
Cuffs. Cuffs.
Is that all right
with you?
Just don't
bash the lady, Marvin.
Just don't hurt me.
Maybe it's just some guy
who looks like Embry.
You want
fingerprints?
I saw him.
Uh-huh.
( door closes )
We're going to
get that money.
I don't want the money.
I just want
to survive this.
You hit me
when my back was turned.
I don't want
to talk about it.
I'm very upset.
I need to express it.
Tough shit.
You're creating
a leadership crisis here.
These people
need to understand
I'm in charge.
Don't be that way.
Three is a hard number.
It changes the dynamic.
May I interrupt
this discussion
to point out
Willis Embry's ass?
It's Embry.
Get out of the way.
So, Marvin...
you're going to blow away
Embry, the realtor,
the woman,
two different rooms
with one burst?
Jessie, I want to thank you
for this opportunity.
To do what?
To sell the house.
You're doing
a good job.
Means a lot to me.
Can I, uh,
have a hug?
What for?
I need one.
O.K. Sure.
Hey, Marty...
Don't do that!
Don't, Marty!
What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
What are you
thinking?
Oh.
Suburbia, man.
Yeah.
You're not going to your
sexaholics anonymous
meetings, are you?
I've been busy.
I'm taking a chance
on you.
Behave yourself
and keep your hands
off the buyers.
I'm sorry.
Sorry isn't good enough.
You'll see.
I will be better.
I promise.
I will.
What do you
think of that?
You used to kiss me
like that.
So you'll really look
up this Louise person?
I promised Tricks.
Honor among thieves?
It's mafia money anyway.
That makes
what you're doing right?
What we're doing right.
( knock on door )
Paper boy.
Hi.
Collecting.
How much is it again?
7.50 plus tip
brings it to 10.
I'm getting
my bike fixed.
You want
to contribute
to a new bike?
Maybe tomorrow.
What are you digging?
Jacuzzi.
Drainage.
Here's 10 more.
Tell your parents
you met my cousin
Willie Goldberg.
From Texas.
You lost your accent.
Did I?
It's none
of their business,
in my opinion.
( door opens )
What a nympho.
For someone who's
turned off to men,
you sure let
Marty think he was
getting somewhere.
What are you
talking about?
I saw you kiss him.
It's a good idea
to avoid outside
entanglements
until we find
the money, O.K.?
You want
to get the light?
Look, not that this is
any of your business,
but Marty and I
are just friends.
Yeah, fine.
You'd never find a man
playing with emotions
like that.
Oh, I never found a man
who had any.
Women are no better.
My girl
told me every day
she loved me,
even the day
she left me.
Maybe she left you
because you called her
"my girl."
( cracking )
Uhh.
I could get you
a good return
on your money.
Shh.
I hear digging.
( thump )
Lyle, are you sure you
got the right address?
I got us close.
All right,
so cheer up.
At least
you've got a good start
on a decent tunnel.
There are no problems
with nosy neighbors.
Ha ha.
( clang )
What are you doing?
What were you doing?
You were digging.
I couldn't sleep.
So you thought
you'd dig quietly,
find the money,
wake me up,
give me my share?
Yeah, right.
Let me do that.
You know,
maybe
it would help you
if you learned
to trust people.
You don't trust me
like I don't trust you.
I didn't say I did.
I came down
because I had lots
of nervous energy.
If you were a man,
you would understand.
You don't think
I have nervous energy?
I can't believe
a psychologist
could be so unaware
of how to talk
to a woman.
You've worked too long
with big, hairy convicts.
You can't relate
to a normal person.
Normal? Please.
It's no wonder
your girlfriend left you.
Sometimes people leave
no matter how much
a person loves them.
Sometimes it's them,
not you.
Get back in the hole.
I said get back
in the hole now!
All right, gentlemen,
let's cut the crap.
What I'm telling you is...
undo me.
I'm going
to whack this guy.
Go on, hit me!
Come on!
You need me.
Norm, stop it.
He's cracking,
I'm telling you.
Undo me.
It'll change your lives.
I can turn your 8 million
into 85 million
in 30 days.
Norman, what are you
talking about?
Not now, pumpkin!
I've got connections
you can only dream about,
and I can prove it.
If you're not convinced,
you can shoot me.
Shoot you anyway.
Go on. Undo him.
This better be good,
wimp.
You call me sir
from now on,
all right?
What are you doing?
I said
what are you doing?
We can't let him do
what he wants.
( Peedi )
Norm?
( gasp )
From Cuba...
with love.
Relax, gentlemen.
It's contraband.
Russia's finest.
Na zdorov'e!
Compliments
of resistance groups
left and right.
Norm,
what is going on?
Where did this room
come from?
The Eisenhower era,
honey.
It's a fallout shelter,
a business write-off.
I can't handle
this shit.
You're bush league.
That's why.
I'll kill you.
Take it easy.
Put it down.
Now.
Good boy, Marvin.
Good boy.
Take a look.
Be my guest.
Go on, gentlemen.
Go ahead.
I'm offering you
connections--
Colombia, Switzerland,
Havana, D.C., Moscow.
It's the new American
capitalism, gentlemen.
Let's make a deal.
First, we make
a simple assault next door,
we off the competition,
but we do it in
the American tradition--
Discreetly--
Or you go back to jail
and me 9:00 to 5:00.
I thought it was
7:00 to 7:00.
Eat my shorts, Harry.
I'm in charge now.
Right, Marvin?
Get out of the way.
Come on.
You know what these are?
Concussion grenades.
Repeat after me.
We can blast the tunnel with
these babies in no time.
Let's shoot him.
He's flipped.
You better talk nice
to Norm,
or these guys
will shoot you.
Wait. Here.
Thank you...
Marvy.
What are you doing?
One working woman's
special
coming right up.
Hope you like 'em
scrambled.
Ah-ah-ah.
If you put salt on them,
they won't be as fluffy.
You want to cook them,
make them fluffy?
They're your eggs.
Have them the way
you want them.
I could make tea.
If you get me coffee,
I'll give you
5 percent more of the money.
Don't let them
overcharge you
on the fine, dear.
Excel.
How do you expect
someone to excel
when they have to ride
this piece of shit?
Maybe Jeffrey
can fix it.
Jeffrey can't change
a typewriter ribbon.
Jeffrey's genius doesn't lie
in things mechanical, dear.
You talk so weird.
That's an expensive bike.
It sucks.
You'll have to clean up
that little girl's mouth.
Jeffrey, get bent.
Oh. Lydia...
do you believe this?
I thought
he was booked solid.
That's bullshit.
What's that noise?
Lyle?
I think
they found the house.
This neighborhood's
too damn noisy.
We can't get
any work done.
Marvin.
Excuse me.
I'd like a word
with you, please.
Is this concrete enough
for you?
Let's call the police.
What, kiss that
8 1/2 million goodbye?
They're trying
to kill us!
We're still alive,
aren't we?
They'll try again.
This thing work?
I thought you said
you were booked solid.
I am.
Isn't our money
good enough for you?
Look, I'm busy.
What is your name?
If they're not gone
in two minutes,
ice them.
Norman...
are you insane?
Honey, take
the phone number
off the truck.
I'm reporting you
to your supervisor.
Why don't
I take your names?
Then if we have
an opening next week,
I'll do my best
to fit you in.
That's the best
I can do.
O.K.?
Babitt.
What?
Babitt. B-a-b-i-t-t.
Babitt.
How can they chat
with Jeffrey
and Lydia?
They want the money.
That's their best hope.
You ever consider
nametags at all?
Excuse me.
The pen.
You get the number,
honey?
Yes, I got it.
Come on.
Where are they going?
Aah!
He used to be
a patient of mine.
Willis, I think
it's time we gave up.
No!
Look! We got them
on the run!
Hey.
I'm going to kill
that Willis.
Hey, Lyle...
you want to keep this?
A little joke.
It hurt.
Norm, could--
Could you ask them
to uncuff me?
I don't want you
involved.
I just want
to be undone.
Pretty soon,
dumpling.
Marvin, we need
the demolition hammer.
Uh...
O.K.
Norman,
you could shoot them.
Shoot them?
Not now, dumpling.
Marvin, if you
shore up that tunnel,
a grenade
will speed things up.
Where are the grenades?
Behind the couch.
I just want to say
I think you're doing
a fantastic job.
Thank you, Marvin.
Coming from you,
that's a compliment.
I never wanted
to be in charge.
Oh.
You spring guys
from the joint,
and they
look up to you
for leadership.
Marvin? Grenades.
O.K.
Now? Will you
let me go now?
Not now, dumpling.
Uh...
how many?
Two.
Good. You did good.
Why build this tunnel?
If we want to kill them,
let's finish the job.
Norm wants a tunnel,
we give him a tunnel.
You don't like it,
you talk to Norm.
I live in this neighborhood
myself.
Beautiful
shade trees.
They've been here
for years.
Quiet
neighborhood?
Very.
Ah, Mr. Goldberg.
Your cousin around?
Uh, no,
she's not, no.
Hi, Marty.
Good to see you.
Jessie, these are
the Bratesmans.
Hi.
Marty, could you people
come back later?
The Bratesmans here
drove from Philadelphia.
They're very motivated.
Just give us an hour.
We have
cleaning to do.
Really, Jess,
the Bratesmans don't mind
if it's a little untidy.
Fine, fine, fine.
We'll be back.
You got a minute?
Well...
Peedi, I don't know
how to start. Uh...
I, um...
are you comfortable?
I'm o.K.
I was just wondering.
I don't know how
to say this. I...
what does Peedi
stand for?
Oh, I never tell
anybody that.
Please tell me.
Penelope.
Penelope Diane.
May I call you
Penelope?
I'll have to think
about that.
At night...
when I'm falling asleep
with my pillow
under my arm,
wishing it was you...
in my mind,
can I call you Penelope?
Can I touch you,
Penelope?
Oh...
Harry.
( Marvin )
Harry! Where's that wrench?
Ugh...
Hey, what's
your problem?
Oh, I-- I'm handcuffed.
( telephone rings )
Wait. I'll get it.
I said I'll get it.
( ring )
Rutledge residence.
Lyle? Willis.
We need to talk.
I mean a real dialogue.
I'll kill you.
I understand
your hostility.
I'm sorry
about shooting you.
I've got a solution
where everybody wins.
I'm still going
to kill you.
Who is this?
Who is it?
Embry.
Tell him
he's a dead man.
Marvin says
hello, Willis.
Listen, I-- I just want
to work out a deal
where nobody gets
killed, O.K.?
He wants a deal.
We'll rip
his arms off.
Agree to anything.
How about
we meet someplace?
Where did you have
in mind, Willis?
You heard about
Tricks Bissell's
money, right?
We heard a rumor.
Tricks wanted something
done with half of it,
but the rest of it
we could split if--
Now who's this one?
Now they have three.
How can they afford
three people?
I got to learn
to read lips.
Lyle, you've got
to work harder on
those hostile feelings.
You shot him
with an arrow.
You blew up
my apartment!
That was Marvin.
Uhh...
Oh.
He gets violent
without his pills.
Maybe you
could write him
a prescription.
What you did
was very aggressive.
You tried to kill us!
Oh, now you're
exaggerating.
Lyle...
remember the progress
we were making
about your anger
at your older brother?
Leave my brother
out of this.
We're not
your patients anymore.
Oh, good, Willis.
Who's this?
What's going on here?
Albert, these, uh,
these men are interested
in the house.
This is Albert's house.
Why are they so dirty?
None of your business,
asshole.
That's O.K., Lyle.
( Albert )
Where's Jessie?
No, no, no, no.
Don't go back there.
Don't-- Don't
touch me, O.K.?
Why not?
Take another step,
I'll kill you.
Albert, why not
come back later
when these gentlemen
are through looking
through the house?
Run a credit check
on this guy.
Why'd you let him leave?
Why'd you?
We want the money,
Willis.
O.K., O.K., O.K.
How about we
divide up my share?
Huh?
There's plenty
to go around.
That sounds like
a good idea, Willis.
O.K.
We bought some time.
He didn't buy it.
( explosion )
Aah!
( coughing )
Oh, wow! Oh!
( gasps )
( car horn honks )
Wimps! We've
got work to do!
Wasn't that
delicious?
Marty,
that was no hour.
Fine.
You know what,
Mr. Bratesman?
Let's start
out back, O.K.?
I like the color.
Oh, yeah.
Goes with your complexion.
Hmm.
Landscaping looks good.
We can swing it
if we lock into
low interest rates?
Dead cats, geometry,
mother...
mother usually works.
What?
Nothing.
Nothing works.
You think she'd
go down 10,000?
I'll talk to her.
Honey--
Just a minute.
What about
a second mortgage?
Did you say
that was possible?
Yes, I think so.
Why don't you check out
the pool, Phil?
May I call you Phil?
Sure. Good idea.
I don't think--
We'll probably have to
do a little sprucing up.
Are you crazy?
Nice...
How expensive is it
to maintain a pool?
Oh, pennies, really.
Ha ha ha!
Honey, look at
this diving board.
Will you stop?
What's wrong with you?
I'm trying to get help.
You are?
Yeah.
So am I.
We meet Wednesdays.
We meet Tuesdays.
Am I hurting you?
Just a little.
Mmm.
Never mind my name.
Just tell me
your reward policy.
If it's illegal,
it's your civic duty
to report it.
Get a life.
Are these the men?
Yeah, these are
the guys right here.
( thud )
J-J-J-J-J-
Jessie!
Oh.
Penelope, can I
get you anything?
Oh! A key.
Norm has the keys.
Oh, he just wants
to protect you, baby.
I'd do the same thing
if you were mine.
Like this?
No.
Like this.
Uh-- Oh, Harry,
Harry, Harry.
Ohh.
Penelope...
I'm going to go
straight for you...
right after
we get this money.
Oh, Harry.
Oh...
All right.
O.K. Come to Papa.
Uhh.
( choking )
Don't ever say that.
O.K.
Uh, I'm sorry.
Sorry, Norm.
O.K., Marvin,
get your gun.
I'll get my gun.
Honey,
be careful.
Don't worry.
Yeah.
It's party time!
Whoa!
Aah!
Hey.
The power.
Did you back this up?
You should've.
Now look what you did.
Aah.
Honey...
Marvin!
Marvin,
come on!
Aah!
This is
the Cherry Hill Police!
You're surrounded!
Come out
with your hands up!
No.
Go!
Positions!
Hold your positions!
Form cover!
You in the rear!
What is it?
It's S.W.A.T.
What's going on here?
Somebody please tell us
what is going on here.
Back off, or
I start killing people!
What's the landscape man--
It's Marvin Boyd.
He's done time
for armed robbery.
We're coming out
with the lady!
Anybody follows,
she gets it!
Where is she?
Can't get her loose.
Go get the key.
Oh. Norm's got the key.
I don't know where he is.
I think he drowned.
Ahh, Normie.
Ahh, Normie drowned.
Oh, oh, Harry.
Uh, you're doing
a wonderful job, Harry.
I love you, Penelope.
Ohh...
He's staying
with the broad.
Yeah? That's his choice.
Let's go.
You look nice.
Thanks.
Here we go.
Keep your head down.
How can I drive
with my head down?
There's Mrs. Rutledge.
Want me
to pick him off?
No. You heard him.
Men, hold your fire.
O.K.,
we're letting you go.
We're out of here,
baby.
Shut up.
( car won't start )
Sounds like the battery.
Oh, I need a pill.
Aah!
D-don't shoot!
Hold your fire!
Don't shoot!
Oh, no.
Oh.
She's not in the car.
Get 'em, guys.
( Peedi )
Aah!
Are you hurt?
No.
Are you sure?
Are you O .K., ma'am?
There's a man inside.
Do you need
a medic?
No.
Are you sure
you're o.K.?
Damn it! Let me talk!
There's a man inside,
and-- And
he saved my life.
He-- He--
He wants to come out.
He-- He wants
to go straight.
He-- He-- He wants a piece
of the American dream.
He-- He-- He makes
great cappuccino.
He--
He's afraid that you're
going to kill him.
O.K. Hold your fire.
Hold your fire!
Uh, Harry?
Uh-- Harry?
It-- It's O.K., honey.
Come on, honey.
Come on out.
( Captain )
Handsome Harry.
Don't-- Don't hurt him.
Oh, Har...Harry.
Mrs. Rutledge,
where is your husband?
Your husband,
Mrs. Rutledge.
Tricks was telling
the truth, huh?
I was
so wrong about you.
$8 1/2 million, Jessie.
When you're through
with that lovey-dovey shit,
hand that to me.
Norm?
Norman, what
are you doing?
The suitcase. Now.
Are they making
you do this?
Come on.
Does Peedi know
about this?
Hand it over!
It's spoken for
by several parties.
Now!
Come on!
That's far enough.
Marty!
On the floor,
both of you!
Look, it's not
her fault, O.K.?
Just let her go.
Just take her with you
or something, all right?
But just don't kill
anybody, o.K.?
How about it, Jess?
That was very nice
of you.
Oh, Marty, no, no.
I-- I couldn't leave
Willis behind.
Then shut up and turn
around, both of you!
You try being realtors.
Me? I'm through
selling ugly houses
to stupid people.
Uhh!
I don't think
your house is ugly.
That's far enough.
That's my daughter.
That's her daughter.
H-h-hey,
somebody stop him!
Ooh!
The biggest crook
of them all.
Freeze!
Swan needs
a new bike.
I figured it'd
be safer if nobody
knew I was alive.
Well, I think
the insurance company--
Oh.
Oh, God.
Oh...
well, I mean-- I mean--
Well... Well...
Look at--
It's just-- It's just--
It's just all rotten!
Goodbye.
You got
a great future, kid.
Hey, Norm.
Sayonara, baby.
Peedi, we can
work this out.
I'll write.
All right,
that's far enough,
you Casanova.
Jeffrey!
He's fooling around
with my wife.
No!
You knew
his phone number!
I don't care
who she slept with.
Give us the gun.
His phone number was
on the "for sale" sign!
Just...sign?
Yes.
Oh.
I, uh...
Well, I'm sorry. I--
Uhh!
Ugh!
Hey!
Hi. I'm Marvin Boyd.
Ma-Marty Rollins.
You never been
in the joint, huh?
The joint?
No, never been.
Well, come on.
We'll sit together.
Look, uh...
I'm sorry about
the way things
turned out.
I, uh...
No. I gambled. I lost.
Yeah.
I met you.
Is that good or bad?
You tell me.
Huh?
Oh...
Oh!
Do you have
Louise's address?
Uh-huh.
* Ice will melt *
* Water will boil *
* Shouldn't you and I *
* Shake off
This mortal coil? *
* It's bigger than us *
* You don't have
To worry about it *
* Ready or not *
* Here comes the plot *
* You feel lucky when
You know where you are *
* You know
It's gonna come true *
( crash )
* It's only natural *
* That I should want to *
* Be there with you *
* It's only natural *
* That you should
Feel the same way, too *
* It's easy
When you don't try *
* Goin' on
First impressions *
* Man in a cage *
* Has made
His confession *
* Now you've seen me
At my worst *
* And it won't be the last time
I'm down there *
* I want you to know *
* I feel completely
At ease *
* You read me
Like a book *
* That's fallin' down
Between your knees *
* Please *
* Let me have
My way with you *
* It's only natural *
* That I should want to *
* Be there with you *
* It's only natural *
* That you should
Feel the same way, too *
* It's circumstantial *
* There's nothing written
In the sky *
* And we don't even
Have to try *
* And we'll be
Shakin' like mud *
* Buildings of glass *
* Sink into the bay *
* We'll be under
The rocks again *
* You don't have to say *
* I know you're afraid *
* It's only natural *
* That I should wanna
Be there with you *
* It's only natural *
* That you should
Feel the same way, too *
* It's circumstantial *
* It's something
I was born to *
* It's only natural *
* Can I help it
If I want to? *
* Ooh *
* Can I help it
If I want to? **