[splat]
(Whitney Cummings)
FROM MY HOMETOWN,
WASHINGTON, D.C.,
PLEASE WELCOME...
ME.
[cheers, whistles, applause]
*
WHAT IS UP, D.C.?
COME ON!
[cheers, whistles, applause]
WOW, D.C.!
MY HOMETOWN, BITCHES!
COME ON!
[cheers, whistles, applause]
I AM WEARING SO MUCH MAKEUP
RIGHT NOW, GUYS,
I AM LIKE
THE CHRISTINA AGUILERA
OF COMEDY.
GIVE IT UP FOR MY MAKEUP.
COME ON!
[cheers, whistles, applause]
THIS IS SO FUCKING AWESOME!
I-- SO GOOD TO BE HOME.
I LOVE D.C. SO MUCH.
I HAVEN'T BEEN HERE
IN SO LONG.
FROM WHAT I UNDERSTAND,
OUR MAYOR
DOES NOT DO DRUGS ANYMORE.
IS THAT WHAT I---
SINCE I'VE BEEN GONE?
BUT, UH,
NOW THAT I'M A COMEDIAN
I TRAVEL SO MUCH NOW
AND MY FAVORITE THING
TO DO WHEN I FLY
IS READ THIS MAGAZINE
CALLED COSMOPOLITAN.
LADIES, DO WE READ
THIS MAGAZINE?
[women whooping]
THIS MAGAZINE
BASICALLY TEACHES US
HOW TO BE SLUTS, RIGHT?
[laughter]
LIKE, THERE WAS
AN ARTICLE IN THERE.
IT WAS LIKE,
"HOW TO TURN ON YOUR GUY."
- HE'S A GUY.
- [laughter]
- TAKE OFF A SOCK, OKAY?
- [laughter, applause]
THERE WAS ANOTHER ONE.
IT WAS LIKE,
"FOR ADVENTUROUS SEX,
"SURPRISE YOUR MAN AT WORK
FOR A QUICKIE."
I'M LIKE,
I CANNOT SURPRISE
MY MAN AT WORK
FOR A QUICKIE, OKAY?
HE DOESN'T HAVE A JOB.
WHAT, I'M GONNA GO UP TO HIM
WHILE HE'S WATCHING
SPORTS ON THE COUCH,
"SURPRISE"?
THEN THERE
WAS THE WHOLE SECTION--
I SWEAR TO GOD--
ON SEX "TRICKS."
TRICKS? I DON'T HAVE TO DO
ANY TRICKS IN THE BEDROOM.
I HAVE A VAGINA, OKAY?
TA-DA!
I JUST GET TO TAKE
A TYLENOL P.M. AND LIE THERE.
THAT'S ALL I'M DOING.
[laughter, applause]
YOU DON'T WANT MY VAGINA
DOING TRICKS.
WHAT IF I WAS JUST LIKE,
WAA-LAH!
A BIRD FLEW OUT.
[laughter, applause]
AND THEN THERE
WAS A WHOLE SECTION,
IT WAS LIKE,
"HOW TO MAKE YOUR MAN SCREAM
IN THE BEDROOM."
GUYS, YOU ARE NEVER...
SUPPOSED TO SCREAM...
IN THE BEDROOM.
THAT IS SO GAY.
[laughter, applause]
OKAY? I DON'T CARE
IF A PIRANHA
IS GNAWING
ON YOUR BUTT HOLE, OKAY?
I DON'T CARE.
[laughter, applause]
AND THEN THERE WAS
A WHOLE SECTION ON "ROLE PLAY,"
WHICH I GUESS PEOPLE
DO THAT NOW.
THEY DRESS UP IN COSTUMES
AND FUCK EACH OTHER.
AND, UH,
- THERE WAS--
- (man) YEAH!
APPARENTLY, THE MOST POPULAR
ROLE-PLAY FANTASY
IS THE "NURSE" FANTASY--
WHICH I DON'T EVEN KNOW.
LIKE, IF I WAS GONNA DO
THE "NURSE" FANTASY FOR MY MAN,
I WOULD JUST MAKE HIM
WAIT IN THE LIVING ROOM...
FOR AN HOUR,
AND MAKE HIM READ
HIGHLIGHTS MAGAZINE...
BEFORE REJECTING
HIS HEALTH INSURANCE, OKAY?
THAT'S HOW
THAT WOULD GO DOWN.
YOU'RE IDIOTS...
MAKING US DRESS UP
IN COSTUMES.
LADIES, NEXT TIME YOUR MAN
ASKS YOU TO DRESS UP
IN A FRIGGIN' COSTUME
TO HAVE SEX WITH HIM,
GO TO THE BATHROOM,
TELL HIM YOU'RE GONNA
SLIP INTO SOMETHING
MORE COMFORTABLE,
COME OUT
IN A WEDDING DRESS, OKAY?
[laughter, oh's]
[humming The Wedding March]
* DA, DA, DA-DA
* DA--
GET A BABY STROLLER.
[laughter]
HE'LL NEVER GET
AN ERECTION AGAIN.
IT'S AWESOME.
I JUST DON'T LIKE
ALL THESE ROLE-PLAY FANTASIES,
'CAUSE I FEEL LIKE THE GUY
IS ALWAYS VERY AUTHORITATIVE,
AND THE WOMAN IS ALWAYS,
LIKE, SO WEAK, YOU KNOW?
IT'S LIKE THE GUY
IS ALWAYS, LIKE, A LAWYER
OR, LIKE, A DOCTOR,
AND THE WOMAN'S ALWAYS,
LIKE, A SECRETARY.
THE GUY'S, LIKE, A PROFESSOR
AND THE WOMAN'S A SCHOOLGIRL.
WHEN YOU GUYS DO THIS,
YOU'RE JUST REMINDING US
OF ALL THE JOBS
YOU DON'T HAVE IN REAL LIFE.
HOW ABOUT INSTEAD OF BEING
A DOCTOR IN THE BEDROOM,
HOW 'BOUT JUST BE
A FUCKING DOCTOR?
HOW 'BOUT THAT?
THAT'S...
I DID HAVE A GUY
DO THIS TO ME ONCE.
I HAD A GUY SAY TO ME--
I SWEAR TO GOD-- HE WAS LIKE,
"I WANT YOU TO BE
A STRIPPER FOR ME."
I WAS LIKE,
"UH, YOU WANT ME TO BE
EMOTIONALLY UNAVAILABLE...
"AND TAKE YOUR MONEY?
I'VE BEEN DOIN' THAT
SINCE WE FREAKIN' MET, OKAY?"
ALL I NEED IS SOME SELF-TANNER
AND A SHITTY SUN TATTOO,
AND I'M READY
TO ROCK THIS RIGHT NOW.
LET'S GO.
DEAD EYES.
[laughter, applause]
I DON'T KNOW--
I JUST WAS LIKE, "DUDE,
I AM NOT DOING
THE STRIPPER FANTASY."
I TOLD HIM, I WAS LIKE,
"CAN WE JUST COMPROMISE?
"HOW 'BOUT I THROW
SOME GLITTER ON YOUR BALLS,
AND WE WATCH AMERICAN IDOL.
HOW ABOUT THAT?"
I JUST THINK YOU CAN'T DO
THE STRIPPER FANTASY
UNLESS YOU HAVE A STRIPPER BODY,
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
LIKE, IF I WAS GONNA,
LIKE, GET NAKED
AND DANCE AROUND,
YOU KNOW, THAT POLE,
YOU GUYS WOULDN'T BE LIKE,
"OH, LOOK AT THAT STRIPPER."
YOU'D BE LIKE,
"WHAT IS THAT EUROPEAN BOY
DOIN' ON A JUNGLE GYM?"
[laughter, applause]
I JUST FEEL LIKE OUR SOCIETY
IS OBSESSED WITH STRIPPERS.
LIKE, AT MY GYM IN L.A.,
THERE'S A CLASS CALLED
"STRIPTEASE AEROBICS."
RIGHT? IT'S LIKE, GET IN SHAPE
LIKE A STRIPPER.
WHAT, IS A PIMP GONNA CHASE ME
AROUND THE GYM FOR AN HOUR,
AND I GET TO DO FRICKIN' BLOW--
WHAT IS THIS CLASS?...
I'M IN.
[laughter, cheers, applause]
I'M JUST NOT ADVENTUROUS
LIKE THAT.
LIKE, I HAD A GIRLFRIEND OF MINE
ASK ME RECENTLY, SHE'S LIKE,
"HAVE YOU
EVER MADE A SEX TAPE?"
SHE'S A SLUT.
UM...
[laughter]
I FEEL LIKE GUYS CAN MAKE
SEX TAPES, RIGHT?
'CAUSE YOU GUYS, YOU'RE LIKE,
EMOTIONALLY UNATTACHED.
LIKE, YOU CAN MAKE A SEX TAPE
WITH SOME GIRL, YOU KNOW,
FROM LIKE, 10 YEARS AGO,
POP IN IT NOW AND BE LIKE,
- [macho voice] "OH, YEAH!"
- [laughter]
I DON'T KNOW WHY I THINK
ALL GUYS JERK-OFF LIKE THAT.
- WHY DO-- WHY IS THAT?
- [laughter continues]
LIKE-- [grunting]--
JUST LIKE... [grunting]
JUST LIKE,
ALWAYS STANDING UP.
LIKE, HUNCHED OVER LIKE...
LIKE A TROLL OR SOMETHING.
LIKE, [grunting]--
AND YOU GO--
YOU LIKE, GROWL-- ARR, ARR.
LIKE--
AND IT'S ALWAYS UNDER
A BRIDGE.
LIKE, WHY DO I THINK THAT?
BUT YOU GUYS CAN WATCH
SEX TAPES. RIGHT?
ALL YOU GUYS HAVE TO DO
IS BE LIKE, "OH, YEAH.
LOOK AT MY BALLS. OH, YEAH."
'CAUSE YOU GUYS
LOVE YOUR BALLS.
YOU GOT TO SEE YOUR BALLS,
AND YOU'RE STOKED,
'CAUSE YOU GUYS--
YOU LOVE YOUR BALLS, RIGHT?
YOU THINK THOSE THINGS
ARE AWESOME.
YOU THINK THEY'RE SO GREAT.
NEWS FLASH--
THEY'RE TERRIBLE.
THEY ARE DISGUSTING.
THEY'RE EMBARRASSING.
THEY ARE AWFUL.
CAN SOMEONE JUST EXPLAIN,
WHY DO ALL BALLS LOOK LIKE
THEY'RE 150-YEARS-OLD?
[laughter, cheers, applause]
[women cheering]
LIKE, CAN YOU PUT SOME SUNSCREEN
ON THAT, PLEASE?
MAYBE SOME LIP BALM
OR SOMETHING-- THAT'D BE GOOD.
AND THEY'RE ALWAYS ASHY.
WHY ARE THEY ALWAYS...
BUT THEY'RE ALSO, LIKE,
STICKY AT THE SAME TIME,
SO IT'S LIKE,
WHAT IS THE TEMPERATURE
DOWN THERE?
I CANNOT FIGURE IT OUT.
WHAT IS THAT WETNESS
GOING ON?
LIKE, WHAT IS THAT?
IT'S TEARS.
IT'S PROBABLY TEARS.
THEY'RE CRYING, 'CAUSE THEY
KNOW HOW UGLY THEY ARE.
THAT'S WHAT'S GOING ON.
THEY LOOK LIKE THAT THING
HANGING OFF A ROOSTER'S CHIN,
JUST RIGHT...UGH.
OH, AND YOU GUYS
ARE SHAVING 'EM NOW--
YOU THINK THAT HELPS?
DO NOT SHAVE YOUR BALLS.
THE LAST THING THOSE THINGS
NEED TO BE ARE MORE VISIBLE.
NO WAY.
GROW IT OUT,
COVER UP THOSE WEIRD,
BROWN SPLOTCHES
AND...VEINS.
THEY'RE AWFUL.
THEY LOOK LIKE DRIED FRUIT.
YOU SHOULD BE ASHAMED
OF YOURSELVES.
HOW DARE YOU?
BUT, LIKE, WOMEN,
WE CAN'T MAKE SEX TAPES.
WE'RE TOO EMOTIONAL, RIGHT?
WE'RE TOO SENSITIVE.
LIKE, IF I WERE TO MAKE
A SEX TAPE WITH SOME GUY,
YOU KNOW, FROM LIKE,
FIVE YEARS AGO, POP IN IT NOW,
I WOULDN'T BE LIKE, "OH, YEAH!"
I'D BE LIKE, [crying mockingly]
"OH, MY GOD. I MISS HIM SO MUCH.
"I'M GONNA
FIND HIM ON FACEBOOK.
- I'M GONNA..."
- [laughter]
I'M JUST NOT LIKE THAT.
LOOK, I HAVE GIRLFRIENDS
WHO WILL TEXT-MESSAGE
NAKED PHOTOS OF THEMSELVES
TO THEIR MAN,
WHICH I GUESS THE WHOLE POINT
OF THAT IS TO BE LIKE,
"OH, HERE'S WHAT'S WAITIN'
FOR YOU AT HOME, BIG BOY...
PHOTOS."
IF I WAS TO DO
A "HERE'S WHAT'S WAITIN' FOR YOU
AT HOME" PHOTO SHOOT,
I WOULD TAKE SOME PICTURES
OF THE FRICKIN' DISHES, OKAY?
THE BILLS RIGHT NOW.
MY VAGINA'S NOT WAITING FOR YOU
AT HOME AT ALL.
IT'S TRYIN' TO BOOK ME
AN ACTING JOB.
IT IS VERY BUSY RIGHT NOW.
I'M JUST NOT SEXY LIKE THAT.
I FEEL LIKE GIRLS ARE SEXY NOW.
I'M NOT A SEXY GIRLFRIEND.
ALL I DO
IN RELATIONSHIPS
IS FIGHT.
THAT'S ALL I EVER DO
IN RELATIONSHIPS.
BUT THE THING IS THAT WOMEN--
WE ARE AMAZING FIGHTERS, RIGHT?
- [women whooping]
- WE ARE AMAZING FIGHTERS.
WE ARE LIKE
EMOTIONAL NINJAS,
- RIGHT?
- [laughter]
OUR FAVORITE TACTIC
IS THE SILENT TREATMENT.
THAT IS OUR JAM, RIGHT?
OUR MAN PISSES US OFF--
"HE PISSED ME OFF.
"I'M NOT GONNA TALK TO HIM
FOR THE REST OF THE DAY.
I'M GONNA SHOW HIM."
LADIES, "THE SILENT TREATMENT"
IS NOT A PUNISHMENT.
[laughter, applause]
IT'S A FREAKIN' REWARD, OKAY?
HE'S LIKE, "OH, THANK GOD
SHE SHUT THE HELL UP.
"OH, MY GOD.
I LOVE THE SILENT TREATMENT.
"I GET TO WATCH SPORTSCENTER
AGAIN TODAY.
I'M GONNA FORGET HER BIRTHDAY
EVERY YEAR."
LADIES, NEXT TIME YOUR MAN
PISSES YOU OFF,
DO NOT GIVE HIM
"THE SILENT TREATMENT."
INSTEAD, GO GOOGLE THE MOST
IMPORTANT GAME OF THE SEASON,
SIT NEXT TO HIM
DURING THAT GAME,
AND JUST ASK AS MANY...
FUCKING QUESTIONS...
AS POSSIBLE.
"I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
"WHO'S THAT GUY
IN THE STRIPED SHIRT?
"DOES HE WORK AT FOOT LOCKER?
"I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
"WHY ARE THEY ALL WEARING
THE SAME OUTFIT?
WHEN ARE WE GONNA HAVE
A BABY?"
EVENTUALLY,
HE WILL SHOOT HIMSELF
IN THE FACE,
AND YOU FUCKING WIN
THAT ARGUMENT.
[laughter, applause]
YOU CANNOT DEFEAT A WOMAN
IN AN ARGUMENT, RIGHT?
IT'S NEVER HAPPENED.
'CAUSE WOMEN,
WE NEVER EXPRESS THE EMOTIONS
WE'RE ACTUALLY FEELING, RIGHT?
WHEN WE ARE MOST PISSED OFF,
YOU GUYS, WHAT DO WE SAY?
[happy voice]
"I'M FINE."
"I'M FINE"
MEANS I'M ABOUT TO STAB YOU
IN THE NECK.
- [laughter]
- OKAY?
WOMEN ARE VERY TRICKY.
WE'RE VERY MISLEADING, RIGHT?
NOT ONLY EMOTIONALLY,
ALSO PHYSICALLY,
WOMEN ARE MISLEADING.
LIKE, YOU'LL SEE
A GIRL OUT AT A BAR.
SHE'S LIKE, 5'7".
YOU TAKE HER HOME.
THE SHOES COME OFF.
SHE'S A GNOME, RIGHT?
[laughter]
WE'RE THE SAME WAY EMOTIONALLY,
AND WE ALWAYS EXPRESS
THE OPPOSITE EMOTION
WE'RE FEELING.
WE DO IT WITH OTHER WOMEN,
TOO, RIGHT?
WE'RE ALWAYS, LIKE,
THE OPPOSITE WITH WOMEN.
IT HAPPENS ALL THE TIME.
LIKE, ONE WOMAN HATES
ANTHER WOMAN.
THE WOMEN SHE HATES
WALKS IN THE DOOR-- IT'S LIKE,
"I CAN'T STAND THAT BITCH.
I CANNOT STAND THAT BITCH.
I HATE THAT BITCH.
I CANNOT STAND
THAT LITTLE SLUT."
[high-pitched voice]
"OH, HI!"
YOU CANNOT FUCK
WITH THAT KIND OF CRAZY, OKAY?
[laughter, applause]
BUT I FEEL LIKE
ALL WE WANT YOU GUYS TO DO
IS ASK US
HOW WE'RE FEELING, RIGHT?
ASK US, "WHAT'S WRONG?"
YOU FINALLY ASK US WHAT'S WRONG,
WHAT DO WE SAY?
"NOTHING."
EVEN IF WE DO ADMIT IT,
IT'S LIKE,
"YEAH, SOMETHING'S WRONG,
"BUT IF YOU
DON'T KNOW WHAT IT IS,
I'M NOT GONNA TELL YOU."
GUYS, LET ME
EXPLAIN THAT TO YOU, OKAY?
USUALLY WHEN WE'RE PISSED OFF
AT YOU BUT DON'T TELL YOU WHY,
IT'S BECAUSE WE SNOOPED
THROUGH YOUR SHIT, OKAY?
CELL PHONES-- WE FOUND
SOMETHING INCRIMINATING,
BUT WE CAN'T YELL AT YOU
ABOUT IT,
'CAUSE THEN
WE'D HAVE TO "ADMIT"
THAT WE SNOOPED
THROUGH YOUR SHIT.
SO WE JUST SILENTLY PUNISH YOU
FOR, LIKE, MONTHS...
UNTIL ONE DAY IT'LL JUST
RANDOMLY EXPLODE OUT.
YOU'LL BE LIKE, "HEY, BABY,
DO YOU WANT TO GO
TO THE CHEESECAKE FACTORY
FOR DINNER?"
"OH, WHY?!
IS THAT WHERE
'JULIE' WORKS?!"
[laughter, applause]
I SNOOP.
I DON'T GIVE A FUCK.
(woman) WOO!
THE PROBLEM WITH WOMEN
AND SNOOPING
IS WE DON'T THINK
WE'RE DOING ANYTHING WRONG,
'CAUSE OUR MINDS CAN TALK US
INTO ANYTHING, RIGHT?
WE COULD RATIONALIZE ANYTHING
IN OUR CRAZY HEADS.
YOU DON'T REALIZE UNTIL LATER,
TILL WE'RE FIGHTING WITH YOU
ABOUT IT,
HOW WE JUSTIFIED IT IN OUR
CRAZY-ASS BRAINS, YOU KNOW?
WE'RE LIKE, "WHAT? I WAS NOT
GOING THROUGH YOUR WALLET, OKAY?
"I WAS JUST CLEANING IT.
[laughter]
YOU'RE WELCOME!"
[laughter, applause]
I THINK THE WORST THING
YOU CAN FIND
WHEN YOU'RE SNOOPING
IS JEWELRY.
THAT'S THE WORST THING, RIGHT?
LIKE, ANOTHER WOMAN'S JEWELRY,
EVEN IF IT'S
AN EX-GIRLFRIEND
OR WHATEVER.
BUT I HAVE FOUND --
HOW PISSED OFF I GOT
ABOUT THE JEWELRY
I FOUND IN MY MAN'S PLACE
WAS DIRECTLY CORRELATED
TO HOW NICE THE JEWELRY WAS.
SO ONE TIME I FOUND THIS REALLY
CRAPPY PLASTIC BRACELET.
I WAS LIKE, "OH, WHAT,
YOU SLEPT WITH SOME GIRL
WHO SHOPS AT 'CLAIRE'S'?
'ACCESSORIES,' IS THAT IT?"
BUT THEN I JUST NAMED
A BUNCH OF STORES
THAT NO MAN
HAS EVER HEARD OF.
I WAS LIKE, "OH, WHAT IS THIS,
FROM 'WET SEAL', HUH?
"WHAT IS THIS,
FROM 'SPIEGEL'?
WHAT IS THIS,
FROM 'Overstock.com'?"
BUT THEN ONE TIME I FOUND
A REALLY, LIKE, NICE,
LIKE, SILVER BRACELET
AND IT HAD, LIKE,
SOME DIAMONDS IN IT.
I DIDN'T YELL AT HIM AT ALL.
I JUST PUT IT ON MY WRIST...
AND HE NEVER
HEARD ABOUT IT AGAIN...
- 'CAUSE I STEAL.
- [laughter]
IT'S MINE NOW, SLUT!
[laughter, applause]
I THINK THAT RELATIONSHIPS
JUST MAKE WOMEN CRAZY.
THEY MAKE
PERFECTLY NORMAL PEOPLE
GO INSANE, RIGHT?
LIKE, I LIKE TO PLAY
A LITTLE GAME,
LIKE, THREE MONTHS
INTO A RELATIONSHIP.
IT'S CALLED,
"LET'S GO THROUGH
YOUR CELL PHONE
"AND DELETE THE CONTACTS...
I DON'T LIKE."
[laughter, applause]
THAT'S WHEN I GET TO
GO THROUGH YOUR PHONE,
YOU GOTTA TELL ME
WHO EVERY GIRL IS IN YOUR PHONE,
AND THEN I DECIDE
IF I FREAKIN' LIKE IT OR NOT.
[laughter, applause]
IT GOES SOMETHING LIKE THIS.
"LINDSEY"...
SOUNDS LIKE A SLUT.
DELETE THAT.
"RICHARD"...
THAT'S A SLUT FOR SURE.
DELETE THAT.
"MOM"?
THAT'S A WHORE.
DELETE THAT.
YOU GUYS HAVE
YOUR WEIRD STUFF, TOO.
I RECENTLY
NOTICED ABOUT GUYS--
I NOTICED THAT EVERY GUY
I'VE EVER KNOWN,
SOMEWHERE IN HIS HOUSE
OR APARTMENT OR WHATEVER,
HAS A JAR
THAT'S FULL OF "COINS"?
WHAT THE FUCK IS THIS?
THE LAST GUY I DATED--
I WAS LIKE,
"OH, MAYBE HE,
LIKE, COLLECTS COINS,
OR MAYBE THAT'S,
LIKE, HIS LAUNDRY MONEY."
NO, THAT WAS
HIS BANK ACCOUNT, OKAY?
[laughter, applause]
LIKE, WHAT ARE YOU, A PIRATE?
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
[laughter continues]
I DATE CHEAP GUYS.
I THINK THAT'S THE PROBLEM.
I RECENTLY HAD A GUY--
I SWEAR TO GOD--
ASK ME OUT ON A DATE
TO GO GET COFFEE.
IS THAT HAPPENING NOW,
IN THE PLAID SHIRT?
YOU'RE DOIN'
THAT WITH GIRLS NOW?
YOU'RE NOT STRAIGHT.
NO WAY.
[laughter, cheers, applause]
WHAT IS THIS SHIRT?
WHAT ARE WE DOIN' HERE?
WHAT ARE WE DOIN'?
YOU'RE FUCKIN' ON TV.
WHAT ARE YOU DOIN'?
[laughter, applause]
YOU'RE FUCKIN'
KILLIN' ME RIGHT NOW.
AND YOU,
DON'T EVEN TRY TO LAUGH.
THIS IS WORSE.
[laughter]
DO YOU SEE HOW HOT
THESE GIRLS ARE?
YOU'RE FUCKIN' BLOWIN' IT.
THIS IS NEVER GONNA HAPPEN.
NO, I LIKE IT.
YOU'RE SEXY.
ARE YOU SINGLE?
- UH--EHH!
- [laughter, applause]
EH--EH--EH!
TOO MUCH CUM IN YOUR MOUTH?
CAN'T TALK?
[laughter, applause]
- OKAY.
- [cheers, applause]
NO, I SERIOUSLY--
I SWEAR TO GOD--
I HAD A GUY ASK ME OUT
ON A DATE TO GO GET COFFEE.
HOW CHEAP IS THAT?
HE'S LIKE,
"HEY, DO YOU WANNA, LIKE,
MAYBE GO GET
SOME COFFEE LATER?"
I WAS, LIKE, "SURE.
"YOU KNOW WHERE THERE'S
REALLY GOOD COFFEE?
"THIS PLACE THAT'S CALLED, UH,
'MORTON'S STEAKHOUSE'...
[laughter]
"YOU PIECE OF SHIT.
[laughter, applause]
"I LOVE A LITTLE COFFEE
WITH MY LOBSTER.
- LET'S GO."
- [laughter]
AND THEN I'M SUCH AN IDIOT
THAT I WENT ON THE COFFEE DATE.
IT WAS AT, LIKE,
4:00 IN THE AFTERNOON.
AND I SHOWED UP TO GO--
LIKE, I WENT UP TO THE COUNTER
TO PAY FOR MY COFFEE--
IT WAS LIKE $1.70 OR SOMETHING--
AND I GO TO PULL OUT
MY WALLET.
HE CUTS IN FRONT OF ME.
HE GOES,
"NO, NO, NO, NO,
NO, NO, NO...
- I GOT IT."
- [laughter]
OH, REALLY?
ARE YOU GONNA GET SOME COINS
FROM YOUR FRICKIN' JAR?
IS THAT HOW YOU'RE...?
WOMEN ARE CHEAPER
THAN MEN, THOUGH.
IT'S NOT EVEN
THAT WE'RE CHEAP.
WE JUST NEVER EXPECT
TO PAY FOR ANYTHING, RIGHT?
SO MUCH SO,
WE HAVE MASTERED THE ART
OF SOMETHING
THAT I LIKE TO CALL
THE "PUMP FAKE"...
[laughter]
WHICH IS WHEN THE BILL
COMES TO THE TABLE,
WE'LL JUST STICK
OUR HAND IN OUR PURSE...
[laughter, applause]
JUST MOVE IT AROUND
FOR AS LONG AS WE HAVE TO
UNTIL YOU GUYS
SIGN THE CHECK.
WE'RE NOT GRABBING ANYTHING.
WE'RE JUST SHUFFLING
SHIT AROUND...
JUST GETTING STABBED
BY PENCILS.
IF IT'S A SMALL PURSE,
WE'LL JUST DO THAT.
AND IF IT'S A CLUTCH,
WE'LL JUST FINGER-BANG IT
AS LONG AS WE HAVE TO.
[laughter, applause]
THAT'S WHEN YOU PUT A FINGER
IN SOMEONE'S VAGINA.
[laughter, cheers, applause]
I ACTUALLY DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHAT'S GOIN' ON ANYMORE.
I DON'T KNOW IF THE GUY'S
SUPPOSED TO PAY,
IF THE GIRL'S SUPPOSED TO,
IF YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO SPLIT IT.
I JUST GOT OUT OF A FOUR-YEAR
RELATIONSHIP JUST RECENTLY.
- (man) WOO!
- YEAH, THANKS.
YOU'RE HAPPY ABOUT THAT?
- YEAH.
- [laughter]
I'M SINGLE.
YOU WANNA DO THIS RIGHT NOW?
[laughter]
THIS IS A WATER BRA.
THIS IS FALSE ADVERTISING.
BUT OTHERWISE...
I'M LIKE, WHAT,
ARE YOU A PEDOPHILE,
- IS THAT IT?
- [laughter]
BUT, NO, I DID, I JUST GOT OUT
OF A FOUR-YEAR RELATIONSHIP.
IT WAS HARD,
BECAUSE WHAT I LEARNED--
AFTER I GOT OUT
OF THE FOUR-YEAR RELATIONSHIP,
I LEARNED THAT WOMEN--
WE'RE NOT GIVEN THE SKILLS
WE NEED TO SURVIVE
IN THE WORLD WITHOUT A MAN.
I LEARNED THIS,
'CAUSE RIGHT AFTER WE BROKE UP,
I GOT A BRAND-NEW CAR.
FOUR DAYS AFTER
I GOT A BRAND-NEW CAR,
I FILLED IT UP
WITH DIESEL FUEL.
(audience)
OH!
NOW, I ALWAYS LOVE
THIS REACTION,
'CAUSE ALL
THE GUYS IN THE AUDIENCE
ARE ALWAYS LIKE,
"OH, GOD!"
AND ALL THE GIRLS
ARE JUST LIKE...
- "SO?"
- [laughter]
LIKE, I DIDN'T EVEN KNOW
WHAT DIESEL FUEL WAS.
I PULLED UP.
THE REGULAR WAS OUT OF ORDER.
THE SUPREME--
I WAS LIKE, "OH, I'LL JUST
FILL IT UP WITH DIESEL FUEL."
AND THERE
WAS A GREEN BUTTON AND A--
I WAS LIKE, "OH, IT'S PROBABLY
BETTER FOR THE ENVIRONMENT
'CAUSE IT'S GREEN."
AND THEN YOU GUYS
ARE PROBABLY WONDERING
HOW I GOT THE NOZZLE TO FIT,
BECAUSE A DIESEL NOZZLE
DOESN'T EVEN FIT
IN A REGULAR CAR.
I JAMMED IT IN THERE.
I WAS LIKE,
"I'M SELF-SUFFICIENT,
GODDAMMIT!-- UGH!"
A MILE LATER,
MY CAR WAS A BALL OF
- FIRE...
- [laughter]
BUT WOMEN ARE NOT TAUGHT
PRACTICAL INFORMATION LIKE THIS.
WE'RE NOT TAUGHT
TO LIVE IN REALITY.
WE'RE TAUGHT TO LIVE
IN OUR IMAGINATIONS,
IN A FANTASY LAND, RIGHT?
I REMEMBER-- IT'S TRUE.
GROWING UP, I USED TO HAVE
IMAGINARY TEA PARTIES.
I WOULD PUT IMAGINARY TEA
IN IMAGINARY CUPS AND DRINK 'EM
WITH MY STUFFED ANIMALS,
THAT'S FUCKING CRAZY! OKAY?
LIKE, IN ANY OTHER UNIVERSE,
THAT'S JUST SCHIZOPHRENIA,
RIGHT?
AND THE PROBLEM IS,
IT CARRIES INTO ADULTHOOD.
LIKE, GUYS, YOU EVER GET
IN A FIGHT WITH YOUR GIRL,
AND SHE'S MUCH MORE PISSED OFF
AT YOU THAN SHE SHOULD BE?
AND YOU'RE LIKE, "WHOA,
THAT ARGUMENT ESCALATED...
REALLY...FAST."
IT'S 'CAUSE
FOR THE LAST WEEK,
WE'VE BEEN HAVIN'
A FIGHT WITH YOU IN OUR
IMAGINATIONS...
[laughter, cheers, applause]
AND IN OUR HEAD,
YOU SAID ALL THE WRONG SHIT.
SO BY THE TIME
WE SEE YOU IN PERSON,
WE'RE LIKE, "OH, YEAH?!
WELL, THAT'S NOT WHAT
YOU SAID LAST WEEK IN MY MIND!"
[laughter, applause]
I THINK
THERE ARE A LOT OF THINGS
THAT WOMEN DO NOT LEARN,
A LOT OF
PRACTICAL INFORMATION.
LIKE, I DIDN'T
KNOW WHAT A 401(k) WAS
TILL LIKE A MONTH AGO.
I THOUGHT IT WAS A MARATHON.
I SWEAR TO GOD.
I WAS LIKE, "WHY ARE MY FRIENDS
RUNNING IN THIS MARATHON?
"400 MILES?
- FUCK THAT."
- [laughter]
AND THE THINGS THAT ARE SUPPOSED
TO PREPARE WOMEN FOR LIFE DON'T.
LIKE, I WAS IN
THE GIRL SCOUTS.
THE GIRL SCOUTS DOES NOT
TEACH YOU ANY SKILLS, RIGHT?
THE GIRL SCOUTS
BASICALLY TEACHES YOU TO SELL
A BUNCH OF COOKIES
THAT YOU DIDN'T EVEN
FRICKIN' MAKE, OKAY?
LIKE, IF YOU'RE
TO TAKE THE SKILLS YOU LEARNED
IN THE GIRL SCOUTS
AND APPLY THEM
AS AN ADULT,
YOU'RE SELLING THINGS
TO STRANGERS IN A MINISKIRT.
YOU'RE A HOOKER.
THAT'S WHAT YOU DO FOR A LIVING.
- THAT'S YOUR JOB NOW.
- [laughter, applause]
BUT GUYS LEARN REAL SKILLS.
YOU GUYS GO TO THE EAGLE SCOUTS
AND LEARN HOW TO, YOU KNOW,
- MAKE ROPES AND-- EHH!
- [laughter]
YOU KNOW,
MAKE FIRES AND STUFF.
AND WOMEN DON'T LEARN
THOSE KIND OF SURVIVAL SKILLS.
I WAS THINKING ABOUT
HOW MUCH THAT PISSED ME OFF
AFTER THAT HAPPENED TO ME,
BUT THEN I KIND OF, LIKE,
GOT PERSPECTIVE.
I WAS LIKE,
"GUYS MAY KNOW HOW TO MAKE
ROPES AND FIRES AND STUFF,
"BUT WOMEN,
WE CAN MAKE...
'PEOPLE.'"
[laughter, applause]
OKAY, THAT IS
PRETTY BADASS, OKAY?
GIVE ME
THE BACKSEAT OF A TAURUS
AND SOME "SUTTER HOME,"
I CAN DUPLICATE!
[laughter, cheers, applause]
AND GUESS WHAT...
IT COMES OUT
ON A FREAKIN' ROPE.
[laughter, cheers, applause]
IT'S HARD, THOUGH.
GOING FROM A LONG RELATIONSHIP
TO STARTING TO DATE AGAIN
IS VERY DIFFICULT.
'CAUSE WHEN YOU'RE IN
A LONG-TERM RELATIONSHIP,
YOU'RE COMFORTABLE, RIGHT?
YOU DON'T HAVE TO WEAR
ANY MAKEUP.
YOU CAN JUST PEE IN FRONT
OF THE PERSON OR WHATEVER.
WHEN YOU'RE
DATING SOMEBODY NEW,
YOU HAVE TO TRY TO BE PERFECT.
LIKE, I'VE BEEN DATING
A NEW GUY, AND I'VE BEEN
TRYING TO BE SO PERFECT.
BASICALLY, THE FIRST,
LIKE, THREE MONTHS
OF ME DATING THIS GUY--
EVERY SECOND
HAS BASICALLY BEEN ME...
TRYING TO NOT FART.
THAT'S ALL IT IS.
EVERY SECOND OF EVERY DAY.
IT'S JUST LIKE,
"PLEASE DON'T FART.
PLEASE DON'T FART.
PLEASE DON'T FART."
MY ASS IS IN THE SHAPE
OF ITS FUCKING LIFE.
- THAT'S THE UPSIDE.
- [laughter]
BUT THE HARD PART
IS THAT I'LL SOMETIMES
STAY AT HIS HOUSE
FOR A COUPLE DAYS AT A TIME
AND I HAVE TO HOLD IT IN SO LONG
THAT BY THE TIME I LEAVE,
I'M LIKE, "ALL RIGHT,
SEE YOU LATER."
[loud ongoing fart]
SOMETIMES YOU CAN
CATCH AIR AND LIKE,
- [fart, fart]
- [laughter, applause]
'CAUSE YOU'RE
ALWAYS TRYIN' TO BE PERFECT
FOR THE NEW GUY,
YOU KNOW?
LIKE, WHEN I STAY
AT THIS GUY'S HOUSE--
THE EXTENT
TO WHICH I TRY TO BE
PERFECT FOR THIS GUY--
I WILL WAKE UP AT 6:00 A.M.
WHILE HE'S STILL ASLEEP,
SNEAK INTO THE BATHROOM,
PUT ON A FULL FACE OF MAKEUP,
SNEAK BACK INTO BED,
SO BY THE TIME HE WAKES UP,
I LOOK LIKE
LADY GAGA OR SOMETHING,
WHICH IS SO RIDICULOUS.
WOMEN, WE DO NOT NEED
TO LOOK CUTE IN THE MORNING
FOR OUR MAN--
WE DON'T NEED IT,
BECAUSE GUYS,
BEFORE YOUR EYES EVEN OPEN
IN THE MORNING,
- YOU GUYS HAVE ERECTIONS.
- [laughter, applause]
YOU DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHAT'S LYING NEXT TO YOU,
AND YOU'RE
JUST READY TO...
HAVE SEX WITH IT, REALLY?
YOU ARE HEATHENS.
YOU GUYS LITERALLY
WAKE UP IN THE MORNING.
YOU'RE LIKE,
"[snorting, exhales]--
WHERE'S A HOLE?
- GIVE ME A HOLE."
- [laughter, applause]
IT IS BARBARIC.
[laughter continues]
BUT I DO NOT LIKE MORNING SEX.
I DO NOT LIKE MORNING SEX.
SO WHAT I STARTED DOING
IS I'LL CUT A HOLE
IN A CANTALOUPE...
[laughter, groans, applause]
PUT IT IN THE MICROWAVE
FOR A MINUTE...
[laughter, groans]
PUT A WIG ON IT,
LEAVE IT IN THE BED,
- AND BOUNCE.
- [laughter, applause]
IT'S HARD,
'CAUSE NOW I'M DATING,
AND A LOT OF MY FRIENDS
ARE SETTLING DOWN.
A LOT OF MY FRIENDS
ARE GETTING MARRIED RIGHT NOW,
WHICH IS SO ANNOYING,
'CAUSE I FEEL LIKE GUYS
ALWAYS HAVE EXCUSES
WHY THEY DON'T
WANNA GET MARRIED WITH ME.
ALL THESE EXCUSES--
LIKE, ONE OF MY FAVORITES IS,
"WE DON'T HAVE TO GET MARRIED.
IT'S JUST A PIECE OF PAPER."
WHICH IS NOT TRUE.
MARRIAGE IS NOT JUST
A PIECE OF PAPER.
IT'S ABOUT
MORE THAN THAT, OKAY?
IT'S ABOUT...
- A DIAMOND.
- [laughter]
YOU THINK
IN THE HISTORY OF TIME
ANY WOMAN WAS EVER LIKE,
"OH, MY GOD, YOU GUYS,
LOOK AT MY PIECE OF PAPER!"
[high-pitch scream]
- DON'T BE STUPID.
- [laughter]
YOU CAN'T PUT A PIECE OF PAPER
ON eBAY WHEN WE BREAK UP.
THAT'S NOT HELPFUL TO ME.
[laughter]
MY OTHER FAVORITE EXCUSE
THAT I'VE HEARD BEFORE IS,
"YEAH,
WE SHOULDN'T GET MARRIED.
MONOGAMY IS JUST NOT NATURAL."
YEAH,
NEITHER ARE FAKE TITS,
BUT YOU GUYS
FRICKIN' LOVE THOSE!
[laughter, applause]
I HAVE FRIENDS GETTING MARRIED,
SO NOW I GO TO ALL THESE EVENTS.
LIKE, I RECENTLY
HAD TO GO TO A BRIDAL SHOWER
FOR THE FIRST TIME EVER.
NOBODY TOLD ME YOU'RE
SUPPOSED TO BRING SEX TOYS.
I SHOWED UP WITH A TEAPOT,
LIKE AN ASSHOLE.
[laughter]
AND SEX TOYS
HAVE GOTTEN CRAZY.
THERE WAS ONE--
IT WAS A VIBRATOR
THAT HAD FEATHERS?
ON THERE, I WAS LIKE,
"IS THAT IN CASE YOU HAVEN'T
HAD SEX IN SO LONG,
"YOU CAN JUST DUST IT OFF...
[laughter]
AND GET BUSY?"
AND THEN I RECENTLY GOT TO GO
TO A BACHELORETTE PARTY,
WHICH THOSE
ARE ACTUALLY KIND OF FUN.
WE WENT TO A MALE STRIP CLUB,
AND THE THING
THAT CRACKS ME UP ABOUT
MALE STRIPPERS
IS THEY'RE ALWAYS IN, LIKE,
POLICEMEN'S UNIFORMS,
RIGHT, AND LIKE
FIREMEN'S UNIFORMS.
- YOU KNOW
- [laughter]
[whistles, cheers, applause]
MALE STRIPPERS ARE ALWAYS IN
POLICEMEN'S UNIFORMS, FIREMEN'S,
'CAUSE THEY SAY THAT
WOMEN LIKE A "MAN IN UNIFORM."
IT'S NOT ABOUT
"THE UNIFORM," OKAY?
WE LIKE MEN "WITH JOBS."
[laughter, cheers, applause]
[chuckles]
YOU WILL NEVER SEE
A MALE STRIPPER COME OUT
WITH PAJAMA PANTS ON...
HOLDING A VIDEO GAME CONTROLLER
AND A POP-TART.
[laughter, applause]
AND I HAVE TO GO
TO WEDDINGS ALL THE TIME.
AND I THINK THE CRAZIEST PART
ABOUT GOING TO WEDDINGS IS LIKE,
THE CATCHING
OF THE BOUQUET THING,
'CAUSE WOMEN
GET PSYCHO ABOUT--
I WENT IN THERE ONCE
TO TRY TO CATCH THE BOUQUET,
- I GOT SHANKED.
- [laughter, applause]
'CAUSE WHEN THEY SAY
IS THAT IF YOU CATCH THE BOUQUET
THAT MEANS YOU'RE GONNA BE
THE NEXT WOMAN TO GET MARRIED.
NA-AH, CATCH THE BOUQUET,
SEE IF ONE GUY TALKS TO YOU
FOR THE REST OF THE NIGHT.
[laughter]
I HAVE FRIENDS GETTING MARRIED
AND HAVING BABIES NOW, TOO,
LIKE, ON PURPOSE.
- I KNOW.
- [laughter]
I FEEL LIKE WOMEN,
AFTER THEY GIVE BIRTH,
THEY JUST GO INSANE.
LIKE, I HAD A FRIEND OF MINE
WHO HAD A BABY SIX MONTHS AGO,
AND SHE CALLS ME UP,
AND SHE'S LIKE,
"DO YOU WANNA COME OVER
AND WATCH MY BIRTH VIDEO?"
(man)
HAH-HAH-HAH!
I WAS LIKE, UH...
[laughter, applause]
I WAS LIKE,
"HELL, YEAH, I DO."
YOU GUYS,
I WENT OVER THERE.
IT WAS THE BIGGEST COOTER
I'VE EVER SEEN...
[laughter, applause]
BUT LIKE BLAIR WITCH PROJECT,
LIKE SHAKY-CAM COOTER.
[laughter]
IT LOOKED LIKE PORN
FROM DOWNTOWN BAGHDAD, OKAY?
[laughter continues]
AND DID YOU GUYS KNOW THIS?
AFTER THE BABY
COMES OUT OF THERE,
A WHOLE BUNCH OF OTHER SHIT
COMES OUT, YOU GUYS.
A JELLYFISH FLEW BY.
[laughter, applause]
A TRAMPOLINE
CAME OUT OF THERE.
I SWEAR TO GOD, JAMIROQUAI
CAME OUT OF HER THING, GUYS.
IT WAS LIKE
CRAIGSLIST EXPLODED.
I WAS LIKE, "I WANNA GIVE BIRTH
JUST SO I CAN FIND MY CAR KEYS."
- LIKE, WHAT...?
- [laughter, applause]
I THINK ALL OF THAT STUFF--
BABIES AND MARRIAGE--
I THINK THAT
ALL THAT'S ABOUT ROMANCE.
I THINK US WOMEN,
WE ARE OBSESSED
WITH ROMANCE, RIGHT,
AND I THINK WE GET BRAINWASHED
FROM ROMANTIC MOVIES.
I THINK THAT IS WHERE IT COMES
FROM. LIKE, I RECENTLY SAW, UM,
THESE MOVIES CALLED TWILIGHT.
- HAVE WE SEEN THIS MOVIE?
- (male) WOO!
RANDOM YELLING GUY?
YEAH, YOU'VE SEEN IT.
I KNOW YOU HAVE,
FOR SURE.
BUT I RECENTLY SAW
THESE MOVIES TWILIGHT.
THEY ARE SO ROMANTIC.
THIS VAMPIRE'S
MADLY IN LOVE WITH THIS GIRL,
AND THEY'RE SO OBSESSED
WITH EACH OTHER.
THEY BRAINWASH YOU.
I WENT INTO THIS MOVIE.
I WAS LIKE,
"OH, SOME MOVIE ABOUT
HIGH SCHOOLERS."
I CAME OUT OF IT,
I WAS LIKE, "OH, MY GOD,
I HAVE TO MARRY A VAMPIRE.
OH, MY GOD."
- [laughter]
- IT MAKES YOU OBSESSED.
GUYS,
DON'T LET YOUR GIRLFRIENDS
SEE THIS MOVIE.
SHE WILL LEAVE
YOUR ASS, OKAY?
AFTER I SAW THE MOVIE,
I WOULDN'T TALK
TO THE GUY I WAS DATING
FOR, LIKE, FIVE DAYS.
FINALLY, HE WAS LIKE,
"BABE, WHAT'S WRONG?"
I WAS LIKE, "I DON'T KNOW.
"I KINDA NEED TO DATE
SOMEONE WHO CAN...
- 'FLY.'"
- [laughter]
BUT THIS MOVIE--
I THINK IT PROVES THAT
WOMEN HAVE, LIKE,
A BAD-BOY COMPLEX,
'CAUSE THE VAMPIRE
SAYS TO THE GIRL
IN THE BEGINNING OF THE MOVIE--
HE'S LIKE,
"I WANNA KILL YOU.
I WANNA SUCK YOUR BLOOD."
SHE'S LIKE, [innocent voice]
"IT'S OKAY. I TRUST YOU."
[laughter]
AND THEN HE ADMITS
THAT HE'S
KILLED PEOPLE BEFORE,
AND SHE'S FINE WITH IT,
WHICH, ACTUALLY,
I'M SUCH A JEALOUS GIRLFRIEND
THAT IF MY VAMPIRE BOYFRIEND
TOLD ME HE HAD KILLED PEOPLE,
I'D BE LIKE, "WHO WAS SHE?
IS SHE PRETTIER THAN ME,
IS THAT IT?"
- YEAH.
- [cheers, whistles, applause]
I JUST WANT TO DATE A VAMPIRE.
I THINK THAT WOULD BE SO BADASS.
LIKE, DATING A VAMPIRE
WILL LITERALLY SOLVE
ALL YOUR PROBLEMS, RIGHT?
LIKE IF,
IF YOU'RE DATING A VAMPIRE,
YOU WOULD
ALWAYS HAVE THE UPPER HAND.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
LIKE, YOU'D BE DRIVING ALONG
WITH YOUR VAMPIRE,
AND HE'D BE LIKE,
"I'M THINKING ABOUT
SEEING OTHER PEOPLE."
YOU'D BE LIKE, "OH, REALLY,
'CAUSE I'M THINKING ABOUT
- "PUTTING THE SUNROOF DOWN...
- [laughter]
- "BITCH.
- [laughter continues]
DON'T MAKE ME GO TO GNC
AND GET SOME GARLIQUE."
[laughter]
BUT THE PROBLEM WITH VAMPIRES
IS THEY LOOK LIKE THEY'RE 20,
BUT THEY'RE ACTUALLY,
LIKE, 100 YEARS OLD.
SO YOU'D BE DATING
THIS HOT YOUNG GUY
WHO, LIKE, GREW UP
IN THE GREAT DEPRESSION
AND, LIKE,
HATES IRISH PEOPLE.
[laughter]
AND THEN, LIKE,
YOU TAKE HIM OUT TO A NIGHTCLUB,
AND HE'D BE, LIKE,
DOING THE CHARLESTON.
[laughter, applause]
OR, LIKE, YOU THINK
HE'S CHEATING ON YOU,
SO YOU
GO THROUGH HIS JOURNAL.
YOU'RE LIKE,
"WHO THE HELL IS THIS SLUT, HUH?
HARRIET TUBMAN?
WHO THE FUCK IS THAT?!"
YOU GUYS NEED TO BRUSH UP
ON YOUR BLACK HISTORY,
- JUST...
- [laughter]
JUST THAT AREA.
[laughter]
WOMEN GET OBSESSED
WITH ROMANCE.
I THINK IT ALSO COMES FROM
THE NICKNAMES WE GET GROWING UP.
WITH MY DAD GROWING UP,
CALLED ME "PRINCESS," RIGHT?
PRINCESS-- HE DRILLED IT
INTO MY HEAD AS A KID THAT
I'M A FRICKIN' PRINCESS.
AND THEN I GREW UP,
AND I GOT TO THE REAL WORLD,
AND I REALIZED
THAT NO ONE ELSE WAS ON BOARD...
[laughter]
WITH THE WHOLE
PRINCESS THING, RIGHT?
PRINCESSES DON'T LOSE
THEIR VIRGINITY AT LOLLAPALOOZA.
THAT'S JUST NOT...
[laughter, cheers, applause]
I THINK WE NEED TO START
CALLING KIDS THINGS
TO PREPARE THEM
FOR REAL LIFE.
YOU KNOW,
"GET IN THE CAR, REHAB.
LET'S GO."
[laughter]
WOMEN GET CALLED THINGS
THAT MAKE 'EM
OBSESSED WITH ROMANCE.
GUYS GET CALLED THINGS THAT
MAKE 'EM OBSESSED WITH SPORTS.
YOU GUYS GET CALLED,
LIKE, "CHAMP"...
- EHH.
- [laughter]
"SPORT."
YOU GUYS ARE SO OBSESSED
WITH SPORTS,
YOU GUYS CAN'T EVEN REFER
TO INCREMENTS OF A RELATIONSHIP
WITHOUT REFERRING
TO SPORTS, RIGHT?
"FIRST BASE."
"WE GOT TO SECOND BASE."
LIKE, YOU DON'T SEE
WOMEN RUNNING AROUND
REFERRING TO INCREMENTS
OF OUR RELATIONSHIPS
THROUGH THINGS WE LIKE.
IT'S NOT LIKE,
"LAST NIGHT, ME AND MARK...
UGH! CHANEL PURSE."
[laughter, applause]
YOU GUYS
ARE SO OBSESSED WITH SPORTS
THAT YOU GUYS
WILL WEAR JERSEYS
FOR TEAMS
THAT YOU'RE NOT EVEN ON...
[laughter]
BUT YOU THINK
YOU'RE ON THE TEAM.
YOU'LL BE LIKE,
"YEAH, LAST NIGHT I GUESS
" WE JUST DIDN'T SCORE ENOUGH.
[laughter]
LAST NIGHT I GUESS WE JUST
DIDN'T PLAY ENOUGH DEFENSE."
- "'WE'?
- [laughter]
"THE REDSKINS
DON'T NEED 'YOU.'
[laughter]
"OKAY, THAT'S LIKE
ME WATCHING GREY'S ANATOMY
IN SCRUBS."
[laughter]
[whistles]
[cheers, applause]
BUT THEN
AFTER THE SHOW IS OVER,
I'D BE LIKE,
"OH, GOD, WE JUST
COULD NOT SAVE THAT GUY.
I DON'T KNOW."
[laughter]
YOU GUYS LOVE SPORTS SO MUCH,
YOU GUYS CAN'T EVEN
THROW YOUR TRASH
INTO THE GARBAGE NORMALLY.
[laughter]
YOU GUYS HAVE TO SHOOT
YOUR GARBAGE ACROSS THE ROOM
LIKE IT'S
AN NBA BASKETBALL GAME.
LIKE, YOU DON'T SEE WOMEN LIVING
OUT OUR DREAMS WITH OUR TRASH.
I DON'T TAKE, LIKE,
A USED GUM WRAPPER,
PUT IT AROUND MY RING FINGER
AND BE LIKE...
[laughter, applause]
"BRAD PITT AND I
ARE THINKING ABOUT THE FALL,
- SO..."
- [laughter]
YOU GUYS LOVE SPORTS SO MUCH
THAT YOU GUYS--
I FEEL LIKE YOU GUYS DO THINGS
YOU WOULD NEVER NORMALLY DO,
JUST 'CAUSE
THEY HAVE SPORTS TERMS
ASSOCIATED WITH THEM.
LIKE, I HAVE A FEELING
THE ONLY REASON
YOU GUYS LIKE BEING SINGLE
IS 'CAUSE IT'S CALLED
"PLAYING THE FIELD,"
'CAUSE YOU GUYS
HAVE CONVINCED YOURSELVES
THAT YOU'RE OUT THERE--
LIKE, "I'M SHOOTIN' AND SCORIN'
WITH THESE CHICKS.
"I'M SHOOTIN' AND SCORIN'.
UH, I'M SUCH A...
I'M PLAYING THE FIELD.
I'M SO GREAT."
NO, YOU'RE
HOME ALONE JERKING OFF
TO PORN ON YOUR COUCH.
THAT'S WHAT YOU'RE DOING.
[laughter, applause]
WHICH, I DON'T LIKE PORN.
I DO NOT LIKE PORN BECAUSE...
- [clapping]
- YOU LOVE PORN?
WHAT DO WE LIKE GOIN' ON?"
WHAT DO WE HAVE
GOIN' ON UP THERE?
YAY PORN OR NO PORN?
- (male) YAY PORN!
- YAY PORN.
- [cheers, applause]
- OH, GOOD, I LIKE YOU GUYS.
D.C., DO YOU GUYS HAVE, LIKE,
POLITICAL PORN, LIKE, KINDA...
LIKE, "OH, LOOK.
IT'S FUCKIN'..."
UH, I DON'T
KNOW ANY POLITICIANS.
- UH...
- [laughter, applause]
[cheers, applause]
I LITERALLY-- THE FIRST THING
THAT CAME TO MIND WAS ART MONK
- WHO WAS NOT...
- (male) YEAH!
YOU GUYS ARE PROBABLY
TOO YOUNG TO REMEMBER THIS.
UM, HE WAS NOT A POLITICIAN.
[laughter]
TEN-YEAR-OLD
IN THE FRONT. OKAY.
[laughter]
I DON'T LIKE PORN,
BECAUSE PORN MAKES YOU REALIZE
ALL THE THINGS
YOU'RE NOT DOING RIGHT.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
EVERY TIME I WATCH PORN,
LIKE, I'M REMINDED
OF ALL THE THINGS I'M NOT DOING.
I SAW PORN RECENTLY.
I SAW THAT WOMEN
ARE SHAVING BALD.
THEIR PUBES BALD.
ARE WE DOIN' THIS, D.C.?
- [woman cheering]
- OKAY, I LIKE THIS.
WELL, YOU SHOULDN'T.
IT GETS WAY TOO COLD
HERE IN THE WINTER.
DON'T SHAVE IT.
YOU'RE 10.
- DON'T.
- [laughter]
DON'T YOU LOOK AT HER.
JUST 'CAUSE
SHE LOOKS LIKE A LITTLE BOY.
- DON'T YOU DARE.
- [oh's, cheers, applause]
I DON'T GET
THE SHAVING YOUR JUNK.
'CAUSE I WAS LIKE, "OH, MY GOD.
LIKE, WOMEN ARE DOING THAT NOW."
SO I WENT TO GO SHAVE.
I GOT RAZOR BURN.
I LOOKED LIKE I HAD HERPES
FOR TWO WEEKS, OKAY?
- THAT'S NOT CUTE.
- [laughter]
GUYS ARE INTO THAT NOW.
YOU GUYS WANT WOMEN
TO LOOK LIKE LITTLE GIRLS,
WHICH IS NOT--
MY WHOLE THING IS
YOU WANT TO DO
A LITTLE-GIRL FANTASY?
LIKE, I ALREADY
CRY AND THROW TANTRUMS
EVERY FUCKING DAY--
WHAT MORE DO YOU WANT?
YOU WANT ME
TO PEE ON YOUR COUCH?
- I CAN DO THAT.
- [laughter]
LIKE, YOU WANT TO DO
A LITTLE-GIRL FANTASY?
HOW 'BOUT YOU PAY ME
AN ALLOWANCE?
LET'S START THERE.
HOW ABOUT YOU PACK ME A LUNCH?
I LIKE THIS IDEA. YES.
[laughter]
I DON'T LIKE PORN,
BECAUSE I THINK IT SETS
THE BAR TOO HIGH.
LIKE, I DON'T WANT TO HAVE
TO COMPETE WITH PORN.
LIKE, I FEEL LIKE WOMEN IN PORN
ARE ALWAYS YELLING SO LOUD,
WHICH I GUESS YOU GUYS
THINK THAT'S SEXY.
I'M NOT LIKE THAT AT ALL.
I'M VERY QUIET IN THE BEDROOM.
I LIKE TO KEEP
A VERY LOW PROFILE IN THERE.
[laughter]
I WILL OCCASIONALLY
WHISPER ENCOURAGING THINGS.
[laughter]
YOU KNOW, I'LL BE LIKE,
"GOOD JOB.
[laughter, applause]
"I REALLY APPRECIATE THAT.
"I REALLY THINK YOU'RE SHOWING
A LOT OF IMPROVEMENT.
[laughter, applause]
[chanting]
RUDY. RUDY. RUDY."
[laughter, applause]
IF YOU GUYS NEVER WATCH PORN,
YOUR SEX LIVES
WOULD BE SO MUCH BETTER,
'CAUSE THE BAR WOULD BE
SO MUCH LOWER, RIGHT?
IF YOU GUYS
NEVER WATCHED PORN,
YOU'D COME HOME,
YOU'D SEE YOUR GIRL
LYING ON THE BED.
YOU'D BE LIKE, "OH MY GOD.
SHE'S WEARING SWEATPANTS.
[laughter]
LOOK AT THAT SNUGGY."
[laughter, applause]
WHY DO I THINK
ALL YOUR PENISES
ARE THIS LONG?
[laughter]
I DON'T LIKE PORN.
WOMEN DO NOT LIKE PORN.
WE'RE WAY TOO SENSITIVE.
DO YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
LIKE, WHEN I WATCH PORN,
I'M NOT LIKE INTO IT,
AND LIKE, "OH YEAH."
I JUST GET VERY WORRIED
ABOUT THE WOMEN IN THE PORN.
I START SPINNING OUT--
I'M LIKE, "OH, MY GOD.
"SHE PROBABLY
DIDN'T GO TO COLLEGE.
THIS IS NOT GOOD.
SHE REALLY NEEDS
A BACKUP PLAN."
[laughter, applause]
BUT I THINK WOMEN
SHOULD WATCH PORN MORE,
BECAUSE WOMEN--
IF YOU GUYS WATCH PORN, LADIES,
YOU WOULD SEE WHERE YOUR MAN
WAS GETTING ALL THOSE
STUPID FRICKIN' IDEAS.
LIKE, LITERALLY
EVERY TIME I WATCH PORN,
I'M LIKE, "OH, THAT'S WHY
HE MADE ME BUY ROLLER SKATES.
OKAY, THAT'S WHY
THERE'S TWO POUNDS OF PUDDING
IN THE FRIDGE-- OKAY."
[laughter]
BUT WOMEN
ARE TOO SENSITIVE FOR THAT.
LIKE, I DON'T LIKE PORN.
IT'S TOO GRAPHIC.
LIKE, IF PORN
WAS MADE FOR WOMEN,
IT WOULD JUST BE, LIKE,
TWO HOURS OF SNUGGLING...
AND AT THE END,
THE GUY WOULD PROPOSE.
[laughter]
I WOULD WATCH THAT.
I WOULD LIKE TO SEE THAT.
I DON'T LIKE PORN.
THE THING THAT CRACKS ME UP
THE MOST ABOUT PORN
IS YOU GUYS DON'T THINK
WE KNOW YOU WATCH IT.
IT IS SO OBVIOUS,
ESPECIALLY IF YOU WATCH IT
ON THE COMPUTER,
'CAUSE EITHER, NUMBER ONE,
YOU ERASE YOUR HISTORY...
IN THE MENU BAR--
AND I KNOW
YOU DID SOME CRAZY SHIT--
[laughter]
OR YOU DON'T ERASE
YOUR HISTORY,
AND I TRY TO GO
TO Google.com,
BUT IT GOES TO
GoodJigglyJugs.com...
[laughter]
DEAL WITH THAT AT 7:00 A.M.
THE OTHER REASON
WE KNOW YOU GUYS WATCH PORN
IS 'CAUSE YOU GUYS
WILL DO THINGS IN THE BEDROOM
THAT YOU'RE OBVIOUSLY,
LIKE, COPYING FROM PORN,
LIKE THE SPANKING THING.
WHEN YOU GUYS DO THIS,
WE'RE JUST
FRICKIN' LAUGHING AT YOU,
OKAY? I'M SORRY.
WE'RE LIKE,
"YEAH, I'M A BAD GIRL.
- "PFFFT!
- [laughter]
- "WHAT AN IDIOT.
- [laughter continues]
PLEASE DON'T FART.
PLEASE DON'T FART."
[laughter, applause]
[cheers, applause]
THE NEW THING YOU GUYS
ARE DOING IN THE BEDROOM
THAT I KNOW
YOU'RE COPYING FROM PORN
IS THE CHOKING THING.
(woman) OH!
YOU ALWAYS KNOW
WHO'S BEEN CHOKED.
[laughter, cheers, applause]
IT'S LIKE,
I DIDN'T KNOW
THE CHOKING THING WAS GOING ON.
IMAGINE MY SURPRISE...
THE FIRST TIME THAT WENT DOWN,
I WAS LIKE,
"UGH. I DON'T KNOW
WHERE HE PUT THE MONEY."
[laughter]
THE FUNNY THING TO ME
ABOUT THE CHOKING THING
IS IT'S THE ONLY FAKE, LIKE,
"I'M GONNA KILL YOU"
THING YOU CAN DO
IN THE BEDROOM
THAT'S ACTUALLY SEXY.
LIKE, YOU CAN'T MIME ANY OTHER
KILLING TACTICS IN THE BEDROOM.
IT'S NOT LIKE
A NAKED GUY CAN COME OUT
OF THE BATHROOM AND BE LIKE...
[imitating Jaws theme]
* DA NA
* DA-NA DA-NA
DA-NA DA-NA *
[laughter, applause]
GUYS ARE
INTO THE CHOKING THING.
SO NOW WHEN A GUY TRIES
TO CHOKE ME IN THE BEDROOM,
I'LL JUST GO ALONG WITH IT.
I'LL BE LIKE,
"OOH-AH!
[laughter]
"UH-AHH-AHH!
UUUUUAAAAAA..."
YOU GOTTA SELL IT!
[laughter, applause]
I USED TO WORRY ABOUT PORN.
I USED TO BE LIKE, "OH, MY GOD,
MY MAN'S WATCHING PORN."
YOU KNOW, "HE DOESN'T LOVE ME,
OR HE'S NOT ATTRACTED TO ME."
PORN IS NOT A THREAT
TO OUR RELATIONSHIPS.
I LIKE TO THINK
ABOUT IT LIKE THIS--
GUYS WATCHING PORN
IS LIKE WOMEN WATCHING
THE FOOD NETWORK.
'KAY, WE'RE BOTH WATCHING THINGS
WE ARE NEVER GONNA FRIGGIN' DO.
[laughter, applause]
WOMEN HAVE OUR OWN VERSION
OF PORN, RIGHT?
OUR VERSION OF PORN
IS ROMANTIC COMEDIES, RIGHT?
WE COMPARE YOU GUYS TO THE MEN
IN ROMANTIC COMEDIES
JUST LIKE YOU COMPARE US
TO THE WOMEN IN PORN, RIGHT?
YOU GUYS TAKE US OUT
TO A FIVE-STAR RESTAURANT
WITH SHRIMP AND CHAMPAGNE--
IN OUR MINDS WE'RE LIKE,
"YEAH, WELL,
MATTHEW MCCONAUGHEY
TOOK HIS GIRLFRIEND
"INTO A HOT-AIR BALLOON
AND GOT HER A DIAMOND NECKLACE
AND A PANDA--
THIS IS FUCKING BULLSHIT!"
ROMANTIC COMEDIES--
THEY BRAINWASH WOMEN.
THEY MAKE US BELIEVE IN, LIKE,
"FATE" AND "DESTINY."
FATE AND DESTINY
ARE NAMES OF STRIPPERS, OKAY?
THEY'RE NOT REAL...
[laughter, applause]
IT'S WEIRD, THOUGH,
BECAUSE ROMANTIC COMEDIES
SET THE BAR SO HIGH
FOR YOU GUYS,
BUT WHAT'S WEIRD
IS THAT GUYS ARE THE ONES
THAT WRITE
ALL THE ROMANTIC COMEDIES.
GUYS RUN HOLLYWOOD.
IF WOMEN RAN HOLLYWOOD,
THE ROMANTIC COMEDIES WOULD BE
A LOT MORE REALISTIC,
SO THERE'D BE
A LOT LESS DISAPPOINTMENT
WHEN YOU LEFT THE THEATER.
NO MORE FRIGGIN' MODELS BEING
CAST AS THE LEAD OF EVERY MOVIE.
LEAD OF EVERY MOVIE
IF WOMEN RAN HOLLYWOOD?
KATHY FREAKIN' BATES, BITCH.
ANGELINA JOLIE
WOULD NEVER WORK AGAIN.
I DON'T CARE.
CAMBODIA CAN FUCKING HAVE HER.
- FUCK HER.
- [laughter]
[cheers, applause]
OUR NEW SEXY ACTION STAR--
OPRAH. BAM!
SHE BLOWS SOME SHIT UP
AND EVERYONE GETS A CAR.
[laughter]
- I WOULD SEE THAT MOVIE.
- [laughter continues]
IT'S FUNNY, THOUGH,
'CAUSE I FEEL LIKE
ROMANTIC COMEDIES SET THE BAR
SO HIGH FOR YOU GUYS.
WE WANT YOU GUYS TO ACT LIKE
THE MEN IN ROMANTIC COMEDIES,
BUT IF YOU EVER DID ACT LIKE
IT WOULD TOTALLY
BACKFIRE, RIGHT?
LIKE CARRYING A WOMAN
UP THE STAIRS.
"I'M GONNA CARRY
MY WOMAN UP THE STAIRS AND
SWEEP HER OFF HER FEET."
IF YOU GUYS TRY TO DO THAT
IN REAL LIFE,
YOU BETTER MAKE SURE YOU DON'T
SO MUCH AS FREAKIN' WINCE.
[laughter]
YOU BETTER GO TO THE GYM.
YOU MAKE SURE YOU CAN
LIFT HER WEIGHT, BITCHES...
[laughter]
'CAUSE IF THERE IS LIKE A...
[grunting]
YOU ARE SO FUCKED.
[laughter]
JUST KILL YOURSELF.
LIKE, IT'S NOT EVEN WORTH IT.
"OH, WHAT, I'M FAT?
IS THAT IT, I'M FAT?
"GEORGE CLOONEY COULD'VE
CARRIED ME UP THE STAIRS.
"RUBEN STUDDARD COULD'VE
YOU HAVE A SMALL DICK!"
[laughter, applause]
ANOTHER THING I FEEL LIKE
GUYS ARE ALWAYS DOING
IN ROMANTIC COMEDIES THAT WOULD
NEVER FLY IN REAL LIFE
IS GUYS ARE ALWAYS
LIGHTING CANDLES TO BE ROMANTIC.
NO. WOMEN ARE OBSESSED
WITH CANDLES.
WE'RE LIKE PYROMANIACS, RIGHT?
YOU GUYS COME OVER.
WE HAVE CANDLES EVERYWHERE.
YOU DON'T KNOW IF
WE'RE GONNA HAVE SEX WITH YOU
OR SACRIFICE YOU, RIGHT?
BUT, GUYS,
YOU CANNOT LIGHT CANDLES.
IF I GO TO A GUY'S HOUSE
AND HE'S GOT CANDLES EVERYWHERE,
I DON'T THINK YOU'RE "ROMANTIC."
I THINK YOU TOOK A "DUMP," OKAY?
[laughter, applause]
WE KNOW WHAT YOU'RE DOING.
STOP-- EHH--
TRYIN' TO "GLADE"
YOUR WAY OUT OF THAT...
CHIPOTLE-- JUST STOP.
[laughter, applause]
THE OTHER THING GUYS DO
IN ROMANTIC COMEDIES
THAT WOULD NEVER FLY
IN REAL LIFE
IS GUYS ARE ALWAYS,
LIKE, SHOWING UP UNANNOUNCED.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
LIKE, I WAS WATCHING ONE,
WHERE THIS WOMAN WAS LIKE,
GARDENING OR SOMETHING
AND THE GUY WAS
LIKE, STANDING THERE,
AND SHE TURNS AROUND,
SHE'S LIKE, "OH, MY GOD,
WHAT'RE YOU DOING HERE?"
AND THE GUY WAS LIKE,
"I JUST HAD TO SEE YOU."
FIRST OF ALL, IT'S 2010.
YOU CAN SEND
A FUCKING TEXT, OKAY?
STOP BEING A CREEPY STALKER.
IT'S WEIRD.
SECOND OF ALL, WOMEN, WE DO NOT
LIKE BEING SNUCK UP ON, OKAY?
I NEED A LOT OF TIME
BEFORE I SEE MY MAN.
A LOT OF THINGS
NEED TO GO DOWN
BEFORE I SEE MY MAN.
I DON'T WANT ANY SURPRISES,
ALL RIGHT?
I GOT TO GET
THE BABY WIPES OUT...
[laughter]
[laughter, applause]
I GOT TO GET
SOME UNDER-EYE CONCEALER
SO I DON'T LOOK LIKE
AN AVATAR.
A LOT OF THINGS
HAVE TO GO DOWN, OKAY?
BUT IT'S SO CRAZY,
'CAUSE WOMEN,
WE PUT SO MUCH EFFORT
INTO GETTING READY--
HOURS BEFORE WE LEAVE
THE HOUSE, RIGHT?
HAIR AND MAKEUP
AND SHAVING AND TWEEZING
AND PLUCKING AND EYELINER--
WHICH IS RIDICULOUS,
'CAUSE WOMEN ARE
NATURALLY BEAUTIFUL, RIGHT?
YOU GUYS DON'T NEED ANY MAKEUP.
WOMEN WAKE UP IN THE MORNING
AND ARE
NATURALLY BEAUTIFUL, PERIOD.
YOU GUYS
ARE FUCKING DISGUSTING...
[laughter, applause]
AND YOU DON'T HAVE TO DO
ANYTHING.
YOU JUST ROLL OUT OF BED
WITH THOSE BALLS.
- HOW DARE YOU?
- [laughter, cheers, applause]
THEY ARE SO AWFUL.
THEY'RE EMBARRASSING.
THAT'S WHAT NEEDS THREE HOURS
OF MAKEUP, RIGHT THERE--
- [laughter, applause]
- SOME CONCEALER, YEAH.
MAYBE A HOT IRON TO...
IRON OUT THOSE WRINKLES,
PLEASE.
[laughter, applause]
BUT THE ONE THING
YOU GUYS DO HAVE TO DO--
LIKE, SHAVE YOUR FACE--
YOU DON'T EVEN HAVE TO DO IT.
IF YOU GUYS DON'T SHAVE,
IT'S SEXY-- IT'S DISTINGUISHED.
IF WE DON'T SHAVE,
"WE'RE LESBIANS."
- THAT'S HOW THAT GOES DOWN.
- [laughter]
WOMEN--
WE TORTURE OURSELVES, RIGHT?
AT ANY GIVEN MOMENT,
WOMEN ARE WEARING
SO MANY TORTURE DEVICES.
LIKE, THONG UNDERWEAR--
WHO INVENTED THAT?
FUCK YOU.
[women cheering]
IT IS TERRIBLE.
LIKE, YOU KNOW A WOMAN
DID NOT INVENT THONG UNDERWEAR,
'CAUSE NO WOMAN
WAS EVER STANDING AROUND
IN FULL UNDERWEAR
AND WAS LIKE,
"YOU KNOW WHAT WOULD BE
SO MUCH MORE COMFORTABLE?
[laughing]
"IF ALL OF THIS FABRIC...
[laughter]
"WAS JUST...
"LIKE, VIOLENTLY...
"RIDING UP MY ASSHOLE.
"IS THERE A WAY
YOU CAN GET ALL THIS FABRIC
"TO JUST TRY
TO RAPE MY BUTT HOLE?
"IS THAT...?
[laughter, cheering]
"I WANT IT JUST TO FEEL LIKE
"A RUBBER BAND
IS SNAPPING...
"I WANT IT TO FEEL LIKE
AN ALLIGATOR IS ACTUALLY
EATING ME OUT--
CAN YOU DO THAT?"
[laughter, applause]
WHAT IS THE POINT
OF THONG UNDERWEAR?
THE POINT
IS SO THAT WE DON'T HAVE
PANTY LINES.
FOR WHAT? YOU THINK
IN THE HISTORY OF TIME
ANY GUY
WAS EVER STANDING AROUND,
LIKE, AT A NIGHTCLUB BAR
WITH HIS BUDDY AND WAS LIKE--
THIS IS MY BUDDY,
BY THE WAY-- UM...
HE WAS LIKE, "HEY, DUDE,
CHECK OUT THAT GIRL.
"OH, MY GOD, SHE IS SO HOT.
"SHE'S SO SEXY.
I'VE GOT TO TALK TO HER.
ALL RIGHT,
I'M GONNA GO TALK TO HER.
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK."
[laughter]
"DUDE, DUDE...
"WHAT ARE THOSE LINES?
[laughter]
OH, MY GOD, NEVER MIND.
THAT'S DISGUSTING."
- [laughter]
- IT'S RIDICULOUS.
AND MOST OF THESE
TORTURE DEVICES MEN INVENTED.
YOU KNOW GUYS INVENTED
HIGH-HEEL SHOES.
THAT WAS A GUY'S INVENTION,
WHICH I HAVE A THEORY
ABOUT THIS.
I HAVE A THEORY
THAT, LIKE, 200 YEARS AGO,
WOMEN WERE WEARING FLAT SHOES
GETTING WHERE THEY NEEDED TO GO.
A BUNCH OF GUYS GOT IN A ROOM,
AND THEY WERE LIKE,
"GOD, THESE WOMEN,
THEY ARE GORGEOUS.
"THEY ARE BEAUTIFUL.
THE ONLY PROBLEM IS
"THEY ARE REALLY HARD
TO HAVE SEX WITH.
"I MEAN,
THEY CAN JUST GET UP
- "AND WALK AWAY.
- [laughter]
"WE NEED TO DO SOMETHING
TO JUST SLOW 'EM DOWN.
"WHAT IF WE JUST PUT,
LIKE, A FOUR-INCH BRICK
ON THE BACK OF THEIR FOOT?
YOU THINK THEY'D DO THAT?"
AND IT WORKS,
'CAUSE I'VE TALKED TO GUYS
EXTRA HOURS LONGER
THAN I WANTED TO
'CAUSE MY FEET
WERE FRICKIN' KILLING ME.
I'VE GOTTEN TO THE POINT
WHERE I'M JUST LIKE, "DUDE,
"CAN I JUST HAVE
THAT ROOFIE NOW,
'CAUSE MY FEET...
"I CAN'T FEEL ANYTHING.
PLEASE."
THOSE HEELS-- YOU KNOW THEY
CALL THOSE REALLY HIGH HEELS--
THEY CALL THEM "FUCK-ME HEELS."
THAT'S WHAT THEY CALL THEM.
'CAUSE WHEN YOU PUT 'EM ON,
YOU'RE LIKE, "OH, FUCK ME.
REALLY?
WE'RE DOING THIS AGAIN?"
I DON'T LIKE TO WEAR
FUCK-ME HEELS.
I LIKE TO WEAR...
"LET'S JUST BE FRIENDS"
SNEAKERS.
[laughter, cheers, applause]
GUYS ALSO INVENTED
UNDERWIRE BRAS, WHICH AGAIN,
ONLY A GUY'S INSENSITIVE MIND
WOULD COME UP WITH THAT.
'CAUSE ONLY A GUY'S MIND
WOULD BE SO INSENSITIVE
THAT THEY
WOULD SEE A SOFT BRA
WITH A WOMAN'S BOOBS
AND WAS LIKE,
"YOU KNOW WHAT THAT THING NEEDS?
I THINK THAT NEEDS
A SKEWER RIGHT THROUGH..."
IT'S NOT A KABOB.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
THIS ISN'T FUCKING FIGHT CLUB.
WHAT IS GOING ON IN YOUR HEAD?
AND THEN IN THE '70s
WOMEN STARTED GETTING PISSED OFF
'CAUSE THEY
HURT SO MUCH, RIGHT?
AND THEN WOMEN
STARTED BURNING THEIR BRAS.
AND THEN GUYS
INVENTED WATER BRAS...
SO WE COULDN'T
BURN 'EM ANYMORE.
- [laughter]
- THAT'S ACTUALLY PRETTY SMART.
I GOTTA GIVE YOU
A GOLD STAR FOR THAT.
AND THEN THEY WERE LIKE,
"YOU KNOW WHAT?
THESE WOMEN-- STILL,
THE BOOBS ARE NOT BIG ENOUGH."
AND THEN YOU GUYS
INVENTED BREAST IMPLANTS.
WHAT? THE NEXT STEP
WAS CUT 'EM OPEN
AND FILL THEM WITH JELL-O?
ARE YOU OUT OF
YOUR FUCKING MIND?
WOMEN, DO NOT GET
BREAST IMPLANTS.
DO NOT LET
SOCIETY'S IDEAL OF BEAUTY--
- [cheers, applause]
- YEAH...
MESS WITH YOUR SELF-WORTH.
DO NOT GET-- LOVE YOUR BODY,
FUCK THE MEDIA.
IT'S ALL PHOTOSHOP.
LOVE YOUR BODY-- YEAH.
SERIOUS NOTE
FROM WHITNEY CUMMINGS.
- UM...
- [laughter]
BUT YOU ALSO DON'T
WANNA GET BREAST IMPLANTS,
'CAUSE IF YOU GET
BREAST IMPLANTS,
YOU'RE JUST GONNA ATTRACT
THE WRONG KIND OF GUY.
EVERY GUY IN AN ED HARDY SHIRT
IS GONNA WANT TO TALK TO YOU.
- IS THAT WHAT YOU WANT?
- [laughter, applause]
EVERY GUY
IN A BLUETOOTH HEADSET
WITH FLAMES
ON THE SIDE OF HIS CAR,
STITCHING ON HIS JEANS...
- IS THAT WHAT YOU WANT?
- [laughter, applause]
SEE, I DON'T HAVE ANY BOOBS,
- AND MY LIFE IS QUIET.
- [laughter]
NO ONE TRIES TO TALK TO ME.
I CAN GO INTO A NIGHTCLUB.
NO ONE HARASSES ME.
NO ONE EVEN TRIES TO HUG ME.
THIS IS NO FUN.
NO ONE WANTS TO DO
THE STERNUM BUMP.
- IT'S NOT FUN.
- [laughter]
I WALK
BY A CONSTRUCTION SITE--
- SHOOOO...QUIET.
- [laughter]
EVERY NOW AND THEN
A CONSTRUCTION GUY'LL BE LIKE,
- "YO, WHAT'S UP, DUDE?"
- [laughter]
WHICH-- I DON'T GET THAT.
WHAT IS THE YELLING AT WOMEN?
WHAT IS THE--
YELLING AT STRANGERS?
WHAT IS THAT?
WHAT DOES THAT ACCOMPLISH?
LIKE, DO YOU THINK
IN THIS HISTORY OF TIME
FIVE DUDES
IN THE BACK OF A TRUCK
YELLING AT A GIRL JOGGING
HAS EVER WORKED?
DO YOU THINK
IN THE HISTORY OF TIME
ANY GIRL WAS EVER LIKE...
[breathing heavily]
AND HEARD, "AY-YI-YI-YI,
LET ME SEE THOSE TITTIES!"
[laughter]
LIKE, DO YOU THINK
IN THE HISTORY OF TIME
ANYONE EVER SAT DOWN
WITH A HAPPILY MARRIED COUPLE
AND WAS LIKE,
"HEY, SO HOW DID YOU TWO MEET?"
AND THE GIRL'S LIKE,
"WELL, UH,
"ONE MORNING I WAS JOGGING,
"AND THIS TRUCK
FULL OF FIVE DUDES DROVE BY.
"ONE OF THEM YELLED OUT,
"'I WANNA
PUT IT IN YOUR BUTT,'
[laughter]
AND I WAS LIKE,
'HE'S THE ONE.'"
[laughter, applause]
I LOVE YOU GUYS.
I'M WHITNEY CUMMINGS.
THANK YOU SO MUCH!
- [cheers and applause]
- THANK YOU!
WOW!
OH, WOW!
THANK YOU!
OH, GOD!
OH, WOW! THANK YOU!
OH, WOW!
[cheers, whistles, applause]
THANK YOU.
DEAD EYES