(soft orchestral music)
(uptempo orchestral music)
(tense orchestral music)
- It's this way.
- Whoa.
It's down there, isn't it?
- Yep.
- Yeah.
- [Pursuer] Here we go, over here.
- We have to hurry.
- Let's get the ropes.
(tense music)
- Ready?
- You first.
- Scared?
- Huh.
- Show off.
(tense orchestral music)
- They're close.
- This will slow 'em down.
Let's go.
(tense orchestral music)
Well, this is it.
But where?
- Should be somewhere on the cave wall.
(mysterious music)
I'll start over here.
- Okay, I'll take this side.
- Shane.
- Is that?
- I think.
- That's it.
That's it, you found it.
- We found it, together.
- Yeah!
Yeah.
- A fist bump? Really Ethan?
- Will they have the map now.
- That's the end of the story, though.
- Yeah.
- Well, I imagine some
sort of happy ending.
- But this is a happy ending.
They found the map.
And now onto the next book of my series
where they'll use it to find the artifact.
- What about Shane and
Sabrina's relationship though?
The romance?
- Romance doesn't really fit in my books.
- I know Mister Action Adventure,
but that doesn't mean you
can't have some romance in it.
They should at least hug
and share a long look,
or maybe even a kiss.
- Seriously, Mackenzie, I
need your help on this, okay?
What did you think overall?
- I like it.
The villain seems a little over the top,
and I don't always get his motivation.
- Good.
What else?
- I like the chemistry
between Shane and Sabrina,
but I really do think
they have a relationship
that could be developed
into something more.
- Duly noted.
- You're not gonna do
anything about that, are you?
- No, but thank you for reading my latest.
You're the best.
- Happy to.
And my compensation?
(oven beeping)
- Just in time.
It's a good bake, I think.
- Heavenly.
- I've offered to teach
you how to make this
like 20 times by now, right?
- I say, why bother learning when?
- When you could be
dependent on me, I know.
- You're dependent on my
opinion of your books.
So it's more like job security.
- But you really like the book though?
- Yes.
You doubt me every time.
- Well, rule number one of feedback
is you don't ask your friends.
- But you do because I'm
always honest with you,
even brutal at times.
- Well, now I just have to
brace myself for my editor.
- It'll be fine, it always is.
- So, anything cool going on at work?
- Nothing like adventures
through the jungle
to a hidden map, no.
- Come on, you have the ultimate dream job
working at a candy company.
- Chocolate.
- Even better.
- It doesn't necessarily
mean it's exciting.
- Well, whatever happened to
that new guy you talked about,
the floor manager.
- Nothing, he's just a new face.
- Well, maybe you should talk to him.
- I'm really not interested
in him, or an office romance.
- Why not?
You deserve to be happy.
- Pass me the jam.
- Yeah.
(bright orchestral music)
- Morning.
- Just in time.
- Oh right, is she?
- I haven't seen her yet.
- Hurry up ladies or you'll be late.
Last quarter, sales were up in a big way.
Good job, everyone.
It is about time.
And now with that, I have good news.
A new customer wants our chocolates,
and not just any customer,
but Golden Gifts.
- Golden?
They have like 300 stores
across the country.
- Try 437 and expanding globally.
This is just what we need
to help with our expansion,
but we need to up production.
- We're already at capacity,
and hiring has been-
- Okay, well come up with a plan Marvin,
and we'll discuss it.
We need this deal, all of us.
Besides I'm more concerned
about our sourcing.
Mackenzie, we need more cacao,
and with increased volume,
we have to get better prices, too.
- Okay, how much more?
- Projections are at 40% more,
so go down and see our vendor in Colombia.
- Costa Rica.
- Yeah, there, go negotiate it.
- Great work.
Scheduling the Golden
Gifts is gonna be fun.
I don't know where I'll fit it in.
- Ah, you'll find a way.
- Any way you can convince Evelyn
that I need to tag along to Costa Rica?
- I can try,
but since I've already been
several times without you,
I think she'll see through it.
- I need to get a better job here.
- It's not so bad.
- Says the one going
to exotic destinations.
- Yeah, it's hardly exotic when it's work.
- You just need to mix business
with a little bit of pleasure, right?
- Like that'll happen.
- It could, if you would just
give up on Ethan the clueless.
- He's not clueless.
I'm just very discreet about how I feel.
- I don't know what
you see in him, anyway.
- You hardly know him.
He's smart and creative,
and it's fun when we're together.
- Because sitting around
reading books is fun.
- To a lot of people, yes.
That's not all we do.
And besides he's always
there for me when it counts.
- Well, you need to
make it obvious to him.
Nothing will happen if you don't.
- No, no, he's too
valuable to me as a friend.
I don't wanna.
- Risk losing his
friendship, blah, blah, blah.
Do something then.
You two are in such a
routine he can't see you
as anything but a friend.
If you want anything to change,
you need to find a way to shake things up.
- Okay, fine, message received.
- Thank you.
- Ethan.
- Hey Larry.
- It's good to see you, man.
- You too.
- Thanks for meeting me here.
Starvin'.
- Ah no problem.
- You want a coffee?
- No, I'm good, thank you.
So, got the draft already, huh?
- Yeah.
- And?
- Look,
it's not my idea,
but the higher ups feel like your work
could use a new dimension.
- What, why?
- You know, to vary things up a bit,
bring in some new readers.
- I thought I had a steady
following, a growing following.
- You do.
It's just not growing
as fast as it needs to.
Your fans, they love the
Blake Coffield series.
But with this one being a new series,
it's a chance for you
to expand your reach.
You know, add something more.
- Okay.
Like what?
- A love interest.
Just a little bit of romance
between Shane and Sabrina?
Yeah, Sabrina.
- Are you messing with me?
- No man.
And look, it's totally not
my call, but corporate.
- There's no way they've
even read the draft yet.
I'm surprised you got
through it this quick.
- Yeah, but they know your formula.
Sorry, not your formula, but
your style, your signature.
And they love it.
But some romance could
boost your potential.
- Well, isn't corporate
worried that romance
is going to chase away
my faithful readers?
- Not if it's done right.
Guys, they don't mind if
the hero gets the girl,
and the sales stats show
that a lot of female readers
are buying this in ebook format.
This will play to them more
while you solidify that readership.
- How am I supposed to
suddenly shift to this?
I mean, that's practically
a whole new genre for me.
- Look, don't stress.
Just weave it in with all
the action and adventure.
It'll be fine.
- Yeah.
I'm not a romance writer.
How can they expect this of me?
- Come on, you can do it.
You're a talented writer.
They obviously think so too,
or they wouldn't have
asked you to do this.
And they just want you to weave
in some relationship stuff.
You won't become the next Jane Austin.
- Yeah, but if I was so talented,
they would've just gone with what I wrote.
Thank you.
- Just maybe think of it like a challenge.
You might even like it.
- But romance is the polar
opposite of adventure.
I mean, even trying to get in
that head space right now, how?
- It should be easy.
I mean, you don't even have to make it up
like the action stuff.
You can draw inspiration
from your relationships.
- Nothing inspiring there.
- What about what's her name? Kara.
- No.
- Lillian?
- Definitely not Lillian.
- Okay, what about the
one with the purple hair?
I always forget her name.
- Cassidy? No.
Here's the thing, those
are all simple dates
and they didn't work out.
So they're hardly romantic examples
for me to follow in a book.
- I see your point.
Well, maybe you just need to
find the right woman for you.
- No, what I need is to find
the right romantic
inspiration for this book.
- Right.
That's what I meant.
- But where to find that?
- Well, maybe you need to go
somewhere for inspiration.
Let an exotic destination
spark that imagination.
I'm going to Costa Rica again for work.
You could tag along.
It'll shake things up creatively.
- Yeah?
I mean, that's not a bad idea, actually.
My book is set in a jungle
type place and Costa Rica.
Okay.
When do we leave?
(upbeat orchestral music)
Wow.
- Okay, so you should be up here.
Yeah, you're right there.
- Okay.
- And then I'm right here.
- Great.
(light orchestral music)
- Oh, hello.
Do you always come to this hotel?
- Not every time, but
it's one of my favorites.
There are a couple
others too, if it's full.
- I gotcha.
How's the food here?
- Pretty good.
- Do you wanna go grab a bite to eat?
- Sure.
- So I've been looking up some things
we can do here in Costa Rica.
- Okay, like what?
- So there's zip lining.
There's this cool volcano too.
- There's five, actually.
- What?
- Yeah, five active volcanoes, I think.
- Okay, well we gotta do all those,
and then there are these
cool hanging bridges.
There's a jungle four by four tour.
A cave excursion.
- Okay okay, wait, did you
forget why you're here?
- No.
- Romance, not adventure,
which is kind of the point
of everything just listed.
- Yeah, but these sound really fun.
- Okay, well then enjoy them.
But I don't think
they're really gonna help
with the romantic angles for your book.
And don't forget,
I do have to actually
work while we're here.
- Okay, well what do you recommend then?
- For romance?
I don't know.
Some people find chocolate romantic.
So maybe check out the,
cacao vendor I have to visit.
- Yeah, maybe.
But what do you normally
do when you come here?
- Work, eat, sleep.
Repeat.
- Come on, that can't be all.
- I did do this animal tour at night.
- That sounds like an adventure.
- It was, but I kept
nodding off the entire time.
It was focused on finding
nocturnal animals, like jaguars.
I woke up and saw these glowing
eyes just staring at me.
- Are you serious?
- Yeah, it was 20 yards away in a tree,
but it woke me up quick.
You could maybe try asking the concierge
about some romantic type activities.
- I could do that.
I might have to be a little
careful how I phrase it.
- Okay, all right.
Here's another idea.
Do some of the exciting
stuff in your book,
but just stop and kind of think through
how to weave in some
romance along the way.
- See now that, that sounds way more fun.
I don't have to do all of these
things alone though, right?
You can come with me on these?
- Oh yeah, no, I'll try,
but I do have to get up early for work.
- Okay, could I go with you tomorrow?
- Sure.
I'll leave the hotel at 8:15.
- Yeah, that sounds good, thanks.
- Of course, yeah.
- No seriously.
Thank you for letting me come along
and for even suggesting this.
And even if the romance is
a complete waste of time,
at least we got to go to
Costa Rica together, right?
- Yep.
We'll always have Costa Rica.
(bright orchestral music)
- This is different than I expected.
- How's that?
- I don't know.
- Were you expecting big
tractors and harvesters,
like for fields of wheat?
- Well, yeah.
- Hang on a sec.
- Hey, buenos dias.
- Buenos dias.
- Hey, you're early.
Can you gimme a few minutes though?
- Sure, yeah.
I'll show my friend
around, if that's okay?
- Si, si.
- Okay, hold on.
So all of these beans are cacao beans?
- No, that's actually
more like the whole fruit.
Beans are really the seeds inside.
Come here, I'll show you.
Here, hold that for a second.
So, you basically just score it,
cut it a little bit, and
then you can just break it.
- What?
Okay, that is definitely not chocolate.
- Well, not yet.
- Can I eat this?
- Yeah.
Go ahead, try it.
What do you think?
- Definitely not chocolate.
Have you tried this?
- Yeah, I've had it once.
- Once? Okay, hold on, hold on.
Come here. Come here.
- Nope, no.
- Come on.
- I'm good, I'm good.
- All right, so what do
you do with all these?
- Well, after the seeds are harvested,
they're fermented and dried
and then eventually
they're roasted in grounds.
- Okay, and that's when you can start
making it into chocolate?
- Something like that.
Well, I better go check
and see if Tomas is ready.
Wish me luck.
- Good luck, but you'll be great.
You're already in business mode.
You're in your element.
So, you know, go get him.
- Gee, thanks.
- Miss Mackenzie, are you ready?
- Yeah, coming.
There's a tour group
starting if you wanna join.
- Yeah, maybe I will.
- Just stay outta trouble.
- Trouble, me? Come on.
- Of course, I am excited to
provide more cacao for you,
but more product means more work.
I cannot help with the price.
- But we can commit to two
years at this quantity.
- I cannot get any lower.
In fact, the price and the cost may go up.
- Higher?
- I'm not sure yet,
but the pricing will
be definitely an issue.
- All right.
Let we talk to my team, but
please just think it over.
Maybe you can come up with a solution
so we're both satisfied.
- Okay.
- Perfect. (speaking in foreign language)
- And I get a chocolate
bar when I'm done, right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah?
Okay.
- Slacker.
- Okay. I will admit this is pretty fun,
but you kind of ruined the
magic for me just a little.
- You'll just appreciate it more now.
(car trying to start)
Everything okay?
- Yeah.
Maybe.
Okay, not really.
- Battery trouble?
- I don't know.
Rental cars, you know.
- Pop the hood.
- What do you think?
- Try the key again.
- Yeah, battery.
Well, the rental car companies are all
kind of a ways back in town.
It's probably gonna take a
while for them to get here.
- Just my luck.
- Well, let me see if Tomas
has something to jump the battery.
Just a sec.
- She seems to know what she's doing.
- Her dad's a mechanic.
- Oh, well it's nice of you both to help.
- I'm just standing here, that's all her.
- Well, either way, thanks.
Sorry to delay your vacation.
- No, it's not a vacation.
It's more of a work thing.
- Oh, I just assumed honeymoon.
- No, man.
We're not together, we're
just friends is all.
- Huh? Cool.
- Anything you could do.
- Okay.
- Well, I'd go straight
to the rental car company,
and see if you can swap
out the battery or the car.
- I will. Thank you.
- It's no trouble, Tomas had the cables.
- Still, you've been very kind.
Both of you.
- Let me take those back to Tomas.
- Oh, thank you.
- Yeah.
- Thanks.
- I'm Lucas.
- Mackenzie.
- Nice to meet you.
- Same.
Oh, sorry.
Ugh.
- Oh, you're fine, here one sec.
Here you go.
So can I take you to lunch as a thank you?
- Oh no, you don't have to do that.
Just drive safely.
The roads can be a little rough.
- Okay then.
Well, thanks again.
- Sure.
(light instrumental music)
Good?
- Uh huh.
It's a little bitter.
- You and you're sweet tooth.
- Oh, says the girl who
works at a candy company.
- Chocolate.
- I did find some inspiration
for my book, though.
- Yeah?
What, are you gonna
change one of the stops
in their adventure to be at a cacao farm?
- No, no.
I'm talking about the romantic angle.
Yeah, Lucas, definitely into you.
- No he wasn't.
- Yeah, he was.
- You're blind to romance.
- I can totally tell when
a guy's making a move.
- What, because you're a guy too,
and therefore it's like the same lingo?
- Yeah, pretty much.
And the fact that he seemed really happy
when I said we weren't dating.
- He asked?
- Kind of.
- That's forward of him.
- Okay, so you're gonna tell me
that you're not interested in him at all?
- A relationship should be
built on something other
than a moment of attraction.
- So you found him attractive?
- That's not what I said.
- Uh huh.
- Okay, new subject, please.
- Okay, fine, fine fine.
How'd your work meeting go.
- Hmm, not great.
They can provide me with an
increase in product we need,
but he's not budging on price.
I'm just gonna have to come up
with some better incentives for him.
- Could find another supplier.
- Yeah. Yeah.
I'll meet with a few other
options while we're here.
You hungry?
- I'm actually not.
Chocolate kind of filled me up
in a totally unbalanced way.
- Well, I'm starving,
so let's get something
to eat really quick.
And then I have to make a few
calls, but other than that,
you wanna pick something to do today?
- Yeah.
Yeah, definitely.
Oh, I actually have just the thing.
Remember when Shane and Sabrina go diving
to that underwater cave in the lake?
- [Mackenzie] Yeah.
- Well, I thought of a cool way
for them to travel to that spot.
Okay.
So maybe cool was a little
bit of an overstatement.
- It's interesting.
- It definitely wouldn't
work for my book though.
- Yeah, not for an action scene.
- Can you imagine?
- Yeah, with the bad guys chasing them?
These are hardly getaway vehicles.
- Okay, well maybe it's
better for a romantic scene.
- I don't know.
I don't know if there's really
anything romantic about this,
and you can barely hold hands.
- We can try it.
Okay.
Well, we're getting our cardio in.
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
All right, seriously though.
Help me brainstorm.
If not the water bikes then what?
- I still like the diving scene.
How to add romance to it though?
- You just can't exactly kiss underwater
with diving or snorkel gear.
- Well, but I mean romance
isn't just about the kiss.
It's about the spark between
them and the trust they build.
- Spark, trust.
- Oh, what if Shane's gear is sabotaged,
so Sabrina shares hers with him,
and that way he doesn't drown.
- And that's romantic?
- Once they reach the shore, yeah.
It can be.
What if it went like this?
(dramatic orchestral music)
Are you okay?
Your gear.
- Sabotaged.
I should never have
trusted the shopkeeper.
- I told you there was
something off about him.
- You should have left me.
- No, I couldn't.
I need you.
- No, you're strong enough alone.
- But I don't want to.
I don't wanna do anything without you.
- No, too much.
- Okay, okay. Fine, fine.
You write what you want.
But my point is romance can
come from less obvious moments,
even life and death adventure.
- All right.
- Can we go back now?
My legs are really burning.
- Yeah, fine.
(light orchestral music)
- Hey.
- Oh, good morning.
- How's the water.
- It's good.
You should try it.
But I'm gonna go out on a
limb and say you have work.
- Yeah, I gotta check out
a couple more cacao farms.
- How long will that take?
- A few hours, you
wanna meet up for lunch?
- Yeah, that sounds good.
- All right, I'll send you the address.
Meet there around one o'clock?
- Perfect.
Good luck.
- Good?
- Amazing.
- High quality, the best of Costa Rica.
- Of course.
Mister Romano,
you have one of the largest
farms in the country.
Are you able to help us with our needs?
- Yes, but not yet.
- Well, when then?
- We are harvesting all weekend.
Maybe in time.
- How much time?
- Couple of years?
Or if one of our clients
change their needs,
I'll call you right away.
- But a plantation of this size,
surely you have enough supply?
- I am doing the best I can.
- Well, thank you for taking
the time to meet with me.
- I'm sorry I cannot help you.
- Okay, well thank you anyway.
- You're welcome.
(somber orchestral music)
- Ah, gracias.
Oh, Mackenzie.
- Lucas, hi.
I didn't expect to see you.
- Yeah, me either, but hey,
I'm really glad you're here.
Let me buy you that lunch I owe you.
- Oh, no.
- Excuse me?
Can I get one more please?
Thank you.
No, I really am happy you're here.
I wanted to see you again.
- You did?
(worker speaking in foreign language)
- Gracias.
There you go.
Do you wanna sit with me?
- Yeah.
(muffled speaking)
- You know, sales and service
really isn't that exciting.
And I used to dread going
to those conventions,
like Las Vegas and
Florida, New York and LA,
but this year with Costa Rica, jackpot.
- Sounds exciting.
- Oh, you know how often do you come here?
- A few times a year.
- [Ethan] Hey, Hey.
- Ethan.
- There you are.
Luke, good to see you again.
- It's Lucas.
- What'd I say?
- Luke.
- Lucas, I'm sorry.
How's the car?
- All fixed.
- So just a minor headache then?
- Yeah.
Or a fortunate mistake that led me
to meet a beautiful stranger.
- Oh you?
- Oh, Mackenzie tells me you're an author.
- Just a couple little
novels here and there.
- He's being modest, for once.
- Well, I'll have to
buy one of your books.
- Please do.
So, where are you from?
- California, bay area,
it's kind of ideal for work.
- So are we, Orange County.
- Yeah, Mackenzie was just
telling me that, it's so close.
- It's a seven hour drive.
- Hardly an inconvenience.
- Well, I have a lot
of work to do actually.
So I should probably
get back to the hotel.
- Oh, all work, huh?
I hope you find time to enjoy it here.
- I do.
- Well, hey, maybe we can
run into each other again.
Say, for dinner?
- Sure, I guess.
Yeah.
- Actually we were thinking
of going zip lining.
I hear it's fantastic.
A real thrill.
- Oh, I've I've never been before.
- You should come along.
I was thinking of tomorrow.
- Sure.
- Till tomorrow then.
- Okay.
- Later.
- Is it just me or did you just
set us up on a date back there?
- What? No, he asked you out already.
- Yeah, I guess, but.
- You just seemed a little
unsure of the whole dinner thing.
So I thought that something
with all three of us together
might make you more comfortable.
Was that that wrong?
- No thanks.
- Okay.
I just figured you're not seeing anyone,
so maybe you were interested,
but if you don't like him,
seriously, just tell him.
- Well, that's little
easier said than done,
but he does seem nice.
I just didn't come on this trip
to date someone I barely know.
- Well, the first rule of writing
is let the unexpected happen.
- Yeah, but my life?
- Yeah.
- Isn't your book.
(both chuckling)
- Okay, all right.
However,
if you do see me taking notes
over your budding romance,
it's just creative research.
- Great.
- I'll try not to be a third wheel.
- You know, romance wouldn't
be so difficult to write
if you weren't so.
- So what?
- Emotionally stunted.
- Ooh.
Yeah, that's fair.
- On the one hand
Ethan's being thoughtful,
but on the other.
- He's making things harder.
- Too bad you won't say,
I can't let myself show
interest in this other guy,
because I'm in love with you.
- Yeah, definitely not something I'd say.
- However, maybe give
this Lucas guy a chance.
Is he cute?
- He's handsome, yeah.
- Huh, perfect.
- But it would involve
me moving on from Ethan.
- And you know, I fully support
that, or make him jealous.
- Of Lucas?
- Yeah.
- He can't be jealous when
he feels nothing for me.
- [Crystal] Good point.
- And I wouldn't wanna use
Lucas or anyone like that.
- Stop being a saint.
- I'll deal with it all later.
Anyway, I really need some
leeway with the vendor here.
Is there any way you could
work some magic with Evelyn,
so I have more to offer.
- I can put a message in
front of her, how's that?
- Crystal?
- [Crystal] I hate to say
not my department, but.
- Fine.
- He's not budging?
- No, not yet.
And I've checked with
some of his competition.
They don't seem to be any help either.
- There are other countries
we can import from.
- Yeah, yeah.
But that's the last resort.
I mean for the timeline that Evelyn wants,
starting over with a new
vendor in a new country
is like a whole bunch of work, delays,
and governmental red tape.
Yeah, I'll just send her an email
and hope she's in a good
mood when she reads it.
(dramatic orchestral music)
- You first?
- Lucas, why don't you go first?
- No, no.
- Come on man.
- No, no, no, you go ahead.
- All right, I'll go first.
Okay, here we go.
How great is this?
Kenzie, how do I look?
- You look like the guy from your book,
the one with the rock climbing.
- Caleb Highmoor?
Ooh, awesome.
All right, here we go. (hooting)
(uptempo orchestral music)
- He's quite confident.
- Oh, he loves this type of stuff.
- [Ethan] You guys are gonna love it.
- Okay, who's next?
- You go, I'll be go last.
- You sure?
- Yeah, mm-hm.
- Lucas, you kind of look a little pale.
- No, do I?
Huh?
- You want some water, maybe?
- No, no.
I think it might come back up.
We are really high up here, aren't we?
- Do heights bother you?
- Not that much.
- You don't have to do this.
- I'm right behind you.
- Okay, for sure.
- [Ethan] Hey, what's the hold up?
- Lucas, you know what?
Why don't you go next?
Okay.
Look, how about we both
just climb back down then?
- Just
one minute.
- Hey, it'll be okay.
Look, see Ethan's already over there.
- Come on.
- Don't worry about
rushing, we'll go slow.
I think you should do one of two things.
There's no pressure,
it's totally up to you.
One, is we climb back down,
go have a soda and laugh this off,
or two, I can hang on here
while our very experienced guide
makes sure you're all set up on that line.
Ethan will wave and holler something
idiotic and encouraging,
and I'll cheer you on while you go across.
And then 15 seconds later,
you land, you can cheer
me on while I go across.
What do you think?
- Second one.
- Okay.
- Ready?
- Maybe, I look ridiculous.
- You got this.
- One,
two,
three.
- [Mackenzie] Go Lucas!
(Lucas screaming)
- You did it.
It's your first time, yeah?
All right.
- Ready?
- For Kenzie.
- Okay, then.
(Mackenzie hooting)
(uptempo orchestral music)
- Yeah.
Great job.
- You did it.
- Oh, thank you.
Thank you.
- [Mackenzie] It's all you.
- Actually one sounded really good.
- All right.
You ready for the next one?
- What? What?
- I'm proud of you.
- Really?
I made a complete fool of myself.
- You were nervous.
There's nothing wrong with that.
- Look I'm sorry you had to have your fun
weighed down by some scaredy-
- Nah, listen, I had a great time.
We both did, right Ethan?
- Huh?
Yeah.
- See?
- You know, I am glad I tried that,
but maybe next time we can
do something on solid ground.
Assuming there is the next time.
- Fair enough.
- All right, well I will see you later.
Mackenzie. Nathan.
- Bye.
- Later.
That was cruel.
- I didn't know he was afraid of heights,
he didn't say anything.
Besides, he can't complain.
He got a nice big ole hug
up there on the platform.
- Oh, no, no, no.
That was me comforting a terrified soul.
- Maybe, maybe a little bit more.
- You think what you want.
- I always do.
- Now, for my book,
I think I'm gonna make
Sabrina scared of heights.
- Why?
- So that Shane can rescue her.
- That's so silly.
I mean why does she have to be rescued
when he's the one that has the problem?
- Because my character
isn't afraid of heights.
Besides, I wrote it so
that she rescues him
during the whole diving bit.
So, it's her turn.
- All right, fine.
(phone ringing)
Hi, Evelyn.
- I got your email.
- Yeah, not the best news yet.
Seems like everyone here
is kind of maxed out
with their current commitments,
and I've been looking at numbers
for other countries, but-
- No, that's gonna kill our timeline.
- Exactly.
- This deal is important,
and if we can't deliver,
we lose Golden.
Golden Gifts is keeping us,
ensuring we stay in business.
And I would hate for us to lose this deal
over a little supply and demand blip.
- I'm still working on it.
I'll find a solution.
- Good, because jobs are
on the line with this deal.
- Are you saying my job is at stake?
- Don't be silly.
25% of the company's
jobs would be at stake,
so keep me up to date.
- Oh, okay okay, bye.
- Hey, how was your run?
- I'm still worked up about Evelyn's call.
- Think that's how they work?
- I mean, I didn't think so,
but I'm in the spending money division,
not balancing the company checkbook.
- Well, maybe she's just bluffing.
- I doubt it.
- Do you want a distraction?
- Like what?
- Like sharing your female
perspective on something.
- Your book?
- Yeah.
- Shoot.
- What do you like in a guy?
Like take Lucas for example.
- Well, you realize I
barely know him, right?
- Yeah.
I mean you're not in love
with him and that's fine.
But just imagine,
based on the time you
spent with him so far,
what stands out?
The good stuff please.
- His vulnerability?
- Women really are different than men.
- You want my answer or not?
- Yeah yeah, no no, I'm sorry.
Yes, please you can continue.
- He was trying to hide
his fear, you know,
because he was embarrassed,
but when it came to it,
he didn't shy away from letting me help.
- Huh.
Okay.
- I mean, instead of being
all like, oh, it was nothing.
I'm all tough, so strong.
He was honest.
He wasn't afraid to admit he was scared
and not too proud to accept some comfort.
- All right.
Next question.
- Yes?
- What would make you
fall in love with the guy?
- Oh, come on.
How can I answer that?
- Come on, you've been
in love before, right?
I just need this whole process
from a perspective that isn't mine.
- I don't know.
What would make me fall in love?
Making me laugh.
Thinking that he values
me, like what I think,
knowing that he cares for me,
like he wants what's best for me.
And seeing that he wants to protect me.
- Protect, like a fight
to defend your honor?
- No, no,
I'm pretty sure that doesn't
actually happen in real life.
I mean, at least not as much
as books and movies make it seem.
- Okay, well then what did you mean?
- Just wanting me to be safe.
- Okay, yeah.
All right, this has
actually been super helpful.
Thank you Kenzie, I appreciate it.
- You off to your writing cave?
- Yeah, I think so,
at least for a little bit.
Probably just order in
tonight, to be honest.
You gonna be okay on your own?
- I'm pretty sure I can handle it.
- Okay, well thank you.
Again, I appreciate it,
I'll see you around.
(light instrumental music)
Good morning.
- I thought you'd sleep in.
- Maybe to work without my wit? Come on.
- Have something healthy.
- So, what is on the agenda for today?
- Checking out another cacao farm.
- How long will that take?
- Hopefully not too long,
but Tomas is supposed to
send over a proposal later,
so I'll need to review that too.
- All right, I'll probably
just chill here today.
(phone ringing)
- Lucas.
Hello?
- [Lucas] Hey, good morning, Mackenzie.
I hope I'm not calling too early.
- Hey, no, I'm already up and working.
- [Lucas] Oh yeah, me too.
Have a pretty full schedule
this morning at the convention.
I have to be on the floor mingle,
but I can break away this afternoon,
assuming you're not sick of a scaredy cat.
I thought I should see if
I can get a better view
of the volcanoes while I'm here.
Would you like to come?
- Well, I actually have
a lot of work to do,
and I also have to check in
with the office back home.
- [Lucas] Oh.
- But I think Ethan and
I can make that work.
- [Lucas] Ethan?
- Yeah, is that okay?
He'll just be bored otherwise, so.
- [Lucas] Oh yeah, okay.
How about two o'clock?
- Let's do three?
- [Lucas] Yeah, great.
I'll see you then.
- Okay, thanks.
Bye.
- Can you see this? Some
guy off to the side.
I am pretty sure that that
is what you just made me
on this excursion with Lucas.
- Okay, but I didn't wanna
make him feel bad by saying no,
especially after how
embarrassed hair he was.
- It's fine, I will come with.
- Thanks.
- You're welcome.
But if any of this makes it into my book.
- I've been warned.
(soft music)
- Hey, how much farther is it?
- About 15 minutes till
we get to the bridge.
- Okay, cool.
- You should see him on road trips.
- Are we there yet?
- The worst.
- Hey, thanks again for coming with me.
- Oh yeah, it's good for
me to see something new.
I've never been here before,
even with all my trips to Costa Rica.
- Wow.
- Well, I'm glad we're doing this then.
Hey, I know Ethan said that
you two are just friends,
but I wanted to check.
So are you?
- Yeah. Yeah.
We are just friends.
It's all we've ever been, yeah.
- Cool.
Sorry, that's just me being in my head.
- That's okay, I know what that's like.
- [Lucas] Oh yeah.
Neat, huh?
- [Mackenzie] Yeah.
- Wait, so this height doesn't bother you?
- No, the bridge is strong
and I get to stay on my feet.
Even if we are a couple
hundred feet in the air.
- It's a pretty amazing view, too.
- Sure is.
- Hey, let me get one of you.
- Yeah.
Big cheesy smile?
- [Mackenzie] Normal one please.
- You're no fun.
- Great.
Hey, let's get one together, too.
- Okay.
- Ethan, you mind?
- Yeah, no problem.
- Wait one sec.
All right, yeah.
- You all good?
- Yeah.
Oh, one sec.
Yeah, great.
- Okay.
- Got it?
- Yeah.
- Awesome.
This is so much better
than working all day.
- Absolutely.
Do you like your work?
- Yeah, sure.
It's getting kind of bland,
but thank goodness for these trips
or I would've changed careers by now.
- Are you the buyer or the
seller at the conventions?
- Mostly the buyer, look for
products that can help us.
Some might be worth partnering
with, some worth acquiring.
- Can I sneak past you real quick?
- It's pretty boring, right?
- I'm here to talk to a supplier.
That's not very exciting either.
- Yeah, well we make it
exciting then, don't we?
- We try.
Zip lines, volcanoes.
- Dinner?
How about it? Just the two of us.
- I can't tonight.
- Well, tomorrow then.
- Sure, yeah, that works.
- Lucas, when do we get to see the lava?
- Lava?
- Yeah man, orange liquid fire, lava?
- Oh Ethan, I don't think
there's any lava flow to be seen here.
- You said these were active volcanoes.
- Well, active and erupting
are two different things.
- What?
(soft music)
Romance.
Okay.
This is it, the volcano.
- Well, how can you be sure?
There are more than one here.
- The river, but we don't have much time.
- No one knows we're here, do they?
- No, it's not that.
(rumbling)
It's the volcano.
- Shane, we can't outrun lava.
- No, that doesn't work.
No, not that either.
We'll be fine,
as long as we're together.
- Shane?
- Kenzie?
- Whoa.
(pensive instrumental music)
Whoa.
(knocking on door)
- Hi.
- Hey.
Look, I'm pretty tired
between the hike and work.
- Do you have a spoon?
Hey Kenzie?
- Mm-hm.
- I'm still really annoyed
about the lava thing.
I'm serious.
- You had unrealistic expectations.
- I did not, I had high expectations.
There's such a difference.
Could I ask you something?
- Uh oh.
- Do you wanna stop seeing Lucas?
- Why do you ask?
- Just because, I mean,
you invited me along today.
So if you don't feel comfortable,
then that says something.
I mean, I can tell him if you want.
- No, it's okay.
- No, as in you'll tell him?
- He asked me to dinner again.
Just the two of us.
I said, yes.
- Okay.
Whatever you want.
- Well, I don't, I
mean, he's nice and all,
but I don't know.
- Yeah.
Maybe something will come of it.
- Maybe.
- I mean, you want that right, with him?
- We'll see.
- Our quality of cacao is better
than what you'll find somewhere else.
I mean, you do gourmet chocolate.
You can't do that with just any cacao.
- No, I know.
But the proposal you sent,
it's more than what I can
bring back to my boss.
I looked up the numbers and
they don't even make sense.
I mean, you're actually
charging more per kilo.
- Yeah, like I said, to produce
more it just costs more.
- Can you actually do it?
Right now, if we agreed to this,
could you make more?
- Not for several months.
- Tomas, do you have the plans to produce
the quantity I'm talking about?
- Like I said, several months.
- Okay. Okay.
I think I understand now.
- Miss Mackenzie, I do want
to keep working with you,
I just don't know how to give
you what you're asking for.
- Yeah.
Look, how else can I
get the quantity I need?
Could you maybe recommend someone?
- You mean like a competitor?
- I don't have much choice.
Mister Amano's farm seemed
to have pretty good quality.
- No, that's the worst-run
farm in the country.
Just stick with me.
- I'm trying, but it's just not enough.
- Well then it's not enough.
It's better than nothing.
(phone ringing)
- Hello?
- I figured it out.
- [Crystal] What, Ethan?
- No, with Tomas.
He doesn't know how we'll
get the yield we need
out of his land.
- How can he not?
- Well, I've been talking
a pretty serious increase,
and he is not the only one.
All of his competitors
are saying the same thing.
They're already at their max.
- You sound like Marvin.
- Well, at least now I know
what the real issue is.
Just need to figure out a solution.
- Any ideas so far?
- Nope.
- Back to Ethan, then.
- No change.
- Lucas, then.
- Lucas is fine.
- Fine or fine.
- He's pleasant, how's that?
- He could be more if you
weren't hung up on Ethan.
- Lucas is handsome and
charming, but he knows it, and-
- [Crystal] And?
- I'm pretty sure he spends more time
thinking about how he looks
than anyone else I know.
- It pays off, right?
- It doesn't matter anyway.
It's all just confusing me, everything.
I'm even regretting bringing Ethan along.
- You shouldn't.
This could be the trip
where you can finally
wash your hands of your pining.
Lucas sounds like the perfect guy
to help you get over Ethan.
Then again, the marketing response
on those strawberry
chocolates is really good.
It's seasonal, but it's worth a shot.
- You're not fooling anyone.
- It's work related.
Kind of.
- Tell Mackenzie to get
a move on, for your sake.
- Will do.
- [Mackenzie] What was that?
- Evelyn.
She said you should get
a move on for my sake.
What is that supposed to mean?
- Don't worry about it, she's just grumpy.
Productive day?
- No, actually.
I need a break.
Let's go do something together.
- I don't know.
My brain's kind of fried,
and I have to be back in time for dinner.
- Well, let's do something close by then.
There's that cave thing, I
don't think that's too far away.
- How about I pick something?
- Okay.
- Really?
- Yeah. whatever you want.
I cannot believe that this
is what you wanted to do.
- What's so bad about a sloth trail?
Somewhere up in the trees, maybe.
There, look aren't they cute?
- Oh yeah.
Yeah, do they have trails
with more energetic animals?
- No, I purposely picked
the most boring animal
just to annoy you.
- Okay, great, great.
- Yeah, we're gonna see
sleeping turtles next.
- All right, so what's the
deal with these guys then?
They just sleep long,
walk slow, happy lives.
- I don't know that much about them,
other than there's a lot
of 'em in Costa Rica.
- Why's that?
- Probably the jungle,
'cause they live in tropical rainforest.
Oh,
guess how far they travel for a day?
- Oh, 10 feet.
- About 40 yards.
- Wow, so much farther.
- Give them some credit though.
They just sleep 15 to 20 hours a day.
- Like me in college.
- The first time I was in Costa Rica,
actually I was driving,
I came across this backup in
traffic, no one was moving.
It was a really like rural area,
so I didn't know what was going on.
Got out of my car to take a look.
It was a sloth, just crossing the road.
- At 0.03 miles per hour?
- Honestly, he looked frozen in time.
Just stretched out like mid motion.
And then a police officer
came, just picked him up,
set him down on the other side.
- So awesome.
Could you do that pose one more time?
What?
- Oh, look.
How's that for romance?
- They're taking a nap.
That could be,
that could be anything, that
could be mother and son.
- That'd be a cute sloth couple, too.
- Sloths aren't monogamous,
and aren't much for true love.
- Really?
- Yeah, so says the
wisdom of the internet.
See, that's just it for me.
I keep getting hung up on
writing the romance and it just,
I don't know, it feels fake.
- It's fiction, it's all fake.
- Well don't misunderstand
me, I'm all for romance.
- You are?
- Yeah.
Writing it.
I'm coming around.
It just,
it's a little tricky and I'm
still trying to figure it out.
- You just have to make
it relatable, to you.
- How?
I mean I've never done the grand gestures
or the big romantic speeches.
- Romance isn't about
the big flashy things.
It's the every day that's important.
- Okay, but the every
day is boring in a book.
- You have a helicopter chase, diving,
repelling off the waterfall.
A little boring won't hurt.
Besides, romance isn't boring.
- Okay, but you just said nothing flashy.
So what's going to feel romantic?
- Little things, you know
that they do for each other,
that show they care.
- Somehow I get the
feeling you're gonna say
that saving each other's
lives doesn't count.
- Think smaller.
- Being able to count on each other?
- Yes, yes.
Or the sacrifices they make, you know,
because they love each other.
- Love?
- Why not?
Real love, true love, comes first.
In love catches up on its own timeline.
- Yeah, no,
that makes sense.
Yeah.
(soft instrumental music)
- Take out, really?
- Whoa, you look great.
- Thanks.
- Where'd you get that dress?
- Gift shop.
- Well, you're, it's very pretty.
- Thank you.
Actually, I have a ton of work
to do, but I'm kind of stuck,
so I figured dinner and a
break might do me some good.
- Okay, well, if you decide
you don't wanna go out.
I mean, I've got plenty to.
- I guess he's here.
- Where are you guys going?
- I don't know.
- Well, are you sure that's safe?
I mean you barely know the guy.
He could be like a criminal or something.
- Now you bring that up?
- I'm just saying.
Okay, have fun.
(pensive music)
- [Mackenzie] Hey.
- Oh, hey, wow.
You look beautiful.
Perfect.
- Thanks, you too.
- Oh, thank you.
You ready?
There's this restaurant
I keep hearing about
from people at the convention.
- Oh, sounds great.
- Okay.
Watch your step.
- Thanks.
So when's the convention over?
- Yesterday, actually.
- Really?
- Yeah, I wanted to
stick around for a bit.
- Well, when do you leave?
- I haven't decided yet.
How about you?
- Friday, for now.
But the whole thing's really fluid
with this deal I'm trying to make.
- How so?
- Well it's, it's delicate, but basically,
I'm trying to figure out
if it's more cost efficient
to start over buying from another country,
or help the farm here figure
out how to produce more.
- Well, here is at least
the problem you know.
- Sure.
- I got pressure from my bosses
to find a better software for
predicting buying behaviors.
It's complicated, I'll spare you,
but we had one in-house.
It had all these issues
and no one believed in it.
So I spent two years on and
off vetting outside options.
We narrowed in on, one acquired it,
spent all this time forcing it to work,
but in the end.
- No better than what
you had the whole time?
- Oh, worse.
Sometimes the best solution
is the one you already have.
- Yeah, except in my case, it's
not really the solution yet.
- Well, try working
with them so it can be.
And that's when I learned my lesson,
me and cats, not friends.
- You have the claw marks to remind you.
- Yep.
Hey, how about we dance?
- No, no, I'm not a good dancer.
- Oh, come on.
I'll lead.
So, what else do I need to know about you?
- Well, we covered families, education,
jobs, pets.
- Okay then.
Oh, most embarrassing moments.
- Oh, no, no.
- Come on.
Okay, I'll go first.
- Yeah, feel free.
- I was supposed to
receive this award at work,
so I invited my family to the ceremony,
and the head of the company calls my name.
I go up on stage.
They hand me the award and I
smile this big old open grin,
and my face is projected
on these giant TV screens
for everyone to see.
And I literally singled out
and hear my parents gasp.
- Why?
- Broccoli, stuck in my teeth.
I made the mistake of
eating an hors d'oeuvre
before I went onstage.
- I'm sure not that many
people even noticed.
- Oh enough did, I didn't
hear the end of it.
- That's your most embarrassing moment?
- Yeah.
Come on, it's horrifying.
You wouldn't understand,
but we have this thing in my family where
we're so proud of who
we are and how we look.
It was awful.
Anyways, your turn.
- Okay.
Well, before my job now,
I was interviewing around.
There's this job I really wanted
at this really reputable marketing firm.
So I go in for an interview
with three of their team,
and I totally think I'm doing really well.
And then as I leave, I hear laughter.
- Oh why, what happened?
- I'd gone to the restroom before,
and I guess I missed that the
end of my skirt got caught.
- Oh no.
- Yeah, so when I went to
leave, that's what they saw.
- Wow.
Okay, yeah.
You know what, that's embarrassing.
- Yeah.
Yeah, it was.
Ethan came over later that day
and brought over food and some comedies,
and we just watched and laughed
until the sting of it all passed.
- You've been friends for long?
- Yeah.
- How'd you two meet?
- Well, we started out as neighbors
in this really crummy apartment.
I just finished college and he was a cook
at this really
hole-in-the-wall restaurant,
not really believing
he could be an author.
- Well, he obviously overcame that.
- Yeah.
Yeah, and we stayed friends
even with all the little
fan groups of his,
and moving to different
places across town.
- That's nice.
It's so easy to fall out of touch.
- Yeah.
I always kind of figured it
was just a matter of time
before we both got too busy
and just kind of forgot about each other,
but he proved me wrong.
Tomas then Ramano.
How can I make that work?
- You mentioned Ramano's
farm, but it's run poorly.
- Yeah, guy's not focused,
getting old, to ill.
- Well, I spoke with him this morning.
He said he needs the money from the farm.
Can't really do the work anymore.
- So?
- Well how's the cacao there?
- It's good, not as good as mine.
- Could it be?
- I don't understand.
- Ramano wants out of the
business, don't you think?
- Yeah.
- What if he was bought out.
- By who?
- You.
- I don't have that kind of money.
- Well, what if we helped?
- How exactly?
- We make the sale possible
in exchange for better terms.
Consider it an advance.
You could run the farm
the way it should be.
And with that you have much
more cacao to sell to us.
- And you could do that?
- I think so.
Could you?
So, I already sent the terms to my boss,
and there was no screaming.
- That's great, progress.
- Yeah, so Tomas is approaching Ramano,
and then assuming Ramano
doesn't get greedy,
we could have everything in
place in the next few weeks.
- That's great, I'm so proud of you.
- Thank you.
Honestly, I'm just relieved
not to have Crystal
and everyone's jobs on the line.
- Well, you shouldn't
have in the first place.
That was all Evelyn.
- Well, it's nearly all
finished now, anyway.
All in all, not a bad trip.
- We should celebrate.
- That's an idea.
- Hey Mackenzie.
- Oh Lucas.
- Hey, what do you two doing here?
- We were just getting lunch
and talking about celebrating.
- Mackenzie figured out a solution.
- Yeah, actually what
you were saying before,
about the solution you already have
and investing more into that.
It got me thinking and yeah,
it's nearly all settled.
- Oh my gosh, I'm so happy for you.
That's amazing.
So how are we celebrating?
- We haven't figured out yet.
- Oh.
Well, you know what?
I have a great idea,
but we would have to
get our swimsuits first.
(bright orchestral music)
Come on, you guys are gonna love this.
- You all right?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
- Did you not wanna come,
'cause I just figured you would.
- Yeah, we're celebrating.
All three of us.
- You'll be fine.
You sure you're okay.
- Peachy.
- So, what do you think?
- How's the water so?
- Beautiful?
Legend has it that after
God painted the sky,
this is where he cleaned his paintbrush.
- Come on.
- Well, I mean, in all reality,
it's probably minerals or whatever,
but isn't it awesome?
- It's amazing.
- If you like this, you're
gonna love the next spot.
Come on.
(light orchestral music)
- [Mackenzie] Wow.
- [Ethan] Okay, I admit,
that is impressive.
- Okay, come on, let's
head all the way down.
(camera snapping)
You should write this
into one of your books.
- Yeah, maybe I will.
- How is your book coming by the way?
Mackenzie said it's a work in progress.
- I'm revising a few things,
but it's nearly done.
- Nice.
You okay?
- I think I saw a monkey.
- Hey, can I ask you a question?
- Yeah, sure.
- Do you think I have
a shot with Mackenzie
after Costa Rica?
I'm supposed to go home this weekend.
I've already extended my trip as it is.
The boss wants me in office on Monday but,
I don't wanna let her go.
- Oh.
- I know the long distance thing.
It's not ideal but,
nothing a quick flight can't solve, right?
- Well, I mean, are you sure
she's interested enough?
- Well, that's why I'm asking you.
Did she say anything about me?
- No.
- Oh, she's gotta feel something right?
- I don't.
So are we gonna go swimming in that?
'Cause I have to admit
that water looks amazing.
- Oh no, no, no.
We're not allowed to swim here.
- Then why did we bring our swimsuits?
- Oh, that's for the next spot.
What do you think?
- It's already totally worth it.
Ethan, how great, right?
You wanted to come to the hot springs?
- Yeah.
Yeah, this is really great.
- Well hey, let's try it out.
(playful music)
- Just right.
Ethan, come on.
- Yeah, careful, don't slip.
- I swear, I can't even
so much as look it a worm
without my heart like
going into overdrive.
- Oh, I'm pretty sure I'd
be scarred for life too.
- Yeah.
- [Mackenzie] Crazy to think
this is all heated by nature.
- Yeah, all the magma, but no lava.
Sorry Ethan.
- Hey, is that a worm
by your shoulder, there?
- Just a stick.
- Oh, sorry.
I thought it moved.
- Ethan loves to tease.
- I'm the same way with my sister.
- I didn't know you have one.
- I thought I brought it up
on our date the other night.
- I guess too busy dancing.
- Well, I think there's
another hot spring.
I'm just gonna go take a quick look.
Can I go?
- Yeah, sure.
- Why not?
- No, you stay here until
I find a better one,
because it's not like
I need your help, so.
- Maybe they have a couple's
massage service here.
- Really?
- A lot of hot springs
have the method spas.
- Okay.
- I'll see if I can book
this one, Mackenzie.
- Lucas?
- My ankle.
- Ethan.
- Are you okay?
- I just hit it when I fell.
- Let me help you, come here.
- I'll help.
- You've already helped enough.
What was that?
Lucas has been nothing but
nice, and you were mean.
- I was not.
He just gets on my nerves
after a while, okay?
I'm sorry I don't have your patience.
- So you thought it was fine
to just push him in the wall.
- I didn't push him in.
I barely touched him.
- First the zip line, now this.
- Hey, he invited himself along.
- He was just being nice.
- Are you sure that's all?
I'll tell you right now, Kenzie,
if you wanted to come on this trip alone
so you could fall in love
with some random guy,
you didn't have to bring me along.
- That's not fair.
I was trying to help you with your book.
- Well don't.
Okay, I'll throw in some
stupid little sappy love struck line,
and Larry and the publisher will be happy,
and that'll be that.
Romance is overrated anyway.
- Well, you obviously don't need it
in your book or your life, so fine.
Whatever you say, Ethan.
- Kenzie, you there?
- Yeah?
- I'm sorry.
(soft music)
I was being stupid,
and it wasn't fair to you or to Lucas.
- Why were you acting like that?
- I don't know.
I think I was frustrated with the book,
and I should have been more patient.
- Well, it's a good thing
we're going home soon.
Maybe this trip wasn't such a good idea.
- No, it was.
It was, you've always been encouraging me
and this trip was you
being really thoughtful,
and I made a mess of it.
- Well, thanks for saying that.
You really should
apologize to Lucas, though.
- Yeah.
- Just saying.
- I know.
We'll see.
- Hey Ethan.
- Hey, thank you.
Do you need help?
- I'm good, thanks.
Well, your ankle, it's not?
- No, it's fine.
Just a bit sore today.
- Okay.
Thank you for meeting me.
I wanted to apologize for yesterday.
I was totally outta line and I really,
I didn't mean for you to get hurt.
- I know, it's okay.
- It is?
- You were just having fun, right?
Some celebration though.
I'm pretty sure Mackenzie
was more upset than I was.
- You're telling me.
- I'm glad we have this
chance to talk though.
- Why is that?
- I've been thinking about
what to do about Mackenzie.
I don't wanna squander
under my chance with her,
so I was thinking about
doing something special before I leave.
- Why?
I mean to what end?
- Oh, to show her how serious I am,
to set the stage,
to make her just as happy to see me,
when we all go home.
The whole long distance
relationship scares me,
and I don't want her
to forget about me, but
I'm committed.
- Sorry, I don't really know what to say.
- Well, what do you think, good idea?
- I don't know.
- Of course, you don't
know what I'm planning.
Sorry, so what I was thinking was
I was gonna take her down
to the lake by the volcano,
and they have this boat
there that I can charter,
and we would just go along the lake,
see all this wildlife,
but wait till the sunset
and then have this
nice romantic dinner
just out on the water.
Cool, huh?
- Yeah, man.
Yeah, sure.
- Well, do you think she would go for it?
- I can't speak for her,
but,
but it sounds like something
that any woman would love.
Aren't you a little
overdressed for the pool?
- Getting some sun sorta, too much to do.
- Is everything okay?
- Yeah, yeah.
Just going over all the agreements,
making sure the deal points work.
How's Lucas?
- He's fine.
Yeah, it's all good.
- Thanks for doing that.
- It's the right thing to do.
- You wanna sit down?
- Yeah, sure.
Sure.
- [Mackenzie] So how's the book coming?
- It's good.
It's good, I was rethinking
some of the romance.
- Do tell.
- Well, I'm not exactly sure when yet,
but at one of the near death moments.
- That doesn't narrow it down.
- I thought that he would say,
there's no one he'd rather be with,
because he thinks that it's the end.
And then he would say sorry,
for getting her into this.
And then he would take her hand,
and they would just hang on to each other.
And even though they were in
danger, it wouldn't matter,
because they had each other,
and he'd always have her.
But he just
never told her how.
He
had never told her how
critical she was
in their adventures, with her research and
yeah.
- Yeah.
Well,
I guess it depends on what
else you've written to
get to this point and their feelings.
- That's a good point.
So I think I'm gonna go write that down,
and see if I can make it work,
and I will, well, I'll see you soon.
I'll see you later, I'll see you in a bit.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, okay.
(introspective music)
- Why can't I tell her?
- I can't keep doing this.
Every time I think maybe
he feels something more,
he proves me wrong.
I'm just, I'm tired of kidding myself.
- You have waited and been
his friend for so long.
I'd say time's up.
- See, I could live with
just being friends, but
sometimes I think there's hope.
That's what makes it so hard,
like these little signs that
just fizzle into nothing.
- Well, the way I see it,
you have three options.
One, cut him off completely.
Two, find out how he feels,
even if it changes your friendship.
Or three, stay in limbo.
- Yeah, I don't like any of those.
- Well, there's always option four.
- Four?
- Move on with Lucas.
(soft music)
- All finished.
- Great.
I'm glad we got this to work.
- I'll take good care of Ramano's farm.
- Your farm.
- Si, que.
- It was a pleasure.
- You too, (foreign phrase) gracias.
- Gracias, ciao.
Hey, I was gonna call you,
but then I thought I heard you come back.
- Yeah, but I'm on my way out again.
- Where are you going?
- Lucas texted and wanted
I do something at the lake.
I'll see you later then?
- Yep.
Yeah.
Don't go.
You and Lucas don't belong together.
Anything, you literally could have said
anything to stop her.
I gotta stop her.
(medium tempo instrumental music)
Mackenzie!
(bright music)
Mackenzie?
My phone, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Hey wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait please, I gotta get to the lake.
Are you going to lake,
are you going that way?
Can I come with, it's very important,
(foreign phrase) please?
- Si, si.
- Thank you, thank you.
Gracias, thank you.
Whoa, whoa.
What, what?
Why are we stopping? Why are we stopping?
(speaking in foreign language)
The lake, I have to get to the lake.
This way? This way?
Okay, okay, bien, thank you.
(dramatic orchestral music)
Whoa.
Mackenzie!
(dramatic orchestral music)
Mackenzie?
(indistinct)
(dramatic orchestral music)
Wait, wait, Lucas.
Mackenzie.
Come on!
- Ethan?
- What is he doing?
- Mackenzie,
I finished the story.
- Can you turn around the boat?
Ethan?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, steady.
- [Mackenzie] What's wrong?
What are you doing here?
- I made it.
I made it.
- Are you okay?
- I'm sorry.
Do have any like water?
- Yeah.
- Oh,
thank you man.
- Ethan?
- I'm sorry, Lucas.
I can't let her go with you.
- [Mackenzie] Ethan?
- Not until she knows how I feel.
- What?
- I've been so scared
about how to tell you
that I've been trying to figure
out how to say it properly,
and I just, I can't wait another minute.
Mackenzie, I love you.
- Ethan.
- Nope, no, no, no, no.
Don't Ethan me, just please, just listen.
I'm sorry, I didn't
mean for this to happen.
And especially for being such a jerk
where you're concerned Lucas,
but this woman is my best friend,
and I cannot let her go thinking
that that's all there is between us,
because I want more.
Please don't go off into
the sunset with Lucas.
No offense.
- She's not.
- What?
- Mackenzie was very kindly telling me
that she doesn't think things
between us will go anywhere.
- Really?
Why?
- Because.
- Because she loves you, too.
- I do.
I have for a long time.
- Why didn't you say anything?
- I didn't know if you'd
ever feel the same way.
- Hey, do you mind taking us back?
Thanks.
- I finished my book.
- You did? (chuckling)
- Yeah.
Can I read the ending to you?
Well, this is it.
But where?
- Should be somewhere on the cave wall.
We'll start over here.
- Okay, I'll take this side.
Miss Sabrina, I want
you to know something.
- What?
- Even if we don't find the map,
I wouldn't change one
moment of this journey.
- Me neither.
- Hey,
I'm serious.
There's no one else that I
would rather be with right now.
- Me neither.
- I never told you.
All these years I never told
you what you mean to me,
but if we're gonna get out of this thing,
with or without the map
or wherever it leads to,
dead or alive,
you have to know,
you are everything to me.
And I know I didn't always see that,
but somehow deep down, I always knew,
that you've been the one
that never doubted that
I could do something.
Now, I don't know what I did
to deserve you in my life,
but I will spend the rest of it,
doing everything that I can to make sure
that you and I are always together.
- You really mean that, don't you?
- I love you.
(romantic orchestral music)
- They haven't even found
the treasure map yet.
- Oh no, they do, that's on the next page,
but it doesn't even matter because,
because he found what he really needed.
Come here.
(romantic orchestral music)
- It's good.
- Just good, huh?
- Corporate is gonna love it.
It feels so alive, now.
- I'm glad.
- Your fan base is about to explode.
I told you adding romance
would work, you did it.
- Thank you, thank you.
- So we can get a series
out of this, right?
I'm thinking six, seven books?
- Whoa.
Actually, I've already
started writing a sequel.
(tense music)
Come on.
- Just another adventure, you said.
- Well.
- Simple.
- [Ethan] I may have
underestimated the situation.
- [Mackenzie] Once again.
- Come on, you wouldn't
miss this for the world.
- You're lucky I love you.
- I sure am.
Let's go.
(romantic orchestral music)
(light orchestral music)