23.976 English SDH RETAiL
DVD Subrip NTSC  17.04.2021
(music playing)
"God forbid that I should go to any
heaven where there are no horses."
R.B.Cunningham-Graham, 1917
letter to Theodore Roosevelt
Hancock County, Mississippi
I feel so blessed when I look out
over our land, honey.
It's so beautiful.
We are so lucky.
- Make me a promise, babe?
- Yeah, anything.
You'll always keep this place
in the family.
Of course.
It's our spot.
When I look out there, all I can see
is my blood and sweat and tears.
This place was huge when I got it.
- I knew what it could be, though.
- Look at it now.
So rich, it's perfect.
(chuckles)
Come on.
I'm gonna race you back.
- That is, if you're up to it, old man.
- Who you calling "old man"?
- I usually win.
- Not this time.
If I win,
you get to do stables tonight.
If you win, I'll do dishes.
- Deal?
- Mm-hmm.
How 'bout when I win, you do
the stables for a week, and the dishes.
- You're on.
- Man: Hup!
Race to Redemption (2016)
Also Known As: Race to Win
- (laughs)
- Whoa.
Oh...
The winner is Miss Hannah Rhodes.
Yeah, a few more yards,
I'd of had ya.
(laughs)
Woman on radio: All right, you two,
you proved your endurance.
Time to wrap it up.
These plates
aren't gonna empty themselves.
- Wash up. Get in here.
- All right, boss lady.
Give me five minutes, I'll be there.
I need the five minutes,
so I don't suggest you take 'em.
(laughs)
Well, don't be too long.
All right.
(horse huffs)
(groaning)
(music playing)
Woman: So what did
you guys do this morning?
Hannah: It was great.
We rode forever.
It was fantastic.
Where is your father?
He said that he wanted to feed the horses
before he had lunch himself.
Typical.
Honey, the horses can wait.
We can't.
Gentry!
Gentry.
I'll come.
Gentry:
I love you, son.
Rudy, I need you to take care of
your mom and sister for me.
And this place.
Don't let it go, son.
It stays with us.
Okay, Dad.
There's something
I need you to do for me.
Gentry?
Gentry, baby!
Baby, wake up.
Wake up. Wake up.
(crying)
He's not breathing.
Go get help. Go!
(sobbing)
Baby, wake up, please.
You can't talk about it to anybody.
Ever.
- You understand?
- I won't say a thing.
I know.
Woman: I think it's a bit too soon
to be packing his things, Anne.
I don't think you're ready,
and I don't think it's gonna
feel right for the kids.
(inhales sharply)
What am I supposed to do now, Susie?
Huh?
I can't afford this place.
I can't tend to it.
I told him we didn't
need this much land,
all those horses,
but he had to have it.
(crying)
Susie:
He did the best he could.
You tried to tell him.
Hey, Mom.
You should eat something.
Yeah.
That is a powerful serve
you got there, Sheriff.
You ever play professionally?
I've just been practicing a bit.
Yeah, well, it shows.
Takes a confident man to master
the delicate game of tennis.
Well, that's what they say.
Your serve.
Oh...
- Story of my life.
- Nah, you just pulled it.
Uh, now, no excuses.
Hey, uh, we appreciate the support
through the campaign.
Look forward to making
some positive changes for the county.
Sure, Sheriff, sure.
Building a better community
is in everybody's best interest.
Don't you think?
Speaking of positive changes,
my partners and I were thrilled to hear
about that jail you gonna build.
We definitely vote in favor of that.
You getting at something, Darden?
Why don't we finish this conversation
back at the house?
Whatever you want.
Follow me.
Hey.
How you holding up, banana?
I'm okay.
Yeah?
(Hannah grunts)
No.
But I will be.
I'm really worried
about my mom and Rudy,
and I'm trying really hard
not to completely fall apart myself.
I feel like they need me.
Yeah.
You know, Han, your mom and I,
we're been through
some really tough times.
And we always get through 'em.
I admire your strength.
- You need to grieve.
- I know.
I just don't have
anything to say right now.
Okay.
When you're ready, I'll be waiting...
with some rocky road
and whipped cream.
(Hannah laughs)
I bet you will.
- You and that sweet tooth.
- Eh.
- I binge in moderation.
- (laughs)
A little.
Well, I gotta get going.
I got a lot of things to catch up on.
And happy that I paid attention
when Daddy was still alive,
or I wouldn't even know
where to start.
Can I have a hug?
Oh, baby.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- Gotta get going.
- Yeah.
- (clicks tongue)
So, what's your interest
in the prison, Darden?
Darden: Assume you're gonna be
looking for a contractor.
I'd like to be on the list
of viable candidates.
- So, there's the catch.
- Oh, no, no catch.
More like a suggestion.
To our mutual benefit.
Listen, Darden.
I know all about you
and your shenanigans.
And I've got a pretty good idea what
this county was like before I took over.
I was hired to do a job, and I'm gonna
do it to the best of my ability.
You understand me?
Coming in loud and clear, Sheriff.
Loud and clear.
- Thanks for the tea.
- Oh, now, come on back.
Play another game.
Jiminy Crickets.
I wanna win one.
(birds chirping)
I took inventory last night.
We have 12 hogs,
42 chickens, and three cows.
Now, we'll keep the chickens,
but we're gonna sell the cows
and hogs to the slaughterhouse.
What do you think, Rudy?
Rudy, you work with
all the livestock.
I wanna know
what you think of my plan.
Rudy?
Talk to me.
Honey, say something.
Hannah!
So, what are you thinking, Doc?
Well, physically,
he's perfectly healthy.
No problems there.
He could speak if he chose to.
So, why isn't he talking?
Well, stress for one thing,
but in medical terms,
we refer to it as "selective mutism".
Hannah, can you give us
a moment alone, please?
Doctor:
It's simple, really.
I assume this is his way of dealing
with the loss of his father.
He's just shutdown... temporarily.
Right. Um...
What else can we do in the meantime?
I want you to reach out
to specialist in Houston,
try to get an appointment.
This is not really my expertise.
There you go.
This doctor should be able to
ignite his speech, I can assure you,
but it will take time and money.
Whatever it takes.
(music playing)
- (sobbing)
- Hannah: Mom?
It's okay.
(engine shuts off)
(insects buzzing)
(sighs)
Why are you banging on my door
at 7:00 in the morning?
- You selling something?
- No, I'm not selling anything.
But I am here on business.
Good morning.
My name is Gregory Darden.
Just what is your business,
Gregory Darden?
Your husband owes me
$150,000, ma'am.
My husband's dead, mister.
So, I guess we're done here.
I meant to say your late husband.
And, no, we are not done here.
I am very sorry for
your recent loss, Mrs. Rhodes.
And I do apologize
for my abrupt behavior.
In the wake of his passing,
this becomes your responsibility
in accordance with
the community property laws
of our great state.
Please don't do this.
Unfortunately, when some dies,
this wicked old world
just keeps spinning around.
This property was collateral
against a business loan.
Now it looks like
I'm gonna have to foreclose.
Unless you wanna pack up right now.
- We can call it even-steven.
- I need to call a lawyer.
That's an excellent idea.
Look, Mrs. Rhodes,
I'm not an unreasonable man.
I'll even hire a realtor to help you
relocate you and the kids,
but I am going to need
that money in 30 days.
Otherwise, you leave me no choice
but to return with the sheriff
and seize the property.
By force if need be.
Am I clear enough?
No.
You're not clear enough.
I can't come up with
that amount of money in 30 years.
30 days, Mrs. Rhodes.
You might wanna call that lawyer now.
We have 30 days to pay Darden
or we're gonna have to leave.
What are we gonna do?
If it weren't for Daddy, he wouldn't
have all the cash flow that he does.
He was right not to trust him.
What a snake.
(sighs) Well, lawyer says
there's nothing I can do.
The judgment's valid.
He's entitled to the money Daddy owed.
What if we race Sheba
in the barrel-racing championship?
We can use the prize money
as down payment at least,
and we can take out a loan
on the rest.
Seriously?
- Hannah.
- I am serious.
We can get her in shape in time.
Donny can ride her.
She won before, she'll win again.
It's not a bad idea, Sue.
None of us have come up
with anything better.
Gent took great care of her,
and said she was his jackpot.
Well, I hope he was right.
(sighs)
Dad loved you so much.
We need you to win us
one more championship, you hear?
Just one.
Ain't no races left in that dud.
Definitely no championships.
Back for more abuse, Mr. Birch?
Somebody's gotta
take care of the horses.
And who else is gonna
do it at this rate?
When you're done with Molly,
I need you to take a look at Sheba.
We might be entering her
in some races.
Good luck with that.
(horse huffs)
Whoa.
Whoa, whoa.
There we go.
- Shh.
- (whickers)
- (neighing)
- Easy now.
- Whoa.
- Mr. Birch, I am so sorry.
She's been kinda rowdy
since Daddy left.
I don't get paid enough for this.
I'll be back when you got my money.
(engine starts)
(whispers)
Easy, girl. Easy.
Donny, I know that
if you ride her, she can win.
(Donny chuckles)
Han, this old girl's past her prime.
Besides, your father still owes me
from last time we raced.
Donny, my dad and I
didn't have secrets.
Which means I know that he shaved
all the wages off your debt.
You owe him ten grand at least.
We had an arrangement
to get that squared away.
So, technically, he still owed me
from our race time.
Well, that really
isn't relevant right now.
- Can you please just try?
- (sighs)
- What do I get out of the deal?
- Pride.
- (laughs)
- You can bring back the legacy
of a man who once loved you.
And pride for yourself
for winning with an underdog.
I would be proud and honored
to preserve your father's legacy,
but I expect to be compensated.
I want 10% of the winnings.
- Five.
- Eight.
Seven.
7.5, you got a deal.
- Greedy deal at 7.25.
- (chuckles)
You're your father's daughter.
(music playing)
Whoa, whoa.
(grunts)
This is a waste of my time.
What's wrong?
She gets winded every 50 feet.
Just doesn't have the endurance.
She's just getting warmed up.
She hasn't been trained in a while.
She'll get it.
I know she will.
I know her competition
is gonna be more than just warm.
Come on. She still has it in her.
I know she does.
I'm sorry.
Your father was a great man.
He's gone, and that's hard, I'm sure.
But you're holding on to something
that doesn't exist anymore.
This horse is not a winner.
And she's never gonna be
a winner ever again, Hannah.
You need to find another way
to come up with that money.
'Cause this is not gonna be
a good return on your investment.
I promise.
So, you're just quitting?
One frustrating day
and you're just done?
My father loved you.
He taught you everything you know
and he gave you your big break.
Honor his memory
and just try harder.
Donny!
(softly)
You're all we have.
Well, hello.
I didn't know you'd be here.
Dr. Smith asked when the horses
last had wormer.
I don't know.
- When did the farrier come last?
- I don't know.
Well, what do you know?
That my husband's gone.
I can't do it without him.
- I'm all alone.
- You have me.
And you are stuck with me.
Whether you like it or not.
They need you, Anne.
(music playing)
This is it.
I wanna put the deck
out here somewhere.
Kinda surround the pool, you know?
I want an entertainment area to grilling.
I like to grill, a lot.
I can make some better use
of them stables.
Maybe a warehouse, boat or RV garage?
Perfect.
Tennis court's out there
somewhere, of course.
Me and the sheriff like to play.
Man, I have been waiting
to get my hands on this property.
I am going to use this place.
- Maybe a nine-hole golf course.
- You think there's room?
Sure. All you gotta do is mow down
some of these fields.
Well, draw it up. More activities
the merrier, don't you think?
What are you doing here?
Get off my property!
Safe to say,
I already own it, Mrs. Rhodes.
Just a matter of time.
Hey! Watch it!
These are imported-handmade.
You need to leave right now,
before I get my rifle.
There's no need for that, Mrs. Rhodes.
Hannah!
Hannah: Yeah, Mom?
I am putting y'all out.
All of ya.
- Get my 30/30.
- You know that, right?
(sighs) Come on.
Let's let the chickens have their day.
(breathing heavily)
Brass is worth money.
Gotta liquidate everything we have
if we're gonna make a dent in that debt.
You're gonna need a lot more brass
if you're gonna pay back Darden.
Um, Donny quit today.
What?
So, the race won't be an option
for us anymore.
Hannah...
why don't you race?
Daddy trained you.
You guys won two races.
- I'm not ready.
- (sighs)
I'm never racing again.
I can't without Dad.
Daddy would never want you to give up
on something you love so much.
- You have to do it.
- No, I don't.
Then what can I do?
I'm not ready.
Daddy...
we need your help.
Everything's falling apart,
and I don't know
how much more Mama can take.
And Rudy won't even talk to us.
Please, Daddy, help us.
Waste.
(horse neighs)
He's thought about
making amends
But he's closed the barn door
way too late
Those folks
are no longer his friends
Yeah, he keeps selling out,
then he tries to buy back
When he wins some money
at the dog track...
Four in a row, old man.
You sure you wanna keep this up?
I almost feel bad
taking this money from you.
It's a Christmas present from my wife.
Seriously gonna drop
your marital timepiece
on a game of nine-ball?
I don't have any way
to win my money back.
Okay.
Me, too.
Rack 'em, old man.
That won't be necessary.
Take this...
and take a hike.
- Christmas come early.
- Move. Scram.
Vamoose.
(chuckling)
How much he take you for?
- It doesn't matter.
- Oh, now, come on.
What's the fun of being rich
if you can't spread the wealth around?
I don't want your money.
Look, I know
you haven't been paid out
the Rhode's place
since Gentry passed.
Let me help you with that.
I know those mouths back at the house
are wide open and waiting.
Like little birds.
(chuckles)
What do you think?
Let me buy you a drink.
All right.
- Just one drink.
- All right.
- That's the spirit.
- (knocks on table)
Where have you been?
I've been freaking out.
"Your father was a good man.
I raised this horse to run.
His name is Atonement.
He's my gift to you.
Race him and you will win.
I hope to visit soon.
Sincerely, your concerned friend".
Is this a joke?
There's no way this is real.
(sighs) Rudy, help me
get this horse to the barn.
We have to get him hydrated
before he falls over.
- Rudy: Wait.
- Rudy!
Come on, Rudy, say it.
Rudy, if you have something
to say just say it.
You should race... for Dad.
I'll do it.
I'll race.
Come on.
(music playing)
Everything okay?
Yep, I'm fine.
You're doing a great job.
You aren't ready to quit on me,
are ya?
You know, sometimes I feel like
I'm the adult in this relationship.
- What do you mean?
- (sighs)
I mean I feel like I'm the one
carrying all the weight,
and you expect me to save everyone.
Bail us out of this mess.
Pay back for Daddy's mistakes.
However you wanna look at it,
I can't stand the pressure, Mom.
Hannah.
It's not fair,
and I don't even think I can do it.
Hannah!
Hannah: It's gonna be hard
to leave this place.
It's like losing Dad all over again.
Except, I haven't even recovered
from the first time.
We're not going anywhere.
You have to have more faith
than that, Han.
We're out of time.
We're completely out of options.
We're not gonna figure it out.
Well, I remember when
your dad took on this ranch.
It was like an impossible task.
No one believed
that he could do it.
He had a vision.
And we take view.
You get what I'm saying?
Yeah. Yeah,
I get what you're saying.
Win that race...
and honor him.
(music playing)
What are you so down for, baby girl?
It's just a test of your strength.
Don't let it break you.
I love you all very much.
I miss you, Daddy.
(cheering and applause)
Announcer: Up next,
we have veteran Charlie East
of Hancock County riding Blue Steel.
That's 15.3 for Charlie East
of Hancock County.
15.3, I can't even
come close to that.
Baby, it's just the qualifying race.
If it doesn't work out today,
you still have another shot.
Your daddy taught you
everything you need to know.
He believed in you.
I believe in you.
You can do this.
Okay. Okay.
I'm ready.
Remember, if you feel him slowing down,
give him a good nudge.
You're in control, okay?
You can do this.
Okay.
That's my girl.
- Okay.
- Announcer: Up next, we have newcomer
Hannah Rhodes riding Atonement.
It's not too late to back out, Han.
You don't have to do this.
I wanna do it, Daddy.
I wanna race.
Well, I've never been
more proud of you.
Thanks, Dad.
I just wish I was someone that
you could've been more proud of.
Nobody's perfect, but in my eyes,
you were as close as it gets.
I'm so proud to be your daughter.
So grown up.
When did that happen?
All right.
You go get 'em, baby girl.
- I'll be right there with you.
- (exhales sharply)
I won't let you down, old man.
I won't let you down either.
(cheering and applause)
Announcer:
That's a 14.9 from Hannah Rhodes.
That run qualifies her for
the 4-Friends championship next week.
- Congratulations, Hannah, and Atonement.
- I knew you could do it!
I knew you could do it.
That was amazing.
(music playing)
Uh, hi.
I have a delivery
for Miss Hannah Rhodes.
You're looking at her.
Here you go, and sign here, please.
Hold that.
- Thanks.
- Oh! My riding boots.
Just in time for the race.
Help yourself to some jerky.
Oh, sure.
My dad used to love jerky.
- Mm.
- Jerky can keep you going all day long,
and it's the one thing
that will never disappoint you.
Is that so?
Certainly never disappointed me.
What?
You seem pretty young
to be out there racing.
(laughs)
Okay.
Well, I've been riding since I was six.
And during the summers,
I attend a program
at an equestrian college
in West Virginia.
So, trust me, I have earned
my spot at that ranch.
Uh, well, it was nice to, uh,
have met you, Miss Hannah Rhodes.
(both chuckle)
- Oh, here you go.
- Oh, keep it. I'll make another batch.
- Wait, you made this batch?
- Yeah.
Maybe you could teach me
how to make it sometime.
Yeah.
(laughs)
I'll see you around.
Anne:
Easy, girl. Whoa.
- Whoa.
- Well...
she's in great shape.
She'd due any day now.
Anne: Any day?
That just darkened my week.
I'm not prepared
to have another mouth to feed.
Give her these twice a day.
It'll help.
- Thanks, Doc.
- See it as a happy time.
Don't let it stress you out.
- Yeah.
- I'll be back in a few days
to check on her.
Probably Friday.
If anything happens before then,
please, call me immediately.
Got you on speed dial.
- Anne.
- Yeah.
I know times are tough right now.
But everything's gonna okay.
(music playing on radio)
Well, if it isn't "Dr. Once Was".
How are you this fine afternoon?
Not as good as
my favorite lying, cheating..
Hold that thought.
- You look like you could use a drink.
- Well, yes, I could use a drink.
- Please.
- What's on your mind?
Whiskey on the rocks.
Thank you.
Now, are we here
to trade loving insults,
or you got something for me?
Spend it wisely.
Don't you worry about that.
Well, I'm all ears.
Got this new colt from somewhere.
- Any idea where?
- Not really.
The girl's working him.
Thinking about running him
in the big race.
Hannah? Why?
The other kid Don quit,
so she's training.
Colt looks pretty good
from what I can see.
- How's she look?
- (chuckles)
Like a three year old on a ten-speed.
(laughing)
Well, that's just perfect.
Here you go.
- Why, thank you, darling.
- You got it.
Here's to the precious three year old
on a brand-new ten-speed.
(chuckles)
(music playing)
Still way off,
and you're all over the place.
You need to push.
Atonement can take it.
Well, I can't!
Okay, I feel clumsy and awkward.
And I don't even think
I can control him right now.
I think you've had enough for today.
You're just getting frustrated
because you're overly tired.
You're not ready to quit
on me, are you?
I think I need to give it
a few more runs.
You can do this, baby.
You're wasting your time
on that animal.
It ain't worth five minutes.
If I was a gambling man, I'd say that
she wouldn't make it through winter.
What did you say?
You really should have me
put that horse down.
It's the humane thing to do.
You get off our property.
And don't you come back.
We can get anybody else
to take care of our livestock.
Good luck finding somebody
to do that for free.
Darden, you remember
you said if I did that thing for you,
you'd have something for me?
Well, I changed my mind.
I'll do it.
Count me in.
Don't you listen to him.
Nobody is ever gonna put
any of our horses down.
You understand?
Don't you worry.
(kisses)
My sweet, strong boy.
(music playing)
Do you know my name?...
Gentry:
I'm real proud of you, son.
I know it wasn't easy to watch
your mom and sister go through all that,
but you kept your word.
Okay, Dad.
I love you.
I love you, too, bud.
My mama's eyes
My daddy's hands
My grandma's heart
If you wanna see
I'll show you more
I'll show you things...
Gentry:
I'm real proud of you, baby girl.
You've come a long way
in just a few days,
and I know you can do this.
With a pretty voice
You're my champion.
Who writes you songs
And holds you close
We sure appreciate you
coming by, my friend.
I got a feeling
things are gonna go our way.
We'll be thinking about you.
I like your bike.
You, um, want some jerky?
Thanks.
Come on, girly.
And it's killing me
I wanna let you in
But I can't keep on like this...
Well, she didn't get
the riding gene from Gent.
Anne: She's just rusty.
Just a girl...
Needs a little time
to get reacquainted.
- Keep going.
- (groans)
This place is as good as Darden's.
Come on, banana!
- (chatter)
- (music playing on radio)
I missed that shot myself.
- The stick slipped.
- Your stick slipped?
That's just sad.
Pay up.
- You don't even need the money.
- It's not about need.
It's about earning it.
Wouldn't you agree?
Look, this thing we're doing
is a business deal.
Just like any other.
But you drop so much
as a stitch anywhere,
you're gonna be out a lot more
than 20 measly bucks.
It's just not right, Darden.
They're good people.
They've suffered enough.
Don't let your conscience bother you.
You got your own debts to pay.
You want out, you pay up.
Pure and simple.
We agreed?
I guess we are.
I love this place.
I think I'm gonna retire here.
Later, gator.
- What is it?
- Deliciousness.
You need that for
the big race tomorrow.
Trust me,
it'll make a big difference.
- (gags)
- Mm-mm.
Mm, I.. I think
I'm gonna throw up.
Mm-mm.
You know how long it took me?
That's like 17 pounds of greens.
To take this many veggies
and make it this big.
There are so many vitamins in there.
Nutrients. Electrolytes.
- We have any gum?
- Vitamin C. Potassium.
No sugar. I want your body
at optimal peak performance.
It's gum.
And what about my mental state?
- I feel like I'm going crazy.
- Yeah, you look like you are, too.
(music playing)
Susie: Right now,
we're most concerned about your speed,
- your balance, your agility..
- Okay, I get it.
Good night. I love you.
Come on, Rudy.
(sighs)
Hey...
I know it's hard with
that much pressure on you, okay?
But your best is gonna be enough.
Enough for your mom
and enough for Rudy.
- Okay?
- You really think I can do it?
Oh, I know you can.
That's why I'm so hard on you.
Remember, I only need your best.
Get some rest.
Okay.
Good night, banana.
(music playing)
(sighs)
Announcer: Welcome to the 2015 Hancock
County Barrel-Racing Championships.
We've got over 100 competitors
here today, all racing the clock
to bring home
that first place buckle.
Announcer #2:
I'll tell you what I noticed, Steve.
This is a much tighter arena
than when I used to race.
It's gonna be very important for
the competitors to hug the corners close
- and get off to a fast start.
- Susie: Your best.
Win or lose, it doesn't matter
as long as you do your best.
I will be so proud of you.
I'm already so proud of you.
I feel like I'm gonna forget
everything I need to know.
Like all of my training is just
gonna completely disappear.
Honey, you know what to do.
- Get out there and do it.
- Announcer: Up next, we have veteran
Charlie East of Hancock County
riding Blue Steel.
- Okay. Okay.
- (cheering and applause)
And veteran Charlie's out of the gate.
He's running strong.
He's making his way to the first barrel.
He goes around the first barrel.
He skipped the pocket hard.
He's making his way
to the second barrel.
Ooh, he's going around the second barrel
now and he's headed toward the third.
Gentry:
You done it, baby girl.
Announcer: He's moving 'round barrel
number two. He's coming on in fast.
I'm so proud of you
and your perseverance.
I love you, Hannah.
What if I can't do it, Dad?
There will be other opportunities
out there if you wanna take 'em.
So no worries.
Get on out there.
Announcer:
Ooh, he's cutting the pockets hard.
He's making his way
to the finish line.
And it's a 14.767.
- Where is she?
- Heck of a run for our veteran
- Charlie East.
- (Atonement whickers)
Up next, we have Hannah Rhodes
riding Atonement.
(cheering and applause)
Hannah's strong out the gate.
She's looking good.
- Ooh, a slight stumble around barrel one.
- Dang it.
Come on, banana.
Announcer: Picking it up right here.
She's getting some speed.
She chasing. She's got around two.
Here she comes.
That's right!
Announcer:
Oh, knocking down barrel three
is gonna take Hannah
right out of today's competition.
(crying)
- What happened?
- It was like we weren't connected.
I went left, he went right,
and I... I don't know what happened.
It was like I was riding
a different horse.
You pick yourself up.
Stand tall.
You did your best,
and everything is gonna be okay.
Hannah, are you okay?
I'm so sorry I let you down, Mom.
No, sweetie.
Oh, you could never let me down.
I'm so proud of you.
Baby, I love you so much.
All right, let's get going on plan B.
We have a plan B?
Not yet,
but we'll think of something.
Anne:
Come on. Let's go.
(music playing on radio)
Oh, there you are, Jeffery.
Nicely done, Jeffery, nicely done.
- My money.
- What money?
You said that if I did that thing for you,
you would give me more money.
- Did I say that?
- Yeah, you did, and I want my money.
I think you misunderstood
our arrangement.
I said I would clear your debt.
I never said I would
pay you for anything.
Hey, you better take it
down a notch, Jeffery!
You best tread
very lightly right now.
Otherwise, you are gonna
ruin my celebration.
You don't wanna ruin my celebration,
do you, Jeffery?
Because that would
make me very angry.
And if I became angry, I would
have to find a place to put that anger.
And there you are.
Right there in front of me.
So...
we done here?
Where is that little girl?
I like that little girl.
(music playing)
I've never been afraid
Of sinking like a stone
Holding on to everything
Jumping in alone
It's like I rush to the bottom
Always craving the deep end
That feeling of falling
Yeah, that feeling of sinking
I am so heavy
When will I just learn to float?
Bye now, girl.
You were always his favorite.
It's just you and me now.
Hannah:
So this is plan B?
Just leaving.
Look at the bright side.
No more maintaining
all this land, this big house.
No more picking up poop for me.
Exactly.
Well, maybe we'll move
to a high-rise in the city.
- The city?
- What do you think?
I can't just park my horse
at a parking meter.
Okay.
Maybe not the city.
I really am sorry, Hannah.
I really am.
For what?
I should never have
put so much pressure on you.
It was never your problem to solve.
It was wrong of me
to burden you with it all.
I like doing all that stuff.
It makes me feel like
I'm filling Daddy's shoes.
Besides, Dad always told me
I was his toughest cowgirl.
Yeah, that sounds like Daddy.
(chuckles)
Now pack.
We have to get this done
so we can just move on.
Promise me one thing, Hannah.
What?
That you just be a kid.
You've always been so grown up.
I want you to just focus on yourself.
Okay?
No more training.
No more excessive chores.
No parenting your brother.
Me, for that matter.
Let that be a change you make.
- Meet some kids your own age.
- (sighs)
Meet a boy.
- (laughs)
- You need that.
I'm really okay, Mom.
You are too much, girl.
All right.
(whickering)
Hey, girl.
Hi.
It's coming, girl.
Mom and Rudy, hurry up.
It's coming right now.
Hurry.
He's got you pretty
stressed out today, huh?
You need something a little stronger?
Pour me something, Teddy.
Well, the whippoorwill
Is a desperate bird
She steals the sunshine...
You could've said no.
Said no to what?
Come on, Jeff.
I saw you talking to Darden.
I heard what he talked you into.
I needed the money.
You needed money, Jeff?
We all need money.
There are more honest ways
to earn a buck.
There are good people, Jeff.
This is your chance
to be one of 'em.
Do the right thing.
Or I will.
When the highway
Is your friend
(sighs)
How.. how is she?
Is the baby okay?
She's just fine.
It's a boy.
What should we name him?
- Redemption.
- (horse huffs)
I think that's a fine name, Hannah.
Oh, I'll get your money.
Oh, not necessary.
On the house.
My thank you to Gent and to you
for always taking such good care of me.
Oh, thank you.
Oh, we'll miss times like these.
You've always been so wonderful.
We have so many great memories
of you and these horses.
Well, we need to make sure
we get this colt on medication
to make sure he gets a good start.
- Use your money for that.
- Thank you.
This is your time now, son.
I'm sorry you had to grow up so fast,
but I know you're gonna do well.
I need you to take care of
your mom and my baby girl.
I love you.
Always.
Hannah:
We can't keep going.
We don't have any more time.
Darden's taken everything away.
Well, our fate
hasn't been sealed yet.
Anything could happen.
Anything.
Well, is that a smile?
- Maybe.
- Oh...
- I like smiles.
- (giggling)
- Where's the colt?
- It's in the barn.
Well, let's go take a look.
I was thinking about making
some of my famous
blueberry pancakes for you two.
I mean, if.. if you want me to.
- Really?
- Yes.
- All right.
- (giggling)
- I'm gonna go get some blueberries and...
- (engine idling, horn honks)
- Do you hear that?
- Is that Darden?
Better not be Darden.
It didn't look like Darden.
- Hey there.
- (horse huffs)
You're a beautiful boy.
You gonna make one heck of
a racehorse someday.
Yes, you will.
That is one good-looking horse,
my friend.
- Morning, ladies.
- Anne: Who might you be?
You one of Darden's goons?
We're almost done packing.
Darden?
I wouldn't be caught dead in
the same room with a crook like Darden.
My name's Carter.
Well, what are you doing here, Carter?
And how does my son
know you and I don't?
I beg your pardon, ladies.
I mean you no harm.
I just came to check on
my colt over there.
Now, let me
tell you something, mister.
- Carter.
We've already lost our ranch.
- Miss...
- Susie.
Susie, I don't come here emptyhanded.
Nor am I here to collect a debt,
like everybody else
who walks onto this property.
What I intend to do
is to write y'all a big ol' check,
and in exchange,
you will relinquish to me
that fine racing specimen
in the stall over there.
What are you talking about?
Gentry bred his mare to a stallion
- ..named Astounding Day.
- No way.
You mean the champion
thoroughbred Astounding Day?
The very same.
I received an invitation
to buy the foal at birth.
- What?
- That's right.
Rudy over there gave me notice,
so I'm here to claim my door prize.
I...
Rudy gave you notice?
This is a signed agreement
between Gentry and myself.
Both our attorneys were present
during the negotiations.
Our agreement took place
long before Gentry's death,
and so it predates
any claim to ownership by Darden.
- Mr. Carter, are you serious?
- I'm serious, little lady.
Now, if y'all don't mind, I'd like to
give you a check and be on my way.
I do want my vet to come
and take a look at the colt immediately.
If y'all don't mind.
This is a fabulous opportunity
for Redemption.
How much did you guys agree on?
Well, I'm gonna shave off
his gambling debts from the price.
After deducting those bets,
I'm gonna owe you $250,000.
What?
250,000?
Is that what you just said?
Yes, he did, and it's too late
to take it back now.
Sir, you just bought yourself
a racing horse.
Um, I'll go grab your paperwork.
- We had a vet..
- We'll handle the paperwork later on.
Rudy, have a good one, sir.
Wait, what time does the bank close?
Is today Friday or Saturday?
- Can we cash this check right now?
- I don't see why not.
I think the bank's open
a few more hours.
Oh!
- Oh! (screams)
- This can't be happening.
(cheering)
Oh, my God!
(screaming)
Hello, Darden.
It's a pleasure to see you.
Well, I'm glad to see
you've touched base with reality.
At last.
Y'all packed up?
Ready to go?
Yeah, I packed.
We were all packed.
But then we unpacked.
So...
Why on earth would you do that?
We found a way to pay you.
- We got your money.
- All your money.
Plus interest.
I assume you'll be satisfied now.
You know, I think it's time that
you and your fan club get going.
Otherwise, we'll have to forcibly
remove you from the property.
Get off our property, Darden.
I'll bet you this thing ain't worth
the paper it's printed on.
Y'all think you can
play me for a fool?
(laughs) We already know
you're a fool, Darden.
But the check is good.
Call the bank.
They're open till four.
Call the bank?
Call the bank.
I'm gonna call the police.
That's who I'm gonna call.
I am serious.
You all need to think about this.
Looks like somebody
already made that call.
(laughing)
You all called the police on me?
Afternoon, Sheriff.
Can I get you anything?
Iced tea? Lemonade?
No, thank you, Susie.
And don't worry,
I'm not here for you this time.
Darden, I'm here for you.
(sighs)
I need you to come with me.
I need to have a little chat with you
down at the station.
John, what's this all about?
Your buddy Jeffery
told us everything.
I got a warrant for your arrest.
I don't want this to be too formal,
so if you just get in the car,
- ..we can make this nice and simple.
- Let me see that warrant.
Give me that warrant.
I'm gonna need to talk to my lawyer.
Yeah, well,
you can talk to him downtown.
Get your hands off me!
I put you in office, you moron!
- I own you!
- Back down, Darden.
Don't make me do this
in front of all these nice people.
This is 100,000 volts,
and it will rectify your noncompliance.
All right. All right.
We'll talk down at the station.
You said you wanted to
get in on the prison.
Well, here's your chance
to get a firsthand look at it.
Well, that was a nice surprise.
What did he do? What happened?
Your girl here lost her race
because he drugged her horse.
He drugged my horse?
He bet against her and stood to win
thousands off her loss.
It was a scheme.
I'm sorry.
It's the ugly truth.
I told you, Aunt Susie.
I felt like I was driving
a different horse.
We're lucky all he did
was kick down a barrel.
It could've been much worse.
I'll be taking that.
You won't be making it to the bank
by four anyways.
He won't be needing that
where he's going.
He'll have all of his needs
taken care of for quite some time.
You can be sure of that.
So... no high-rise?
Nope, no high-rise.
You okay with that?
Oh, I am so much more
than okay with that.
(laughs)
Hey, you're the delivery guy.
The one who gave me my boots.
That's my beef jerky.
Yep.
Also reserve deputy sheriff.
Somebody's gotta deliver the mail just
like somebody's gotta protect this county.
- Guess I'm the guy for both jobs.
- Guess so.
By the way, you got me hooked.
There's nothing like homemade beef jerky.
(laughs)
When are you gonna show me
how to make some?
I don't even know you.
Can't just share my deepest,
darkest secret, can I?
Well, maybe we should
get to know each other.
- Yeah.
- I get off work a little later.
I could swing by..
I mean, if that's okay with you.
- That's just fine with her.
- Mom.
Please do come by.
I'm making my famous blackberry cobbler.
- We'd love to have you.
- Mom.
I will be here.
- Bye.
- Toot-a-loo, Ron.
- (laughs)
- Mm.
So what's next, Rudy? Hmm?
You know, I kinda like the idea
of breeding and selling horses.
You make quite the sales boy.
And I got a lot of
really good names for 'em, too.
Like, uh, Misty.
Or Shadow.
Or Charming.
Rooty Tooty Fresh 'N Fruity.
(both laugh)
Hey, I love you.
I love you so much.
And I am so happy
that you're back with us.
Let's get going.
(music playing)
Hey, pretty lady.
I'm sorry about
all the trouble I caused.
I wanna thank you.
For saving this place.
Thank you for what you've done
for our baby girl.
You gave her her confidence back.
And she might not have won
this time out,
but she'll be ready
for the next time.
It's all coming together.
Y'all just keep moving.
We will.
They miss you.
I miss you.
(laughter)
What, you too old
to let your Aunt Sue feed ya?
Yes, he is.
- I'm gonna get you.
- Stop embarrassing him.
Well, everyone,
it has been a heck of a year,
but we made it through.
So glad that y'all could join us here
for his birthday.
I love everyone
at this table so much.
Happy birthday, Rudy.
Susie:
Happy birthday.
- Anne: Oh, my gosh.
- (laughing)
I love you all very much.
I'm real proud of who you are
and who I see you becoming.
Can't wait to ride with you again, Han.
One of my favorite things
in the world to do.
I'm excited to ride again
with you, too, Dad.
I love you, honey.
I love you more. Always.
I'm always here.
Always.
(music playing)
Race to Redemption (2016)
Also Known As: Race to Win
(music playing)
I am leaving on a journey today
Packing up this soul
and this skin
There are things
I've been meaning to change
I don't think I can without going
And I will climb, climb, climb
the highest hill
Till I'm face to face with the sun
My eyes will see
Their burning reflection
I'm coming undone
Leave a trail of sorrow
and shame
And all of the hurts I've held onto
They are much too heavy
a weight
To take all the places I want to
And I will climb, climb, climb
the highest hill
Till I'm face to face with the sun
My eyes will see
Their burning reflection
Oh
I'm coming undone