(ominous music)
(woman screams)
(spray can rattles)
(man laughs)
(man coughs)
(birds chirp)
(foreboding music)
("Wrong Goods" by Uglybones)
(shouts lyrics angrily)
- [Lev] Fucking jump!
(hardcore punk music)
- I don't know
why you'd do that!
- Do what?
- Pick up the stumbled
brother then topple over.
Don't get fucking trampled!
(shouting lyrics angrily)
(shouts lyrics angrily)
(crowd cheers)
Hey!
- Yeah?
- Don't play "Boozehound".
- What?
- If you play that song,
I'll fucking kill you!
- All right, man, yeah.
All right, so we're Uglybones,
thanks for coming out.
(crowd cheers)
("Not the Same" by Uglybones)
(shouts lyrics angrily)
(eerie music)
(crowd cheers)
All right, next one goes
out to someone special.
You know who you are.
("Boozehound" by Uglybones)
(shouting lyrics angrily)
- Shit, James.
♪ Straight Edge Kegger
(shouting lyrics angrily)
(hardcore punk music)
- You look like you
can use a smoke.
- No thanks, I don't smoke.
- Really?
Your loss.
- I don't drink either.
Thanks, though.
- [Sean] So you're
one of those, huh?
- One of those what?
- You know.
True till death dicks.
Oh, hold on, I'm not
trying to offend you.
Just, I've never
really understood it.
- You wouldn't.
- Aw, come on.
Don't be like that.
I mean, I get it,
for the most part.
Group of fans palling
around, same beliefs.
I even get you thinking
it's the moral high ground.
I mean, I don't agree with it.
- Obviously.
- [Sean] But I sorta get it.
- All right then, Confucius,
what don't you get about it?
- I don't get all
these scenes anymore.
Wasn't the whole point to
get away from the clubs?
Hardcore has turned into
this cliquey version
of the mathletes.
And you straight edge
fucks are the worst.
- Fuck you.
- Hey, fuck you too, buddy.
I'm just saying, I
got into this music
because it was fun and chaotic.
You know, bouncing
around, picking up change.
You know what I mean.
Just, it doesn't seem
like your pals in there
are having much fun anymore.
You included.
- I'm fine, man, I just
needed a little air.
- Sure, man, whatever you say.
- Look, I gotta...
(hardcore punk music)
- Come on, Manners.
Leave the kid alone.
Hey kid.
Look at me.
I am not gonna ask again, kid.
(foreboding music)
Why'd you wear that shirt?
- What?
- I know you heard me, kid.
What's with the shirt?
- Tell him you're a patriot.
- Stay the fuck out of this.
- I don't know, my
girlfriend bought it for me.
- I didn't ask who
got it for you, kid.
What I asked was
why you wore it.
- I don't know,
it's just a shirt.
I thought it was cool.
- Shit.
What a twig. (laughs)
- Know what?
You're right.
It is cool.
It's a cool shirt.
So cool, in fact, that
I just have to have it.
- I can ask her
where she got it.
- Jesus, kid.
- I believe that what
my brother's saying
is that I don't
want another shirt.
What I want is that one.
- And what am I
supposed to wear home?
- Well, that's not my
problem, now is it, kid?
- You really should've
thought of that
before you wore that stupid
bullshit shirt in there.
(sighs)
- Give me the shirt
or take a beating.
Your choice.
- I can't, I can't
give you the shirt.
My girlfriend will kill me.
- Better her than us.
- Please, just...
- Getting impatient here, kid.
- Just...
- Done.
It's done.
- Thank you, Brad.
And thank you, kid!
(hardcore punk music)
Oh.
Tell your girlfriend I
said thanks for the shirt.
- Get up.
Kid, I'm not fucking asking,
get up off the ground.
- Keaton.
- What?
- It's Keaton, not kid.
- Tell someone who gives a shit.
- Brad!
Smile, Manners.
- You all right?
- I should've fought back.
- No.
No, you really shouldn't have.
You never get in a
fight you can't win.
How much money you got?
- Are you gonna
take my money too?
- No, just how much
you got on you?
- Five bucks.
- Get back in there
and buy a shirt
off the Uglybones merch table.
- Thanks, I guess.
- Whatever, don't
get all sentimental.
You owe me if I see
you at another show.
(horn honks)
- Daddy's calling,
better run home.
- Fuck you.
- Fuck you too.
Looks like you're
buying me a drink.
(solemn music)
- Brad.
Hey, yo, Brad.
(patrons chatter)
Earth to Brad.
- You good?
- Yeah, I'm sorry, I'm
just a little out of it.
- You think?
- All right.
Benefits show.
Who's doing what?
- Yeah, Tricky's on lineup,
Manners is out
putting up flyers.
- I'm running merch
table, getting a distro.
- Awesome, man.
Anyone coming from Antifa?
- Shit.
I'll get on it.
I keep forgetting.
- You gotta at least reach out,
otherwise we'll never
hear the end of it.
- I know, I know.
- All right, and I'm
bringing the cell jammers
for whenever the cops
break up the show
for a stupid reason
like last time.
What's Brad doing?
- I don't know, man, sorta
sounds like it's all covered.
What?
- Kinda seems like the
last couple of things
have been all covered.
- Come on, I promoted
for the show at Tricky's.
- Posting online is
not exactly the type
of help I'm meaning.
- All right, so I'll reach out
to he anti-fascist guys then.
- No, I got it.
- No, don't sweat it.
I gotta go.
- We just started.
- So catch me up later, yeah?
Tricky, Damon.
Boomer, go fuck yourself.
(tense music)
- Fuck you too, man.
(record crackles)
("Nous" by Noose)
(shouting lyrics angrily)
- You like Noose, huh?
- What, no.
Duh.
That's why I have it
over there on my shelf.
- Always with the jokes.
I just meant that
they're a pretty hardcore
straight edge group.
Kinda surprised you dig them.
- You know, hanging out with you
is turning out to
be a real blast.
- Dick.
- So I have to be edge
to like good music?
You ever watch porn?
- What?
- Do you ever watch pornography?
- Well yeah, not like
a lot or anything.
- So then are you
into exploiting women?
Or better yet, are you just
into seeing naked dudes?
- What, no, of course not.
- Well, then there you have it.
- There you have what?
- Just because
you like something
doesn't mean you have
to support the message.
Yeah, try keeping up.
One of these days
I'll learn you.
- Would you ever
listen to Flathead?
- Hell no!
- Cause they're Nazis?
- No, because their
music fucking blows.
Granted, it helps other Nazis,
and I'm not gonna
support that shit.
But if their music
was good enough,
I'd still probably listen.
- You would?
- Yeah, I mean I am
a big fan of lyrics,
so if their shit
was all hate speech,
then I probably wouldn't
be that interested.
But you know, good
tunes is good tunes.
You think you agree
with everything
every band ever says or does?
I doubt it.
- Aw, you may be
right about that,
but I still wouldn't
support groups like that.
- So then what about Uglybones?
- I don't follow.
- They're notorious partiers.
All their shit is about
getting fucked up.
- Yeah, I can't support that.
- Yeah, I know.
So...
- So what?
- So then why did you
even go to the show?
- Oh, that's was James' idea.
- Yeah, why am I not surprised?
- What?
What, you know James?
- I know of him.
And I know his type.
(eerie music)
- You know, never
understood the whole
family picks you up thing.
- Well, it's not like you
had the support system
to even grant you the option.
- Still.
I fucking hate
these college kids.
I mean, each year, more and
more move out of the dorms
and into the neighborhood.
- It's a free country.
- Yeah?
Bullshit.
Hey, hipsters!
How's about you
stay gone this time?
- Spring break!
(James chuckles)
- What's that all about?
All right, let's have it.
What's been going
on with you lately?
- [Brad] What do you mean?
- Come on.
Can't bullshit a
bullshitter, Bradley boy.
- Don't call me that.
- So sorry, sensitive guy.
- I hate when you call
me that, all right?
- Well, out with it.
(sighs)
- I don't know, man,
I've just been getting
sorta bored lately.
- Okay, well let's do
something about that.
We can go see a
show up in the city
or go mess up some
yuppies downtown.
- That's just it, though.
Been getting bored of that.
- With what, the shows?
- No, man, the music,
the fights, the politics.
- What the fuck's
that supposed to mean?
(tense music)
- Just feels like
it's all sorta...
- Sorta what?
- Sorta pointless.
- What?
- I just feel like we
aren't doing anything
to help out anymore, you know?
- We got the fucking
Nazis out of our shows.
Don't you fucking tell
me we've done nothing.
- That's not what I meant.
- What the fuck do
you mean then, Brad?
- Chill out, bro.
- Bro?
Don't you fucking tell
me to chill out, Brad.
- Know what, don't go fucking
barking orders at me, James.
I'm not one of your
goddamn cronies
you can just boss
around, all right?
- Yeah, you're not, which
is why I wouldn't expect you
to be the one to start
acting like such a pussy
all of a sudden.
- Go fuck yourself.
- [James] Don't you
fucking walk away.
- The hell off me.
- Shit.
I'm sorry, man.
I lost my temper.
- [Brad] Get the
fuck off my porch.
- Come on, man.
Brad.
(door closes)
- Never.
He's never put his
fucking mitts on me, man.
- You need a drink.
- Hardy har, funny guy.
- No, I'm serious.
You need to relax.
- I don't believe in that.
- Believe in what, relaxing?
You know, I'd
almost believe that.
- I don't need to
drink to relax.
- Right, I can see that.
- Smug fucking asshole,
I should've done
something, said something.
I should've hit him back.
- Hey, got you a drink.
You know, didn't you
tell that kid at the club
he shouldn't pick a
fight he can't win?
- So?
- Well, come on.
- You don't think
I could take James?
- (chuckles) No.
- Bullshit.
You're an asshole.
Think your OJ's
past its due date.
- Um, no.
No, that wasn't it.
- Sean, what the hell?
- Dude, I'm sorry.
You scooped it up
so fucking fast
I didn't even have
time to stop you.
- Think I'm gonna be sick.
- You know, you did
just have a drink.
Why not have a few more?
- No, no, Sean, there is no
way I'm taking another drink.
("The Cult Song" by
Shannon & The Clams)
(wailing and scatting)
♪ One of us, one of us,
one of us, one of us ♪
♪ Sick of the dancing,
sick of the chanting ♪
♪ I don't wanna be in
your cult no more ♪
♪ Sick of the Nikes,
sick of the Kool-Aid ♪
♪ I don't wanna be in
your cult no more ♪
♪ Sick of Moroni,
sick of nephi ♪
♪ I don't wanna be in
your cult no more ♪
♪ Ooga-booga, ooga-booga,
ooga-booga, baby ♪
♪ We are not under
mind control ♪
♪ Sick of the dancing,
sick of the chanting ♪
♪ I don't wanna be in
your cult no more ♪
♪ Sick of the Nikes,
sick of the Kool-Aid ♪
♪ I don't wanna be in
your cult no more ♪
♪ Sick of Moroni,
sick of nephi ♪
♪ I don't wanna be in
your cult no more ♪
♪ Ooga-booga, ooga-booga,
ooga-booga, baby ♪
♪ We are not under
mind control ♪
(scatting)
♪ One of us, one of us,
one of us, one of us ♪
♪ One of us, one of us
♪ Hook 'em and scrape 'em,
and fill 'em full of blood ♪
♪ I don't wanna be in
your cult no more ♪
♪ Sick of the dancing,
sick of the chanting ♪
♪ I don't wanna be in
your cult no more ♪
♪ Sick of the Nikes,
sick of the Kool-Aid ♪
♪ I don't wanna be in
your cult no more ♪
♪ Sick of Moroni,
sick of nephi ♪
♪ I don't wanna be in
your cult no more ♪
(chuckles)
- Maybe you should
slow down a little.
(coughs)
(groans)
Damn it!
(chuckles)
Really?
- Yeah, that happened.
- Wasn't at the Capitalist
show last weekend.
- Yeah, he didn't show for
Damon's party last week either.
- Yeah, I know.
He hasn't been
answering texts, calls.
(sensual jazz music)
- Well, my sister
heard he's gonna be
at the party on Tinkler.
- What, at the house?
Go ask your sister.
- You really think?
- Anybody else we
know on Tinkler?
(heavy metal music)
(screaming lyrics angrily)
(hardcore punk music)
- Well, look who
decided to show up.
Here you go, try this.
It's called beer.
It's amazing.
Oh, come on.
Just one fucking sip to find
out it's not gonna kill you.
I promise that you
won't get molested.
- You're such an idiot.
- Yeah, sometimes.
Yeah!
(coughs)
- This go bad, or this just
how bad it always tastes?
- Yeah, sometimes, but, you
know, you'll get used to it.
- It tastes disgusting.
- Very good.
(partygoers chatter)
(garage punk music)
(shouts lyrics angrily)
Maybe.
- Maybe what?
- Maybe, that's her name.
This is her house.
- Oh.
Well, thanks.
(toilet flushes)
- (gasps) Fuck.
All right.
Step two.
(screams aggressively)
- Thank you!
- Maybe.
- Yeah.
- No, my name, it's Maybe.
- No, I meant
like, yeah, I know.
- Oh, do you now?
Well then it would seem you
have me at a disadvantage.
- Yeah, I guess.
I'm sorry.
(laughs)
I am Brad.
- Brad?
- Yeah, it was my dad's name.
- Nah, sounds like
a fat girl's name.
- What?
- Claire.
- Shit, yeah, got it.
- Thank you.
- You, you want a drink?
- Yes.
(guitar strums)
(knocking)
(groans)
- It's so warm.
(insistent knocking)
(hardcore punk music)
- So I gotta know.
What made you break edge?
- Oh.
Are we gonna get
into this right now?
- We don't have to.
It was Sean, right?
You're gay for Sean?
- God damn it.
(laughs)
- But seriously, I wanna know.
- All right.
I did it because
I'm gay for Sean.
- (laughs) You shit.
- No, I just, it just
got old, I guess.
- Got old?
- No, I mean, it
turned into something
I didn't really want it to be.
- Isn't the whole point
to be uncompromising
and hold to the
rules of the club?
- It's not a club.
- It's a bunch of guys, right?
- Yeah.
- Do you own anything
that matches?
- Well, yeah, but...
- Then it's a club.
So what changed
about the not-club?
- When James and I started in
on this whole straight-edge
thing, it was just as a means
to get rid of all the
bad shit at shows.
Skinheads, drug dealers.
- Skins?
- Yeah, red laces, not SHARPs.
A bunch of the guys that
were coming to our shows
were affiliated in
one way or another.
- Okay.
Still doesn't explain much.
- All right, sorry.
Well, when we started,
it was just about
making sure kids
had a safe space.
No fascists, no drugs,
and it wasn't an STD fest
like with the hippies.
- Oh, yeah, gross, hippies.
- Yeah, but as time went on,
James got more
and more militant.
The list of rules grew.
He cut ties with a lot
of our friends who,
who he thought weren't
true believers.
- True believers?
- Yeah, like edge
till death types.
- Gotcha.
- Now it just feels like an
exclusive club for bullies.
Shows are just as
unsafe and violent
for the younger kids
growing up in the scene.
- Oh, I hate that word.
- Yeah, me too, actually.
Just get this feeling like
I've wasted a lot of my life
worrying about what
other people are doing
rather than doing what
I wanna do, you know?
- That sucks.
- Yeah.
Sucks.
- But now, you're doing what
you really wanna do now, right?
- Yeah, kinda.
- What do you mean, kinda?
- Oh, nevermind, it's dumb, I...
- [Sean] Gay!
(giggles)
- You, you want another drink?
- Yes, please.
How you feeling?
- Feel like there's a
mosh pit in my stomach.
(laughs)
(foreboding music)
(chatting)
(guitar strums)
(mumbles)
(whoops)
- This is not my microphone.
(man shouts)
Here we fucking go!
(grungy punk music)
Trail of Death.
(audience cheers)
(hardcore punk music)
(screams lyrics aggressively)
- Come on, bitch, you've
been in here forever.
- Fucking fall in?
- Come on.
- [Young Woman] Come on,
lady, you fucking fall in?
Get out!
God, come on.
(screams lyrics aggressively)
(grungy punk music)
(hardcore punk music)
(screaming lyrics aggressively)
(ominous music)
(alternative rock music)
- Did you hear that?
- No.
Keep going?
- Sure.
- [Singer] What just happened?
- [Man] I think
we're under attack.
- Under attack?
(suspenseful music)
- [Man] Get away
from the window!
- What the fuck?
- [Man] We're all gonna die!
(crowd clamors)
- [Damon] What the fuck?
- [James] Get in there.
Now.
(crowd clamors)
- Please.
Did somebody call the cops?
- We tried already,
nobody has signal.
- Shit.
(tense music)
They're using a jammer.
- [Woman] A what?
- They're blocking our service.
- We should fight back.
There's more of us than them.
- Just let me
think for a second.
- [Damon] What was that, man?
This isn't what we agreed to.
- [James] This isn't
a fucking democracy.
You were here, too.
So it's either you or it's them.
Weigh it.
- [Damon] What the shit is that?
(eerie music)
- James.
(crowd murmurs)
- We need to go for help!
- [Man] We should lock
ourselves in the basement.
- We'll be trapped down there,
you fucking idiot!
(crowd clamors)
- All right, nobody panic.
We need to stay calm and stay...
(crowd screams)
Wait, stay in the house!
(tense music)
(man cries)
- Oh my gosh, no!
(shouts in pain)
(suspenseful music)
- [Man] Come on!
Come on!
(wails)
- Fuck!
(grunts)
Help!
- [Boomer] Well go get her.
(unsettling music)
(suspenseful music)
- Need a push, man!
What, what the hell!
(screams)
What do you mean, man?
(unsettling music)
- Wait.
Help!
(girl coughs)
- [Girl] Can somebody
please hold back my hair?
(tense music)
(woman moans)
- Yo, what the fuck?
- [Maybe] You're
in my fucking room!
(screams)
- [Man] Please, no.
Help, please.
Let go!
No.
Oh no!
No, please.
Please, I'm your friend!
- (screams) Brad!
Let me go, let me go!
(man gurgles)
No, stop, stop!
Get the fuck off me!
Stop, stop it!
God!
Stop, get the fuck off me!
Brad!
- You all right?
- Yeah, I think so.
- What do we do with him?
- Fuck it.
Say goodnight, asshole.
(foreboding music)
- [Tricky] Shit.
Sort of poetic, isn't it?
Well, time to pop your cherry.
- [Damon] I don't
think I could do it.
- [Tricky] You
don't have a choice.
You know James,
just get it done.
Bully for you, keep moving.
(woman screams)
- Let's go.
Are you fucking kidding me?
- Just go, we gotta get in.
(tense music)
- [Man] Okay.
All right.
Okay.
(man screams)
Okay, you got
this, you got this.
Oh shit.
Nope, nope, nope, nope.
Okay, I gotta get something.
(murmurs)
Okay, that'll work.
One thing.
This, okay.
(man screams)
- We gotta go.
We gotta get out of here.
- It's gonna be all
right, I promise.
Here, here, take this.
(suspenseful music)
(knocking)
- We're gonna die!
We're gonna die.
We're gonna die, we're
gonna die in here.
We're gonna die.
(knocking stops)
(door rattles)
(tense music)
It's not ours.
- [Man] Swear.
(man screams)
- What the hell are
we doing in here?
This is the bathroom.
- Just wanna duck
out for a second.
(tense music)
- What are you doing?
- Look.
- Oh my god, Charlie.
- You stabbed me.
(groans)
(foreboding music)
Weed.
(door closes)
(woman screams)
- Yeah, I wanna report a loud
house party on Tinkler Street.
Uh-huh, between Main and Ferry.
Huh?
Nah, I'd rather
remain anonymous.
(snores)
(tense music)
- Manners, get out!
Get the fuck down now!
- [Tricky] Jimmy, what the fuck?
- I got it.
- The cops are here...
- I said I got it.
- [Brad] What was that?
- [Maybe] Cops are here.
- Stay out of sight, stay quiet.
Everything will be fine.
Hi there.
- Hey, what's going on tonight?
- Just a house party, Officer.
- House party?
Seems pretty dead.
- Yeah.
Everybody's pretty much
cleared out at this point.
- [Tricky] Manners.
Manners!
Manners, get the fuck over here.
Look.
(officers chat)
- Well, we had a noise complaint
from some concerned
neighbors up the street.
- Really?
Well, we're all done tonight.
Bands took off and everything.
- And they left all
their equipment?
- It's a house kit.
Bands play here all the time.
- I see.
(train horn blares)
- Look, guys, I hate to do this,
but I think we're
gonna have to go inside
and take a look around,
just to be safe.
- What the fuck are they doing?
Why aren't they coming in?
- James could talk his
way out of anything,
but there's no way they
won't check out the house.
There's no way.
- Respectfully, I've gotta
ask you not to do that.
- Excuse me?
And why would you do that?
- Look, just between us.
There are still a couple of
underage kids inside hiding out.
- Ah, yeah, I see.
- You guys know how it
was when you were younger.
- [Female Officer]
Yeah, yeah, I get it.
- We honestly don't want
any problems, Officer.
- All right, guy, I
don't want to have
to come out here
again tonight, okay?
- No problem, sir.
- Why are they leaving?
- Calm down.
- What do you mean, calm down?
We have to stop them.
- We can't, there's
still more of them.
- [Female Officer] If
those kids all stay,
put them to bed, will you?
- [James] Yes ma'am, no problem.
- Can't let him
know where we are.
- No, we have to let them know.
- Stop, they'll kill us
before the cops get up here.
Stop.
- Stop!
- (screams) Help us, help us!
- Hey, stop!
- Oh god.
- Fuck.
- Damon.
Go get that bitch.
No.
No guns.
We'll just attract
more attention.
Where the fuck is Tricky?
- I don't know, I
think he took off.
- All right.
Get in there, let's
button this shit up.
(ominous music)
(gasps)
(suspenseful music)
(grunts)
- Oh god.
Oh god.
- I am so fucking
tired right now.
- Me too, but we gotta
stay on our toes, right?
- Right.
Jesus, man, are these
the type of people
you used to hang out with?
Cause I thought you said
they just beat people up.
- Yeah, well I guess
they changed the rules.
- [James] Oh, Bradley!
I'm home!
- I have to fight him.
- [James] Bradley!
- If you go down there,
they'll kill you.
- They're here killing all
these people because of me,
I can't just sit
up here and hide.
I always hide from him.
Everyone here's too drunk
to even defend themselves.
- Brad, you are drunk.
(tense music)
- Hey, what about the roof?
- Yeah, yeah,
that's a great idea.
We can go up and
hide on the roof.
- No, that's a terrible idea.
I mean we could climb
down from the porch roof.
- Right, right,
that makes sense.
I'm sorry, I'm still
sorta high right now.
- All right, come on.
(tense music)
Just go.
- Brad.
Oh, no, no!
(cries)
No, no!
(suspenseful music)
Fuck! (screams)
Get off me!
Stop!
(yelps)
(screams)
(grunts)
(hisses)
- We aren't finished yet.
- What was the point
of all this, James?
- You don't know?
I guess you never got it.
(grunts)
You know what the
point was, Brad?
The point, Bradley boy,
is that you're not fucking
better than me.
(Brad coughs)
- James, no.
(gun fires)
(acute ringing)
(groans)
- That was so loud!
See, I told you.
- Told me what?
- I told you you
couldn't take him.
- Shit.
(eerie music)
(gasps)
Shit!
- What the fuck?
- You what the fuck?
- You're the reason I
fell off that damn roof.
- I am not!
- To be fair, he
probably saved your life.
- Hey.
(uplifting music)
Kinda hard to argue
with that, I guess.
(groans)
Well, is somebody
gonna help me up?
(chuckles)
I am never drinking again.
- [Sean] Aw, come on.
That's what they all say.
Just give it a few hours.
- [Brad] We should probably
call somebody, right?
- [Sean] What?
Cause that worked out
so well the last time.
- [Brad] Look, I'm just saying
we call committed murders.
- [Maybe] Well, I mean,
technically self defense.
- [Sean] I was saving
somebody's life.
Think I was fine.
- [Brad] You shot James
in the head, Sean.
- [Sean] Well, yeah,
some people deserve it.
- [Maybe] Yeah, I was gonna say,
some people are just
asking to get shot.
- [Sean] Yeah, I know.
Have you ever met
a Swedish person?
They suck.
- Yeah, yeah,
but I was winning the fight,
so that was a defense.
- [Maybe] Oh yeah, were
you really winning,
or were you just being
naturally crafty?
- [Brad] Yeah, I walked
over and punched him
right in the face.
- Looks like your face
was turning.
- [Brad] That's when the
fight ended, basically.
(chatting)
(Boozehound" by Uglybones)
♪ Do you want the foot down
♪ I got pills to
make you shout ♪
♪ Blonde people with
bloodshot eyes ♪
♪ I got grease to make it live
♪ Boozehound honey
♪ Better not slow me down
♪ Are you a Boozehound, honey
♪ You shouldn't be around
♪ Fuck you
♪ Do you want a lover to fuck
♪ I got a date, you're in luck
♪ Hot and mean
♪ Hit your fucking spleen
♪ Boozehound honey
♪ Better not slow me down
♪ Are you a Boozehound, honey
♪ You shouldn't be around
♪ Boozehound honey
♪ Better not slow me down
♪ You shouldn't be around
♪ Boozehound honey
♪ Better not slow me down
♪ You shouldn't be around
♪ Boozehound honey
♪ Fuck you, fuck you, fuck you
(snores)
- Guys?
Is anyone still here?
("Vicious Fix" by The Fritz)
♪ Break this on my head
♪ I'm dead, too many minutes
♪ Fifty guys,
they've got friends ♪
♪ They're the realest,
everybody says ♪
♪ Got a bone to pick
♪ I need a vicious fix
♪ Vicious fix
♪ My mom is sick
♪ I need a vicious fix
♪ If you don't get my fix
♪ Flake out for them chicks
♪ Got plenty real rebels
♪ Prospects, see you in hell
♪ Got a bone to pick
♪ I need a vicious fix
♪ Vicious fix
♪ My mom is sick
♪ I need a vicious fix
♪ Vicious fix