- By the way, I hope you're free
the second week of October.
- Three months from now? Why?
- Well, I went ahead and
booked a hotel room.
Uh, a suite actually...
A very nice suite
for the National Advertiser's
Convention in Vegas.
- Well, let's see if I can fit
you into my social schedule.
Considering you're a major
part of my social schedule.
- It was George Sand
who once said,
"There is only one happiness in life: To love and be loved."
It should come as
no surprise that George
Sand was actually a woman.
I've known for a long
time that women feel love
much more deeply than men.
- Spending time with you
and everything, it's...
the best I've felt
since before Jack died.
- Yeah, both of us have had
a rough couple of years.
- It hasn't been easy.
- Yeah, it's weird
not hearing from Michelle.
Five years of marriage
and it's like...
We never even met.
And, you know, this
whole dating thing.
- Ah, depressing, really.
What little
I did of it, I hated.
- Well, you have to admit...
Occasionally, it pays off.
[Sobbing]
- I'll never forget the day
I lost the only man
I ever truly loved.
The day Kathryn Brown
took him away from me.
[Sobbing]
- I knew it.
I knew it!
- [Kathryn]: Why did you
let me have that piece
of cheesecake?
- [Brian]: Ha! Ha! So I
wouldn't feel guilty.
- [Kathryn]: Thank
you for dinner.
- Well, thank you for the
company.
I'll walk you to your car.
[Police siren]
- I learned long ago that
anything worth having
is worth fighting for.
I couldn't just sit back
and watch as Brian was
ripped away from me.
- Allison!
What the hell are
you doing here?
- You were cheating on me
the whole time, weren't you?
How is she?
- Who?
- The woman I saw
you with tonight.
I saw you with her.
- Wait, you followed us?
Allison, are you
out of your mind?
This has nothing to with
Kathryn, I didn't even meet her
until after we broke up.
[She laughs]
- I don't believe you.
I saw what she was doing!
I saw her coming on to you.
- What?
- Why can't you see?
Men just can't see.
- That's ridiculous...
- No, there are some
women who thrive
on stealing men away
from other women.
- That's ridiculous.
I didn't leave because Kathryn
stole me away from you.
I left because of this.
Because you're acting insane!
You broke into my house
for God's sake!
- You gave me a key.
- Which you gave back.
Which means you made a copy.
- I just want
to talk to you.
Because we can work
everything out.
Come on, Brian,
don't give up on us!
- Sometimes, people get to know
more about each other and
it doesn't work out.
I... I explained this to
you a couple of months ago.
- Remember when I told
you about my father?
You said you couldn't believe
that he would walk out
on me and my mom.
You said that you
would never do that!
You see, so I can't
let you do that to me.
- Allison...
You and I, we just...
can't be together.
- Now I know that
there are some things
that you don't like about me.
But I can change.
I can change that.
You see, I won't be...
jealous anymore. And
I won't be controlling.
- Allison. It's over between us.
You have to leave.
- No. No, no, no. I just want
to talk this through.
Come on, come on. Let me just...
We can work this out.
- There's nothing more
to talk about.
I'm asking you to leave.
- To, to leave? No no no no!
You don't understand! No!
NO! NO!
[Mug breaks]
You should be asking
me to marry you!
- That's it, I'm
calling the police.
- No no no! Give me the phone!
Give me the...
[Crying]
At first I felt betrayed
by Brian. Hurt.
Rejected. Hopeless.
I couldn't eat,
go to work, go out.
I couldn't do anything.
But the sadness
eventually went away.
And then I just felt angry.
Angry at him.
But mostly, angry at the woman
who had come between us.
Kathryn.
It was true, Brian and I had
been having some problems.
All relationships do.
But Kathryn used
the opportunity.
And that's what they do,
women like her.
Home wreckers. Mistresses. Whatever you wanna call them.
They go for men who belong
to someone else.
And they steal them.
It took me three months,
and then I knew.
Knew what I had to do.
And the key, was Brian's sister.
Jordan.
[Dialing]
[Cell phone ringing]
- Hello?
- Hello, Jordan?
- [Yes.]
- Hi, Mary Connor from the
Philadelphia Reporter.
I spoke to you a couple of weeks
ago about doing an interview.
[It's for the ecology
report I'm doing.]
- Right, on the
conversation project.
- Mhmm, you said you
thought you'd be back
in Tennessee this week.
Do you have an hour
or so to meet with me?
I could come to your house.
- Oh, no, actually,
I'm on my way to Charleston
for the clean air rally.
Charleston, really?
Maybe I could go.
Where are you staying?
- At a hostel near
the rally site.
I'm only gonna
be there overnight
but I'm sure that we can
find some time to meet.
- Oh wait, no, I'm looking
at my schedule,
and that's not going
to work for me.
Um, why don't I just
call you next week,
and we can figure
something out then.
- Sounds good, thanks Mary.
- Thanks.
[Knocking]
Hi, Becky, come on in.
- You must be so excited.
What made you decide
to go to L.A.?
- You know, I've been thinking
about it for a long time and,
I don't know. The timing
just finally seemed right,
- Well, lucky you.
After meeting with Jack's
attorney this morning,
it doesn't look like I'll be
able to go on a vacation
for a long time.
- Oh, right. I forgot.
So it didn't go well I take it.
- He wants to get out of paying
alimony and child support.
I guess he wants to spend all
his money on this new
girlfriend.
He's being such a jerk!
I've pretty much had
it with men now.
- It's like Brianand that Kathryn woman.
You should've seen all
the things she did to try to
seduce him. It was disgusting.
- Wait a sec, you saw them
together? I didn't know that.
- Um, yeah. Um, I ran into them
at a restaurant a while back.
That's how I knew
he was cheating on me.
Keys!
- Yeah, well, what goes around
comes around, right?
I'm a big believer in karma.
- Me too. Thanks for taking care
of the plants while I'm gone.
- I'll call you as soon
as I get back.
- Alright. Bye.
- Okay, bye.
[Laughing]: "Karma". Right.
That should be enough
to knock her out.
♪
[Struggling]
I didn't want to kill Jordan.
But it had to be done.
The plan was the most
important thing.
This whole thing
wasn't just for me.
I was doing it
for everyone woman
who'd had the man she loved
ripped away from her.
Including my own mother.
- Allison.
- Dad, where are you going?
- Uh... Honey, your mother
will explain it to you.
It has nothing to do with you..
Sometimes parents, they uh..
You'll understand when
you're a little older.
- Dad?
Dad!
Brian had a cabin
outside of town.
Taking Jordan's body there
wasn't easy for me.
He and I had some wonderful
weekends at that place.
But those times were over.
- Mom, I honestly don't
understand what the big deal is.
No one's gonna know if
I'm fifteen minutes late.
- The judge made it very clear.
Your curfew is eleven.
- But it's summer. Everyone
else gets to be out until
at least midnight.
I look like an idiot checking my
watch every fifteen minutes.
Come on.
Mike and I are just gonna hang
out and play guitar. That's it.
- You're on probation,
Scott, for one more year.
[Sighs]
- Brian. You get what
I'm saying, right?
Can you please explain
to her that the whole
world isn't gonna end
because of 15 stupid minutes!
- Well, I think if the judge
wanted your curfew to be 11:15
he would've said so.
But that's not really the point.
What you mom is saying is that
she wants you to do
the right thing because
it's the right thing to do.
- No! You know what? Mom?
I cannot wait until I turn 18 so
I can get the hell out of here!
- Aren't you glad
you didn't have twins?
I better get going.
Harvey's been sick all week
and his entire presentation
is resting on my shoulders.
- Oh, I'm sure they'll love your
campaign, it'll be brilliant.
- As long as it sells more
toothpaste, everyone
will be happy.
Love you.
- I love you.
- Maybe just one
more for the road.
What are you doing
for lunch tomorrow?
I think I could finish this
presentation around noon.
- I'm free.
- Good.
Pick you up at 12:30.
- Okay.
- See you.
- As usual.
[Loud music in earphones]
[Tires screeching]
- Ah!
Ah!
- As you two get even closer,
things might get harder for him.
- Scott seems to like Brian.
I mean, he hasn't come
out and said that, but,
he did ask him his opinion
about a girl last week.
- I'm not saying it has
anything to with Brian, but
when things get finalized
and Brian moves in,
Scott might be thinking more
and more about the fact
that he lost his dad.
- I'm not sure he'd
talk to me about that.
- Well, just be patient.
Scott will eventually figure
out that you're not enemy
number one.
[Laughing]
[Cell phone ringing]
- Hi, this is Brian Hagan,
not here to take your call.
Please leave a message.
[Beep]
- Hey hon, it's me, I'm just
wondering where you are.
Maybe your presentation ran
late. Um, give me a call
when you get this. See you soon.
[Ringing]
- [Brian Hagan's office.]
- Hi, Candice, it's Kathryn.
Is Brian there?
- [Uh, no. I was about to call
you to see if you knew
where he was.]
[He didn't show up for his
presentation this morning.]
- What?
- [And he didn't call. Nothing.]
- Umm. That's not like him.
Call me as soon as you
hear from him, okay?
- [I will. Bye.]
[Cell phone ringing]
- Thank God, sweetie,
where are you?
- [Man's voice]: May I speak
to Kathryn Brown, please?]
- I'm sorry, who is this?
- [Detecting Simmons. I'm
looking at Brian Hagan's
emergency contact list.]
- Emergency contact?
- [Are you Kathryn Brown?]
- Yes, that's me.
- [What is your relationship
to Mr. Hagan?]
- He's my fiancé.
What's going on?
- [There's been an accident.
I'm sorry. Mr. Hagan's dead.]
- Wha...
you don’t want me to stay longer?
I can.
- No, it's okay.
- I'm gonna call later,
and see how you're doing.
But if there's anything at
all that you need before then
my cell is on.
- Thanks, Joy.
- Kathryn.
Again, I'm... I'm so sorry.
- Thanks, Ian, I'm glad
you could make it.
- So, have you heard
from Jordan yet?
- No, I called and left her a
message on the cell phone number
that Brian had for her, but
she never called me back.
- She may not even be
in the country right now.
She's always coming and going.
Who knows if she even
got the message.
She'll be very upset
she missed the funeral.
Brian's the only
family she had left.
- When was the last
time you talked to her?
- I haven't seen her
in two or three years.
- I even called the woman who
owns the boarding house
where she stays,
and she hasn't seen
her in weeks.
- There's not much
more you can do.
She'll get the message
eventually.
So, how are you holding up?
- I'm still in
shock to be honest.
- Look, um, I'm going
back to New York tomorrow.
I'll back out here
in a couple of weeks.
I'd like to take you
out to lunch or something.
- Okay. Sure.
Thanks for being
such a good friend.
- Well, I loved
you very much.
- Um, Kathryn?
- Yes?
- I'm sorry to just
show up like this.
Um, I just couldn't
believe it when I heard.
- Are you Jordan?
- I can't believe he's gone!
- Oh, honey. Come on in.
- I was horrified when
I finally got your message.
And I realized I had
missed his funeral.
My cell phone was stolen. And
I didn't replace it till
I got back here.
I was down in Charleston
for a big rally.
- Brian told me you were
active in a lot of causes.
- I was always busy. You know?
I should've come
to see him more often.
When he told me that he was
being transferred to
Philadelphia,
I told him...
told him...
that I would visit.
And here he is, two years
later, and I never did.
- Honey, you could have never
known this was gonna happen.
- No.
No one could've
known I suppose.
Well, even though I missed
the funeral, I just...
I have to help take care
of his things, you know.
There was so much to do.
After our parents died.
And um, Brian
did most of it.
- Where are you staying?
Do you have friends here?
- No. No, I don't know
anybody in Philadelphia.
I was thinking about
staying at Brian's, but...
I don't know, seeing
all of his...
stuff around me. Might
be just too, um... hard.
- I understand.
[Sighs]
- You know, I think
I'll just get a room.
I saw some motels.
Out on the highway as
I was coming into town. So.
- Are you sure?
Jordan, you can
stay here with me.
Wow, thank you.
This is a beautiful home.
- Thank you.
- My husband and I bought it
twenty years ago and,
when he died, I um,
I didn't want to leave.
- Well, I can see why.
Thank you for the invitation.
- It's my pleasure.
After all, you know,
you're... practically family.
- [Sobbing]: Oh, thanks.
Brian told me you were
a really nice person.
- Extra blankets
are in the closet.
And the bathroom
is just down the hall.
- Oh, this is great, Kathryn.
Much nicer than where
I usually stay.
- I'm sure you're tired,
I'll let you get some rest.
And I'm gonna go run some
errands, and I'll make
some dinner later.
- Thank you. If there's
anything I can do to help...
- No, not at all.
Just so you know,
Scott should be home in about
an hour, in case he gets
here before I do.
- Alright. Well, I can't
wait to meet him.
- Okay.
- Kathryn bought my act,
hook, line and sinker.
She had no idea how much
I wanted to meet her son.
"Triple Kill."
Will Scott and I become
the best of friends?
"Most definitely."
- I did get the notice that you
completed your community
service.
That's good.
That's very good.
So.
How's work?
- Fine.
- You getting there on time?
You're not having any problems
with any of the other employees?
- No problems.
- Good. That's good.
Keep following the rules,
you'll be in good shape.
- Uh, sir?
Me and a couple
of my friends,
we're thinking of going to
Baltimore to see a band there.
- You know you can't
leave the county.
- Yeah, I know, but...
I was thinking, maybe...
- You know the rules, Scott.
Look if things
keep going smoothly,
for the next six months
or so, I'll consider it.
But not for now.
Look, you're on
the good path. Stay on it.
I'll see you in a
couple of weeks, okay?
And be on time.
- Honey, do you have
any concept of time?
- Scott: [Yes!]
- You said you would
be home by now.
- Yes, mom, I know I'm late. But
I'm two seconds away from my car
then I'm gonna get in, I'm going
to drive, and I will be home
in twenty minutes max.
Give me a break, will you?
I'm not seven years old.
- He sometimes has trouble
keeping on time.
- Did Brian ever tell you
anything about Scott?
- Nothing really.
- Well, he's been in
some trouble lately.
- Oh?
- Two years ago, not long
after his dad passed away,
he and another boy,
Jason, stole a car
and went on a spray painting
spree at Scott's school.
- Uh-oh.
- Yeah, so he's on probation,
and has to follow all the rules
or he may wind up back
in juvenile hall.
- Huh...
Rules. What kind of rules?
- Like he has to keep
his appointments,
obey his curfew, stay
fairly close to home.
- Wow, that must be
tough for a teenager.
He can't even leave the city?
- He can't even leave
the county. Which pretty
much is the city.
- What if he has to go on
a school trip or something?
- He can't go.
A few weeks ago,
his whole chemistry class went
to Pittsburgh and he had
to stay behind.
- Wow. That's awful.
- Uh, listen, because Scott's
running a little late,
I'm gonna go to the den
and do some paper work.
Um, do you mind
watching the sauce?
- No, no, that's fine.
I just hit a major
bump in my plan.
I had no idea Scott
was on a leash
held by the police.
It was going to be
harder than I thought to
get what I wanted from him.
But I'd come too far
to let this stop me.
- [Scott]: Hello?
- Hi. I'm Jordan.
Brian's sister.
- Scott.
- Glad you could make it.
- Your mother invited
me to stay here for a few
days. I hope you don't mind.
- No, that's cool.
I'm starving.
- Then let's get that pasta.
This one's of us in the Bahamas.
God we loved that trip.
- Wow, you really took
a lot of pictures.
- Yeah, and I organized
them all into this album
because Brian wasn't
one for keeping them.
I can't believe he didn't
have any pictures of you.
- Well, you know Brian. He
wasn't into taking pictures.
This is the three
of us at the beach.
Scott wanted to learn how to
surf, so Brian and I took him.
- [Brian]: A toast.
To you.
- Mm...
- I love champagne.
You're such a gentleman.
- Anything for
your birthday.
- I can't tell you how
much I appreciate this.
Since my grandmother died,
I haven't had any family
to celebrate with.
And nothing is lonelier than
being by yourself on
your birthday.
- Yes, well, this year
will be different.
- Everything's been different
since I met you, Brian.
I love you.
- Mm, look at this one.
- Wow. You look great.
I'm really glad
Brian found you.
Did he tell you about
any of his exes?
- A little bit
about his ex-wife,
and then that one crazy
woman he dated for a while.
Did you ever meet her?
- Uh, no. What
was her name?
- Uh, Ali, Alice, Allison,
something like that.
I don't know,
a complete psycho.
- No, he never said
anything like that to me.
- Well, he didn't really
like to talk about her.
I mean, he told me
a couple of stories.
Apparently she was very
jealous and obsessive.
She used to accuse him all
the time of cheating on her.
She would just show
up at restaurants
when he was trying to take
clients out to dinner.
- She did?
- He finally just
got so sick of her.
He told me
when he met me
he was so happy to meet
someone refreshingly normal.
Can you imagine?
Poor Brian.
I miss him so much.
- So do I.
[Guitar playing]
- Hey!
- Hey.
You're into music? Me too.
- Yeah? What kind
of music do you like?
- Oh, all sorts of stuff.
You know Top 40,
alternative, rock.
- What rock bands
do you like?
- Oh, well...
My favorites would have to be,
from classic rock, ACDC.
And, um, newer
bands, Triple kill.
- Triple kill? Man I love
those guys, I can't believe
you listen to them.
- Why wouldn't I? Don't
you dare say I'm too old.
- No no, that's not
what I meant.
You know, they're playing
in Baltimore next month.
- Really?
Maybe we could go
see them together.
- No, I can't go.
It's too far, you know.
Part of my probation.
- Well, that sucks. What
if your mom was okay with it?
- Mm-mm, I still couldn't go.
My probation officer's
like super strict.
He'd totally freak.
- Mm, well maybe they'll
play Philadelphia soon.
Hey, what's "Jitters Café"?
- Oh, it's just a coffee
shop where I work.
- Well, maybe I'll
come check it out.
- Yeah, you know,
anytime you want.
- Cool.
Well, I guess I'll let
you get back to playing.
- Yeah.
- Hey. Maybe we can see Triple
Kill, you know, some other time.
- Yeah.
- Think!
Okay.
There's gotta be a way.
Good morning. It smells
really wonderful.
- Would you like some?
- Sure.
- Oh, by the way, I meant
to tell you, Jordan,
if you need help with
Brian's things later,
I'd be more than
happy to help.
- Aw, thanks.
Thanks, but, I'll be okay.
I'm just gonna head over there
and start in on his stuff.
- Morning.
- Hey honey, would you like some
breakfast before you go to work?
- Mm, something quick.
- Hey, I thought I might stop
by the café later and grab
a cappuccino.
- Mm, yeah, that'd be cool.
And it's on me.
- Well then, if you're buying,
I'll definitely stop by.
I'll probably
need a, you know,
break later anyway.
- Okay, well, I gotta role.
- That's nice.
- Do you happen to
have a house key
that I could borrow just in case
I get back before you guys?
- Absolutely.
Top drawer on the left.
- Thanks.
- Hey.
- Hey, yeah, I'm almost
done here so...
- No rush, I'll just go inside
and decide what I want.
- Okay.
- Hi, can I help you?
- Um, yes. I'd like an iced
caramel coffee blended please.
- Sure.
- Her drinks on me okay, bro?
- Ah, you must be Jordan.
Scott told me about you.
- Did he say nice things?
- As a matter of fact, he did.
- Hey, love your tat,
that's cool.
- Yeah, thanks. I got
one on my back too.
- Hey, uh, I was thinking
of getting one too.
- Yeah? I almost got
one last year.
- Yeah, my mom she'd probably
flip out if I did though.
I'd never hear
the end of it.
- Dude, so just get one
where she can't see it.
- There's one in a magazine that
I saw that I really liked, but,
I don't know.
- You don't think your
mom would be okay with it? I
mean everybody's got them now.
- Trust me, that
doesn't matter.
- See, I was thinking of getting
one in memory of Brian.
Kinda like, he'd
always be with me.
- That's a really
good idea, Jordan.
- I thought maybe a little
sunburst on my back.
Think I should do it?
If it'll make you feel better,
then yeah, definitely.
- Will you go with me?
We could do it now?
- I would be happy to.
Um, yeah!
- Good. For Brian.
- Okay. I just gotta
get my bag and my jacket.
- [Tattoo artist]: Alright,
gorgeous, you're good to go.
- [Laughing]: Are you
sure you don't want one?
- Ah, man.
- I'll pay for it.
- Okay. What the hell!
Oh man!
Okay, um...
There's this design I saw in a
magazine that I really liked.
The Chinese
character for Truth.
So let's do it right here.
- Alright, sounds good.
Here we go.
- You know, it doesn't even
really hurt that much.
- No, nothing compared to
the horror stories you hear.
Or maybe it's 'cause you're
such a big, strong man.
- So, uh, you hungry at all?
- Yeah, yeah,
I'm starving.
Guess there's
nothing like scarring your
body to build up an appetite.
- Uh, how about a burger?
- Perfect, that'll
hit the spot.
[Cell phone ringing]
- Just one sec.
- Hello?
- [Scott.]
- Yeah, hi mom.
- [Anything wrong?]
- No no, everything's fine.
Listen, you don't have to make
dinner for me, or Jordan.
- Are you sure?
I defrosted your favorite steaks
from the place you like.
- [No thanks.]
- Yeah, we're gonna grab
something here before
coming back.
- [Alright.]
- Okay, listen, I gotta go.
I'll talk to you later
- [Take care.]
- Okay, bye.
[Laughter]
- Hi, honey, how was your day?
- Uh, good. I'm gonna go
lie down, watch a movie
or something.
- Are you feeling okay?
- Yeah. Okay,
good night.
[Phone ringing]
- Uh, would you mind?
- Sure.
- Hello?
- [Is this Kathryn?]
- Oh, no, no it isn't.
Hang on a second.
- Hello?
- Kathryn, it's Ian.
- Hi, Ian.
Jordan, it's Ian.
- Ian, Ian Mathews?
- Oh! Yeah, I didn't
recognize his voice.
- Ian, guess what?
Jordan's here.
- [Wow, really?]
- Yeah, she's staying
with me for a few days.
- I'll put her on
when we're done.
- [How you doing?]
- Oh me? You know,
I'm holding up pretty
well, all things considered.
- Scott's about the same,
17-year-old boy, you
know how that is.
- [Good.]
- No, but Jordan,
she's been great.
- [Give her my best.]
- Sure, I know she would
love to see you.
Do you want to talk
to her right now?
- [Sure, put her on.]
- You know what? I am gonna call
him later, my stomach is...
Um, I'll be back.
- Um, she can't talk
right now, I guess.
- Damn you Ian. Brian is dead!
Leave us alone!
- So how's Scott doing?
- Well he and Jordan
are getting along.
They've become instant friends.
- Really?
- They even had dinner
together last night.
- Well, that's better than him
hanging out with that one guy
I suppose. What was his name?
- Jason.
- Right, Jason.
- I can't complain.
It's given me some
time to myself
that I didn't even
know I needed really.
- So, when are you coming
back to work fulltime?
I don't want to rush you, but
I do miss seeing you everyday.
- I was thinking
probably Monday.
I think it'll be good
for you to get back.
- It'll help get
my mind off things.
- You know, it does
get better, Kathryn.
I know that sounds
trite at the moment,
but it will get better.
- Blood?
You got a tattoo? Scott,
what were you thinking?
- Mom, honestly, this is
not something to have
a heart attack over.
- It's something you're
gonna regret later.
- That's not true.
- It's not just that. Why didn't
you discuss it with me first?
- Yeah, that
would've been a good idea.
- And second, you lied!
You told me you were going
to dinner instead of what
you were really doing.
- That's not how it happened,
Kathryn, we did go to dinner.
- Well, neither of
you told me about the
tattoo when you got home!
- Well, yeah, that's 'cause
I knew you were gonna
flip out like this!
- Oh, you want me to condone
you getting a tattoo, Scott?
- Mom, Jordan got one too!
You know, the only person
that's acting all psycho
about this is you!
- You got one together?
- Honestly, Kathryn, I don't
know what the big deal is.
I mean they're everywhere.
- He's 17, Jordan!
- I'm sorry. I had not idea
this would start a big fight.
- No. Everything is a fight!
- Scott.
- I'm going to Mike's.
- Scott?
- Forget it!
- I'm sorry, Kathryn.
- I would've appreciated
it if you had discussed
this with me beforehand.
And when I am in a discussion
with my son, keep your
opinions to yourself!
- Of course.
Hey! You're back. Come here.
- I just wanted to apologize for
getting you in trouble before.
- No, that's okay, uh,
don't worry about it.
I knew how she was gonna
react. I shouldn't have
gotten a tattoo.
- Well, since you
guys are both so great,
I hate to see you
upset with each other.
- Well, trust me, the
fighting started a long
time before you showed up.
- Well, still.
If you ever wanna get
anything off your chest,
you know where to find me.
- Thanks.
- I mean that.
I like you a lot.
- I like you too.
- Good night.
- 'Night.
- Scott and I were
growing ever closer now.
And I was just waiting for the
perfect opportunity to arise.
To finally get what I wanted.
- It isn't just her
- Bro, bro. Man, check this out.
Chemically Insane's gonna be at
the Black Fox recording studio
tomorrow night at 9.
- And?
- They're recording a new album.
Oh, and did I mention
who their new drummer is?
Jason.
- What?!
- Yeah. I bumped into
him this morning,
he said we could go hang out
at the studio tomorrow night
with all those guys.
- I don't know if I can go.
Me and Jason aren't supposed to
hang out with each other ever
since we go arrested.
- Oh man, come on!
When are we ever gonna get
another chance like this?
- Man, I don't know. My mom's
probably gonna freak out.
And she's already pissed off
about the whole tattoo thing.
- So we leave by 10:45,
you're home by 11. No problem.
- Hmm! Alright, I'll
work something out.
- Clean that up.
- Get out of here.
- So, how is everything
going at Brian's house?
- Well, you know, it's hard.
But I'm working on it.
[Doorbell]
- Ah, that must be Ian.
- Ian?
- Oh, I forgot to tell you.
He called me earlier
to say he was dropping by.
- Damn it!
- [Ian]: Is Jordan around?
I haven't seen her in ages.
- Yeah, she's here
in the kitchen.
Uh, she was in the kitchen.
Jordan?
I don't know where she went.
- Okay, okay, wait. Who said
anything about backing down?
- Mike: [You did, bro.]
- No, I never said
I wasn't gonna go.
- [So what are you
gonna tell your mom?]
- I don't know, I'll tell her
we're going to a movie
or something.
- [Can you hang
with us all night?]
- No, I still have
to be home by curfew.
- [Sure, whatever.]
- No, I need to hear
you say it, Mike.
- [Say what, dude?]
- That I need to be home by 11.
- [Okay, 11 o'clock.]
- Okay.
Um, so I'll look at, you know,
see a movie that
ends around 11.
And I guess
I'll pick you up...
I'll pick you up later.
Okay, I gotta go. Yeah.
- [Catch you later.]
- Alright, later man, bye.
- Hey there.
- Hey!
What movie you guys
going to tonight?
Maybe I can tag along.
- Okay, um,
here's the thing.
You gotta promise not
to say anything to my mom.
- Of course not.
- We're not really
going to a movie.
There's this band
that Mike and I like,
and our friend Jason invited us
to hang out with them tomorrow
night, so.
Jason is the guy that
I got into trouble with.
So I'm not really
supposed to go.
- Don't worry.
I won't say a word.
- Thanks, Jordan.
Uh, maybe you and
I could see a movie...
some other time.
- Sounds good.
That's the good thing
about secret plans.
Sometimes you have
to rely on other people
to keep them a secret.
- Jordan. What happened
to you last night?
- What do you mean?
- Well, Ian was here and
he wanted to say "hi".
And we couldn't find
you anywhere.
- Oh, umm...
Well, to tell you the truth,
I just couldn't face him.
You know, whenever
I see somebody that
knew Brian really well,
it just makes
me want to cry.
It's so draining.
- 'Morning.
- Hi, honey.
- Mom. Jordan.
- Today's your day off, right?
- Yeah.
- Any big plans?
- I'm gonna go see a movie
with Mike probably,
but other than that, no.
- What about you, Jordan?
- I'm gonna go up to Brian's
and finish up, you know.
- Well, I have late meetings.
So, I'll be home around nine.
Enjoy your movie, honey.
- Yeah, okay.
- Bye.
Hey, Scott, would you be
available any time this weekend
to come up to Brian's cabin
and help me finish packing
up his stuff?
I decided I'm gonna sell it.
- Um, no, sorry,
Jordan, I can't.
My probation officer, he won't
let me leave the county.
- Oh, I'm sorry. No,
I completely forgot.
- Do you want me to ask Mike?
If, you know, he could
come and help you out.
- No, no, that's okay.
I'll find somebody.
So have fun tonight.
It'll stay our
little secret.
[Laughter and talking]
- You guys sound as good
live as you do on disk.
- And I told you so! And could
you believe that guitar solo?
- Ah, tight!
- You wanna pass me a beer, bro?
- Sure. Scott?
- Just a pop for me, man.
- Hey, what's the deal
with your P.O?
I heard he's a
real hard ass.
- Yeah, you know.
- I got so lucky!
The chick I have, she doesn't
care what I do, as long I
don't get arrested again.
- That's... That's... Dude!
I don't know how you do it!
- Ah, well, you know!
- Yeah, it's a nice one. You did
a good job filling it in.
Hey man, we're ready
to rehearse again.
- Oh, hey listen, I gotta
get going. But thanks
for having us, man.
- Anytime, bro.
[Guitar playing]
- Hey, you're ready to go?
- I actually might hang
around a little bit longer.
Jason will drive me home.
- Alright, cool.
Later, bro.
- Bro.
[Engine not starting]
- Damn it.
[Dialing cell phone]
[Cell phone ringing]
- Hey, Scott.
- [Hey, Jordan, where are you?]
- Just driving back
from Brian's, why?
- [Uh. I'm in a bit of trouble.
I could use your help.]
[My car won't start. I think
maybe my battery's dead
or something.]
- Don't worry about a thing.
I'll be there to pick you up.
Just give me the address.
- 2213 Baker Street.
In the parking lot
behind the building.
- Ten minutes.
- Okay. Thanks, Jordan,
I owe you one.
- Yes, you do.
- Police radio: [Unit 52.
We have a report of suspicious
activity in a parking lot]
[at Baker and High Tower.
White teenage male.]
[Possible auto theft.]
- This is Unit 52.
I'll check it out.
[Phone ringing]
- Hello.
- Hey, mom?
- Scott, where are you?
- [Uh, I'm at Mike's.]
Um, listen, his neighbor,
somebody, blocked my car
in the driveway, so...
We're trying to find them, but
it could take a little while.
- Okay. Do you want me
to come pick you up?
[We can get your car
in the morning?]
- No, that's okay.
- I think Mike's brother is
gonna give me a ride home,
So I'm just calling
to let you know that it
might take a little bit longer.
- Okay, well just get
home soon, okay?
- Okay, I will. Bye.
[Police siren]
- Megaphone: [Step back
from the car please.]
- Whose car is this?
- Uh, it's mine. I'm just having
trouble getting it started.
- Can I see your license
and registration, please?
- One sec, my registration's
in the car.
- Okay, have a seat in the car.
- Damn it.
Well this certainly
wasn't part of the plan.
But I can see it making
things turn out even better.
- Come over here, please.
- Scott, what's going on?
- Who are you?
- Uh, Jordan. A friend.
He called for a ride
when his car broke down.
- Listen, Officer, he hasn't
done anything wrong.
- Relax, lady. We got a call
that someone was breaking
into a car here.
- This is his car!
- You're on probation. For
vandalism and stealing a car.
- But Officer, he hasn't
done anything wrong.
- He's in violation
of his curfew.
- I have extended
curfew because I work.
- Look, we'll go
to the station, we'll
take care of it from there.
- Jordan!
- I'm taking him
to the Hoover station.
Tell his parents to meet
him there. Let's go.
[Sighs]
[Phone ringing]
- Hello.
- Kathryn, hi.
It's Jordan.
Listen, I don't know how
to tell you this, but...
Scott's on his way downtown.
He's been arrested.
- What?!
- Um, yeah. It's
just a misunderstanding.]
His car broke down. And I was
on my way to pick up him up,
and someone must have thought
that he was trying to
steal the car
[and called the cops,
I don't really know.]
- I don't understand.
I just talked to Scott.
He's at Mike's house.
- Uh, yeah. Well,
he's not with Mike.
He was in a parking lot
on Baker Street.
And, look, I was just
coming to get him, and, and..
[the cops were already
here when I arrived.]
- Oh, my God. Where did
they take him?
- Hoover Street station.
Do you want me
to meet you there?
- No, I'll handle this myself.
Can I speak with you?
Jordan, this situation
isn't working out anymore.
- What do you mean?
- I made it very clear to
you that I didn't want you
interfering with my son.
And what's the first
thing you do?
You pick him up from somewhere
he isn't even supposed to be.
So I don't catch him in a lie.
- Kathryn...
I was just trying to help.
I mean, I didn't think that...
- Mom, don't talk
to her that way.
- Go upstairs to your room.
- Mom, the only reason
Jordan got involved
was because I called her.
- That's not the point.
This thing you two
have between you.
Whatever it is.
It needs to stop.
[Breathing hard]
- Jordan, I want
you out by tomorrow.
- What? Mom, what "thing"?
- What are you talking about?
- Oh, you know exactly
what I'm talking about.
- No, Mom! You know what it is?
You're just jealous.
You're kicking her out
because you're jealous.
You're jealous that she's cool,
and fun, and easy to talk
to and you're not!
- Scott, go to your room!
- You just hate the idea
of me having any friends.
- Kathryn, please.
Can't we talk about this?
- You can find a hotel.
[Gasps]
- Mom...
I hate you.
[Crying]
- No, hey, come on.
Jordan, please don't cry.
Look, I'm really sorry
about all of this.
- I just don't know
what I did wrong!
- No, you didn't
do anything wrong.
It's just, this
is just not fair.
- I'm not gonna stay here if
she doesn't want me to stay.
Look, Kathryn, I will go, okay?
Tomorrow, I will pack my things
and I will go stay in
Brian's cabin.
- Thank you, Jordan
Scott.
- Leave me alone.
- Did you remember
you have an appointment
with Officer Kingman today?
- Yes.
- How are you gonna get there?
Your car's still downtown.
- I'll take the bus.
- Scott!
Hey.
- Did I, um, did
I just overhear your mom
saying you had an appointment
with your probation officer?
- Yeah, he's gonna
be thrilled to death
about what happened
last night.
- Seriously, Scott, you did
nothing wrong last night.
You know, why don't you
let me go with you,
and I can try to help
explain it to him.
I can give you a ride, and
then afterwards, you
can go get your car.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah. I mean, what happened
to you last night was
totally unfair.
I was there, I saw it.
- Okay. Yeah. Um...
My appointment's in an hour.
- Okay.
Let's hop in the car.
- I appreciate what
you're saying, Miss Hagan
but this isn't about curfew.
The problem with the car, being
late, I understand all that.
What you don't seem to
understand is that the judge
made it perfectly clear
that he was to have
no contact with Jason.
- I know you're
just trying to help.
But there's more
to it than that.
Thank you for coming in.
But I need to speak
to Scott. Alone.
- Okay.
- I really don't think
you take this seriously.
- Yes, I am. Okay, look.
This wasn't about
going to see Jason.
I just wanted to meet the guys
in the band, that's all!
- You listen, Scott. One more
screw up like this and...
And I make it official.
- What? Come on.
- Straighten up, Scott!
- I'm really sorry, Scott.
- Don't worry. I mean,
you tried to help.
That was very cool of you.
- You would've done
the same thing for me.
- Of course.
- Sure I can't take
you to your car?
- Nah, it's just
around the corner.
- Keep in touch, okay?
- Yeah.
Hey, Jordan.
Thank you.
[Struggling]
[Cell phone ringing]
- Hello?
- Scott.
I am so glad to get you.
It's Jordan.
- Jordan. Hey, what's wrong?
- Um, I'm really sorry
to call you at work. Um...
[I need your help. And
I didn't know who else to call.]
- Okay, tell me, what happened?
- Well, I stopped at the store
to get some boxes to pack
up Brian's stuff.
And I think somebody stole
my wallet, or I lost it.
I don't know. But I don't have
any money or credit cards,
[or anything!]
- Okay, just calm down.
[Calm down. Where are you?]
- I'm at the cabin. And...
[The SUV is almost out of gas,
and I don't know what to do.]
- Can you call the auto club?
- No. You have to be a member.
And have a card, and...
My wallet, Scott.
[My wallet is gone.]
- Okay. Just let me
think for a second.
- [Scott, can you
come and get me?]
[I mean, you're
the only one I know.]
- Jordan. I can't. I mean...
I'm at work. And I'm not
supposed to go that far out.
[Scott, please? I need help.]
- Okay. I'll see if I can
switch shifts with someone.
And then I'll come get you.
- Thank you, Scott.
I knew I could count on you.
- Listen, just sit tight, and
I'll be there in an hour or so.
- [Okay. Thanks.]
- Hey Mike?
- [Yeah.]
- Hey, what's up, man?
It's Scott.
- [Hey, dude.]
- Listen. I need you
to do me a big favor.
- [Thanks, Kathryn.
We'll continue to work
on it from our end]
[and submit the budget
to you next week.]
- Great, thank you.
- [Talk soon. Bye.]
- Scott...
- The mobile unit you
are trying to reach is
out of this service area.
Please try your
call again later.
- "Out of this service area"?
[Ringing]
- Jitters Coffee Café,
this is Mike.
- Hi, Mike, this
is Scott's mother.
May I speak with him please?
- Uh, he's...
Uh, he left early.
- Early why?
- [I don't know.]
He just called me and
asked me to switch shifts.
- And he didn't
give you a reason?
- Just that he was helping
someone move, but...
- Who? Jordan?
- Uh... He didn't say exactly.
- Gas is working.
Alright then.
[Phone ringing]
- Hello?
- Hello Jordan, this is Kathryn.
I'm just calling because
I really need to get
a hold of Scott.
- Oh, well I'm sorry, Kathryn,
But there's no reason
he'd be here.
- No. I was just wondering if
you knew where he could be.
- No, I don't. Not at all.
- Oh, well thank you.
If you do happen to hear from
him, will you please have
him call me?
- I sure will, Kathryn. Bye.
- [Bye.]
[Knocking]
- Kathryn. Is something wrong?
- I don't know. I can't
find Scott anywhere.
I called the coffee shop and
they said he left to help
somebody move,
which made me think of
Jordan, about the cabin.
But she says she hasn't
heard from him.
- Well, he's not on his cell?
- The message says
it's out of range, which again
made me think of the cabin.
- And you sound like you
don't believe Jordan.
Well, she does know that
he can't leave the city
because of his probation.
- She knows. But she also knew
about his curfew too, and...
In fact, every time Scott's
been in trouble lately,
she seems to be right there.
- You'd think having her move
out of your home would
be enough.
- Well, she wasn't necessarily
overjoyed about that.
You know what? I'm just gonna
go up there and see for myself.
- That's a long way
to drive on a hunch.
And we've been waiting for that
meeting today for six months.
- Tell Dean Smith I had
a family emergency.
But the absolute minute
you find out his decision
on the new budget proposals,
please call me. Promise?
- Sure. But you said cell
phones don't work up there.
- Right. Here is the
landline to the cabin.
Call me here.
Okay.
Thank you.
- Hello? Jordan?
- Scott! Hi!
Oh, my God, I'm so
glad to see you.
- Don't worry about it.
Everything's gonna be okay.
- Oh, I'm sorry, I hope I didn't
get you in any trouble.
I just didn't know who
else to call.
- No, listen.
Nobody's gonna find out. And
besides, it's the least
I could do for you.
after everything
you've done for me.
So, umm...
You wanna follow me to
the gas station in the SUV?
I got some cash and
we can fill it up.
- That's great. That's amazing.
You know what? Could you just
help me a bit? I gotta get
all of this stuff
packed up and that picture
is way too big.
I need help with that.
So, what do you think?
- Well, I don't have
to be back for a little while.
Couple of hours, so.
- Great. Great.
Well I'm exhausted,
I'm gonna fall over.
So I'm gonna get us some
coffee. If you could get
started on the knick knacks,
that would be great. What
do you take in your coffee?
- Two sugars.
- Okay.
Here you go.
- Oh, thanks.
So, what are you gonna
do with all this stuff?
- Oh, I'm gonna
donate most of it.
Just keep a couple of things
that remind me of Brian.
Scott, can you hold this for me?
- Yeah.
- Scott?
Scott? You okay?
- What? Yeah, I don't
know. I just...
I'm just like really really
tired all of a sudden.
It just hit me.
- Scott!
[Scott groaning]
Scott are you okay?
- Yeah...
No, I...
I don't think so...
I don't know.
- Don't fight it. Just
let yourself fall asleep.
Just relax. It'll all
be over soon.
- What?
- Don't worry. You'll be asleep.
You won't feel a thing.
I'm sorry.
You're really
an innocent victim.
Victim of people
like your mother.
Who don't care if they ruin
other people's lives.
See, Scott, Brian
and I were in love.
We were soul mates.
We were gonna be married till
your mother took him from me.
Now that old gas line
in there is gonna leak.
They'll be an explosion
and a fire.
The final part of my plan.
To right the wrong
your mother did to me.
Like I said, don't worry.
You'll be asleep.
You won't feel a thing.
First, I have to move
your body into the den.
So your remains are
found next to Jordan's.
- [Whispering]: Jordan...?
- That's right.
The DNA will show that
you really died next
to the real Jordan.
Which won't come
as any surprise.
Since you had a crush
on her. Or me.
Didn't you?
Don't worry.
You'll be gone in a few minutes.
- [Kathryn]: Scott? Jordan?
Scott? Jordan, what's
wrong with him?
- I don't know!
I don't know! He's sick.
I went to the bathroom to look
for something to give him but...
- Scott, honey. Scott.
What's wrong?
- Mom...
- He said he wasn't feeling
well. And then he just
fell into this chair.
[Scott mumbling]
- I don't know
what's happening here.
I'm gonna call 911.
- Sorry, Kathryn.
I'm afraid I can't
let you do that.
What the hell are you doing?
- Well, this wasn't really
part of the plan, but now
that you're here,
I guess you'll just have
to suffer the same fate
as your son.
- Jordan, what are
you talking about?
- Well, for starters...
It's not Jordan. It's Allison.
Allison? The same Allison
you stole Brian from?
The same one you called
"the crazy woman" that
he dated before you.
- Oh, my God. What did
you do to my son?
- He's just sleeping.
You have no idea the time and
effort that I have put
into all of this.
- All of what?
- Well, getting close
to you and Scott.
Of course Jordan was the key.
- The key to what?
- I knew that if you lost Scott,
you would feel the same
pain that I felt
when you took Brian from me.
- That is not true.
Allison, look. I know
that you're mad at me.
That's fine. But, please, Scott
has nothing to do with this!
Please let me help him!
- No, you were supposed
to live without Scott.
The same way you made me
live without Brian.
But now I guess you just
don't get to live at all.
Scott's body was supposed to be
found here next to Jordan's.
And now, there's just gonna
have to be three bodies.
Instead of two.
[Phone ringing]
[Gunshot]
[Struggling]
- Ah!
I love you.
I knew it.
Dad, where are you going?
- Allison.
- Dad!
- Allison?
Ah!
[Dialing]
- [911, what's your emergency?]
- Yes, hello! I'm calling from
a cabin on Avarench Road.
There's been a shooting and
we need help right away.
- Hey!
- Hi, honey.
- So you said you'd
be here at one.
- And it's quarter after.
- You're late. Maybe I inherited
my "Always Late" gene from you.
- Careful, buddy. You'll
understand why I'm late
when you know who
I've just seen.
Your probation officer.
- Bad news?
- Well, that all depends,
on whether or not you like
the band Triple Kill.
- Mom, I don't get you.
- He said you can go to their
concert next week in Baltimore.
- What?! Are you kidding?
Man, that's awesome!
- He'll allow it this one time.
There's not that much time left
in your probation anyway.
- Oh, Mom! Thanks for
making this happen.
- There is one condition though.
- Oh no. I knew it.
- You gotta treat
your mom to lunch.
- I think I can
handle that.
This guy came in this morning,
with fifty cents...
♪