(soft electronic music)
(uptempo dance music)
- I wish Solange was here.
I hate flying.
She always makes me one of
her special drinks when I fly.
It's like teleportation.
You knock one back, and
the next thing you know
you're in Paraguay or Guam or Utah.
- Utah?
- Mm-hmm.
- What were the two of you doing in Utah?
- I can't tell you.
(laughing)
- You never tell me the beginning
or the ending of a story.
It is always a headlong plunge into drama.
When do I get to meet Solange?
Maybe she can tell me
some of your secrets.
- Over my dead body.
- [Kevin's Friend
Voiceover] The best thing
about Kevin's funeral was Solange.
I recognized her immediately
from her low budget Italian horror films.
All the ones Kevin and I loved.
"The Rabid Ghouls",
"War for Water",
"Rat Attack!"
We watched them so many times
I could do whole monologues of them.
♪ Deep in my soul ♪
♪ I know ♪
♪ That we were never meant to go ♪
♪ Walking alone ♪
♪ So be mine ♪
♪ In the sunshine ♪
♪ Hold me so tight ♪
♪ In the night ♪
♪ I see our lantern shining bright ♪
- Do you want me to drive?
- No, I'm gonna drive.
- [Kevin's Friend] I don't know,
it seems a little weird,
you driving at your son's funeral.
- No, I practically gave birth
to him in a car I can drive.
And, you don't have
your license yet do you?
- No, but I can drive a couple miles.
- No no no, it's my car, I'm driving.
Get in.
- Okay.
(slow jazz music)
(group laughing)
- I need a drink.
To Kevin.
- [Kevin's Friend Voiceover]
Kevin never got tested for HIV.
When he was diagnosed with
lymphoma, being who he was,
it wasn't surprising that he
ended things the way he did.
(slow jazz music)
- Oh, hi,
I was just going through his stuff.
I know it's rude but I
just wanted something
to remember him by.
- I understand.
I feel the same way.
It's so strange we never met before.
- Not really,
he liked to keep his
friends in different boxes.
You weren't in my box sweetheart.
- Which box was I in, the
boring childhood friend's box?
- The safety deposit box?
- I guess.
We were friends since we were 15.
- I know.
How did it happen?
What do you know?
- Well, from what they could tell he
went to the beach, walked
out as far as he could
onto the sandbar and pulled the trigger.
They have no idea how he got a gun.
They didn't find it.
It must have gotten washed
out to sea with the tide.
- [Solange] Wow.
- So how did you guys meet?
- Hmm, how did we meet?
Well, I was in Rome
filming "Decapitator 2",
and Kevin was screwing the producer,
this so-called Italian Mafioso.
He would parade Kevin around
and dare people to give him shit about it.
Kevin loved the attention and the drama.
He stayed with me a
while when producer guy
ran off with the money, bastard.
- Kevin always had a thing
for Italian criminals.
- Don't we all?
I really miss him.
- [John] Me too.
- Hey, don't forget me, huh?
- Are you serious?
How could I?
Come on, hey hey hey.
Geez, don't start talking like that.
(birds calling)
(crickets chirping)
- Don't you want to just
kill those fucking crickets?
(laughing)
So promise me you'll get tested,
quit smoking, and get
your drivers license.
- [John] I promise.
- Thank you.
- [John Voiceover] Solange
and I spent the weekend
with Kevin's mom.
It just seemed natural.
Solange seemed to need to
make a connection with me.
She was sympathetic, warm.
I needed that.
Darla slept most of the weekend.
She seemed to become younger and younger
like she had absorbed
some of Kevin's energy before he left.
I had always liked how she
treated us like real people.
On our last day on the cape,
Solange said she wanted to
talk to me about something.
- Hey John, would you like to work for me?
Be like a production assistant
slash personal assistant.
I'm gonna do this
food-lifestyle-magazine show in Europe,
and I need some help.
Kevin was gonna do it but then.
- [Kevin] Promise me one more thing.
- I'm not giving up sex.
(laughing)
- No, not that, no.
Go travel though.
Get out of this fucking country.
Go see the world.
- Fuck it, count me in.
- [Solange] Great!
- [John Voiceover] I had a
stupid boring cubical job.
I had already lost my best friend.
I'd been single for a million years.
I had nothing else to lose.
Hi, this is John.
I won't be coming in to work tomorrow
or ever again for that
matter, thanks, bye.
- [John Voiceover] She was
vague about the details
of her food-magazine-lifestyle show.
When I tried to ask her questions about it
she would go off on some tangent
about how she did a show just like this
in Northern Ireland or Morocco,
as if that would reassure me somehow.
All I could get out of her
was that she wanted to call
it the un-tourist guide.
Welcome to Paris and your new life.
See you later, love Solange.
(smooth jazz music)
(laughing)
♪ Time to get up ♪
♪ And take a bow ♪
♪ Time to wake up ♪
♪ Don't you go now hound ♪
♪ Stop the dreaming ♪
♪ As the time is now ♪
♪ With heavy hearts it's hard to see ♪
♪ Why Monday won't leave gravity ♪
♪ Keep the weight off ♪
(lyrics muffled)
- Oh you made it.
Are you excited?
Sorry I didn't fly with
you, I have this phobia.
I couldn't get tickets on
the same flight anyway.
- Phobia?
About flying?
- No silly, flying together.
It's a quirk.
- Okay.
- Scoot over, so aren't you excited?
- Yes, yes I am.
- Great, welcome to my world.
Time to make a little change,
make a little change,
make a little change.
Look I got a camera.
The guy at the camera
shop said it's the best.
- Okay.
- I want it shot all guerrilla style.
What do you think?
- Um, it's good, it'll work.
- Good good, look I know
I should have waited
and let you pick it out
but I was way too excited.
And you know what, we should
film something tonight.
- Tonight?
- Yeah, just a little
something something, no biggie.
So you think you can figure
it out, get it to work?
- Yeah, no problem.
- Wow, you are good.
Hey love can you go get some ice?
I need to shower and get changed.
- Sure.
- Thanks.
(light instrumental music)
- I couldn't find any ice.
- John, this is Alain.
- Bon soir.
- Hello.
- [Solange] He's a big
fan of my one-hit wonder
from back in the 80's.
- Robots are un-American.
- I love it.
It was a big hit in
Europe, but not in America.
- Look.
- Oh my God, where did
you get this picture?
- Oh I always travel with
my press stuff just in case.
When you are as obscure as I am,
your fans tend to be die-hard.
- Ro-ro-robots.
Ro-ro-robots.
- Sweetie, that's the dance mix vocals.
Apparently, they are playing
it in all the hit clubs here.
"I'm a revival, revival, my survival."
That was my follow up, not quite a hit.
Alain do you know that one?
- No.
- That was the day.
Too bad I never saw a dime for it.
In those days you were
paid in cocaine, literally.
John, did you ever see that video?
- No.
- Oh it was hot.
Know what, I gotta find
that eyeshadow again.
- You want some more coffee?
- Sure.
- I found it!
Alain invited us to a party.
Tell him about it sweetie,
momma needs to concentrate.
- It's this group of art
terrorists, terror artists.
They are called Panic Culture.
- Okay.
- No what could be more
un-tourist than that?
Hey, you think you can get
that camera to working?
We need to start filming.
- Sure.
♪ We must defeat them ♪
♪ With our truest love ♪
♪ We must stop them ♪
♪ Show them what we're made of ♪
♪ They will never win ♪
♪ Robots are un-American. ♪
Come on lets go party!
Hey, make sure you get a
good shot of us entering.
- [John] Okay, hold still.
Okay.
- How's that camera working?
- It's good, don't talk
though, I'm filming.
- [Solange] Oh yeah right.
Do I look okay?
- [John] Yeah, you look good.
- We go? Action?
- [John] Yes, action.
(in foreign language)
(pulsing dance music)
- Get him!
Capitalist bitch, shit eater.
That is the robot woman, get her!
- See, they recognize me, keep filming.
(mumbling)
- You eat shit?
Look at that shit-eating grin.
Shit eater.
- Did you get any good shots?
Did you get my reaction?
- [John] I did.
- Would you like a drink?
- Yes, please.
- [Woman] You can drink my piss.
Drink my pee, scum.
- Beer.
- [Woman] Hey, have
you heard of this thing
called disco dumping?
- [John] No.
- I thought it was a New York City thing.
- They used to do that
back in the eighties.
It's when someone blows coke up your ass.
You have to be empty though
if you know what I mean.
- Alain said you were from New York City.
- Yeah, I mean no, I'm
from Boston, it's close.
- And do you say New York City or NYC?
I think NYC sounds cooler.
Put him with the others.
(pulsing dance music)
- Thanks.
Great party.
- Yeah, I told you there were cool, no.
- Yeah.
- Sorry.
- I could use a drink,
do you have a free hand?
- Oui.
- Thanks.
- Cindy is a bit messy tonight.
Her performance, not so good.
- A little more?
- That good?
- Hey.
- Are you all right?
- No.
Just pull right up top now.
Go to the top.
- Ready?
- Yeah.
- You all right?
- That's good.
- Are they gonna come back?
- I hope so, but then again I don't.
(in foreign language)
- That's Giles, Cindy's boyfriend.
He is a bit crazy.
It's okay, he doesn't understand English.
(in foreign language)
- What's wrong?
- I have to go.
I am going to go talk to
him for a few seconds.
I'll be back.
- Okay.
- That Cindy, she has
been doing that thing
she was talking about.
- What?
- The disco dumping.
Well she has dumped and now
she is sliding all around in there.
- Oh God.
- Giles is threatening to kill her
and all his boyfriends have left
and it smells terrible.
Fucking bisexuals.
(in foreign language)
(laughing)
- Hey, what are you doing?
Give me that camera back.
- There's some great stuff on here.
- There had better be.
- Oh my God, she filmed herself shitting.
- The Germans will love that.
- You look perplexed.
- I'm just waiting for my synapses
to have trouble recognizing each other.
- [Kevin] Oh darling I
live for that moment.
- You've been in that moment
for quite some time now.
- Well yeah, why not?
Anyway, I didn't mean for
this to become a pity party.
I just want to burn through
whatever life I have left.
- Is drinking a good idea?
- Now that is a real question.
I don't feel sufficiently
plastered to answer it though.
Chin chin.
God I love the beach.
Why do we have to sit next
to the fucking hippie art?
It's like burning man.
Let's tear that fucking
hideous thing down.
(laughing)
(knocking on door)
- [Alain] Bon jour.
- Hey.
- I thought you could use some breakfast.
- Thanks.
That's really sweet.
- Sweet?
- Yeah, nice?
- [Alain] So, you had fun last night?
- Yeah I did, did you?
- Yeah, pretty weird
people but they are fun.
- Interesting, interesting people.
I had a good time with you.
- So, what are you doing today?
- I don't know.
I thought Solange would
be here, she's not.
I just woke up actually.
- I still can't believe I met her.
I've got to get back to work.
- [John] Uh-oh.
- Enjoy your breakfast.
- Thank you.
Will I see you later?
- Oui.
(phone ringing)
- Hello?
- Bon jour sleepy head.
You like your new phone?
I got it so I could keep track of you.
- Where are you?
What time did you get up?
- Oh baby I never sleep,
being un-dead and all.
- I'm beginning to think
you're not joking about that.
- Look, great news, I set up
a shoot for this afternoon.
It's this old restaurant
that is suddenly hip again.
Apparently everything old is new again.
I texted you the address, did you get it?
- Let me see.
Yeah I got it.
- Okay great, so I'll see you later, ciao.
- [John Voiceover] When I wasn't filming
Solange for the show.
I was busy falling in
love with Alain and Paris.
Alain worked at the hotel during the day
but was also in a band
called Plateau Repas,
which I think translates to Dinner Plate?
I fantasized about staying in France
and making a movie with Alain,
or at least a music video for his band.
He totally changed onstage,
it was amazing to see.
- [Alain] One two three, kick it!
(in foreign language)
(upbeat electronic music)
(audience cheering)
- Hey you.
- Hey.
- Can I see the frame?
- Sure.
- [Solange] Oh fantastic!
- Yeah.
- I love this place.
It's so touristy that
it's become un-touristy.
- Hey do you want me to
film you saying that?
- Yeah, great idea.
How do I look?
- Great, just let me re-light.
- Oh don't worry about
it, we'll fix it in post.
Just film me.
- Okay.
- I love this place, it's so touristy
that it's become un-touristy.
How was that?
- Great, just don't say "how was that?"
- Oh John don't worry we'll just dub it.
Besides this is just for the pilot,
you know to raise some money.
So it's no big deal, just do whatever.
Film anything.
- [John Voiceover] Alain's band started
getting a lot of attention.
Even that crazy performance artist Cindy
started hanging around them more.
They were playing every
night at cool venues.
To quote Solange, in some of
the most un-tourist places.
I guess that's what gave
Alain the idea to have Solange
perform her European one-hit-wonder
after them one night.
She was totally flattered and excited
and spent a whole day trying
to remember all the lyrics.
She kept joking that it was
gonna be her big comeback.
We had no idea that it would
also be Cindy's big debut.
She was hell bent for the big time.
(crowd screaming)
♪ The planet moves
silently, into the night ♪
♪ Spaceships descend
against harsh floodlights ♪
♪ Something is touching my
skin like a soft machine ♪
♪ Life is detected, it feels so alien ♪
♪ The probe is rotating in the sun ♪
♪ War has started, invasion has begun ♪
♪ Our circuit is broken from
destroyed view screens ♪
♪ A metallic form of Mephistopheles ♪
♪ We must defeat them
with our truest love ♪
♪ We must stop them ♪
♪ Show them what we're made of ♪
♪ They must never win ♪
♪ Robots are un-American ♪
♪ The power of our love within ♪
♪ We must defeat them
with our truest love ♪
♪ We must stop them ♪
♪ Show them what we're made of ♪
♪ They must never win ♪
♪ Robots are un-American ♪
♪ The beat is a sonic power from within ♪
(gun firing)
(crowd yelling)
- [John Voiceover] Solange
and I spent three hours
with the police.
She spoke to them in French.
I have no idea what she
said, but they let us go.
Solange assured me that
everything was cool,
whatever that meant.
- It's like violence is
always lingering around me.
I was five years old
when the first gun was
pulled in my presence,
and not long after that I
had seen my first dead body.
By the time I was thirteen I
had been in two car accidents,
a bank robbery, and had
fallen off a damn bridge.
Don't worry nothing physical
was permanently damaged.
I can't say that about my personality.
When I was little I used to cry a lot,
a big crybaby,
and my mother would say,
"breathe Solange, breathe, relax."
But she knew damn well my childhood
was no place for relaxation.
It was like an ice cube in the sun.
Look, I know I should
have explained this to you
before we left, but I didn't
want to frighten you off.
And don't get me wrong, I am not bragging,
or trying to seem tough or worldly.
It's more like the wrong person
at the wrong place at the right time.
You know, I think that's
what attracted Kevin to me.
He was always convinced that something
was gonna blow up and he
wanted to be there when it did.
Come on, let's go to Italy.
I'm taking a shower.
Damn I knew that girl Cindy was crazy.
So much for my big comeback.
Hey babe if you see Alain tonight
say goodbye to him for me okay.
And listen, don't miss the train tomorrow.
- [John Voiceover] I
didn't mention the gun.
I kept putting it off,
like it would disappear in
that big black bag of hers
if I didn't bring it up.
(bright electronic music)
♪ So I say every day ♪
♪ So I say every hour
as time is passing by ♪
♪ So I say every moment ♪
♪ So I say every second
I got I gotta say ♪
♪ In time everything will change ♪
♪ And nothing we have stays the same ♪
♪ In a flash, in a blink of an eye ♪
♪ It often changed overnight ♪
- You sure about this?
- Yeah let's just do
it now before it starts
falling off on its own from the chemo.
I'll do you next.
- Oh no.
- [Kevin] Oh yeah.
- No no no no no.
- I won't tell anybody.
- No, you will look good.
You will.
- [Kevin] Go ahead just do it.
♪ Sad seeing you again ♪
♪ Sad seeing you just
once in my lifetime ♪
♪ Sad see you to wonder ♪
♪ But at least it won't
matter to the hands of time ♪
♪ Because time has never been a prayer ♪
♪ And you've gone right to the end ♪
♪ In a flash in a blink of an eye ♪
- Okay I'm done.
♪ Can often change overnight ♪
- [John Voiceover] I couldn't figure out
how to say goodbye to Alain.
But then he made it easy for me.
- Oh shit.
- What is it?
- My boyfriend.
- Boyfriend?
You've gotta be kidding me.
(in foreign language)
(bright pop music)
- I love trains.
Sometimes I wish I could
stay on a train forever.
- It would get boring
after a while, though.
- Yeah maybe, but real fast.
How do I look?
- [John Voiceover] You look great.
- [Solange] Come on, don't lie.
Ruggero was my make-up
artist from the drama years.
- [John Voiceover] Drama years?
- [Solange] Yeah, Italian
horror movie star years,
he specialized in zombie drool.
- Really?
- Yeah, and Giacomo should be here too.
He was my modeling
agent from the eighties.
He had like a small
agency like a boutique.
And, matter of fact now
he's in the restaurant game.
You know what, he just
opened up a new one.
We should do a segment on him.
- Sure.
- Ciao Ruggero.
- Ciao, how are you Solange?
John, Solange talked so much about you.
- Nice to meet you, thank you.
- No, no, no, let me fix your face first.
- Johnny John, this is Giacomo.
- John, Ciao.
- Ciao Giacomo, how are you?
- How are you finding Italy?
- I found it, love it.
I feel like I've been here before.
My mother's family is from Italy.
- You must feel it in your blood no?
- Yeah yeah, I guess so.
- [Giacomo] Where is your family from?
- My grandmother's family is from Naples
and my grandfather was born in Rome.
- So you are Southern.
- Yeah, by the long way around.
- [Giacomo] Good.
- Why?
- The northerners have colder hearts.
You have a very marketable smile.
- Huh?
- Your smile, it's very commercial.
I manage models, Solange once.
- Okay, what could you sell with it?
- A smile?
A good smile sells food and furniture,
print ads, not every model
is on the runway for Gucci or Prada.
- That's just what I want to hear.
I can sell grapefruit and sofas.
No, no, it's just a typical story for me.
I could be in a glamorous
profession like modeling
but I would be hawking ravioli and desks.
- Desks can be very glamorous.
- I'm sure they can be.
So I inspire domesticity?
- Si and trust,
a good smile says trust me.
- [John Voiceover]
Giacomo was half-Italian,
half-French, raised in Paris.
So there was pretty much
no inoculation against him.
I was totally at his mercy here.
- So how's it going, anything good?
- I haven't really been filming.
- No, I'm not talking about that.
I'm talking about you
and Giacomo, any sparks?
- Yeah, I think you
know the answer to that.
- Yeah, I think you're right.
- What a beautiful place
where I will never live.
- Che cosa?
- Nothing, just being flip.
- Okay flipping guy.
Let me put some music.
This is the living room.
Here is the kitchen.
- Very nice.
- I have money to spend
on stuff I will never use.
There is a bathroom here.
Another living room.
Here is another bathroom.
- Another bathroom.
- Yes.
This is my mother's bedroom
when she visits from Romagnese
which is north of here.
- Romagnese?
- Romagnese.
- Si.
Here is my bedroom, which
doubles as a guest room.
(upbeat pop music)
(lyrics in foreign language)
- My wife.
- You're married?
- A long time ago.
You are the first guy I've
had sex with in this bed.
- Well technically we haven't
had sex in the bed yet.
- The first guy I've had in this bed then.
- And how long have you had this bed?
- One week.
- [John Voiceover] There should
be a word for infatuation
that links lust and love more closely.
I bet there is one in Italian.
That feeling that you are in love,
but you are just completely
sucked into the gravity well
of someone else's gaze.
Romantic yes, real no.
- This place is beautiful isn't it?
Do you think I should get a place here?
I like how it's handy to the city
but it still has like a small town vibe.
- Yeah, that would be beautiful.
- Yeah, but it would be
hard to get any work done
with all the fucking and
eating going on in Italy.
- I wouldn't mind.
- Oh this is the life, not
my life, but a good life.
(upbeat funky electronic music)
(phone ringing)
(in foreign language)
- They are having problems
at the restaurant.
Nothing is ready for the opening.
I have to get going.
- No problem.
- It is a problem.
I wanted to stay here with you.
I will drive you to
Ruggero's, it is on the way.
- [John Voiceover] I felt more fuck-high
and in touch with my Italian
heritage than ever before.
And with an all too familiar
pang I felt in love as well.
Oh, is Solange here?
- No, she is shopping or something,
I cannot keep track of her.
- Okay.
- [Ruggero] Was the sex good?
- What?
- Was the sex very good?
- Ummm yeah, thanks.
- Giacomo is charming.
He's a charmer when he wants to be.
That is how he gets all
the boys to the bed.
- Oh really?
- [Ruggero] Yes, oh by
the way Solange left you
some money on the table.
- Wow.
- [Ruggero] She said you
should buy some clothes for tonight.
Would you like me to
help you with something?
- Just a second.
(phone ringing)
- [Ruggero] Okay.
Another boyfriend?
- I'm sorry, do you mind?
- Of course not.
- Hello.
- Where are you?
- Italy.
- When are you coming back to France?
- I can't, remember, I'm working.
- I need you.
Since that thing at the club
I haven't been able to
leave the apartment.
- What about your boyfriend?
- He has left me.
- I'm sorry.
- I'm not, I mean yes I'm sorry.
I want you Johnny John.
I need to see you again.
- I don't know if or when
we are coming back to Paris.
- I understand but I
hope you will come back.
- Me too.
- Really?
- Yes.
- Thank you.
- I have to go, call me later?
- No, wait there is
something else I have to say.
There was this man who came
to look for you and Solange.
I said you left me and I
didn't know where you were,
which wasn't a lie by the way.
- Was he with the police?
- No, definitely not.
- What did he look like?
- Some Italian guy with long hair.
He wouldn't take his sunglasses off.
- Okay, thanks for telling me.
If he comes back don't
tell him we are in Italy.
- I won't.
- I will come back to Paris soon.
- I hope so.
- Bye.
(upbeat dance music)
- You are American aren't you?
- Yes, how can you tell?
- Uff, you aren't smoking.
- No.
- I heard that in America
you can't smoke anywhere anymore.
- That's true.
Actually, I don't think you
can smoke in here either.
- Nonsense, as you get older
smoking becomes a necessity,
at a certain age cancer
can be welcomed with open arms.
- [Solange] Hey, send
more drinks this way.
- [John] That guy has been
staring at you all night.
- No biggie,
I might know him from
somewhere or vice versa.
- Alain said there was a guy who came by
when we left Paris looking for us.
The description fits.
- No, I'm sure he is fine.
Hold on.
(funky music)
- I am sorry that I cannot
spend more time with you.
- Don't worry about it.
Things are going good right?
- So far, yes.
I must get back.
(dissonant electronic music)
- No, I don't know him and
I'll make a point to never.
Come on let's go.
- We haven't eaten yet.
- We'll get a pizza someplace.
- What about the filming?
- We have enough.
Look he'll be here all night.
You stay with me tonight, all right?
We'll see him in the morning.
Come on let's go.
(slow jazz music)
(lyrics muffled)
♪ Not empty words ♪
♪ Back in Hollywood ♪
♪ That's where feel like ♪
(lyrics muffled)
♪ With heavy hearts it's hard to see ♪
♪ Why Monday won't leave gravity ♪
♪ Keep the weight off ♪
(lyrics muffled)
♪ With heavy hearts it's hard to see ♪
♪ That Monday won't leave gravity ♪
♪ Keep the weight off ♪
(lyrics muffled)
♪ With heavy hearts it's hard to see ♪
♪ That Monday won't leave gravity ♪
♪ Keep the weight off ♪
(lyrics muffled)
- [Ruggero] Hello.
- Buongiorno sunshine, want some eggs?
Good hangover food.
- Sure.
- Here is an article about
Giacomo's restaurant.
- Oh, what does it say?
- It's a bit scandalous,
also in the way it's written.
It says twelve people were made sick with,
I don't know how to say it in English,
it's the food that made them sick.
Very, very, sick.
But they write the article
with a lot of insults.
Not very objective.
The poison is like the
stuff for injections
for the lines in the face.
- Botulism?
- Si, it is the Botox.
I'm sure Giacomo is going to
be very very upset by this.
Let me call him.
Lin, bring me the phone.
- [Lin] Si.
- Good thing we didn't stick
around for the food huh?
Oh that was icky wasn't it?
- Yeah.
Is it gonna be okay?
- It depends, I mean
the place was spotless
and the kitchen is state of the art.
I don't know how that could have happened.
Maybe it was the supplier, who knows?
Puts that part of the show
out of commission huh?
- Yeah.
- What are we gonna do now?
- I think we should pack.
- We're leaving Italy?
- Hell yeah.
I think it's a good idea
before someone offers us
a free dinner that ends up
in the toilet for ten hours.
Besides there's this party
in Berlin we should be at.
You know, for filming.
- Okay.
My stuff's at Giacomo's though.
- Then we should go get it.
- He's not there.
Or maybe he's not answering the phone.
Maybe he got the Botox?
- It's okay, we're going over there.
We'll see what's up.
Right John?
- Right.
- Come on, get your stuff let's go.
(banging)
- What is the hurry?
Can't we wait for Giacomo
to make sure he is okay?
- He'll survive, he always does.
Besides, the cab is waiting.
- So send it away.
- I can't, okay.
- Why?
- I poisoned the food
at Giacomo's restaurant.
- What?
- The chef, the chef at
Giacomo's restaurant,
I was hired to ruin him.
See he fucked with this girl,
and this girl's fiancé and her uncle
hired me to destroy him.
It's a basic revenge job.
And in about eight months,
he's gonna get killed.
- Solange, what the fuck?
- I do jobs.
- Jobs?
- Jobs that most people don't want to do.
I get paid to fuck with
people and sometimes,
well actually most times,
people get hurt.
- Oh God.
Chefs kill themselves over
their reputations all the time.
Something like this is a career stopper.
- What about Giacomo?
- You know what, he's a dangerous man.
He got his money in a
hundred different ways
you do not want to hear about.
I did more than model
for him back in the day.
We should get out of here
before he comes back.
I don't know how much he knows.
- I don't believe you.
- You had better.
He's a killer too.
- So everyone you know is a killer?
I mean, What is this?
Like some killer dating
slash escort service?
- He's not a killer like I am...
Hold on let me rephrase that.
I really don't consider
myself to be a killer.
- Oh, okay.
I really like Giacomo.
- You know what?
I suggest you get over that crush
with both knees and your dick intact.
So come on and let's go.
- Solange,
John,
what a surprise.
How did you get in here?
- I still have keys remember.
- Of course, you are like the cat
never forgetting the old tricks.
- [Solange] We heard about
the restaurant, sorry.
- Yes, I've been at
the police all morning.
It doesn't look good for my chef,
but do not worry, it will not touch me.
I will not let it touch me.
- That's good.
Yeah, we ere hoping to
see you before we left.
See we have more shooting to do.
The show must go on.
So we came to get the
camera and John's stuff.
- That is Solange always on the run.
- Yeah, well the taxi is waiting.
So I'll give you guys some
time alone to say goodbye.
Ciao.
- Ciao.
(tense electronic music)
- I am so glad you are okay.
It was really nice to have met you.
I am sorry we have to go.
- It is ironic that Solange brings
both good and bad luck with her travels,
because I would not
have met you otherwise.
- Yeah, that is true.
- I wanted to take you to the beach.
- That would have been nice.
Maybe next time I'm in Italy.
- She distracted me with you,
but it's okay,
you must sometimes take
the bad with the good.
- Thanks.
- You should go now.
(pulsing electronic music)
- Does he suspect anything?
- I don't know.
His tongue didn't give anything away.
- I feel so stupid.
I should have never taken a job
so close to the people I know.
It was like a challenge.
It's like a rush.
I feel like a damn idiot.
- Maybe you should take up skydiving.
- I'm sorry.
- Why am I here?
- Well Kevin was gone and
I couldn't do everything
without somebody being here.
- Kevin knew about this, about your work?
- Yeah, he knew everything.
I don't know how else
to explain it to you.
He was like my absolver.
- He took your confessions.
So I'm his stand in?
I need a drink.
(upbeat electronic music)
- [John Voiceover] Kevin told
me once about how he would
pick up guys at the Tiergarten in Berlin.
Sometimes they realized
they were both after money.
They had a good laugh
and then had a contest
to see who could get the most.
Kevin won of course, but then
one of the guys robbed him.
Someone like this guy, unknown,
cute and most likely bummed
that I can't speak German.
(upbeat electronic music)
(in foreign language)
- Wait.
(upbeat jazz music)
What are we doing?
- Getting a feel for it, checking it out.
- Okay what should I be filming?
- Just get some establishing shots.
This place is cool isn't it?
- Yeah,
so is there even gonna be a show
or is that just like your cover?
- Oh shut up, of course
there is gonna be a show.
- Okay.
- Okay, there she is.
I knew she'd be here.
- You knew she'd be here?
- It's my job to know
where these people are.
- Okay Solange, you're wigging me out.
Is she a hit or something?
- No, silly, for the show, film her.
- Okay.
- She was in Dargento's last movie.
You know the Italian horror master?
- Of course, I saw you in
his movie "Ghoul School".
- Yeah, that among many others.
But she only had one line,
and she didn't get herself killed,
which to me is ridiculous.
If you are gonna be in Dargento's movie,
you at least get yourself killed.
Ciao Isabella.
- Ciao Solange.
- [John] Hi.
(in foreign language)
- I'm sorry, I don't speak German.
- Oh you are American?
Oh poor thing.
Let me buy you a drink.
(in foreign language)
- Thank you.
- No problem, you are welcome.
What are you doing here?
- We are shooting a film
about cool hip clubs.
- Oh, how nice.
- Thank you.
- Nice.
- Thanks, oh I loved
you in "Hypochondria,"
you are my idol.
- Thank you sweetheart.
- How did it look?
- Great.
- Thanks.
- She got her tits done
too late if you ask me.
Those must be producers,
the ones ogling her.
- That's your acting verdict?
- Uh, yeah no one wants to
see a girl with tiny tits
get killed in Dargento movies.
You know what?
I told her you were a producer too.
So, she should be over
here right about now.
Expect tits.
- Hi there.
- Hi.
- Solange was telling me all about you.
- Oh?
- Yeah.
(phone ringing)
- I'm sorry I have to take this.
- Oh you're American?
- Yes, excuse me.
- Okay I'll wait, I'll wait here.
- Hello.
- Hello Johnny John,
where are you?
- I'm in Berlin at a club.
- It's so loud.
When are you coming back to France?
- Soon I hope.
- I would love that so much.
- Me too.
I think someone dosed me.
- What?
- It's some kind of hallucinogenic,
they must have put it in my drink.
I hope it doesn't last too long.
- What the fuck?
Get out of there.
- I will, I will try.
- Don't go flying out any windows.
- I won't.
I have to go.
I'll see you soon.
- Be careful,
wait wait,
don't hang up.
(upbeat dance music)
- Oh nice camera,
what are you filming?
Can I be in your movie?
I've got props.
Come on let's go for my close up.
- I am America.
I am the statue of liberty.
I am freedom.
I am New York, I am beautiful
and glittery come back to me.
Europe is the past, America is the future.
Suck of the tit of patriotism baby.
Take of my culture.
Let me pull down your pants
and show you what
American ingenuity can do.
I am America and I will rape you.
(in foreign language)
- No, no.
I have to go back to Paris.
I think someone dosed me.
I think it's some acid
with some really good E.
- [Solange] What is this,
a fucking love parade?
I'll go get our coats.
- Okay John come on, we've got to go.
We haven't got a lot of
time before she gets back.
- What?
- Solange dosed you, quick.
- [John Voiceover] I
felt like I was drowning,
and not because of the drugs.
- You've got to get just what you need.
We haven't got a lot of time.
Man, she gave you some really good shit.
Come on.
- [John Voiceover] It was
like I was becoming Kevin.
Being pulled out to sea in an undertow.
I think Solange dosed me to
try to turn me into Kevin,
that is what I wanted to believe anyway.
I don't know what Isabella's deal was.
She said Giacomo had sent her,
which wasn't exactly reassuring.
- [Isabella] Okay you ready?
Let's go, come.
- [John Voiceover] I
just wanted to escape,
to catch my breath
somewhere safe and far away,
and safe and far away was Alain.
♪ And I'm running as hours ♪
♪ Running as days by ♪
♪ Running is just fine ♪
♪ Time goes faster ♪
♪ I'll be running for hours ♪
♪ Running for cover ♪
♪ Running forever ♪
♪ In a flash of a blink of any eye ♪
♪ In a second it passes you by ♪
♪ In a flash in a blink of an eye ♪
♪ It all can change overnight ♪
- Don't worry, we will
take care of Solange.
- Who is we?
(dramatic instrumental music)
(light romantic music)
- Are you happy to see me?
- Yeah, you have no idea.
It's so good to be back here.
(light instrumental music)
(dramatic instrumental music)
- John?
- No no no no no, relax.
What the fuck are you doing here?
Stop, stop, don't come any closer.
- What the fuck is going on John?
- Stay out of it Alain.
- [Solange] I think there is a
little more you need to know.
It's a long story.
- Long or short, it's not
gonna make any difference.
- Well maybe it will after you hear this.
Kevin had help at the beach.
I helped him.
- What?
- Well, you use your
powers for evil so much,
how about using them
for good for a change?
- Kevin I don't exactly
call any of this good, baby.
- I need this.
I can't watch my mom nursing me backwards
into oblivion Solange.
I just want to disappear.
- Kevin, if you care
anything about me or your mom
you wouldn't ask me.
- If you care about me,
you'll do it.
Don't lecture me Solange.
I'm dying.
- Fine, you want the businesswoman,
you'll get the businesswoman.
So when?
- As soon as possible.
If I wait too long, I won't
be able to get out of bed.
I need to be able to walk out there.
- You were always about the drama.
(laughing)
- I was thinking of you,
it's less clean up.
- Damn, now why didn't I think of that?
- You're slipping?
Maybe it is time to retire.
- Maybe.
- [Kevin] Oh and one last thing,
promise me you'll get John out
of that damn office cubicle.
- [Solange] I promise.
- So you came here to tell me this?
Why?
I mean it's not really
that shocking anymore,
knowing what I know.
Is this guilt?
- No, I don't feel
guilty for helping Kevin
with his final wish.
It was upsetting though.
I'd be a total monster if I
felt nothing, don't you think?
- You've had a lot of practice.
- Huh?
- Playing monsters.
- Look John, stay with me
right now in this moment.
Shit is hitting the fan quick
and unfortunately, it involves you.
- No, no way, I'm not with you anymore.
- Remember the guy at the restaurant?
- So what?
- He's after me.
- That Italian guy that came here?
He knows where I live, get out!
I am calling the police.
- [Solange] Okay, okay,
but first give me the gun
and the money you took from me,
then I'll leave you alone.
- And if I don't?
- I'm retiring anyway,
but I just can't walk away
from this without protection.
- Give her the things.
- You know, I would say I'm sorry,
but I promised Kevin I'd
get you out of that cubicle,
and I did that at least, didn't I?
John?
- John!
- [John Voiceover] Solange
didn't need the money or the gun,
she needed her absolver.
She needed to confess to me about Kevin.
(dramatic orchestral music)
(gun firing)
I heard from Solange a few times.
She wanted the footage I shot.
I didn't reply.
I did everything I promised you I would.
I got tested, got my drivers license.
I got out of that damn cubicle.
I almost quit smoking.
But I can't live the life
you didn't get to live.
I've got to start something new.
I guess that's what you and
Solange gave me, something new.
(upbeat pop music)
♪ I felt it in the air it was a romance ♪
♪ I looked into your eyes
you gave me a smile ♪
♪ And nothing else existed for a while ♪
♪ Hold me so tight ♪
♪ In the night ♪
♪ I see our lantern shining bright ♪
♪ I know you'll be mine ♪
♪ In no time ♪
♪ In the moonshine ♪
♪ Deep in my soul ♪
♪ I know ♪
♪ That we were never meant to go ♪
♪ Walking alone ♪
♪ So be mine ♪
♪ In the sunshine ♪
♪ Hold me so tight ♪
♪ In the night ♪
♪ I see our lantern shining bright ♪
♪ I know you'll be mine ♪
♪ In no time ♪
♪ In the moonshine ♪
♪ Deep in my soul ♪
♪ I know ♪
♪ That we were never meant to go ♪
♪ Walking alone ♪
♪ So be mine ♪
♪ In the sunshine ♪
♪ Hold me so tight ♪
♪ In the night ♪
♪ I see our lantern shining bright ♪
♪ I know you'll be mine ♪
♪ In no time ♪
♪ In the moonshine ♪
♪ Deep in my soul ♪
♪ I know ♪
♪ That we were never meant to go ♪
♪ Walking alone ♪
♪ So be mine ♪
♪ In the sunshine ♪
(upbeat electronic dance music)
("Robots are Un-American" by Solange)
♪ The probe is rotating in the sun ♪
♪ War has started, invasion has begun ♪
♪ Our circuit is broken from
destroyed view screens ♪
♪ A metallic form of Mephistopheles ♪
♪ We must defeat them
with our truest love ♪
♪ We must stop them ♪
♪ Show them what we're made of ♪
♪ They will never win ♪
♪ Robots are un-American ♪
♪ The power of our love within ♪
♪ The time is near for
all of us to fight ♪
♪ So we're watching the
darkness of the light ♪
♪ If something was with us ♪
♪ Like in dreams ♪
♪ Will you hold me tight ♪
♪ Despite what it seems ♪
♪ We must defeat them ♪
♪ With our truest love ♪
♪ We must stop them ♪
♪ Show them what we're made of ♪
♪ They must never win ♪
♪ Robots are un-American ♪
♪ The power of our love within ♪
♪ We must defeat them ♪
♪ With our truest love ♪
♪ We must stop them ♪
♪ Show them what we're made of ♪
♪ They must never win ♪
♪ Robots are un-American ♪
♪ The beat is a sonic power from within ♪
♪ Break it down ♪