Rowena.
Uh. Are you still up?
Everyone's coming early tomorrow.
Relax, Mom. Getting up early
on Christmas is what I do best.
Ayayay. What a mess. I thought we agreed
you'd clean up, Rowena.
I wanted to,
but I was so excited for Christmas.
Uh-huh.
I didn't know you still had this.
I love that thing.
It reminds me of the Christmas
when we all went to go see The Nutcracker.
Surprised you still remember it.
You were so young.
Well, I slept through half of it,
but the other half really landed.
It almost made my list. Look.
Okay.
"Rowena's top five Christmas memories."
"Number five: The Christmas
Around the World exhibit at the museum."
That's where we took that picture
of you and Gabriella under the big tree.
- "Number four: The pier."
- Remember?
We got to see all the holiday performers.
And I got to ride the Ferris wheel.
That was a classic.
"Number three:
The Santa versus Elves hockey match."
Which Dad and I
will definitely want to watch tomorrow.
"Number two: That big platform thingy."
The giant platform thingy that opens out
so you feel like you're flying
over the city.
Right. At the top of the Hancock building.
But you were too scared
to even step on it.
Okay, yeah, but I watched Gabby do it
from only a few feet away.
The look on her face was priceless.
And my number one favorite
Christmas memory: The Winterfest.
- Obvi.
Can we please go back to the Winterfest
tomorrow, Mom?
Well, honey, we might have to
switch things up a little bit this year.
It's our first Christmas
with some new faces.
You mean Diane and Louie?
Honey, I know that these memories
mean a lot to you,
but, hey, we can make new memories.
Christmas isn't only about tradition.
It's about us being all together
despite the changes.
But don't want anything to change.
I know you don't, honey,
but sometimes change is for the best.
And you'd know that if you cleaned
your room every once in a while.
Okay, lights out, you, or someone's
not getting a visit from Santa.
Buenas noches, mi niñita.
Buenas noches, Mama.
Good morning, Chicago!
It's that day you've all been waiting for.
- That's right. It is Christma...
- Christma...
Boo!
Louie! Oh, you're gonna get it!
Got you, you little devil.
What are you doing? Having fun upstairs?
Yeah, I was having lots of fun with Ro.
Hey, sprout. Merry Christmas.
Merry Christmas, Dad.
Uh, why didn't you come wake me
like you always do?
Well, I wanted to,
but Louie asked to do the honors.
Looks like he got the job done.
She's totally up.
Yeah, she is.
Come on, Ro. Come say hi to Diane.
Up, over.
Yes, just like that!
Guess who decided to join us.
Morning, sleepyhead.
Rowena, Merry Christmas.
Your dad told me
that you made the softball team.
What position do you play?
- Goalie.
- Ro.
Okay. Shortstop.
Dad, I made a list of my favorite
Christmas memories for us to do again.
Which do want to do first?
Gee, I don't know, sprout.
I think your mom's planning
a nice day for everyone.
We might have to play this by ear.
Uh, but we can at least watch
the Santas versus Elves match, can't we?
This has got to be the Santas' year.
Oh, I hope so,
after the last couple beatdowns.
Although I'm hearing that
the Santas' center is out with spasms.
Again? That guy should really stretch.
- Uh, do you think...
- What's a center?
Uh, a position in hockey. Usually
the middle player on the forward line.
- Do you think we could...
- What are spasms?
Something you won't have to worry about
for a long time.
I'm sorry, sweetheart.
What were you asking me?
- Do you think the Santas could still...
- Shoelaces.
Who took the last chocolate?
- Stop it!
- It wasn't me.
Uh, maybe Santa was hungry last night.
Don't give me that, Dad.
I'm not a little baby like Louie.
- Watch it, Ro.
- But, Mom,
we trade off every year
who gets the last chocolate.
This was supposed to be my year.
It was me. I'm sorry, Rowena.
I-I didn't know about your tradition.
Look what I can do.
Oh, Louie, that's wonderful.
- He's only had one class.
- Oh.
Hope you asked Santa for a blankie.
'Cause it's gonna be cold
out of that spotlight.
Ay, Gabriella.
You two are looking lively indeed.
How was midnight mass?
- Ooh.
- Absolutely transporting.
Good.
Oh, Diane, it's so good to see you.
It's good to see you, Sofia.
And you too, Hector.
Diana, por favor. I already told you
all my friends call me Doc.
- Well, Merry Christmas, Doc.
- Merry Christmas.
- Oh.
- Oh, my little Rowena.
Did you like the sweater?
I made it myself.
We haven't opened presents yet, Ma.
- Oh.
- But thanks for the spoiler.
Aw.
All right. All right.
You'll smother the poor girl.
Ro, are we having a nice Christmas?
- Oh.
Mmm.
It's my fault.
I should never have dragged you
to that greasy spoon diner.
Ro.
Oh, no.
Ew!
Sausage and eggs.
Uncle Gerry. Uncle Bruce.
Merry Christmas!
You got a dog?
Perfect. She's awake again.
We adopted Olive from the shelter.
She kept us up all night.
- Okay. Come in.
- Hey, you wanna hold her?
- Yes. Oh, my God. Isn't she cute?
- Here she is.
Who do we have here?
Who is it? Oh, it's a baby.
Oh. Oh.
It's a good thing you're not a cat
'cause cats make me so sneezy.
Oh, hey, I know a little boy
who'd love to meet you.
Uncle Gerry?
It's not mine. Hers.
Well, then you give her the socks.
I love my new Mariachi CD.
It's a scrapbook and paper.
But, Mom, you always get me clothes.
Which you never like. You always complain.
Yeah, at first.
But then you make me try them on
and I low-key love them.
That's like our thing, Mom.
Why are you messing with the program?
I will still buy you clothes.
I just thought
you might like something new.
This is definitely new, all right.
I made cookies.
Yum-yum.
- Oh, is there dairy in them?
- Oh, no. No dairy.
I love dessert for breakfast.
Especially cookies.
Is there kale in this?
There is indeed. You've got a great nose.
They're my best sellers.
- Oh, I need to try one.
- I guess.
Honey, pick up after yourself.
Someone is going to break their neck.
This is what we do every year, Mom.
Gabby and I make a mess
so that you can get mad and clean it up.
That is not funny.
And if you're trying to make me mad,
it's working.
Yes, open this one.
Oh!
It's a stage makeup kit.
Your dad said
that you were in the school play.
In third grade.
My favorite part
was definitely the makeup.
No way!
- Aw.
- How cool. A bow and arr...
Oh.
Honey, come on. You are killing me.
This one's from your uncles.
I hope you like it.
- This, Ro, is what we call a judogi.
- Oh, wow.
It's what all true judokas wear.
- Wow.
- I got one too!
Twinsies. Hiyah!
Oh, look at him.
I told you he'd look cute.
- Oh, okay, that is really cute.
- Oh.
All right, sprout.
You're gonna like this one.
I noticed yours was getting old
so we got you...
A tablet!
With knobs?
That's a classic.
Mira, you turn the knob's to draw,
then shake it up and…whew.
Like it never happened.
- I think there's been a mix-up.
- Yeah.
Awesome!
Okay, buddy, that was supposed to be for...
I love it so much!
- Can we play catch now? Can we?
- I'm sorry, sprout. We'll figure it out.
Why don't you grab your glove
and meet us outside?
That was my glove.
- Carolina.
- Sí?
Your father and I want to give you
something very special.
- Oh, okay.
- Mmm.
This was given to us.
It's been in our family for generations.
Passed down to me
from my bisabuela, Lucia,
from Puerto Rico, who had it passed
from her tatarabuela, Maribelle.
Ay. I still remember her
serving arroz con gandules in this.
Gracias, Mama. Thank you.
I love it. I love it.
- Where's my phone?
- I love it.
Ew! Dog slobber.
- ¡Ay!
- No!
And to think all those kids
used to call me butterfingers.
Oh!
I'm okay.
Okay, well...
Well, that just happened.
I guess I'm just gonna go look
for my glove.
Yeah.
- Bruce.
- The bowl! Oh, my God!
Well, at least you didn't pee on it.
And you just peed on it.
Cool.
Ew.
Ready? Here we go.
Nice. You got it.
Throw it back.
- Perfecto.
- Oh, man, I'm starving.
- It's good? Not too salty?
- Try abuela's tamales.
- Uh-uh.
- Ah, you t... You took the last tamale.
I'm done eating. Can Dad and I go watch
the rest of the match?
Uh, sprout, I just sat down.
- And last I checked, it pains me to say…
- Mm-hmm.
- …the Elves are crushing my Santas.
- What?
- I'm gonna get that five dollars.
- I know. I know.
You can go after everyone's finished
with dinner and dessert.
I made gingerbread cake.
Oh, did somebody say gingerbread?
Okay, now…
Because last year
you didn't save any for the kids,
so I'm instituting
a one-slice rule para ti.
Th-That is a baseless accusation.
I could sue you for defamation,
or you could cough up the gingerbread.
Oh, I know.
We should make him perform for his cake.
Gerry's been taking a stand-up class.
- Bruce, you said you wouldn't tell.
- What?
He only gets cake
if he tells a joke.
Mom, the match is almost over.
Fine. You can go watch,
but first finish your dinner.
Stand-up comedy. Gerry, that's awesome.
And he's still a tad shy.
Hey, why don't you show them
that bit that you've been working on?
- Bruce, I'm still working on it.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Come on, Gerry. Do it.
- You gotta do it.
- Do it, Gerry.
- Do it! Do it! Do it!
Okay. Okay.
Just be kind
'cause it's still a work in progress.
Well… …here goes nothing.
All done. Come on, Dad. Let's go.
Rowena. Sit.
Thank you.
Okay.
So I'm a lawyer, right?
As you already know.
And the hardest part of being a lawyer…
…is turning off work mode
when you get home.
Hilarious, Uncle Gerry. Wonderful show.
You know,
we're off to go watch some hockey.
Ro, he hasn't gotten to the punch line.
Sit down.
You're doing great, Ger. "Work mode…"
Right.
So, the hardest part of being lawyer
is turning off work mode
when you get home.
You already said that.
Ro, will you let your uncle
finish telling his joke?
I'm just trying to help.
You know what I just realized?
I don't even like gingerbread.
I move we strike the discussion.
- Come on, Ger. Continue.
- Gerry, Gerry!
- Come on, guys. No.
- Gerry! Gerry!
I said no!
I don't even want any cake.
Just leave me alone. Okay?
- Gerry!
- Come on, Uncle Gerry.
- Come back!
- There goes Bruce. Great.
And now the dog.
I just have to have
some more of this bread.
- It was so good.
- It was fantastic.
Oh!
- Oh!
- What?
My dinner.
Well, clearly dinner's officially over.
Does anybody wanna watch the match?
Anybody?
- Anybody?
- I will.
Anybody else?
- Five minutes left in this match.
- Santas are nearly out of time.
- Where is Rudolph when you need him?
- Come on, Santas. D up!
Woo! Let's go!
What? Come on! Where is the remote?
Can you believe what's happening
- on this ice?
- Okay.
- Let's go!
- The Elves are running away with this.
More like skating away.
It's gonna be awkward
in Santa's village tonight.
What is going on?
Okay. Okay.
Give me the remote, Louie.
- Why?
- So I can beat you with it.
- Then no.
- I'm gonna count to three.
- One.
- Catch.
Ow!
Whoa!
Ro, what is going on?
He started it.
He wouldn't let me watch the match.
- I hate him!
- That's enough, Rowena.
Yeah, that's enough, Ro-wiener.
Why do you always take his side?
Rowena! What did you do to my laptop?
I'm going to kill you!
Get in line.
- You ruined Christmas!
- I ruined Christmas?
You ruined Christmas.
All of you ruined Christmas.
I'm sure you don't mean that.
So, let's just all take a deep...
You're not even in this family, Diane.
Why are you even here?
Do you wanna get grounded
on Christmas Day?
This is the worst Christmas ever.
- Ro, you have to clean this mess up.
- Ro, you better get back here, young lady.
I'm so sorry.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hey, hey, hey, now.
- What gives?
- Sorry, sorry, sorry!
I didn't see you there.
It's been a long day.
Tell me about it. I got stuck in a chimney
face down in Sweden,
and then Rudolph... You know Rudolph?
He's the one with the...
Well, his nose went out over Toronto.
Had us flying blind for a stretch.
Look, I know you're not really Santa.
I mean, your beard is clearly fake.
My bea...
This? Yes, yes. This is clearly fake.
You got me on that one. It's...
I just wear this for the windburn
on the sled.
Let me ask you something.
And this is between me and you.
Do you know anybody
who's ever actually seen Santa?
Then how do you know what he looks like?
I mean, maybe Santa is tall
and terrified of ceiling fans.
Look, I'm 12, okay?
How can one guy make it across
the whole world in one night?
Oh, okay. Well, time is a tricky thing.
A lot can happen in a day.
Say that again.
Time is a tricky thing.
A lot can happen in a day.
I can't wait for this day to be over.
Oh.
Uh-oh. You hear that sound?
That's the sound of somebody
not having a very fun Christmas, huh?
Well, I tell you what.
Lucky for you, Santa is here.
Ho, ho, ho!
Ho...
I seriously think
I pulled something on that one.
But go ahead. Come on. Give it to me.
Tell me what you want.
The only thing I want is for things
to go back to how they used to be.
You mean, like a do-over?
Yeah.
So that this awful day
could have never happened.
So that I can have
a normal Christmas again.
Could you say that again?
Louder. I didn't hear you.
I wish I can have my Christmas again!
That's what I thought you said.
Ro?
- What are you doing out here?
- I was talking to tall Santa.
Honey, what is going on with you?
I understand
that you're having a hard time
but your behavior
is completely inappropriate.
But he really was here.
You've got to believe me.
Okay, let's go inside.
I want you to apologize to everyone.
Now.
Good morning, Chicago!
It's that day you've all been...
I must've hit record or something.
Boo!
Why are you still here?
Got you, you little devil.
What are you doing? Having fun upstairs?
- Yeah, I was having lots of fun.
- Dad?
- With who?
- With Ro.
What were you doing?
What is happening?
- Just like that.
- Are you doing it?
- The head bob?
- No.
- Over, up.
- Just like that. Yes.
Guess who decided to join us.
Morning, sleepyhead.
Rowena, Merry Christmas.
Your dad told me
that you made the softball team.
So what position do you play?
Is this a joke? We already did Christmas.
Shoelaces.
Hey, sweetie,
I know it was kind of a shock
having me and Louie here for Thanksgiving,
but we all thought
things would be easier by Christmas.
Look what I can do.
I'm still dreaming. That's it.
- Ow!
- Nope. Definitely awake.
Ay, my little Rowena.
Did you like the sweater?
I made it myself.
Haven't opened presents yet, Mama.
Ay.
All right. All right.
You'll smother the poor girl.
Ro, are we having a nice Christmas?
- Oh.
Mmm.
Abuela,
you went to the greasy spoon diner again?
Oh, it's my fault.
I should never have dragged you there.
Ro.
Not again.
That does it. This isn't funny.
Hey, Mommy, did you make the, um…
- Si.
- Yes.
This is good.
You're all mad at me for yesterday.
You're trying to teach me a lesson.
Aw, thanks, you guys.
I totally get it now.
I'll be so much better. I promise.
Honey, what are you talking about?
Nobody is mad at you.
Okay, here. Open my present.
I hope you like it.
A scrapbook!
And paper?
Wrapped in more paper?
Ro, you don't have to be sarcastic.
I made cookies!
Diane, can I open your present?
I've always wanted a stage makeup kit.
Ro, have you been peeking at your gifts?
No, Mom, I swear. I can be good.
I'll even like the tablet with knobs,
which was probably meant for Louie,
but I don't care anymore, see?
I've learned my lesson.
So can we all just stop with the joke now?
Please.
This is not good.
- Yes!
- Yes.
Guess who decided to join us.
Morning, sleepyhead.
Rowena, Merry Christmas.
I think I messed up.
I wished for Christmas again,
and now I'm stuck in the same day.
Crazy.
You guys don't believe me.
Fine.
- Hey.
- Let me guess.
Mom and Dad sent you to be Big Sister.
Well, I am your big sister.
Plus, I would've come on my own.
Eventually.
- Look, I know what you're going through.
- Trust me. You have no idea.
This is hard for me too.
I may not show it
the same way you do, but…
My laptop!
I didn't mean to spill the juice on it.
It was Louie's fault.
Well, lucky for you, you missed.
What?
I didn't spill the juice on it this time,
or slip on the skateboard.
The nutcracker didn't break.
It's like the day never happened.
Everything just reset.
But if everything resets,
then nobody remembers anything.
I can change what happens!
There's no consequences whatsoever.
I can do whatever I want!
Dear Santa, I really appreciate you
letting me relive Christmas
over and over and over…
Anyhoo,
if I'm gonna be stuck in this time loop,
I'm gonna have some fun.
It's sledding time.
Okay, see you soon.
Merry Christmas.
- Jokes for charity.
- Get your jokes for charity.
Get your jokes for charity.
Get your jokes.
Hi. Would you like to make a donation?
You two must be new around here.
How about some advice instead?
You see that girl over there?
That's Gretchen.
She used to take my lunch money.
Do not try and sell her a joke.
Thank you.
Oh, oh! Oh, my eggs! Oh!
Oh, cool!
Ho, ho, ho!
Uh, Tall Santa?
You drive a limo too?
Oh, yeah. Santa's side hustle, baby.
I also cover a tech support hotline.
Aha. Speaking of which, just one second.
Tech support.
Oh, yes.
Yes!
Oh, no, no, no. Have you tried restarting?
Oh, my. It sounds like it's broken.
Hold on just for one moment.
I'll have to ask you to hold
just a second.
Whew! Tough times.
Tough times. So what's the plan, Stan?
- It's Ro.
- Oh, I'm sorry.
Uh, what is your plan, Ro?
And the plan is to have Christmas
like we used to.
"Like we used to"?
Don't you need more people for that?
Like your family?
My family's a bit busy with other things,
so I'll just have to do it for them.
Okay, Ro. You got this.
It's just a little drop.
No need to be scared!
Get out of the way! Watch out!
Sorry!
Time to play.
Let's see. What should I do first?
Huh?
Boo!
Dad, Merry Christmas!
Merry Christmas, sprout.
- You and Louie have fun up there?
- I'll say.
Thanks for sending him to wake me.
That kid is a real delight.
- Yes!
- Up, over.
Guess who decided to join us.
Morning, sleepyhead.
Rowena, Merry Christmas.
Diane, Merry Christmas to you.
Aw.
Hand over the chocolate, lady,
and nobody gets hurt.
Mmm. Mmm. Mmm.
- I am getting notes of cinnamon…
- Mm-hmm.
And a hint of victory.
- Abuelita!
- Ah!
We haven't opened present yet,
but between you and me,
I love the sweater.
Oh, my Rowena.
All right. All right.
You'll smother the poor girl.
- Ro, are we having...
- Having a wonderful Christmas, Abuelo.
Thank you for asking.
Oops.
Clumsy me.
Gabby, could you be a dear
and go pick those up?
Oh, Abuela, you're just so beautiful.
Oh!
How did she know
which boxes had all the chocolates?
It's easy. I'm psychic.
Ha! Funny, Ro.
You're the one taking the comedy class,
Uncle Gerry.
You told them?
Okay, who wants to open presents?
Yay! Let's do it, Mom.
I cannot wait for my new scrapbook.
Or how about a makeup kit, Diane,
because you know me so well.
And gee, Dad, I'd sure love that glove,
but Louie switched tags,
so I guess I'll just settle
for a tablet with knobs.
Oh.
- You believe me now or need more proof?
- No, Ro, wait. That is enough, okay...
More proof!
Okay. First,
I'll just need to ask a few questions.
Dad,
how much cash do you have in your pocket?
Uh, it was $62.10.
Okay. Um, Uncle Gerry,
what color is your underwear?
My underwear?
Just answer the question.
Light blue.
Eh, I'd say more robin's-egg blue.
Would've been the same answer
if you asked yesterday.
And Abuela?
Who was your first crush?
You don't need psychic powers
for that one, mija.
- That would be...
- Antonio Diego.
He had these green eyes,
the color of an old nickel
and hair like a horse.
- Diane.
- Mm-hmm?
You're so good with dogs.
Did you ever have one?
Uh, Ro, where are you going with this?
I-I think it's nice
that Rowena wants to learn more about us.
Yes, I did have a dog once.
His name was Biscuit,
and he was
this adorable little French bulldog,
and I loved him so very much.
And then one day
I left a bag of chips laying around.
And I couldn't find Biscuit.
And I went all over the house,
and I went, "Biscuit."
- Okay, okay, okay.
- "Where are you? I'm so sorry."
- Okay, Ro, I think that's plenty.
- Okay.
You're right, Dad.
I'll see you all next time.
Huh?
Good morning, Chicago!
It's that day you've all been waiting for.
- That's right. It is Christmas!
- Christmas!
That's good, Rowena.
Boo.
$62.10.
Uh, light blue,
the color of your underwear.
But Bruce thinks
it's more of a robin's egg.
- Either way, you should do your laundry.
- You see?
I am very busy.
- Oh, and Abuela?
- Hmm?
I am so glad that you chose Abuelo over…
Antonio Diego.
Besides, it's only hair.
Horse-hair Antonio?
- Oh, and Diane?
- Uh-huh?
Biscuit says hi.
Biscuit?
Yeah. The little French bulldog sitting
right next to you?
He's got a bag of chips in his mouth,
and he is not too happy
about you holding Olive.
You will not get in here.
Hey, can I get one of those?
I've missed you so much.
Time to spice things up.
Merry Christmas.
The Santas versus Elves, please.
And step on it.
Mm-hmm.
I'm Israel Idonije.
And I'm Hosea Sanders.
Welcome to Chicago's own
Santas versus Elves.
The 25th Santaversary.
Come on, Santas!
Throw some elbows! Get naughty!
Well, the Santas
are really looking sluggish out there.
That's what they get
for eating cookies all night.
Oh, ow!
I'm gonna need more snacks. Excuse me.
- Congratulations, you two.
- How's it feel to win a thousand dollars?
We can visit my parents in Florida.
This is the best Christmas ever!
Excuse me.
Did they just win a thousand dollars?
They sure did.
They guessed the closest number
of candy canes in that snowman,
and they won the raffle.
What was the winning number?
Seventeen thousand…
…five hundred and thirty-six.
9,000 are red, 8,536 are green.
How'd she do that?
- I don't know, but…
- This is incredible.
…what do you plan to do with your money?
Merry Christmas again!
That's so cool.
Wow.
Woo-hoo!
Time to face my fear.
Mm-mmm!
Uh-uh. Mm-mmm.
Woo! Crushed it.
Hey, Santa, I did the big platform thingy.
With enough practice,
you can learn to do anything
and make things happen
the way you want them to.
- The Santas versus Elves, please.
- Mm-hmm.
Welcome to Chicago's own
Santas versus Elves.
Take it! Take it!
Go! Go!
Ow!
And the Elves score again!
Will the Santas ever beat the Elves?
The Elves have never looked tougher.
They got a discount
for the short one?
Bring it, Elves.
That might be the littlest Santa
I have ever seen.
Check out the hands on that little Santa!
Come on.
Yes!
- It's a miracle!
- Ho, ho! Ho, ho, ho!
A Christmas miracle!
- Yes. Here we go.
- We are gonna win this. It's our year.
- Come on, Mom.
- This is our year.
Hey, Ro, we're playing What's That?
You can be on our team.
It wouldn't be fair.
Ro, sweetie, it's just a fun game,
and none of us are very good at it,
except for Gabby.
And of course I draw for a living, so…
Same time every Christmas.
Don't worry. Me and Bruce will carry them
up to your room after this.
You mean after we finish
kicking your butt.
- Oh, ho!
- Oh!
- It's going down.
- No way.
- A lot of big talk.
- We're gonna win.
- Come on. Ro, sit.
- All right, we got this, Mom. Let's go!
- Come on, Carolina. You got this!
- We're gonna win this time. Let's go!
And go.
- Okay.
- Planet.
Yes. Good guess.
- Nice, Ro.
- Okay.
- Zoo.
- Wow.
- Yes, that is also correct.
- Toast.
- Yes.
- Frog.
- Bow tie.
- Yes.
- Hit the road.
- Two left feet.
- Yes.
- Circus.
- Green with envy.
- Yeah.
- Palace.
- Uh-huh.
- Close but no cigar.
- Yes.
- Pinwheel.
- Yeah.
- Raining cats and dogs.
- Yes.
Time.
Can we trade Louie for Ro?
- No. No. She's on our team.
- No!
- Do you want this money?
- Yes.
- Give it back! Give it back.
- But that money's for charity!
Maybe I have a charity of my own.
It's called Get Over It.
Ooh.
I can't say I didn't warn them.
- Oh, oh! Oh, my eggs! Oh!
- Ooh.
Welcome, everyone, to the 15th
annual Santa versus Elves hockey match.
One hot cocoa, please.
And don't skimp on marshmallows.
- I shan't skimp.
- Tall Santa?
Weren't you just driving the limo?
Yes, of course I was, but as you can see,
I am a man of many hats.
Even tiny little elf hats
that tend to make my head itch.
- So, is your family meeting you here?
- They're still busy,
but I pretty much know everyone here
so it's almost like we're family.
Isn't that right, Frankie?
What?
Uh, how do you know…
Weird.
Um… …she's just nervous
'cause she's proposing to her boyfriend
at the Winterfest tonight.
- Oh, that's sweet.
- Yeah.
Too bad an ornament's gonna fall
from the tree and "shatter" her moment.
Oh! Well, that's not sweet.
Why don't you, uh,
go give her a little heads up?
Eh, I've been busy.
I'm reliving
my favorite Christmas memories.
Fun, I'll give you that,
but aren't some of those favorite
Christmas memories involving your family?
Well, yeah, but I don't know, Santa.
Everything's different this year.
My dad brought his girlfriend
and her little boy, who is a nightmare.
Things just aren't the same
with my family.
Yeah, yeah, I hear you.
You know, once upon a time,
the North Pole was a quiet little place
back when it was just me and Mrs. Claus
and Dasher and Dancer.
Smash cut to today
and there are nine hungry reindeer
and a thousand noisy elves.
My point is families change.
But what's important
is you're all still together on Christmas.
Yeah,
but I don't want my family to change.
And Christmas was so much better
before Mom and Dad split.
Yeah, well, maybe so,
but while you're running around
trying to relive the past,
think of all the fun new memories
you're missing out on.
Besides, Ro,
they will always be your mom and dad
even if they're not together.
Why didn't I think of this sooner?
I could get Mom and Dad back together.
What? So that's, that, that's, that's
your takeaway from... from all of this?
Yes. This could solve everything.
Okay, Ro, well, all right.
One hot chocolate, extra marshmallow.
And thanks, Tall...
Uh, Tall Santa?
Weird.
- Hey, Mom?
- Hi, sweetie.
If you had to pick one Christmas
to live over again, which would it be?
Hmm. That's interesting. Why do you ask?
Just wondering.
If you had to,
which Christmas would you relive?
Well, my favorite Christmas…
…would be your first Christmas.
- My first Christmas?
- Mm-hmm.
You were nine months old.
It was also our first Christmas here.
Your mom and I planned a party.
We spent two days
getting the place together.
We didn't have much furniture,
but we had a tree and Christmas lights
and a wreath for the door,
and we had these horrible,
ugly, matching Christmas…
…sweatshirts.
They were absolutely hideous.
- Oh. And of course nobody could come.
- Why not?
A big storm came in out of nowhere,
snowed in the whole block.
We lost power. No TV, no lights.
Fortunately,
your mom kept a box of candles.
And we lit every single one.
And the place was just…
…spectacular.
And your mom and I sat
drinking hot cocoa and telling stories
while Gabriella played with her toys,
and you crawled around on the rug
like a little crocodile.
It was just the four of us then,
and things were so much simpler.
- Those were… - Great times.
I know what I have to do.
First things first,
let's get rid of any distractions.
Here, kitty, kitty, kitty.
Come here, Cupcake.
I know you're around here somewhere.
I've been hearing you meow.
Here, kitty, kitty, kitty.
Come on, Cupcake.
There you are,
you little runaway.
I'm gonna need more tuna.
That ought to do it.
Ooh. Nice catch.
Eye on the ball.
Nice.
That was great! Good job, Louie!
Diane, are you okay?
Oh, my gosh.
Okay, okay. I got you. Let's go upstairs.
- Come on, Louie.
- Now, easy. Easy, easy, easy.
Oh, boy.
Oh, my! What happened?
It's just a sneezing fit.
- Okay.
- Maybe we should get Doc?
- Yes.
- No. I'll be fine.
Just let him enjoy his Christmas.
I just need to take a deep breath.
Oh!
Uh, we have medicine.
Oh, no thank you.
No, thank you, sweetheart.
That stuff makes me sleepy.
Honey, your nose is lighting up
like Rudolph.
I think sleepiness
is the last of your worries.
But I don't wanna miss...
Okay.
Okay. I-I think I'm gonna get you
a cold washcloth,
and then you can lay down
in the guest room.
- Yes, yes.
- Yeah.
- Okay, here we go.
- Okay.
Got it, got it, got it, got it.
Feel better!
One down, three to go.
- I know they love it.
- How do you know?
Did you see her face?
- I seen her face. Is it?
- That's the only gift that she did love.
- Hello?
Am I speaking to Olive's daddy?
I'm sorry. Who's this?
I found this adorable little dog,
and her tag says, "I'm Olive.
If I'm lost please contact my daddy."
Poor girl was whimpering at my door.
She seemed so hungry and helpless.
- Car keys?
- Who is it?
I'll be right there.
I'll tell you in the car.
We'll be right there. We're heading out
right now. Thank you so much.
Hey, where have you been?
Playing. Where is everybody?
Diane's asleep in the guest room,
and your uncles went to go get Olive.
Little stink ball ran off this morning
and got an hour out of town.
Oh, my! Poor thing.
Thankfully,
your grandparents are still here.
- Okay, can you help me finish the dishes?
- Yeah.
And the grandparents will be asleep
by What's That,
which leaves only one.
Hey, Louie. Wanna see something cool?
All right.
But why do we have to be in the bathroom?
Because it's the best reception
in the whole house.
Observe. You can watch whatever you want.
Whoa. Even scary things
like a shark ripping off a man's head
and the man comes back
as a zombie and eats the shark?
I like your vision.
Let's see what we can find.
But my mom says if I watch scary things,
I'll have bad dreams.
Something tells me
you'll forget everything by morning.
Uh, I just got off the phone
with the electric company.
They can't send anyone until morning.
Ah, that makes sense.
It is Christmas.
On the bright side, the place
does look great with all these candles.
Mmm. It was Ro's idea.
You know, it kind of reminds me of...
- Our first Christmas here.
- Yes! Yes!
I was thinking the same thing.
I made hot cocoas.
Mom, Dad, sit. Enjoy yourselves.
You've both earned it.
Love you.
- Okay.
- Um…
- How did she… - I don't know.
- This is insane.
- I know. There's...
You must have taught her.
Really beautiful.
Gosh. Oh, uh, thanks, Sprout!
Thank you.
- Where's everybody?
- Shh.
Mom and Dad are having a moment.
- This is amazing.
- Right? I know.
- Cheers.
- It's coziness in a cup.
- Yeah.
It's working.
What are you doing?
I'm making mom and dad fall in love again.
All they needed
was some time to themselves.
You are such a baby.
Mom and Dad aren't getting back together,
and you need to accept that.
And you need to have a little faith.
Observe.
What are you… doing?
Um…
Lina, I know today
couldn't have been easy.
Are you sure it's okay if we sleep over?
What am I gonna do?
Kick you out now?
I'm kidding.
Besides, I think it's good for the girls
to see us all getting along,
especially on Christmas.
Um… is that mistletoe?
Why do I have the feeling
we are being watched?
Let the smooching begin.
That's it? No, no, no, no, no.
That can't be it.
Yeah, you're a real cupid.
Gabby pie, did you put up this mistletoe?
Nope, that would be…
- Rowena!
This might be harder than I thought.
Dad,
some kids at my school are going steady.
They brag about having their own song.
- Kids still say "going steady"?
- Bear with me, Dad.
I'm trying to speak in terms
that you can relate to.
Anyway, did you and Mom ever have a song?
We had a wedding song.
Really? What song?
What was Dad like
when you were first married?
What was it you liked about him?
He was always very handy.
He designed this house, you know.
Anytime anything needed fixing,
he was there.
And I always thought that that was very…
impressive.
Impressive.
Nice.
- What are you guys eating?
- Mmm?
Yeah, that should do it.
Merry Christmas.
Thank you.
Whoa!
You might wanna take a shower.
Jackpot.
Thanks for the help.
See you by the fire.
Love, C.
"Thanks for all your help.
See you by the fire. Love, C."
Hmm.
Did you need something?
- I was wondering if you could be my model.
- Ro, I have so much I have to do.
This was my present from Diane.
I wanna show her
how much I appreciate her gift.
Oh. Well, that's nice, honey.
It will only take a second, I promise.
Okay.
How do I look?
The important question is how do you feel?
Beau...
Like I escaped from the circus.
I guess that answers both questions.
And if your client gets
a little too jumpy,
tell them you're just enhancing
what's already there.
You are beautiful.
Huh. Not bad.
What do you think?
I think I need more tools.
Pat, pat, pat.
A little pat, pat, pat.
And there you have it. You are all set.
Now, listen, all of this is fun
and looking beautiful is fantastic.
Just remember that you are beautiful
on the inside, and that is what counts.
Perfect.
Mmm. Where did you learn all this stuff?
It's makeup, Mom, not rocket science.
Now, hold still so I can finish
contouring your nose.
But I like my nose.
I do too.
We're just enhancing what's already there.
Okay.
And voilà.
Wow, Ro. Huh.
And one last thing.
Oh! Oh!
Bad idea.
- Very bad.
- Bad idea!
Very bad idea.
I just got off the phone with the...
Oh, my. I can't believe
you still have these things.
Look how adorable you two look.
I made hot cocoas.
Mom, Dad, sit.
Enjoy yourselves. You've earned it.
Okay.
Thanks, Sprout.
- Cheers.
Where is everybody?
It's yours if you help me.
- Well, aside from the power outage…
- Mm-hmm.
…the sneezing fits
and the dog disappearance…
- Mm-hmm.
- …today wasn't a total disaster.
On the bright side, the place looks great
with all these candles.
Mmm. It was Ro's idea.
You know, it kinda reminds me of our f...
- Our first Christmas here.
- Yeah.
- I was just thinking the same thing.
- I know.
Wow.
Hey!
Dad, we want to dance.
- Okay!
- Come on!
Who needs power when you can
play music from your phone?
- Right?
- What you got?
Yeah, Gabs.
- There we go.
- Yeah.
- Come on, Ro.
- Do one foot in and out.
- Oh, okay, Mike.
- Look at that.
Hey! Shake it low!
- Oh! Oh!
- Get low!
Whoa! Whoa! Hey!
There you go, Mom. It's okay, you're fine.
Hey. Whoa.
- Oh.
- Come on.
- Mmm.
I love this song.
I'd hope so.
You picked it for our wedding.
- Mmm. That's right, I did.
- You did.
- Oh. I've got good taste.
- You do.
Ooh. Oh.
Wow!
- What is going on?
- What?
Seriously?
Who put a remote control fan
on the mantle?
What?
Seriously?
What is happening to this place?
- Crazy.
- I feel that this is my new look.
It turns out the house is still a work
in progress even after all these years.
It's too bad I can't find the guy
who designed the place.
- Oh, wait.
- Touché.
What are you doing?
Is that mistletoe?
Why do I have the feeling
we are being watched?
- Girls?
You know, I feel bad taking your money.
But not bad enough not to take it.
But they're supposed to kiss.
They're supposed to fall in love.
Things are supposed to go back
to how they used to be.
Ro, that's never gonna happen, okay?
It doesn't matter what you do.
You don't know that.
You don't know what I can do.
- Dad's getting re-married.
- You're lying! It's not true.
Mike.
Come on.
It is true, Sprout.
I asked Diane to marry me,
and she said yes.
Why didn't anybody tell me?
Honey, we wanted to.
Our plan was to wait until the new year.
Why?
Because we didn't wanna ruin
your Christmas.
Oh.
Rowena, honey, it's gonna be okay.
But I-I miss our family.
I miss the way it used to be.
I know. I know you do, sweetie.
And it's okay to be sad.
But hey, hey, we all love you.
And this just means
that our family is growing
and there'll be even more people
who love you.
I don't want more people to love me.
Rowena, honey.
- Mike.
- I…
Merry Christmas, sleepyhead.
Don't you wanna get up?
Maybe run a brush through your hair?
Why, Mom? What's the point?
Honey, because it's Christmas.
And you're a kid.
What are you reading?
"A Christmas Carol."
It's about this guy, Ebenezer,
and everyone's giving him a hard time.
But he's not so bad.
He just wants things to be the way
they always were.
Is that what it's about?
Sounds like you need to keep reading.
But not right this minute.
Your father and Diane are here,
so get your butt downstairs. Vámonos.
Guess who decided to join us.
Ro?
Everything okay, Sprout?
Yep, it's Christmas.
The gift that keeps on giving.
Yay.
Ew.
Does anybody else see this?
- ¿Qué?
- Ro is drawing the Mona Lisa.
- Yeah, Hector, I'm sure it's great.
- No, I mean literally.
It's the Mona Lisa.
I'm out.
- Louie! Louie! Louie!
- No!
No.
This tastes delicious.
Oh, ho, ho!
Good morning, Chicago!
It's that day you've all been waiting for.
It's us, Bruce.
This is nice. No, this is going
to go great in the condo.
- It's gonna match our coffee table colors.
- Papi, those socks.
Thank you, Pop!
- Mike, is there any trash over there?
- Oh, yeah.
Yeah. And then smart. And then…
- Under the table.
- Ro! Ro! Hey, come here.
- Rowena!
- Hey, sweetie,
- don't you wanna open your presents?
- Yeah. Sprout, what's the matter?
- I just don't believe in it anymore.
- You don't believe in what, sweetie?
I don't believe in Christmas.
- What?
- Louie, cover your ears.
Rowena, you don't mean that.
Christmas is the most wonderful time
of year.
- Yes.
- Is it, Abuela?
- Really? What's so wonderful about it?
- Um, presents, duh.
- Yeah, Ro.
What about presents?
Uncle Bruce, do you even remember
what you got me last year?
Sure, I do.
- It was a... It was...
- Oh, Rowena.
What'd I get her?
Yeah, I'm sure I loved it
but I can't remember what it was either.
None of us need these presents,
so what's the point
of doing it every year?
Honey, it's not about the presents,
it's about the thought behind them.
And what about all the other great things
about Christmas?
- Like Christmas trees.
- Yeah.
- Yes.
Look at this tree, Uncle Gerry.
If you really think about it,
it's probably sad.
One day, it was in the woods
minding its own business
and then some jerk comes along
and chops it down.
And now it's in our house
and we've covered it with lights
and festive decorations.
How would you like it
if someone brought you into their house
and covered you in lights
and festive decorations?
I wouldn't like it. Not one bit.
Thank you, Louie.
Face it, you guys. Christmas is overrated.
Ro.
Hey, big guy.
I know we haven't chatted in a minute,
but I could really use your help.
Thanks for the Christmas wish,
it's been a lot of fun.
But could you please make it stop now?
Your friend, Rowena.
Hey, Mom?
Can you mail this to the North Pole?
Oh, honey, the post office is closed today
but we can mail it tomorrow.
- Tomorrow. Tomorrow. Tomorrow. Tomorrow.
- No!
No!
Hey, you!
I need you to take back the wish,
you hear me?
I've had enough! Take it back!
Hey, what are you doing up here?
Everyone's downstairs.
What do you care?
Mom and Dad are worried about you.
Don't you care about their feelings?
Nobody asks me about my feelings.
Yeah, well,
you're not the only one going through
a rough time right now, you know.
I-I miss the way things were
just as much as you do.
But you're younger than me, right? So…
you don't remember what it was like.
You don't have to remember
all of the fighting.
But everyone's happier now.
You know, families change.
I'm not happier, okay?
I don't want our family to change.
I know.
And I didn't either.
But in a way, it kind of already did.
The day you were born,
everything changed.
You know, you were new and I...
I definitely didn't like it,
but I saw how happy you made Mom and Dad.
So, I decided to give you a chance,
even though you annoy
the heck out of me most of the time.
You'll always be my little sister.
And I wouldn't change that for anything.
Everything's gonna be okay.
All right? I promise.
I'm sorry I took your laptop.
And your sketchbook.
- You're a really good artist.
- Okay, you don't have to say that.
But thanks.
Come on, let's go downstairs.
Gabby.
I think I'll give new people a chance too.
But only because
I've tried everything else.
Come on.
Okay, Bruce. Okay, Bruce. Do it!
Pumpernickel bread.
It's too big. Make it smaller.
Is that a mariachi band?
- Does that look like a mariachi band?
- It is a mariachi band.
It's a shark!
Doc, it's your favorite!
Mariachi?
Oh, it is a mariachi band! Hey!
What?
- Whoo!
- Whoo-hoo!
Oh, my God!
You see! Hey, hey, it's a mariachi band!
- Did you know it was me?
- I was totally surprised.
Do you wanna be the ghost?
Not really.
Hey, Louie?
Boo!
That was so good!
Let's go downstairs. It's Christmas.
Hang on. Your shoelace is untied.
- Thanks, Rowena.
- You're welcome, Louie.
I got you, you little devil.
Incoming!
Huh? Whoa! Hey!
What is this, a wrestling match?
All right, which one of you is The Rock
and which one of you is John Cena?
- I don't know.
- I'm Rock.
- Over up. Over...
- Yes! Like that. Yes!
- Guess who decided to join us.
- Morning, sleepyhead.
Morning, everyone.
Rowena, Merry Christmas.
Your dad told me
that you made the softball team.
That is amazing!
What position do you play?
Shortstop,
but coach wants me to practice pitching.
That is incredible, sweetie.
Well, then you're going
to especially love your present today.
- Diane, don't ruin it.
- I know.
Well, let's just say it's really
gonna help you out on the team.
Sorry, Sprout. She's just excited
'cause she picked it out herself.
Whoa.
- Diane picked out the glove?
- Yeah.
- Wait. What?
- How did she know?
Cool.
Oh, my little Rowena.
Did you like your sweater?
I made it myself.
We haven't opened presents yet, Mom.
- Oh.
- But I bet I'm gonna love it.
And look what I made you.
It's an herbal tea.
I found it in the kitchen.
It's supposed to be great
for your upset tummy.
- Nice.
- Give it back!
- It's mine now.
Stop. What are you gonna use with it?
Gretchen.
- But that money's for charity!
- Maybe I got a charity of my own.
It's called "Get Over It."
- That's enough, Gretchen.
- And what are you gonna do about it?
That's enough, Gretchen.
And what are you gonna do about it?
It's a Christmas present.
Now give them their money back.
We're ready to learn Judo.
Okay.
A great man once said,
"It is not important to be better
than someone else
but to be better than yesterday."
Is that not true?
- Yes, sensei.
Begin!
Hiyah!
Hiyah! Hiyah!
I'm telling my mommy!
- Yes!
- Whoo!
- I believe this is yours.
- Thank you.
And I believe this is yours. On the house.
Wyatt, take it away.
- What did one plate say to another plate?
- I give up.
Dinner's on me!
Is this your little brother?
Yeah. That's right.
It's Christmas. Why the heck are you guys
out here selling jokes?
It makes us feel good to help others.
That's what Christmas is about.
Daddy says
everyone should do what they can.
Every little bit helps.
Oh, oh, oh!
Goodness! I almost dropped my eggs.
- We wouldn't want that, Mrs. Brown.
- Oh.
- Now, let me help you cross the street.
Nice to see you again!
How're you doing?
Hello.
Oh! Andy, amazing cookies.
Brenda, you can stop checking your phone.
Spoiler alert, he doesn't call.
Hey! Merry Christmas, Will.
Merry Christmas, Elise.
Have fun visiting your parents in Florida.
Who was that?
Oh, Phil, hold my stuff.
What?
Winston, will you...
- That totally would have hit her.
- How'd you know that would happen?
Don't you have a better question,
you know, to ask him?
Right. Marry me?
Yes.
My work here is done.
Hey Santa,
I just want to thank you
for showing me the true meaning of family.
Thanks for the lessons, big guy.
Now, I think I've got some people
to go help.
Jokes for charity. Get your jokes, people.
There's enough for everyone.
Hi. I'd like to buy one joke, please.
- Knock, knock.
- Who's there?
- The interrupting cow.
- Interrupting cow...
Moo!
Come on, Cupcake. I've got tuna.
Was that Rowena?
- Cupcake. Oh, my gosh, it's a miracle!
- Oh!
What's this?
Hello, precious.
I've never... I've never seen it.
It's the best Christmas movie.
Ro, what're you doing?
Oh. Just being helpful.
Wouldn't want anyone to break their neck.
- Thank you!
- Did you hear what she said?
It's the best present
I could ever think of. Good daughter.
Raised right.
Oh.
So?
Diane, these are great.
- Really?
- Told you.
Yay!
Carolina, your father and I
want to give you something very special.
This has been
in our family for generations.
Gracias, mami. Thank you.
I love it. Love it!
Ew!
Come on. Get it, Olive. Get it.
Come on. Get it, Olive. Come. Get it.
Do it! Do it! Do it!
Okay, just be kind, you know?
It's still a work in progress.
Well, here goes nothing.
You can do it, Uncle Gerry.
Hey, you're the funniest person I know.
You got this.
Okay.
So, I'm a lawyer, right?
As you already know.
And the hardest part of being a lawyer
is turning off work mode
when you get home.
Hey, Gerry?
Wait, that's supposed to be me?
- I don't sound nothin' like that.
- Oh, my God!
- Do you mind taking the garbage out?
- You know I don't talk like that.
- Who that is?
- But, Gerry,
I took the garbage out last week.
Objection! Argumentative.
I motion to dismiss!
Whoo!
- Yeah!
- Hey, hey!
- He's pretty good!
- He did good!
What did I tell you?
You killed it. You killed it.
I love you.
Hey.
Thanks, Ro.
Speak for yourself.
I've taken a few art classes in my day.
Yeah, I've seen his work, you guys.
He's a real Picasso.
Merry Christmas, Carolina!
- I baked banana bread.
- Oh, my. Thank you.
You didn't have to do that.
We wouldn't have had the ingredients
if it weren't for your little Rowena.
Is she here? We wanted to say thank you.
Okay, yep, just come in.
Come in. Yeah, sure. She's right... Okay.
Hey, Carolina. I made bread pudding.
I know it's Ro's favorite.
She brought our Cupcake home.
And the best Christmas gift ever.
Two new little babies.
You raised the most wonderful girl.
- Can we say hello?
- Oh. Yeah, okay.
Bread... Bread pudding, okay.
Merry Christmas!
Let me guess, Ro?
If we have a girl,
we're naming her Rowena.
Let's not put the cart before the horse.
- Can we?
- Yep. Just... Yep. Yep. Come in.
Yep. Take that. Okay.
When was she at Winterfest?
Hi!
- Ah.
- Hmm?
Come in.
Hi.
Rowena, do you mind explaining to me
what is happening?
How is any of this possible?
Time is a tricky thing.
A lot can happen in a day.
Well, I g...
Here we go.
Hi.
Hi. Oh. You're having a party.
- Oh.
- Sorry to interrupt.
No, no, no, not at all. How can I help?
I'm Henry. These are my kids.
We just wanted...
Mom, these are my new friends,
Holly and Wyatt.
Come on, guys. I wanna show you
my uncles' new dog.
Hey.
Ro helped them raise money
for the foundation today.
Oh. I'm sorry, the foundation?
It's just a small charity.
The kids lost their mom a while back.
Oh. I'm-I'm so sorry to hear that.
Anyway, we just moved to the neighborhood.
- Welcome.
- Thank you.
I just think it's so nice
the way they've already made friends.
Yeah. Oh, good.
This is my mom.
- Hi, Mom. I'm Henry.
- Hola.
Nice to meet you, Henry.
- Carolina?
- Yeah?
Why are you keeping
our handsome guest in the doorway?
Oh, oh. Yes, come in. Sorry, come in.
Thank you.
Mom.
Okay.
That's so good!
That's hysterical. That's so funny.
Mushroom. I get it. It's a mush, mushroom.
Try my stepmom's kale cookies.
It sounds weird, I know,
but it's surprisingly delicious.
And the green makes it super Christmassy.
- Okay. Thank you.
- Wow, thanks.
Merry Christmas.
I'm the stepmom. I'm her stepmom.
- Can I help? There's so many people.
- Yes.
- Hallelujah!
- All right.
Thank you. We have so many people.
Thank you so much.
Thank you. It's beautiful.
What do you call a room with no doors?
Anyone? Anyone?
A mushroom.
Right?
Who wants cocoa? Do you want some cocoa?
- I want some.
- Yes, please.
Okay. Let's have some cocoa while we cook.
It's a latke, Pop.
Mazel tov!
- Yeah!
- Hey!
Okay, okay, okay.
Give me two of the latkes
with no sour cream.
All right, here we go.
You know what?
You guys can make whatever you want.
- Yes!
- Just use your imagination.
What's up?
What's this?
Ro…
I used my savings.
- A tablet?
- This one doesn't come with knobs.
But, Ro, I didn't get you anything.
You were there for me when I needed you.
I couldn't ask for more.
Or a better big sister.
Merry Christmas, Gabby.
Merry Christmas, Ro.
Come here.
- I love you.
- Love you too.
I'm so glad you all ended up here tonight.
I did a lot today, you guys.
I mean a lot. A lot.
But one thing I haven't done
is thank my family.
Oh.
Rowena, this is so unlike you.
I-I know, it's sappy.
But it's also Christmas, and none of you
will remember this, anyway.
That's why we have cameras, honey.
- Yes!
- Yes, Uncle Bruce!
So, a long time ago someone wise told me
that Christmas isn't only about tradition.
It's about spending time
with the people you care about.
I said that yesterday.
I was getting to that, Mom!
Quit hogging the limelight.
- Oh.
- My bad.
And you were right,
because here we all are,
together…
and I've never been happier.
Oh. I'm gonna cry.
I've seen a lot of Christmases in my time.
I mean, a lot. A lot.
But this one definitely tops the list.
Yeah!
I love you.
- Who's ready for some Christmas carols?
- Yeah!
All right, here we go.
- The Christmas cookies were great.
- Yeah.
Bread pudding looks like mine.
Hi, honey.
Oh. A Christmas Carol.
My favorite. Are you reading this?
I finished it this morning.
What'd you think?
I get why it's a classic.
Some parts were a little scary,
but he needed to go through it.
And why is that?
So that he could become a better person.
Someone who isn't afraid of
letting new people in.
It's never too late for a reset.
How did I get the smartest girl?
- Hey, Mom?
- Hmm?
I had a great Christmas.
Even if you don't remember
any of it tomorrow…
- I'm happy.
- Honey, what are you talking about?
Of course I'll remember it.
But just in case you don't…
I'm still glad we had today.
I'm happy too, Rowena.
Merry Christmas.
All right.
Buenas noches, my little niñita.
Buenas noches, Mama.
Wake up. Wake up.
Thank goodness
we can retire this song until next year!
Louie? Where's your white sheet?
- You wanna play ghost?
- No.
Is it still Christmas?
Christmas was yesterday.
It's over.
Christmas is finally over! Whoo!
Mom!
- Mom?
- Dad?
- Mike!
- Let's check outside.
Good idea.
There you are, Sprout.
We were about to find you to say goodbye.
You're leaving already?
Why? You haven't had enough of us?
I'm so glad you came, Diane.
Oh.
It was so good to see you, Ro.
I can't wait to do this again next year.
What are you guys doing for New Year's?
Or President's Day?
And don't you have
a birthday coming up, Dad?
- Gabby pie, come here. I love you.
- Love you too, Dad.
I love you, Sprout.
See you soon.
- All right.
- Wow!
Later, Louie.
Nice.
- Well, we better get going.
- Okay.
- Bye, you guys. Love you.
- Bye!
- Bye, Diane.
- Bye, Louie.
- Louie, seat belt!
- Thanks for the kale cookies!
I'll send you the recipe.
Thanks, Lina.
You're welcome. See you, Mike!
Bye! Thank you so much!
- Bye!
- Bye, girls!
Hey, who wants breakfast?
- Ooh! Me.
- I do! Yes!
- Chocolate chip pancakes?
- Yes!
Yeah.
- I'll be right there.
- Okay, honey.
Where the heck have you been?
Oh, no.
Uh-uh, uh-uh. Give me a break, kid.
It has been a really, really long day.
Tell me about it.
Mmm. So, did you get through your list?
How'd you know about my list?
I've been known to keep a few of my own.
Nothing fancy like yours, though.
Uh…what's this supposed to be?
The naughty list?
Nah, I prefer to think of it
more like a second chance list.
Deep down even the naughtiest kids
want to be nice.
Some just need a little more time.
Okay. So, how did I do?
Ro?
I better go.
Thanks, Santa.
Ho, ho, ho!
Santa?
Bye, Santa.
Ho, ho, ho!