(dramatic music)
(tapping)
- The tackler flash
coming through.
- Radio, con, bring
the message to con.
(buzzing)
(people chattering)
- [Man] Go, go, go!
Watch your back!
- Hurry.
- I got it.
- Watch your back.
Let's hurry.
- [Man] Here we go, here we go.
- This is it, Stevie.
World War III begins.
And all our wives
are back home in bed
with our best friends.
- Chief, that ain't
good coming from you.
You're married too.
There's certain things
a man doesn't do
and that's one of them.
- Ah, speak for yourself kid.
All's fair in love
and war, right?
(chuckles)
- Advance sequence, make comment
and two's ready for firing.
(chattering)
- Quality control's activated.
- Open number one hatch.
- [Sailor] Open hatch, aye, sir.
(whirring)
- [Radio] Bravo niner,
you're cleared on runway two.
(dramatic music)
One minute 34, one minute 35,
one minute 36, one minute 37.
(tapping)
- [Man] Faster
gentlemen, faster.
- [Radio] 226, 227, 228.
- Hatch four open, sir.
- Very well.
- Nestor, Captain.
- [Radio] 241, 242, 243,
244, 245, 246, 47, 48.
- System's ready in this test.
Have your men stand down, Arie.
- Aye aye, sir.
- [Man] Secure from
battle stations.
- [Man] Just a test, boys.
- Nice going, chief.
Broke three minutes
for the first time.
- Anyone else still the
same place to get laid,
right, skipper?
(laughter)
- [Girl] No, no!
Hey, no.
(laughter)
- Hey, put me down!
- No, we're not going to.
- [Girl] No way!
- Put him down.
Oh!
Oh no, how many
times have I told you
to stay away from your
daddy's car, you bad boy?
Go on.
Look at you, you're filthy.
I'll have to wash
all this again.
Look at him strut.
Just like his father.
(laughter)
(hammering)
Hey.
Can I get you something?
- Um.
I'm Linda Bellamy.
- How you doing?
- I'm Lee's wife.
- How, how can I help you?
- Well I guess,
I guess I just needed
to talk to someone.
I guess to you, um.
Has Johnny written you?
- Johnny never writes.
- He doesn't write me either.
- I see.
How long has this been going on?
- He loves me.
And I love him.
And I'm gonna marry him.
- Want a drink?
Hmm?
- No.
Got a job?
Did you ever have a job?
How about high school?
Did you finish high school?
- I haven't had time
for all of that.
- Well, you better start
'cause I don't think your
husband's gonna be giving you
a lot of money if you're
running out on him.
And then there's the,
uh, housing allotment
and child support
for our four kids.
- Mom.
Mommy.
Hey, mom.
Noah's hogging the hose.
She won's let me spray.
- This is Michael, our son.
Michael say hello to the lady.
- Hi.
(phone rings)
(sighs)
- That's, uh...
That's probably Lee.
I told him I was coming here.
Look, I'm sorry, okay.
I'm sorry I bothered you.
Just, just, uh...
Tell him I went shopping, okay?
I went shopping at the exchange.
- Control, this is sonar,
we have a live one.
Sounds like an Ivan Victor
Class contact bearing 155,
range 1,000 yards and closing.
- How the hell's
he gotten so close?
- New bearing, one niner zero,
distance 800 yards,
still closing.
- Break ship for ultra quiet.
Officer of the deck, make
your new depth 800 feet.
- New depth 800
feet, aye aye, sir.
- [Radio] Break
ship, ultra quite.
- Ultra quite.
- Contact all bears, one
niner one, ring stat.
- Sonar.
Patch audio into
the control room.
Let's all hear what
Ivan sounds like.
- He's blowing his
full in tanks, captain.
He's still closing.
- [Radio] 550 yards and closing.
- Son of a bitch
is gonna nail us.
- Listen, Stevie.
Do you want to hear the
captain wet his pants?
- [Radio] 450 yards.
400 yards.
350 yards, still closing.
- [Man] Sparks, get the attack
cyper ready to transmit.
- All cued up, sir.
- [Man] Looks like
we're cued up, captain.
- [Radio] 200 yards.
150 yards.
100 yards.
50 yards.
(sinister music)
- Okay, tape apes,
another victory at sea.
- It's like Ivan never
even knew we were here.
Almost rammed us 'cause
he couldn't hear us
in his own noise.
Sounds like the
freeway at rush hour.
- Yeah, if it weren't the enemy,
I'd almost feel sorry for him.
- [Man] Unbelievable.
- Let's take it
down to 1,000 feet.
Get under the thermal climb.
- Helm, all head 2/3.
Let's take her
down to 1,000 feet.
(buzzing)
- [John] Let's have
the documents checked,
the full security lockdown.
- [Woman] So why
don't you leave him?
- Why did I marry
him is the question.
I knew I was getting into
the first minute I
laid eyes on him.
He's the only man
besides my grandfather
who's as smart as
he thinks he is.
Johnny's the first guy I...
I met that made me
feel like I was...
On the inside track
going somewhere.
Now I don't think I'm
smart enough for him.
- Oh come on,
don't give me that.
He's running around.
He's got an itch
he can't scratch.
That's not smart, that's horny.
(laughs)
- He's always horny.
I don't know what he's gonna
do, what he's thinkin',
what he wants.
I like it.
It's exciting.
I don't know, sometimes I think
there's something
really wrong with me.
- So what are you gonna do?
- Kill him.
(laughs)
- Then what?
- He wants me to wear those
red panties he gave me.
(laughs)
I'm gonna.
- What's so funny, Mom?
(laughs)
- [Barbara] Nothin'.
(upbeat band music)
- Hey!
- [Man] Sir!
(laughter)
(ship horn blaring)
- Baby!
Well that's a hell of
a way to treat a sailor
just home from the wars.
- Maybe.
- Come on, give us a kiss.
- I don't think so.
- Well now that you've
proven yourself to the boys,
let's talk about the girls.
- Okay, let's.
- Linda Bellamy ring a bell?
- [John] Lee's wife.
- Come on, Johnny, I think
you can do better than that.
- I honestly don't know
what you're talking about.
- Well there must be
something you remember.
She certainly remembers you.
- Are you crazy?
She's a zero.
- [Barbara] Well that's
never stopped you before.
- Come on, Barbara, I
never went near her.
Who told you this?
- She did.
- Well wait a minute,
wait a minute.
I know what she's doing.
Lee told me she's been trying
to get him to quit the Navy.
That's why she came to you.
She's just trying
to make him jealous.
Hey, come on, come on.
You don't buy that
crap, are ya, huh?
- You have a really
bad track record.
- We've been apart too much.
I'm gonna get shore duty
so we can be together more.
- Really?
- Yeah, I want to
see more of the kids,
take those picnics
like we used to.
Move up, get a commission,
maybe like Art, huh?
- Damn you.
(engine rumbling)
- Hey look, you
guys, he's coming!
Come on.
- Hurry!
- I want to see Daddy.
- Come on.
- Look, hon, uh...
Art's in town, he
sent me a message.
I'm meeting him for a drink.
- It's your first night home.
- Look, Barb, I gotta meet Art.
I gotta borrow some money,
try to keep this place going.
Maybe he can bring
some guys from his ship
over drinking some night.
Hey.
I'll be home early.
We'll make a night of it.
- You could at least
say hello to the kids.
- I won't be long.
- Bye.
- He's coming, he's coming!
(engine rumbling)
(laughter)
- Hey, babe.
Bring us two more
doubles, will you?
Scotch with my name on
it and keep 'em coming.
Hey, put your money up, Art.
Charleston's my port.
The thirst is my game, right?
Hey.
Nice buns, don't you think, Art?
Honey, with your body, you
know what'd look good on you?
- What?
- Me.
- Thank you, Johnny.
(laughs)
- How's the bar doing?
- Well, the bar's doing alright.
You know, we need to expand.
You need to put a
little more money in it,
another thousand at least.
- Rita's already complaining
about the first thousand.
- Ah, forget the bitches, right?
Here's to us, the Walker boys.
Listen, Art.
You gotta have a
vision of it, man.
I mean, I'd like for
it to be a place that
Dad would want to drop
into for a few beers
and sit at the bar
and shoot the breeze
with all the old geezers,
play the big radio announcer.
You remember, uh, this is Johnny
Walker, the night stalker,
WJZA Scranton PA.
These are my two sons.
This is Arthur and
Johnny Walker, Jr.
(chuckles)
After a few rounds,
he'd start buying shots
for the whole bar.
- Yeah, it sounds
like Dad, all right.
Johnny, listen, um.
A thousand's a lot
for me right now.
- Having fun?
- She gets off at 11.
She's got a girlfriend,
real nice too.
Hey, Irene, why don't you ask
Bobbie for my brother here
and we'll make an
evening of it, huh?
- You two couldn't
afford us, sailor boy.
- Whew! (chuckles)
- All right, sailor.
What'd you learn today?
Tell me something new.
Tell me something I don't know.
- [Girl] I know
something, let me.
- Come on, girls, bed time.
- Aw, Mom, do we
have to go to bed?
- No, no, yes, you have to.
- I don't want to go to bed now.
- I don't care.
- But I'm the oldest.
- [Barbara] Doesn't matter.
- [Art] What about Barbara,
can't she make it good?
- Ah, Barbara's up
to her butt in kids.
She don't know what
a good time is.
All she wants to do is
go on family picnics.
I mean, look.
Place called a Bamboo Bar has
gotta have some juice smashes,
gotta be the kinda place
people want to come to
and hang out and get loose,
you know what I mean?
Barbara is not
your party person.
All I ever wanted was a little
money making opportunity
and I got the only bar
in the whole country
that's losing money.
Now what the hell am I gonna do?
- Hold on, hold on, you
got a little, Johnny.
But you gotta get something else
going on the side besides girls.
Find something to generate
a little extra cash.
Find something else on the side.
- Yeah, well how about you?
What's your scam,
selling your hair?
- Listen, you know when I
was stationed up in Groton,
we knew a guy who had
connections with the mob.
He'd buy all the electrical
pumps I could order.
I used to deliver a
pump end of every month
just to make ends meet.
- A pump at the end of
every month? (chuckles)
That's about your speed.
(laughs)
These girls like a
little feed first
and then they like to go
somewhere and work it off.
Hey, Irene!
- Later, Johnny,
have a good night.
- [Man] President Lyndon
Johnson reviews comment
on today's anti-war protest
as police estimated the
crowd at no more than 23,000.
While organizers--
- You can sleep with Michael.
(door slams)
- Stat at attention, sailor.
- Yes, sir.
- Tell me what you
learned today, sailor.
Tell me something new,
something I don't know.
- I missed you, Dad.
(sighs)
- It's you and me, sailor.
You and me against the bitches.
You understand?
(police siren blaring)
You go back to sleep.
- Yes, sir.
- [John] Let me in, Barb.
Open the damn door.
(thuds)
(gasps)
- You're a liar.
You weren't out
with Art this late.
I know where you were.
I'm sick of this bar.
I'm sick of being broke.
I'm sick of you running
around with all our money.
- Yeah, maybe there's a
message in there somewhere.
- You know what?
Beer man cut us off today.
You know what he wanted to do?
He wanted to take out his
bill in trade with me.
- [John] For that kinda money,
maybe you shoulda
slept with him.
Hey!
- Is that what
you want me to do?
You want me to
whore for you, huh?
Well if I'm gonna get a pimp,
I'm gonna get someone
who'll bring a little money
into this house.
- Damn it!
- [Barbara] Go on, run away!
(door slams)
- Come here, Mike.
(birds chirping)
- [Woman] Registered
materials delivery.
Who's the custodian officer?
- I'll take care of this
one, you go on home.
(sinister music)
(keys clanging)
(grunts)
You're a dead man
anyway, Walker.
You're just too damn
dumb to know it.
(clacks tongue)
Hey, drop me off here, will you?
(birds chirping)
(engine rumbling)
(woman chattering)
That was dumb.
Keep it simple, stupid.
- Yeah.
- I need to talk to
somebody in security.
Do you speak English?
Take me to the
director of security.
KGB.
- Follow me.
- Why did you come here?
- I'm...
An American naval officer.
- And why did you come here?
- I'm interested in selling
classified United States
documents to the Soviet Union.
I want to sell top secrets.
Valuable military information.
I brought along a sample.
This is a current key
list of the KL-47.
If you know anything,
you know what that is.
- Wait here, please.
- Why isn't this signed?
All K lists must be signed.
This is worthless.
- It's just a routine slip.
It doesn't mean anything.
Half of them are never signed.
We have too many
to sign them all.
We only sign the top one.
- I must know your name.
- My name's James.
James Harper like the whisky.
- I must see some
official identification.
- Why is this necessary?
It's a straight business deal.
You want it or not?
- Please do not worry, we
will protect your identity.
We desire this document
you have brought us.
We want more such documents.
We welcome you, dear friend.
So please, let me have
your identification.
Thank you, Mr. Harper.
Please have a seat.
Please, please, sit down.
- Look, uh.
Can't we hurry this up?
I gotta get back to the base.
- Please sit down.
It is necessary that
we proceed slowly.
- Like hell it is.
I got the midnight watch.
I can't be late without calling.
I got a long drive
back to Norfolk.
I want to talk about the
money right now or I walk.
- That wouldn't be
wise, Mr. Harper.
(speaks foreign language)
- We are making arrangements
for your secure departure.
I'm sorry it has taken so long,
but there are many
precautions one must take.
Please, sit.
Now is your coming
here politically
or financially motivated?
- It's purely financial,
I need the money.
- $1,000 in $50 bills.
- Where are we going?
- Shh.
Your coat and your hat, please.
- Hi, Miss Walker.
- Oh my gosh, it's so big!
- I know.
- So shiny.
(children chattering)
- Hi!
- So what do you think?
(sighs)
You like it?
- Oh my god.
Oh my god.
- Come on, it's great.
- Look at this.
(giggling)
- Nice, huh?
- [Girl] Oh my god!
- Oh, don't go out
there, it's not safe!
- It's all right, it's
got a safety rail.
Come on, let me show
you the kitchen.
The rugrats can eat over here.
(children chattering)
- [Girl] Look at this room!
- Our furniture's gonna
be terrible in here.
It's so beat up looking.
- Well we'll just get
all new stuff, huh?
I'll wait on you to get here,
give you something to do.
- This kitchen is huge!
- Yeah, so now you can do all
that fancy Italian cooking
you've been bragging about.
Whatever it takes, uh,
here's 1,000 to get you started.
I want you to fix this place
up any way you want it.
Get yourself and the kids
dressed up too, okay?
It's not enough, you
just ask for more.
- This is much more than
your moving allowance.
How can we afford this?
- Don't worry about it.
I got a great deal
on this place and...
I got a second job.
I'm gonna be making
some extra cash,
running cars from
here up to Washington
for a rental agency.
It's all under the
table, there's no taxes,
so don't say
anything to anybody,
not even the kids, okay?
- Are you sure it's okay?
- Barbara, don't start
raining on the picnic.
Come on.
(children giggling)
You get these rugrats
under control.
We got to start teaching
this kids some manners.
- Let's ride the
elevator again, Daddy.
- He's into it already,
aren't you, kid?
Come on, let me show
you to your room.
You're too old to be sleeping
with the bitches now.
Come on.
(chattering)
- Hello, my dear friend.
Do you enjoy the view?
How was the trip from Norfolk?
Was there much rain?
- Nothing unusual.
- Have you seen any
cars more than once?
Think carefully.
- No, I wasn't followed,
I doubled back five times.
- Did you bring
a package for me?
Did you follow
the shopping list?
- Yes.
It's in the shopping bag.
- First give it to me.
I have an envelope for you.
We agreed to a monthly salary,
$4,000 a month as
long as you continue
to obtain the KL-47 key lists.
In addition, you will be paid
extra for all specific items.
You will never receive
less than $2,000 a month
as long as you have access to
crypto material of any sort.
- Okay.
What do I have to do to earn
the extra above the 4,000?
What specific items
you interested in?
- Not too fast.
Let's first talk a little
about security, my friend.
I urge you to invest this
money wisely and quietly,
not spend it lavishly on
expensive cars and clothes.
An American family sedan
is an excellent car
and quiet the nerves of the FBI.
- I've got all the
car I need right now.
Look, don't worry about me.
I've got a little
business on the side.
I can cover this money easy.
- And your wife?
Is she a reliable woman?
It's quite possible she
may become suspicious.
Is she a loyal partner
to you and your marriage?
- My wife does what
I tell her to do.
Come on, let's get
down to business.
I got a long drive
back to Norfolk.
Let's go down your list.
- We are very
interested in the KW-70
absolute cryptographic system.
We will pay bonuses
on any key lists
and technical
manuals on this item.
- What kind of bonuses?
- $1,000 extra.
If you can get a complete
month's set of key lists
within two weeks
before the next drop.
- Oh.
That could be difficult.
But I'll tell you.
If I get 100%, I want
double, 8,000 a month.
- Agreed, my friend.
It's too dangerous to
meet again face to face.
We will not meet
for a long time,
but we will become
great friends.
We will write each other
letters in the drop packages.
This is a miniature Rota reader.
Memorize the instructions,
then destroy them.
It will enable you to read the
circuit boards in the KL-47.
Let no one see this device.
Anyone with crypto clearance
will recognize this instantly
as decryption equipment.
- Just don't worry about it.
- If there's any emergency and
you want to see me at once,
the instructions will tell
you how to arrange a meeting.
- Wait, wait a minute.
Uh...
What about the pill?
- A pill, what pill?
- Well aren't you gonna give
me some kind of suicide pill
or something in
case I get arrested?
- We don't do such things.
We want you to know
we're very concerned
about your welfare.
We know the
difficulties you face.
So many people who come to us
help us for a couple of
years and then retire.
We hope you will be one of them.
Goodbye, my friend.
(chuckles)
(squeals)
- Mom, Daddy's coming!
- All right, um, finish
setting the table.
Cynthia, watch Michael.
Laura, help me get the
appetizers out of the fridge.
Come on, let's go.
- I'm home.
- [Barbara] Hi.
- Well hello, darling.
(giggling)
- Laura, bring the appetizers.
- Hey, kids, hello, buddy.
- You can serve
your dad now, honey.
- Thank you, darling.
Just leave the tray.
Go find the other kids.
Here's to you, Barb.
(glasses clink)
Mm!
You make a great martini,
I'll say that for you.
Sit down.
Let's talk.
(giggles)
You know, I really like what
you've done with the place.
It looks great.
- Thanks.
- Kids too, they're not
rugrats anymore. (laughs)
They're 100% improved.
I think we should celebrate.
I think we oughta have a party.
Get a jump on Easter
and have a big blowout.
What do you say?
- No, I--
- I'll get one of
those new hi-fi systems
and we can invite
all the neighbors too
and then we can turn that sucker
up as loud as we want, huh?
- I don't think we should be
throwing our money around,
Johnny, we just barely moved in.
- I told you not to
worry about the money.
Just relax and enjoy it.
I don't understand you.
At first you complain
about no money
and then you don't
want to spend it.
Give us a taste.
I've been thinking about
getting a little boat,
taking up sailing.
Got my eye on this 24-footer
down at the marina.
You know...
You should have a hobby, Barb.
Why don't you start taking
movies of Mike and the girls.
Here, here's 500.
That'll get you started.
Just tell me what you need.
- What I really need is
to know what's going on.
All those $50 bills can't
be just from running cars.
(laughs)
- Hey.
The days of powdered milk
and resale shoes are over.
That's all you need to know.
Here.
I'm finished.
- It's not exactly an answer.
- Look.
These guys I'm working for are
local scuzzy mafia, alright?
They're trying to go legit,
so they're working under
the table a little bit.
It's no big deal.
So the less you
know, the better.
Or maybe you don't want
the family together.
Maybe you want us
out in the street.
Here.
- [Barbara] All right, Johnny.
(gloomy music)
(tapping)
- I'm going now, John.
The only thing hot is this pink
on the recent
Arctic anti-sub ops.
Get it out of
priority distribution.
- Right, Captain, and one thing.
I'd like to put in a request
for some tech manuals
on the new KW-7.
We're just not up to date
on all the modifications.
- Okay, put it on my desk.
I'm off.
My wife will kill me
if I miss dinner again.
It's PTA night.
(laughs)
- Hey, Sampson.
Run this through the other
KL-47 for me, will you?
Make photocopies of
all this raw data here
so we calm ourselves.
I think this one's
garbling again.
Something's wrong with it.
- [Sampson] Why me, chief?
I got all these
pinks to get out.
- Oh and I got my
eye on you, Sampson.
You're the one of
these tape apes
who can talk and scratch
himself at the same time.
I'm gonna make a hot
runner out of you.
You're gonna be
chief and thanking me
before you know it, buddy.
- Skipper's a hot run, ain't he?
Guy can transmit faster
than he can talk.
That's somethin'.
- Yeah, well let me know if
they ever decipher his bull.
(sinister music)
(beeping)
- Trash bag.
Documents drop.
(whistling)
- Barbara, come
in here a minute.
Barbara!
Where the hell are you?
- That's a good question.
Working late again?
- Maybe.
- It's a funny thing
about work, isn't it?
What'd you say your work was?
(chuckles)
- You tell me.
You've obviously
been checking it out.
- Well a wife's supposed to
care about her husband's work.
Isn't that what you always said?
- Some things have changed.
- Document drops?
Emergency procedures?
They sure have.
- Look.
I'm just selling some
routine information
to some business contractors.
It's no big deal.
- Is that why they pay
you in stack of $50 bills?
- What do you care?
It's just business.
Relax, will ya?
You got your life, I got mine.
- Is that it?
My life is separate from yours?
Is that the way it's gonna
be from now on, Johnny?
- You tell me.
- What about the kids?
What about the family?
What about me?
What you're doing is dangerous.
- What am I doing?
- You're stealing secrets from
work and you're selling them.
- Give me a break.
- You're a liar!
You're a traitor!
- Shut up.
Somebody might hear you
and take you seriously.
- You're a spy for the Russians!
You're a spy!
Traitor, Johnny Walker!
(screams)
(gloomy music)
- Barbara.
I'm sorry.
We were snowed under with debts.
We woulda lost everything.
We put it in the bar.
I just grabbed the first thing
that I could to bail us out.
I could have left, I could
have just walked away from you.
That would have been
easier, but I didn't.
I stayed and I got it
together here for all of us
because I want this
family to stay together.
Are you listening to me?
How can you say that
I don't care about you
when I'm doing all of this
so that you and I can have the
kind of life that we deserve?
- They're gonna
send you to jail.
- Look, I'm just doing it
till we can get
back on our feet.
We'll get us a little
house by the ocean,
nice school for the kids.
That's all we need, right?
And that'll be the end of it.
It's just paper.
That's all it is.
I mean, they call it a secret,
but thousands of people see it.
It's just a game.
People buy it, people sell it,
but it doesn't make a
damn bit of difference.
All that matters is us.
It's not easy for me.
I'm scared.
But I can't just stop.
That's why I haven't
made love to you
and that's why I
haven't been home.
- Why didn't you tell me?
- I didn't want to scare you.
Sometimes at night
I just watched you
while you were sleeping.
It's the only thing that
kept me from going crazy.
- Don't lie to me.
- I'm not.
I love you, I've
always loved you.
But you gotta know that if uh...
If they catch me,
I'm a dead man.
If it happens, I...
I'd just like for
you to take the kids
and go up to Maine,
stay with your sister.
- I couldn't stand
it if you got caught.
- Honey, I gotta make one
more delivery and that's it.
We're gonna transfer to the
West Coast or something,
just put it all behind us.
(moans)
Don't leave me.
Help me.
- Depth steady at 60
feet, surface secure.
ESM and UHF Mast deploy, sir.
- All ready with a
Zulu flash, Davis.
Cue to transmit, sir.
- Transmit.
- Skipper, we have
a submerged contact
on our port valve on
2,000 yards and closing.
He sounds like an
Ivan Alpha Class.
- Prepare to dive.
Make your depth 1,000 feet.
Right standard runner.
- Prepare to dive.
(buzzing)
- ESM and UHF Mast lowered.
All secured for dive, sir.
- Dive.
- [Man] 50 degrees angle
down on the planes.
All ahead full dive.
- Make your depth 1,000
feet and balanced out.
- Skipper, he's
going down with us.
- [Man] What?
- [Man] He's sitting in
our right coordinates.
He's almost ahead of us.
- That's impossible.
Definitely a
simulated attack, sir.
I think he knew
exactly where and when
our transmissions
were to take place.
He was waiting for
us right on position
and I think he knew our
standard evasive tactics.
He followed us right down
through the front and behind.
- What are the numbers, Harry?
The raw data?
- 56 encounters with
Russian submarines
and 50 spotted in the
last survey period.
318 in this survey period.
That's an increase of uh--
- That's a damn increase in
the size of our underwear
if Ivan can get his subs
into our pants like this.
Any Soviet technical advance
would have to be extremely
complex to cover this.
I don't think it's a
technical advantage.
I think they're getting
their information
from somewhere else.
Anybody want to
argue this with me?
- I do.
There is one area where a
single technical advance
could give the
Soviets an advantage
in all areas all at once.
That's codes and decryption.
- If they've got the
advantage on us there,
they won't tip their hand
unless we surprise them.
We need a kind of
countermeasure we can undertake
to prove Ivan's
reading our codes.
(upbeat band music)
- [Man] I gotta go.
(chattering)
(ship horn blares)
- Smile, will ya?
You look good when you smile.
- Don't much feel like smiling.
- Hey, listen to me.
I got free of all that stuff.
I told you I'm clean.
I'm lily white, just another
sailor doing his job.
- Why do I feel so nervous?
- 'Cause you know you've got
to go fix up our new house.
You gotta make it beautiful,
get kids to school
and live the
California life, hmm?
- [Barbara] Hey.
- Keep the home
fires burning, baby.
(ship horn blares)
- Kay!
Kay, honey.
- How'd you find out?
- I was just seeing
Johnny off, what happened?
- Jimmy was killed in Vietnam.
We're, we're taking
him home now.
(solemn music)
(rumbling)
- As the death toll is
climbing near to it,
90 kilometers west
of reaching 75
for a total of 152.
The offensive, which began as
a search and destroy mission
of the 173rd airborne
division continues to battle.
(birds chirping)
(banging)
(gloomy music)
- Liar.
Liar, Johnny.
(sinister music)
(fire crackling)
(sighs)
(sobs)
(upbeat band music)
- [Man] Liberty
uniform, rest white.
- Get ready to open your bags.
Get all that port out of
there, I'm not kidding.
- Just the briefcase.
- I have permission
to come ashore, sir.
- Hi, Mr. Walker.
- I didn't know you were
a smoker, Mr. Walker.
- Well, I like one afterwards,
if you know what I mean, sir.
- Well you have a good one.
- I certainly
intend to try, sir.
Hello, babe.
I'm home.
What's that you got
in your hand, Barb?
You gonna shoot somebody?
Your husband maybe
just back from Vietnam.
Don't let the booze
make you reckless.
I see you had your day
with all the money.
What in the hell
did you do with it?
You couldn't have drank that
much, you'd be dead by now.
- I want a divorce.
- Well that's a
nice welcome home.
How 'bout a kiss too?
- I know you're still spying.
I can't stand it anymore.
I don't need you anymore.
I got a job.
- A job?
You're just a piece of thirst.
Who gave you a job?
- I'm working as a
cashier in a restaurant.
- Great.
That's about your speed.
How do you make it
through the day?
I mean look at you.
Your hand's shaking 'cause
you want a drink so bad.
- You made me what
I am, you bastard.
- All right then.
Go ahead.
Pull the trigger.
Go ahead, shoot me.
Shoot me!
(gun fires)
You want to learn how to shoot?
I'll teach ya!
(gun fires)
- [Girl] Come on, run, hurry!
- There won't be
anybody saying anything
about spying to anyone,
will there, huh?
Huh?
(gun fires)
- No.
- They're trying to kill us.
We gotta get out of here.
- I'm not going.
I'm not going.
(gun fires)
(sobs)
- I think you need a
drink, don't you, babe?
(whimpers)
You can hardly wait, can you?
Just hear this.
No divorce.
It's not good for my
security clearance.
Now let's go to bed.
We'll have a little
homecoming party.
Here's to it.
(chuckles)
I brought you a little
present from Hong Kong.
(ship horn blares)
Women in the Navy will never
serve on ships during combat.
That's the bottom line.
Go into advanced communications.
You already got clearance now
to classified material, right?
Afternoon, Admiral Murnett!
You want to go
party tonight, huh?
- Who was that clown, Admiral?
- That's Johnny Walker.
Thought the Navy would
have been smart enough
to retire him by now
or court marshal him.
He worked for me on the Jones.
I tell you, on a 90-day
underwater cruise,
you gotta have a
joker like Walker.
He says all the things
behind your back
that the men want to say.
He's an ongoing
low-grade verbal mutiny.
I used to call him
the great ventilator.
- I'm not sure we need a
Navy full of jokers, sir.
- By the book all the way.
I think I hear an Aplas
talking there, Sam.
- That's affirmative, sir.
- We're calling it code
name Scorpion, Ben.
- Scorpion, yeah, seems like
an appropriate name to me, sir.
- If the Russians run when we
stage the nuclear accident,
we'll know for sure
they've cracked our codes.
- I hope we're wrong, sir.
- So do I, Ben.
- Sir.
That personnel
file you requested
is from Walker, John A. CW03.
It doesn't register with the
records so I put a trace on it.
- Something about this Walker
always seems to
ring a little off.
How about his, uh, clearance?
- Here's the security
clearance update roster, sir.
Mr. Walker's clearance
is due for renewal, sir.
- Let's get the paperwork in
for his background
security check.
Send a copy over to staff
in Talleham's office.
I'd like to know his
efficiency rating.
- [Man] Reactor scram, reactor
scram, prepare to surface.
- Nuclear accident report.
Z Flash to Hannibal
for immediate aid.
- Sir, the nuclear
accident report
has been received
on the Hannibal.
- Now we'll see how good
a fisherman Burnett is.
- [Man] They have the reactors.
Cut the engines.
Z Flash SOS.
(speaking foreign language)
- In this there reports a
surge in roosky radio activity.
(speaking in foreign language)
- [Man] They're moving
some of the alphas down now
to check out the
radiation levels.
- Sir, the Sorbitral
has changed course
to intersect with the Hannibal.
- Well, boys, looks like
we've got our answer.
Ivan isn't reading our minds.
He's reading our mail.
(bubbling)
- The security in
this place stinks.
I mean it doesn't even
come up to the quality
of the security in
a convenience store.
They throw these bags around
so that half the seals on
the code packs are broken.
There, patch these up with tape
before you distribute
them, honey,
otherwise Skipper's
gonna have a hemorrhage.
So, Edith, who's the new
girl with all the tears?
- She's the admiral's yeoman.
She just left her husband.
Forget it, John,
she's not your type.
She thinks with her brain,
she doesn't sit on them.
- Huh, well maybe we can
help her out with that.
Why don't you fix me
up on a little date?
- No way.
Oh incidentally,
somebody up above must
have caught your act.
They flagged your file.
You must be up for some
hot new assignment.
I couldn't find your file.
It's probably up in payroll.
Oh, oh, I forgot to tell you.
They want your
clearance up to date.
- Hey, here she comes.
Do your thing.
How about tonight, huh?
- Why don't you just
think of him as a loner?
Just the right guy for awhile
till you get your own
little red wagon fixed.
Hey, Johnny, there you are.
Take two and call
me in the morning.
- Hi, ladies.
- Hi.
- Give me a double with
my name on it, Joe,
and pour them again
for these ladies.
- Oh no, not for me,
I've got to get home.
- Home?
That's where you go when
you got nothing else to do.
- Or if you feel a
headache coming on.
I will see you guys later.
- Edith, don't do this to me.
- It'll be fine.
Bye.
- Take care of that
headache, Edith.
So.
Edith tells me you've been
having a real rough time.
- Yeah, I guess.
(siren blaring)
(guns firing)
(yelling)
- You're gonna get me my
file, aren't you, sweetheart?
Welcome aboard the
USS Johnny Walker.
(sinister music)
(clicking)
We're in business.
Hey, Jerry.
Our Navy cruises are
never like this, huh?
(laughs)
Hey, did you see that
movie, uh, Easy Rider?
- Oh yeah.
- That guy, uh, Jack Nicholson,
the straight lawyer guy.
(laughs)
- Do you remember when he gets
stoned for the first time?
Man, that was the best
part of that movie.
- No, no.
The best part was they
cut a straight guy
in on a crooked deal
and he jumped at it.
That's the best
part, he goes for it.
I mean think about it.
Put yourself in his place.
You hear the deal and you think
hey, would I go for
something like that?
I mean, that's the point
of the whole movie.
Guys like us, would we go for it
if they laid one on
us out of the blue?
- One time score?
Sure, I'd be up for
that in a minute
and I know what to do with
the money too, believe me,
not like those
dudes in the movie.
- Yeah, well...
I got a one shot deal for you.
Listen close.
I'm only gonna say this once
and if you don't go for
it, you just say so.
We won't ever talk
about it again ever.
All good things are simple.
Classified information is money.
That's it.
If you don't take
advantage of it,
you're just throwing
all that money away.
- Throwing it away?
What do you mean?
- Classified information is
valuable to one of our allies.
It's like that guy
Nicholson in the movie.
It's not exactly legal, but
doesn't damage our security any
if this ally gets it.
Makes it safer probably.
Cuts out the chances
of the mistakes.
- What ally?
- Well I got this
contact in Europe.
Buyer wants to know our
strategic intentions
and sometimes it's
just not polite to ask
even if you are one
of our best allies.
But my contact tells
me Israel is the buyer.
- Israel.
I wouldn't even think of that.
Listen, John, tell
me more about this.
See, I'm working on all the
latest high-tech hardware,
but I think the Israelis
can handle it, you know?
(seagull cawing)
(phone ringing)
(knocking)
- [Sam] Come in.
- Sir.
I got a call from
intelligence section, sir,
that security investigation
you were looking into,
Walker, John. A, Junior.
- Thanks, Trudy.
What'd they turn up?
- They didn't, sir.
They have no record
of any recent update
in Mr. Walker's clearance.
- Well according to
this his clearance
was in April this year.
Must be some mistake.
This isn't the pink copy.
They usually send the pink
copy from NIS, don't they?
- I believe so, yes, sir.
- Schedule Walker.
I want to see him ASAP.
(moans)
- Yeah, that's it.
Oh, you've got great hands.
Oh, I'm all out.
Go get me another one out
of the freezer, beautiful,
and put another one in there.
Double time!
- It's my turn now.
- Oh yeah, what did you
learn today, sailor?
Tell me something new,
something I don't know.
- I can sing.
- Oh, what can you sing, huh?
How about the Star
Spangled Banner?
- That's corny.
- What's the
matter, you too good
to sing our national anthem?
Come on, sing it.
♪ Oh say can you see
♪ By the dawn's early light
♪ What so proudly we hailed
♪ At the twilight's
last gleaming
♪ Whose broad stripes
and bright stars
♪ Thru the perilous fight
♪ O'er the ramparts we watched
♪ Were so gallantly streaming
♪ And the rocket's red glare
♪ The bombs bursting in air
♪ Gave proof through the night
♪ That our flag was still there
(phone ringing)
(tapping)
(buzzing)
(clears throat)
- Captain Lennox will
see you now, Mr. Walker.
- Chief Warrant Officer
Johnny Walker, Jr.
reporting as ordered, sir.
Chief Warrant Officer
Walker, John A., Jr.
reporting as ordered, sir.
- Stand at ease, Mr. Walker.
Seems to be some discrepancy
in your security clearance.
There's no record of
your recent clearance
in the intelligence section.
Your file's just photocopied.
We're trying to trace
the original with NIS.
- You know the Navy, sir.
It could be anywhere.
I wouldn't worry about it.
In fact, if I were you
I'd just ignore it.
- Ignore it?
You better start worrying
about it, mister,
'cause I'm going to get
to the bottom of it.
- Well, I doubt that it'll
make much difference, sir.
See, this is my request
for 20-year retirement.
It's all approved and in order.
The medical clearance is
attached, as you can see.
With my cumulated leave time,
I'll be retiring from active
duty at the end of this month.
- That'll be all, Mr. Walker.
- Thank you, sir.
You want a divorce?
Okay, I'll give you a divorce.
I'm not only divorcing you,
I'm divorcing all
your damn brats too!
(shattering)
Just take them all,
go up to Maine,
that's a good place for you!
I don't want any
visitation rights.
Take them out!
Go to Maine!
You like it up there, don't you?
You want to do your
own thing, bitch?
You do it!
Just stay out of my life.
Until you can get
yourself together enough
to get out of here,
I'm moving out.
I can't stand your face anymore.
So you stay out of my way.
(banging)
Michael, front and center!
(crickets chirping)
Stop that.
Tears are for bitches.
- I don't want you to go.
- I'm gonna tell
you a secret, okay?
You gotta promise not to
tell the bitches, right?
Right?
- Right, Dad.
- I'm gonna give you my
private phone number.
You call me any time you want
collect, whenever you want.
Are you ready to receive?
- I got nothing
to write it down.
- Right hell, you
remember it, sailor.
You're not gonna get in the Navy
if you can't remember
a seven-digit number.
It's 555-6423.
- I'm not coming with you.
I'm not going to Maine.
I'll go live with Dad.
- Just a minute, Laura.
- Leave me alone!
- Don't you fight me!
- Stop it, stop it!
- In case the phones are tapped,
we better have code names.
I'll be Tiger Breath.
You be Wild Man.
You got that, sailor?
- Right, Dad, I
mean, Tiger Breath.
- Take charge, Wild Man.
I'll talk to you.
Hey, don't let the
bitches get you down.
What's that number?
Repeat transmission.
- 555-6423.
- You got it, Wild Man.
Talk to you soon.
(engine rumbles)
(gloomy music)
(jack hammer rumbling)
(phone ringing)
Yes?
What, I can't hear you.
This is JH.
- You're very disturbed,
your sudden retirement
from the Navy.
This is a serious change.
What you have done
is very serious
and very dangerous
for both of us.
My superiors are very worried.
You should have
consulted me in advance.
- It wasn't time.
Look, I've got some
great souvenirs for you.
- You will be sent
a Vienna procedure.
Follow the instructions exactly.
Come immediately.
We must talk.
(birds chirping)
(gentle music)
(speaking foreign language)
(engine rumbling)
(gloomy music)
(people chattering)
(sinister music)
My dear friend, I
greet you at last.
- Listen, uh, somebody
was following me.
I checked out of the
hotel you booked me into.
If you're looking for me,
I'm at the Intercontinental
from now on.
- Let's exchange cameras first.
My superiors are not very
happy with what you have done.
Leaving the Navy service
without consulting us first
was a serious mistake.
The access to key list
has been interrupted.
- Oh, no.
This guy I got is
mister key list.
You're gonna love the stuff
he's gonna get for you.
Jerry's a real asset.
- Walker, we are
very serious people.
We do not believe in suddenly
changing a known source
for an unknown one
just like that.
Do you understand the
difficulty you're in?
I think your security
precautions were
not very successful.
You had a three-year assignment.
All Navy postings
are for three years.
Why was this change?
The FBI suspect your activities?
- Oh, no way.
- Then why did you
retire so suddenly?
- Look, I was gonna have to
pull another tour at sea duty.
I've been in there 20 years.
I just wanted out.
- Out is a very
dangerous place, John.
People can get hurt walking
out without permission.
You're not the only
one at risk here, John.
The price could be very
painful for both of us.
How do you know this Jerry's
a counter intelligence?
- Jerry?
You gotta be kidding.
Jerry's not smart enough
for counter intelligence.
Hey look, he's an old
time buddy of mine.
I've invested a lot
of time in Jerry.
I know what I'm doing.
This is a perfect setup.
- Recruiting is a
tricky proposition.
The chance of exposure increases
every time someone is
added to the circle.
I want to meet this Jerry.
You have to set us up.
- No.
No way.
He'll never go for that.
Now get that straight.
Look, without me,
Jerry's a cockroach.
He doesn't even know you exist.
He'd disappear back
in the woodwork.
- And what if anything
should happen?
What if you should be
detained for whatever reason
from the next meeting?
Would you send
him in your place?
- Look, I'm getting
sick and tired of you
second guessing me
every damn time.
Just get off my back!
I am freezing my
butt off out here
trying to bring you back
into the real world.
I don't need this.
I'm gonna get a cup of coffee.
Do you want a coffee or not?
- A coffee would be agreeable.
(horn blaring)
- What do you say we go for
a thank-god-it's-Friday drink
at the Blue Boar Inn?
I'll buy the first round.
Let your husband cook
dinner for a change.
- My husband always
cooks dinner.
I got him trained.
I'll see you there.
- Okay, great, bye.
Hey guys, wait.
Hey, how you doing?
- He likes you.
All he needs is a
little encouragement.
Oh and married to Roger,
I might go for a
little of that myself.
He's a good boy, Ray.
- It's been so long, I
don't even know the score.
Besides I gotta sit Tommy, give
Cynthia a chance to get out.
- We all gotta get
out a little, hon.
- See you tomorrow.
Bye.
(crickets chirping)
- It's okay, Ma.
You're looking good.
(camera clicks)
- What are you doing?
- Just getting your
picture with Tommy.
A grandma with her kid.
Cynthia'd like that.
- Where'd you get that camera?
- I borrowed it from
a kid at school.
Dad said if I was any good,
I could help him with his
detective work this summer.
- What?
- Getting evidence and stuff.
- No, you can't, you can't.
You, we, you have to help me
paint the house this summer.
- God, Ma, it's so boring here.
What do you expect me to
do, go surfing in the woods?
- You'll have plenty
of years to go surfing.
We'll have fun
painting the house.
- But I already talked to Dad.
- No, you can't, that's final.
I don't want to hear
another word about it.
- Geeze, have a
cow, why don't you?
(baby crying)
- Shh.
Come here, it's okay.
(door slams)
- Watch your collar, get them
real tight up there, okay?
Hi.
- Hi.
- We're gonna have a run
over on this invoice.
You want a little
extra, you and Mary?
- Sure.
- Okay.
- You get a half hour
bump if you skip dinner.
- Hey, Ray, you owe
us both dinner after.
- You got it.
Excuse me.
- I told you.
- I got too much on my mind.
- Okay, but I'm gonna tell
Ray you're hot to trot.
- Really, what's hot to trot?
- Hey, buddy.
- Hey, how are you?
- All right.
- Whoa, bag.
- It's fine, you can
stay at my house.
I got the whole house to myself.
- John, I got some stuff
I want to talk about.
- That's it?
It's barely 100
exposures in six months.
Jerry, the stuff you've
been getting is great.
Uh, kudexes and auto-demi
systems are what they want.
- It's tough now, Johnny.
Alameda is a bitch.
There's no secure place
to photograph anything.
I got this
by-the-book commander.
He's bucking for rank,
you know what that's like.
It's just too difficult
to get anything, John.
It's too dangerous.
I put in for early retirement,
I'm getting out of
the Navy for good.
That's the last of it.
I'm going to college.
I'm gonna be a stock broker.
(chuckles)
- You won't finish
college, Jerry.
They're gonna make it
look like an accident.
The minute you quit, you're
more valuable to them dead.
(chuckles)
- Come on, John.
You been reading
too many spy novels.
- Yeah?
Here, look at this.
And this and this.
Go on!
Stabbed him with an umbrella
on the London Bridge,
left a poison pellet in his
leg, he was dead in four hours.
Damn KGB.
- You mean the Russians
are getting this stuff?
- Yeah.
- John, why didn't you tell
me it was the Russians?
- I just found out myself.
- Oh yeah, yeah right.
- They set me up, Jerry.
How was I to know where
this stuff was really going?
- Do they know my name?
- I'm afraid they...
Know everything
about both of us.
Hey.
The good news is
the sky's the limit.
How about a raise
to 6,000 a month?
You can get a van,
drive it on the base,
have your own personal studio.
- It doesn't bother you?
I mean, Russians
getting this stuff.
- Well, we've always
been eavesdropping
on one another, right?
I mean there've
always been spies.
Maybe it's better
that the two countries
don't have any secrets.
Maybe it's safer.
Here.
(people chattering)
- You get whatever
school you choose
and that will be your selected
career path in the Army.
- I want to sign up.
(moaning)
(phone ringing)
- Baby, the phone.
- Yeah?
Yes, yes.
Yeah, hello.
(hushes)
Well sure, I'm surprised
to hear from you.
No kidding.
(chuckles)
Well that's great.
Yeah.
No, I'm just proud you're
doing something with your life.
Of course, dear,
I mean, it's okay,
it's the best
service for a woman.
Uh huh.
A radio officer?
Honey, that's fantastic.
- Yeah, but I'm still
short three credits
and I got to take a
correspondents course
or I don't graduate on time.
It's kind of expensive.
$100 and Mom doesn't have it.
- Hey, don't worry about it.
I'll put a money order in
the mail in the morning
and listen, you're gonna
do this with bells on.
I'm proud of you, honey,
and I'll put my money on it.
Hey, I'll tell you what.
Why don't I fly up and get you
and you can come back
here and stay with me
till you have to report,
how about that, huh?
Why, sure.
Okay, it's a deal.
You just tell your Mom.
- Don't worry, I will.
Yeah.
Okay and I'll let you
know when I get the money.
Yeah.
Thanks again.
Goodnight, Dad.
I'm looking forward
to seeing you.
- Me too, babe.
Bye.
- Who was that?
- My daughter.
- You know, I never
see you this happy.
- Oh yes, you have.
- Here comes Dad.
Yo!
I'll carry your bags.
(whirring)
- Just throw that stuff
in the back, Wild Man.
You better put a
bungee cord on it.
We might run into
some turbulence.
- Right, Tiger Breath.
- Thanks, Mom.
- For what?
- For finally bringing me here.
I'm sorry about all the yelling.
- Me too.
You're so beautiful.
You got everything
in front of you.
Listen to me.
Don't trust him.
No matter what he does, what
he says, don't trust him.
Okay?
- Yeah.
I'll call you.
- Okay.
- Bye.
- Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
- Hi.
- Congratulations on
your graduation, honey.
- Thanks.
- Oh, you look beautiful.
I'm so proud of you.
- Thanks.
- Let's go, let's go.
- Okay.
- Come on, Tiger Breath.
Take me with you.
Just for a couple of weeks.
- Tell you what, you
go to summer school
and get your grades
up, show me something,
then we'll talk about it, huh?
Hey, I'll talk to you.
(engine rumbling)
(whirring)
(gentle patriotic music)
(applause)
- Private first
class Laura Walker.
Distinguished honor
graduate class 179.
(applause)
Private first
class Russel Green.
(crickets chirping)
- Hello, Dad.
Hi, it's Laura.
Well, um, I have some problems
that I really can't
talk to Mom about.
(dog barking)
(birds chirping)
(knocking)
Dad.
- I knew you'd screw it up.
- So long, babe, I gotta run.
See you later, Johnny.
It was nice to finally meet you.
- All right, I'll see ya.
Well, you're just a loser
like all the rest of the kids.
I had such high hopes for you.
But you're not gonna
amount to a damn thing now.
- Dad, everybody gets
married and has babies.
- Yeah, but you had such a
great career going for you
in the military and
honey, it is a sure thing.
You had it and you
just screwed it up.
I mean, sometimes I just
can't believe this family.
(sighs)
But you're my daughter
and I'll help you.
And I can.
But you gotta stay in the Army.
- But Dad, I'm pregnant.
That, that's why
I'm getting out,
because I want this baby.
- I know, I know, honey.
But you're just not
thinking straight.
Getting out's a bad idea.
I mean how are you
gonna support yourself?
You think he's gonna help you?
You're gonna be on your butt.
Listen, you got to get smart.
You got a lot of time.
You can have more kids.
But you need to get
rid of this one now.
- Mm no, I can't.
I can't.
No, it's not even
up to me anyway
because Josh wants the baby too.
- Well, sure he does.
It makes him look good,
makes him feel like a man.
But you just gotta start
thinking realistically
about life, kid.
Now, the Army is your ticket.
I could help you
make some real money.
As long as you stay in the Army.
- What, what do you mean?
- Would you risk
two years in jail
to hear what I'm about to say?
- Maybe.
- No, no, there's
no maybes here.
I mean this is like,
uh, like a mafia family,
like in The Godfather.
It's the real thing.
There are no maybes.
You see, all good
things are simple.
I got this friend in Europe
that buys anything classified,
tech manuals, encoded radio
traffic, crypto anything,
but especially codes, key cards.
Now, that's the big ticket.
You've already got
your clearances.
You're handling
encrypted traffic, right?
- Yeah.
- All we gotta do is get
you somewhere out here,
get you some
headquarters somewhere
and you gotta get smart,
honey, and move up.
Listen, the kinda money
I'm talking about,
you can have lots and
lots of babies later on
when you can afford them.
You need to put this
one up for adoption now.
Now, you don't worry
about the arrangements.
I'll take care of that for you.
What do you say?
- Um.
- This is, uh..
Just the beginning.
- [Man] Just take it easy now.
Whew!
All right, careful now.
(tires squeal)
(grunts)
(clock ticking)
- Night, Ma, see
you in the morning.
- Just a minute.
I want to talk
with you, Michael.
- It's two o'clock, Ma,
I gotta hit the sack.
- Just sit down and
talk with me, okay?
We can't go on pretending
like this anymore, Michael.
You're on probation.
You're not supposed
to be out so late.
I know you're fooling around
with that girl, aren't you?
- Come on, Mom.
I was just out with Jimmy
and Dave watching some TV.
- Don't you lie to me.
I know you're having intercourse
with that Skenley girl.
She buys you beers.
I've seen the police report.
- Look.
I'm going to Virginia with Dad.
- Listen to me, Michael.
I love you.
I don't want you
to go to Virginia
this summer with your dad.
I want you to stay here with me.
Please, just...
Just do that for me, please.
- Mom, I love you.
But it's time for me to
break away from here.
I have to leave.
I want to live with Dad.
Understand?
- Your father fools
around with whores.
Is that what you want?
You want to go down there,
you'll end up chasing
whores your whole life.
- Mom, you're always
on Dad's case.
Lay off.
He's my father.
I'm going to bed.
- Your father isn't the
great American patriot
you think he is.
- And what are you?
- I'm not a spy
like your father!
Your father's a spy
for the Soviet Union!
- All right, Mom.
You're absolutely right.
I'll catch you later.
- [Barbara] You're gonna
get like Johnny Walker!
- [Michael] You bet!
- [Barbara] No.
(engine rumbling)
- Every fish got
his favorite worm.
This guy is building
a new patio out back
and his worm is
cement. (chuckles)
See, this is the oldest
swindle in the world.
Men got all the money and
women have got what men need
and everything else
is just negotiations.
This guy's ex-wife, trying
to get her point across.
She figures she didn't
get enough in the
divorce settlement,
so she's tipped the
insurance company
that this guy's back
problem is a phony.
And look, look, here he comes.
Look at him.
He sees it.
Yeah.
Cement, baby.
All right, he sees it,
but he can't believe it.
Two bags, man. (chuckles)
Smile.
(camera clicks)
Disability, give me a break.
See, what'd I tell you?
Here he comes again.
Come on.
(camera clicks)
He sees us.
Here.
Keep shooting.
Keep shooting, Mike,
that's where the money is.
(camera clicks)
- You son of a bitch!
I'll kick your head in!
(banging)
Open that up!
I'll get you!
(chuckles)
(dance music plays)
(people chattering)
- Don't you do that, honey!
(hollering)
Yes, yes!
Oh, man.
- Mix it up.
(laughs)
- See, it's like a
chess game, Mike.
Every case is the same, but
every case is different.
You got to think it
out, perfect setup.
Then the other guy does
all the work, right?
If you figured it
out just right,
bingo, another sucker
bites the dust.
Ah, but these are
just everyday turkeys.
I just do this to keep my
hand in between the big stuff.
- Yeah.
What kind of big stuff?
- Hey, you were good
the other day, Wild Man,
but you're not old enough yet.
- Hey!
I can do anything you
can do, Tiger Breath.
- Oh yeah?
- Yeah.
Old enough for what?
- Hey, when you're
ready, I'll let you know.
Show me something
first, finish school.
- Oh!
- Hey, bring us another
round over here.
So, uh...
So what were you
thinking about doing
when you graduate
from high school?
- I'm gonna be a private
investigator like you.
Team Walker, right?
- Wrong.
That's what I thought
you were thinking.
Nah, this is a career for after
you retire from something.
You know, I'd be thinking
military if I was you.
Like see the world,
learn a job skill on the
cutting edge of technology.
Get it on in a foreign
language, right?
- Yeah.
Okay.
I've been thinking about
joining the Navy like you did.
- Well all right, son.
You know, that'd
make me real proud.
Here's to it.
To us.
Team Walker and the
United States Navy.
(waves splashing)
- What are you doing
reading that schematic
out here, Whitworth?
If anybody got ahold of this,
they could build a decoder.
Understand?
- Yes, sir.
- Now damn it, this
should only be looked at
in a secure supervised area.
That means the code
vault, Whitworth.
- Yes, sir.
- Now if I catch this
kind of violation again,
I'll put you on report.
♪ Happy birthday to you
♪ Happy birthday Admiral Art
- [Woman] Make a wish!
- Yeah!
Hey, I'm the
mastermind of this gig.
How about my hug, huh?
- No, you're not
the hugging kind.
- Oh!
You know, I got a
son about your age.
I got an idea.
We're gonna be out
on the boat tomorrow.
Why don't you drop
by and meet him?
I think you two kids
might hit it off.
What do you say?
- I'll think about it.
- Look, it's in the
afternoon, don't worry.
He's a real nice kid,
he's not like me.
- Well, then how can I say no?
- [John] All right.
(birds chirping)
- Oh man.
If that old kook does
not have his girlfriend,
I am definitely taking a hike.
- [John] Hey,
you're looking good.
- Hi, honey.
- Hi.
- Come on, glad
you could make it.
Welcome aboard.
- Thank you.
- Mike's gonna be real happy.
Mike, come here.
This is the girl I
was telling you about.
This is Rachel Allen, Mike.
- [Michael] Pleased to meet you.
- Hi.
- Well come on,
let's cast off, huh?
I'll get you a drink.
Let's get this cruise up
to flag speed, sailor.
- Well, uh...
How about another drink?
- No, thanks.
One is my limit.
Where do you go to school?
- Oh, you wouldn't know it.
- I might.
- It's a private place.
No big deal, it's just a
small place for the, uh,
mentally deficient.
- Try me, I mean I've lived
around here my whole life.
I might've heard of it.
- Sonnenbrille Academy.
- You gotta be kidding.
My stepsister goes
there, Connie Allen.
- Right, right, she
goes out with, uh,
oh what's his name,
what's his name?
- Billy.
- Billy DeButte.
Billy Butt we call him.
(laughs)
- No way.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Billy Butt?
- Yeah.
- He is, he is.
(laughter)
- It's getting late.
You know, if you're
not in bed by 10,
you don't get any, Johnny.
Goodnight, you two.
- Well, nice to see you, Rachel.
Glad you could
make it out today.
Goodnight, goodnight. (chuckles)
- They're quite a
pair, aren't they?
But you don't have to go yet.
- I really had a
good time today.
Thanks for having me.
- Me too.
(hums)
- Look, I'm acing biology,
so I know that your
pituitary gland
is sending some very
interesting signals right now
and I don't want you
to have a problem
going to sleep tonight.
So I think I'll say goodbye.
Don't worry, I can
get to my car okay
and I really did
have a great time.
See ya.
- Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
I had a...
I had a good time too.
Um, can I give you
a call sometime?
- That would be great.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Well, goodnight.
- Goodnight.
- Jerry, old buddy,
this is just 1/3
of the money as a down payment.
But you gotta give them three
months worth of key lists.
They want the complete 90 days,
no breaks guaranteed, huh?
(sighs)
- John, this money is
nothing, you know that?
I mean what it would cost them
to break the codes we're
giving them is millions.
They're getting it cheap.
- Hey, you know what.
That's a good bargaining point.
I'll bring that up
next time I see them.
- Means I gotta put out
to active duty again
in order to get access.
You know I just got
married and my uh,
my wife doesn't want me
going away so much anymore.
- Ah, she'll do what
you tell her, right?
Does she know?
- No.
I told her I was
working with you
on some sort of secret
deal with the government.
That's all she knows.
(chuckles)
She wants me to get
out of the Navy, John.
You know, look,
you knew that this
wasn't gonna last forever.
It's time for me to get out.
- Well, Jerry.
You know, your retirement's
gonna cause me some problems.
But uh...
Man, it's really gonna
hurt you financially.
I mean I thought you liked it
in these big $100,000 bingos.
Wait.
What are you gonna
do when you get out?
Huh?
I mean, Navy pension
is kinda small potatoes
for you now, isn't it?
What is it, uh...
12,000 a year and
change after taxes, hmm?
Here's to it.
- Well at least there's no risk.
- Ah, what risk?
You know, the FBI are too
busy dressing up like Arabs
and catching congressmen.
There's no risk and
there's no taxes.
- What if we're caught, Johnny?
What if we get arrested?
- There's still no risk.
We go to the CIA and
become double agents.
It's standard procedure.
- Don't joke about this, Johnny!
- Hey!
I'm not joking.
- When the time
came, you retired.
I put in my papers
for fleet reserve.
Once they're approved, my
resignation becomes effective.
One year, September next.
- Okay.
It's all right.
Listen.
September's down the road
and around the bend, right?
Come on, let's enjoy what
we got going here now, huh?
Come on.
(chuckles)
(glasses clink)
Oh yeah, listen.
The guy said they were having
trouble with the KWR-37,
the one that made it
from the schematic.
Said it's garbling.
I said listen, my man
Jerry, he's the expert.
- Yeah, well they're
probably just not reading
the crossover logic right.
That stuff's super complicated.
- Yeah?
Here.
Mark it for me.
(gloomy music)
(booming and crackling)
(yelling)
- Maybe you could
go in the Navy.
They got these deals where
you're stationed together.
- Michael, you don't have to
go in the service, you know?
You could get a
job with your dad.
We could get an apartment,
go to school at UVR.
Oh, wouldn't that be fun?
- Yeah, but I gotta go.
I already promised my dad.
He's expecting me to.
- You do everything
your dad expects?
- Yeah, I guess I do.
It was okay until I met you.
Boy, he really messed
up there, didn't he?
- What's the matter?
- I don't know.
Sometimes...
I feel like I'm in
some kind of prison.
- You're not.
You're free.
It's Independence Day, see?
(crackling and booming)
- So how do I tell him?
- You walk up to him and
smile your cute little smile,
definitely take
advantage of the smile,
and say "Dad, it's a
free country, man."
- Man?
- Well, maybe not man.
- Raise your right hand.
Say I, state your full
name and repeat after me.
- I, Michael Lance Walker.
- Do solemnly swear.
- [All] Do solemnly swear.
- That I will support and defend
the Constitution of the
United States of America.
- [All] That I will
support and defend
the Constitution of the
United States of America.
- [Officer] Against all
enemies, foreign and domestic.
- [All] Against all enemies,
foreign and domestic.
(siren blaring)
(engine rumbling)
(people chattering)
(clock strikes)
(birds chirping)
(horse hooves clicking)
(people chattering)
(sinister music)
- Hello, John.
- Hello.
- John, this is your new friend.
He will be meeting
you from now on.
- Yeah, okay.
How are ya?
- So what have you
brought us this time?
Was your trip
pleasantly uneventful?
- No, somebody was
following me again.
I had to shake them.
Took the subway.
- Give us your
camera case, please.
- You must forgive our plan.
The photographs at your last
drop were not very good,
every one out of focus.
- Everything from
the drop is useless.
- Why didn't you
tell me this before?
- We had our reasons.
Your friend has never before
taken a bad photograph.
Why now is every roll
overexposed, fault, useless?
It is obvious this
is intentional.
This is a signal that he
has changed allegiance.
- No, no, no, look, he
just wants more money.
He thinks what he's
giving us is worth more.
He's talking about
a million dollars.
He's just trying to put
a squeeze on us here.
Look, he's got copies,
I guarantee it.
He doesn't make mistakes.
Now I know I can get
new copies from him.
- You will get nothing.
Until he gives us clear
photos for all documents,
the operation is not secure.
- No one has lost confidence
in you, my friend,
but we have experience in this.
There are many
signs that the man
has begun to betray our trust
and this is one of them.
This is very serious business.
It's important that
Whitworth continue his work.
- Look, everything is in
the camera case and more.
Much more.
It'll be in the next
drop, I guarantee it.
(thuds)
Look.
I know this guy.
I lived his life,
you understand?
Half the things he knows
he learned from me.
Money's what winds his toy.
Just leave him to me.
- This will be our last
meeting, my friend.
I give you this
special ballpoint pen.
It's in memory of
our friendship.
- Yeah, well thanks.
(suspenseful music)
I don't have anything for you.
Goodbye, my dear friend.
- Get screwed.
(engine rumbles)
(people chattering)
(brakes squeal)
(dramatic music)
(yelling)
(brakes squeal)
(ethereal music)
(birds chirping)
(dog barking)
(banging)
- Hey, John.
- All your photographs
were out of focus.
- [Jerry] What are
you talking about?
- You hung me out to dry, man!
They almost killed
me because of you.
If you wanted to
increase the price,
you should have told me.
Look.
This is for you, read it.
Read it!
- That's not fair, John.
That's not fair.
It's not my fault the
pictures didn't come out.
- No?
Who the hell's
fault was it then?
I mean, you take
thousands of photographs
and all of the sudden, man,
everything comes
up out of focus.
- I don't think we're being
paid enough, all right?
Now, I deserve to
be paid regular.
Now you can go back
and tell them that
or else I'm out of all this.
They can get some cheaper labor.
- Sit down, Jerry.
Where you gonna go?
Huh?
Where you gonna spend
your hard earned money?
You're a dead man.
As of this minute,
you are a dead man
and I'm the only person in
the world keeping you alive.
- That's not true, John?
- No?
You don't think so?
Okay, fine.
I'll see ya.
You just see what happens.
- Johnny, wait a minute.
- You know what we're gonna do?
We're gonna take a little trip
and we're gonna get the
copies of those photographs.
I know you took plenty
of copies, didn't you?
All in focus, right?
Right.
And we're gonna
take those copies
and we're gonna send
them to our friends
and you're gonna count
yourself damned lucky.
- Look at the boat go up.
Do you see the boat?
So what made you look me
up after all this time?
I thought you weren't
speaking to me.
- Yes, atta boy, atta boy.
- Huh?
- Well, I don't know, I was
just out here on business
and I wanted to see my grandson,
wanted to see how
you were doing,
so I decided I'd look you up.
- How come you always
manage to look me up
when I'm down and broke?
(chuckles)
- Well that's not too hard.
I mean ask yourself
the real question.
Do you want me to
help you or not?
- I can't reenlist
because of Chris.
- Well, don't worry about that.
I talked to a recruiter for you.
He says all you gotta
do is sign custody over
to Barbara and me.
I mean, Barb would
love to have Chris.
Get that welfare check.
What do you say?
- I'm not letting go of Chris.
- Listen to me, listen.
One week max with
Barbara, that's all.
You just fill out
the custody form,
re-up in the Army,
get your posting,
rent a decent apartment.
I'll bring Chris back
to you the same day.
I'll even get you a sitter.
You know, you gotta start
thinking about Chris's future.
I mean, my man in Europe's
getting worried about you.
He's beginning to think
you're gonna get
too old to reenlist.
- You've talked to
somebody about me?
- Yeah, it's just like
any other business.
I discuss changes,
personnel moves,
inventory with my client.
- I don't believe it.
- Ah, hey, come on.
Look this way.
One more with you and Chris.
Smile, come on.
(upbeat band music)
(cheering)
- I want you to be my wife.
Will you marry me?
Huh?
(laughs)
- What's the matter?
- Nothin'.
- What?
- Um.
It's something, I guess.
I've been meaning to tell you.
It's difficult.
- You don't have to
ship out again, do you?
- No, no, no, that's not it.
Look.
I can see what you're thinking
when I look in your eyes.
So tell me the truth, okay?
- Okay.
I will, what is it?
- I don't want to have any kids.
I want to get a vasectomy.
- That's it?
- Yeah.
(chuckles)
- Oh, Michael.
I was worried.
I don't want to
have kids either.
- No?
- Ever, any.
I just want it to be me and you.
- It's too easy to mess up kids.
- Mm hmm.
(solemn music)
(phone ringing)
- [Johnny] Hello?
- [Barbara] Hello.
- [Johnny] Who is this?
- It's me, Barbara.
- [Johnny] I don't need this.
- Wait, I have to talk
to you about Michael.
- [Johnny] Barbara,
leave me alone.
- Don't hang up!
(clicking)
(waves splashing)
- I mean, I'd like
to see you make E3
the first time up like I did.
It ain't easy, you
gotta bone up on it.
(chuckles)
Ah, what am I saying?
You'll be wearing my
chief's hat before too long.
You know I've been
saving it for you?
- That'll be hot.
Chief Michael Walker
reporting for duty, sir.
- Yeah, Wild Man! (chuckles)
You got this Navy
stuff figured out.
They're suckers for all
that enthusiastic gung-ho.
You give them that attitude
and you can lay back behind it
and have yourself a ball,
get yourself some
Navy bras, right?
Oh, but I forgot.
You're a married man now.
(laughs)
- Not yet.
But don't worry about me.
I'm getting mine.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- Yeah? (laughs)
Well, I guess you're
old enough now.
Old enough for a lot of things.
- Like what?
- Like knowing how I make my
real money, serious stuff.
- What do you mean?
- I mean a couple
of hundred thousand,
maybe a half a million
in a good year.
It's getting better and better.
- Come on, Dad.
- Hey, you're a natural, kid.
I spotted it in you
right from the start.
I mean, you're a surfer, right?
You like cutting it
close to the edge.
See, when you're
operating out there alone,
nobody knows the deal but you.
It's like you're
in your own zone.
It's like everybody is
sleeping, like zombies.
I mean sometimes I can even
make them say what I want.
It's like I'm a step
ahead of everybody.
- Listen, anything you
can do, I can handle.
- Can you?
- Sure.
- It's like a mafia deal.
It's totally secret,
totally, you got that?
I mean, it's father son,
just between you and me.
- Okay.
- You know, President Kennedy's
father was a bootlegger.
(laughs)
You make enough money
and you automatically
get respectable, right?
You send your son
to the White House.
- So what is it you do?
Come on, Dad.
- Well.
Like all great ideas,
it is very simple.
Continuous access to
classified information.
That's it.
I'll teach you
everything I know.
You can take over the business.
It's like I said,
you're a natural, kid.
You can pass it on to your son.
See I got these people in Europe
that'll pay a lot of money
for various kinds of
classified information.
After awhile, I'll
introduce you to them
and you can run the whole show.
- The whole show?
How big is it?
- As big as you want, Wild Man.
I've been doing it
for almost 20 years.
- You've been a spy
for almost 20 years?
- Yep.
(gloomy music)
(waves splashing)
- [Man] Do you both enter
the contract of marriage
without any prior commitments
or reservations of intent?
Say I do.
- I do.
- Now, exchange your rings.
Pursuant to the
powers invested in me
by the laws of the
commonwealth of Virginia,
I pronounce you man and wife.
You may kiss the bride.
(audience hollering)
(yelling)
(laughs)
(applause)
- Oh!
Great!
(laughter)
(sinister music)
Sailor!
What are you doing in this room?
You know it's off limits.
What are you doing
with those documents?
They're classified.
- I was just looking
for that tech manual
that chief wanted, sir, 11-507A.
(chuckles)
- You had eight minutes.
How many exposures did you get?
- Seven.
- Seven?
Ah, you gotta do
better than that.
I can get 12 in a minute.
- I...
I can't concentrate
on the camera.
All I'm doing is
listening for you.
- Oh, that's a good
place to start.
Camera skills will get better.
Come on, let's try it again.
(dramatic music)
(people chattering)
(banging)
- What's this door
doing locked, Walker?
- Uh, sorry, chief.
I must have locked
it by mistake.
- [Chief] What the hell are
you doing in here this early?
- I had to catch up on the
strike ops filing, sir.
- Don't ever lock
that door again.
That is a reportable
security violation.
Do you copy?
- Aye aye, sir.
(birds chirping)
- Would you come see
what that big spender
gave us for a wedding present?
Would you look at this?
Well what does he think we do,
sit in front of the
TV eating snacks,
playing switch my
channel like him and Sue?
Hey, this is, um...
Security business for my dad.
You shouldn't get
in my knapsack.
- These things are all
marked secret, Michael.
I know what these mean.
Is this where you've been
getting your money, Michael?
- Let's just forget it, Rach.
You just shouldn't get in
my knapsack, that's all.
- Oh stop it, Michael.
Just tell me the truth.
You could get in trouble.
This is crazy.
- Okay.
I can get busted for it.
It's illegal.
I'm doing it for my dad.
It's part of his security work.
I'm careful, I know
what I'm doing.
- What in the world is
your father thinking?
What are you thinking?
You know how dangerous this is.
You could go to prison.
Just promise me, okay?
Just say that you'll stop.
- You're wrong.
- [Rachel] You don't
what you're doing.
- You're wrong.
- Just say it.
Understand, wrong.
It's okay, it's under control.
My dad knows how to
take care of things.
Anyways, I'm finished
with it when I ship out.
That's the end, period.
I told Dad already,
so don't worry.
- I am worried.
- Rach.
I love you.
After this cruise, I'll
get out of the Navy.
We'll move to California.
We won't have to think
about this anymore.
I'm gonna go to
college, get a degree.
- You sound just like your dad.
(phone ringing)
- Hello?
- [Michael] Mom?
- Michael, what's the matter?
What's wrong?
- Listen, Mom.
Rachel and I are gonna
buy you a ticket.
I want you to come down
and visit us for a week.
We haven't seen you
since we got married.
- Is something wrong?
- Nothing, Mom.
I'm shipping out, that's all.
The Shiloh's rotating
over the Mediterranean.
I'm gonna be gone on a
cruise for a long time.
And...
I just want to see you.
- Don't tell your
dad I'm coming, okay?
- Don't worry, I won't.
(rumbling)
- [Woman] Flight
149 to St. Louis
is now boarding at gate seven.
Flight 149 to St.
Louis is now boarding--
- Hi.
- Hi, you look great.
- Before we go to the apartment,
I want you to drive me downtown.
- Where you want to go?
- No, I don't want
you to get involved.
I just want to go
downtown, take a cab back.
- Here, here, here.
Barbara, where do
you want to go?
- I'm not gonna let
him hurt Michael.
- What are you talking about?
- I'm turning
Johnny into the FBI.
- What?
- He's doing something illegal.
I can't talk about it.
I gotta do it.
- Barbara, wait a minute.
- John's a spy.
- Oh man.
- He's been doing business
with the Russians for years,
since Michael was a little boy.
- This is crazy, Barbara.
You don't know this, you don't
know this at all for sure.
- Of course I do.
I know everything.
Why do you think he's been
punishing me for years?
Why do you think he's
trying to destroy me?
- Listen, you have to talk
to Michael first, okay?
Just wait until you
talk to Michael?
- Why?
Why do I have to
talk to Michael?
- You just should.
- Why?
Is Michael involved?
- No.
No.
Of course he's not involved.
I just think that all of this is
a little too
emotional right now.
Maybe you need to think it
through with Michael first.
- [Michael] Hey, Mom, hold on.
Mom, wait a second.
- I want to speak
to Johnny Walker.
- Let me see if he's free.
Wait, you can't go in there!
- Don't you touch me.
- Hey!
- [Secretary] She
can't go in there.
- You owe me alimony, $10,000.
I want it right now.
- Just tone it down,
will you, Barbara?
- I'm sick of tired of you
nickel-and-diming me to death.
You've got a lot to pay
for and I want you to pay.
You don't give me
what you owe me,
I'm gonna tell everything.
Understand?
Everything!
- Keep it in the room, will you?
- We've got nothing.
- You can all take care
of yourselves just fine.
I don't have that kinda money.
It's not happening anymore,
Barbara, believe it.
- You're a liar!
I know what you're
doing to Laura
and you are not gonna
do it to Michael.
- Will you just
shut up and listen?
You're in this and you know it.
You want to end up in jail?
- Jail would be a lot better
than the way I live now
doing other people's
dirty laundry
while your girlfriend gets
her nails done every week.
- Hey, you could be getting
your nails done every week
if you hadn't screwed it up.
- I screwed it up?
I screwed it up?
If you don't stay away from
Michael, I'm gonna kill you.
- You better think
about this children
that you claim to
care so much about.
You better have a long
talk with Michael.
Hey!
Here he is.
Come talk to him.
(door slams)
Mike, she was totally
out of control.
She was drunk as a skunk.
Can't you keep her
away from the bottle?
I mean we got a
real problem here.
- No, we don't have
a problem, Dad.
You have a problem.
She wants a little
respect from you.
She wants the money you owe her.
Why don't you just pay her?
- Paying the money's
not the point.
You gotta tell her
you're involved with me.
If she knows you're in it,
she's not gonna go
shooting her mouth off.
But you gotta tell her.
She's not gonna believe
me if I tell her.
- No way.
No way, I can't, Dad.
She'll kill herself
if I tell her
and you can't tell her
either, promise me.
- Your mother is not
gonna kill herself.
There's too much left to drink.
You gotta tell her
before you ship out.
Just think of it
as family business
and take care of it, Mike.
Look.
You'll go to prison
too if she talks.
Believe it.
They'll throw away
the key on both of us.
It's got to come from you.
Just tell her and we can relax.
Make it your top priority, huh?
(upbeat band music)
- Hey, Jimmy!
Jimmy, take a picture of us.
Come on, Ma.
Come on.
Come on, let's take a pic.
Thanks, carney.
- Hey, let me get
one of you guys.
- [Man] Now hear
this, now hear this.
Make all preparations
for departing port.
All visitors must depart
the ship in five minutes.
- Mom.
- Just...
I just want you to be careful.
- I'm always careful, Mom.
I just want to get in
some surfing and uh,
Rachel's saving to
come over this summer.
It'll be great.
- [Man] Now hear this, on deck,
set to sea and anchor detail.
- Look, Mom.
You haven't talked to
anybody about Dad, have you?
- Did he tell you to say that?
- No, Mom.
I can think for myself.
- Michael, are you
working for him?
- No way, Mom.
No way.
- Please don't lie to me.
- I'm not lying, Mom.
I wouldn't do that to you.
Not after what you've
been put through.
God, I love you, Mom.
I love you more than anyone.
- Love you.
- Hey, sailor.
You got one of those for me?
You be good until Naples, okay?
- Aye aye, doctor.
(gloomy music)
- Walker.
- Chief.
(humming)
- Little early for that, Walker?
- Uh, no, chief.
We're on a double burn schedule.
- I need a runner on
this op order, chief.
Where's Walker?
- I think he's
processing a burn, sir.
He'll be in the fan
room, want me to get him?
- I'll get him.
Walker, what the hell you doing?
- I threw away a message
I should have filed, sir.
I'm just looking for it.
- Okay, uh, when
you're finished,
I got an op order I want you
to run up the line for me.
- [Michael] Yes, sir.
- Hello, Wild Man,
this is Tiger Breath.
It's Thursday, I just got
your first letter today.
Things seem to be
going good for you.
Can't wait to see those photos.
Sounds like you've
got your act together.
I called Rachel today.
She's working her buns off
trying to make some extra cash
for that trip to Europe.
I have to visit you
in Naples in July.
We can check out
the scene together.
It'll be fun, huh?
(solemn music)
- Yes.
I'd like the number of the FBI.
(phone ringing)
- FBI, Price speaking.
- I want to report something.
I want you to know my
ex-husband is a spy
for the Russians.
He's been a spy for 20 years.
My husband hid his
photographs at the drop sites
and, uh, they were
outside Washington, D.C.
He took me with him on
several of those drops.
- What happened?
Describe the procedure for me.
- Well, he had um,
he had film cassettes that uh...
That um...
He would put in regular
plastic trash bags
and he would take these
bags to the bushes and um,
put them in his spot
and mark them with uh,
soft drink cans.
Would you excuse me?
I uh, I have to get some ice.
Thank you.
About a half an hour
later he would um,
drive to another spot and um,
pick up another trash bag and
inside the trash was money.
- How much money?
- Maybe uh, one time I
remember it was over $50,000.
That was just in the beginning.
I mean, I'm sure that
there's a lot more later.
- How long ago did this happen?
- I figured it out,
I think it was 1967.
- 17 years ago?
When did you and
your husband divorce?
- I don't see what
that has to do with it,
but we were uh, we were
divorced eight years ago.
- All this happened while you
were married for nine years?
Do you have any evidence
of more recent activity?
Other contacts in the Navy?
- Well I thought that's what
you were supposed to find out.
I mean, um...
Uh...
(sighs)
Yeah.
There was um...
There was this guy named uh...
Um...
Jerry Whitman, Whitson.
I don't know,
something like that.
I...
Uh...
He's out in California.
Johnny spent a lot
of time with him.
- How long ago was that?
- Look.
What if I brought
somebody else in here
to testify to all this?
What if my daughter
Laura told you
about the times that he tried
to recruit her as a spy?
- Well, that would
corroborate your story.
But...
What does your husband do now?
- He's living in our
old family house.
He's a private investigator
in Norfolk, Virginia.
- Okay, that's it for today.
Not unless anybody's
got anything else.
- We oughta run
through the crazy file
just to keep
Rafferty off our ass.
- [Man] Just read the
headings for me, Rafferty.
Let's expedite.
- All right.
(phone ringing)
Let's see.
I got a 3/4 disability
Korean war vet
who hears radio henoy
on his dentures.
- I could use a pair that tune
in the golden oldies station.
- Yeah, here's a good one.
I got a film projectionist
out in Cambridge.
He thinks the martians
are doctoring the popcorn.
- Probably not the martians.
- Here's a woman,
alcoholic, clothes washer.
She thinks that her
ex-husband who's a private eye
is the head of a major
Russian spy ring.
- You're getting
better, Rafferty.
Let's see that.
Probably just renegotiating
her divorce settlement.
She doesn't like her husband.
But she's got lots of details.
Details are the key, Rafferty.
Now write up a summary of that
and send it to counter
it, Washington.
Put in all the detail.
Cut down on the drinking part.
(dramatic music)
- I'm inquiring about
the investigation
of Jonathan Walker, Jr.
Walker.
Yes, it's been two months now
since my mother last
called your office
and I don't understand why
it's taking you this long.
- These activities
your mother described
happened a long time ago.
They aren't a top priority.
- He's a spy.
He's a traitor.
He's tried to get
me into it a lot.
I could call him on the phone
and he'd do it right now.
(engine rumbling)
- [Man] I see the
Bureau's oil pans
are up to the usual standards.
- Oh, I got an air tail
on this from Boston.
We're going to have to
think this one through
pretty carefully.
It's got that feel for me.
- Well let's locate him first
and I'll work out a
surveillance plan.
- You know, everything she says,
it's custom KGB trade pat, Bob.
Trash bags, soft
drink cans, $50 bills.
- We need a name for this file.
- How about Family Affair?
No, that's a little
too close for security.
I had a horse out
in Buey last week,
I can't get the
name out of my head.
Wind Flyer.
- How'd he run?
- In the money and big.
- [Bob] Let's hope
you like colts.
- Did your father ever
attempt to recruit you
in his espionage operation?
- Yes, he did, several times.
- Did you subsequently deliver
any such documents to him?
- [Laura] No, I did not.
- To the best of your knowledge,
is your father still
engaged in espionage?
- Yes.
With a man named Jerry
Wentworth in California.
- Your daughter named an
associate of your husband
named Jerry Wentworth.
Do you recognize this name?
- It's Whitworth.
It's Jerry Whitworth.
He's married now.
They live in California.
He used to be in the
Navy with Johnny.
I think he's still in the Navy.
- Do you have reason to
believe your brother-in-law
Arthur Walker is
involved in espionage?
- Arthur's...
A weak man.
And John controls him.
- Do you have reason to
believe your son Michael Walker
is involved in espionage?
- No, I know he's
not a part of it.
I warned him that
his dad was a spy
when he went into the Navy.
I asked him if he was
working for his dad.
He said he wasn't.
He doesn't lie to me.
(phone ringing)
- Yeah?
Oh yeah, what do you got, Bob?
Yeah.
We better alert the Fresco
office about this guy.
Spell it.
- W-H-I-T-W-O-R-T-H,
Whitworth, Jerry.
And listen to this.
Michael, the son,
he's in the Navy.
Active duty at sea, USS Shiloh.
(whooshing)
(clanging)
(camera clicking)
- Because!
- Doesn't look as if he has
a care in the world, does he?
- [John] Don't do
that, don't do that.
(giggles)
- [Man] Print out their
full service record,
all possible intersects.
- Keying in Walker's Navy
record and Whitworth's.
Now I'll punch in the
correlation search mode
and let's see what we've got.
(beeping)
- Looks like between
these two guys,
the Russians bought the store.
- Now punch in the
son, Michael L. Walker,
United States Navy active duty.
- Between the three of them,
they've been on every
class of submarine,
carrier and communications
command in the US Navy.
- [Michael] I'm getting
so many souvenirs for you.
At the rate I'm going,
I'll have over 100 pounds.
Two big boxes.
I'm running out of
space and looking
for a little advice here.
I feel like I'm
out in left field.
What's the situation with Mom?
Rachel wrote that she's
calling her again.
She's mad about the money.
I get the feeling that
something is going to happen.
- What are you worried about?
You told her you're
working for me, right?
Next transmission,
I want to know exactly
what you said to her.
Exactly.
I'm gonna call her
myself right now.
Listen to this.
I'll tell her myself in person.
- [Barbara] Hello?
- [John] Barbara, it's John.
Listen, I've got to talk to you.
I'm gonna send you
a plane ticket.
You could fly down to
Norfolk for Easter,
visit Rachel and Laura.
- [Barbara] I don't know
if I can get off from work.
- [John] You want $10,000?
Make a little effort, right?
We've got things to discuss.
We can't do it on the phone.
- Now we got a real
control problem here.
Barbara is a heavy drinker.
Walker is suspicious and
he's a trained investigator.
He'll take her apart.
He'll give her a couple
drinks, she'll get mad,
tell him that the jig is up,
he'll go get on an airplane,
fly down to the Bahamas.
- Have her postpone
the meeting, stall him,
tell him she can't make it now.
- No way, she's been after
him for months on this money.
If she backs off now,
he'll know for sure
that she's reported him.
She's gotta go through with it.
- You spoke to her last.
What did you think, Bev?
- She's scared.
She told me that if he gets
angry, he can hurt her.
He's done it before.
But she'll do it if
we can protect her.
- This guy's security-conscious
plus he doesn't
talk on the phone.
We can't risk a
tracer on his van.
He checks it out
before each trip.
He uses counter
tailing procedures
every time he leaves the house.
We can't risk giving
her protection.
She's gotta know that.
(gloomy music)
(gentle music)
- You know something, Mom?
The way you're fixing
up for this date,
it's almost like
you still love Dad.
(engine rumbles)
(suspenseful music)
(horn honks)
(people chattering)
- You bring all your girls
to this classy joint?
(chuckles)
- Everybody thinks I'm rich.
I mean this whole family thinks
I just reach into my pockets
and I'm gonna solve
all their problems.
I'm not making that
kind of money anymore.
I wish I was.
- Since when did you
start talking cheap?
Don't you want your new girl
to find out how much
money you've got?
- If I hadn't had to get out
of the Navy because of you,
I'd have made a
million dollars by now.
Now that's how much you cost me.
- You didn't bring me
all the way down here
for this big dinner just to
tell me how broke you are.
- Maybe I just wanted
to see you again.
- Right.
- I guess you had a little talk
with Mike before he left, huh?
- I talked to Michael.
- So now you're not gonna be
wanting to talk to the FBI.
Are you?
- What are you saying?
Are you saying
Michael's involved?
- Involved in what?
I told you I'm not
doing that anymore.
Look, all I'm saying is that uh,
if you go talking about me
you're gonna ruin his chances
for advanced clearance
and his promotion.
You don't want to do
that to him, do you?
- Is Michael working
for you or not?
Yes or no?
He'd never work for you.
I know him.
- You know, you're
looking beautiful tonight.
What are you so uptight about?
You're not afraid
of me, are you?
- No.
- You haven't flapped your
mouth about me, have you, Barb?
- No.
No.
Of course not, I
couldn't do that.
I don't have the nerve.
You know me, Johnny.
- You know, I...
I'd really like for
us to be friends.
After all...
We'll never be separated.
We have kids together, right?
Oh.
This is for you.
- Thank you.
(car door slams)
(engine rumbles)
(dramatic chord)
(solemn music)
(sobs)
- Jerry's not gonna
make it on his own.
I'll give him two years max.
His wife ain't
gonna support him.
(phone ringing)
Hello?
- [Art] Johnny?
- [John] Hi, bubba, what's up?
- [Art] Listen, I've
got some bad news.
Aunt Amelia died.
They're having the
funeral on Sunday.
I know you're real close to her.
She practically raised you.
So Mom and I figured
you'd want to be there.
(sighs)
- Yeah.
I really should come.
She was my favorite, I just...
I can't.
I got this meeting out of town.
It's...
- [Art] Can't you change it?
- No, no, it's locked in.
It can't be changed on
this short of notice.
Can't they change the date
till Monday or something?
- [Art] Johnny, be serious.
There's a lot of
relatives coming.
Arrangements have been
made, stuff like that.
- She was a great lady.
- [Art] Nobody will
change that now.
They can't.
You gotta come, Johnny.
- I, I just can't.
- [Art] Can't you
send someone else?
- No.
Look, it's business.
Nobody else can take
care of it but me.
- [Art] Well, just postpone it.
- No, it can't be postponed.
- [Art] Listen,
Johnny, this is family.
- Look, bubba, please.
Any other day, you
know I would be there.
Any other day but Sunday, I--
- [Art] Mom's gonna be
real unhappy about this.
- I'll send flowers.
- [Art] All right, Johnny.
- I'm sorry.
(birds chirping)
(speaking foreign language)
(engine rumbling)
(tires squeal)
- [Man] Windflower one,
this is Windflower five.
I have target vehicle heading
north on interstate 95, over.
(gentle jazz music)
- Windflower Net,
this is Windflower one
proceeding to special
surveillance center.
Maintain maximum
tracking distance.
Aircraft will maintain contact.
- [Man] This is Windflower five.
Target vehicle has
taken exit 23, over.
(birds chirping)
- [Woman] He's heading north
on Prince and Orchard Row.
- [Man] This may be a dry run.
We don't want to
saturate the area.
- Attention Windflower Net.
Russian diplomat plate
DSX144 entering drop area.
(gloomy music)
(engine rumbling)
(brakes squeal)
(yelling)
- Here it is, over here!
I got it, I got it!
- No film.
- [Man] Clear out,
they're coming.
- Okay, clear it
out, clear it out!
Let's move it, quickly!
- [Man] Come on!
- Sedan DXX144 turning
onto Prince Orchard Row.
- What the hell happened?
- The reason that he didn't stop
is they picked up his signal.
That was a 7 Up can.
The Russian thought that he
missed the drop and went on by.
- Where's Walker right now?
- He didn't find his
money, that's for sure.
- And he didn't find his
own drop when he went back.
He didn't find the
can, we picked it up.
So now he's holed up in
a room at the Ramada Inn
trying to figure it out.
- Let's hope he thinks it's
the Russian who blew it.
- [Man] I've got enough
for an arrest warrant.
We got the classified documents
from the Shiloh
and the drop-off.
Let's pick him up.
- Well you make sure
you get him alive
or we got no case
against arrest.
- Don't worry, I want to hear
what John Walker has to say.
- Better send a coded
message to the Shiloh.
Let their commander know
that he's got a problem.
(cars whooshing)
(gloomy music)
(sinister music)
(gun clicks)
(phone rings)
- Yeah?
- [Man] Hello, Mr. Johnson.
This is the front desk.
I'm sorry to disturb you.
Is your van the red Chevy
with Virginia plates?
- Yeah, what's up?
- [Man] There's
been an accident.
Guy ran into you.
He's at the front desk now.
If you can come down with
your insurance information,
we can clear the whole
thing up for you.
- Okay, I'll be down.
- [Man] Thank you, sir.
(gloomy music)
(bell dings)
- Freeze, FBI!
Drop the weapon!
- Okay, okay.
- Drop it now!
- Easy.
(grunts)
- [Man] Grab the gun!
- You're under arrest for
violation of the espionage laws
of the United States.
- You think maybe you
should contact the CIA
before you do
something you regret.
They can use me. (chuckles)
- Take him up to the
Mastered Arms Office.
(yelling)
(spits)
- There he is, there he is!
- That's him!
(yelling)
- Mike!
Michael!
- Walker, I'm with the FBI.
You're under arrest
for espionage.
- [Woman] Mr. Walker!
- [Man] Arrested for espionage
are John A. Walker, Jr.,
also his brother Arthur
and his son Michael,
currently serving
aboard the USS Shiloh.
Authorities in Washington
and the Pentagon--
- No, no!
(yells)
Oh, no!
No, no!
- Mom, Mom, it's okay.
- No!
(screams)
(yelling)
- [Woman] C5.
C3.
♪ Oh say can you see
♪ By the dawn's early light
♪ What so proudly we hailed
♪ At the twilight's
last gleaming
♪ Whose bright stripes
and bright stars
♪ Through the perilous fight
♪ O'er the ramparts we watched
♪ Were so gallantly streaming
♪ And the rocket's red glare
♪ The bombs bursting in air
♪ Gave proof through the night
♪ That our flag was still there
♪ Oh, say does that
star-spangled banner yet wave
♪ O'er the land of the free
♪ And the home of the brave
(gloomy music)