Are we rolling?
Yeah.
Okay.
Hello, I'm George
Harris, and this is
my thesis project on fear.
Myself and the camera man,
What's up?
Simon, and three other friends
are gonna be going
into the woods
in complete isolation
to, hopefully,
better understand fear.
Is that good? You got it?
Yeah.
Cut it.
Uh, he uh, George wants me to
do some sorta diary,
so here you go.
We are on our way to pick
up George and Elizabeth.
Uh, we're gonna pack up and go.
The, they wanna
go to Amityville,
you know, get spooky ghosts.
I don't know why we
have to drive so far
when we have perfectly
good ghosts here.
And here we are.
What are you doing?
Get out of here!
Oh my God!
Uh.
Shut the camera off.
Well, here it is.
Uh, called a bunch of people,
got a bunch of emails,
went back and forth
through a lot of people,
but I finally got it.
This is the original
'97 Amityville tape.
Uh, hopefully, it
has, it can shine
a little bit of light on some of
the stuff that I'm
trying to figure out,
but it's here and I have it.
And, we'll see what happens.
Hi, babe. It's me.
So, I decided to bust out your
brother's wedding gift to us.
And here I am using
the camcorder.
So, I decided that I'm
gonna make some videos
as I move into
the new house that
we just closed on right
before you got deployed.
So, um, I just wanna make sure
you don't miss anything
while you're overseas.
So, I figured that we could
watch them when you get back,
and, okay I'm gonna
show you the house.
Okay, three, two, one, ta-da.
Look how cute it is.
Woo!
Okay, so this is
the front porch.
Look how big it is.
We can get a new patio
set, and put it here.
And then we can eat
breakfast together
out here in the mornings.
And, um, it needs
some new paint,
but that's okay,
it's gonna be great.
I wish you were here.
Okay, um, all right,
let's go inside, okay.
And we're inside.
Okay, so I haven't
seen it yet either.
Whoa, there's a lot
of stuff in here.
Okay, this is great.
Uh, okay.
So then this is the living
room area through here.
And then this is the other side.
Oh, this is so cute, okay.
And then through
here is the kitchen.
So we have our
fridge, and our table.
Oh wow. Awe.
You can see right
outside to the backyard.
Oh, that's beautiful.
And then this is our sun room.
Oh, I wish you were here.
Okay, so now we're
going upstairs.
And we're, huh.
There are a I, oh gro,
oh god, ew, uh.
Oh great, okay
well, that's gross.
Okay, um, oh god.
Oh, and they're crunchy
when we step on 'em.
Oh okay, uh, okay, uh well,
this is one of the rooms
with two tiny beds,
but we'll bring in a
nice big bed, won't we?
Get it?
All right, so,
going through here.
Hello.
And...
What's this?
Oh, well, oh.
Oh, it's really
humid in here, uch.
Mm...
Ooh.
Ah, that's so squeaky, okay.
Yep, that's enough, okay.
Um, I'm gonna go into the
really creepy basement now.
Okay, let's, oh god.
Oh, oh god.
Okay, well, like, this could
be nice if it was finished.
Put some storage in
here, could be cool.
Um...
Hm, there's a lot of
broken glass back there.
Okay, well, that's good to know.
And water.
Oh great. Oh shit!
Yep, okay.
Yeah, so the basement is a no.
Um, you can go down
there when you get back.
Nice big strong man.
Uh...
'Cause I, wow, scared
myself half to death, okay.
Um, yeah, but that's basically
the tour of the house.
Oh, you'll love it,
okay, so there's
a firing range actually
just down the street.
So, you can keep up
with your gun play.
Um...
So yeah, all right, well
that's my first video.
So, I love you, a
lot, and I miss you.
Ooh, that's cold.
Oh, come on, see,
why don't you join the party?
Take your top off, pop the top.
Uh, hey.
So, y-you get upset when I
film you earlier but not,
now it's okay?
You know, it's a little
thing called consent.
Woo.
Isn't this kinda weird
that's your brother
over there, or...
Not, I mean, it's kinda
like when we were kids
in the bathtub,
except more tattoos.
You're shuttin'
off that camera now.
Hey, shut that camera off, and
you're deleting it right now.
Now!
We're on our way to pick
up Simon's friend Lisa now.
I've never met her,
and I'm very excited
that she's gonna
come aboard because
she's gonna give us a fresh
perspective on the situation.
Sarah?
Yeah.
What are you afraid of?
Oh god, um, obscurity.
Really?
Yeah.
I'm fairly confident
that's not what it is.
Well no, I mean, like,
it's not even so much that,
it's just that I'm
afraid of being alone.
Does that make sense?
Like, - Kinda.
If no one else knows who
you are you never existed.
If no one, if nobody knows you,
if you don't, if
you're alone, you,
did you even exist,
where you even there?
It's like if a tree falls
in the forest, you know?
Ladies and gentlemen,
I give you Mother Earth
herself, Lisa Sheets.
Come on, come on. Here it is.
There you go. Come on.
Lisa?
Yeah?
So, what's with the chickens?
Is it, do you have
them for the eggs,
the meat, what's the deal?
No, I just, I-I
wouldn't eat them.
I think that they're cute.
Uh, I like having
animals around.
They make me feel at peace.
I like submerging
myself in nature,
and taking care of animals
really makes me happy.
Seems like a lot of
work for no eggs or meat.
You know?
Yeah, I guess, like, people
have cats and dogs, you know.
Yeah, yeah, they're like pets.
I love chicken.
Sandwiches.
Fried chicken.
Yeah.
Gross.
You might think that the
chicken thing is weird,
but I think it's
weirder that you wanna
go out into the woods
to experience fear
when the woods are so peaceful.
It's a little bit different
in Amityville, I think.
Like, Amityville, Amityville?
Yeah.
Is there a problem with that?
I thought you said there's
nothing to be afraid
of in the woods.
Why do we have to go there?
Because this
is a thesis on fear.
So, uh, what are you
afraid of, big brother?
I think, um, we're gonna wait
'til we get on location
to discuss that.
He's afraid of
letting our father down.
Hi, babe. It's me.
So, I'm gonna start
my aerobics workout.
And this is so you
know that all of this
is gonna be ready for
you when you get back.
So just, don't laugh to much
when you watch this, okay?
Just, all right, okay,
here we go.
Hm.
Hm hm hm hm.
Hm hm hm heh.
Hi. Uh, can I help you?
Oh, um, I have a delivery.
Oh, my groceries, great.
Come on in, come on in.
I never thought
I'd be delivering
groceries to this house.
Wait, what?
Uh, I don't wanna go...
Oh, that's okay, you want to
have a glass of
water or something?
Yeah, come on in, come on
in, make yourself at home.
I mean, I haven't really
yet, but come on in.
All right, um, hi babe. It's me.
Um, so, funny story.
So, I had our
groceries delivered,
which is crazy, right,
and kind of adorable.
Um, but the guy
who delivered them
started telling me about,
um, that
our house is the haunted
house of the town.
That apparently everybody
knows about except, um, us.
So that was great to find out.
Um, so, it's been kind of weird.
But I talked to Doctor
Stevens, actually,
and she told me that I should
keep talking to the camera.
Which I was gonna do
anyways to keep you updated,
but she thought that
if I kept talking to it
that I wouldn't feel so
lonely, or so anxious.
So, now I just feel really
weird and embarrassed,
and this is really awkward,
but it's gonna be fine.
And if I hate it then
I'll just throw the tapes
down the garbage disposal
and you'll never find out.
Um, so, it's great.
Um, but the house
needs a lot of work.
Um, we need new
wall paper upstairs.
And the floors are gross.
Actually, all the
floors are gross.
And, oh, and the toilet
doesn't flush either.
So I had to go outside,
and get a bucket,
and then bring it in, and then
fill the toilet with water,
and then I, I'm just way too...
Tired to be doing all
this, but it's fine.
And,
So, it'll be great.
Um, but you know,
that's probably why
we got the house for so
cheap, because it's haunted.
'Cause there are just
so many ghosts in here.
And maybe the ghosts will
help me fix the toilet.
'Cause you're not here to do it.
Um...
But I miss you, and
it's gonna be great,
and I think you're really gonna
love it when you get back.
And I promise I'll make it
really pretty, and not too girly.
Um...
Yeah. And oh, and the
idea of there being ghosts
in this house is not
an April fools joke,
so don't try to pull that,
cause I know you will.
Um...
Yeah, so that's it.
Hey.
Hi sweetheart, it's me.
Um, just getting ready for bed.
I miss you, and I
hope you're safe.
Um, and I wish you were here.
Okay, well not, not
here in this bed
because this bed is small,
and old, and creepy,
but in a nice big bed that
I actually ordered today.
So, hopefully,
it'll be here soon.
But, yeah, um...
Come home soon, I love you.
Excuse me, sir?
Yeah.
Do you have a
moment to talk for a second?
Sir, how does it
feel, like, to live
in the most haunted
city in America?
I enjoy living
here, but you know,
all this ghost
stuff, it's all hype.
So you don't
believe in the ghosts that...
No, no, I mean,
most of the time
it's just, it's just stories
made up for tourists like you
to come around and spend money.
Do you, personally,
believe in the paranormal?
No, no, I can't say I do.
But I would probably
avoid the house.
You know, those people,
they don't like people
steppin' on their lawn,
a-a-and you know, people
have harassed the enough.
If I was you I'd just, I'd
just avoid it at all costs.
I-it makes sense,
I'm just tryin' to
get to the center
of why people say
that this places is
haunted if the people
that live here don't believe it.
Because of the
books, the movies,
I mean, it,
it's all just made up.
Do you think
the house is haunted?
Oh, I mean, I've been
there a couple times,
and it's pretty freaky,
but mm, I don't know.
I don't know if it's haunted.
Do you know where it's at?
'Cause we really wanted
to go down there,
maybe get a couple shots of it.
You wanna go down there.
Yeah.
Okay, well I could get
you the, the address.
I have it, I know the address,
but it's gonna cost ya.
Really?
No, no, just messin' with ya.
Yeah.
All right, let me write
it down for ya, here.
Cool.
Okay.
Yeah.
Uh, where's your pack?
Maybe you could lend a hand.
Hey, I got the camera goin'.
Uh, you keep doin' what
you guys are doin'.
Guys, we got about 40
more minutes of daylight,
and about 100 yards
away, let's go.
Got our camp all set up, now
we just need a roarin' fire.
He wouldn't let us
bring any marshmallows.
Okay.
Here we go.
It's me again.
Here I am.
Um...
It's just been such a journey.
Um, I, oh, I went to the
hardware store this morning.
Which, I, gonna be
honest with you,
didn't know what I was doing,
had no idea what I was doing.
Um, but I found some new stuff,
to, like, take down the gross
wallpaper that's upstairs.
And so, hopefully, I'm
gonna use these muscles,
do it all by myself.
And, um, I miss you.
So, that's nothing new.
It gets really cold at night.
And I miss you cuddling with me,
um, to keep me warm.
But, things around the house
are going better, I guess.
I put in a lot of orders
for different stuff,
to, like, come in.
Um, I started going
through all of this stuff
that the previous owners left.
I guess they didn't
wanna take it with them
and didn't wanna
live with ghosts.
So, I started going through it.
So that's a new project,
because you know,
I have nothing better
to do with my time,
than add another project.
Um, but found
some pretty cool shit.
So, like, some of it might stay.
Um, we'll see.
And then I brought in our stuff.
And that's getting
kind of organized.
I don't really know where
you want everything,
so I'm just gonna put it there,
and then if you don't
like it when you get back,
then you can just change it.
Um, but yeah, and it's
been nice outside.
Like, the weather's
really beautiful.
There's a couple
patches of, like,
these purple flowers
around the corner
by the shed that are
really beautiful.
So, hopefully, they
probably won't be here
when you get back,
but that's okay.
I'll take pictures of them.
All right, so we're
goin' on a field trip.
And I'm gonna take you outside.
Yeah, look how great
the paint looks, babe.
This is gonna be so fun
to do all by myself.
Phew, and it's hot outside.
Hey, did you hear
all those guns?
Remind me of you.
Goin' around the corner.
Look how cute these are.
Okay, well those are dandelions,
but I'm just gonna
leave 'em, awe.
Goin' around the corner.
Okay, look how pretty these are.
Now, I don't know, oh
god, that was a bee.
Okay, no, we're fine.
It's fine.
Awe, look how pretty these are.
I don't really know
anything about flowers.
I could not tell you
what these are named.
But they're really pretty.
I miss you, and I love
you to the moon and back.
And, come home soon, okay?
All right, you guys, pizza.
Everybody take a slice, please.
I know you guys are hungry.
Uh, vegan.
Oh, okay.
Thanks, though.
W-what are you doing?
What...
I'm eating.
Lizzie.
She wants pizza.
Good.
So, you're eating grass.
It's not got a lot of...
No, it's clover, it's good.
It's kinda sweet, you want some?
No.
Yeah.
Mm.
No seriously, it's nice.
Like, if you bite, like,
right here it's kinda sweet.
That sounds terrible.
You're really eating grass?
No, it's clover.
Oh, okay.
- Why, why won't...
- Duh.
Why won't you eat the pizza?
I'm vegan.
So, about this video,
what is it exactly?
That is really bright.
We're doing a
documentary on fear,
uh, what people are afraid of,
why people are afraid
of these things,
what made these people afraid
of these things to begin with.
What are you afraid of?
I'm most afraid of people.
We, as a species, are capable
of such beauty and loving,
and yet we hurt each other.
What? Hey.
No, no, no,
- keep going.
- What we're doing
as a species to this planet
and our blindness to
that is terrifying.
So that's why you eat grass.
I think she's afraid that people
will find out that she
doesn't know anything.
That's what I think.
So, what makes you so
right about everything?
It's just daddy issues.
I wouldn't take
it too personally.
I don't know if anybody
remembers what I said,
but you guys check your phones?
- Uh...
- I, mine's dead.
I got no bars.
- Yeah.
- Mm, right.
- No bars.
- So service, exactly.
Isolation.
It lets us enjoy the
spirit of the nature,
like, really immerse
yourselves in it.
I don't know, I'm
just gonna miss Tumbler.
Check that out,
look at those skills.
What was that?
It's just a dog.
That is not a dog.
It sounds like a wolf.
It couldn't have been either.
I was a boy scout, I kind
of know these things.
- Give me the camera.
- Don't go, don't go.
- No.
- Let me see it. I'm goin'.
Simon, just
give him the camera.
Come on, give me the camera.
You're not goin'.
Of course, I'm not going.
Just let him go.
No.
Hang out with
the weird chick, I'm goin'.
Hey.
What?
I'm going with you.
Why, why does she get to go?
So, I'm sorry about
that comment earlier,
the daddy issues comment.
I just, I didn't like how
you were talking to her.
You were kind of cutting
into her a little bit,
and she's a nice girl.
II know,
it's all right, like,
you know I'm gonna
talk about dad at
some point, anyway.
So, I understand, it's fine.
All right.
What are you doin' out here!
Uh, we're camp,
we're camping, there...
Camping?
What's with the camera?
We're doin'
a project for school.
What's with the gun?
There's dangerous
animals out here.
What are you doin'
out here at dark?
Yeah, we just heard an animal,
and that's why we were comin'
out here to check it out.
You're damn right,
you heard an animal!
So you come lookin' for it
in the dark with
nothin' but a camera?
Yeah.
Are you outta your mind?
No. I mean, no, we were just,
we just wanted to know
what that noise was.
Look, son, there's
dangerous animals
out here all over this place.
My girl went missin' about
a month ago, my daughter.
And I been lookin' for her.
You got parents you care about?
- Yeah.
- Of course.
Well, unless you
want them goin'
through the same thing I am,
you will get your ass
back to that campsite
and stay there until it's light.
- All right.
- Well, this,
this is a public place, I mean,
we're not breaking any
rules, we're just...
You're right, you're right,
you're not breakin' any rules.
But you want your
parents to get some kinda
nice little letter about
what happened to you
when you get hurt out here?
Liz, come on.
- All right.
- All right, okay.
All right, we're going.
So, with George
out of the picture,
what actually scares you?
Where you all serious about
what you were sayin' earlier,
or, explain it a
little bit better.
Yeah, I mean, I
mean what I said.
People scare me
more than anything.
I mean, what we
do to each other,
what we're doing
to the environment.
Just think about
the ozone layer,
and climate change, and I
mean, like, terrorist attacks.
I mean, the wolf in the
woods, it could be a person,
someone that wants to hurt us.
I mean, if it was a
wolf, then it's hungry,
but if it's a person,
it's just cruel.
Do you believe
in the supernatural?
I believe there's
something out there.
Everything has a
spirit, everything.
And with what people
do to each other,
they can be so
ugly to each other,
I feel like there
must be some kind
of vengeful deity,
or evil spirit.
Okay, so I found another
gem upstairs today.
Oh, you're not ready for this.
Oh, you are not ready for this.
Okay, I'm gonna show you.
Ta-da!
Right? Right?
Who keeps this?
Me, I'm gonna keep it.
This is hysterical.
Buttoned, unbuttoned,
buttoned,
unbuttoned.
Okay, I'm gonna button it.
This makes me feel like
one of those, like,
19th century matriarchs who
treats their kids like shit,
and then expects to be taken
care of when they're older.
Actually, you know, I can jut
hear the kids downstairs now.
And they're really hungry.
'Cause I forgot to
make their dinner.
He's gonna be so mad.
Hey, you're back.
Didn't know where you were.
Hey.
Did you find
the spooky animal,
snarling beast out in the woods?
- There's no animal.
- Nope.
Eh, what did I tell ya?
Hey, Simon.
You know, you're the most
fearful person I know, and uh...
Not.
Just form
knowing you for so long,
Dude.
And knowing
that you were afraid
of the high dive,
You don't go-
- And you,
basically, pissed your pants
the first horror
movie you went to see.
I wanna know what
you're afraid of.
You know what,
I'm gonna take a shit.
Come on.
And I'm gonna film
it for posterity,
and you can put it in
your little documentary.
Whatever, George can suck it.
Chinese piece of shit.
This place is spooky.
Oh, yeah, that's, that's nice.
There you go, George.
You can put that in your video.
Uh, hello?
Shit!
You know
what I'm gonna ask you,
'cause you're next, so...
You never played hockey,
but always had that stupid mask.
My biggest fear is
uh, slasher flicks,
or you know, masked killers.
I know it's generic
and, I don't know,
stereotypical, I guess,
but, I don't know.
George used to torture
me when we were kids.
He'd run around and, he
would wear that mask,
and I just, I don't
know, it scared me.
And I guess it stuck with me.
All right, camera.
All right.
Be careful with it.
Yeah, how do
you even operate this thing?
God.
Heavy.
Okay, so, George, what
is your biggest fear.
Really?
Well, you're movie.
You know what my
biggest fear is, kinda.
Well, I might, but the people
that are gonna be watching
the documentary don't.
My dad used to take
me to games, and,
like hockey games, and
baseball games all the time.
And he always used
to, after the trip
we would go out for
ice cream, and he would
tell me about how
when I grow up,
I'm gonna be just like
he is, and I'm gonna be
just as successful as
he is, and that one day
I'm gonna be able to
send my kids to school.
And...
I remember one time I
was telling him about
how maybe, that's not what
I wanted to do with my life.
And I remember the
look on his face was
the same look he gave
me when he tried to
break it to us that
mom was leaving.
And that's when I realized
that I can't let him down.
So, I'm afraid of failure.
That's the bottom line,
I'm just afraid of failing.
I can' fail.
Give me the camera back.
Hello?
Uh...
Do...
Do you need help?
I have an idea.
What you thinkin'?
How would you feel about
going into the woods with
a camera by yourself.
You mean, not like, by myself,
I mean if you guys,
like, followed behind me.
No, that's the whole
point, it's by yourself.
That's the scary part about it.
That's what you're afraid of.
I'm not going in
there on my own.
Guys, guys, we're not alone.
There was somebody out here.
There was this little girl.
She was, I don't, I don't know.
Oh my god.
She was just walkin' around.
It was...
It was probably a deer.
A deer? It was a kid.
I saw it plain as day.
She was gone, I, I don't...
If there's a kid out there,
we should go try and find her.
You're afraid of the dark,
you're probably just spooked.
I am not makin' this up.
If there's a little girl,
we're gonna go find her.
So, let's go, okay?
Yeah.
Come on.
Come on, Simon.
You comin'?
This way?
Yeah.
I'm back.
Um, here we are again.
Uh, I'm in the
kitchen this time.
Um, things have been good.
I slept really, really,
well last night,
actually, surprisingly.
Um, I don't know, it was like
you were here last night.
It wasn't as lonely.
And it felt like
your arms were around me.
Um, I missed that.
Uh, yeah, uh, things
have been good.
It's been really
sunny out recently.
It's been gorgeous.
And, oh, okay.
So I bought these new
mugs that are so cute.
Look how cute these are.
We don't have room for them,
but I bought them anyways,
'cause I couldn't help myself.
I'm sorry, I love you.
Uh, but yeah, um, it's good.
I think my plan today is
to organize the kitchen
a little bit, 'cause I've
been focusing on other rooms.
So I'm gonna come back in here
and go through the plates,
and um, the spoons, and
all of that, but uh...
Oh! Okay!
So, I bought this new patio set.
And so, hopefully,
that's what's coming in.
Oh, you're gonna love it.
It's so cute, it's so cute.
We're gonna, um...
Um, hello?
Hello?
Jesus.
Is anybody out here?
Hello?
So, how far
out did you see her?
It wasn't too
far, but then again,
I got kinda thrown
off, you know, I was,
she was there, and
then she wasn't, and...
Hey, hey, stay with the group,
don't go too far out.
I just wanna
find this little girl.
I'm not afraid of the woods.
I just don't wanna lose ya.
Lisa's one
with the woods, guys.
Hello?
Hey, we know you're out there.
Oh my god, stop. It's a deer.
Oh.
Was she like...
She looked lost.
Does she look like your age?
Uh, what, what was she?
Real, real, little.
She looked like, I don't know,
kids get lost on the
trail all the time.
Oh, yeah.
Come on, Lisa,
don't go that far ahead.
Okay.
Yeah.
She probably saw the fire
and wanted to, you know, she's
probably lookin' for help.
Yeah, maybe she saw
our fire, you know.
Maybe she's walking
towards our campsite.
- Nope.
- Hello?
She is not waiting.
Yeah, she's persistent.
I just wish we
could stay together.
All right,
I'm gonna, oh god, wait up.
Hey, don't leave me.
Everybody, stay together.
All right, uh, I'm back.
Um, last night was terrible.
Um, I woke up in the
middle of the night,
and um, scared
myself half to death,
actually is what happened.
Um, I don't know,
I, like, must have
just, like, been making
a video to, like,
say good night and
left the camera on.
And I, like, fell asleep, and
was sleeping really soundly,
and then something,
I don't know.
There was some, like,
noise or some thud
that happened and scared
the shit out of me.
And I woke up and saw,
there's this red light
on the camera, and I don't
know what I thought it was,
like a rat, or like a
bug, I have no idea.
And, yeah, so um, but it's fine,
and it was my fault,
and I guess I just
left the camera
rolling all night,
and didn't think about
it, and fell asleep.
Um, so I'm exhausted,
'cause I couldn't fall
back asleep, um, at all.
Um, but uh, yeah, things
are great in the house.
Um, it's not as drafty as it
has been the past couple days.
Um, 'cause I'd sealed off
some of the windows upstairs.
Um, I started painting the
second guest room, blue,
'cause that's your
favorite color.
Um, yeah, so it
looks really good.
Actually, I like
the shade of blue,
and actually, I'm
doing a lot better job
than I thought I would.
It all looks really even.
Um...
I miss you, so, like,
that hasn't changed.
Um, and hopefully I'll sleep
really well tonight
because I'm so exhausted.
Yeah.
- So.
- It's me.
Is anyone else
freaked out about
not finding that little girl?
I mean, I'm worried for her.
Yeah.
Just a little bit.
I...
What?
I didn't expect
to see somethin' like that.
None of us did.
It's so weird,
a little girl in
the middle of the
woods by herself.
Yeah.
I mean, there's gotta
be an explanation.
You think maybe, uh,
I mean you know where we're at,
I mean, you think it
might have been a ghost?
Oh, come on.
Oh, come on with that, dude.
It could be.
It, you never know.
There is no such
thing as ghosts.
You're so certain?
Well...
I mean, you don't see them.
You know how sometimes
you look at, like,
a really tall,
looming, twisty, tree,
and it just looks kinda evil?
Like, you see it.
Nah.
You lost me.
That's what I believe in.
That...
You just don't get it.
No one gets it.
I mean, other than that
it's been a pretty good trip.
I would...
Yeah, speaking of, great.
Oh god, ew, that's
my brother, that's...
- ew.
- Great.
I feel sorry for you.
Is it like this all
the time with them?
Oh god, I don't
know, probably.
Come on.
Ew.
Well, uh, just
throwin' it out there,
I mean, this would be
the perfect opportunity
for a threesome.
Ho ho, oh my god, dude
I'm a graduate, okay.
My experimentation
days are over.
Yeah, we'll just be over here,
Harder.
And you can stay in
that part of the tent.
Well, I mean, - Yeah.
The offer's there.
Good night, Simon.
Okay, I'm back.
So, um, yeah, I've
just been feeling
really creeped out
being here along.
Um, yeah, so I um,
I went and talked
to Doctor Stevens
again, and she told me
that I should learn
how to face my fears
head on and do some
research on the house,
because then, maybe,
I'd feel better
if I knew some of
the history of it.
I don't know, whatever.
So, I went to the library
and found this book.
So, um, I'm gonna
read you some of it.
Um, okay, um, in 1974
a family were found
shot dead in their
beads, and the oldest son
was found guilty of
committing the crime.
He had claimed that
an evil presence
was speaking to him
throughout the house
and that it had, in
many ways, seduced him
into committing the crime.
He's still in
prison to this day.
Since then, several
families have moved
into the house and shortly
have left afterwards
claiming that the
house is haunted.
Okay, um, well that explains
how all this furniture
has just been left over.
This place is like
an estate auction.
However, two of the
families who claimed
to experience paranormal
activity in the house
all went on to attempt
to gain publicity
for books and movies
using their experiences,
which has deeply harmed the
validity of their claims.
Most find it to
be outright lies.
You hear that, sweetheart?
We could be famous.
Um, well, while I
was at the library
I found another
book that I thought
would help me even more.
So I found this gem.
Um, let me just show you
the first page of this
so you can just really see what
I'm dealing with right now.
Uh...
I'm so lonely, if
you can't tell.
And so needy.
Um, I want you to come home.
Yeah, 'cause this, this, this,
this book ain't,
it's not cuttin' it.
So, um, yeah.
I miss you a lot.
Yep.
What are you doing?
You missed all the good parts.
Do you love me?
Of course.
Would you do anything for me?
Yeah.
Okay.
Look.
It's the house.
The house.
Yeah, like, the
one from all the stories.
This is it.
I didn't want the other guys
to see it and get
all freaked out
'cause we're camped right around
the corner from it,
but, this is it.
Can we go back?
There's
nothin' to be afraid of,
it's just a house.
Pretty cool though, right?
Yeah, yeah, sure.
Let-lets go back.
Let's go back.
Hi, it's me.
Um, I actually feel a lot better
after having done all that
research on the house.
And um, I don't know, maybe
Doctor Stevens was right
that we're just afraid
of what we don't know.
So, yeah, it was a good day.
And um, I have a lot planned
for tomorrow, actually.
And um, I miss you!
Can't sleep?
Nope.
Mind if I join ya?
Not if you're gonna film me.
I'm just using the light.
All right.
You can't sleep either?
Nah.
I ended up calling
the police last night.
I just woke up,
and I kept hearing
all of these noises,
and I didn't...
I didn't know what to do.
And they showed up,
and they were so nice,
and so polite, and
they walked all the way
around the house, and
in every single room,
and all the way in the basement.
And I...
And there was nothing.
Nothing in this house except me.
So, by process of
elimination I'm the problem.
I just, I don't get it.
You know, I have a
12 year old sister,
and she can stay
home by herself,
but me, I can't.
I can't be here by myself.
But you know, the one good thing
about the police
showing up is that
every single neighbor came
out to see what was going on.
And there I was in my
pajamas on the porch...
Like a moron.
Because there was
nothing in the house.
You know...
I should be able to do this.
I want you to come home
and be proud of me,
and all the work
that I've done here.
I'm really sorry.
Okay, well I ordered some
new stuff for upstairs.
Hopefully, that's what that is.
Hi, um, yeah let's
just go around back.
That'd be great.
Okay, guys, we're close.
So, Elizabeth,
what do you think
about your hike of
the damned in these
spooky, ghost filled woods?
It's a little more
annoying when you
have that camera in
my face all the time.
I can get closer.
Oh, yeah, that'd be great.
Oh, what's on that?
But yeah, so far
so good, I guess.
What's wrong with
your girlfriend?
She's just driving me crazy.
We still goin' the right way?
Yeah.
Yeah, mister
nature man with his compass.
I'm sure of it.
Back this way, sorry.
Ah.
Watch it.
Brilliant.
Ow.
Look out for that, Simon.
Like...
Somebody should
start putting flowers it it.
It'll probably stay in.
This is exactly
what you wanted.
This is what the
documentary's about.
Looking good.
Awe, you look so pretty.
Awe, thank you.
Uh-Huh.
I'm over it, I'm...
Oh, it's you two again.
I see you got some more
friends with you this time.
You got your camp site set
up for tonight, all ready?
No, I think we're gonna
hit the road after this.
Well, if you change your mind,
you make sure you stay to
that campsite after dark.
It's dangerous out
here like I told you.
Dangerous, like a ghost?
A lot of people think
this is a haunted area.
Don't be stupid, boy.
I'm talkin' about wild animals.
Sir, uh, last night
you had mentioned,
uh, you were looking
for your daughter.
Um, we, one of us
might have possibly
seen something that
was uh, may have been,
um, a child in the woods.
This guy thinks he saw it.
Where?
Like, up, up
the hill back that way.
All right, just
remember what I said.
Stay out of these
woods after night.
Stick to your campground
and you'll be safe.
Oh, sure.
Okay.
Come on, he's.
Got that goin'?
- Yeah.
- Okay, cool, good.
All right, guys, we're
staying one more night.
What? No.
What are you talking about?
Uh-uh, dude, that's
not what I signed up for.
Listen, we're gonna
pack up these tents,
we're gonna pack up our bags,
we're gonna go
about 100 more yards
into the woods, and we're
gonna stay one more night.
That's all I'm askin'.
- Uh...
- That's asking a lot.
That's asking a lot.
Why, 'cause you're scared?
- Exactly.
- We're all scared.
Right, that's the point.
For fear, right?
That's what this
documentary's all about.
'Cause we're all scared, right?
We all came...
So we're staying
one more night.
We're gonna get
everything packed up,
and we're gonna stay
one more night out there
and really get what
we need to get.
We signed up to sit
around a camp fire
and talk about what makes
us, w-what our fears are.
We didn't sign up...
Yeah, dude, I'm not...
We're not
expecting to run into a man
in the woods with a gun.
Not cool with this.
Everything's gonna be
- completely fine.
- Whoa.
Listen.
The reason I have this,
That's nice.
Is so everyone
knows I'm not gonna
let anything happen to you.
We're safe, okay?
So if you're
worried about safety
or you're afraid of
being hurt out there,
no one's gonna get hurt.
I won't let you get hurt.
So let's pack everything up,
and let's go to the woods.
Wha, no, no. One more night,
it's one more night, and
that's all I'm askin'.
- No.
- Put that down,
and help me pack up this stuff.
Hi, babe. It's me.
Um, I'm gonna do another
aerobics work out,
try to keep the routine goin'.
Okay, here we go.
Hello?
Hi, yeah, uh, no, no, I asked
for the linoleum flooring.
Yeah, yeah, okay,
I'll be here all week.
So...
Friday morning would be great.
Yeah, just let me
know whenever works
for you guys and I'll be...
Hold on.
Hello? Hello?
I need you to face
your fears, all right?
Okay.
That means you
gotta go out there
with this camera
by yourself, okay.
Can't you go with me?
No.
Like, j-just follow,
just follow behind.
The whole point is
that you're doing this
by yourself in the dark, okay?
Take this camera,
you'll be fine.
All right?
- Okay.
- Okay?
Um, if I scream, I
mean, if I yell out
or something, are you gonna,
are you gonna come get me?
No, we're gonna
wave our flashlights
and you can come to us, okay?
Go ahead.
Okay.
All right.
I don't wanna be alone.
Exactly, go ahead.
Oh god, oh god.
Help!
Okay where are they?
Where are they?
Help! Help me!
Oh, thank god,
there they, there.
Guys, I think, I
think I saw her.
I think I saw the little girl.
All right, okay.
She, was back there.
Okay, we'll
find her, we'll find her.
Oh.
Wha...
We need to go find help.
We need to go, we need
to go, we need to go.
Ooh, all right.
Welcome to the back yard.
Um, so I'm just tryin'
to clean some stuff up
before the contractors
come out again.
Um, yeah, our
contractor's name is Tony.
And he talks to me like
I don't know anything
about building.
You know, which may
or may not be true,
but he's still a sexist.
But it's fine, um,
so, um, oh god,
I'll clean up all
of this eventually.
Oh, okay, so I
wanna show you, um,
I don't know, the
foundation around
the corner of the house
has been really weird.
Like, on this end, well this,
well this is the sun room
on this side, and then
this is the living room,
but it's been, like, sinking.
Now I don't really know,
like, what's going on.
But I, oh, that was a be.
But I was...
Yep, nope.
Okay, it's done, we're done.
This is finished.
Let's get our packs and go.
- Car now.
- No, I'm with you.
I'm with you, let's go.
Okay, everybody grab a pack.
Just screw the
tents, let's just go.
Jesus.
Guys, wait up a second.
It's so dark, you need to
walk in front with that light.
This even the right way?
- Yeah.
- I don't know,
I feel like we've
been walking forever.
Just keep goin' this way.
Seriously,
we've been walking forever.
It's all right,
we're goin' the right way.
We've been goin' north for
the last hour and a half.
There's no way that we're
goin' the wrong way.
We've been going in a
straight line this whole time.
So, I think we should just
continue going in
a straight line.
Does anybody else have any
better ideas than that?
- Anybody?
- I don't know.
I guess just keep going north.
Exactly.
Didn't anybody bring
a map or something?
Okay, so I went back outside,
after composing myself and
building up the courage to do so.
And it turns out that
it was rust water.
So, that's why it was
red, because it's just
been raining a lot,
and it must have
just gone through
the pipes, and...
Yeah, but I didn't
have to call anyone,
and I figured it out by myself,
and progress.
So, maybe now I can go fix
the toilet by myself too.
I can do this.
Watch out.
None of this looks familiar.
None of it looks familiar.
Exactly, that's a good thing.
Do you wanna hold
on to the compass?
Do you, would you feel better
being in charge of the compass?
I don't know what else to do.
And we're stuck.
We are, we hiked, and we hiked,
and we hiked, and
we got nowhere.
I don't know what's goin' on.
What we need to do is
go find that little girl
and make sure that she's safe.
She's right.
I'll go.
I'm gonna go too.
Nah, I'll go.
You go straight,
and it meets back up...
W-w, uh, hold up, um, uh...
We took it earlier, we
took this path earlier.
You go straight, I'm
gonna go left, okay.
It meets back up.
Uh...
Just do it, just trust me.
I have a lantern, I'll be fine.
Just go straight,
I'll go this way.
We'll cover more
ground that way,
and we'll find the little girl,
we'll meet back up, and
we'll go back to camp.
Okay?
- Just go.
- Fine.
- Just go, just go, just go.
- Whatever.
We have to do this.
- [All right.
- Elizabeth] All right.
Hello?
Nothin'.
I made a couple rounds,
and there's nothing.
Shit.
Simon!
Oh my god.
Shit.
Oh shit, oh, oh my god.
Oh shit!
Back on the trail, it forks.
His blood's all over my hands.
I thought we could
cover more ground
if we split up, and he was...
Oh my god.
Guys, I have a radio.
Oh, god.
Oh thank god.
Hello, if there's anybody out,
if there's anybody out there,
this is an emergency,
we need help.
What was that?
We need help. We need help.
I don't know.
What the hell was that.
I don't know!
We, we didn't
find the little girl.
We're not gonna
We didn't
find the little girl.
We're not gonna
Just, just sit tight.
It's okay.
We didn't
find the little girl.
Lisa, we're not gonna
The little girl is gone!
Lisa! Lisa, stay here!
What do...
We can't keep splitting up.
Lisa!
Hey, wait up.
Lisa, come on.
I see the little girl.
What?
I see her, she's right there.
Where?
She's right there.
There's nothing there.
What? I'm going to her.
Did you find her?
I lost her, I
don't know where she is.
Get your shit, and let's go.
We gotta get outta here, now!
Grab you bag, now, go!
Come on! We gotta go.
Wait up! Wait!
Where, where'd you go?
Little girl, little girl?
Where are you, where'd you go?
I know where you are.
You wanna play with me?
You wanna play?
You wanna play with me? Yeah?
Oh my god! Stop!
No! Stop! What are you, no!
Let me go!
Keep moving, go.
Go, go, faster, come on!
Would you shut up,
and turn that
fucking camera off?
It's our only proof
of what's goin' on right here,
and it's providing us light!
You know what,
professor, you wanted fear?
You fucking found it!
Fuck you!
Move. Go, go, go!
We are.
You're not movin' fast enough.
We gotta get outta here, now.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
We gotta get outta here, go.
Go, go, go, go now!
Shut up, shut,
shut, don't talk, don't talk.
Where is she?
Take the light.
What? No.
But.
Do remember that
house I showed you?
Yeah.
Go straight to that
house and don't stop.
Come.
Just go, I will find you.
No, no, no...
- I will find you.
- Come with me.
Baby, I promise,
I will find you, go.
Oh god, oh
god, oh god, oh god.
Jesus Christ.
Help!
Somebody help me!
Hey, hey, everything's fine.
You're okay.
Everything's goin' great.
Okay?
Everything's fine.
Listen, this is gonna
be perfect, I promise.
But I need your help, okay?
I know this is gonna be
scary, and that's okay.
'Cause it's gonna be perfect.
Tag.
You're it.