Hello?
Hi, Troy, I heard you were
having a party tomorrow night.
Where'd you hear that?
Oh, you know, I have my ways.
Uh.
Well, are you gonna invite us,
or are you gonna leave us hanging?
Us?
You know, the girls,
silly, Cameron and Sandra.
Unless you don't want us to.
I mean, if you think it might bother Tonya.
No, um, I want you to come.
Good, maybe we can
find a little quiet time.
You know, get away from the
group, et cetera,
because I have something that
I've been wanting to tell you.
Something you wanna tell me?
Bye, Troy.
Oh my God.
Nice one, Beck.
I am totally dragging you to
try out for the spring play.
Mr. Blackmore would love you.
Oh, memorizing lines
aren't really my thing.
I just like, like, make
up stuff on the fly.
It's more exciting that way.
Troy is having a minor
heart attack right now.
I know, right, he's going,
uh, something, uh, something
you have to tell me?
Yeah, maybe I'd like to show him something.
Shame, shame.
Okay, so, we have
Troy's party tomorrow night,
but what're we gonna do with our Saturday?
Any ideas?
I thought I heard something.
Maybe Troy and his buddies are coming over
to try and sneak a peak.
Oh, please, Beck just called him at home
like 30 seconds ago.
It was like a, like a crunching.
I'm serious!
Oh relax, they'd have
to get past the main house
just to get back here.
Past my all seeing parents.
They'd have to be pretty sneaky.
Something adventurous.
We could explore The Morgantown woods.
See if the rumors are true.
That I like.
We could go undercover.
I can dress like the Ninja.
The Ninja is so lame.
We'd be like a team of female assassins.
Nice, I've got a bunch
of old clothes out here,
like black hood sweatshirts and stuff.
Rise and shine, Freaky Farley.
You've got a visitor coming in today.
Farley, my name is Dr. Timson.
I'm one of the most respected
doctors in the region.
Are you married?
Oh, yes, I am, but I don't
believe that's any of your...
May I call you Mrs. Timson?
I would prefer Dr. Timson.
I like Mrs. Timson.
Oh, I suppose that is acceptable.
Thank you, Mrs. Timson
Do you know why I'm here?
Same reason all the other
so called doctors have been here.
And why is that?
Because you wanna find
out how my sick mind works.
I suppose you could
put it that way, Farley.
That's right, Mrs. Timson.
I happen to think I'm
here to help you, Farley.
To find a way to channel your
anger in a more healthful way.
Blahty, blah, blah, blah.
Listen, Farley, you can
cooperate with me or not,
but it's in your best
interest to cooperate.
It's not like they'll ever
let me out of this place, Mrs. Timson.
I've done terrible things,
terrible, terrible things.
Aren't you familiar with my case?
Don't you know what I'm capable of?
I am familiar with your case, Farley,
but I'd like to hear it all from you.
Are you willing to do that for me?
I suppose so, Mrs. Timson.
After all, there's nothing else
for me to do in this, this.
Place?
That's right, but in the future,
allow me to finish my own sentences.
Fine, I'll be recording this, Farley.
Do you mind?
Please do.
Why don't we start with
the death of your mother.
You'll never replace her!
You get ahold of yourself, young man!
I'm not a young man, Mrs. Timson.
I'm old, very old.
Well, maybe not yet,
but where I am now is where
I'll be when I'm very old.
I wasn't very old when Mom died though.
I was just a boy.
Think of that, Mrs. Timson.
For a young boy to lose his mother.
That's not the way it's suppose to happen.
I remember she had gone away the day before
to do some work on our family cabin.
I thought I'd wake up that morning,
and see that she'd returned.
Instead, it was my dad who woke me up.
He didn't say anything at first.
He just put his hand on my shoulder.
That was the last time
my father showed me any
kind of understanding.
The next day I spilled some milk.
Farley, how could you!
Look at this mess that you made!
Now, help me clean it up
before your mother comes home.
You know how they say
you shouldn't cry over spilled milk?
You've made a terrible mess.
Now, go out back and
wait for your punishment.
Well, I ended up
crying quite a bit that day,
but it wasn't because of the milk.
It was the way he punished me for it.
It's not about the milk, son.
It's the principal.
You've got to stop being
so dreamy, so careless.
Sure, you may not be the
brightest kid in your school.
You may not be the best
on your baseball team.
If only you weren't so afraid of the ball,
but we'll toughen you up yet.
Dig me a hole about four feet
wide and about four feet deep.
Well, what's it for?
Absolutely nothing, that's the point.
And another thing.
Would you change that shirt?
You've been wearing it for a week now.
I don't think so, Dad.
The shirt stays.
It seems like so much of my
childhood was spent at the hole.
Digging it out, filling it in,
and sometimes while I was digging,
Dad would stand over me giving advice
on how to live my life.
And that's the thing about women.
I've seen those girls in your
class, heartbreakers I bet.
Probably best to stay away from them.
Okay, son.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, where you going?
I need you to fill the hole
in, then come in for dinner.
Well, what do we have here?
I hit a rock.
What're you gonna do about it?
I guess I'm gonna have to pick it out,
and then keep digging.
Well, when you get four feet,
why don't you give me a holler,
and I'll come out and measure it,
then you can fill her in.
Yes, sir.
That's how things were,
overly strict rules, perverse punishments,
never catching a break.
I got used to it.
Son, these came for you in the mail.
Well, I was thinking maybe
I could just take a couple of courses.
Son, what did we say about this?
You're too old for college.
You missed your chance.
Besides, who's gonna pay for this?
You don't even have a penny saved.
But, Dad, if you just.
Son, the answer's no.
You'll stay here until
I can find you a job,
a practical job,
and you'll happily take it.
Whoa, whoa, watch where
you're going, buddy.
Sorry.
Sorry is not gonna cut it.
No, I think the situation
calls for something more.
Maybe you should get back here,
and buy Betty and I a slice of pie.
That'll ease things over.
Help to subdue our feelings of rage.
I don't have any money.
Then I suggest you run,
and don't come this way,
till you're ready to make
reparations to Air Force Ricky.
Hey, Freaky Farley.
Freaky Farley, Freaky Farley,
Freaky Farley, Freaky Farley, mm, mm.
Farley, come in here, please.
Come inside, son.
Time to discuss your future.
So, tell me how the job search is going.
No leads yet, Dad.
That's bad, Farley.
That's very bad.
Son, did you listen to my show last night?
Of course I did.
Well, apparently you
didn't listen too well.
What with an 86 on this morning's quiz.
Well, I guess my mind might've
been drifting a little bit.
Anyways, we discussed the importance
of persistence in job hunting.
Business leaders are so busy today, son,
that they don't have
time to give some nobody
a call back looking for a job.
That nobody needs to keep on calling.
Show up unannounced.
Always be around until gosh darn it,
the businessman has no choice
but to offer him the job.
Do you know what I mean, son?
Yes, Dad, although I wouldn't
say it really help me get
a job at the radio station.
What do you mean by that?
I'm the son of the most popular personality
at the station,
and I still didn't get the position.
I had nothing to do with that.
President Tarkington selected
Katie fair and square.
Besides, I tend to stay
out of office politics.
Katie's much more suited
for that line of work than you are, son.
Thanks a lot, Dad.
But I do have something lined up for you.
I understand it wasn't easy for you
to get me this opportunity,
but what is it?
Well, it's quite an
opportunity for any young man
with the drive to succeed.
But what is it?
Well, you remember Mrs. Green, right?
No.
Well, anyway, she's in charge of personnel
down there at the phone company.
You have an interview with
her Thursday at two o'clock.
What I need for you to do
today is go to the library,
and look up as much as you
can about the phone industry.
You have got to go into that interview
armed with information.
You know, telecommunications
is a fascinating field, son.
I mean just think about it.
Thanks to the telephone,
I can call my friend, Harvey, in Seattle,
and talk to him as if he's
right here in the room with me.
But Dad, I don't even want an office job.
You know what I really wanna do...
Son, would you get your
head out of the clouds?
I mean Park Rangers don't make very much,
and there are very few
openings in that field.
Besides, you don't know a
thing about the great outdoors.
Well, that's because you
don't take me to the cabin, so...
I will not discuss this subject.
Now, go to the library,
and study up on the
history of the telephone.
Hey, check this guy out here.
Oh my God.
What a freak boy.
Oh man.
Dad could only boss me around so much.
I had better things to do
than got to the library.
The trogs, the trogs.
What?
These woods, they're infested with trogs!
Whatever, old man, get out of my way.
I know you, you're the Wilder boy.
How do you know me?
I love your father's radio show.
He's helped me with my life.
Yeah.
It's a shame about your mother.
What do you know about my mother?
It's too sad to recount.
Those trogs, now that's
a story worth telling.
I don't wanna hear
about your stinking trogs, old man.
Get out of my way.
Hey kid, kid, can I walk
with you a little while?
It gets lonely out here.
Go away.
Stinking trogs.
What did he mean by trogs?
Shut up, lady.
Allow me to tell this story at
my own pace, you understand?
Go on.
Dad always thought I listened to his show
in the safety and comfort
of my own bedroom.
Boy was he wrong.
Ever since I was 16,
when I got a portable radio
with earphones for my birthday,
I spent my time walking
the streets of Morgantown,
and I'm not ashamed to say it.
I saw a lot of very interesting things.
Well, I'm off to my interview.
Good luck, son.
Let's see what Mrs. Green thinks of this.
Dad could force me to
go to the job interview,
but he couldn't force me
to make a good impression.
So, Farley, your father tells
me your eager to work here.
Is this true?
Actually, Mrs. Green,
I'm only here to see you.
I've always thought you were
an incredibly attractive woman.
Now, what do you say
you ditch your husband tomorrow after work,
and meet me at lover's lane?
I'll be there waiting for you.
I had some thinking to do.
Dad wasn't going to be
happy about my little stunt.
There would be repercussions.
I decided to take a ride down the river,
and let all my troubles disappear awhile,
but it turned out I was
in for a rude surprise.
My tube was missing.
Where could it be?
No one ever came into these woods,
but then it dawned on me, the hobo.
He must've seen where I hid it.
I was ready to go look for him
when I got an unexpected visitor.
Hey, Farley, I knew I'd find you here.
Can't believe you still hang
out in these stupid woods.
You need to grown up.
What do you want?
Well, your dad told
me to come look for you.
I heard you did a really
good job at your interview,
and he wants to congratulate
you, so come on.
I won't take no for an answer.
Wait, let me get out of this outfit first.
I gotta get back in my suit.
Your dad says a girl should
never see a boy undress
before they're married, I'm leaving.
Congratulations, son, have a seat, son.
I always knew my son would
make a good impression.
Mrs. Green gave me a call.
She said that she never met a young man
with so much potential.
She also wanted to make sure
that you're gonna make
that second interview
as you discussed.
Oh, Freaky Farley,
you're old enough to vote.
Vote for me in the next election.
Okay, Mr. Mayor.
That's a great drawing.
Does she know she's a model?
Leave me alone.
So, you're Freaky Farley?
I've been waiting to
meet you for a long time.
What're you talking about?
I'm familiar with your work.
You're a legend around town.
Who are you, Nancy Drew?
I wish, I'm Scarlett Carter.
Can I walk around town tomorrow with you
and see you in action?
I don't care.
It's a free country.
That Scarlett was quite
a beauty, Mrs. Timson,
and smart, and interesting.
I couldn't help but be attracted to her,
but I was also kind of afraid of her.
She was so confident,
so knowledgeable on every
little detail of Morgantown.
I had never met a girl like her before.
There you are, Freaky Farley.
I've been looking for
you all over the place.
Come on, let's go on my route.
I like to go up here past telescope guy,
turning left at the end of the street
near the heavy metal drummer,
and curl around past the witches place.
That witch is a real character.
No matter what time of year,
she always has Halloween decorations up.
I know, I've been studying her.
You ever notice when she goes downtown,
all the guys are falling all over her?
Have you seen how short her dresses are?
I guess I really haven't noticed.
Yeah right, all guys are suckers
for a girl in a witch costume.
They think that she'll
seduce him or something.
I don't quite get her yet.
I mean does she really
think she has powers,
or is it all just a show for attention?
I think she thinks she has powers.
Yeah, I guess that makes
her a more innocent character.
It's not exactly the most
exciting neighborhood,
but I'm able to save money
and concentrate on my work.
I'm kind of writing a novel
about characters in a small
town much like this one.
I'd say you're number three
on the list of local celebrities.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah, and ahead
of you is definitely the Ninja.
You know him?
Ninja?
You know, that guy who goes around town
dressed as a Ninja,
hardly ever says anything, really weird.
Oh yeah, maybe I've seen him.
And ahead of the Ninja
is definitely the bearded hobo
who lives down by the river.
I know that guy.
He stole my floating tube.
Well, I know where he lives.
I can take you there if you want.
You mean now?
Yeah, or are you afraid to
go into the haunted woods?
I'm not afraid.
It's just, well, I should be getting home.
My dad's probably gonna be
mad if I don't get home soon.
Okay, next time, see
you around, Freaky Farley.
It was the same old, same old with my dad.
He had me back out at the
hole first thing next morning,
but it didn't bother me one single bit.
I was on cloud nine.
I couldn't stop thinking about Scarlett.
I had to find a way to see her again.
You should really listen more
closely to your dad's show.
Not only would you not
do so much shoveling,
you might actually learn
something from him.
I listen to his advice all day long.
I don't need to listen to it at night too.
Well, I'm really excited
to start working at the station next week.
Anyway, how's it going with
the telephone company thing?
Your dad seems to think you got the job.
He's pretty proud.
Not proud enough that he
didn't punish me this morning.
Well, you know, you're
still living in his house.
You gotta live by his rules.
Why don't you go away?
Okay, I'm gonna go lay out
my outfits for work next week.
I had nearly forgotten about Mrs. Green
from the phone company.
What was I going to do about her?
I told her to meet me
after work that night,
and it seemed like she was really planning
to ditch her husband to go out with me.
She must've been in an unhappy marriage.
I decided to stake the place out.
See if she'd actually show up.
Hey, what're you some kind of weirdo?
Come on in, loverman.
Why don't we um, go to the hotel?
Actually, Mrs. Green,
I came here today to tell you
that I don't really wanna date you.
I only acted that way in the interview,
because I didn't wanna get the job.
Well, that's an interesting technique.
Yeah, I didn't think you'd
really be interested in me,
and I'm flattered that you were.
Well, I'm glad I flattered you.
Now, if you don't mind,
I need to go home to my husband,
and see if he is still willing
to go on the romantic weekend getaway
that I canceled with him for you.
I, um, I...
You, you, you, here's what's gonna happen,
first thing Monday morning,
I'm gonna give your father a call,
and let him know that his son
has no future in the telephone industry,
or in any other job in
this town if I can help it.
♪ Freaky Farley, where can he be ♪
♪ Outside my window staring at me ♪
♪ Freaky Farley, what's his plan ♪
♪ Peep as many girls as he possibly can ♪
Ooh, sorry, not usually that clumsy.
Come on, I'm gonna show you
where the bearded hobo lives,
so we can get your tube back.
I can't, my dad makes me
take a listening comprehension
test every morning.
He's gonna be up any second.
Forget him, let's go.
Brush teeth, then go.
Understand, good hygiene, then go.
I suppose most hobos have beards,
but I think he's the only hobo
in the entire town anyway,
and calling him just plain hobo
doesn't have such a good ring to it.
Don't you agree?
Yeah, the bearded hobo
sounds like a pretty good name to me.
So, I bet you're wondering
how I found out where you live.
Yeah, it had crossed my mind.
I did a search on history's
most notorious peeping Tom's,
and your name came up.
Really?
Yeah, no silly, I'm just joshing you.
Well, you said you had to go home
to listen to your dad's radio show,
and at that time of night
the only option is advice with Rick Wilder,
so I looked up Wilder in the phone book.
Hmm, clever.
I thought so.
There it is.
That bearded hobo, what a jerk.
I can't believe I've
never been here before.
I thought I knew every inch
of the Morgantown Woods.
We crossed that line a ways back.
These are the haunted woods of Fensdale.
Home to ax murderers,
druids, and the bearded hobo.
So, these are the Fensdale Woods?
I haven't been here in years.
My family's got a cabin out here,
but my dad doesn't let us go anymore.
He probably doesn't wanna be killed.
By whom?
Take your pick.
There are some crazy
cults that meet up here.
This one time on a big
rock, I found black candles,
a pair of panties, and a can of sardines.
Maybe some campers were planning
a romantic dinner or something.
Yeah, right, and then there are the rumors
about the violent forest beasts.
Let's get outta here.
What about your tube?
Oh, we'll come back sometime
when the bearded hobo's here,
and you know,
it would be better if
I had the satisfaction
of watching him watch me
take it away from him.
Okay, I'll buy it.
I was getting ready to call you chicken.
You know, um, if we keep
on hanging out like this,
you'll have lots of
chances to call me chicken.
Yeah, and anyway, I should be getting back,
because uh, forget about
being murdered by monsters.
I got a dad back home who's
probably planning to kill me.
Home sweet home.
Hey, looks like someone got up early today.
Yeah, I went for
a little walk in the woods.
I'm sorry I didn't leave a note,
but I'm ready to take my test.
Oh, no test today, son.
After all, you'll be employed soon.
A young man, not a boy anymore.
How'd that second interview go?
I'm not so sure I want the job.
Oh, you'll take the job, young man.
It's okay to have dreams,
but better to have a regular paycheck.
Yeah, I guess we'll be hearing
from Mrs. Green on Monday.
Good, I'm proud of you.
It feels good to say that.
I'm proud of you.
Dad.
Yeah, son.
I was thinking about the cabin
that we used to go to with Mom.
It's in the Fensdale Woods, right?
Whatever you're getting
at the answer is no,
and I don't want you to bring it up again.
Do you hear me?
That cabin is in the middle of
a dangerous stretch of woods.
You haven't been up there, have you?
No, sir, I don't even remember where it is.
Good.
Hey Farley, whatcha doing?
Leave me alone.
Golly, I was just gonna ask you
if you were gonna go see your girlfriend.
What're you talking about?
You know what I'm talking about.
Word around town is that
you and Scarlett Carter
are a hot item.
Where'd you hear that?
I know people.
Whatever.
What's bothering you so much?
It's nothing, it's just
my dad and I got in a fight.
What else is new?
Well, it's different this time.
I brought up a subject
that we never discuss.
The cabin?
How do you know about the cabin?
Well, your dad and me, we confide.
Yeah, ever since Mom died,
Dad never takes me there anymore.
I mean just because she
got in a car accident
on the way home from the cabin?
I don't get it.
All I can say is this, trust your dad.
He's a wonderful man.
I'm going this way.
Mom had driven out to the
cabin one weekend in May.
I remember because my
birthday's on the third.
She was going to straighten
things out for the summer.
The next day,
Dad told me she had died in a car accident
while driving home.
After that we never talked about Mom again.
I was feeling pretty low, Mrs. Timson,
but it didn't last.
And why was that.
Because I saw Scarlett again.
There was just something about that girl.
She seemed to make all
my troubles disappear.
Just a minute.
Let me reload the tape.
But what if I wanna keep telling the story?
Like the time...
No, no, wait, wait,
wait till I load the tape.
Are you ready now?
These were the best days of my life by far.
Just being around Scarlett was
changing me for the better.
So, besides walking, what
do you like to do for fun?
Do you like to go to parties?
Have you ever been to a party?
Farley.
Do you like that girl?
You should go talk to her.
Oh no, Scarlett, I couldn't do that.
I get kind of nervous around girls.
Besides, that dog looks ferocious.
All you need is some practice.
Pretend I'm that girl.
Um, I, uh.
Forget that, I'll be you, you be her.
I'm Freaky Farley, I usually
spy on girls through windows,
but now I'm gonna talk to you face to face.
Just kidding, more like this.
Oh, what a cute dog you have.
What kind is it?
Uh, uh, I don't know.
You don't know what kind of dog you have?
What kind of pet owner are you?
You wanna go to the movies?
Sure, Scarlett, I'd love
to go to the movies with you.
Perfect, see how good it works?
Now, go ask her.
Aw shucks, we missed her.
You'll just have to talk to her next time.
Come here, there's
something I wanna show you.
Oh my God, he's doing some
kind of cat scratch thing,
like tiger kung foo or something.
Check it out.
Silly Ninja.
I think this is all for show.
I bet he couldn't even beat me up.
Yeah, he looks like a
total wimp, no offense.
None taken, I'll test our
little theory, watch this.
Hey Ninja, you think because
you wear those ninja clothes
and do those stupid exercises
that nobody will challenge you to a fight?
Well, you're wrong.
I challenge you to a fight.
All right.
I did it, I intimidated Ninja.
Am I your hero, Farley?
Um.
I said, am I your hero?
Yeah, maybe I should put you down.
I think that's a good idea.
Scarlett!
Farley, if this is about you
having some sort of crush on me,
you can forget it.
You're not man enough
for me and you know it.
Now, come on, let's go get your tube back
from the bearded hobo.
Of course, her
telling me that I wasn't worthy,
made me love her more.
She was everything I'd
dreamed of in a girl.
I didn't even care that she
belittled my meager attempt
at a profession of love.
She was right anyway.
I couldn't handle someone like her.
That weekend was the
best weekend of my life.
Dad wouldn't find out
how I blew the job interview until Monday,
so I had two precious days of freedom
that I could spend entirely
with my new friend, my
best friend, my dream girl.
What?
Ow, that hurt!
Oh, it's you again.
Look, little lady, why don't
you just stop terrorizing me!
I've got enough to handle
with this family of trogs out here.
You know, they're not babies anymore.
They're getting bigger and
bigger and hungrier and hungrier.
Yeah, yeah, the trogs.
I'm still mad you poked me.
I could sue you for all
you're worth, you know.
No, no, please don't, I'm sorry.
I didn't know you were there.
I'll do anything.
Why don't you take me to see
the trogs, Mr. Bearded Hobo?
Sure, sure, hey wait, why
do you wanna go see the trogs?
Don't you know they're dangerous?
I still wanna see them, or I'll sue.
Oh, okay, okay.
Now!
Nobody steals from Freaky Farley!
You little minx.
Sorry, I guess you'll
have to show me your trogs
some other time, Mr. Hobo.
Do you always speak of
yourself in the third person?
I thought it would
be nice for dramatic effect.
I liked it.
That guy's crazy.
He always talks about these
trogs that he takes care of.
I didn't know that you'd
ever even talked to him before.
Oh, yeah, I go out there and
terrorize him all the time.
We need loonies out there.
It makes the world more interesting.
Let's go swimming.
But Scarlett, I don't
even have a bathing suit.
Don't tell me you need
a swimsuit, nature boy.
You practically live in the woods.
Scarlett, uh, what do you mean?
Scarlett, the water's uh,
the water's really cold.
Wow, Farley, you have no problem
watching naked girls through their window,
but you have a lot more
trouble when they're close up.
Tomorrow we'll steal the
key to your dad's cabin,
and the next day we can
go check the place out.
Okay.
I'll meet you at your place tomorrow.
Now, get out of here.
I'm suddenly quite ashamed of my nakedness.
All right.
Just, just catching up on my reading.
Son, it's time we talked about women.
Dad, I've heard your
opinion on relationships
every night on your radio show.
I think I know your views.
A father has every right to
talk to his son man to man.
Well, what is it?
Well, I understand that you've
been seeing a girl lately.
How do you know about that?
That's not important.
A father has every right to
know what his son is up to.
Now, let me tell you something.
I really believe that you should stay away
from that crazy girl,
and start seeing a nice,
wholesome young woman.
You don't know anything about Scarlett.
I might not know much about her,
but I do know a lot
about the girl next door.
She's a sweet, kind,
young, intelligent woman
that would make a perfect
daughter-in-law some day.
Katie, are you serious?
She's the most annoying girl in the world.
You may find my advice
slightly annoying, son,
but someday you'll come to appreciate it.
Now, just consider Katie for awhile.
I'm not gonna punish you for your rudeness,
because you did so well
on your job interview.
Someday you'll be an independent man,
and you'll make your own decisions.
My only hope is that you choose
to obey and respect you father.
I'm gonna go take a walk in the woods.
Hey, Farley.
You were just listening
to this whole conversation?
You and my dad are unbelievable.
You wanna come with me
for the Spencer Farm Moonlight Hayride?
No, didn't you just hear me call you
the most annoying girl in the world?
Get out of here.
Okay, deny your feelings if you must,
but you know where you can find me.
The next morning while Dad was away,
Scarlett showed up.
She wanted to find the key
to the cabin and maybe a map.
I was a little scared, but
I couldn't say no to her.
Now, if I was a key, where would I be?
Scarlett, we gotta be careful.
My dad will notice if
anything's been moved.
We'll find it.
Farley!
Oh man, that's my dad.
He doesn't let me have
girls over the house.
He's gonna kill me.
So, this is your plan, Farley.
Wait till your father gets
home and get me in the closet?
Oh, Scarlett, I wouldn't do anything...
Whatever, come on, we've
got a window to climb out.
What do you think your dad
would've done if he found us?
I don't even wanna think about it.
Do you think violence would've ensued?
A few years ago no,
but lately he's been goin so crazy, maybe.
See that guy?
Yeah.
I call him the lyric poet.
He's really cool.
Always here composing poetry,
probably about some girl.
Yeah, probably.
I like a guy who goes to the
library at least one a month.
Anyway, he's gonna be a
major character in my book.
Am I in your book?
We'll have to wait and see.
Here's a map of Fensdale Woods.
Your dad's cabin is right here.
What good's the cabin
if we don't have a key?
Oh, I forgot to mention.
I found the key in the closet
when we were oh so close to each other.
So Farley, are you gonna
invite me to your dad's cabin?
Yeah, um, I wanna get there a little early
and check it out though.
Why don't you meet me there at noon?
The next morning was like a
trip back to reality for me.
I had such a great weekend
that I'd forgotten all
about Mrs. Green's promise
to call my dad.
But as soon as the phone
rang, I knew it was over.
Hello?
Well, I'm sorry to hear
about that, Mrs. Green.
He will be getting a talking to now,
and for weeks to come.
All right, goodbye.
That was Mrs. Green, Farley.
She said that the interview
didn't go so well.
She also said that you were
completely unprofessional
and that you don't have a
future in any field whatsoever.
I'll go get the shovel.
No, this calls for more drastic measures.
First of all, you're not
to see that harlot again.
Her name is Scarlett.
Second of all,
you're to donate your
floating tube to Goodwill.
But I use my floating tube all the time.
Well, you should've thought about that
before you embarrassed the family, now go.
No.
Excuse me?
No, I won't do it.
You dare talk back to me
after all I've done for you?
Stop, you go out that door, and
there will be repercussions.
You'll be sorry, Farley Wilder!
I wanted to get out of Morgantown
once and for all.
Just start walking and never come back,
but first there was
somewhere I needed to go.
Somewhere I hadn't been in years.
As a boy, I had been so happy there,
and then suddenly everything just went bad.
Everyone always said the
Fensdale Woods were dangerous,
but I just had to see that cabin.
Why do you continually disobey me?
Why do you feel the need to test
every rule I've made for you?
You asked me why we don't come out here.
It's because weird things happen out here,
and if the mayor wasn't in such denial,
he would've done something about it by now.
I want to hear it from
you once and for all,
why won't you just tell me what happened?
Because it was all too painful.
Your mother was killed out here.
Saying she died in a car
accident just made things tidy.
It was all so confusing.
But if you just...
It's my burden to bare.
You were just a child,
and children shouldn't
have to be frightened
of mysterious deaths in the woods,
so I told you she died in a car accident.
And when you tell a story like
that, you better stick to it.
Lest they lose faith in you,
but you lost faith in me anyways.
You lost faith in your father.
Why, I don't know?
I've tried for years and years
to break that rebellious streak out of you,
and nothing, nothing at all.
You are a stubborn, stubborn boy
who is only gonna do
whatever you want to do.
Well, thanks to your stubbornness,
you put yourself in
danger and that girl too.
As it looks like you two
were getting ready to have
a little get together.
That's right, Scarlett is
planning to meet me here.
These woods are so dangerous.
I don't even know if
she's gonna make it here.
Why, son, why didn't you listen to me?
The rest of Morgantown
listens to my advice.
I get paid good money to give good advice,
but my own son is so pig headed,
he'd rather risk a young girl's life,
than to admit that his father is right.
Well, I am right, and
I've always been right.
Now, we're gonna finally figure out a way
to straighten out your life.
Now, I'm taking you home.
Are you disobeying me?
I'm only gonna say this once, get up.
Farley, how could you?
Like this.
He was finally dead and
that's when I saw her.
Katie, she'd seen it all,
and now she needed to be killed.
My trogs keep growing, Farley!
They're coming after me!
They're gonna eat me!
They're coming after me, Farley!
They're coming after me!
What happened after that?
Patience, Mrs. Timson.
Allow me to tell the story at my own pace.
Although I am getting a bit thirsty.
Now, where was I?
Well, you just stabbed the hobo,
and you were basically, completely insane.
Right.
Hey, dude, a little help.
Playtime is over.
Dude, not cool.
Hey, freakmiester.
Busy!
Too busy to talk to your
old pal, Air Force Ricky?
Whoa, don't you know it's
not polite to ignore people?
Recruitment day!
I was in a murderous rage, Mrs. Timson,
but I wasn't about to kill
a poor, innocent little boy.
Finally, I made it to Katie's house.
She was about to pay for all
those years of annoying me,
and agreeing with my dad.
She was about to pay the
ultimate price, but then.
I need the police!
I called earlier.
Where are they?
When I woke up,
they told me it was the
Ninja who did that to me.
Can you believe that Ninja?
What a wimp.
If we had fought face to face,
he wouldn't even have a chance.
Since then I've just been
in here waiting to die.
Sometimes though, I do draw.
What?
You're not telling me everything.
Well, I did leave out
all the times I went to the bathroom,
but I figured it wasn't
important to my story.
Quit it, Farley.
Something happened in the woods
on the day that you killed everyone.
Says who?
Says me, the examiner
says it was around noon
when your father was killed.
10 minutes later the hobo was dead.
Then it wasn't until four o'clock
when the football players died.
Now, you know as well as I
that it wouldn't take you four hours
to get back to town from Fensdale Woods,
especially for somebody
who knows those woods
as well as you did.
You could've done it in 45 minutes.
What're you suggesting, Mrs. Timson?
I'm suggesting that something happened
during those four hours.
Something that you've never
told anyone else about.
And what makes you think I'd tell you?
If what happened out there
is what I think happened,
it'll be well worth your while.
It could give you a chance
to see the world outside these walls.
Really?
Yes, really.
Well then, I never thought
I'd tell this to anyone.
I thought I'd take this one to my grave,
but if it means what you
say it might mean, why not?
Just after killing the hobo, I heard it,
I heard her, Scarlett's cries for help.
And mixed in with her cries,
something unlike I've ever heard before.
An unholy sound, a monsters roar.
Farley.
Scarlett, I'm so sorry.
I didn't know there were
beasts in these woods.
I never would've invited you here.
I'm so sorry.
Farley, it's not your fault.
I need you to do something for me.
In my room, above the garage,
in my desk, in a box is my manuscript.
I need you to get it published for me,
after you check it for spelling
and grammar, of course.
She was dead.
My Scarlett was dead and gone forever.
Then I came face to face with her killers.
That's right, Mrs. Timson.
The trogs really did exist.
I didn't even need my knife.
I was so filled with rage.
They had killed Scarlett.
They had killed my mother.
They got what was coming to them.
After killing the monsters,
I felt I could do anything,
but Katie was the first order of business.
I had to get her before
she told the police.
That's everything I need to know.
Thank you, Farley, we'll be in touch.
But what about your end of the bargain?
I just revealed to you the
only secret I've got left.
And I'll make sure the right
people find out about it.
Just give me a few days.
Farley, if you had to,
do you think you could
kill those beasts again?
You have no idea what I'm
capable of, Mrs. Timson.
No idea at all.
Luckily, these deaths have all happened
so deep in the woods
that nobody has had to
witness such tragedy.
Yesterday's incident, however,
was the closest to town we've had,
causing some to criticize our fine mayor
for refusing the governors offer
to send in the National Guard.
Here's what the mayor had to say.
Morgantown has always
taken care of its own problems,
and will continue to do so.
The only reason the governor or his army
should come to our town
is to take on our world
famous Apple Bobbing Festival.
A wonderful event, fun
for the whole family.
Hey, any visitors for me today?
No, nothing.
This is Tess Howard.
She answers the phone here at City Hall.
We call her the communications director.
Mr. Mayor, may I begin?
No, you may not.
This meeting is clearly confidential.
If anyone discovers
the woods are filled with the hungry trogs,
and not just routine grizzly bears,
no one will come to our Apple
Bobbing Festival this year.
Do you understand?
Now, let's hear from our town witch.
Thank you, Mr. Mayor.
I'm fairly certain I've
concocted the perfect potion
to rid this town of
beasts once and for all.
If you'll provide me with
the proper protection,
I'll go into the woods
and take care of business.
Well, sounds reasonable to me.
But, Mr. Mayor.
What is it?
Over the past year,
we have sent some of
our most resourceful men
into those woods,
and what has happened?
Each one of them has become
a delightful meal for these beasts.
There is one man who not only
survived his encounter with these beasts,
but he actually killed some of them.
Farley Wilder has never
admitted he killed those beasts.
Until now that is.
- It's true, folks, Dr.
Timson played me the tapes.
Farley really did kill those beasts.
But we can't let this maniac go free.
He's killed so many innocent people.
We won't give him any weapons this time.
He can kill them with his bare hands.
It's either him or the National Guard.
There will be no National
Guard coming to our town
for anything other than apple bobbing.
Let's not forget the
town's witch's suggestion.
I happen to think she shows some potential.
Mr. Mayor, you can't be serious.
Just look at her.
She means business.
Farley's the only one who
can kill these beasts,
but we know the one man
that can stop Farley.
Yes, freedom is mine!
Now, Farley,
the mayor has agreed to your request.
Each summer, one day a month,
you will be able to take
a relaxing tube ride down the river,
supervised, of course.
You will receive this reward
only if the team is successful.
You will be going into the
woods with two other people.
One will be Denise, the town witch,
who seems to think she can drive
the beasts off with a spell.
Apparently, the mayor was rather smitten
with this young girl,
and just couldn't refuse her.
The other will be Ninja.
Ninja?
That's right.
The mayor wants to make sure
you won't try any funny stuff,
like coming into town to kill again,
so Ninja will be watching over you.
Ninja, I can't wait to see him again.
Finally.
So, the infamous Farley.
Never expected to see
you out and about again.
Do you see that you've got
your arch nemesis here?
I've hired him to keep an eye on you.
One false move and he'll do
you in like he did before.
Farley, do you understand me?
Absolutely, Mr. Mayor.
So it's true.
Can you really kill these beasts?
That's right, Mr. Mayor,
and could kill you if I wanted to.
Luckily for you,
I don't feel much like
killing you right now.
You'll be free for one day,
then back to the loony
bin where you belong.
Do you understand, Farley?
Happy to help the city, Mr. Mayor.
What're we waiting for?
Let's kill some beasts.
So, what's in the bag, witch?
Lots of things, my spellbook,
my divining powders, my healing berries.
She seems pretty confident,
doesn't she, Ninja?
For your information, I am quite confident.
You'd be surprised by the
power that nature has.
Well, you'll be surprised
by the powers my fists have.
Just keeping you on your toes, Ninja.
How much longer until we get there?
My feet are killing me.
Hello, are either one
of you gonna answer me?
Trog tracks, and they're fresh.
We're probably close.
Time to start practicing
your spells, witch.
I was gonna practice anyway.
I'm not just doing it
because you told me to.
Copper, copper, behold the law.
Twice the moon beyond the sky.
Reach to cut the golden bough.
Perish darkness, quell the lies.
A lot of good
these nursery rhymes are gonna be.
Copper, copper, behold the law.
Twice the moon beyond the sky.
Reach to cut the golden bough.
Perish darkness, quell the lies.
This is it, witch, you're on.
Unholy powder for unholy beast.
Let me go, let me go!
Hey, Ninja, you ready to
watch a killing machine?
One trog down, who's next?
Hey, Ninja, you wanna finish this one off?
Well, Ninja, guess it's time for you
to bring me back to the mayor.
Of course, you could always say
that you lost me out
here in the wilderness.
No, you wouldn't do a thing like that.
You're an honorable Ninja, let's go.
Are you sure this is the place?
You're lucky I like you.
Otherwise, I would've left
you in the woods.
Ninja, what happened?
Did the beasts get you?
Farley?
He's on the loose.
I have to warn the people
now, the townspeople.
W-M-O-R, more talk radio.
Hi, you're listening to
advice with Katie Reidy.
Each day I proudly dish out
your daily dose of advice
in the spirit and tradition
of my mentor and advisor, Rick Wilder.
Right now, we have Lester on the line.
Thanks for calling, Lester.
Hi Katie, I just love your upbeat style.
Ah, thanks a lot, Lester.
You know, having a positive outlook on life
is really important to one's success.
I honestly don't know
where I'd be right now,
if I didn't look on the
bright side of things.
Same goes for me,
but the reason I'm calling
is that I have a bit of a problem.
You see, I usually have a booth
at the Morgantown Apple Bobbing Festival.
Oh, hold on, Lester.
Okay.
As most of you may know,
our fine mayor has a
direct line to the station,
and apparently he's calling right now
with an important message.
Oh, hello, Mr. Mayor.
Katie, I'm afraid I have some bad news.
Convicted killer, Farley Wilder,
escaped from Manarmy Home
for the Criminally Insane.
Direct all citizens of
Morgantown stay in their homes,
lock their doors, and remain
there until further notice.
The police force is on high alert.
Please continue to spread the word
to your listeners
throughout the night, Katie.
Do you understand me, Katie, Katie?
Katie!
Hello, Morgantown, hello, Mr. Mayor,
and welcome to the first addition
of The Freaky Farley Show.
I'll be taking your calls.
♪ Hey, baby, I don't wanna win back time ♪
♪ Don't need to tell ya
that you're out of line ♪
♪ Another thing that's going around ♪
♪ I don't need a love
that'll bring me down, yeah ♪
♪ Forget about that without saying a word ♪
♪ You know it's all right,
baby, I'll be heard ♪
♪ The ring pays better than
playing rock and roll ♪
♪ My ship came in but
my pockets are empty ♪
♪ My heart can't pay for
the bills they send me ♪
♪ They say salvation is
damn good for the soul ♪
♪ But there's only one way to do it ♪
♪ You better move it or lose it ♪
♪ There's only one way ♪
♪ Only one way to do it ♪
♪ Looking for an answer but I got no fill ♪
♪ Just waiting for the
moment is what I do ♪
♪ Ain't no fun to wait another day ♪
♪ Shooting like a star
right out of the sky ♪
♪ Faster than the eclipse of the TVI ♪
♪ I better burn out before I'm blown away ♪
♪ But there's only one way to do it ♪
♪ You better move it or lose it ♪
♪ There's only one way ♪
♪ Only one way to do it ♪
♪ There's only one way to do it ♪
♪ You better move it or lose it ♪
♪ There's only one way ♪
♪ Only one way to do it ♪
♪ Freaky Farley is coming for you ♪
♪ You better lock your doors tonight ♪
♪ He's gonna fill you
full of fear and fright ♪
♪ Well, since his mama died ♪
♪ It's just him and his dad ♪
♪ Who makes him dig a hole
when he does something bad ♪
♪ He starts believing everybody ♪
♪ When they call him a freak ♪
♪ Until Scarlett comes to town ♪
♪ And befriends him for a week ♪
♪ Instead of spying on girls ♪
♪ Now he's with a real one ♪
♪ They go around town and
they have lots of fun ♪
♪ Freaky Farley is coming for you ♪
♪ You better lock your doors tonight ♪
♪ He's gonna fill you
full of fear and fright ♪
♪ Well, he kills his
dad in a cabin of logs ♪
♪ Then he finds that Scarlett
has been killed by the trogs ♪
♪ He kills the trogs and everyone in town ♪
♪ He would've kept killing
but Ninja took him down ♪
♪ But it's not his fault ♪
♪ He's a tormented soul ♪
♪ No, it's not his fault ♪
♪ He was out of control ♪
♪ But it's not his fault ♪
♪ It was his daddy's abuse ♪
♪ No, it's not his fault ♪
♪ But still that ain't no excuse ♪
♪ Freaky Farley is coming for you ♪
♪ You better lock your doors tonight ♪
♪ Gonna fill you full of fear and fright ♪
♪ And now the mayor's in a jam ♪
♪ And the trogs are back again ♪
♪ He takes a risk and frees
Farley from his chain ♪
♪ He tells him kill the trogs
with the Ninja as his guard ♪
♪ But Farley won't be stopped ♪
♪ For him it's not hard ♪
♪ Freaky Farley is coming for you ♪
♪ You better lock your doors tonight ♪
♪ He's gonna fill you
full of fear and fright ♪
♪ Freaky Farley is coming for you ♪
♪ You better lock your doors tonight ♪
♪ He's gonna fill you
full of fear and fright ♪
♪ Freaky Farley is coming for you ♪
♪ You better lock your doors tonight ♪