Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
[Steve] Mr. President.
[reels whirring]
We have to act now.
They marched on Poland,
and we did nothing.
And they kept marching.
They've taken control
of most of Europe. And Russia.
- It's...
- [Roosevelt] An invasion.
[Steve] That's not all,
Mr. President.
He's been searching
for ancient artifacts
since 1933.
[Roosevelt]
You mean magical artifacts.
Merciful heaven.
What a maniac.
Unless, of course...
he's right.
I take it that's where
your big idea comes in?
[Steve] Let me introduce you
to the team.
Rex Tyler, known as Hourman.
He's one of the best scientists
America has to offer.
Now, he's developed
a chemical called Miraclo
to enhance speed,
strength, everything.
An hour at a time.
Then there's Dinah Lance.
- A bit of a fire brand with sonic sound abilities...
- [shrieking]
...that have gotten her shunned
by her community.
Next, since attaining
his powers of speed,
Jay Garrick has been
a full-time crime fighter.
And he's willing
to serve his country.
Finally, Carter Hall,
an ancient Egyptian
in a modern Egyptian's body.
Oh, and he's got wings.
[Roosevelt] Ancient Egyptian?
You can't be serious.
[Steve] Claims this is his
[clears throat]
fourth reincarnation.
- [Roosevelt] He's one of ours?
- [Steve] Yes, Sir.
[Roosevelt] I see. Lights.
[clicks button]
And you think they're enough
to fight back the Nazis
and magical artifacts?
I know they are.
But, who will lead
this motley crew?
I think
I've got someone in mind.
What do you say, Mr. President?
Are you ready to end this war?
[dramatic music playing]
[birds chirping]
[Barry] I can't remember
if I locked the car.
Or the apartment.
Or turned off the coffee pot.
[Iris laughing]
Honestly Barry, I don't know
how you've survived this long.
Hey, this is
our first trip to Metropolis,
I want it to be perfect.
According to the trajectory
of the sun,
we should have
the max amount of light
if we set the blanket... here.
Think we'll see Superman?
I thought you were
taking a day off.
Right, right, you're right.
[scoffs] I should have
brought sunscreen.
- Can I get your back?
- [sternly] Barry...
Cold cuts, bread, mayo.
Oh, I forgot the cheese.
No, Barry.
Do you think it might rain?
- I can grab an umbrella, just in case.
- Barry, just...
focus.
Everything okay?
What are we doing?
We're having a picnic.
You wanted to get out of town,
away from...
[whispers] my other job.
But, we're never fully away
from your other job.
[somber music playing]
That's not fair.
It's who you are,
and I love that about you.
But, Barry, it's been... years.
What do you want from me?
Is this just a fling?
Because I...
No, no, Iris...
It's okay if it is,
but I'm not interested in...
I love you.
It's just...
the best way to keep you safe is
by making sure no one finds out.
If you really believe that,
then break up with me, Barry Allen.
Iris...
Life is dangerous.
It shouldn't stop us
from living it.
[distant explosion]
Go. You have work to do.
I... I'll make it up to you.
Tomorrow. I promise.
- [glass breaking]
- [all screaming]
[sinister music playing]
Resistance... is... illogical.
[grunting]
I have you now, Superman.
[grunts]
Superman! What can I do?
[straining] Maybe help
with the tentacles?
Right. Sure.
[grunts and groans]
Are you all right?
I will be
after we take care of Brainiac.
What do you say?
Interested in a team-up?
I thought you'd never ask.
Another meta.
- Chance of success down to 95%. Recalibrating.
- [beeps]
[machine whirring]
[grunts]
Accelerating projectile.
[buzzing]
[groans]
Superman!
Recalibration. Success at 99%.
[whirring and beeping]
Are you okay?
That gem... it's Kryptonite.
It's the only thing
that can hurt me.
But, you're like a God.
So, what's the plan?
Don't get hit. Avoid the beam.
Punch really hard.
Save the day.
I like it.
[Flash grunts]
[ominous music playing]
[Dr. Fate's voice echoing]
Keep running!
Follow my voice.
[ominous music playing]
[soldiers grunting]
[growls]
[groans]
[sinister music playing]
[glass breaks]
[gun cocking]
[soldiers grunting]
[screaming]
Any sign of him?
Not yet.
We should have gone with him.
We had our own mission.
We're running out of time.
Rex's hour is almost up.
If we don't leave soon,
civilians will die.
We wait.
Steve won't let us down.
Go check on the left flank
and report back.
[Flash grunts]
[straining] What kind
of crazy gun was that?
It will take more
than the speed of Hermes
to stop an Amazon, fiend.
Who are you?
So, they've got
one of their own.
- [planes whirring]
- Wait, what?
[guns firing]
Wonder Woman, what's the plan?
Regroup with the others.
Tell Carter
to take care of the planes.
We need to buy more time.
Did President Roosevelt
send you?
President Roosevelt?
What? What's happening?
Keep an eye on...
whatever this is.
I got him, boss.
Am I dead?
Sometimes feels like it
in France.
France?
- [man shouting in German]
- [woman pleading in French]
Someone's in trouble.
Everyone's in trouble
right now.
You're not going any... where.
[woman shouting in French]
[all pleading in French]
[speaking German]
[guns cocking]
Nazis?
[clangs]
[guns firing in slow motion]
[Nazi soldiers grunting]
[breathing heavily]
What... what is... [groaning]
I've never been
out of breath before.
[straining] Not again!
Who've you got there,
Wonder Woman?
Is he one of theirs?
It's unlikely he'd be working
for the Germans.
[straining] Right.
So, I think
I know what's going on here.
I can't... breathe.
[gasping and breathing heavily]
I'm... I'm from the future.
Jay, report.
Uh, it's not impossible.
I mean, with the Speed Force.
Sounds more like something
a Nazi would say.
There are things that
we don't understand, forces...
I don't want to hear
about reincarnation, Carter.
Make him talk.
What about your lasso?
I'll get him to talk.
[cracks knuckles]
[sternly] We don't have time
to discuss this.
[explosion]
We've got a fight to finish and I
have less than ten minutes left.
[planes whirring]
Take cover!
[glass breaking]
Wait!
[Hourman] It's Steve!
[triumphant music playing]
Hawkman!
[ominous music playing]
Based on the trajectory,
the velocity,
Hawkman's wingspan...
he won't make it.
[Steve] Come on! Come on!
[engine explodes]
[engine sputtering]
Let's try for
one piece, Trevor.
[Flash panting]
[grunts] Whoa! What's going on
with my speed?
[breathing heavy] You got this.
Come on.
What now, Red?
A Flash classic.
[electricity crackling]
[Jay groans]
[sizzling]
It's good
to see you, too, Princess.
[Flash panting]
I see you picked up
another playmate?
It seems I misjudged you.
Thank you.
[panting] Heh.
- Retreat back to our extraction.
- Wait.
They're gonna
tear this village apart.
Look, I saw another division
headed this way.
They're looking for me.
We can't leave them.
Spread out.
Hourman, you and Jay
with me on the ground.
Carter, you and Dinah
take the sky.
- And I can do...
- Nothing.
Look, if you really are
from the future,
we can't complicate
the timeline.
Oh, right.
I've seen that movie.
Get Steve to the extraction
point in one piece.
He'll lead the way.
[Flash] This is crazy.
I've never seen this many
heroes working together.
[Steve laughs] Kid,
you ain't seen nothin' yet.
How come I've never heard about them?
About this?
The JSA?
Justice Society of America.
Yeah I know. Corny.
We're top secret.
Real high-level stuff.
Even have a war correspondent
embedded with us
to spin the stories.
Keep the super-powered team
off the front page.
Why try and keep it a secret?
This is the coolest thing
I've ever seen
and I can run faster
than sound. Usually.
Coolest? That's nifty.
Look, they're not infallible.
And if Hitler found
any sort of weakness,
it will be the end of the world
as we know it.
[Black Canary shrieks]
- [shrieks]
- [screaming]
[all grunting]
[straining]
[speaking German]
[grunts]
We've used the giant bird
excuse twice in the last month.
I don't think we'll
get away with it a third time.
Let's not push our luck.
Just refer to Carter's attack
as an experimental prototype.
Be sure to give the soldiers
all the credit.
They protected the citizens.
Without them, we wouldn't have
been able to focus.
Makes my job easy.
And what do I write
about this guy?
Nothing, as usual.
We don't even know your name.
Oh. Uh... I'm Flash.
Well, we've already got
one of those.
How about Future Boy?
That will work for now.
Future Boy,
this is Shakespeare,
our war correspondent.
Do I know you?
[Steve] Princess,
I've waited long enough.
Is this happening?
This is happening.
[Steve] I can't
hold this in anymore.
Will you marry me?
Good attempt, Trevor.
He upped his game.
[chuckles] Flowers.
If he doesn't quit soon,
I'll lose my bet.
Wait... what was that about?
He proposes every day,
and every day she says "no."
Didn't take you for a stalker.
Stalker? Is...
You mean like a cad? A wolf?
No, no. It's...
it's nothing like that. I...
If it really bothered her, I...
She promised one day
she'd say yes.
When... when it was
the right time, of course.
And that...
Well, that makes
every other day just worth it.
Thank you, soldier.
Extraction's here.
Of course, you know, if she ever does
say yes, I might drop dead from shock.
[birds chirping]
[Wonder Woman]
We said we would end this war.
It's been two years.
That's not our call, Diana.
Too many people
have died already.
- We can stop this.
- [loud crash]
Oh my goodness.
Please, take a seat.
You want to stop this?
Future Boy could stop It.
That's not a good idea, Dinah.
We can't use the future
to change the past.
It would create a paradox
and this Flash won't be able to
return to his own time period.
Or this could be
how it happens.
That much I knew.
See, there's this movie...
Paradox. Unable to go home.
Right. Shutting up.
[Wonder Woman] Dinah's right.
We need to utilize
every meta-human we can.
We can't keep putting civilians
in danger.
Well, I suppose
those of us without power
are just chopped liver?
So, we're just supposed
to let people die?
Oh, we can handle ourselves,
your Highness.
Don't worry about us.
Oh, I get that the rest
of the gang have powers...
War is a place for warriors.
Not a place for wishes.
Well, everybody's gotta die
some time, Princess.
I won't.
Look, it's gonna take everyone
to get off the sidelines
and onto the field
to win this war.
And if I die,
at least it'll be
for something I believe in.
Are they always like this?
Like a broken record, son.
[Steve] You've got
a new mission.
We can't decode the intel.
So, that fight was what? A gas?
What exactly was
this intel supposed to be for?
The Germans are looking for
a new artifact.
They're saying
it's a game changer.
If we can't read the code,
then what's the mission?
Now, I have a lead
on some help.
A man with mystical abilities.
They pulled him
out of their camps
and stuck him in a securely
guarded castle in Bavaria.
They say he can break any code.
Problem is... he's insane.
Insane?
And what are we
going to do about him?
What do our scientists think?
The best course of action...
After narrowing in
on the potential outcomes...
Not to mention
the quantum physics,
which is really something
that should be studied here...
To the point, gentlemen.
He should stick with us.
For research.
Then, Future Boy...
welcome to the team.
[crickets chirping]
[vehicle approaching]
[suspenseful music playing]
We should slip in
without notice.
You've seen your wings, right?
This place is a fortress.
We won't be able
to take it by stealth.
Stick to the plan.
You all know what to do.
Jay and Rex worked these out.
They're for communication.
When you have a message,
tap the earpiece in Morse code
and the message will be
received in our own ear pieces.
Oh, do I get one?
No. You're with me, Future Boy.
Let's move out.
[yelps]
[soldiers grunting]
[gun cocking]
[clangs]
Shouldn't we have attempted
to be more...
I don't know, stealth?
Carter worries too much.
You're very... upfront.
Like Steve said,
we all die sooner or later.
[sighs] What? It is a joke.
No it isn't. Not to Steve.
He thinks it's as simple
as asking a question.
He doesn't realize
what he asks.
[man screaming in distance]
That sounded...
Bad.
[earpiece beeping]
It's Steve.
He needs us to see something.
Now.
Can't you just zip in, take out
their guns and zip out?
- I could, but...
- But what?
Well...
my powers
haven't been acting right
since the other Flash arrived.
Of course.
Why is it always us?
[Jay] Don't belly ache.
It's not always us.
It's just mostly us.
I should take a swig
of the Miraclo.
You can't.
It's not been 24 hours yet.
I'm no use to you like this.
We're running out of options.
[gun cocking]
If this goes haywire,
blame the new guy.
[groans]
[gun firing]
[grunts]
[gun cocking]
Who says an old dog
can't learn new tricks.
[Black Canary sighs]
This is not what I had in mind
when I joined
an elite fighting force.
But you've got so much
experience digging through dirt.
You all right?
Regular good-time Charley.
You've been hard
on Future Boy.
It's just he...
he doesn't know
anything about us.
We're supposed to be
a secret.
No, I know, but...
But what?
[sighs]
What's the point of all this
if we aren't even remembered?
We fight, we die.
Death probably isn't scary
when you have someone
waiting for you.
And what about the nice
detective back home?
Larry?
I don't really think
he's the one. You know?
Listen, I know
things seem dire,
but one day
this will all be over
and we will all need
to live again.
For me it's finding
that other half
that I look forward to.
[man screaming]
[tense music playing]
That's, uh...
That's not what
I think it's for, is it?
[chains clanking]
Shakespeare is looking.
Diana...
I didn't know.
Let's go help.
Two corridors left.
I'm checking now.
[door creaking]
[flies buzzing]
[flies continue buzzing]
[coughs]
[door creaks]
It's... you.
He said you would come.
And here you are.
This is yours.
I'm supposed
to give this to you.
What are you
talking about, kid?
Take it. Use it.
You have to make sure
it never happens.
I'm sure that's why
I'm back here now.
He said you'd know
what to do.
Who said?
[soldier] Halt!
[gun fires]
[grunts]
[creaking]
[Jay] How's it going?
[thudding]
[water dripping]
[Dr. Fate] Should we tell?
Yes. Yes, they should know.
They should know.
[speaking Latin]
No. It...
it can't be.
[continues speaking Latin]
Do you know this guy?
[groans]
I know him
from a previous life.
Is this...
He's the code breaker?
He wasn't like this before.
Well, make him snap out of it.
- We're not equipped to handle...
- [Dr. Fate] Dead.
They're all going to be dead.
[shuddering]
They need to know.
They should know.
Jay, do you have the code?
We need your help, my friend.
Can you translate this?
[gasping]
[groaning]
Well, that was anti-climactic.
[groans]
[Steve] Shakespeare,
the bullet hit you dead on.
Steve, release these captives.
You keep calling me
Shakespeare, but it's...
[exhales]
It's Clark.
It's Clark Kent.
Well, you... you're Superman.
It's me, Flash.
How did you get here?
Did you follow me
through that time warp?
Is this a rescue?
Why do you have a mustache?
Stuck? What are you
talking about?
You... [sputters]
You're Superman.
You fight for truth, justice.
You save people.
I don't even know how
to wrap my head around this.
You are invincible?
I'm a little tough-skinned,
that's all.
If you stand by
and do nothing...
you are as bad as the Nazis.
[chain clanking]
You're wrong.
Then why are you here?
- To get this story.
- But you...
You're one of the most
selfless people I know.
I don't know you.
In my time on this planet,
I learned you look out
for yourself.
This planet?
But in my time...
Something's different.
What about your parents?
Martha and Jonathan Kent
died in an accident
when I was three-years-old.
I was sent to an orphanage.
I'm going to make sure the
captives get out of the building.
Does that make me complicit?
Wait, this...
I'm not...
This isn't...
Are you all right?
I'm not in the past.
This isn't a different time.
What are you talking about?
This is...
this is a different Earth.
I have to find Jay.
Was he always able to do this?
This... and so much more.
- These are...
- Coordinates.
For where?
- It looks like...
- The Bermuda Triangle.
No, he's not ready yet.
Yes, he's received
the package,
but he doesn't know
what it means.
It's you.
I saw you when I traveled here.
Please, do you know a way
for me to get back home?
Back to my universe?
Your universe?
But this would be Earth 1,
the real Earth.
This is the multiverse theory.
You're not
making this up, right?
You may return,
but you have another task
ahead of you
and a lesson you must learn.
Only then can you...
No, I won't tell him
about the League.
You will see her again soon.
And...
You should go.
It's starting.
[Steve] Sounds like
this guy's gone cockeyed.
Maybe.
But Hitler worked hard
to keep this place a secret.
Where's Shakespeare?
[sighs] He's on his own.
What are the coordinates for?
The Bermuda Triangle.
But it's... it's a legend.
So are we. Got anything
for us, Future Boy?
We're not in my world.
This isn't my past.
I don't...
I don't know where to start.
Steve, can you get us a ship?
I'll do you one better,
Princess.
Just try it on.
See if it fits.
- You're relentless.
- That's why you love me.
[door creaks]
Two. Maybe three.
Down bubble, five degrees.
Slow propeller by 50%.
[hinges creaking]
Contact?
Two, maybe three ships
above us.
Do they know we're here?
We're about to find out.
[sonar pinging]
Ooh, is it hot in here,
or is it just me?
Splashes.
Down bubble, full speed.
Right rudder, 15 degrees.
[tense music playing]
[alarm blaring]
- Report!
- Leaks toward aft.
Engine room is flooding.
Where your tools,
and how do you fix leaks?
[pants]
[hinges creaking]
Ooh! And Iris says
I'm not handy.
[continues panting]
What's happening?
The depth charges have
knocked out our engines.
We have to surface.
If we surface, we're dead.
Is there any way
to restart the engines?
You have an extra
20 batteries lying around?
No. But I have
the next best thing.
[explosion]
Give me a hand.
There she is. What now?
We build up enough electricity
to jump start her.
[electrical buzzing]
Well, I'll be...
What the hell are you doing?
Going out there.
Look this behind me
and flood the tube.
Steve?
You are just so beautiful
when you're about to kick
some Nazi tail.
You know, there is a captain
on board.
Let me make an honest
Amazon out of you.
See you when I get back.
- [alarm beeping]
- Someone's flooded Tube 1.
Did you order
a torpedo launch?
- No
- [thudding]
Then what is it?
One guess.
Sir, depth charges...
They're...
going up.
[sonar pinging]
[explosion]
You okay?
Yes, we had... help.
What kind of help?
Some sort of... aqua men.
Greetings, surface dwellers.
On behalf of our king,
we welcome you.
What is this place?
An outpost.
A place where the people
of Atlantis can stay informed
about the irrational behavior
of the monkeys above us.
Rude.
Come. Our king
would like a word.
[beeping]
My King, here are the ones
that repelled the boats.
Welcome.
I am Arthur,
ruler of Atlantis and all of
the oceans of this world.
What brings you to my kingdom?
Your Highness, I am Diana,
Princess of Themyscira.
I know of your island.
I'm sorry for your loss.
Thank you, but what happened
there could happen
to the rest of the surface
world without your help.
The boundaries of my kingdom
far exceeds those
on the surface and demand
my undivided attention.
Tell me,
why should I care about
the affairs of those above?
Because these Nazis
will not stop
until the whole world
is theirs.
Above and below.
Yes, the blood of air breathers
does run hot.
I think you speak true,
daughter of a Hippolyta.
I will help you.
Sire...
[whispering indistinctly]
Come. There is something I have
that might turn the tide
in your favor.
Hm. The king of Atlantis
made a pun.
Please, in here.
I see nothing.
Quite.
[powering up]
[grunts]
I'm afraid Atlantean magic
is quite powerful.
There's no use
in trying to escape.
Maybe he would have if you had
gotten here sooner.
But now...
Heil Hitler.
Once upon a time,
a modern day pirate
smuggling, traversing the ocean
to make my fortune
and then,
a storm destroyed my ship
and the Atlanteans saved me.
Little did they know
that my particular talents
would grant me control
of their king.
[Hourman]
So you're human like us?
Then why side with the Nazis?
Don't you know
what they're doing up there?
Of course, I do.
It always pays
to be on the winning side.
And with the Allies superpower
team off the table... [chuckles]
Honestly, I'm surprised
you took the bait.
The codes.
You set us up.
Obviously. The war
is all but over.
And you have lost.
Enjoy the solitude
of this prison
because when we return...
[grunting]
No. Wait.
Why did I imprison those people?
They seemed upright...
True.
Because they are
the enemy, Sire.
They want to rule your kingdom,
pollute your water,
enslave your children.
Enslave? No.
We must help these Germans
win their war,
and then,
when both sides are weak,
we'll destroy them all.
Yes?
Yes.
It's time to show those above
what true power looks like.
[clanging]
- Give it a rest, will you?
- [panting]
We need a plan.
I think Red over there
is working on it.
- You okay?
- What? Yeah, yeah.
I'm just...
Ever since I've arrived,
I've been less.
Maybe I've lost some energy
from overextending myself
by getting
to this world, but...
The Speed Force.
What's the Speed Force?
Well, it's just
a working theory,
but it's a little like
photosynthesis.
You know, the way plants
convert sunlight into energy?
Imagine the Speed Force
is the sun,
and we draw energy from it,
converting it into
our speed abilities.
I've been having
the same problem.
If both of us are drawing
from the Speed Force
at the same time...
We'll be less powerful.
Although if we could somehow
combine our energy...
We might regain full power.
How will that bypass magic?
Physics are universal, Diana.
When I was younger, I could
vibrate between molecules
phasing through solid objects.
Have you ever done that?
Seriously? You can do that?
What the heck have
I been doing all these years?
All right.
Hands on the floor.
Start vibrating.
You'll feel it when it's close.
I'll try to help.
[grunting]
Keep going!
[grunts]
Oh, [chuckles]
I can't believe that worked.
Seize him!
[grunting]
Where did your king go?
I will tell you nothing,
mouth-breathing, finless...
[groans]
I yield.
- You made it.
- Thanks to Jay.
Stand back.
We have to get
to the surface.
Warn the Allies
of the Atlanteans involvement.
No, there's no time.
It turns out the Atlanteans
and Nazis are launching
a surprise attack against
the Eastern Seaboard of the US.
Then we stop them.
Yes, but that's not all.
One of the guards
said that King Aqua... Man
is headed down to the trench.
Someplace nearby.
He's going to unlock
some sort of cage.
So... what's in the cage?
I have no idea,
but it can't be good.
Right. You're coming with me
to stop him from opening...
whatever.
- And the rest of us?
- Take the submarine.
You have to beat them there.
Be careful.
I'm always careful.
We both know that's not true.
[tense music playing]
[sonar pinging]
I think I found them.
Dead ahead.
What does this do?
Oh!
Atlantean pressure suit.
Cool.
- [punches landing]
- [men grunting]
[men grunting]
[chuckles]
We were getting worried.
So were we.
Captain, I need you
and the boys
to get us to New York
as soon as possible.
It would be my pleasure.
You heard the man.
Let's move.
Take us out of this hell hole.
Full speed.
They've got quite a lead.
There's no way
we can beat him there.
We have to try.
Jay, how are you feeling?
Ship shape.
Are you up for supercharging
those batteries again?
I have to be. This is war.
Now, Your Highness,
use your trident
to focus your call.
Unlock the gate.
Bring the creatures.
Seal our victory.
Yes!
[grunts]
[glass cracking]
[Advisor] My.
You're a strong one.
Don't worry.
You'll get
your fill of violence.
[gasps]
Something is wrong.
Ah. My head.
[grunts]
Ah...
Good.
[rumbling]
What's... that?
[gasping]
[people screaming]
[man] Oh, God!
[siren wailing]
[grunts]
[Black Canary whistles]
Hey, fish lips.
How about a real fight?
[shrieks]
[beeping]
Keep it up, gents.
[grunts]
Master race, my rear.
Shake your tail, Canary.
[shrieks]
Join the army. Fight Nazis.
Fall in love
with an Amazonian princess
and end up in an Atlantean tank
taking on bad guys.
Steve Trevor, never complain
about being bored again.
Send these fish
back to the sea.
Sh...
[roars]
- [woman] Over there.
- [man] Do you see it?
- [boy] Look.
- [man] Is that...
[gasping]
[roaring]
They're going to destroy
your home, my King.
It's best
to destroy theirs first.
[pulsating]
[roaring]
[people screaming]
Hawkman, civilians.
I'm never eating seafood again.
I don't know.
I bet it tastes fine in butter.
Canary and I will
get the big guy.
The rest of you stop those...
things from getting
to the city.
Let's give them hell, boys.
After you.
How gentlemanly of you.
[shrieks]
[roaring]
[gasps]
[screaming]
[grunts]
[Black Canary] No, no, no.
It's okay.
You're going to be okay.
You're a terrible liar.
Stay with me, Carter. You...
[sobs] You can't.
You can't go.
[grunts]
I'm not leaving.
Not forever.
[grunts]
Listen, little bird.
You spend so much time
building walls,
keeping people out,
and I know
you've been hurt before, but...
you have to
promise me something.
Promise me you won't
give up on this.
On life.
On love.
Remember. [grunts in pain]
It's the only thing
worth living for.
[gasps]
Carter.
Please.
Chay-Ara.
I'm coming.
I'm...
[Black Canary crying]
[roars]
[shrieks]
[screaming]
[roaring]
Okay.
So I guess the big one is mine.
[grunts]
[Atlantean commander]
Surrender.
Sorry.
I'm an American.
We don't do surrender.
You okay?
Yeah, I think so.
[grunts]
Told everyone I wasn't much use
without...
And stay still. Here.
Put pressure on it.
[groans]
[straining]
Steve, what are you doing?
Whatever I can.
[Black Canary shrieks]
Yeah. That was me.
[snarling]
[roaring]
You call that a scream?
[shrieking]
[grunts]
Perfect.
You know? I gotta admit.
You're pretty tough
on the outside.
[explosions]
[Wonder Woman straining]
[engine accelerating]
Steve?
You okay?
Yeah.
[groans]
Just need a minute.
Take your time.
I got this covered.
Who dares?
[grunts]
Steve Trevor.
Colonel in the US Army,
Wonder Woman's boyfriend.
I admire your bravery.
But your fate
will be like the rest.
You have no business
fighting with gods.
But I do.
[Wonder Woman] Enough of this.
You will not win today
or any day.
The hearts of humanity
yearn for freedom
and I aim to help them
achieve it.
Then you are a fool.
I said enough.
What have I done?
Oh, what just happened?
[sighing] And good riddance.
[Advisor] You think this means
you've won?
You and your league
can't stop the Fuhrer's reign.
Can't you hear it?
The sound of defeat.
The sound of failure.
No. No. What did you...
[blade thrusts]
Ah, I won.
I always win.
Steve, you okay?
I'll be fine.
Go.
Mother of God.
If those bombers
reach the city...
[Black Canary] We have
to do something.
We can't just sit here.
[Wonder Woman] Where's Hawkman?
We might not have to.
Look.
What in the world?
No...
not this world.
[Flash] You shaved.
Shakespeare?
Clark.
My real name is Clark.
But you can call him...
Superman.
I don't understand.
Weren't you just a reporter?
I was... Am.
But I couldn't sit
on the sidelines any longer.
I guess it was time
to get in the game.
[Hourman] Diana.
Steve?
Stay still.
We'll get a doctor. We'll...
Ah, come on, princess.
We both know
that ain't happening.
[grunts]
This can't be.
I thought when
the war was over, we'd...
Tomorrow is never guaranteed.
Only today.
Right now.
That's why we fight, right?
[coughs]
But honestly...
being with you...
I wouldn't trade it for all
the tomorrows in the world.
So what do you say, Diana?
Grant a dying man
his final request?
[sighs wearily]
[Wonder Woman sobbing]
[Jay] Where's Aquaman's crony?
[Flash] I don't know
where he went.
There's not a trace.
And trust me,
this is what I do.
It's like he just...
disappeared.
[Black Canary] Don't worry,
Future Boy.
We'll find him.
Leave it to us.
Right now,
we need to get you home.
[Wonder Woman]
Thank you...
for everything.
We'll be sorry to see you go.
Yeah. I wish
I could stay but...
I've got a world of my own that
needs all the help it can get.
I can't take this.
You said...
you understood why I said no.
I was wrong.
Don't...
don't make the same mistake.
- [Jay] Ready, kid?
- [Flash] Yeah.
[grunts]
You were just... And then you...
I guess it doesn't matter.
Great work, Flash.
Thank you.
No problem, Shakespeare.
Uh, I mean, Superman.
Okay.
I should be off.
Nice working with you.
Wait.
Listen. Brainiac won't be
the last to show up
and threaten our cities,
our world.
There'll be others.
There always are.
But there are also
others like us.
Heroes.
Maybe if we stick together,
we can keep the peace.
You know...
Fight for truth, justice,
the American way.
What are you suggesting?
Like a club?
Yeah, something like that.
[Iris] How long were you there?
[Barry] Maybe a week.
Here, it wasn't even a second.
- Sounds...
- Crazy?
[laughs]
A little bit.
Yeah, it was.
Oh, shoot. I forgot something.
[giggles] Glad some things
haven't changed.
The future is uncertain.
It could be full of bad things
or good things.
But whatever the case,
it's better
to face it together.
I know we said that we could
always have tomorrow,
but whatever tomorrows I have,
I want them to be with you.
Barry.
What are you doing?
So, what do you say?
Will you marry me?
[gasps] Yes.
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull