[intro music]
Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
[crowd cheers]
Yes, yes.
Hey, Chief.
I'm not sure this is the right
time.
Fuck that. They know me, Sport.
Any chance your nine-inch claim
is a bit of an overstatement.
What?
Are you some authority
on my cock now?
I've seen that. I'm not sure
that makes me an authority.
When? After our workout.
Yes.
Well, it's not nine inches after
I peel off my bone handles.
Even still.
Even still what, shit bird?
The physics just don't equate.
[chuckles]
You think a woman of Jade's caliber
was going to settle for six inches?
Look, all I'm saying
is you are not nine.
[exhales]
Fine, eight.
If you think I'm
dropping down to seven,
you need to go see
a motherfucking optometrist.
[crowd cheers]
The [?] is dropping in 30 seconds, people.
Who wants him?
Fuck, yes.
You know what time it is.
[music]
[crowd cheers]
I love my baby so much.
I love you too, sweetheart.
[music]
Your time is now. Instagram.
I finally get to kill
myself a commie.
Lock and load, motherfuckers.
[crowd cheers]
I love you.
I love you too. Get him.
[crowd cheers]
After all the talk, all the insults,
World War III is finally erupting.
Tyron, USA versus Russia.
We've broken this fight down.
Stylistic,
literally down to a molecule.
These guys cannot stand each
other.
It's going to make
for a spectacular match up.
It could be an instant classic.
[music] [crowd cheers]
Cash is in the cage.
The crowd is on its feet.
Let's through it to the ring
announcer, Richie Simmons.
Come on.
Now, for the fight
we've all been waiting for.
From the sold-out
MGM Grand in beautiful
Las Vegas, Nevada,
it's time, for damage.
In the blue corner,
fighting out of st.
Petersburg, Russia,
standing five foot 8 inches,
weighing 170 pounds with
an impressive of 18 wins,
four losses,
the world's number one
welterweight contender, Timothy
'the Terrible' Koslov.
[boos]
In the red corner,
standing five foot
nine inches, weighing 171
pounds,
fighting out of Birmingham,
Alabama.
[cheers]
With a record of 37 wins,
one defeat,
the undisputed Lightweight
Champion of the world,
the undisputed Welterweight
Champion of the world, the Slayer,
Lukewood Cash [?].
[cheers]
All right, gentlemen, bring it in.
Bring it in, guys. Let's go.
Gentlemen, you've both received
your shots in the locker room.
You all know the rules.
If you want to touch gloves, do so now.
You can't just commie fuck
with nerve of agents fight?
It's 1:00 AM on the east coast.
Cash, do you want
to get this thing started?
This election-meddling
son of a bitch won't take long.
America, suck dick.
[crowd cheers]
Get back to your corners.
All right, let's go. Let's do this now.
Blue corner, are you ready?
Red corner, are you ready?
Fuck, yes.
Let's go. [bell]
[crowd cheering]
Come on.
Yes, yes.
That's it, fight's over.
Roses are red, violets are
blue.
I'm feeling pretty tits right now
but sure could really use a blow job.
That almost rhymed.
Eat your heart out,
Emily Dickinson.
Yes sir, baby.
Cash, you are not posting that.
Never baby.
Oh, yum, yum, yum, yum,
drink looks tasty too.
[laughs]
If that's all right, sweetheart.
Please do not encourage that, Jeez.
Its called humor, darling.
Not where I come from.
Oh, burn.
[laughs]
Isn't my son a face God, Dazz.
Here we go.
I mean it's hard
to believe with that
faggoty hair and those
pretty-boy looks.
Chief here slipped one
past the goalie back in college.
Sport was the youngest
ever to make the US judo team.
Can you please shut the hell
up and just drink your drink.
Deserey, we'll let you know
if we need anything else.
No problem. Just let me know.
Thank you.
Are you fucking blind.
She's tighter than
a seven-year-old Korean boy.
Enough with the damn Olympic
card.
Since when did throwing
out a resume for a tasty
piece of hair pie
become a goddamn crime.
Have a beer with me,
jack her back to the mansion.
No mansion jacking.
I've got a calculus test
tomorrow.
Fuck arithmetic.
Well, you need to know
mom's going to breathalyze
my ass right when I get home
too.
Goddamn whack job she is.
Hey, dillweed she might be
your ex but she's my mom.
Way to go, Jetty.
Apologies, Sport.
How is Miss Looney
Tunes doing anyway?
She's still on match.com.
No, threw in the towel last
month.
What about Tard? How's he?
Come on, can you please not
call him that for me, please.
Fine, pussy hole.
Don't you ever stop?
Yes.
About 10 seconds before I puke.
How is Timofey 'The Terrible'
feeling right about now.
About $3 million richer.
You?
I made a million bucks
per second last night, Sport.
Crap. This is me right
here on the left.
Love you, Jade.
You too, Jetty.
You got Kareef tomorrow at 3:00
PM.
I'll be there.
Thanks for including me.
Always, Sport, it's fun.
Fucker.
Hey.
Too slow pussy hole.
This is mine, fucker.
[music]
I'm going to need you to help
me out this afternoon, Jett.
Well I've got Kareef at 3:00
PM, Mom.
Just take his Xbox with you and
stick him in Patty's office.
Patty is busy, Mom.
No she's not, trust me.
I don't want to go to the gym.
He called me a tard.
I talked to him, that's done,
okay?
I want to play with Patrick.
No chance, baby.
But I want to.
Today's no good, Q.
Can you get him his meds
and finish up everything?
I got a client at 7:45.
Yes, go.
Just don't forget your lunches,
okay? I love you guys.
Yes, I love you too. Here you
go.
Swallow.
Open. Good man.
Hey, when you're finished?
Plate in the sink, brush your
teeth, and get dressed, okay?
Okay.
Hey, Jett. Hey Jett.
Yes?
Will there always
be toys in the world?
Look I've got a huge test.
Just tell me yes or no
and I'll promise I'll stop.
Yes, there will always be toys.
Forever?
Yes.
[bell]
Ace, what's up, bro?
All good man. You good?
Catch you, boys, later.
Alright.
Yo Q.
Hey, how you doing, man?
Looking handsome, dog.
Thanks, bro.
Feel good, boss.
My man.
Hey, your dad is filthy, man,
that's the only way to describe it.
Dude, where you there when he
made it rain at Olympic Gardens?
How did you guys see that?
Excuse me, I have a question,
do you guys ever stick out
your tongues at each other?
Quinn.
Quinn, did you know Fat Lexy
have big, giant lovely boobies?
[laughter]
Patrick, come on now.
It's funny, Mr. Stewart.
No, it's not funny.
Your dad is the shit.
Okay Jerry. Come on man, what's
up? You want detention?
No sir.
No, that language
doesn't fly in my class.
Make it quick, Jett.
Tongue fixation.
No it's not tongue fixation.
Jet what the heck is wrong with
you.
Okay, everybody,
calm down, all right.
Thanks for the heads up.
[background noise]
Thanks, Jett.
Improper integrals, huh?
Can you get lower than an F?
Seriously when she hands
back our tests mine's
going to have a big red
G written across the top.
No.
Hope this fighting thing works
out.
Nice baby, nice. You hit that
hammer. Again. Good, good.
Now, don't get lazy, come on.
Move together. QUick and fast. Let's go.
There you go. Move, move, move.
Go.
Vaughn's Fight Academy,
this is Patty.
Paid for this suit too.
Jamie's on two.
How's Quinn holding up in
there?
Other than asking me if he can
watch Pornhub, splendidly.
Jesus. All right.
Jamie, you shaved that
hideous fucking beard off yet.
Fuck you, Cash.
I'm sitting here with my attorney
Mr. Adelsberg, aka the Jew assassin.
He's just informed me
that you and Rami once
again are giving
it to me up the dirt shoe.
Shocking.
The gate, merchandise, pay per
view, foreign PPV all the way down.
Your numbers in Russia
alone aren't even close.
Yes, all right.
I'll get into it with Rami and
I'll get back to you fellows. Okay?
What does that even mean?
They're worse than Putin.
Yes, but they can be defeated.
Three, two, one. Good, twist.
[noise]
Is this Colbie fucking Caillat.
Caillat.
Holy fuck,
my son's a turd burglar, fellas.
How do you expect to issue
a beat down when you're
listening to all that West
Hollywood Meryl Streep bullshit.
Colbie's hot Chief.
Her, Taylor, and Selena, and they do
more for charity than you ever will.
I give millions to charity,
dickface, it's called taxes.
We got to hook you up.
System of a Down, Death Tone, Rob Zombie.
I love my girls, deal with it.
If you say so, Sport?
Are you ready to deal with me?
No, not a chance.
I can't even lift my arms.
Hey, I'm wearing skinny jeans,
buddy. We're even.
Get the fuck up here.
You don't need that pussy headgear.
Come on.
Come on, pussy. Judo fag mama's
boy.
[music]
Oh, shit. We've got a bleeder
here.
Cash.
Hey, Insta, what's up?
Yes, I'm back from Vegas
with my boy Jett here,
about to be arrested for child abuse.
Come on, Sport.
That's right.
Come on Jett, get fisted, baby.
Get fisted.
Take three,
maybe put on some of that Call Me
Maybe shit it'll wake his ass up.
Holy crap.
Finish him, what you doing?
This is fucking stupid.
You hit me in the fucking face,
huh?
Fuck off. Fuck off.
Fuck off. Fuck. I tap.
How's that feel?
Fuck off.
Yo, Patty, you delete that shit.
Now.
I'm deleting. Jesus.
[music]
Hey, Quinn, go to bed.
Am I good?
Yes, solid, Q.
Keep practicing you can be in a real
band soon slay babes left and right.
Now got to bed.
[laughs] Slay babe.
Hey, Jett.
What?
I have a question.
Do some girls have wieners?
Where'd you hear that?
I saw it on benaughty.com
[chuckles].
Are you visiting those sites
again?
Do you want mom to kill you?
I won't do it again. I promise.
Well, you do it again
and I'm telling her.
Because it's weird, right?
Yes. Very.
Now look, it's 10:20 go to sleep.
Oh wait, did I have melatonin?
Yes.
Can you have mom peek on me?
You promise?
Yes.
Okay, love you, Jett.
Love you too.
More than yourself? Say it.
More than myself. Now go to
sleep.
Hey.
Not again mom.
Made $200 in four hours.
It's twice what I make at Pro
Sport.
Where?
The Yard.
Mom, everyone we know goes
there.
Don't give me that look.
Physical therapists at 41 is great
but waitress at 41 is pathetic.
Providing for my boys is
pathetic?
How many nights a week?
No ballpark. Three, four?
Yes.
Four nights a week, I have
Quinn?
He's making millions.
You want to ask him for more
money?
Because I'm not doing that.
[sighs]
[tap water running]
I fought that son of a bitch
in court for 10 years.
All the while, he never gave me
a dime for Quinn's heart surgery,
never a dime
for his stomach surgery.
I know he's back in your life,
and I know he's helping you follow
your dreams, so I keep quiet,
but it's real goddamn hard,
Jett.
[phone ringing]
[background noise]
Got you good today?
Yes, I do. That was only
the second time in what?
22 years of fighting that
I got caught by a roundhouse.
Yes? When was the first?
10 years ago, Claude.
Is that the only time
you ever lost a fight?
In my life? Fuck, no.
Birmingham's 75% black.
Homies went Reginald
Denny on my ass hourly.
Hey, I got a nice
surprise for you tomorrow.
Don't be late.
What is it?
Then we multiply
all of this by delta X,
which is two over N, and this is
going to be the setup for rewriting
our definite integral
using Riemann sum.
[bell ringing] Have a good after
day, everyone.
[background noise]
How did you do?
Oh, sorry.
It's not your fault.
[background noise]
Bye, good job. See you. Good
job.
Great work. Good job. Great
work.
Yes, well, wish me luck.
What are you doing after
school?
Ms. Malek.
Hello, Jett.
Is there anything I can do?
Yes, you can avoid Las Vegas.
That trip was planned.
You've known about
this test for a month, Jett.
Oh,
what if I did some extra credit?
[sighs]
I think it runs a little
deeper than that.
That 41 was generous.
Look, you missed a lot
of important stuff last year.
What about a tutor?
If I don't pass your class,
I don't graduate.
Just $25 an hour.
Whatever it takes.
[music]
Yo, Chief.
You ready?
Yes.
Meet your sparring partner?
You want me to spar
Enrique Castaneda?
Number three
welterweight in the world.
We got to fix your jab.
Excuse me. Are you okay?
Are you sure?
Yes. I'm fine, ma'am.
I appreciate your concern though.
Thank you.
Okay. Hey, y'all.
[background noise]
Quinn, look towards me, please.
I'm watching the game.
There's no TV in here, Quinn.
Just shut up and look towards
me.
Finish your hamburger. Now.
I'm going to go watch the game.
[crosstalk] Hi.
Yes, is this Johnny?
My name is Jett Boykins.
I am a senior at Ramsey High.
Hi.
Hello. [chuckles]
My name is Quinn. What's your
name?
I was referred to you by Ms.
Malek.
I have a question.
Yes?
Do you like every shake out
your tongues at each other?
Yes, that works perfectly.
Thank you and I'll talk to you.
Bye.
So did you want to see it?
We're sorry to bother you, ma'am.
Start walking, Quinn.
Hey, stop pushing me.
What happened to your face?
I got my butt kicked.
Stop.
Shut up.
Get in the car.
[car door opening]
What is your freaking problem,
Jett?
It's all just so weird and
disturbing okay?
I can't take it any fucking
more.
Well, I have bullied syndrome.
Don't give me that bullshit.
It's my fault.
Yes, whose fault is it then?
You're such a jerk.
Ow.
I hate you.
I hate you back.
[sniffles]
That hurt.
Hey, Jett,
care to listen to Christmas
music?
You would have been
so proud of Kingston today.
Mr. Tanaka moves him up
from an orange belt to a green.
Hold on. He skipped blue?
He number one for his age.
[laughter]
Little fucking stud.
I love you.
I love you too, baby. What?
What's wrong?
I think I'm going to be sick.
We should go.
I just ordered the bone-in.
I know.
I'll order you whatever you want.
Please, I'm going to throw up.
Okay.
All right. All right.
[background noise]
Shit.
You sexy little minx.
Fuck, you're so beautiful.
You're so fucking beautiful.
[chuckles] I love you.
I love you.
Fuck.
Hey.
Yes, what's up?
Can we just talk for a second,
please?
Didn't we already
talk enough at dinner?
Let's see.
Kingston's kicking ass in karate
and you want a bodyguard, right?
It's about Susan.
I just went limp. Thanks. Fuck.
[grunts]
Listen.
I know you insist on keeping
her stuff separate from me.
I don't insist on anything.
We have a contract, remember?
Okay, well, I'm sorry to tell
you this but I'm your wife.
I'm going to have
an opinion or two on certain
topics which means you are
required to listen to me. Okay?
Okay. Go.
Cash, they need money.
Where is this shit coming from,
babe?
I've been thinking about this
shit for the past nine years.
We never help with Quinn.
He's not your son, Jade.
No, he's not.
He's your son but that doesn't mean
I'm not allowed to help care for
him, does it?
Fine. Take him for an
afternoon.
Have Kingston play with him.
Great, but that's it.
Why? Why, Cash?
Why can't we just love him?
Love him like we love Kingston?
Because he won't love us back.
My god. Of course, he will.
Why do you say that?
Why do you even think that?
Because she lied to them about
me.
Cash, you hit her.
Yes, after she attacked me,
honey.
I had to wait two years
before I could even see them.
No, she lied to the cops.
She lied on the stand. Fuck her.
She gets what she gets
and she shouldn't
be throwing a fucking fit about
it.
Because of her,
they have to suffer?
Suffer? No, they learn.
Hard work, adversity, struggle.
That's how winners are made,
not cuddling Kingston
around like a fucking...
No, no, no don't you
fucking do that shit.
Don't fucking start with me,
Cash.
I took fights for 2000.
I worked two jobs.
I had two little kids.
We were this close to
being homeless, baby.
My old man didn't give me jack
shit.
Your old man was an abusive drunk
who didn't have jackshit to give you.
If I give money to Susan, she gives
money to Jett and that can't happen.
We have four houses and nine
cars.
I'm done talking about this.
Four houses and nine cars,
Cash.
Jade, fuck you.
Fuck you, get the fuck out of
here.
Yes, I will you fucking cunt.
Hi.
Hey.
Did Quinn go to bed okay?
Yes.
I'm a terrible mother.
Mom.
How do I allow my child?
This is who I am.
Fighting isn't who you are,
it's what you do.
Clearly I fucking suck at it.
Bud, what happened?
I got my ass fed to me, Mom.
No, with Q.
I just wish I had someone else,
someone to share with
because it never stops.
I always feel like a failure.
I ask a lot of you,
it's not fair, it's not.
Did I ever tell you about my first
Williams Syndrome convention?
No.
I had no clue what
I was getting into.
Quinn had just been
diagnosed and I entered this
hotel lobby and saw 400
little Willy's running around.
I'm like, "Oh my God."
I was like a zombie going from
session to session obsessed with
getting information
to somehow fix this
problem and I hadn't even cried
yet.
When a mother learns that she's going
to have to take care of a special
needs child for the rest of her
life she requires a good cry. Right?
Yes, you didn't cry. Not once.
Then I went into the last
session of the weekend.
It was on siblings.
There was this doctor up there with
this long grey hair and this beard,
all these years
of research and experience.
He was talking about how
brothers and sisters of kids with
special needs turn
out to be the most
wonderful loving, giving adults.
I just lost it.
I could not stop crying,
tears just...
because I knew that would be
you.
How's the grill?
Hurts.
Yes, well you'll recover.
I know I will recover.
Look, sometimes it just seems
like you like seeing me hurt.
What the fuck do
you know about hurt?
I'm sorry.
You should check
out my fight against
Ricky Promoter Co
at some point tomorrow.
Pay close attention to my
striking and side leg kicks.
You're telling me this why?
You need to get away from your
judo, Sport.
Destroyed Randa,
it will destroy you.
Jaime wants his fighters
upright,
not swap and spit on the canvas,
capisce?
Kapsosh.
El hombre.
Woman.
La mujer.
Male friend.
El amigo.
Female friend.
La amiga.
Es muy guapo.
Hey, I'm sorry I lost it.
Love you, buddy.
I won't do that again, okay?
Okay.
Are we even?
I'll let you beat me
the next we wrestle.
Just once.
[laughs]
This week we are still using derivatives
to figure out limits but now,
we're looking at limits that
end in indeterminate form.
This is called L'Hôpital's rule.
[background noise]
[phones ringing]
I just watched the Prootr Co
fight.
Hey, Sport. I just woke up
late.
Can we talk about this at the
gym?
No. Don't give me that. What
gives?
Ricky was supposed to fight Mitch
Radowski next month in Memphis.
Mitch broke his hand yesterday.
Serious? Hell, put me in coach.
Jett, he's a tough fucking thick
neck with 28 fights under his belt.
You have three.
Come on, anytime,
anywhere on a moment's notice, Chief.
All right, pussy hole,
I'll get into it.
All right.
Say it, Quinn. Fuck.
I'm not going to say it.
My mom will kill me.
How will she know? Come on.
Fuck.
Hey, Patrick,
that's not how we roll, my man.
What did I do? Fine.
Hey, kid. Guess what, you get to
ride the bus home with Gerry today.
Wait. What? No chance. No.
What do you mean? You love the
bus.
Not anymore. I don't.
Tanner Van Holt rides it now.
You think I'm bad?
Yes. He said Santa isn't real.
Get out.
Last week, you threw Jerry's
thermos right out the window.
Buy you a new one, Gerry?
Come point him out to me.
Tanner, Van, Holt, number
71.
Hey, Tanner. I'm Jett.
Yes, I know who you are.
You threw Gerry's thermos
off the bus window last week?
I didn't know it was his.
It was rolling around
everyone's feet.
Right. Well, I'm afraid you're going
to have to buy him a new one, my man.
I'm not sure if that's
going to happen, Jett.
It's not a fucking question.
Get him a new fucking thermos.
All right, man. You got it.
You got that?
Yes, man.
Get the fuck out of here.
Hey, Jett.
You think you could have handled
that a bit more diplomatically?
Diplomatically?
Yes, like an adult?
You'll never understand.
I understand a jerk when I see
one.
Can you go ask Tanner nicely if
he'll buy Gerry a new thermos?
Can you do that?
Yes.
You're better than that.
Control the head. Control the head.
Grab your shirt. First triangle.
[grunting]
Good.
God. [grunts]
Nice.
Hey, Sport. Memphis.
Three weeks. Get psyched.
[cheers] [chuckles] Are you
ready, Kareef?
[background noise]
You went through a stoplight
with an open container?
Nice example you're
setting for your kid.
Well, you got to learn how to drive
with an OC at some point, sport.
Okay. Rule number one, always
keep
your roadie stove
between your thighs.
When a cop pulls you over,
his first glance is always the cupholder.
Rule number two, never sip while
flying through an intersection.
You got a lot of liberal
homos out there
who'd love to call 911 on your
ass.
Don't let liberal homos see me
drinking while driving. Got it.
Rule number three,
before each swig,
you check your side
views and your rear views.
[police siren]
Rule number four,
in case of an emergency,
hide the said beer in son's
pocket.
[music]
[car door closes]
I'm going to fucking
kill that bitch.
[police siren] [music]
Motherfucking shit.
[background conversation]
Of course. Are you kidding me?
Yes, sir.
Any day.
Thank you, sir.
[background conversation]
Yes, sure thing.
Again, my bad.
Yes, sir.
Okay.
[music]
[car door opens]
[car door closes]
Rule number five,
with Cash Boykins,
the previous four rules don't
apply.
[engine starts]
[music]
[car stops]
All right, Sport.
Come on in, Chief?
Two minutes? Come on, man.
Explain the deal. Get her pumped.
Say hi to your other son?
[sighs]
The shit I do for love.
[door closes]
Jett.
Hey. I've got a surprise.
Quinn, how's it hanging?
Good.
Susie.
Cash.
Look, you two need to talk.
Will you both please
take the high road?
I have, hundreds of times.
The low road's better.
[chuckles]
Jett, can you get a
bath going for Quinn?
He's stinky.
No, I'll put on deoderant.
No, you need to soak, okay?
Come on, Quinn. Let's go.
All right, guys.
Got anything to drink?
Just Chardonnay, in the fridge.
[fridge door opens]
[fridge door closes]
For the love of Christ.
[bottle lid opens]
[glass clinking]
[Chardonnay pouring]
I can remember your Two-Buck
Chucks smelling like cat piss.
You don't remember a lot of
things.
Oh, fuck me. I walked
right into that one, didn't I?
What do I owe this pleasure?
Got Jett a fight for the 28th.
WFA 247 in Memphis, third undercard
against Tricky Ricky Promotor Co.
Remember him?
Jesus.
Number 12 contender, should
be a solid litmus test for him.
Can he beat him?
Well, his kickboxing
certainly improved.
His grappling's solid.
What about his judo?
Fuck judo. What he needs is a
jab.
So find him one.
Does he need to miss school?
No. No, shouldn't.
Two hours with Kareef before
and after school should suffice.
How much?
WFA minimum, $10,000 a show,
another $10,000 for a win.
I may be able to bump
that up to $15,000.
I could front you $10,000 now
if you need help with Quinn.
We're not a fucking daycare
service, Susan.
Yes. That was my fault, I'm
sorry.
I knew you were incapable,
but I rolled the dice anyway.
All right.
Well, I'll have Patty wire the
10Gs into your account tomorrow.
You're welcome, Susie.
Fuck you, Cash.
[footsteps]
[door opens]
[door closes]
[crowd cheers]
Boykins, take a seat.
I'm now pissed.
Fucking stinks like a bitch.
Fuck it. Your inside
leg kicks are killing him.
He opened himself
up to a traingle chop.
I know. I fucking blew it.
If he does it again,
you put him to sleep.
Time is up.
Let's end this shit now.
Go, baby. Let's go.
Let's go. [bell rings]
How did you score round two,
Tyron?
I had that as a-
- Keep your focus. Stay focus
now.
big round for Boykin.
Barely minimal.
It's 10, nine, nine.
Come on, Champ. Not this.
It's been a very
close fight so far.
It may very well come
down to round three here.
Moleko is very fast.
That's a fast one.
I know.
[screams]
That's the kick.
He's going for a heel hook.
What an escape by Boykins.
Get this motherfucker. [cheers]
Counter. Big counter.
He's looking to-
- I think it's a counter. Ground
and pound. I think he's back up.
They are eating some
huge shock to this fight.
Look at this, a luminary rope.
Rolls right into his shoulder
lock.
Over plot. Now, we do a
triangle.
Come on. [cheers]
There you go.
He takes the advantage.
Now going for the body.
He's taking punches but he's
dishing him out as well.
Oh my...
[screams]
Going back and forth. [honks]
Just exhausted to end round
three.
It could come down
to a split decision.
The fight was very close.
Even that round, it was a thing.
What a fight. This is
really too close to call here.
Now, you got that baby.
It's all you.
[applause]
The judges are taking their
time.
Ladies and gentlemen,
we have a split decision.
Judge Watson scores the fight
29-28.
Boykins. [cheers]
You're a smart man.
[claps]
Judge Goldstone scores
the fight 30-27 for Motoco.
[cheers]
You are a cheat.
Come on.
Nobody likes you.
Judge Max scores the fight
29-28.
The winner, the Pride of
Ramses High.
[cheers]
Jett Boykins is your winner.
You showed a lot of heart there,
champ.
Unbelievable fight.
[crowd cheers]
That's what I'm talking about.
[claps]
I didn't doubt it for a second.
Come here.
[crowd cheers]
[music]
Thank you. Good day. Good
stuff.
That was super, Jett.
Good for the soul, Jerry.
Your ball buster.
Have you seen what's on chapter
15?
Point conversions.
That's what I live for.
Now, you care about conversions.
You're on autopilot girl.
What do you mean autopilot?
You didn't hear?
Kim got accepted into West Point.
Damn.
Is there anything you can't do?
Don't get me wrong.
I'm thankful to you both.
You built a $5 billion Goliath.
As a result, many of us have
created a level of wealth behind
our wildest dreams
but in the last five years,
you think in addition to owning
the WFA, you own its fighters.
I don't blame
you for thinking like that.
We've allowed ourselves to be owned.
You got five bill.
Well, 95% of your fighters under
your banner have very little savings,
health insurance that only covers
injuries, no pension funds.
You participate in revenue
sharing.
Yes, we do, Jamie.
Revenue sharing amongst the 512
WFA fighters under contract is 8%.
NFL owners and players
split revenues 50-50.
When you look at it like that, boys,
the WFA is a nice form of slavery.
I have heard enough of this
shit.
Calm down, Jamie.
We fighters,
we come from very little means, Rami.
When I was in sixth grade,
Sherman Steel kicked my ass.
I didn't come home for three
motherfucking days because
I knew my old man would beat me 10
times worse for, "Losing to a nigger."
I remember my first MMA paycheck.
$1850.
I went out, bought myself a 12'er
of Nati light, paid my rent,
pulled Jamie aside, and said,
"God bless you, Messa.
Thank you, thank you."
You are such a prick. I can't...
Goddammit, the truth hurts,
doesn't it, Jamie?
Here's the deal,
I own two WFA belts.
I bring in three million
pay-per-views per fight.
Without me, WFA is just three
letters in the fucking alphabet.
[chuckles]
We're a little bigger than
that, Champ.
Oh, yes? [chuckles]
A little.
[chuckles]
But you are a very
important part of the family,
very important.
Thanks.
What do you want, Cash?
You gentlemen need to put together
a package, full insurance, benefits,
pensions, higher revenue
sharing, upping the minimums.
Cash.
I better not want to wipe
my ass with it, Rami,
because we're this close
to organizing a union.
I won't get every fighter to
join, but I'll get 40%.
I'll establish an NLRB board.
We'll have elections.
Oh, yes, baby.
It'll be quite the ass-fucking.
Come on, David.
[footsteps]
You want me to put a little
smiling face emoji on it?
Sure. [chuckles]
Nice job.
Okay, I have $20.
With that $20, I decide
if I'm going to do this right,
I need to get my breath fresh,"
so I bought toothpaste.
Toothpaste costs $4.75.
I'm going to get a loaf
of bread because
I need to make a sandwich when I get
home, preferably, I like salami.
You know what I mean?
I don't know about you all.
What's your favorite sandwich?
Pepperoni sandwich.
Oh, you love pepperoni
sandwich?
That's some good pepperoni.
All right,
let's get into the problem now.
Here we go. $20, right?
Everybody see that?
Yes.
Okay, with that $20, I decide to
buy a toothpaste that costs $4.75.
With that $4.75, I also decided,
"You know what?
I'm going to buy some
bread that costs $3."
How much change do I get back?
Go ahead, Quinn.
$12.25.
That's right. $12.25.
My man. $12.25. [bell rings]
Have a good day.
I'll see you guys later.
Have a good day. Enjoy it.
Get out in the sun.
Get some vitamin D.
Killing it.
Get some vitamin D, boy.
[chuckles]
I know. [chuckles]
I'll come get you in a bit,
all right?
Okay.
You're a good dude, Mr.
Stewart.
Thank you, Jett.
You're a good dude yourself.
Hey, I have an old Army buddy
whose son wants to get into MMA.
Is there any chance
we could get coffee.
Yes, of course. Anytime.
Awesome. You're awesome for
that, thank you, man.
Hey, do you know Keaton
Carmichael?
I do know Keaton.
I wrote her a letter of commendation.
Wait, you went to West Point?
No, but after the Silver Star,
I was fortunate enough
to meet Senator Cummings,
and to get into West Point,
you need to be sponsored by a senator so.
Moving and shaking, Mr.
Stewart.
Bam, bam. That's how I do it.
Are you married?
No.
Girlfriend?
You're starting to scare me.
It's not for me.
Okay.
Okay?
I think I got somebody for you.
Great, I haven't been
out on a date in a long time.
Yes?
I think everybody wants
to roll with you, man.
Well, I do know how to roll.
[laughter]
You know what I'm saying?
I don't mean to sound shallow,
but...
Don't say it, mom.
He's in a wheelchair.
Yes, that's what happens when
brave
men go out to war and get shot,
mother.
He's good-looking, he's great with
Quinn, his penis still works.
[chuckles]
Tell me you did not
ask about his penis.
Of course I did.
You think I want my mom
hanging with some flat tire?
[chuckles]
Jett William Boykins, tell me
you didn't ask about his penis.
[chuckles] Penis.
[chuckles] No, I didn't.
I had Derril ask him.
He was subtle about it.
Oh, sure.
One, two, three,
four, four, five.
[chuckles] This might be the
worse pushups I've ever seen.
Well, yes. I learned it from
you.
Yes? Well,
you bend these little arms [?].
Let go of your hand.
What are you going to do?
I'll kick your freaking ass.
Mom, help. Ow. Ow.
Damn. Where has this been?
I heard Mr. Stewart's stacked.
Kampai.
To a great mom.
I don't know about that.
Come on, Susan. Just say thank
you.
Thank you.
[laughs] Yes.
I feel like single moms with special
needs kids have it the hardest.
It's been quite a ride.
Yes, I know.
Yes?
Yes.
How much do you know?
I know everything. It's my job
to.
Has Quinn ever
talked to you about it?
No. I mean, honestly,
I don't think he remembers.
Do you have discussed it with
Jett?
Tidbits here and there.
He doesn't remember the big stuff.
You know when Jett-
-Set us up?
Yes. When he set us
up, I googled you.
No.
Yes. [laughs] I totally did.
You were a top-ranked tennis player.
Hard to believe, right?
Look at me now.
What are you talking about?
You look amazing. You do.
Thank you.
You are grounded, young lady.
What?
Hey, no excuses. Pee in this
cup.
No phone for a week. So?
It was nice. Thank you.
No problem.
I love you.
I love you too, mom.
[music]
Hey. Come here, little guy.
Come here. Come on.
Show me what you got.
Show me these tough hands.
All right, one, two, three.
Show me the hands.
What's it like being a Stewardess?
Are you afraid of flying?
No, I really enjoy it. I get
to-
- All right. Stand there.
Stand there. Put your hands up.
Remember? Hands up.
No. What are you doing?
You're not paying attention.
Listen to me.
One, two, three, come on.
What's wrong? [chuckles]
Focus. One, two, three.
[chuckles]
No. You're laughing.
What is that? What is that?
That's not what I taught you.
This tastes like shit.
Come on. Pay attention.
No. What are you doing?
You're not listening to me.
Pay attention.
I don't want you growing
up to be a pussy.
[music]
[police siren]
Come on, pussy boy.
[music]
I'm going to fucking
kill that bitch.
[police sirens]
Motherfucking shit.
[music]
What the fuck?
You're trying to kill him.
Do you remember that?
Do you remember?
Because I fucking do.
You little motherfucker.
I don't fucking need you anymore.
I'm not helpless. Fuck you, man.
I don't fucking need you.
You just shut your own
fucking throat, bitch.
Quinn. Quinn.
Cash, stop. Cash, relax. Stop
it.
Relax, man.
All right. I'm good, I'm good.
Get him out of here.
Everybody, time to go.
[glass shatters]
Jake.
Why did I black it out?
I remember him hitting you,
and the police,
I just didn't remember why.
Maybe you wanted to forget.
[music]
Patty, love it.
How far are you willing
to go with this?
Pay me 100 grand for the entire
video, and you'll find out.
[video playing]
Fuck.
You piece of shit.
What the fuck?
Cash.
You're trying to kill him.
Do you remember that?
Do you remember?
Because I fucking do.
You little motherfucker.
I don't fucking need you
anymore.
[music]
Did you know there's a news
van?
Yes, I know. Come in.
We've been here ever since it went viral.
You have vocab on Wednesday
and biology's on Friday
and your written
assignment is in this folder.
It's pretty self-explanatory.
Thank you.
Where did he come from?
He just crashed.
He was up all night.
All the online stuff sent
his anxiety through the roof.
He's so sweet. I just love him.
I'd kill for those lips.
The hair is what gets me.
I've tried every gel known to man
and still can't figure it out.
Welcome to Holland.
What?
Welcome to Holland, the poem.
You have to read it.
It was written by a mother whose son
has Down's, I'm paraphrasing here.
When a woman is getting
ready to have a baby,
it's like planning a trip to Italy.
She was excited.
She buys six guidebooks and plans a
trip to the Vatican, the Colosseum,
a winery in Florence.
When she arrives, the pilot
says, "Welcome to Holland."
She's like, "Holland?
No, no, I signed up for Italy.
There's no way in hell
I'm staying in Holland."
But she has no choice,
that's where she landed.
She learns Dutch
and she buys new guidebooks.
She visits the windmills
and sees a few Rembrandts.
All the while, all her friends
are just living it up in Italy,
bragging about how great it is.
She realizes that
she can't let it get to her.
She can't spend time mourning
over Italy because then she'll
never be free to appreciate
the true beauty of Holland.
I'm not sure if I love
that poem or despise it.
Yes, me neither. I appreciate
it.
I appreciate you.
Thank you, Keaton.
I mean it.
You're welcome, Jett, I mean
it.
Look, Cash, I don't know
who leaked it and I don't care.
You don't know who leaked it.
You must think I'm fucking
stupid, Rami.
You don't think I know what
goes on in my own camp?
I just follow the numbers.
As do I, which is why I thanked
the bitch before I fired her.
Let's talk cabbage.
Okay.
50 million upfront, guaranteed.
What are we looking at?
Five million pay-per-views, six?
Jamie is probably still
jerking off to YouTube.
I can't pull it out.
The catch, Rami?
The catch is you drop
this union nonsense,
pensions, healthcare, all that.
Forget it.
Come on, Cash, you honestly
want to spend the next 10 years
of your life in court flying
back and forth to LA.
I will never allow a union,
not now, not ever.
I only want five million
upfront.
If word ever leaked out to my fanbase
that I was guaranteed 50 mils,
25% wouldn't buy the fight
out of principle alone.
I want half of everything else.
You're insane.
You're asking me to fight my own
son, you fucking goat roper.
Half the gate, half the
merchandise, half all pay per view,
and access to the books. That's
the deal, decide now. Yes or no?
Up to you, pal.
Keep smiling, Rami.
Please tell me
you're not doing this.
Doing what?
Fighting Jett.
I'm done.
What?
I'm so fucking done with you.
I'm done.
How are you done, Jade?
He's your son, Cash.
Hey, how are you done?
Divorce done?
You better fucking answer me.
How are you done?
Cash, you're hurting me.
This will be the last fucking
mistake you ever made.
Are you threatening me?
Oh, it's not a threat, baby.
It's a fact.
If you're smart,
you'll learn the fucking difference.
I'm sorry.
He offered us half,
baby, of everything.
We'll make $100 million on this
fight alone, maybe even $200. Jade.
Good evening. Welcome to the
Yard.
We've got some great specials
today.
Hello, Susan.
Hey.
You've been offered another
fight.
Child Services should lock me up
for even mentioning this to you.
Tell me.
Boykins versus Boykins.
God.
How much?
$200,000.
Holy crap. Did he agree to it?
You can't do this.
What do you mean?
Of course, I can do it.
I can't in good conscience.
Look, mom.
I'm 18, I can do whatever I want.
Jett, you're not thinking
about the ramifications.
It's $200,000, mom.
He can kill you, baby.
Stop.
I know him too well.
After that video and all the
shit he's taken on social media,
he wants to kill you.
Mom, I'm his son.
He's a psychopath.
Please, sweetheart, for me.
Just give yourself one more year.
I mean, you are a child.
There will be other opportunities
like this. I promise you.
What if there's none?
Then this wasn't meant to be-
-No-
...in the first place.
...no, no. Fuck.
Please don't do this.
No. This isn't about you, mom.
It's not about
you and it's not about Quinn.
For once, it's about me.
I didn't think I'd see you
again.
That makes two of us.
I bet your head is
spinning in a hundred
different directions
right about now.
Yes.
I was just listening to a guy on a
podcast, he called you insane.
He's got me pegged.
I'm here because I wanted
to thank you, Ms. Malek,
and all my teachers who've
bent over backward for me.
That's what makes this so hard.
I really want to graduate
and someday go to college,
but I don't know how
to make it all work right now.
Don't drop out, Jett.
I'm missing my semester finals.
Take them after you win.
Look, I'll take care of the
powers that be on this end.
You just take care
of business on yours. Good?
Thank you.
You know all the great
mathematicians were insane?
Maybe that's how you approach
this.
You have one very difficult
problem in front of you.
Solve it.
[phone ringing]
Hey, grab a pen and paper.
Yes, I'm ready.
429241017.
Who am I calling?
That's a closed number.
The only one who
will beat you there.
I'll see you in Vegas.
Motherfucking Kareef hooked it
up, baby.
Lovely guy.
[music]
Jett.
[?].
You're joking, right? Claude.
Truly.
No, no, no. I'm a hugger.
You better get used to it.
You're hungry?
Yes.
All right, come inside
and we'll get you set up.
Let me help you, give me your
bag.
Thanks.
This way.
Give me your phone, please.
You'll see it in one month.
This way. Voila.
Smells good.
Nice.
Bon appetit, guys.
Are you scared?
Yes.
For two decades now,
Cash Boykins has been one of the most
polarizing athletes in all of sports.
He's not a modern-day
slice of Americana.
He's the whole pie. Why this
fight?
Why your own son? For the money?
Revenge for that post?
Or does it go even deeper?
Look, Jett has a lot of talent
and he's got a bright future.
But he won't improve
unless he fights the best.
Unfortunately, that's me.
The Apocalypse is finally upon
us.
We are just a few weeks
away from what promises
to be the most controversial
fight in WFA history,
between Cash Boykins
and his 18-year-old son Jett.
How about that, partner?
Syd, honestly, I believe
we've officially reached a new
low in this great
country you call America.
I don't care how much money
he's-
- You don't care about how much
money, what planet are you from?
Fathers don't fight sons under
any circumstance. This is family.
Family who don't much
like each other right now.
Here's the deal, the fight
game is all about the Benjamins.
Sure.
It's about money.
If there is a specific demand,
you go after it.
Jett's fight against Promotico,
did you even watch it?
I did. I did. Thank you, Syd.
Yes, but Tricky Ricky Promotico ain't
Liquid Cash Boykins, the Slayer.
Cash is the greatest fighter
in the history of the sport
and this boy has a zero percent
chance of beating the king.
Zero percent would
mean there's zero appeal,
which means there would
be zero reason to do this fight.
That's not the case. Keep in
mind.
Cash's fight against
Evil Fate the Terrible
did about $2.7 million
buys at $79.95 a buy.
Now they're estimating that this
bet will do over $6 million buys,
at $89.95 a pop. Benjamins,
baby.
Yes, Syd, I think you've had a few
too many tokes of Colorado's finest.
Not this morning.
I will tell you this, every high
school kid will not ask their parents,
they will demand that
their parents buy this fight.
The video has already gone
viral. 50 million views.
Jamie, about that 200 grand,
add a zero.
You be good for mom.
I love you, buddy.
I love you, too.
Come here.
I'll be back Sunday morning.
Will you still be here?
Come on, Jade.
Cash, I warned you
before we got married.
Zero tolerance.
We had a contract.
I know. I'm sorry, babe.
Me too. Kareef?
Hey, Jade.
How you doing, little man?
Kareef.
Just wait until I get back,
please.
I love you.
See you guys.
[music]
What was it like to beat Cash?
Do you really want to know?
Yes.
You're going to find
out soon because
you're going to beat this guy,
right?
You must fight smarter,
take emotion out of it, stick to the plan,
and you will outwit him.
Yes?
Yes.
Hey, is it true the Rock's
coming tomorrow night?
That'd be sweet.
Any of you guys seen Skyscraper?
That is a fucking masterpiece
man.
Feeling good, Cash?
My balls are in this robe,
big time.
Cash, do you feel any
remorse for fighting your son?
Shit no. Every 18-year-old
kid out there deserves
a good old fashioned ass whooping.
It builds character.
He's been saying that exact same
line to me since I was three.
Cash,
the way you're talking to him,
the fact that you're already
drinking, it only reaffirms-
- You know what it reaffirms,
honey?
It reaffirms that I could really
use a handjob right about now.
Cash, that's sexual harassment.
Lick me where I shit, Jamie.
[laughs]
Now that's sexual harassment,
people.
Hey, in his defense,
the abuse stuff was 10 years ago.
He paid his dues.
That doesn't change the fact that
he's an absolute piece of crap,
so you can feel free to sue his
ass.
My baby is so sweet, ain't he?
You won't be thinking
that tomorrow night.
I can guarantee you that.
Is Sport going
to give me a licking?
I could have knocked your sorry
ass out four months ago, chief.
I don't remember
it going down like that.
Yes, you don't remember
yesterday.
This is true.
Hey, barkeep, get this guy
another Bloody Mary.
Good idea, Barkeep.
Make it a double.
Next?
Come on. Daddy needs shoes.
No, you won. We won. Yes, go
ahead.
Take it out. Let me get it.
On a four, on a five, on a six,
on an eight and throw
all these the hard way,
Oh boy.
What the fuck is this?
Shit.
Sir, could you please?
Shit. Sorry, baby. Wow.
Now, this is some great shit we
got going on in here baby. Right?
I'm Cash.
Hi, Cash.
How are you doing? I'm Dan.
Dan? Tell me, Dan.
How is it you can see the dice
from all the way down there?
Cash, go to bed.
Hey, look at all these
little cute $25 chips, Susie.
You two want a few bananas?
I only got about 50 left, but hell,
they ain't doing me any fucking good.
[laughs]
I think you might
need those for later.
What? Hey, you got that right.
I do need these.
Do you want to help me out?
Because I'm good
but I ain't that good.
Come here.
Let me tell you something.
Then she went down on [?].
[laughter]
Do you believe this?
I liked it. He's good.
He's okay,
whatever the hell your name is.
Dan.
Dan. Oh, cool, man.
Do you need a ticket or something
for tomorrow night's battle?
What the fuck
you know about battle?
Hey, Jett.
Yes?
Is "Screw you" bad?
Yes.
What about "Anal"?
[laughs] Very bad.
Have a dessert.
Heck, yes.
Wait, what about my diet?
No rules tonight.
All right, you can have as
much dying sugar as you want,
or you can be up late. Okay?
Okay.
We won't fight till 10 o'clock.
My body peaks at 12,
so I need to sleep late, understand?
I want two chocolate sundaes
with whipped cream and Skittles.
Yes.
[phone ringing]
This is [?].
Ever heard of a neck crank?
I have not.
It's the closest thing
one human being can
do to another before
ripping his head off.
Sounds fun.
You're looking for some fun?
Come on up
to the Presidential Suite.
Jade not making this trip?
I think she's leaving me,
sport.
Oh, good for her.
It won't last. She will be
back.
Don't bet on it.
[sighs]
What's Claude's
grand plan this time?
I can see you two
butt-fuckers now watching film,
sipping on some Bordeaux,
talking socialism.
[laughs]
I'm just glad I finally
figured out the truth.
The truth, huh, and what's
that?
That you're just
a really weak person.
You're weak when it comes to Jade,
pathetic when it comes to Quinn, mom,
but maybe your biggest
weakness is yourself.
I pray I never end up like you.
You won't.
Know how I know that?
Because tomorrow night you die,
Sport.
Tomorrow night, I kill you.
[music]
Okay.
[?], kid.
Also fighting out of Birmingham with
a record of 38 wins, one defeat,
the undisputed Lightweight
Champion of the world,
the undisputed Welterweight
Champion of the world, the Slayer,
Liquid Cash Boykins.
[crowd cheers]
Come on, Jett.
How are we doing?
Shake up a little, Jett. Shake
up.
[crowd cheers]
All right, guys, bring it in.
Bring it in, gentlemen.
Gentlemen, championship fight here.
You both know the rules.
If you want to touch gloves,
go ahead and do so now.
All right then, go back to your corners.
Come out on my call.
Cash, quick question.
My daughter is just done with karate.
Can she be next?
[laughs] [crowd cheers]
Go back to your corner.
[crowd cheers] [applause]
Are you ready to go?
Cash, are you ready to go?
Let's fight. [bell rings]
Here we go, Kenny.
Father versus son.
Man, you could feel
the tension right now.
Cash comes out strong,
looking for that spinning back kick.
He's trying to take his head
off.
Now attacking the body,
trying to slow down Jett.
Smart strategy.
Jett needs to use his distance.
That's what he does best.
It's hard to do it against an
aggressive fighter like Cash though.
Looking to counter. Nice front
kick.
The son hits the floor.
He just hit him in the face. Same corner.
What the fuck are you doing?
Jett trying to go to the
ground.
Come on. Get up.
Cash is not having it.
Let's go. Get back to your
feet.
It's a smart thing.
He knows he has
the advantage on the feet.
Let's fight.
He has so much
experience with his striking.
He's trying to get a little wild.
This is going to favor Cash.
Big combination there from Cash.
He's rocking.
Picks him up.
Excellent double-legged takedown.
This is not good for Jett.
This is exactly what
happened to the [?].
This is a bad spot to be in.
There's only 10 seconds to go
here.
Let's see if he can
secure a position.
He could finish
it here in round one.
[bell rings]
Saved by the bell.
That was a close call.
[music]
A huge round for Cash.
Tyron, how'd you score
that first round?
It finished very strong with
the elbows, started off strong.
I'm going to go with a 10-9.
We will see what the judges say.
Wow, what a round by Cash.
My goodness.
Now, listen.
Listen to me carefully.
Please, don't brawl with this guy.
Don't fight with him.
Come on, Jett. You got this.
What does Jett need to do here to
even things up here in round two?
Well, Jett needs not
to play into Cash's game plan.
He was trying to scrawl and
brawl by standing in the pocket.
That's not the game plan.
He needs to use his distance, leg kicks.
Get in and get out. [bell rings]
Here, we go. Round two.
Cash coming out strong again.
Very aggressive.
Trying to back up Jett Boykins.
Jett has to do a better
job by sticking and moving,
using the distance,
getting in, and getting out.
Tyron, to your point,
he just did it right there.
Excellent lateral movement.
This is what we didn't see in round one.
[crowd cheers]
Oh my God, judo throw.
Great reversal there by
Jett Boykins. There's his judo.
Those are the judo takeouts
we expected to see in round one.
See if he can limp leg out of
this.
Cash trying to turn
this into a single-leg
takedown and Jett
limp-legs out of it.
Back to the feet.
Much better defense there
from Jett Boykins this time out.
He's keeping him off balance.
Nice right hand as well.
Jett has enough against the
cage.
Needs to get that
space off the fence.
Great wrist control.
Beautiful throw.
Nice [?].
Not a whole lot of time left
here, Tyron.
Big kick there by Jett Boykins.
[bell rings]
Yes, baby, yes.
It goes to the body.
What an end to the round
there from Jett Boykins.
You can see his confidence building.
Cash looks very frustrated.
That's what I'm talking about.
That was beautiful.
Great. Hey, he went in the corner
and listened to his coaches,
came out with a brilliant round.
Did stick and move, stole the
cookie, left the crumb behind.
That's what he has to do.
I call it one to one.
Keep kicking that leg till
it cannot stand no more,
and we're going to take
him to the ground.
Stay focused, stay focused
and go keep kicking that leg.
Absolutely amazing fight so
far.
let's what round three
has in store for us.
Here we go, Tyron.
That's a cheap shot by Cash.
Of course.
Why wouldn't Cash do that?
He's known for this.
He's foot-stomping.
That is not illegal, but that is
not cool here in mixed martial arts.
A big shot.
Mr. Referee.
Keep fighting.
This is not where Jett wants to
be.
Come on.
[?] not able to get control
here.
He's getting down
very low with his face.
He's ready for that throw.
Second bounce.
Cash is driving the cage.
[?] Stop driving the fence.
Yes, that's another cheap shot.
If he turns it into a takedown,
that should be a point deduction.
This referee is letting Cash get away
with some serious rule-bending here.
Remember how that feels, boy?
I made you, bitch.
Come on, come on.
Come on.
That's right, bitch.
You remember where you came
from.
Sit down.
What the hell are you doing?
Don't fight emotional.
Hey, listen guys.
Hey, Cash, if you grab the fence
like that again, I'm going to take
a point away. Do you understand?
You want to lose this fight?
So wake up and put
yourself together.
We're going to go back to the
plan.
We're going to go back to the kick
and the footwork and stay focused.
I am not a bitch.
You stick to the goal, boy.
Relax.
We're going to take him
to the ground again. Look at me.
Do you want to win this fight?
Okay, so we focus.
Keep the distance. Chop down that leg.
We just lost that round.
Okay, man. You do what you do.
We got this, all right?
You prepped for this.
Let's go. let's go.
[bell rings]
With Cash top on our scorecards
anyway, two to one,
Jett Boykins needs
to come out strong.
Beautiful kick to the head.
Okay, that's it. Stop right here.
Stop right there. Time out.
Go to the mutual corner right
there.
I told you last round,
grab the fence again,
I'm going to take a point away.
I got to take a point away.
That's one point deduction.
Red corner. Grabbing the fence.
That is going to help Jett.
Jett will be up in this round here.
Stay right there.
All right, guys,
We're going to restart this fight.
Let's clean it up, gentlemen.
Are you ready to go?
You ready to go? Let's fight.
That is going to give
some confidence back
to Cash as we start
this round again.
A big knee there.
[grunts]
Get off me.
[bell rings]
Fuck.
Go back to your corner.
This is it right here.
You ready to go?
Let's fight.
Fifth and final round here.
Tyron, it's do or die for both
of these men.
What a combination by Cash.
Jett's starting to score
some combinations.
[crowd cheers]
Don't stop with the lyrics,
go to the fucking face!
Listen to your fucking trainer.
Come on, finish him.
Do what he fuckin' tells you
bitch.
Rip his face.
Do it. You fucking pussy.
Stop, stop.
No.
No, no, no, no, no.
He's blocking the referee.
I hope Jett is okay. This is not
a good moment right now.
[crowd booing]
We see very little
movement from Jett right now.
Jett, get up, man.
Yes.
This is a scary moment right
now.
What's going on?
Jett.
Get up, man.
Hey. Hey, Jett.
I'm sorry, ma'am.
I can't allow you...
Guys, guys, let her in. Let her
in.
Jett, Jett. Please, Jett.
Please, please.
Please. Jett, baby, wake up,
please.
Please, please.
His eyes, his eyes just moved.
[gasps]
[whispers]
Jett, are you okay?
Did I hear a loss?
Can we get a stretcher, please?
Hey, Jett, Jett, Jett.
We cannot take any risk.
No, please. I'm okay.
Stretcher.
Mom, mom. I'm fine, tell him.
I'm fine, mom. Mom, I'm okay.
I'm ok..
[applause] [crowd cheers]
[music]
I'm so proud of you. I'm so
proud.
[crowd booing]
[crowd cheering]
[music]
[Legendary by Welshly Arms
plays]
Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
Take a look around me.
Taking pages from a magazine,
been looking for the answer
ever since we were seventeen.
You know the truth can be a weapon to
fight this world of ill intentions,
a new answer to the same
question,
how many times will
you learn the same lesson?
I think they got it all wrong.
This is what we came for,
and we couldn't want it anymore.
Could never turn back now,
got to leave it all on the floor.
Been dreaming of the payoff,
through the struggles and the trade-offs,
write in truth heading on the
way up, tell them the truth,
but they think it's just made
up.
I think they got it all wrong.
We just got to hold on,
and on, and on, and on
'cause we're going to be
legends,
Eventually, they're going to
know who's right.
To make a stand
you got to win the fight.
Can't stand the heat, then just
stay out the light for you might
never make it out alive.
You gotta live without
the columbines.
Let everybody hear your battle
cry.
Yes, we're going to be legends,
going to get their attention.
What we're doing
here ain't just scary.
It's about to be legendary.
We're going to be legends,
going to teach 'em all a lesson,
got this feeling that
we're so sweet caring.
It's about to be legendary.
Legends.
[music]