Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
[instrumental music]
Jack: Mountains breathe...
just like the rest of us.
If you sit still,
you can feel their pulse.
Air becoming life.
Fire propels that pulse
beyond a manageable rate.
And air becomes death.
[chainsaw whirring]
Time goes on, new trees rise,
and bones get buried...
but the ghosts never leave.
[whirring]
[whistling]
Kicked a little left.
Look good to me.
[breathing heavily]
I've been eyeing
that top section.
You wanna go pop
some off with me?
The access is a little tricky.
You good?
- Yeah, I'm good.
- Alright.
Maybe we can squeeze
through here.
[whirring]
[thunder rumbling]
- Good shit today.
- Thanks, Tick.
You look like you know
what you're doing up there.
- You've been doing along.
- Off and on.
Huh?
I'll be seeing you.
- I'll see you tomorrow.
- Alright.
Hey.
Heard you did good
out there today.
It'll be a long run.
Lot of days.
I can do this. That's good work.
Alright. Good deal then.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Hey, Dave, thanks, man.
Yeah, of course.
[sighs]
[engine revving]
Come on.
There we go.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
[instrumental music]
[engine revving]
♪ It ain't my style
not even for a country mile ♪
♪ Ride ride ♪
♪ On this
saddle my saddle ♪
♪ It's a beautiful night
the air is right ♪♪
[squeaking]
[engine revving]
[cell phone vibrating]
Let's go.
Come on, Jack, you're late.
Jack: Yeah, I know.
Better run.
Tick: Come on, let's go.
[cell phone vibrating]
Tizer: All I'm saying is don't
make your back cut so high.
You've got barber chairs
all over this place.
Briggs: Bullshit.
Come on, ladies, let's go.
[birds chirping]
Kelly: No, I see the change.
Of course.
Oh, one second.
I have to take this.
I'll see you when I land.
Jack! Thank God. Um...
How are you?
Good.
Kelly: Did you get my message?
No. I've been working.
Kelly: Okay. Well, I, uh...
I need a favor.
Jack: What, Kelly?
I need you to pick up
your daughter.
Kelly: She's at this
Sky Camp in Wyoming
and something came up,
I can't get there in time.
But I just thought
maybe you could...
Sky Camp? What's...
Umm, it's an astronomy camp,
just outside of Cody.
She has a flight leaving
Jackson Monday morning.
[chuckles]
I can't go to Wyoming tomorrow.
That's six hours to Cody
and another four hours
to Jackson.
Kelly: I'm not asking for much.
I'm not going to
Wyoming tomorrow, Kelly.
It's just a ride.
Jack, I just need to
get her to the airport.
Well, you're her mom,
I'm sure you'll figure it out.
Lady, we're here.
Jack, it's been a long time.
I just think it would be
good for her to see you.
It's just not a
good time for me right now.
Kelly: She's your daughter.
I can't. I'm sorry.
No, no, don't hang up.
[exhales]
[knocking]
Hey, it's not nap time yet.
Let's go, Jack. Tick tock.
[phone chimes]
You good?
[instrumental music]
[whirring]
[music continues]
[creaking]
[engine revving]
You know it's a day rate,
not hourly, right?
Yeah, I know, I know.
I just wanted to finish
clearing that tree. That's all.
Well, pace yourself.
We got a long run.
Oh, hey, Dave!
I really appreciate
the work and all.
It means a lot to me.
You bet.
I need to take a
couple of days though.
[chuckles]
You serious?
You just started. I got 23 days
to finish this job.
I'm not gonna finish on time
if I don't have a full crew.
No, I know.
Man on radio: Buzz for Dave.
You aren't making
this easy, man.
Go for Dave.
Man on radio: These extra
Stihls showed up.
Where do you want them?
Dave: Just put them by
the loading dock.
I'll grab 'em in the morning.
What are we talking about here?
Two days.
I want this job, man.
I really do.
- Is everything okay?
Jack: Yeah, no, it's fine.
I... I just need to
head to Jackson.
Jackson? What's going on there?
My daughter.
I need to pick up her up
at this camp, and take...
Okay.
You still got your CDL?
Jack: Yeah.
I picked up a new truck.
It's outside of Spokane.
I was gonna have someone
drive it here for me,
maybe you could
pick it up for me?
Yeah, I can do that.
Call the office
and they'll give you details.
- Thanks, Dave.
- Just a couple of days.
- I need you back.
- You bet.
[engine revving]
[instrumental music]
[music continues]
[panting]
[clears throat]
[exhales]
[engine revving]
[instrumental music]
♪ Two eyes on the road ♪
♪ Two wheels below ♪
♪ Darkness approaching ♪
♪ Hundred miles to go ♪
♪ Wind's been pushin' ♪
♪ From across the sea ♪
♪ Over the mountains ♪
♪ To come involve with me ♪
[engine revving]
[music continues]
♪ Now a passenger ♪
♪ Strapped to my back ♪
♪ Walking at me ♪
♪ And I walk right back ♪♪
Julie: You must
be Hanna's father.
I'm the Camp Director, Julie.
Nice to meet you. Jack.
Julie: You've got a real bright
young lady there.
Wasn't too keen
on the social events,
but really took
to the course work.
- She lives with her mom.
- Oh. She was lovely.
Take care, Hanna. I hope
you can come back next year.
Have a good drive.
I didn't think you'd come.
I got it.
Don't you have a car?
Your mom said you got a
9 o'clock flight
out of Jackson tomorrow.
We'll stay the night just
outside of town, okay?
[engine rumbling]
[instrumental music]
[music continues]
I'm gonna fill this.
You want anything?
Kombucha.
[dings]
What's this?
It's all they had.
How much farther?
Yeah, we're almost half way.
I need to charge my phone.
Jack: Turn it off,
save your battery.
It's gonna get cold.
You have anything warmer?
I'm fine.
Well, suit yourself.
[instrumental music]
[engine revving]
Why'd we stop?
It's not much farther to camp.
Camp?
Put this on.
It's only getting colder.
Mom didn't say
anything about camping?
We'll stop just north of
Dubois...
I'm not camping!
Hanna, what are you doing?
I'm not camping.
I'll find a hotel.
Hanna, there aren't
any hotels around here.
Shit! I need to charge my phone
and wash my face! Ugh!
[engine revving]
[thunder rumbling]
What's the plan here, Hanna?
You just gonna walk 25 miles
to the next town, are ya, huh?
Hanna, stop!
It's not what you expect,
me neither.
I don't ride at night, okay?
Especially over this pass.
It is cold and dangerous.
There are deer and elks
scattered everywhere.
Now come on, get on the bike.
It's a good campsite.
It's not far.
It is what it is, Hanna.
Mom was right about you.
[instrumental music]
[music continues]
Thanks.
Not so bad, huh?
You don't camp much
anymore, do you?
So?
You used to.
I don't remember.
Yeah, we used to take you
all over the place.
This one time, I think
we were at Yellowstone.
You were probably three.
Your mom had pulled out these
marshmallows to make s'mores.
And you got so excited.
[instrumental music]
Yeah, it's been a while.
[barking]
[music continues]
Good morning!
Morning.
Um, thanks.
It's beautiful, isn't it?
Yeah.
Well, we better get going.
We got a couple hours
of ride ahead of us.
Okay.
[instrumental music]
[engine revving]
[music continues]
[airplane droning]
You ready?
You gotta come with me
to the gate, Jack.
I'm an unaccompanied minor.
[indistinct announcement]
[instrumental music]
Hanna: Hi, I don't have
my boarding pass
and my phone just died.
That's okay.
What's your last name, sweetie?
Elliot.
- Hanna?
- Yeah.
Did you guys have a
nice stay in Jackson?
No, not really.
Female 1: I see you are
traveling alone.
Is this your dad?
Yeah.
Female 1: I'll need
to see some ID.
I'll need to see some ID.
I'm sure you know this,
but you'll have to accompany
your daughter to the gate
and wait for the plane
to depart.
[indistinct]
Sir?
Yeah.
Am I in an aisle seat?
Female 1: Oh, let me see.
No, right now I have
you in a window.
Can I switch?
Unfortunately, honey,
it's a full flight this morning.
Hanna: I really hate windows.
The seats have
already been assigned.
So move someone!
She's 12, for Christ's sake.
I'm 13.
As I just told your daughter
the seats are all assigned,
I can't...
You can't? Or you won't?
- Excuse me?
- Dad, it's okay.
No, do your job, lady.
Move someone over, bump someone
up, do what you gotta do.
Dad?
But put this child in a seat
where she's goddamn comfortable!
Dad! What are you doing?
Sir, I'm gonna have to
ask you to calm down.
Calm down?
It's fine. I'll just ask someone
to switch with me.
[instrumental music]
[indistinct announcement]
[music continues]
Dad?
[retching]
[airplane droning]
What time do you board.
It already left.
Jack: What?
You missed your flight?
Me? You were the one who didn't
take me to get on my plane.
Damn it!
[laughs]
Alright, grab your bag.
We'll catch another flight.
I already checked.
Same time, tomorrow.
Shit!
Come on.
You got to be kidding me.
A bus. We'll get you on a bus.
A bus? I'm not taking
a bus back to LA?
Well, I'm not staying here!
We could get a hotel. I have
mom's credit card, we can...
No. I can't do that.
I shouldn't even be here.
Do you understand that?
I have got a job, I have a life.
My own problems.
I don't even know why
your mom called me.
You are not my problem!
Enough with you!
You think I don't know that?
I hate you.
Get your helmet!
What?
I gotta go to Spokane.
You're coming with me.
Spokane? Where's Spokane?
Eastern Washington.
Washington? Really?
That's the deal.
You'll catch a flight
from there.
I just want to go home!
You wanna go home?
This is how you do it.
[airplane whirring]
Are you okay?
Call your mom. Let her know.
Good?
Yeah.
[engine revving]
[instrumental music]
♪ He was laid to rest ♪
♪ In a place I don't know ♪
♪ He made his bed ♪
♪ In a house he called home ♪♪
You have some toilet paper
or something?
Uh...
♪ And maybe he wrote down
a song or two ♪
♪ And play this fiddle to
get you off his mind ♪
♪ And maybe he wrote down
a song or two ♪
♪ And play this fiddle to
get you off his mind ♪
♪ She... ♪♪
Shit.
♪ Was so... ♪♪
It's a long ride.
We're gonna take a few days.
Okay.
♪ I'm staring at water ♪
♪ Trying to... ♪
♪ With my fingertips ♪
[indistinct singing]
♪ Any limit ♪
♪ Every path ♪
♪ Is caught up ♪
♪ In the avalanche ♪
♪ I know the path... ♪♪
That is too much.
Sorry.
Are you alone?
What?
Do you live with anyone?
No.
[chopping wood]
And you like it like that?
Yeah, I do.
Mom doesn't talk about you
much anyways.
I prefer it too.
[sniffs]
You prefer what?
To be alone.
We need more wood.
[panting]
[bird calling]
[exhales]
[instrumental music]
[music continues]
What?
What did you tell your mom?
When you called your mom,
what did you say to her?
You didn't tell her, did you?
So?
You're really screwing
me here, Hanna! You know that?
[boat engine revving]
What do you care?
Pack up!
No! You're not
telling me what to do.
God dammit, Hanna, I'm your dad.
My dad? You're not my dad!
Hanna: Urgh!
What?
Was I suppose to tell mom,
"Sorry, mom, dad had a total
frickin' meltdown,
threw up all over the place,
and I missed my flight?"
That's enough.
I'm the one who shouldn't
be here.
I'm ready, Jack.
[instrumental music]
[engine revving]
[clanging]
How do people live out here?
[blowing]
I mean, it's so depressing.
What do you even do?
Would you knock it off!
Chill.
[whistling]
[horse snorts]
[instrumental music]
I think I got it running.
I'm getting pretty hungry.
How about we get
some real food?
[neighing]
Okay.
♪ It arrived on my doorstep ♪
♪ A fallen bird from the sky ♪
♪ Lost in the snowstorm
returning home to die ♪
♪ I wrote in cursive to you ♪
♪ The ink was made from
a winter's afternoon ♪♪
You want some of these fries?
I'm good.
You guys save room for dessert?
Ah, no, I think we're good.
- Okay.
- Can I get a refill?
Ya, you sure can.
Is that your
Wide Glide out there?
Yeah.
Late '90s?
'98.
Great looking bike.
Alright, whenever you
get a chance.
I'll be at the bike.
Hey. Here you go.
Thanks. Um, this is for you.
Thank you.
You guys having fun out there?
It's okay.
Yeah, I remember taking rides
with my dad, some great trips.
Okay, take care.
[engine revving]
Female 2: Bye, Shelly!
Have a great night.
Female 2: Sounds like your
jets are clogged.
Yeah, they might be. I haven't
ridden her in a while.
Where are you guys going?
Spokane.
[honking]
Oh, you're gonna wanna get that
looked at before you head out.
You know what, my dad's got
a shop at the house.
I'm sure he'd take
a quick look for ya.
That's very kind, but, you know,
I think we're good.
Aww, don't be silly,
my dad's been working
on these things his whole life.
He'd love it.
I don't want to impose.
Female 2:
Really, not a big deal.
We're just a few
miles outside of town.
Yeah, okay.
Okay, I'll pull around.
Jack: You okay with this?
It is what it is, right?
[chuckles]
Yeah.
[engine revving]
By the way, I'm Helen.
Jack. This is
my daughter, Hanna.
Can I ride with you?
Helen: That okay?
- Yeah.
Can I take a shower?
- Hanna!
- It's fine.
Of course, you can, sweetie.
Alright, you wanna
follow me, Jack?
Helen: Seat belt on?
Hanna: Yeah.
Helen: Okay.
[instrumental music]
[engine revving]
Helen: You guys are camping,
huh?
No tent though...
And your dad's the real deal.
I don't know.
I bet you came
through Yellowstone?
Did you guys see anything
cool out there?
We saw a grizzly bear.
That was pretty cool.
Helen: That is pretty cool.
You guy see any buffalo?
- Quite a few.
- These guys?
No, it's like this.
Helen: Like that?
- No, they curve.
- I gotta curve it.
Yeah?
I bet you and your dad
do this a lot, huh?
My dad's an asshole.
Oh, okay.
Yeah, you know what,
I thought he seemed a bit shady.
I haven't seen my dad
in four years.
That's a long time.
Helen: This is good then.
- What?
Helen: You guys
taking this trip.
- Helen?
- Yeah.
I really appreciate you helping
us, but can we not talk?
Sure.
[engine revving]
Ah! I really appreciate this.
Ah, it's no problem at all.
Dad, this is Jack.
- Jack Elliot.
- Hello, Jack.
My names's Roy.
And this is my daughter, Hanna.
Hello. Nice to meet you.
Where you guys headed?
- Spokane.
- LA.
Well, I'm getting around
her flight out of Spokane.
- Vacation?
- Yeah, something like that.
Something like that?
Dad, uh, I was hoping
that you might help him out
with the bike.
Carburetor's been giving
them some trouble.
Well, it doesn't look like she's
too well cared for.
I haven't ridden her
in a while.
Listen, if it's too
much trouble...
Nonsense, wheel her up inside.
I'll take a look at her.
Right, you're ready
for that shower?
Ah.
- Oh.
- Mind your manners.
She'll be fine.
Jack: Never seen this
sprint before.
Roy: '67 SS.
They only made
'em from '61 to '68.
Man, it's beautiful.
Let's see what we got
going on here.
Oh! There's your problem.
How many miles you've
been riding like this?
Hand me that set of 16s.
Well, I started south out of
Basin, and picked
my daughter up at camp
in Central Wyoming.
Starting from Montana, huh?
I'm impressed
you made it this far.
Okay, you're gonna have to
rebuild this thing entirely.
I mean, I can clean it out a
bit, get you back on the road,
but I'd take her easy out there
if I were you.
I appreciate it.
I couldn't just let you ride
out of here like this, you know.
Fellow Montanan and all,
especially with that
sweet little girl of
yours on the back.
Help me here. Hold this for me.
Uh-huh.
Here we go.
[instrumental music]
♪ I've learnt
and I've forgotten ♪
♪ So many things ♪
♪ Been spun around and around
on you ♪
♪ Hope it rings
and I wanna know ♪
♪ How are you so... ♪♪
Hanna: Good dog. Come here.
Jack: Just sitting there
underneath the tarp.
Roy: Could have been under that
tarp for the past 50 years
by the looks of it.
Tires were all rotted, but the
body was in pristine condition.
Just 50 years of
dust on top of it.
How's it looking?
Well, you were right
about the carb.
Yeah, can you fix it?
I'll be able to get
'em back on the road.
And how much longer
are you thinking?
Well, we need to soak it a bit.
Couple more hours, at least.
It's getting late.
Well, you can't rush this. This
thing was gummed up real bad.
Well, Jack,
where are you guys staying?
I was hoping to get as
far as Thompson Falls.
Thompson Falls?
That's four hours.
Well, we'll get a motel
or something.
We're not camping?
You know, there's not much
from here to there.
I mean nothing decent anyways.
Well, we've got a spare
bedroom downstairs.
Hanna can take that.
Couch folds out.
Ah, that's very kind of you,
but we've got a long day
ahead of us.
I know, I don't
wanna hold you up,
but from what Hanna shared,
I just...
Sounds like you guys could
use a good night's rest.
No, thank you. But we should...
Dad, can't we just
leave real early in the morning?
Well, that'd make for
a longer day tomorrow.
You okay with that?
Yeah.
You like whiskey, Jack?
Come on, join me.
Yeah.
[instrumental music]
Let that ball go.
Now all these guys.
Use whatever you think.
Do it up. Here.
[laughs]
Hey.
Hanna says she's a vegetarian,
so I thought
I'd make a
nice little Primavera.
That sounds great. Thanks.
Can I rinse off?
Ah, yeah, that door
just on the left.
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
[indistinct]
There you go.
Helen: Okay.
[laughs]
Hope you're hungry, Jack.
Smells delicious.
Well...
Alright.
Hanna...
[laughs]
Roy: I'm not the only one
who does that.
So, Hanna, tell us more about
this camp?
- It's an astronomy camp.
- Astronomy?
Well, that's not your
typical summer camp.
I won an essay contest
and got invited.
Roy: Well, that's very
impressive.
Well, what did you learn about?
I can show you something.
Okay.
- Outside.
- Oh.
Ah. Sure.
- I'll get my coat.
- Ya, I'll get this later.
[instrumental music]
Okay, so on any given night, you
can see almost 20 quadrillion
miles away with the naked eye.
But that number is kind of hard
to make sense of,
so we use light years as a more
manageable unit of distance.
Okay, that...
everybody knows that.
What's really cool to me
is what that actually means.
Take the North Star
for example.
Well, its real
name is Polaris.
People think Polaris is
the nearest star
after the sun
because it's light is so bright,
but it's not even close.
It might not even
break the top 100.
It's actually 433 light years
away.
Which means if we were somehow
standing on Polaris right now,
we'd actually be looking at
earth 433 years in the past.
So like, 30 years
before the pilgrims
landed on Plymouth Rock.
I like looking up
and thinking about that.
Like I'm looking into the past.
[instrumental music]
Jack, I think you got a future
Astronomer on your hands.
Now thanks for sharing, Hanna.
Okay.
Well, we got a long day
ahead of us tomorrow.
Let's try and get some sleep.
[music continues]
You want an extra blanket?
Hanna: Why did you leave?
It wasn't working, Hanna.
For any of us.
You could come back home now.
It doesn't work like that.
Hanna: Why not?
You don't want me in your life.
You understand?
This...
This isn't real.
How do you know what I want?
I'm gonna get you home
to your mom.
Get some sleep.
Is she comfortable?
Yeah.
Got a little bit left
in this bottle.
If you wanna
finish it off with me?
Sure.
She's a good girl.
Yeah, I know.
So, have you always lived
here with your dad?
Nope.
Believe it or not,
I used to live in New York.
That was a lifetime ago.
And then my mom passed,
my dad took it pretty hard.
And I wasn't too tied down
back East, so I came on home.
Wasn't planning on staying here,
but, you know, now Montana
can have that effect on you,
you know.
From what my mom shared,
and this,
this was before I was born.
My dad went through a real
rough patch, and it was
about some accident, I don't
really know the details,
he doesn't talk about it.
He got really distant,
and angry.
And that just got harder
and harder on her.
She never said it, but I think
she was about to leave.
So luckily, or not luckily,
his dad passed suddenly,
and they came back
and they never left.
And she always said
this place saved him.
Look, I don't know your story,
Jack, and I don't wanna ask you.
But whatever it is,
it's not too late.
You know, that little
girl needs you.
[instrumental music]
Thanks.
Yeah. Of course, Jack.
[birds chirping]
Dave, It's Jack Elliot.
Dave: Jack, where are you?
I heard you never
picked up the truck.
Jack?
I need to be with my daughter
a few more days.
Dave: Jack, I'm glad you're
getting your family time
but we had a deal. I'm supposed
to have a full crew here.
I know.
I appreciate the work.
I just can't come back
quite yet.
Dave: Well, I can't promise
anything will be waiting.
I understand.
Thanks, Dave.
I think I... I caught one.
Okay...
[screams]
Uh-oh.
Now remember to
take her a bit easy.
I can't thank you enough, Roy.
Ahh, it's always nice to
have some good people around.
Oh, that reminds me.
Hanna! Let's go! Hanna!
Coming!
You take care of your dad, okay?
He needs you.
- Thank you.
- You're so welcome.
[laughs]
You guys ride safe, okay?
Lots of wildlife
this time of year.
Figured you might need this,
riding into Washington and all.
I want that back though.
Oh, well, if it's okay, I can
drop it off on my way back down.
We'd like that.
Roy: Sounds good.
Now get going.
[engine revving]
[instrumental music]
♪ I've let all the ghosts
from my own past ♪
♪ They've seen it all
they say it won't last ♪
♪ But at least now I know ♪
♪ And I might have some time ♪
♪ To undo all the hurt
and forgive all the wrongs ♪
♪ Share the gospel of peace ♪
♪ Can we all kid along ♪
♪ Can I get out of my own way
before it's too late ♪
♪ It's a beautiful life
that's happening for you ♪
♪ It's a beautiful life I can't
wait to see what you do ♪
♪ It's a beautiful
life in love ♪♪
♪ I hear you coming down... ♪♪
Here you go.
For me?
Yeah.
To remember me by.
Hey, there's a
ghost town up ahead.
You wanna check it out?
Definitely.
Hey, thank you.
Yeah.
[instrumental music]
[engine revving]
♪ Ooh ooh ooh ♪
♪ Brief moments of bravery ♪
♪ Relaxes into cowardice ♪
♪ Glimpses of profundity ♪
♪ Dances with the precedence ♪
[screams]
Ah!
Jack: It must have been a
mining town.
Hanna: Wonder
what happened to them.
Jack: Well, you know, when they
couldn't find any more gold,
they had to go elsewhere.
Hanna: So you just
leave your shoes.
Jack: No, they were probably
lost or found somewhere.
I really like it out here.
Yeah, me too.
I'm glad I'm here.
♪ What if you opened up ♪
♪ Your doors and let me stay? ♪
♪ Ooh ooh ooh ♪
♪ Ooh ooh ooh ♪♪
[water gushing]
What happened to you?
Mom don't talk about it either.
I have these memories.
You were always training.
You wore that big suit
with the collar.
I thought you
were a super-hero.
And those planes...
I loved watching them
take off and land.
I remember the day of the fire.
Everyone seemed so nervous,
but not you.
You told me it was your job,
that everything would be okay.
You hugged me.
Then afterwards at the
ambulance, your face was
all black, and you had
bandages all over you.
I wanted to hold your hand,
but I was scared.
I thought you were a zombie.
That was the last time
you ever hugged me.
[instrumental music]
[sighs]
[music continues]
One, two.
Wait, dad!
Three!
[water splashing]
Dad?
[indistinct]
[screaming]
[instrumental music]
Dad!
[music continues]
Dad! Dad!
[screams]
Jesus, that was crazy.
Whoo! Whoo!
[instrumental music]
[water splashing]
[breathing]
It's freezing!
Why didn't you tell me
it was so cold?
- It's so cold.
- Oh.
Ah. No.
- Where you going?
- To get dry clothes!
Ah! Huh.
[water splashing]
Well, hey there.
That's your daddy down there?
Y'all from around here.
No, I guess no. You're looking
more like a city girl to me.
Nice bike.
Don't touch that!
Hey, calm down, old lady.
We're not here to bother you.
[laughs]
We're here to cool off.
It's our hole. We go swimming.
Come on now.
Don't worry, he's just
messing with you.
Joe, let's head upriver.
We got towels in the truck.
Denny, where is the cooler?
Man, I give you one job.
Denny: I don't know.
Hanna! Hanna!
Joe: It's probably still
on the porch. Dumb shit.
Jack: Hanna!
- Oh.
- It's my bag.
Then take it.
[screams]
Hanna!
[groans]
Ah, Hanna!
Denny: Come on, man,
let's find another spot.
Jesus, cut it, man.
What do you mean
you're out of here?
Denny: Hey, man.
[grunts]
[groans]
Dad!
Come on, let's go.
God dammit. You're crazy, man.
[engine rumbling]
[choking]
Shit.
- Hanna, get on the bike!
- No!
Hanna, get on the bike!
- Yeah.
- Man.
You're not making any sense.
- Get on the bike!
- No.
Don't leave. Please don't leave.
[engine revving]
[instrumental music]
Dad!
Hey! Pull over!
Oh, shit, man. Is he here?
Denny: This guy is insane!
[music continues]
[police siren blaring]
Pull over, you son of a bitch!
Pull over!
Hey!
Come on!
[music continues]
[police siren blaring]
[instrumental music]
♪ How deep's the water? ♪
♪ You say it's not ♪
♪ How long is it flowing? ♪
♪ You say it's gone ♪
Just wanna let you know
that your daughter is safe
and your bike's in the back.
Her mom should be here
in about an hour or so.
Just thought you'd like to know.
♪ I guess it was a ♪
♪ A picture in my mind ♪
♪ Oh lover you seem
to be hiding ♪
♪ Something from me and
I'll find it ♪
♪ How you would seem
to repeat and dream ♪
♪ But they mean nothing to me ♪♪
Can I see him?
I'm sorry, darlin',
I can't let you back there.
Are you sure you don't
want something to eat?
Alright, well, your mom should
be here in about an hour.
Let me know if you
need anything, okay?
Kelly: Hanna!
Hanna!
- Mom?
- Hi.
Oh, baby.
[sighs]
Mike: Looks like your
ex-husband got into it
with a couple of our local boys.
Kelly: Everyone's okay?
Mike: Yeah, yeah, they're fine.
One of them clocked him
pretty good though.
How's he doing?
Not saying much, but we
had him checked out, seems fine.
Listen, I don't think anyone's
pressing any charges here.
But he still gonna have
to spend the night.
Okay. Thank you.
Mike: Ma'am.
[instrumental music]
Kelly: Hey, kiddo. I got us some
breakfast from up front.
Nice people here.
When can we go see dad?
Well, I imagine he'll be
getting released pretty soon.
You wanna take a shower?
No, I'm fine.
Okay, then.
Why don't you eat some
breakfast?
I'll take a quick one,
and then we can go see.
- That sound good?
- Yeah.
Kelly: We don't have
too much time though.
Our flight's at 2:00, and the
airport's a few hours drive.
[water pattering]
So I think we can just get
some lunch at the airport.
That sound good?
[instrumental music]
Hi, I was wondering when
my dad will be released?
Who's your dad?
Jack? Jack Elliot.
Oh, he was released an hour ago.
What?
Hey.
You left me.
Hanna, those guys...
I don't care! You left me.
[engine revving]
You left me.
You're right.
I did leave you.
I left all of you, my marriage,
my life, all of it.
Why?
Why, dad? Why did you leave?
Because I couldn't
take it anymore!
Everyone was driving me crazy!
Everyone was trying to help,
trying to tell me what I needed.
But nobody knew,
nobody had any idea!
I lost all of them that day.
I lost everything.
Everything?
I was still there!
Hanna, that's...
You're right!
You're right.
[instrumental music]
It's like my body shut down.
And I was just
trying to survive.
And it made me so...
It made me...
Stop caring.
I tried to power through,
I tried to...
And I was just lying to myself.
I had to get away.
So I left.
And I'm so sorry.
[music continues]
Are you okay?
What are you...
Hanna?
Dad's taking me to the airport.
Sorry, mom.
[instrumental music]
How much farther we got?
About three hours.
[laughs]
[engine revving]
[instrumental music]
Jack: The winds, they shift.
Fire pushes right up
the hillside.
I know we can't get away.
The smoke, it's all around me.
I can't breathe.
I dropped my pack, and I pushed
through the rocks and tell
everyone to follow me, but when
I get there, I'm all alone.
Except for those flames.
I thought... This is it.
I push along the perimeter,
about ready to collapse
when I see this rock slide.
So, I hunker down,
and bury my face in the rocks,
and I make my peace.
There's been this emptiness.
And then I saw you standing
in that parking lot.
I'm scared, Hanna.
[instrumental music]
[phone vibrating]
It's probably mom.
- Hello?
Tick: Jack, my man!
- Tick?
Tick: Yeah, buddy!
Hey, listen, I don't know
how you got a vacation already,
maybe some hanky-panky
with the boss.
I don't wanna know, but...
Are you coming back or what?
I'm definitely one-man
show without you here.
The new guy is Green!
Yeah, man. I'm coming.
[engine revving]
[instrumental music]
♪ When the rain's pouring down
you can't see the light ♪
♪ But you know that it's dark
you're used to the night ♪
♪ Don't know which side
of the line's feeling right ♪
♪ So you veer to the left ♪
♪ Oncoming headlights
are pullin' you in ♪
♪ Ghost you lost
in a fight ♪
♪ Should've been you
they'd be alright ♪
♪ Can't see through smoke ♪
♪ Can't see through hindsight ♪
♪ All you can see are
those two poachin' lights ♪
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
[music continues]
♪ People asked how you were? ♪
♪ All you could say was fine ♪
♪ They couldn't understand
the truth beatin' inside ♪
♪ So just be honest
stop with the lying ♪
♪ They questioned they prodded
so you got outta line ♪
♪ Walking through the woods
lost in the pines ♪
♪ I know where I am
I'm losing my mind ♪
♪ I got out here early
but I'm all out of time ♪
♪ The lights of the
oncoming truck are on mine ♪
♪ And you pull me back ♪
♪ Across those two
yellow lines ♪♪
[music continues]