John Kennedy: TO HALT
THIS OFFENSIVE BUILDUP,
A STRICT QUARANTINE ON ALL
OFFENSIVE MILITARY EQUIPMENT
UNDER SHIPMENT TO CUBA
IS BEING INITIATED.
ALL SHIPS OF ANY KIND
BOUND FOR CUBA
FROM WHATEVER
NATION OR PORT,
WHERE THEY'RE FOUND
TO CONTAIN CARGOS
OF OFFENSIVE WEAPONS,
WILL BE TURNED BACK.
IT SHALL BE THE POLICY
OF THIS NATION
TO REGARD
ANY NUCLEAR MISSILE
LAUNCHED FROM CUBA
AGAINST ANY NATION
IN THE WESTERN HEMISPHERE
AS AN ATTACK
BY THE SOVIET UNION
ON THE UNITED STATES.
I HAVE DIRECTED
THE ARMED FORCES
TO PREPARE
FOR ANY EVENTUALITY.
[MAN SPEAKING RUSSIAN]
[GUNSHOT]
[MOANS]
[ALARM SOUNDS]
[MEN SCREAMING]
Man: LET ME GUESS.
THEY'RE SENDING US
MORE FILES.
Man:
20 FROM GERMANY,
10 MORE FROM SUDAN.
YOU KNOW, HENRY,
WE'RE ON THE FRONT LINE.
WE DON'T HAVE TIME
TO BROWSE THROUGH FILES.
FRONT LINE?
BERLIN, '54--
THAT WAS FRONT LINE--
EYEBALL TO EYEBALL
WITH JOE STALIN.
DIDN'T STALIN
DIE IN '53?
AW, HELL,
'54, '53, '52.
WHAT THE HELL?
[LAUGHS]
HENRY, COME ON.
NOT EVERYBODY CAN BE
OUT THERE SAVING
THE FREE WORLD,
AND FRANKLY, I'M BETTER
AT EURO-SOVIET
ECONOMIC RELATIONS
THAN I AM
AT SMUGGLING MICROFILM.
SO WHAT?
I SAY YOU PLAY WITH
THE CARDS YOU'RE DEALT.
WAIT.
OH, MY GOD.
ROY, LOOK OVER THERE
QUICK.
WHAT?
DAMN, I WISH I WAS
20 YEARS YOUNGER.
[MAN WOLF WHISTLES]
SHE REMINDS ME OF A CHICK
I USED TO KNOW.
DON'T TELL ME--
BERLIN, '53? '52?
YEAH, YEAH.
LET ME TELL YOU
ABOUT THE NIGHT WE MET.
SHE'S WEARING THIS TIGHT,
BOLD MINIDRESS
WITH A FLUFFY COLLAR
ON IT.
WHEN SHE WALKED BY ME,
I SWEAR, ROY...
UH-OH.
HERE COMES THE CIA.
GOING ON A GIRLIE HUNT?
Roy:
THAT'S VERY FUNNY.
HI, ROY.
HEY, MAGGIE.
HOW'S MY GIRLFRIEND?
BORED.
I NEED SOME EXCITEMENT
IN MY LIFE.
ARE YOU GOING
TO ARREST ME?
MAGGIE, PLEASE.
OH, NO.
NAH...
BUT I TELL YOU
WHAT I AM GOING TO DO.
I'M GOING TO GO
TO THE STORE
AND BUY YOU
YOUR FAVORITE CHOCOLATE.
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
YOU DO IT.
SHE GOT ME AGAIN.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Henry:
SWEET KID,
BUT YOU SPOIL HER.
OOH.
EXCUSE ME, HANDSOME.
SHE DEFINITELY
PREFERRED YOU, HENRY.
NO. SHE HAD THAT "WHO'S
YOUR FRIEND" LOOK.
IT MUST BE THE SHIRT.
WHAT'S WRONG
WITH MY SHIRT?
Henry:
IT'S PINK.
HA HA HA HA!
COME ON. YOU CAN BUY ME
A CUP OF COFFEE.
PASTRIES. PASTRIES.
FRESHLY BAKED.
PLEASE. PLEASE.
VERY--VERY FRESH.
AH, VERY, VERY...
VERY...
YOU WANT?
I TELL YOU
SOMETHING.
PASTRIES?
OH, WHAT A BEAUTIFUL
LITTLE GIRL.
[LAUGHS]
PRETTY.
BEAUTIFUL.
LOOK WHAT I HAVE.
LOOK--LOOK
WHAT I HAVE.
THANK YOU.
A GIFT FOR YOU.
GOOD GIRL.
YOU ARE A GOOD GIRL--
A SWEET LITTLE GIRL.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[BARKS]
[SPEAKING
NATIVE LANGUAGE]
HEY, THERE GOES
YOUR GIRLFRIEND.
AW, YOU'RE JUST JEALOUS.
HA. I COULD BE, TOO.
HEY, HENRY,
YOU EVER THINK WHAT IT MUST
BE LIKE TO BE THAT OLD?
CAREFUL.
THERE'S LIFE
IN THE OLD DOG YET.
WHERE'S THAT BAG
SHE WAS CARRYING?
IT'S NOT THE SAME.
MOMMY?
[SIGHS]
MOMMY.
MAGGIE, PLEASE.
[LAUGHS]
MOMMY.
MOMMY, LOOK, PLEASE.
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
[COUGHS]
Roy: OH, MY GOD.
MAGGIE!
STAY CLOSE.
DON'T DO ANYTHING
STUPID.
JUST DO AS I SAY.
OK.
[SIREN]
Man:
HE'S GOT A GUN!
MOVE! MOVE!
Man:
HE'S GOT A GUN!
THERE'S 2 GUYS!
Henry: ROY,
CHECK OVER THERE.
Roy: SORRY.
Man: YANKEE.
HEY, YANKEE.
[SIREN]
HEY, STOP.
[CAR HONKS HORN]
THERE!
THERE SHE IS!
STOP THE CAR!
[CARS HONKING HORNS]
COME ON! COME ON!
COME ON!
Henry:
ROY, COME ON!
Woman: IS HE OK?
HENRY, WAIT!
HEY, HEY, TAXI!
Roy:
OH, MY GOD.
HENRY!
SHIT!
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
NO! PLEASE, PLEASE,
DON'T SHOOT!
UHH!
STEP AWAY FROM THE CAR!
I SAID, STEP AWAY
FROM THE CAR!
NOW!
YOU'RE UNDER ARREST.
I MEAN IT.
I SWEAR, I'LL SHOOT.
I THINK NOT.
NOT IN THIS LIFETIME,
MY FRIEND.
[TAXI DEPARTS]
[GUNSHOT]
[HONKS HORN]
HENRY.
HENRY!
HEY, HEY.
B-BERLIN...
'52.
'53.
'54.
Roy: NO.
NO!
[GROANS]
YOU SON OF A BITCH.
[COUGHS]
COME ON.
GRAB HOLD.
LET'S GO.
Man: WE GOT HIM, SIR.
WE GOT THE BOMBER.
IT'S CASPER, SIR.
THIS IS
THE NINTH EMBASSY
HE'S BOMBED IN 2 YEARS.
HE'S GOT A LOT OF BLOOD
ON HIS HANDS.
Man: I WANT HIM
OUT OF THERE IMMEDIATELY.
WE GOT IT
TAKEN CARE OF, SIR.
I'VE CONTACTED
THE CLOSEST
EXTRACTION TEAM.
THEY CAN BE THERE
IN 6 HOURS.
THEY'LL CHOPPER HIM
INTO STUTTGART AND
JET HIM OUT OF THERE.
IT'S TOO RISKY.
WE'RE DEALING WITH
THE WORLD'S LEADING
TERRORIST.
HIS PEOPLE ARE ALREADY
LOOKING FOR HIM.
WELL, THERE IS
ANOTHER WAY, SIR.
THE NAVY'S GOT A SUB
IN THE AREA.
THERE'S SOME SORT
OF MANEUVERS.
JACK SHAW
IS THE CAPTAIN, SIR.
SHAW?
DIDN'T WE SEND HIM
OUT THERE
TO KEEP HIM AWAY
FROM ANY REAL ASSIGNMENTS
UNTIL HIS TIME
WAS SERVED?
YES, SIR. THAT'S BEEN
THE CONDITION
OF HIS CONTINUATION
SINCE HE GROUNDED
HIS LAST SUBMARINE.
IS THERE ANY GOOD NEWS?
NOT REALLY, SIR.
THERE IS ONLY
ONE SURVIVOR--
A YOUNG AGENT
NAMED TURNER.
HE'S AN ANALYST,
REALLY--
POLITICAL TRENDS,
ECONOMIC ASSESSMENTS.
YOU MEAN THE COFFEE BOY.
[SIGHS]
TURNER'S
GOT NO LEGITIMATE
FIELD EXPERIENCE,
BUT IF YOU WANT TO MOVE
NOW, HE'S ALL WE'VE GOT.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
GET A HOLD OF TURNER.
MAKE HIM FEEL GOOD.
TELL HIM HE'S GOING
TO ADD A NEW CHAPTER
TO HIS RéSUMé.
GIVE HIM THE USUAL BULL
ABOUT HONOR AND COUNTRY.
YOU TELL SHAW THAT
IF HE MESSES THIS UP...
I WILL PERSONALLY
BURY HIM AT SEA--ALIVE.
[SNEEZES]
GOD BLESS YOU.
♪ THEY JUST
COVER UP NICE ♪
♪ THEIR BEAUTY
♪ IS A DAGGER
♪ THAT CUTS LIKE A KNIFE
[MUSIC STOPS]
[YAWNS]
BUMPY RIDE?
MM-HMM.
[LAUGHS]
Man:
YOU TURNER?
Roy:
YEAH.
CAPTAIN JACK SHAW,
S.S.N. ROOSEVELT.
I GUESS THAT MAKES ME
THE NEW BABY-SITTER.
EXCUSE ME?
IT'S NOT EVERY DAY
I GET A CALL FROM
THE ADMIRAL-IN-CHIEF
TELLING ME THAT
I'VE BEEN LOANED OUT.
HEAR YOU GOT LUCKY
AND KNOCKED ONE OUT OF
THE PARK, SPECIAL AGENT.
YEAH. IT'S SOMETHING
LIKE THAT. THANKS.
AND IT'S NOT
"SPECIAL AGENT"--
JUST "AGENT" WILL DO.
I'LL TRY
TO KEEP THAT IN MIND.
TAKE HIM OUT.
Man: YES, SIR.
♪ I CAN BE CHILLIN'
♪ I CAN SLAM
♪ I CAN BUST A MOVE...
[PEOPLE CHATTERING]
Woman: I LIKE
THIS HIP-HOP VERY MUCH.
THIS IS
A NUMBER ONE HAND.
[ALL TALKING AT ONCE]
OK. OH, YEAH.
OK. OK, EVERYBODY.
LISTEN TO ME.
I MAKE A DEAL WITH YOU,
MR. BRICKMAN.
IF YOU WIN,
I TAKE OFF EVERYTHING--
TOTALLY NAKED.
Man: OH, YEAH!
OH, YEAH?
WELL, LET'S ROLL WITH IT.
BUT IF YOU LOSE,
YOU 100% NAKED
BLACK MAN.
WE SHOULD JUST SLAP ON IT.
YEAH.
WE HAVE A DEAL?
AIN'T NO BACKTRACKING NOW.
NO GOING BACK.
SHOW ME WHAT YOU GOT.
COME ON.
AW, YEAH.
STOP YOUR GRINNING
AND DROP YOUR LINEN.
BAM!
FULL HOUSE.
[MEN CHEER]
OOH!
Man:
OH, YEAH!
OH.
OW.
Man:
TAKE IT OFF, BABY.
OOH, OUCH.
HELLO. IT'S TITTY TIME,
TITTY TIME.
YOU GOT ME.
YOU GOT ME. OHH.
MR. BRICKMAN,
ROYAL FLUSH.
[MEN CHEER]
NO, NO.
[LAUGHTER]
Man: ROYAL NAVY!
ROYAL FLUSH!
COME ON. COME ON.
COME ON, NOW.
DON'T BE SHY.
NO. NO, NO.
YOU CHEATED. YOU CHEATED.
YOU CHEATED.
MR. BRICKMAN,
IF YOU CANNOT DO,
I CAN DO FOR YOU.
IT'S OK.
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
PLEASE.
SHE CHEATED.
SHE CHEATED, NOW, Y'ALL.
[LAUGHS]
COME ON. I WANT
TO SEE SOMETHING.
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT.
STEP BACK. I DON'T WANT
TO HURT NOBODY.
CAPTAIN ON DECK.
[MUSIC STOPS]
AHEM.
AT EASE.
AS YOU'VE BEEN INFORMED,
WE HAVE A VISITOR ON BOARD--
ACTUALLY, 2.
SPECIAL AGENT
TURNER HERE
IS FROM THE CENTRAL
INTELLIGENCE AGENCY.
HIS TRAVELING COMPANION
HAS EVIDENTLY MADE
ENOUGH OF A NAME
FOR HIMSELF
TO WARRANT A FREE RIDE
HOME WITH US.
SPECIAL AGENT
TURNER HERE
IS A REGULAR JAMES BOND
IN THE FLESH.
OH.
UH, JUST
AGENT TURNER IS FINE.
IT'S NICE TO MEET YOU,
AGENT TURNER.
DOCTOR FINCH
IS ANOTHER ONE
OF OUR SPECIAL GUESTS.
SHE'S ON LOAN
FROM THE OCEANOGRAPHIC
INSTITUTE
WHILE WE RUN AN ANALYSIS
OF THE FASCINATING
CHANGES OF THE OCEAN
UNDERCURRENTS
AND THE MARINE LIFE
IN THE AREA.
SHE'S A SPECIALIST.
THAT I AM.
IS, UH, THAT THE AREA?
UH, UH, YEAH.
AFFECTIONATELY KNOWN
AS THE DEVIL'S EYE.
27 SHIPS
HAVE GONE DOWN THERE
OVER THE PAST FEW YEARS--
ALL UNEXPLAINED.
HENCE, THE OLD SAILOR'S
MYTH ABOUT A GIANT SERPENT
THAT ATTACKS ANY SHIP
THAT DARES TO ENTER
THAT PARTICULAR AREA.
MAKES THE BERMUDA TRIANGLE
LOOK LIKE A DUCK POND.
THANK YOU, DR. FINCH.
AS USUAL, YOU'VE BEEN
MOST INFORMATIVE,
BUT RIGHT NOW, I HAVE
THE ADDED PROBLEM
OF FINDING
SPECIAL AGENT TURNER
A SPARE BUNK.
OH.
REALLY? UM...
BECAUSE, UH,
I HAVE A SPARE BUNK.
I'M SURE THE SPECIAL
AGENT WOULD PREFER
TO SLEEP
IN THE CREW'S QUARTERS.
OH. I'M SORRY.
WOULD YOU RATHER--
NO, NO.
THAT'S--THAT'S FINE...
OH.
ACTUALLY.
WELL, THEN,
THAT, UH, SETTLES THAT,
DOESN'T IT?
EXCUSE ME.
I JUST, UH...
HAVE TO, UM...
GET MY, UH, PANTIES.
MR. BRICKMAN.
SIR.
YOU'RE A LOUSY
CARD PLAYER.
PANTS UP.
TAKE US DOWN.
SIR.
DOLPHIN DEPTH.
Man: YES, SIR.
YOU KNOW,
I WAS A HERO ONCE.
I ACTUALLY CAPTURED
A WHOLE BOATLOAD OF IRAQIS
IN THE GULF ACTION.
OF COURSE, I HAD TO
TURN THEM RIGHT BACK OVER.
IT STILL PISSES ME OFF.
BUT THAT'S A WHOLE OTHER
STORY I WON'T GET INTO.
Brickman: ANYBODY KNOW
THIS DUDE THEY'RE
BRINGING ON BOARD?
HE MEANS, LIKE,
TERRORIST OR SOMETHING.
TERRORIST, MAN?
I TELL YOU WHAT.
IF MR. SPECIAL AGENT
GREENHORN
THINKS HE CAN HANDLE
THAT GUY AND THE CAPTAIN--
HE HAS NO IDEA.
NO IDEA.
NO. HE HAS...
I'LL GIVE HIM A DEAL
ON SOME FLORIDA SWAMP LAND,
AND HE CAN BUILD
SKYSCRAPERS ON 'EM.
[LAUGHS]
REALLY?
HOW MUCH?
[SONAR PINGING]
CAN I HAVE
SOME WATER, PLEASE?
LOOK, THERE IS NO NEED
FOR ALL THIS ANIMOSITY.
WE HAVE A BOND.
I MEAN,
YOU DID SAVE MY LIFE.
I OWE YOU, ROY.
I WOULD'VE DIED
IN THAT CAR,
BUT YOU PULLED ME OUT.
NOT MANY PEOPLE WOULD'VE
CARED THE WAY YOU DID.
IT WAS SO BRAVE OF YOU.
I'M BEGINNING TO THINK
IT WAS A MISTAKE.
OH, THERE ARE
NO MISTAKES, ROY.
LIFE PRESENTS
SITUATIONS.
WE REACT TO THEM,
WHICH IS HOW
WE ARE MEASURED.
THE KEY, I FIND,
IS TO STAY FOCUSED
ON WHAT YOU REALLY WANT.
THAT WAY,
YOU WILL ALWAYS REACT
ACCORDINGLY
AND HAVE NO REGRETS.
YOU THINK I'M GOING
TO HAVE REGRETS?
OF COURSE, ROY.
ONE OF US HAS TO,
AND IT CAN'T BE ME.
IT CAN'T BE HENRY...
ANYMORE.
[LAUGHS]
[SPEAKING
NATIVE LANGUAGE]
YOU'RE LATE.
A WOMAN'S PREROGATIVE.
THAT'S HIM.
AGENT ROY TURNER.
HE HAS CASPER.
THESE WERE PULLED
FROM A RUSSIAN SATELLITE
6 HOURS AGO.
THEY ARE BOTH ON BOARD.
THEY'RE TRANSPORTING HIM
BACK TO THE UNITED STATES
VIA SUBMARINE.
OUR CONTACTS ARE ACQUIRING
THEIR COORDINATES
AND TRAVEL ROUTES
AS WE SPEAK.
I'LL ORGANIZE
THE ESCAPE ROUTE.
JUST MAKE SURE
YOU'RE READY WHEN
CASPER MAKES CONTACT.
Man: AT THIS MOMENT,
OUR PEOPLE
ARE INFILTRATING
A CRUISE LINER.
Woman: YOU STOP THAT
RUNNING DOWN THE HALL.
IT'S DUE TO EMBARK
SHORTLY.
THEIR IDENTITIES
ARE UNKNOWN.
THEY WILL BE DISGUISED
AS PASSENGERS
OR CREW MEMBERS.
THEY WILL NOT
REVEAL THEMSELVES
UNTIL THE LAST
POSSIBLE MOMENT.
SORRY.
Man: ONCE CASPER
IS RETRIEVED,
THEIR ORDERS ARE TO
BLOW UP THE CRUISE LINER
AND ELIMINATE
ALL WITNESSES.
THEY ARE PREPARED TO
GIVE UP THEIR OWN LIVES
IF NECESSARY.
WHEN EVERYBODY
IS IN POSITION,
THEY WILL LOG INTO
THE SHIP'S MAIN
COMPUTER SYSTEM,
AND AT THE MOMENT
OF CONTACT
ALTER ITS COURSE
TO INTERCEPT
WITH THE
ROOSEVELT.
[SHIP HORN BLOWS]
[RINGS]
THE CREW'S CAPTAIN
HAS BEEN ORDERED
TO FOLLOW
ALL INSTRUCTIONS.
CAPTAIN, TELEPHONE.
Woman: HOW CAN YOU
BE SURE HE'LL COMPLY?
THIS IS
THE CAPTAIN SPEAKING.
Man on phone:
REMEMBER, WE ARE WATCHING
EVERY MOVE YOU MAKE.
ONE MISTAKE,
AND THEY DIE.
Man: WE HAVE
HIS FAMILY.
HE WILL DO
ANYTHING WE WANT.
[SCREAMS]
[SIGHS]
Roy: AHEM.
OOH.
AGENT TURNER.
BURNING
THE MIDNIGHT OIL AGAIN?
YEAH, I GUESS.
I TELL YOU, THE LAST WEEK
HAS BEEN SO CRAZY
I DON'T KNOW WHAT DAY--
LET ME. OW!
OOH.
THANKS.
WHEW.
SO, YOU HAVEN'T
SAID MUCH FOR
THE LAST FEW DAYS.
WHAT'S YOUR STORY,
TURNER?
ARE YOU REALLY SOME KIND
OF, UH, SUPER SPY?
UH, NO, NO.
THAT'S JUST SHAW TALKING.
I--I'M TRAINED
AS AN ANALYST.
UH, THIS IS MY FIRST BIT
OF FIELD DUTY.
IT KIND OF CAME
AS A SURPRISE...
ALL AROUND.
BUT YOU, UH--YOU DID
ALWAYS WANT TO BE
AN AGENT, RIGHT?
YEAH, ACTUALLY.
UM...
ALTHOUGH, I DID HAVE
A BACKUP PLAN.
I KIND OF THOUGHT I'D BE
A COLLEGE PROFESSOR.
YOU KNOW,
TEACH POLITICAL THEORY...
W-WRITE A COUPLE BOOKS.
I DON'T KNOW.
CALL ME A CLICHé.
I GUESS I THOUGHT
IT MIGHT BE A NICE WAY
TO SEE THE WORLD.
OH, REALLY?
SO, UH...
WHAT'S THE DEAL
WITH YOU AND SHAW?
YOU GUYS LIKE AN ITEM
OR SOMETHING?
OH, PLEASE.
JACK SHAW
IS A PETTY,
SELF-INVOLVED,
CRAZY SHELL OF A MAN.
DID HE TELL YOU ABOUT
CAPTURING THE BOATLOAD
OR IRAQIS YET?
YEAH. HE MENTIONED
SOMETHING ABOUT IT. YEAH.
WELL, YOU KNOW,
LIKE HE SAID,
HE DID CAPTURE
THE ENTIRE PATROL BOAT,
BUT THE PART HE TENDS
TO LEAVE OUT
IS THE FACT THAT HE RAN
A U.S. NUCLEAR SUB AGROUND
TO PULL IT OFF.
HMM. WELL...
YOU KNOW,
I'VE--I'VE...
I'VE DONE SOME PRETTY
CRAZY THINGS MYSELF.
I, UH...
ACTUALLY, RIGHT--
RIGHT BEFORE THIS,
I, UH--WELL,
I APPREHENDED
THESE 2 REALLY
NOTORIOUS--
[GUNSHOT]
[FLUSHES TOILET]
I COULD'VE DIED
OR SOMETHING.
IT'S ALL YOURS.
OH, YEAH.
YOU KNOW, WITH SHAW,
IT'S ALWAYS
AN ADVENTURE. HEH HEH!
[CRASH]
[MACHINE BEEPING]
[CREW CHATTERING]
WHOA.
[ALARM SOUNDS]
[BOTTLE BREAKS]
THAT WASN'T GOOD.
EXCUSE ME.
[ALARM SOUNDS]
RUDDER FAILURE, CAPTAIN--
UPPER AND LOWER.
I'D SAY SOMETHING
HIT US, BUT--
THERE'S NOTHING
ON THE SCREENS.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
WHAT'S THE PROBLEM?
AH, IF IT ISN'T
OUR RESIDENT VIPs.
I HOPE WE DIDN'T
INTERRUPT ANYTHING.
YEAH. WHY ARE WE
STOPPED?
WE'RE EXPERIENCING
WHAT YOU MIGHT CALL
TECHNICAL DIFFICULTIES.
LOOK, DON'T WORRY.
I MEAN, YOU TWO
JUST GO BACK TO SLEEP.
DO WHATEVER
YOU WERE DOING.
I'VE DISPENSED A DIVE TEAM.
THEY'RE CHECKING OUT
THE DAMAGE.
MR. BRICKMAN,
GIVE ME THE VISUALS
ON THE DIVERS A.S.A.P.
AYE, AYE, SIR.
I WANT TO SEE
WHAT'S GOING ON OUT THERE.
[BREATHING QUICKLY]
[STRAINING]
[STIFLED SCREAMING]
Brickman:
LUCAS, LOPEZ,
HOW ARE YOU GUYS
DOING OUT THERE?
LET ME KNOW
WHEN YOU'RE IN POSITION.
HEY, BRICKMAN,
I'VE ONLY GOT
ONE SET OF LUNGS.
I'M MOVING
AS FAST AS I CAN.
THIS VISIBILITY'S BAD.
Brickman:
OK, MR. TAYLOR,
LET'S SEE
WHAT WE GOT.
Taylor: OK. GOT YOU.
WE GOT VISUALS.
Brickman: HEY, YOU GUYS
LOOK FAT ON CAMERA.
YEAH, MAN.
JUST LIKE
YOUR LAST GIRLFRIEND.
Brickman: IF WE CAN GET
HER FLAPS CLOSED,
I MIGHT BE ABLE
TO SWEET TALK HER
INTO SOME ACTION.
SHE LIKES IT
WHEN I TALK DIRTY.
OOH, YOU'RE GETTING ME
ALL EXCITED.
LUCAS, SEE IF YOU CAN
CLOSE UP THE FLAP.
LOPEZ, CHECK OUT
THE LOWER RUDDERS.
UH, MR. BRICKMAN
IS GOING TO HUMOR US
WITH HIS LATEST
PICKUP MOVES.
CAPTAIN, WE'RE GOING
TO NEED ALL THE SWEET
TALKING HE'S GOT.
IT LOOKS LIKE
SOMETHING BIG HIT US.
OK, LUCAS,
YOU HEARD THE CAPTAIN.
SEE IF YOU CAN
STITCH HER UP.
I'LL BE BACK.
Lucas: OK, BRICKMAN,
DON'T GET JEALOUS.
I'M ABOUT TO WARM UP
YOUR GIRLFRIEND.
[BREATHING]
Lopez: THIS IS LOPEZ,
CAPTAIN.
I'M APPROACHING
THE RUDDER.
MAN! LOOKS LIKE
SOMETHING RIPPED INTO US
WITH A GIANT CAN OPENER.
[OCTOPUS ROARS]
Lucas: CAPTAIN,
THERE'S SOMETHING STRANGE
GOING ON OUT HERE.
STILL THINK I SHOULD
GO BACK TO SLEEP?
Lucas: LOPEZ, MAN,
I'M GETTIN' A CHILL
DOWN MY SPINE.
SOMETHING JUST
DON'T FEEL RIGHT.
ARE YOU OK?
Lopez:
YEAH, I'M OK.
WAIT, I THINK I SEE--
I SEE SOMETHING
MOVING OUT THERE.
CAPTAIN.
CAPTAIN, WE'RE LOSING
VISUALS ON LOPEZ.
THIS IS NOT GOOD.
THIS IS REALLY NOT GOOD.
Shaw:
TAYLOR, FIX IT.
I WANT TO KNOW WHAT
THE HELL'S GOING ON.
Lisa:
WHAT'S HAPPENING TO THEM?
Brickman: JACKSON,
CHECK THAT FEED LINE NOW.
[SCREAMING]
Brickman: CAPTAIN,
THIS DON'T LOOK GOOD.
Lisa: SOMEBODY
DO SOMETHING.
Man:
WHAT THE HELL'S
GOING ON OUT THERE?
Taylor: THERE'S JUST
SOMETHING WRONG.
THERE'S SOMETHING
VERY WRONG.
Brickman: DAMN!
LUCAS, LOPEZ,
GET OUT OF THERE NOW.
CAN YOU HEAR ME?
GET OUT OF THERE!
Man: SIR,
ALL COMMUNICATIONS
ARE DEAD.
EXTERNAL MICROPHONES
NOW.
EXTERNAL MICROPHONES,
AYE-AYE, SIR.
[FRANTIC SCREAMING]
SALVANTO, GIVE ME
A PING TOTAL RADIUS.
[SCREAMING]
[OCTOPUS ROARS]
THEY'RE GONE, SIR.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
GONE?
I MEAN, THEY'RE GONE,
THEY'RE GONE.
THEY DISAPPEARED
OFF THE SCREEN.
THEY'RE GONE.
I NEED A READING NOW!
PING AWAY!
Taylor: OK.
OK, WE GOT SOMETHING.
Lisa: WHAT IS THAT?
MOVING OFF
THE PORT SIDE.
Shaw:
SALVANTO, IDENTIFY.
IDENTIFYING.
Salvanto:
IT--IT'S NOTHING, SIR.
NOTHING? BUT--
WHAT DO YOU--
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
THERE'S
NO SIGNATURE MATCH.
WE'VE NEVER HAD
A SONAR READING
LIKE THIS BEFORE.
WHATEVER IT IS, THOUGH,
IT'S SITTING
OFF THE PORT SIDE
ABOUT 200 HUNDRED METERS.
AND IT'S NOT MOVING.
MR. BRICKMAN, IS THERE
ANY CHANCE WE CAN
TURN AROUND TO FACE IT?
NEGATIVE.
NOT ON THESE RUDDERS.
WHAT ARE WE
GONNA DO, SIR?
SIR, WE CAN'T JUST
LEAVE THEM OUT THERE.
SIR?
MR. BRICKMAN...
TAKE US DOWN.
GO SILENT.
YOU HEARD THE MAN.
FULL POWER. LET'S HOPE
THESE RUDDERS HOLD UP.
EXCUSE ME, CAPTAIN,
I HATE TO POINT THIS OUT,
BUT NOW MIGHT BE
A REALLY GOOD TIME
TO CALL FOR HELP.
I'M WELL AWARE
OF OUR SITUATION,
SPECIAL AGENT TURNER.
AND WHILE I APPRECIATE
YOUR ENTHUSIASM
AND CONCERN,
I REALLY THINK IT'S BEST
IF YOU TOOK CARE
OF YOUR BUSINESS
AND YOU LET ME
TAKE CARE OF MINE.
LOOK, SHAW,
I KNOW YOUR GAME.
I KNOW
ALL ABOUT YOU.
OH, REALLY?
WE ARE OBVIOUSLY
IN TROUBLE.
NOW IS NOT THE TIME
TO TRY TO BE A HERO.
HERO?
AND WHAT THE HELL
DO YOU THINK
YOU'D KNOW ABOUT THAT?
P.A.: AGENT TURNER,
REPORT TO THE BRIG.
AGENT TURNER,
YEAH,
I'LL BE RIGHT THERE.
HEY, UM, BRICKMAN,
IS THERE ANY WAY I CAN
GET A COPY OF THOSE TAPES
FROM THE DIVERS?
WHY DON'T YOU TALK
TO THE CAPTAIN?
NO, LISTEN, LISTEN,
I THINK I CAN HELP HERE.
HEY, LADY, IN CASE
YOU HAVEN'T NOTICED,
WE JUST LOST A COUPLE
OF GOOD MEN OUT THERE.
AND IN CASE
YOU HAVEN'T NOTICED,
YOU NEED ALL THE HELP
YOU CAN GET,
SO I SUGGEST THAT YOU
TELL ME HOW I CAN GET
A COPY OF THOSE TAPES.
HEY, HEY.
YOU WANT 'EM?
IT'S ALL DIGITAL.
LOG ON TO THE SHIP'S
MAINFRAME AND--
WHAT ARE YOU DOING, MAN?
WE'RE IN TROUBLE HERE.
WE DON'T HAVE TIME
TO MESS AROUND WITH--
TAYLOR!
ENOUGH.
GREAT.
BRICKMAN, I JUST--
NOT NOW.
[GAGGING]
Guard:
HOLD ON. HOLD ON!
IT'S GONNA BE OK.
WHAT THE HELL'S
GOING ON?
I DON'T KNOW, SIR.
I FOUND HIM THIS WAY.
HE'S--HE'S
GOING INTO SHOCK.
HE'S CHOKING.
JUST BE CAREFUL.
BE VERY CAREFUL WITH HIM.
OHH! UHH!
AAH! AAH!
UH-OH. LOOKS LIKE
WE'RE IN TROUBLE
AGAIN, ROY.
WAIT A MINUTE.
WHAT THE HELL WAS THAT?
OK, WAIT, BACK UP.
OH, GOD.
UH, ROGER THAT.
MR. BRICKMAN,
ENGINES FULL UP,
300 METERS.
AYE-AYE, SIR.
THERE'S A MOUNTAIN RANGE
ABOUT 7 KILOMETERS
AHEAD OF US.
NOW, IF I CAN GET US MOVING
IN A STRAIGHT LINE,
WE CAN RUN FOR THE HILLS
AND SEE IF THIS THING FOLLOWS.
DROPPING REMOTE
DETONATION MINES
AS WE GO?
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
IN THESE CANYONS,
I'D SAY YOU'RE CRAZY,
BUT WHAT ELSE IS NEW?
GOOD.
LET'S ROCK.
YOU'RE THE CAPTAIN.
BY THE WAY,
DO WE KNOW EXACTLY
WHAT IT IS THAT'S
GONNA BE FOLLOWING US?
I HAVE NO IDEA,
BUT IT'S GOT A TIGER
BY THE TAIL.
SALVANTO, WE'RE GOING
INTO UNKNOWN TERRITORY.
LET'S HOPE THIS THING
TAKES THE BAIT.
AND, UM, WRITE A LETTER
TO YOUR MAMA.
Casper:
IF YOU WANT HIM TO LIVE,
JUST TAKE THE KEYS
AND UNLOCK ME.
DON'T DO IT, SIR.
I'M READY TO DIE.
OK,
NOBODY NEEDS TO DIE.
Salvanto:
CHECK THIS OUT, SIR.
YOU CAN STILL SEE IT.
THERE!
MR. BRICKMAN.
DEPTH--
300 METERS, CAPTAIN.
20 KNOTS AND CLIMBING.
Taylor: 20 KNOTS CONFIRMED.
HOW ABOUT A LITTLE
LOOP-DE-LOOP?
CONFUSE THE MOTHER.
IT'S MOVING INTO POSITION.
COME ON. COME ON.
[BEEP]
WE GOT IT.
THERE. RIGHT THERE.
MR. BRICKMAN,
READY THE MINES.
AYE, SIR.
CAPTAIN, YOU ARE NOT
GONNA BELIEVE THIS.
LISTEN,
I ENHANCED THE VIDEOTAPE
FROM LOPEZ AND LUCAS.
AS FAR AS I CAN TELL,
WE'RE DEALING
WITH SOME KIND
OF GIANT SEA CREATURE.
OH, GOOD, THAT MAKES
MY PLAN A LOT EASIER.
WHAT PLAN?
THE ONE WHERE I'M GONNA
BLOW IT OUT OF THE WATER.
THIS THING'S GETTING
BETTER BY THE MINUTE.
[BEEP]
THAT-A-BOY.
YOU SEE, THERE IS
HOPE FOR YOU YET.
Salvanto: SIR,
200 METERS AND CLOSING.
Brickman:
PRIMED AND READY.
AND...DEPLOY.
175 METERS.
MINES AWAY.
AND...
Salvanto:
125 AND CLOSING.
DETONATE.
COME ON.
Lisa:
DID WE GET IT?
Salvanto: YES!
WE'VE GOT IT, SIR!
IT'S DISAPPEARED
OFF THE SONAR.
YES! OH, BABY!
YOU ARE A MAN!
YOU ARE A VERY BAD MAN!
I'M A BAD MAN!
I SHOOK UP THE WORLD!
WHOO!
OHH! HMM!
MR. BRICKMAN,
MAINTAIN COURSE AND SPEED.
SEE HOW FAR THOSE RUDDERS
WILL TAKE US.
WHAT DID I TELL YOU?
TIGER BY THE TAIL.
MMM!
Casper: COME ON, ROY,
YOU KNOW IT MAKES SENSE.
GOOD BOY.
YOU'VE DONE WELL.
ALL RIGHT, LET HIM--
LET HIM GO.
THEY'LL GET YOU FOR THIS.
YOU WILL BURN.
LIKE I SAID...
NOT IN THIS LIFETIME.
UHH!
Salvanto:
WAIT, WHOA, WHOA.
Brickman: CAPTAIN,
YOU'RE NOT GONNA BELIEVE THIS.
SIR, IT'S STILL THERE.
Lisa: OH, MY GOD.
WHAT DOES IT WANT?
Shaw: INCREASE SPEED,
MR. BRICKMAN.
Brickman: YES, SIR!
Salvanto: SIR,
IT'S GAINING ON US.
SPEED--46 KNOTS.
IMPACT IN 60 SECONDS.
DEPLOY ALL THE MINES.
NOW.
WHAT THE HELL
IS THAT?
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
Salvanto: OH, MY GOD.
IT'S HEADING STRAIGHT
FOR US.
SIR!
IMPACT IN 20 SECONDS!
19, 18, 17...
MR. BRICKMAN,
BRACE YOURSELF.
EVERYBODY MAINTAIN
YOUR POSITION.
THIS IS YOUR CAPTAIN
SPEAKING.
THIS IS AN EMERGENCY.
LOCK DOWN ALL MAIN VALVES
AND PREPARE FOR IMPACT.
LET'S SEAL IT.
Salvanto: 11...
JESUS.
10, 9, 8,
7, 6...
Shaw: HANG ON.
Salvanto: 3, 2...
EVERYBODY HANG ON!
1, SIR!
Shaw: HOLD ON!
Taylor: SIR,
WE'VE LOST CONTROL!
MAINTAIN YOUR STATIONS!
SALVANTO,
GIVE ME A READING!
Salvanto: SIR,
IT'S GOT A GRIP ON US!
IT WON'T LET GO!
REVERSE ENGINES FULL!
WE'RE BEING PULLED DOWN!
WE'VE GOT
MINIMAL CONTROL!
Crewman: COME ON,
MOVE IT! MOVE IT!
I CAN'T HOLD IT, SIR!
I CAN'T HOLD IT!
COME ON!
COME ON! COME ON!
[OCTOPUS ROARING]
Lisa: DO SOMETHING!
WHERE? WHERE IS IT NOW?
WHAT IS OUR DEPTH?
GET ME OFF
THIS SINKING SUB!
GET OFF ME!
TAYLOR, GET A GRIP!
HOW FAR ARE WE
FROM THAT MOUNTAIN RANGE?
Salvanto: OH, SIR,
WE'RE RIGHT ON TOP OF IT!
WE CAN'T AVOID IT!
FULL ENGINES, MR. BRICKMAN!
NOSE UP! ON MY ORDER!
CAPTAIN!
ENGINE FULL! NOSE UP!
Salvanto:
I CAN'T CONTROL IT!
SPEEDING UP IN DEPTH!
WE'RE GONNA HIT!
750 METERS!
ANY DEEPER, AND WE'RE
GONNA CRACK LIKE AN EGG!
[WATER DRIPPING,
POURING]
[COUGHING]
[ALARM SOUNDING]
[BEEPING]
Shaw: EVERYBODY, OK?
WHOO!
YOU OK?
YEAH.
Man: MR. BRICKMAN,
TAKE A LOOK AT THIS.
CAPTAIN...
800 METERS.
MAYDAY, MAYDAY.
THIS IS
THE
SSN ROOSEVELT.
WE ARE DOWN.
I REPEAT, WE ARE DOWN.
Lisa:
I NEED A DRINK.
CAPTAIN,
WE'RE AT CRUSH DEPTH.
SHE'S NOT GONNA HOLD.
SALVANTO.
SIR?
GO CHECK OUT THE DAMAGE
IN THE ENGINE ROOM.
AYE, SIR.
YOU KNOW HOW TO PRAY,
MR. BRICKMAN?
NOW'S THE TIME.
¡ARRIBA!
[SINGING IN SPANISH]
[DANCE MUSIC PLAYING]
Maid: HELLO?
[KNOCKING]
IS ANYBODY THERE?
HELLO?
Woman: YOU FOOL,
YOU LEFT THE DOOR OPEN.
ROOM SERVICE.
[MAID SIGHS]
WHAT A MESS.
I HOPE THESE PEOPLE
ARE GOOD TIPPERS.
WHAT IS THIS?
IT'S YOUR TIP.
AAH!
Lisa: SO, GET THIS.
BASED ON ITS SIZE
AND SPEED--
I MEAN, THERE IS
NO SCIENTIFIC EXPLANATION
FOR THE THING THAT HIT US.
BUT WE KNOW DIFFERENT,
DON'T WE?
WE KNOW IT'S OUT THERE,
AND WE KNOW IT'S NOT
TOO FRIENDLY.
YOU'RE MAKING AN ASSUMPTION,
CAPTAIN. IT LIVES HERE.
YOU DROVE A NUCLEAR SUB
THROUGH ITS LIVING ROOM.
YES, IF I GET
THE OPPORTUNITY,
I'M GONNA BLOW IT INTO
SO MANY LITTLE BITS,
YOU'LL BE ABLE
TO OPEN UP YOUR OWN
LITTLE SUSHI RESTAURANT.
YOU LIKE SUSHI,
DON'T YOU?
WHAT IF SOMEBODY
WALKED INTO YOUR HOME
AND PISSED ON YOUR CARPET?
FORGIVE ME FOR APPEARING
TO BE UPSET,
BUT IN CASE
YOU HAVEN'T NOTICED,
WE'RE STUCK
AT A DEPTH THAT...
WELL, FEW MEN GET
THE OPPORTUNITY
TO EXPERIENCE
UNLESS...WELL,
THEY'RE ABOUT TO DIE.
I JUST LOST 2 MEN TODAY,
2 VERY GOOD MEN.
WHAT?!
DID...DID THE NOISE
WAKE YOU?
LOOK, WE WERE ATTACKED
BY AN UNDERWATER CREATURE
OF SOME KIND.
I'M STILL TRYING TO
FIGURE OUT EXACTLY WHAT.
I DON'T HAVE TIME
FOR THIS.
WHEN YOU'RE FINISHED
WITH YOUR BRIEFING,
SPECIAL AGENT TURNER,
I'LL BE DOWN
IN THE ENGINE ROOM.
I DON'T NEED THIS
RIGHT NOW.
I THINK IT'S ABOUT TIME
WE STOPPED PLAYING GAMES
WITH THE ROOKIE
AGENT, OK?
CASPER'S GONE, AND
YOU GOT A DEAD SAILOR
ON YOUR HANDS.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
HE'S ESCAPED.
HE'S GONE.
NO! THAT WAS
YOUR RESPONSIBILITY!
HE WAS YOUR PRISONER!
YOU BETTER BE LYIN'!
I HATE TO BE
THE BEARER OF BAD NEWS,
BUT I'M A LITTLE BIT
OUT OF MY ELEMENT HERE.
I'M NOT A FIELD AGENT.
I--I'M CERTAINLY
NOT AN ESCORT.
I DIDN'T EVEN ASK
FOR THIS ASSIGNMENT,
SO I APOLOGIZE IF
THINGS AREN'T GOING
QUITE AS PLANNED.
AND I'M ASSUMING
THE SAME COULD BE SAID
ABOUT YOURSELF RIGHT NOW.
AND WOULD YOU PLEASE
STOP CALLING ME
"SPECIAL AGENT"?
AGENT TURNER, YOU'VE
JUST BEEN PRESENTED
WITH AN OPPORTUNITY.
NOW DO YOU WANT TO
GO HIDE IN THE CLOSET,
OR DO YOU WANT
TO DO SOMETHING ABOUT IT?
IT'S OK.
IT'S OK TO BE AFRAID.
LOOK, I KNOW EXACTLY
WHAT YOU'RE GOING THROUGH
RIGHT NOW.
YOU WANT TO BE JUST
LIKE ME, DON'T YA? HUH?
A MAN WHO TAKES ACTION?
OH, MY GOD.
YOU KNOW WHAT I THINK?
I THINK THAT YOU ARE
ENJOYING THIS.
ACTUALLY...
I'M SCARED SHITLESS.
BUT I FIND THAT TO BE
A HEALTHY EXPERIENCE
EVERY NOW AND AGAIN.
SO, SPECIAL AGENT,
IF YOU FEEL UP TO IT,
LET'S GO FIND
YOUR PRISONER.
[WRITING]
OK.
[BANG]
[GASPS]
OHH! OHH!
OH, GOD.
GREAT. I'M SOAKED.
AAH! AAH!
HA HA HA HA!
OOH, I LIKE THAT
IN A WOMAN.
EXCUSE ME.
OW!
WHY DOES THIS
ALWAYS HAPPEN WHEN I TRY
TO MAKE FRIENDS, HUH?
OH, GOD!
UHH!
NOW, IF YOU'RE A GOOD GIRL
AND DO EXACTLY AS I SAY,
I MIGHT BE INCLINED
TO LET YOU LIVE.
UH, OK.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
LET'S DISCUSS
THAT SCENARIO, OK?
MMM, GOOD.
OK?
GOOD.
VERY WELL.
OK.
THERE ARE SEVERAL
POSITIONING BUOYS
ON THIS SHIP,
ALL OF THEM CONTROLLED
FROM THIS STATION.
I WANT YOU TO CHANGE
FREQUENCY SIGNAL
IN ONE OF THEM,
AND LAUNCH IT.
DO YOU THINK IT'S SOMETHING
YOU CAN DO FOR ME?
BUDDY, I'LL TEACH YOU
TO SING
HAPPY BIRTHDAY,
IF THAT'S WHAT
YOU WANT, OK?
Taylor: CH-CHRIST, IT...
[STAMMERING]
LIKE A CRAMP.
FEELS LIKE A CRAMP.
CHRIST.
LIKE A CRAMP.
COME ON, RANDALL.
DON'T DO THIS
TO ME, MAN.
COME ON.
COME ON,
TAYLOR, TAYLOR.
TAYLOR.
I LEFT THE LIGHTS ON
AT HOME, MAN!
HA HA HA HA!
COME ON, TAYLOR!
COME ON, MAN!
DON'T DO THIS TO ME, MAN!
I NEED YOU!
WE NEED YOU!
I LEFT THE LIGHTS ON
AT HOME.
WE GONNA MAKE IT.
SHE'S HOLDING.
SHE'S HOLDING, BABY.
SHE'S HOLDING, MAN.
COME ON, TAYLOR,
COME ON, MAN.
SHE'S HOLDING, BABY.
JUST--JUST STICK WITH ME.
STICK WITH ME THROUGH THIS.
JUST DO YOUR JOB.
THAT'S ALL YOU GOT TO DO.
JUST DO--DO YOUR JOB, MAN.
COME ON, MAN.
WE GONNA MAKE IT.
SHE'S HOLDING.
WE GONNA MAKE IT, MAN.
JUST DO YOUR JOB.
WHAT YOU SEE?
TELL ME WHAT YOU SEE.
CONCENTRATE ON
WHAT YOU'RE DOING.
WHAT YOU SEE?
THAT'S ALL YOU
GOT TO DO, MAN.
SHE, UH...
SHE'S--SHE'S...
SHE LOGGED ON
TO THE MAINFRAME,
AND SHE'S SETTING UP
A POSITIONING BUOY.
RUDY, RUDY,
GET ME THE CAPTAIN.
BRICKMAN.
I DON'T CARE! GET ME
THE GODDAMN CAPTAIN!
GET HIM NOW!
I WANT HIM NOW!
Lisa: WHEN THE BUOY
HITS THE SURFACE,
IT'LL SEND OUT
OUR COORDINATES
IN YOUR CODE
ON YOUR FREQUENCY.
Crewman:
WHAT'S GOING ON?
COME ON, THIS WAY.
Shaw: IN HERE!
HOLD IT!
DON'T MOVE!
Casper: GUYS,
WELCOME TO THE PARTY.
JUST GETTING
TO KNOW EACH OTHER.
HEY, GUYS.
HEY, PAL,
YOU GOT 2
PISTOLAS
AIMING AT YOUR HEAD.
SURE YOU WANT
TO JOKE AROUND?
ACTUALLY,
FROM WHAT I GATHER,
WE'RE ALL
IN A BIT OF A JAM.
OK, THAT'S IT.
OK,
LET'S TRY IT AGAIN.
Lisa: OH, MY GOD.
YOU'RE COMING WITH ME,
AND YOU'RE GONNA KEEP
YOUR MOUTH SHUT
WHILE DOING IT.
DO I MAKE MYSELF CLEAR?
OK, TAKE IT EASY,
CAPTAIN.
TAKE IT EASY, CAPTAIN.
I'M...
I'M JUST DIFFICULT,
NOT--NOT FOOLISH.
UHH!
Lisa: NO!
[BEEPING]
OOPS. DID I DO THAT?
[OCTOPUS SCREECHES]
Crewman:
WE GOTTA GET UP TOP!
WE'RE TAKING ON WATER!
NO! NO!
JUST STAY COOL.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
GET BACK
TO YOUR STATION,
SOLDIER!
GET BACK
TO YOUR STATION!
Crewman: WE GOTTA
GET OUT OF HERE!
GET OUT OF HERE NOW!
JUST STAY COOL!
WE BETTER GO.
GET BACK HERE!
DON'T YOU LEAVE HERE!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING, MAN?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
GET BACK
TO YOUR STATION!
LISTEN TO YOUR ORDER!
THERE IS NO MORE ORDER, MAN.
THAT'S THE FUCKING ORDER.
COME ON, LET'S GET HIM
OUT OF HERE. MOVE!
EASY, CAPTAIN.
AS I SAID,
I'M NOT FOOLISH.
Taylor: I'M SORRY.
I'M SORRY.
YOU COWARDS!
EVERY SINGLE ONE OF YOU--
COWARDS!
COME ON. COME ON.
THAT'S ALL YOU GOT?
COME ON! COME ON!
GIVE ME SOME MORE!
THAT'S ALL YOU GOT?!
[MEN SCREAMING]
LET ME THROUGH.
WE'RE GONNA DIE!
Shaw: OH, MY GOD!
HELP!
WE'RE TRAPPED!
OPEN THE DOOR!
Lisa: THEY'RE TRAPPED.
Roy: DO SOMETHING.
COME ON!
I CAN'T GET IT OPEN!
OH, GOD!
THEY'RE GONNA
DIE IN THERE.
Shaw: HURRY, GO!
GET OUT OF HERE NOW.
WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
IF I GET THIS DOOR OPEN,
WE'RE ALL IN TROUBLE.
THIS WHOLE SECTION'S
GONNA FLOOD.
Casper: LISTEN TO HIM, ROY.
COME ON!
WE'RE ALREADY IN TROUBLE.
HEY, I'M NOT GOING ANYWHERE.
YEAH,
I'M NOT GOING ANYWHERE
WITHOUT YOU TWO.
GREAT!
2 MORE HEROES.
YOU'RE CRAMPIN'
MY STYLE.
I'LL GO.
STAY RIGHT THERE!
OHH.
OH, MY GOD.
WHAT ARE WE
GONNA DO?
GET OUT OF HERE.
GO! COME ON!
COME ON!
GO! GO!
AAH!
HA HA HA HA HA!
Lisa: YOU CREEP!
Shaw: WE'RE LOCKED IN.
AAH! LOOK OUT!
WE'RE GONNA DROWN!
WAIT! THE EMERGENCY HATCH.
COME ON.
OK.
[WHIMPERING]
AUNTIE EM, AUNTIE EM,
AUNTIE EM...
THIS WAY!
COME ON! COME ON!
AAH!
Roy: COME ON!
WE DON'T HAVE MUCH TIME!
LET'S GO!
COME ON, QUICKLY!
Lisa: WE'RE GONNA DIE!
ALL RIGHT, IT'S OPEN!
IT'S OPEN.
COME ON, COME ON!
COME ON!
LET ME HELP.
LET'S GO, LISA.
TAKE YOUR HAND
OFF MY ASS, SHAW!
IT'S OK, IT'S OK.
I GOT YOU.
YOU GOT HER?
SHAW! IT'S GOT HIM!
SHAW!
HEY! GET IT OFF ME!
GET IT OFF ME!
HERE YOU GO.
GIVE ME YOUR HAND,
GIVE ME YOUR HAND!
GOD! AAH!
MOVE OUT OF THE WAY!
GET IT OFF ME!
DO SOMETHING!
GET THE GUN, QUICK!
Roy: I CAN'T GET
A CLEAR SHOT!
GET OUT OF THE WAY!
GET OUT OF THE WAY, LISA!
I CAN'T SEE!
I CAN'T GET A CLEAR SHOT!
SHOOT IT!
SHAW! DON'T MOVE!
COME ON! DO IT!
OH,
FOR CHRIST'S SAKE!
GIVE ME THE GUN!
KEEP STILL, SHAW!
KEEP STILL!
SHOOT IT!
SUSHI TIME!
[OCTOPUS SCREECHES]
Roy: SHEESH! WHOA!
COME ON.
[WHIMPERING]
[GUNSHOT]
[BEEPING]
Man:
CASPER'S MADE CONTACT.
APPROXIMATELY 20 KILOMETERS
SOUTH BY SOUTHEAST.
Woman: ACTIVATE
THE NAVIGATIONAL
OVERRIDE.
WE NEED TO TURN
THE SHIP AROUND.
WE DON'T HAVE MUCH TIME.
I'LL INFORM
THE RESCUE HELICOPTER
WE HAVE A HEADING.
Navigator:
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
CAPTAIN,
WE'VE CHANGED COURSE.
Captain: I KNOW.
DON'T BE CONCERNED.
I HAVE ORDERS
TO SET A NEW COURSE.
CAPTAIN.
THANK YOU.
Woman: WHITE BIRD,
THIS IS CHAMELEON.
WE'VE MADE CONTACT.
WE HAVE A LOCKDOWN.
I REPEAT.
Man:
WHITE BIRD TO CHAMELEON,
HEAR YOU LOUD AND CLEAR.
SETTING COURSE FOR PICKUP.
[GASPS]
JEEZ.
WHAT HAPPENED?
WHERE IS EVERYONE?
THEY'RE ALL GONE.
THEY PANICKED.
I TOLD THEM,
I SAID JUST STAY COOL.
I ORDERED THEM TO MAINTAIN
THEIR STATIONS,
BUT THEY WOULDN'T LISTEN.
C-SECTION IS BREACHED.
THEY'RE ALL DEAD, CAPTAIN.
THEY GOT TO BE.
I TOOK A READING
FROM THE COMPUTER.
THE REACTOR APPEARS
TO BE UNSTABLE.
HANGIN' ON
BY A THREAD, CAPTAIN.
ONE MORE HIT,
I'M TELLING YOU,
ONE MORE AND...
FREE FALL.
WHAT'S THE STATUS
ON THE ENGINE?
SALVANTO, HE'S--HE'S
STILL WORKING ON IT.
CHECK THIS OUT.
Lisa: OK.
I WAS ABLE TO LAUNCH
A REMOTE CAMERA.
BEEN CRUISING AROUND
OUTSIDE THE SUB.
THERE'S AT LEAST 5,
6 SHIPS DOWN HERE.
I MEAN, DIFFERENT COUNTRIES,
DIFFERENT TIME PERIODS.
IT'S LIKE--IT'S LIKE
IT'S SOME KIND OF
INTERNATIONAL GRAVEYARD.
DEVIL'S EYE.
WAIT A SECOND.
GO--GO BACK.
TAKE IT BACK,
TAKE IT BACK.
OH, MY GOD.
THE
LENINGRAD.
Lisa: YOU KNOW IT?
YEAH. IT'S INFAMOUS.
I ACTUALLY THOUGHT
IT WAS A MYTH.
DURING THE CUBAN
MISSILE CRISIS,
AN AMERICAN SUBMARINE
CLAIMED TO HAVE
TORPEDOED
A RUSSIAN SUB
CALLED THE
LENINGRAD.
EXCEPT NO WRECK
WAS EVER FOUND,
AND THE RUSSIANS
COMPLETELY DENIED
ITS EXISTENCE.
Brickman: I ALSO
FOUND THESE CLOSE BY.
THEY MUST HAVE SPILLED OUT
WHEN THE SUB BROKE UP.
Lisa: WHAT'S WITH
THE SKULL AND CROSSBONES?
THAT'S WHAT THEY WERE
SHIPPING TO CASTRO.
CAN, UH...CAN WE GET
A WATER SAMPLE
FROM INSIDE THERE?
YOU NAME IT,
I'LL TAKE IT.
ENGINE ROOM.
THIS IS THE CAPTAIN.
OVER.
SALVANTO!
CAN YOU HEAR ME?
WELL,
I'LL TELL YOU WHAT.
WE ALL BETTER
DO SOMETHING QUICK,
OR THIS THING IS
GONNA TAKE US DOWN.
YEAH, THE QUESTION IS,
WHICH ONE?
Shaw: OK. I'M GONNA
CHECK THE ENGINES.
TURNER, I NEED YOU
TO WATCH MY BACK.
BRICKMAN,
PULL THE WATER SAMPLES.
DR. FINCH, DO AN ANALYSIS.
SEE IF YOU CAN FIND OUT
EXACTLY WHAT WE'RE DEALING
WITH HERE.
Shaw: SALVANTO,
WHERE ARE YOU?
Shaw: IT'S SALVANTO.
I'M GONNA NEED SOME TIME
TO START HER UP.
OK. ALL RIGHT, IF I'M
NOT BACK IN 5 MINUTES,
YOU LOCK THIS DOOR,
YOU GET THE HELL
OUT OF HERE.
I HOPE THEY'RE OK.
OH, GOD. MMM.
HOW YOU DOING, BRICKMAN?
HUH? YOU OK?
[SCOFFS]
YOU SERIOUS?
LOCKED IN A ROOM
WITH YOU?
WHAT MORE
CAN A MAN ASK FOR?
UH...TO LIVE?
Roy: OH, MY GOD.
NO!
COME ON, CASPER!
COME ON!
WHAT DO YOU GOT?
COME ON, ROY, IS THAT
THE BEST YOU CAN DO?
LET'S GO.
THAT'S THE SPIRIT!
FIGHT, ROY! FIGHT!
THAT'S IT, ROY.
WE'RE ALL SQUARE.
LAST TIME
I LET YOU LIVE,
BUT NOT NOW.
HA HA HA HA!
[LAUGHING]
DON'T MOVE.
THAT'S GOOD.
THAT'S VERY GOOD, ROY.
YOU KNOW, THERE'S
A REALLY GOOD CHANCE
THAT WE'RE NOT GETTIN'
OUT OF HERE ALIVE,
SO WHY DON'T YOU
GIVE ME ONE REASON
WHY I DON'T KILL YOU
RIGHT NOW?
UH...
Shaw: BECAUSE...
YOU GOT A JOB TO DO.
THE ENGINES ARE DEAD.
BRICKMAN WAS RIGHT.
THE REACTOR'S UNSTABLE.
WE GOT 25 MINUTES BEFORE
THE
ROOSEVELT
EXPLODES.
HEY. COME ON.
LET'S GET HIM OUT OF HERE.
Lisa: WELCOME HOME, GUYS.
ROUGH DAY AT THE OFFICE?
Shaw: OH, YOU KNOW,
COPIER JAM,
KILLER SEA MONSTERS,
THE USUAL.
HA. I WISH.
THIS THING IS A THIRD
OR FOURTH CYCLE MUTATION
OF WHAT WAS ONCE
PROBABLY AN OCTOPUS.
LISTEN, I, UH, BROKE DOWN
THE WATER SAMPLE
FROM INSIDE
THE RUSSIAN SUB.
IT CONTAINS
A CRUDE PATHOGEN FORM
CALLED
TRICOTHECENE MYCOTOXIN.
OK? FANCY NAME
FOR THE ANTHRAX VIRUS.
BIOLOGICAL WARFARE?
UH-HUH. THIS STUFF
IS A SYNTHETIC HYBRID.
VERY POWERFUL.
Roy: THAT EXPLAINS
THE ENTIRE COVER-UP.
IF KENNEDY HAD KNOWN,
HE WOULD HAVE LAUNCHED.
I MEAN, THE BACTERIA IN IT
MUST HAVE AFFECTED
THIS THING'S ANCESTORS,
AND THE MUTATION
HAS COMPOUNDED
OVER EACH GENERATION.
WELL, EXPLAINING ITS
INCREDIBLE GOOD LOOKS
AND, UH, GOOD NATURE OF
OUR LITTLE FRIEND, YEAH.
HA HA HA!
AND AS FAR AS I CAN TELL,
THIS THING ALSO SUFFERS FROM
AN EXTREME IRON DEFICIENCY.
HENCE THE OVERAGGRESSIVE
BEHAVIOR.
UH-HUH.
NOW,
IT'S NOT JUST A MUTANT,
BUT IT'S ANEMIC?
YEAH. CONSIDERING ITS SIZE,
ARE YOU KIDDING?
THIS THING
HAS A CRAVING FOR MEAT
THAT WOULD SCARE A COW
OUT OF ITS SKIN.
WHITE MEAT
OR DARK MEAT?
OK. IF THIS CREATURE
NEEDS MEAT,
THEN THAT MEANS
THERE'S A WAY
WE CAN BAIT IT, RIGHT?
UH, SO, WHAT?
YOU SUGGESTING
WE DRAW STRAWS?
NO. NOT QUITE.
WHAT I'M SAYING IS
THAT THERE MAY BE
ENOUGH TIME FOR US
TO BUY OURSELVES SOME TIME
AND GET THE HELL OUT OF HERE
WITH THAT SUBMERSIBLE.
YEAH, I GOT A GREAT IDEA.
WHY DON'T WE GET AHOLD
OF SOME T-BONES, AND
WE CAST OUT SOME LINES?
NO, NO, NO,
WAIT A MINUTE,
WAIT A MINUTE.
ROY IS ONTO SOMETHING
HERE, OK?
PROTO-LYTE.
Shaw: WHAT THE HELL
IS THAT?
IT'S A HIGH POTENCY MIX
OF AMINO ACIDS
AND MINERALS,
SPECIFICALLY IRON.
I USE IT TO FEED
DOLPHINS AND WHALES.
MM-MMM. FLIPPER FOOD.
SEE, NOW,
YOU'RE LOSING ME.
OK, LISTEN,
IT IS THE PROTEIN
THAT THIS THING
IS AFTER, NOT US, OK?
I MEAN, IT COULD SUCK
ON A BOTTLE OF THIS
FOR HOURS.
Roy: OK, THAT'S IT, THEN.
WE PUT A LITTLE BIT OF THIS
IN ONE OF THE SHIP'S
COMPARTMENTS,
WE LEAD THE CREATURE TO IT,
AND WE LET IT FEED.
BINGO.
WELL, LISTEN, I HATE
TO BRING THIS UP,
BUT WE HAVE, WHAT,
18 MINUTES
BEFORE THIS SUB TURNS
INTO A MICROWAVE.
18 MINUTES?
YEAH.
Lisa:
THAT'S NOT A PROBLEM
ON MY PART.
YEAH, WELL,
IT'S A PROBLEM ON MY PART.
WHY ARE WE
SITTING HERE TALKING?
LET'S DO SOMETHING.
WELL, COME ON, CAPTAIN.
YOU'VE BEEN PRESENTED
WITH AN OPPORTUNITY.
YOU WANT TO GO HIDE
IN A CLOSET,
OR YOU WANNA
GET SOMETHING DONE?
PLEASE WARN
SPECIAL AGENT TURNER
THAT HE'S ABOUT
TO PUT HIMSELF
IN VERY SERIOUS
PHYSICAL DANGER.
AW, DID I HURT
YOUR FEELINGS?
YOU WANT DR. FEELGOOD HERE
TO MAKE YOU FEEL--
TURNER, YOU--
YEAH?!
HEY, LISTEN,
BREAK IT UP, ALL RIGHT?
THE TESTOSTERONE LEVEL--
JESUS, I'M DROWNING IN IT.
MOVE IT, CASPER.
DON'T EVEN THINK
ABOUT IT.
Brickman:
WHAT'VE WE GOT?
6 MINUTES.
OK, EVERYONE,
JUST SHAKE IT UP,
POUR IT EVERYWHERE.
YEAH, YOU WANT IT?
YOU GOT IT.
COME ON, BABY!
DINNER TIME!
[SQUEAK]
Lisa: YOU HEAR IT?
EXTERNAL MIKES
ARE STILL ON.
Roy: SOUNDS LIKE
SOMEBODY'S HUNGRY.
SHE SMELLS IT.
JUST A LITTLE LONGER.
Brickman:
QUICK! COME ON!
IT'S COMING.
I HOPE THIS WORKS.
THIS HAS GOTTA WORK.
IT'S GOTTA WORK.
PAYBACK'S A MOTHER.
Shaw: ALL RIGHT,
LISTEN UP!
THERE MAY BE
AIR POCKETS
DOWN THERE,
BUT WE HAVE TO BELIEVE
THAT IT'S FLOODED.
THE SUBMERSIBLE'S
OUR ONLY WAY OUT.
WHAT IF THIS THING'S
ALREADY DOWN THERE?
Shaw: THAT'S WHAT
I'M ABOUT TO FIND OUT.
HA.
OK, IF I'M NOT BACK
IN 30 SECONDS,
YOU JUST HAVE TO ASSUME
THAT IT'S ALL CLEAR
AND COME ON THROUGH.
EVERYBODY UNDERSTAND?
Brickman:
30 SECONDS.
Lisa: OK.
SEE YOU
ON THE OTHER SIDE.
Roy, Lisa: YOU GOT
TO SAY IT THAT WAY?
Roy: OK, OK,
LET'S GET READY.
HEY, HEY, HEY,
I--I CAN'T SWIM
WITH THESE ON.
OH, I CAN'T,
I CAN'T, I CAN'T.
WHAT THE HELL HAPPENED
TO YOU, CASPER, HUH?
EVER SINCE I KICKED YOUR ASS,
YOU'VE BECOME SUCH A WIMP.
20, 21,
22, 23...
Brickman: COME ON,
WE GOTTA GET OUT
OF HERE.
25, 26, 27, 28...
LET'S GO.
THAT'S IT.
OK, LET'S GO.
Lisa: THINK HE'S
GONNA MAKE IT? 29...
IT'S TIME TO GO.
HE MUST HAVE MADE IT.
30.
DOWN WITH ME?
AAH!
COME ON!
OK. OH,
FOR CHRIST'S SAKE.
UHH!
WHOA.
WHOA,
HO HO HO HO.
BRICKMAN, ONE WORD--
ONE LITTLE WORD...OK?
AAH!
[COUGHING]
BRICKMAN?
COME ON!
COME ON, BABY.
COME TO PAPA.
Lisa: TURNER,
WHERE ARE YOU? AAH!
AAH!
[LISA SCREAMS]
Roy: COME ON,
CASPER, SWIM. SWIM!
WE GO TO GET OUT OF HERE!
LET'S GO!
Casper: I CAN'T
MAKE IT! UHH!
OH, MY GOD!
WE'RE GOING TO DIE!
COME ON, YOU GUYS!
SWIM!
AAH!
LISA!
Roy:
OH, GOD! OH, GOD!
AAH!
Roy:
HOLD ON, I'M COMING!
DON'T GO! DON'T!
Brickman: GET OUTTA HERE!
GO! GO!
BRICKMAN, HOLD ON!
BRICKMAN!
[SCREAMING]
LISA,
GET OUT OF THERE!
OH, MY GOD!
Shaw: COME ON. OK.
OH, GOD.
THAT'S A NICE OUTFIT,
BUT DO YOU THINK
WE HAVE TIME?
SHAW, NOT NOW.
Casper: UHH!
BE CAREFUL, DAMN YOU!
COME ON, CASPER.
COME ON, GET UP!
MOVE IT!
WHERE'S BRICKMAN?
HE DIDN'T MAKE IT.
OH, GOD.
ALL RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT,
WE GOTTA GET MOVIN'.
COME ON.
THE REACTOR'S GONNA BLOW.
OK.
EVERYBODY,
GET YOUR GOOD-BYES IN.
COME ON,
LET'S GET OUT OF HERE.
WE GOT 3 MINUTES.
LET'S START HER UP.
AAH, OK.
HEY, TURNER, YOU BRING
ANY LEMONS?
WHY?
'CAUSE I THINK WE'RE ABOUT
TO NUKE US UP SOME CALAMARI.
COME ON. COME ON!
DON'T FAIL ME NOW.
Roy: IT'S RIGHT
ON TOP OF US!
Shaw: GET HER UP
BEFORE THIS THING
CRUSHES US!
COME ON!
WE GOT 20 SECONDS!
Lisa: COME ON!
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
IT WON'T DISENGAGE.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
IT WON'T DISENGAGE?
HEY, LOOK, WE CAN'T
GO OUTSIDE AND PUSH IT.
Lisa: ONE MORE HIT,
AND WE'RE LUNCH.
DO SOMETHING!
COME ON, BABY,
YOU CAN DO IT!
OK, HERE WE GO.
HOLD ON TO YOUR BOXERS,
BOYS.
ONE LAST TIME
FOR MAMA, BABY.
COME ON. READY...
TO LAUNCH!
GO!
COME ON.
COME ON,
BABY, COME ON.
OH, YES!
OH, YEAH.
AAH!
WHOA!
Lisa: HANG ON, EVERYONE!
OHH. GENTLEMEN,
I THINK WE DID IT.
DOCTOR,
I COULD KISS YA.
IN YOUR DREAMS, SHAW.
YOU'RE THE ONE
THAT'S WEARING
THE WET T-SHIRT.
HEY,
COULD ONE OF YOU GUYS
STOP QUARRELIN'
AND TELL ME
WHAT THE HELL THAT IS?
[LAUGHING]
Lisa: TELL ME I'M DREAMIN'.
WELL, THAT,
SPECIAL AGENT TURNER,
LOOKS TO BE
OUR RIDE HOME.
THANK YOU.
REALLY?
OK, TAKE HER UP.
WITH PLEASURE.
LET'S GET THE HELL
OUT OF HERE.
Man: HEY.
HELLO.
Roy:
HEY! DOWN HERE!
[DANCE MUSIC PLAYING]
THIS WAY.
CAPTAIN.
CAPTAIN?
JACK SHAW, CAPTAIN,
S.S.N. ROOSEVELT.
MOVE IT, CASPER.
Shaw: BOY, ARE WE GLAD
TO SEE YOU.
WELCOME ABOARD.
MOVE!
Man: STAY
WHERE YOU ARE.
DON'T MAKE A SOUND.
DON'T MOVE.
WHOO!
HA HA HA HA!
OH, IT'S GOOD
TO HAVE YOU HERE, KIDS.
I WASN'T SURE
YOU'D MAKE IT.
OH, YOU GOT TO BE
KIDDING ME.
ROY...
IT SEEMS THAT MY SHIP
HAS FINALLY COME IN.
IT'S JUST A LITTLE
BIGGER THAN I EXPECTED.
LET'S ESCORT OUR GUESTS
DOWN TO THE ENGINE ROOM.
Roy:
I'M GOING NOWHERE.
Lisa:
LEAVE HIM ALONE.
Roy:
OHH!
LEAVE HER.
THANK YOU.
Pilot: WHITE BIRD
TO CHAMELEON.
ESTIMATED PICKUP
IN 12 MINUTES.
Casper: LIFE'S
BUT A WALKING SHADOW--
A POOR PLAYER
WHO FRETS AND STRUTS
HIS HOUR UPON THE STAGE
AND THEN IS HEARD
NO MORE.
IT IS A TALE
TOLD BY AN IDIOT--
FULL OF SOUND AND FURY,
SIGNIFYING NOTHING.
CAPTAIN...
THERE'S SOMETHING
ON THE RADAR.
[RADAR BEEPING]
Woman: WHAT IS IT?
WHAT IS IT?
Captain: WHATEVER
IT IS, IT'S BIG,
AND IT'S MOVING
IN OUR DIRECTION.
OH, MY GOD.
IT'S COMING CLOSER.
Casper:
AH, FELIX,
JUST IN TIME.
Lisa: WHAT ARE YOU
LOOKING AT, SHORTY?
WHOA.
ICK.
ROOM SERVICE.
LOVELY.
THAT'S ON ME, GUYS.
Man: THE HELICOPTER'S
DUE IN A FEW MINUTES.
SET THE TIMER
AT 14 MINUTES.
MUSTN'T MISS
THE FIREWORKS.
Man: CAPTAIN,
IT'S COMING CLOSER.
IT'S HEADING
STRAIGHT FOR US.
Woman:
WHAT IS IT?
Man:
IT'S GOING TO HIT.
OH, MY GOD!
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
[OCTOPUS ROARS]
DON'T MOVE!
KEEP YOUR HANDS UP!
STAY DOWN!
[FIRES MACHINE GUN]
WATCH OUT!
NO!
[OCTOPUS ROARS]
LET ME GUESS.
BIG...
SLIMY...
ABOUT 8 ARMS.
DON'T YOU JUST LOVE HIM?
MMM.
AAH!
OUT OF THE WAY!
MOVE!
[ROARING]
[SCREAMING]
AAH! AAH!
AAH!
OSCAR...
KILL THEM.
I'LL BE ON THE DECK.
MY PLEASURE.
FELIX.
TIME TO DIE.
YOU FIRST.
OSCAR?
HUH?
OHH!
[FIRES]
UNH!
OH, NO.
Roy:
OH, THAT'S NOT GOOD.
THANK YOU.
ANYTIME.
UNH!
AAH!
I THINK IT'S BROKEN.
TAKE IT EASY.
THIS SHOULD HELP.
YOU'RE SO GOOD TO ME.
Roy:
I KNOW.
HEY, GUYS.
WE GOT TO GET
OUT OF HERE.
Shaw:
WHAT ABOUT CASPER?
WHAT ABOUT THE BOMB?
WE GOT ABOUT 6 MINUTES.
YOU GO GET CASPER.
I'LL DISMANTLE THE BOMB.
GREAT.
DISARM THE BOMB?
I'M WITH HIM.
YEAH, I THOUGHT SO.
[BEEPING]
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
Casper:
GET OUT OF THE WAY!
OUT OF THE WAY!
COME ON!
CASPER!
Roy:
GET DOWN!
NOW!
ROY...
PARTING
IS SUCH SWEET SORROW.
I MEAN IT!
LOOK, IT'S OVER!
THIS TIME,
I'LL SHOOT!
ROY!
LOOK OUT!
AAH!
ROOM SERVICE.
[LAUGHS]
DON'T MAKE ME DO THIS!
NO. NOT AGAIN, ROY.
THIS IS DISAPPOINTING.
WHAT A BORING WAY
TO END THIS
AFTER ALL
WE'VE BEEN THROUGH--
YOU WITH A GUN IN YOUR HAND
WHICH YOU CAN'T FIRE
AND ME RIDING OFF
INTO THE SUNSET.
Lisa:
COME ON, TURNER.
BON VOYAGE, ROY!
OH, COME ON.
SHOOT HIM.
Roy: NOT IN COLD BLOOD.
I CAN'T.
I WIN, ROY!
I WIN!
HA HA HA!
[ROARING]
OH, GOD.
HA HA!
[GASPS]
NOT IN
THIS LIFETIME,
OLD CHAP!
[MOANING]
[OCTOPUS ROARING]
THE BOMB!
COME ON, COME ON,
COME ON!
Roy:
HEY, HOW'D YOU DO?
HOW'D
YOU
DO?
WELL, AS THE EXPRESSION
GOES, HE'S DEAD.
YOU TOOK HIM OUT?
I DIDN'T HAVE TO.
SEEMS EVEN OUR FRIEND
KNOWS A BAD GUY
WHEN HE SEES ONE.
LOOK, I COULDN'T
SHUT IT OFF,
BUT MAYBE WE CAN DUMP IT
OVER THE SIDE.
IT'LL SAVE THE SHIP,
AT LEAST.
WELL, IF THERE'S
ANYTHING LEFT TO SAVE.
I MEAN, THE CREATURE'S
RIPPED IT HALF APART,
AND IT'S COMING BACK
FOR MORE.
ALL RIGHT, THEN,
WHY DON'T WE JUST, UH,
SHOVE IT DOWN
THE DAMN THING'S
THROAT?
SHAW, THIS IS SERIOUS.
ACTUALLY, HE'S GOT A POINT.
WHAT HAVE WE GOT TO LOSE?
I MEAN, IF WE GET
ONE MORE CHANCE
TO BLOW THIS THING UP...
THE SUBMERSIBLE.
LOOK, JUST GET ME TO IT.
I'LL HANDLE IT
FROM THERE.
NO WAY, SHAW.
TURNER!
LOOK, DON'T YOU
TAKE THIS AWAY FROM ME.
[BOMB TICKING]
HUH?
ALL RIGHT.
YOU GOT 3 MINUTES,
50 SECONDS.
HERE.
MY BRONZE STAR--
FOR LUCK...
SPECIAL AGENT TURNER.
YOU KNOW,
I'VE HEARD ABOUT THE KIND
OF LUCK YOU HAVE, SHAW,
BUT, UM...
THANKS.
I KNOW THAT THIS...
THIS MEANS A LOT TO YOU,
AND, UH--
GUYS, COME ON.
YOU'RE GETTING ME
ALL TEARY-EYED HERE.
GO ON. GET THE HELL
OUT OF HERE.
OK. GO ON. GO.
I'LL SEE YOU
ON THE OTHER SIDE.
Both:
WHY'D HE SAY THAT?
OHH.
[OCTOPUS ROARS]
HOW MUCH TIME
DOES HE HAVE?
DON'T ASK.
WHERE THE HELL IS HE?
HE'S GONE FISHING.
WHERE THE HELL
DO YOU THINK HE IS?
OH, CHRIST, I HOPE
HE MAKES IT BACK
IN ONE PIECE.
YEAH, ME, TOO.
HE'S GOT MY STAR.
WHAT? YOU KNOW,
YOU ARE SO...
UHH!
AAH!
Roy: OK.
PLENTY OF TIME.
DON'T PANIC.
JUST...
I DON'T SEE HIM ANYWHERE.
THERE!
WHAT'S THAT?
NOTHING.
COME ON, ROY, COME ON!
Roy: 24 SECONDS.
NO PROBLEM.
ALL RIGHT.
OK. IT'S JUST LIKE
DRIVING A CAR--
UNDERWATER.
OK. OK.
I'LL TELL YOU--
IF HE PULLS THIS OFF,
HE CAN KEEP
THE DAMN STAR.
RIGHT.
BUT, DARLING,
I'M CERTAINLY NOT
GIVING UP ON YOU YET.
OH, MY GOD.
[ROARS]
COME ON.
LET'S GO, BROTHER.
COME ON!
YOU WANT TO EAT THIS?
LET'S GO!
LET'S GO! COME ON!
[OCTOPUS ROARING]
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
Lisa:
WHERE IS HE?
I DON'T SEE HIM!
OH, GOD.
DO YOU SEE HIM?
DO YOU SEE HIM
ANYWHERE?
ROY!
HEY, DID YOU SEE THAT?
HEY!
HEY, BUDDY!
WE DID IT!
Roy:
WHOO!
♪ I'M BLURRED
♪ TOTALLY OUT OF FOCUS
♪ HOW WE MEANT TO BE
JUST BE CONFUSED.
CAPTIONED BY THE NATIONAL
CAPTIONING INSTITUTE
--www.ncicap.org--
♪ YOUR MEAN
♪ SOUL MEANS
♪ I'VE LIVED
THIS GOLDEN MORN ♪
♪ COULDN'T SEE
♪ WHO I WAS
PAST YOUR SCORN ♪
♪ FLOWERS ARE PRETTY
♪ THEY JUST
COVER UP NICE ♪
♪ THEIR BEAUTY
♪ IS A DAGGER
♪ THAT CUTS LIKE A KNIFE
♪ I'M BLURRED
♪ TOTALLY OUT OF FOCUS
♪ THIS PICTURE IS NOT ME
♪ I'M BLURRED
♪ TIMING, MEANING,
EVERYTHING ♪
♪ I'M BLURRED
♪ HOW WE MEANT TO BE
JUST BE CONFUSED.
THIS PICTURE IS NOT ME.
♪ I'VE LEARNED
♪ HOW TO HIDE
♪ BEHIND
A WELL-REHEARSED LIE ♪
♪ PRETENDING
♪ I'M SOMEONE ELSE
♪ THERE'S A STRANGER
INSIDE ♪
♪ FLOWERS ARE PRETTY
FLOWERS ARE PRETTY.
♪ BUT THEY CANNOT
DISGUISE ♪
♪ THE GRAY SKY
♪ AND EMPTY HEART
♪ THAT I SEE
THROUGH THESE EYES ♪
♪ I'M BLURRED
♪ TOTALLY OUT OF FOCUS
♪ THIS PICTURE IS NOT ME
♪ I'M BLURRED
♪ TIMING, MEANING,
EVERYTHING ♪
♪ I'M BLURRED
♪ HOW WE MEANT TO BE
JUST BE CONFUSED.
TOUCH...
A TRUE GRAY.
[SPEAKING FRENCH]
♪ FLOWERS ARE PRETTY
FLOWERS ARE PRETTY.
♪ BUT THEY CANNOT
DISGUISE ♪
A GRAY SKY.
♪ A GRAY SKY
♪ AN EMPTY HEART
THAT I SEE THROUGH
THESE EYES.
♪ THAT I SEE
THROUGH THESE EYES ♪
♪ I'M BLURRED
♪ TOTALLY--T-TOTALLY
OUT OF FOCUS ♪
♪ I'M BLURRED
♪ THIS--THIS PICTURE
IS NOT ME ♪
♪ I'M BLURRED
♪ T-T-TIMING, MEANING,
EVERYTHING ♪
♪ I'M BLURRED
♪ HOW WE MEANT TO BE