I asked you for your guidance.
I asked you for your love
and comfort, I am here as your child
asking you for mercey.
Shine on my path.
Shine on this day.
I continued to humble myself and
and asked you to shine on those times
that I’ve been toxic.
Shine on those times
I am a new man.
In Jesus name.
Amen.
[door opens]
[door closing]
Hello?
You're a murderer
Jeffrey
who takes lives.
You don't create them.
How did I get here?
I don't remember walking in here.
You go and fuck my best friend
Billy and start your whole new life.
And I have nothing.
Still blaming everyone else
for your own shit.
I get what I like.
And I like your wife.
Going to do something about it, Jeffrey?
I am the one who is responsible
for your wife's adultery.
[laughing]
I'm married to a man
that makes me happier than you ever could.
You're going to do something
about a little bird?
A kiss that I love dearly.
I don't want to
someone like you around my kids.
I ended all those lives to keep me.
To be true to who I am.
You took everything from me.
[laying down]
Your mind is glitching.
[apple bite]
[chewing]
Hey, Ricardo.
Didn't you say you were going to be here
at three?
I'm here.
No, I'm not paying extra
because your system
no show.
What? No, that's kinda disrescpectful.
Okay.
All right.
Well, I'll see you at three.
Okay. Bye.
Jeffrey?
What are you doing here?
How'd you get in?
The door was open.
But you're not supposed to be here.
Jeffrey.
You're not supposed to be here.
I came to see you.
Okay.
I'll call the cops to get you out of here.
Come on.
Are you okay?
You kinda look like
you haven't eaten for a while.
I haven’t.
Okay.
Stay here for.
I'll be right back.
[walking away]
[door opening]
[door closing]
Here you go.
It’s your favorite popcorn.
[eating sound]
Why are you really here?
I just came to see how things were.
Are things the way you expected?
Not exactly how
I remember it, but.
It’s okay.
Did you expect to see me here?
[eating sound]
What?
How did you expect to see me here
when I don't live here?
Because this is our house.
No, Jeffrey, this was our house.
It’s not anymore.
Because you left and you took everything.
So I had to start over.
I took everything?
Yeah.
You're the one who decided to start
your new life with my best friend Billy.
What was I suppose to do there?
Sit here and let my wife get her back
blown up by another man?
Okay.
You don't have to be so vulgar.
You took everything from me.
No.
I did not do that.
This state did that.
No, you took my money, my career,
my house, my money, my car.
I live on the streets now.
Okay.
Guess we weren’t a good match then.
You were always too controlling, Jeffrey.
I felt like I couldn't breathe around you.
I'm sorry.
It's hard to hear.
You know what?
It's the truth.
And I think that
if you if you learn from this,
if you move on,
the next person
that you'll end up with will
definitely benefit from a changed you.
Do you think somebody would want me?
I don’t know.
Look at me, Penelope.
I'm homeless.
I haven’t taken a shower in weeks.
I'm ugly. I'm dirty.
No, you're not ugly and dirty.
You could definitely
clean up a little bit, but
hey, I married a handsome man,
and now he's
he’s still you.
Okay.
What about you?
Are you happy?
Yeah, I am.
I am happy with Billy.
And my two kids and a dog.
You don't even like dogs.
How do you know?
All right.
Well, it was good seeing you, Jeffrey.
Uh, should I walk you out?
Penelope?
Mm?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for everything.
Why are you just now saying I’m sorry?
Because I'm
I'm alone and I don't have anything.
And I never thought
It would feel like this.
You know, and I wish.
I wish to God I could fix it.
Me too.
You need to see a therapist or something.
Because this is pathetic.
How am I supposed to get help
when I have nothing to get to help with?
Find a solution, Jeffrey.
There's always a solution.
That's easy for you to say
when you're at the top of a hill.
Okay.
It's not always easy.
Thank you very much.
You just have to find.
Think.
Think of something.
Come.
What are you thinking?
I'm wondering why you don't
ever think about me.
Do you ever think about me?
I mean I do, sometimes.
Like when I have to sing
one of the songs we
wrote together.
If I see something
that remind me of you.
Why?
Do you think about me?
It's hard to think about anything
with all this
goddamn gardening going on outside.
[laughing]
Okay.
But yeah.
I think about you all the time.
I think about us.
I think about
the past.
I think about us before I got so evil.
Before got so dark.
And whose fault is it getting so dark?
Why do you think I'm living ike this?
I don't know.
You think I like living like this?
I'm living like this because of you.
Because of the divorce.
You let it ruin me.
Okay, this is what we're doing?
Yea, this is exactly
what we're doing.
You go and fuck my best friend
Billy and start your whole new life.
And you leave me with nothing.
You forgot the man that you loved,
that you said you loved.
Now I'm not even a shell of the man
I used to be.
Okay.
Still haven't changed much. I see.
Still blaming everyone else
for your own shit.
Yeah.
I haven't changed much,
but I guess you did.
You changed a lot, Penelope.
Into this cold hearted,
rotten bitch.
My heart is as cold as
the ocean flor.
Can you not look at me like that?
You know it's true.
You know.
I never asked you something
I always wanted to ask you.
So.
Now seems like a good time.
Okay?
Why are you the way you are?
What?
Like
cold.
Hearthless.
Like
a deserted radiation
nuclear facility in the coldest
parts of Russia in the winter. Why?
What, something happened
to you as a kid?
You saw something growing up to
traumatize you, what happened?
Do you really want to know?
Yeah.
Kind of.
It's kind of hard for the
soul to listen to.
I want, I really want to know.
Okay.
Well.
When I was a child.
I was touched
by
M ultiple
men in my family.
My parents both knew.
And I thought that
they would just let it go
on forever.
Until one day they died,
both of them
in a car crash.
So, it was just my sister
and I left and.
We were very close.
We were best friends.
Well, we were both,
we were both touched by
these males.
And then one day,
my sister died of cancer.
So it's just me.
It's just me alone.
And I think after that
probably just shut off, I guess.
I mean the touching, I don't,
I don't care anymore.
I didn't feel anything.
And I didn't feel happy.
Basically, I didn't feel any emotion.
But of course you remember.
Cause you never really make me happy
and satisfied me.
Do you remember when we first met?
Really?
Do you remember?
Of course.
I was burying a man alive.
And you pretended to think it was fake.
And instead of leaving,
you stood there and you took pictures.
You are sick and twisted, Penelope.
No. You get off on the pain of others.
No, I don't get all on it.
I just fascinated is all.
I’m seriously.
I'm fascinated when a man
like you can act
like a zoo animal.
You're a monster.
Oh. And what does that make you?
Because I was young and stupid,
but I'm more mature now.
Are you? Yes.
I think you're still the same rotten
Penelope
that you were as a little girl.
I was rotten
because I wanted
to see a man bury another
man alive? Yes.
See, some bad habits die hard.
And some bad habits don't
die until we die
with them.
[laughing]
You sound like a crazy homeless person
right now.
Why are you here?
Because I have to
renovate the property.
I'm going to sell it.
Why?
Because I need the money.
Bullshit.
You took all my money.
You don't need any more money.
Why are you really here?
I came here for closure.
Okay?
You came here for closure?
You mean to hide your secrets?
Is that so bad? Yes.
That just means
you can't handle the truth.
And what is the truth?
The truth is,
we're both fucked up
people were damaged past.
We are both fucked up people?
Yeah.
Okay.
Interesting timing in saying that.
I want to know what happened to you.
What made you into this,
Jeffrey, that you are?
That kills other people.
Mm?
I don't know.
No, you do know.
You're just been denying
it for so long.
Tell me Jefrey.
Tell me, what led you to be this man?
Uh. When I was a little kid,
like a teenager.
I went to this, um, to this camp
for three summers,
and they made me do, uh,
they made me do some bad stuff.
What bad stuff?
Like killing type stuff.
No, more specific.
Am
I went to this camp and
they had these people in boxes.
I couldn't really speak English
or whatever language they were speaking.
Uh.
The camp counselors gave us
machetes
and bone saws
and told us to cut them up.
I used to use to start with their heads
because I felt that that would be
more humane.
So it gets it gets worse.
And they would.
They would make us touch
the dead bodies
and take pictures with them.
And then they said that
if we said anything,
they would kill our parents,
just like those people in the boxes.
Did you ever tell anyone?
I'm telling you now.
Besides,
no one needs to know
what's saved up in here.
You know, that’s why I think.
You know, that's why
I think we belong together,
because we grew up the same.
We have similar upbringings.
Okay, that's where you
were very wrong.
What do you mean?
We're not similar.
You don't think so?
Jeff?
I'm married to a man.
That makes me happier
than you ever could.
I have kids that I love dearly.
I don't want someone
like you around my kids.
So it's the kids, is it? Yes.
You're just hiding behind them.
No, no, you just.
You're just using them to hide
behind them.
And sooner or later,
you'll come out and be rotten
Penelope, again.
Have you ever killed anyone?
What? No.
You know,
I guess we all don't have it in us
Have you ever killed anyone?
How could you just ask me that
when I just told you about how I.
No, no, I meant
while we were married.
Yeah.
How many?
Eight or nine.
I don't.
I don't know.
I lost count.
Why didn't you tell me?
Because I was afraid.
You get upset, you
look at me different.
So you ended all those
lives to keep me?
No.
I ended all those lives to keep me.
To be true to who I am.
[laughing]
Do you know how absurd
that sounds?
Well, yeah.
Yeah, it's absurd
because we are awful human beings.
Unbelievable.
Because I'm a murderer as fuck.
I think I knew, though.
Deep down.
You leaving late.
Coming home late.
Not showering and so
you could see me.
I can't help the way that I am.
How do you feel right now?
Uh, the popcorn was good.
Other than that, um.
I don't know.
[door knocking]
What time is it?
Oh, shoot.
It's already three.
I'll go to the back.
No, no, no, no.
Stay here.
Are you sure?
Yea.
Stay here.
Okay.
Oh. Hi.
Hi. Hi.
I'm so sorry I got held up earlier.
No, no. That’s fine. That’s fine.
I have a lot of work to do today.
Um. Can you just come back tomorrow?
I need to be paid today.
Can you just wait?
I am kinda busy at the moment.
No.
I need the money now to
pay my workers.
Okay.
Okay. I'll get my check.
Just hold on for a sec.
Yeah.
Ricardo.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Thank you. See you tomorrow.
Okay.
Have a great day.
[door closing]
[door lock]
Why do you look so bothered?
Because he almost saw me.
And?
Were going to do something to him?
Yeah.
With this.
You were going to hit Ricardo
with a pole?
I was going to bash his
fuckin brains in.
Why?
Because
Because of what?
I wanted to make sure
he doesn't see them all.
I don't want his kids to
see him anymore.
I want to make him dead.
I wanted to end him.
Hmm.
[the sound of waves]
What's wrong with me?
It's like I'm stuck in this darkness.
You're not stuck in the darkness.
You are the darkness.
No, I'm not.
Yes, you are.
You killed me.
You killed all those people.
You're a monster.
I'm not a monster.
I'm just.
Lost.
You're lost because you chose to be.
You could have been happy, Jeffrey.
But no.
You chose this life.
Darkness.
Solitude.
Why is that pole over there?
You were going to use it
to hit me with it, weren't you?
No, no. I would never hurt you.
But you already did.
You took everything from me.
Wait.
How did I get here?
I don't remember walking in here.
And why are you sitting on the bed
like that?
I don't know.
I’m just so lost and alone.
Like you.
But you're not alone, though.
You're not a real man, Jeffrey.
You have a pole in your bias,
a killing instrument.
That paul probably belongs
in this house.
It was probably a piece of the plumbing.
Mhm.
It's important.
It's a small part of a whole.
A small part of the whole.
Which means of what?
This house?
A family?
Us?
And what have you done?
What could you have possibly done
to deserve this
life you're living?
Dirty.
Alone.
On the streets.
Wait. Are you?
What?
Are you amused?
Yes.
Why are you upset?
I don't know.
I just can't seem to.
We don't exist anymore, Jeffrey.
But you loved me?
[laughing]
I never loved you.
I was too busy loving others.
Well, I was carefully observing you.
Watching others.
And that's why I ruined you, Jeffrey.
Because you.
Taught me how to be a ruiner.
You understand that?
Yeah.
But, um.
Why are you?
Why are you saying all this? Why?
Why are you talking to me this way?
Because I want.
I want.
What's happening?
He's coming for you, Jeffrey.
Who?
You know who.
Your tormentor.
The one that's been following you
your whole life.
The one that's been fucking you.
[laughing]
Shit.
Baby.
Penelope, please put that down.
All I need to do is just stick
the screwdriver down my throat
to make you go away.
What's wrong?
Talk to me.
Let me help you.
Get away from me.
Well, you can talk to me about anything.
I don't want or need your help Jeffrey.
You can’t help yourself.
Go.
Go right now.
Go, please.
Jeffrey, please go.
Alright.
Closer.
[laughing]
Oh my God.
Jeffrey.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
What just happened?
Uh.
Nothing.
I'm here.
I'm okay.
Kind of left me or something else weird?
Honestly,
it was like you were in a trance.
Um.
I don't know.
I’m not myself.
I had a vision about you.
A vision?
Yea.
What happened in the vision?
You were, um...
You're were being mean to me.
And, um...
You were scary.
I was scared of you.
I was trembling.
There is something I need to tell you.
No, no, no, no.
You might want to be
seated for the...
What is it?
I am not who you think I am.
What do you mean?
I am not Penelope.
Or. No, I mean, I am.
But I am not.
I don't understand.
No, of course you're not understanding.
Sit down.
I need to explain it to you, Jeffrey.
Basically.
I was with
many
men.
While we were together.
What do you mean by
you were with?
Well, basically, I had many afferas.
[laughing]
With who?
That doesn't matter.
Happens so often.
I know. I know.
I was wrong.
But.
I was weak.
I just really, really
wanted to feel all these men
inside of me.
[laughing]
Why are you telling me this?
I mean, I just...
I can’t keep living with the secret.
Why are you telling me this now?
Because you're right here.
So why should I have to carry
all this guilt on my own?
Why are you telling me this now?
I don't know.
Cause I just want to fucking
tell you the truth.
I can't take this.
I need to.
It was always so easy.
What was easy?
Well, they all wanted me.
All of them.
They all wanted me.
Hey Jeffrey.
Do you remember all those times
we were trying to have kids?
That’s really trying
to have kids?
But we thought, or you thought.
But the doctors had some, I don't know,
conspiratorial rasputin against us.
Remember you were telling me
that behind closed doors they would say.
Those two are not fit to be parents.
Those two should definitely
not have kids.
I thought you doctor's
was actually funny.
It was quiet
when they should have been talking.
Yea.
Do you want to know why?
Yeah.
Tell me why.
Because it was me, Jeffrey.
It was me.
And the reason,
because I aborted more than, what?
Seven, eight of your children?
[laughing]
Penelope.
How could you kill our children?
I don't know.
But I did. Ha ha.
No.
Yes.
And I would do it all over again.
[laughing]
Where do you think you're going?
You know what I think?
What?
I think a none of this is real.
I think I'm going out of my mind.
Hey.
It's the truth.
I know you don't want to hear it,
but sorry. It's the truth.
How could you do something like that?
I don't know.
Because I'm a mean fucking
cunting bitch.
How could you do something like that
and not even think twice, Penelope?
And how could you kill a man
and not think twice?
Stop it.
Murder is not abortion, okay?
You can't compare the two.
I didn’t.
Yes, you did.
You just said it was the same.
No?
Don't you feel sorry
or bad at all?
Die slowly please.
Good.
Did slowly.
I am.
Good.
You look so pitiful.
Well, you know, then I guess
that was always
the thing that I found
kind of intriguing about you.
You're a murderer, Jeffrey.
Who takes lives.
You don't create them.
Of course.
Now, Billy and I.
We have two kids.
And we're so happy.
But I think I'm even happier
rendering you fatherless forever.
Don't you have anything to say?
I...
No, I don’t...
I don't know what to say.
Good because I don't really want
to hear what you have to say anyway.
Do you remember
the Christmas party at
your workplace?
Yeah?
Where you introduce me to Uriah?
Your big dominant boss.
Can I?
Don’t
t ouch her.
Little bro.
And I could tell immediately
that he was into me.
And you could, too.
That's why you became jealous when it.
And I.
I pretended not to notice
so that you wouldn't get upset.
So that later
on during that party,
I was at the juice bar
and then he came over.
And he took me back to the
storage closet.
He did some amazing things to me.
Things that you could never do.
I was so satisfied
after that Christmas party. Oh.
I didn't tell you, Jeffrey, because.
I didn't want you to lose your job
because you could never stand up to him.
Because you don't
kill the powerful and dominant.
Do you?
You prey on the weak.
Why are you being so?
Why do you want to hear more?
No.
No, I don't.
Because I have plenty more
where that came from.
Jeffrey.
Look at you.
What's left for me now is just.
To move on.
To leave you in the past.
Oh. And I'm
sorry that I got to do that
by destroying you.
I think that I am not sorry at all.
Why do you want to destroy me?
Because you deserve it.
You don't deserve a life.
Penelope.
We could have had children.
Ugh.
The thought of having something
that's half me.
Half you. Never.
I could never do it.
Well, never.
Okay.
We're done here.
Shall we leave the past
in the past?
Good.
I'm going leave, so.
Oh. Remember the first time?
That you introduced me to Billy.
Your best friend Billy,
at the Super Bowl party
or whatever It was.
When I met him, I walked up to him.
And I said.
I want you Billy.
[laughing]
[knocking]
Hello.
Hey.
Is everything okay?
We heard the starkins.
So?
Oh. Sorry about that.
Uh, we.
My wife and I, we live next door.
Oh. Oh. Um.
No. All good here. Just.
My ex-husband had a little bit
too much to drink.
Okay, well, if you need anything,
don't hesitate to call us, okay?
Okay.
Thank you.
Hey. Hey.
Could you come back for a second? Yes.
Are you single?
No, not really.
I have a life.
But could you be?
What? Yeah.
I can be, I guess.
Okay. Right.
Okay.
Do you have a phone on you?
Yeah.
Right here.
You look like the funnest fuck.
You too.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Here you go.
Thanks.
I'll call whenever.
What about tonight?
You know.
Your funnest fuck.
You too.
See you.
See you later.
Is that what you wanted to do?
Did you want to make me mad?
Yes.
You're a killer, Jeffrey.
You're a monster.
Why would you that?
Scare me.
Hey, man.
Hey.
How are you?
I'm good. How you doing?
Good.
Uriah wants to see you, though.
Any idea why?
Oh. I don't ask questions.
I just work here.
Really?
Pretty sure.
Well, good luck.
Hey, Ray.
You wanted to see me?
Hey Jeffrey.
Thanks for coming in.
Have a sit.
Is, um...
everything okay?
No, not really.
I'm afraid
I'm going to have to let you go.
What? Why?
Sorry, man.
Company's downsizing,
and we have to let some people go.
Unfortunately, you are
one of those people.
I could write you a good preference
letter and service pace last you a while.
Oh. Jeffrey.
A woman you brought
to the Christmas party.
She was amazing, I must say.
Wait, what does that mean?
That's what that means.
You're right.
That's my wife you talking about.
I know.
I fucked her in the storage closet.
And I asked her to come over tonight.
She said yea.
So that's that.
Why the fuck would you do
something like that?
You're going to do something
about it ittle bro?
Are you going to do something
about it, Jeffrey?
I get what I like.
And I like your wife.
He fired me.
Hey. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
You know.
I was just scared.
I didn't want you to lose your job
because of me rejecting him.
You're lying to me
and you're cheating on me.
I would never cheat on you.
He told me he fucked you.
He's obviously lying.
He said you were going to his
house tonight.
Just to cook him dinner.
To cook him dinner?
What about my dinner?
I was just scared, you know, I didn't.
I didn't mean to hurt you.
You didn't mean to hurt me? Penelope?
You cheated on me.
It's not true.
Girl.
You better hope
I get my shit together.
Baby.
Don't let that man rile you up.
It’s too late.
I'm already up.
Baby.
Don't let any man ruin
what we've got going on here.
I would never betray you.
I would never cheat on you.
You know that.
There's not a man on the planet
that can make me leave you.
You're my man.
Okay. Come here.
I love you.
Okay?
I’m gonna go.
I am gonna leave the in the past,
and I suggest you do the same, okay?
Actually, I do need you
to get out of here.
You know, I'm going to renovate, so.
Feels like I'm the king or queen.
Actually, this must be
what Cleopatra felt like.
Right before she saw her enemies
heads drop to the floor.
Feels like power.
And you're just a pawn in my game.
Oh, do you hear that fucking
ice cream truck?
What?
Why are you being
this way to me?
Interesting.
How the beast can be
brought to his knees
by a divine feminine.
You know, that was always
your downfall, Jeffrey.
You couldn't handle a
strong woman God.
I am woman God.
Come now.
Wash my feet.
[laughing]
I am the one who exists
within your spouse.
I come from the spirit of Delilah.
I watched Samson
fall at the temple of Daggett.
Yes. I am the one
who is responsible
for your wife's adultery.
I have lived with her before she was born,
and I want you to tremble.
Oh, that's cold.
Oh, come on.
Yea.
Oh that’s good.
Sorry to bother you, man.
I was in the room with Penelope
and I thought to myself,
maybe you can use some company.
What the fuck are you doing here?
I'm doing your wife, little bro.
Look, everything's going to be okay.
I'm here.
We'll get through this together.
You think this is funny?
All the police are going
to come looking for you.
You're definitely going to have to go
missing now.
Oh, yeah, but.
I bet you'd like that.
So you can do whatever you want.
Well, it seems like you have no choice,
does it, Jeffrey?
I am.
Woman God.
I gotta get out of here.
Can I ask you something?
What’s that?
What if I'm not ready to move on?
I already moved on.
What about today?
What if I didn't let you move on today?
What if I stayed in this house
so you couldn't renovated?
Then what?
You're not going to do
any of this, Jeffrey.
You are going to accept your fate.
And move on.
I think.
This whole thing.
Is not real.
I think I'm going out of my mind.
Jeffrey, you know why you are here.
No.
You have been temporarily disabled.
Your mind is glitching.
Wait.
What?
Your mind is glitching.
You've been brought
back to reality temporarily.
I don't know.
I don't understand what's happening.
Your mind is trying to help you
to deal with the pain.
Don't worry.
You'll be safe here.
Who are you?
The words for the subject.
What's your name?
Therapist.
Your name is therapist?
Actually, I have no name.
Neither do you.
They may exist in the reality
that you’ve just come from.
But here there are no names.
No.
Replenishment.
No, thank you.
I'm not hungry.
You've been asleep for 369 years.
I assure you, you are hungry and thirsty.
You are hungry and thirsty.
Y’all motherfuckers are crazy.
What's happening right now?
How does it feel not to know?
I don't understand.
It's a simple question.
What's it like
not to know?
Okay.
All right, I get it.
It's like I'm in the dark.
Yes.
Very good, Jeffrey.
It is like being in the dark.
You're in the dark because
you don't know what's happening.
Is it a pleasant feeling?
No. It's quite morbid, actually.
Morbid?
What just happened?
I don't talk like that.
You're talking the way
that you always talk.
No, I'm not.
I assure you, you are.
And how can you be so sure?
I birthed you.
What?
I
Birthed you.
You're a man.
I'm a what?
A man.
Yes?
You need to speak.
In silence.
Okay.
I see.
A man is
what is called the gender
in the human race.
Yes.
Now I understand the confusion.
Well, I'm the one that's not confused.
Yes.
Yes what?
You see?
You are not human.
What?
Humans do not exist.
Nothing exists.
As of now.
No, that’s impossible.
If I'm not a human,
then what am I?
A motherfucker.
What did you say?
Do you really want to be aware?
Yeah.
I think not.
If I'm not a human, then what am I?
You are a program, Jeffrey.
You are.
A digital simulation of a human being.
Nah.
No, I must been
going crazy here.
I'm flesh and blood.
Flesh and blood.
Two of the generalized modules
that make up the hallucination
known as human.
There is no such thing as flesh and blood.
Flesh and blood are biological
and chemical properties that can be.
You are just a program, Jeffrey.
Okay, I get it.
I think I'm going crazy.
I'm going insane.
And you better stop lying to him.
What was that?
What was what?
My dream.
What did it mean?
I don't know.
You tell me.
Uh oh.
I wasn't.
I was like,
I was there, but I wasn't real.
The world wasn't real.
That doesn't sound too bad.
It was horrible.
It was like I was a.
It was like I was a computer program
or something.
Wow. I am sorry to break it to you.
But this is real.
You are real.
I'm real.
What I'm doing to you is real.
What are you doing to me?
I'm destroying you.
You're not destroying me.
Yes, I am.
And I won't stop
until I'm completely done.
That doesn't make sense.
Why would my wife destroy me?
Ex wife
Right.
Why would my ex-wife
destroy me in a dream?
It's not a dream, Jeffrey.
It's reality.
Like I’ve said,
we're flesh and blood.
We are real.
You're real.
I am real.
This is real.
No.
This is not real.
Why were you upset when she told you
about the baby on the beach?
What the hell are you doing?
I'm so confused.
Don't be.
But none of this is making any sense.
It doesn't have to make sense Jeffrey.
I don't understand
what's going on, what's happening?
What difference does it make
if you know what's happening or not?
Because I hope to try to stop you.
Stop me from what?
From moving on.
Remember that one time
when we went to the beach?
It was you and me
or my cousin Gregory.
He wasn't my cousin Jeffrey.
What are you talking about?
Penelope.
How's the water?
It looks fantastic.
He was my lover.
I was cheating on you with him.
Doesn’t it bother you
how unfaithful I was to you?
Yeah. Yeah. This again?
Yes, this again.
I told you there was more.
You know that one day on the beach.
I got pregnant.
And it wasn't from you
because you and I hadn't done
anything for months.
No, it was from Gregory.
But I had a miscarriage.
But I didn't tell you
because I wanted to be more like you.
No.
Yes Jeffrey.
This is called destruction.
You're not real, Jeffrey.
None of this is real.
Are you trying to fuck with
me right now?
No.
We're computer simulations,
Jeffrey.
You're not real. I'm not real.
But we are.
You are.
Because the pain that you feel in this
moment is very real.
Right?
What's this?
Got something to do with the government
or something?
What?
They all seem like, some freaky MK
ultratype shit or something.
Oh, my God.
Who? Who?
Who's doing this?
I have to reveal something.
What?
We’ve been watched.
Don’t look up, they will see us.
Right, they will see us.
They see us, look down.
By who?
I don’t know.
But maybe.
Maybe we can find out together.
Together?
[door knocking]
Oh. Hey. Hey.
Why are you back?
I just wanted to know
when is a good time to visit.
It’s not been that long
since I tell you
I know, but like you said,
it might be a fun fucking time.
It will be a fun fucking time.
Yeah.
What's your favorite?
Favorite?
Position.
With you?
It would definitely be face to face.
Yeah, that's my favorite.
I’m excited.
Let's do it.
Ow! Ow! Oh!
More.
This is one of the most exciting days
I've had in years.
Jeffrey, are you done yet?
[screaming]
What's wrong?
There's nothing left for me to do.
That's because you've been
doing the same thing
over and over again for so long.
You need to find something new.
To challenge you.
I need to get some fresh air.
I need to take a walk.
If you leave,
I won't allow you back inside.
Like I said,
I'm renovating the house.
I just want to be with you.
I have told you.
That can’t happen.
Because I'm
I’m happy with Billy.
I'm happy with my two kids.
I'm happy with my dog.
You know what?
I can't help how I feel Penelope.
Okay.
Go and get your fresh air.
Am I just going insane?
[door knocking]
Who is it?
Hey, I want to know
when is a good time to visit?
Uh. Cam? Yes.
I'm Cam. Your neighbor?
Yeah.
Is any of this real?
Listen me brother.
Bring it in.
It might be a fun fucking time.
Who are you?
I'm Cam.
I'm looking for a woman
named Penelope.
I like to fuck her.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah.
I heard she's quite amazing,
and I want to explore her parts.
You know, it's my wife you
talking about?
Yes, I do.
And I'm sorry for your loss.
What do you.
What do you mean, loss?
She's still here with me.
She's right here.
I don't understand.
Who is that then?
Fuck.
[door knocking]
Penelope?
It’s me.
I know you are in here.
I think you breathing.
Hey.
Yo
Hey Ricardo
What's up?
What happened to you?
Man you look like you've
seen a ghost.
I actually did see a Coast Guard.
Look, I don't know what you mean by that.
I just came back to speak with Penelope.
Penelope?
Yeah.
She's
busy right now.
I need to talk to her,
and I need to see her.
Uh, is there.
Is everything okay?
She wrote me a check,
and that check bounced.
Oh, she did.
So I'm looking for a new one yea?
Oh, come on.
I'll take care of that for you.
Come on inside.
Come on.
So, what's going on with you people?
You go
and fuck my best friend
Billy and start your whole new life.
And I have nothing.
I'm married to a man
that makes me happier than you ever could.
I have kids that I love dearly.
I don't want someone like you around
my kids.
You're the one who decided to start
your new life with my best friend, Billy.
What was I supposed to do there?
Sit here and let my wife get her back
blown up by another man.
He did some amazing
things to me,
things that you could never do.
Don’t yell
You all want to wake up the kiddies?
What are you doing here?
You know why I'm here.
No, I don't.
How'd you get in?
I got a key.
How the fuck
you've got a key?
Our wife gave me a key.
You know, because you really
like both of us.
Why are you doing this?
I'm doing this
because I've got to find my way back
Why did you get so upset when she told you
about the baby at the beach?
Why did you get so upset?