(bright chiming)
(suspenseful music)
(liquid sloshing)
(engines revving)
- Woohoo.
(engine roaring)
- [Man] You need some light, Archie?
- Sam, I'd recognize your voice anywhere.
You ain't fooling nobody.
- [Sam] You owe this town, Archie.
- Yeah.
- I don't owe nobody nothing.
- All right.
- You boys get the hell
outta here.
- Let's get him, come on.
- Go on, now, get outta here.
- Come on, boys.
- Yeah, let's get him.
- Let's take care of this.
All right now.
- Go ahead, get him.
Go ahead now.
(masked man laughing)
(glass smashing)
- Go on, get out.
(windows smashing)
- [Man] Hurry up. Get in.
Get in there, come on.
- Look out.
- I ain't sellin'.
This is my five acres.
I'll use 'em any way I choose.
I'll build a pyramid of empty
beer cans on 'em if I want to.
- Use less old drunk.
- I ain't scared of you.
Get out!
- Watch him!
Watch yourself.
(kicks thudding)
(men yelling)
Watch him, boys.
- [Man] Get him good.
- Come on, get up.
- [Man] He ain't breathing.
- Hey, we got a problem in here.
- You stay here.
What the hell'd y'all do in here?
- We didn't touch him. He was drunk.
- What are we gonna do?
Our fingerprints are all over this place.
(coughing)
(tense dramatic music)
- [Man] Let's go. Get on now.
Come on, come on.
(flames igniting)
(men calling out)
Come on!
- [Man] Get down outta there.
- [Man] Get in the truck bed, let's go.
(thoughtful music)
- Now Linda, don't do a big number.
I'm family. Remember?
Yeah, put away the furniture
polish and think, oo,
messy kitchen and coffee mugs.
No, I don't want to face
that drive down from Dallas.
I'll take the train.
(knocking at door)
Hold on.
- [Man] Afternoon.
- Yeah. Hi.
Well roll out that big, Texas sunset.
I can't wait to meet Eddie and the kids.
And oh and give the kids a
big, special hug for me, okay?
I love you too. Bye.
- I see flannel is in again.
- Not in my closet.
- What are you looking for?
- Oh my tickets. They were right here.
You know, maybe I should postpone.
- No. No more postponements.
How many years have you
promised and then now shown up?
- 15.
- Shame on you.
- It's not as if I didn't try to go home.
There was just too much blood
under the bridge, Morgan.
I, if I'd gone home I'd have
to pretend to forgive my father
and forget all the stuff I never could.
- You're not going back
to your old hometown
and all those bad memories.
Your father's dead, Martha,
it's safe to come outta hiding.
- I'm a coward, Morgan.
I bailed out and left Linda there
to deal with my dad's
drinking and the fights
and the craziness.
It killed my mother.
I thought it'd kill me too.
- Sounds like survival to me.
Now go home and make it right. Okay?
- Okay.
- Bye bye.
- Bye.
(train whistle blows)
- [Man On PA] May I have
your attention please?
Train number 21, the Texas Eagle,
Texarkana, Marshall, Longview,
Dallas, Fort Worth, and Taylor.
For those of you boarding
nearest Rocky Valley,
please allow a few moments
for incoming passengers to detrain first,
attendants will then help you aboard.
Thank you.
- [Man] All clear here, Bill.
(men calling out in the background)
(upbeat country music)
- Yeah. What?
Who?
No, she's busy. She can't come out.
Well call back in an hour.
(suspenseful music)
(door closes in the distance)
(men yelling)
- [Man] I'll get him.
(tense music)
(whip cracks)
Come on, come on.
(men cheering)
- [Man] Come on. Get up.
Come on. Get up.
Go on.
- Get up.
- Yeah.
(men yelling)
- [Man] Let me at him.
- [Man] He doesn't really know anything.
- [Man] He knows about the fire.
- [Man] He might cause trouble for us.
(man yelling)
- He's getting away again.
- [Man] Come on now.
(gunfire pops)
(man yells)
(victim wheezes)
- Oh hell, Mike.
- Is he dead?
- [Man] Yeah.
- I only meant to scare him.
I mean he shouldn't have bolted like that.
- You idiot.
- It was an accident.
I mean, you could see that.
- Come on. Let's go.
- Let's go.
- Throw it down.
- [Man] Go get the truck.
(men calling out in the distance)
(upbeat country music)
(music overpowers voices)
- [Man] That went down real good.
- Martha!
Don't believe it.
I think I'm gonna cry.
Oh, I'm so sorry. Eddie was
supposed to pick you up.
And I just can't believe you're here.
Can you ever forgive me?
Things got backed up here.
- What time did you get off?
- Well, not for awhile.
- I need to talk to you.
- Oh, I know. Me too.
If you can just wait
until the crowd thins out.
Where's your bags?
- By the door.
- They're by the?
Okay, they'll be safe. Come on.
Wonderful.
What's the matter?
- Linda, it was something-
- Linda, your order's up.
Come on, you got customers.
- Jake, this is my sister.
- Oh yeah, your sister from LA.
Y'all really do favor each other.
Why don't y'all go ahead and go on home.
I know how long it's been
since you seen each other.
- But Betty's off and-
- That's all right. I'll handle things.
You go on. Go on.
Very nice to meet you.
We really do like your sister.
- Hey Jake!
- Go on.
- [Man] We'll see y'all later.
- Jake's been great.
Can you believe it?
I actually like my boss.
(Linda giggles) Come on.
We got some pretty country out here.
Not a lotta nightlife.
But I'm sure you get enough of that in LA.
(men calling out)
Okay, okay, I know you're probably angry-
- Linda, I saw a man murdered tonight.
- What?
- I was coming from the train station.
- Oh my God. Are you okay?
I mean, you actually-
- I saw this group of men and they were,
they were beating this
guy and I heard the shot
and I saw him fall.
And I don't know, the one who did it
was, was wearing a mask.
- So you didn't actually see his face?
Yeah, he took it off and I,
and I got a good look at him.
- Did you call the police?
- No, I was just so scared.
- Okay, um.
Eddie's working late, but he'll,
he'll be home in a little bit
and he'll know what to do.
- Okay.
(car door closes)
(door squeaks)
Hi.
- Hi!
- Kids in bed?
- [Girl] They're playing
rabid dog in their pjs.
(Linda laughs)
- All right, well thanks, Lorraine.
I'm sorry, this is my sister, Martha.
- Hi, heard a lot about you.
- Hi.
(kids growling playfully)
(Lorraine laughs)
- Hey, is this the way you
want to meet your aunt, Martha?
Come here, you rabid dogs,
let me wipe off your face.
(Linda laughs)
- 'Night kids. Thanks, Linda.
Nice meeting you too.
- Nice meeting you, too.
- Well, Emily and Timothy,
this is your aunt, Martha.
Hi, you two.
You know these pajamas
look pretty familiar.
- You bought them for me on my birthday.
- And half the toys in this house.
- Remember this?
- Hmm, Christmas two years ago.
- My dad says I can catch real good now.
- Really?
They're beautiful.
- It's not exactly the
homecoming I had in mind.
(door opens)
- Daddy's home!
- Daddy!
- Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
How's my babies, huh?
How's my big baby?
Mm.
- And this is Eddie.
How do you like him without his mustache?
- Well, well. (Eddie chuckles)
We sure have been looking
forward to this, haven't we?
Well, I tell you something,
your sister has been running
around, making me crazy.
Make me crazy, I keep
telling him to calm down,
your sister ain't expecting The Ritz.
She knows you got kids.
- Honey, things got really
messed up about picking her up.
- Yeah, I know, I'm sorry about that.
Sorry about that.
I had to work overtime.
Had to pull a drive shaft
out of a cab last minute.
And then one thing and another and...
Can I get you a beer?
Anything?
- Oh, no.
No thanks.
- I sure could use one.
- Okay.
- Angels, time for bed.
Why don't you say
goodnight to Aunt Martha.
- Goodnight, kids.
- How 'bout your daddy, huh?
Come here, gimme a kiss.
I'll tuck you in later, alright?
Sleep good.
- Okay, bedtime.
Come on, come on, come on.
Hey babe, there should
be another fan out there.
Boy, never known the air to be so dead.
Come on, sit down.
Kid's stuff.
We're saving up for air conditioning.
Boy, these Texas summers are getting worse
or I'm getting older.
Kids don't seem to mind none though,
but I sure can't take it no more.
- [Linda] Here you go.
- Thanks baby.
- Honey something
terrible happened tonight.
Martha saw a man murdered.
Saw the killer's face and everything.
- Is that right?
- Well, I really didn't see him clearly.
- I thought you said you saw his face?
- Yes, but it was dark.
- Where?
Where'd you see this?
- I really don't know the town.
Somewhere by the train station.
- Did you call the police?
- Just about to, when you came in.
- I'll do it.
- Well I'll get your bags.
And I'll show you to your room.
- [Man] No, go ahead, just unlatch it.
- [Man] Alright.
- [Man] We gonna have to
section this area off.
- Akins, what the hell are you doing here?
County seat's 40 miles away.
- Well I was out at the
lake, got this over the wire.
Daikin Larson?
- That's what the ID says.
- Name rang a bell.
Larson contacted my office a few days ago.
I was on vacation.
So he left a message.
- What kinda message?
- He was suspicious about
the death of a pal of his.
- Pal huh?
Who would that be?
- Archie Maddox.
- [Man] No sir. Let 'em know...
- How long has our Larson been here?
- According to motel manager
he's been here less than a week.
- Mm hmm.
- Sheriff?
Eddie Pick called.
It seems there was a witness to this.
- Oh, good.
Mind if I tag along?
- (laughs) Now, I never
heard of a county prosecutor
just tagging along.
- Usually they want to take charge.
- Well, you know, you can
do all the questioning.
It's still a local matter.
- All right.
- Uh, I don't know how
many men, it was dark.
A man being beaten and running.
I heard a shot and then he fell.
That's all.
- Did you see the man who shot him?
- Well, like I said,
it was dark and he was wearing a mask.
- I guess I sort of saw
him when he came over
to look at the body.
- If he was wearing a mask,
how could you see his face?
- Well you said he took off the mask.
- Yes.
Yes he did.
He, he took off the mask.
- [Sheriff] But it was dark.
- Yes. Dark.
- [Sheriff] Anything else?
- No.
- Could you identify this man?
- I'm not sure.
- Well, thank you.
Thank you.
Good to see ya, Linda.
Eddie.
- That's it?
- Yeah. For now.
- All right.
For now then.
I wanna check out that motel room.
His personal stuff.
- Alright.
- You okay?
- Not really.
- Linda!
- Okay, I'll be right back.
(suspenseful music)
(tense music)
Hurry up and eat your breakfast.
- [Child] I don't want that.
(voices muffling in the next room)
- It tastes like dirt.
- That's 'cause you keep
pounding it like dirt.
Now quit pounding it,
sit up straight and eat.
Don't play with it.
- [Martha] Good morning, everybody.
What's for breakfast?
- Morning.
- It's dirt.
- Oh. Mm.
- Oh yuck.
- Oh no, no, no.
Did you know that the lone ranger
never eats with his mask on?
- All right, come on kids.
You got school. Daddy's got work.
Let's go.
- You know what?
- What's that?
- A smiley face.
- A smiley face?
Oh, right in the middle is a?
- Nose.
(Martha laughs)
- You know the kids are wonderful, honey,
You did a great job.
- Yeah.
Eddie and I were gonna wait.
But, (mutters) we figured what the hell?
I love him, Martha.
- I can see that.
- He's not the most educated guy.
You know?
But he did okay.
I mean, he had a rough childhood,
a lot of abuse like us.
But he really got it together
and he loves the kids.
- How does he treat you?
- Mm, he loves me.
- You know, mom and dad
loved each other too,
but we know what that was like.
- Yeah well, that's not us.
I mean Eddie hardly ever drinks.
And he's never heavy handed
with Timothy or Emily.
- Or you?
- Well, only when I over cook the eggs
and then he bats me around a little bit.
- So don't cook eggs.
(both laughing)
You know, I'm, I'm really sorry
it was so rough with Dad at the end.
- It was always rough with Dad.
- You know I wanted to
come back for the funeral.
- No you didn't.
Well you didn't.
- Nope, I guess I didn't.
- Well, thanks for the checks.
I mean it covered everything we needed.
- Didn't cover what you needed.
- I managed.
I mean Eddie was there, thank
God, and he helped out a lot.
But let's forget the past. Okay?
- [Man] What's the matter?
- There's a witness.
- A witness?
What do you mean a witness?
- Well, she didn't see much.
- She? Who's she?
- Name is Martha Dubius.
She's here visiting her sister.
- Well go on.
Who the hell's her sister?
- Linda Peck.
- Eddie's wife?
- He didn't tell you.
- (sighs) No wonder he's
been avoiding me all morning.
- You know, this whole
thing has gotten real messy.
First that Archie Maddox
situation was bad enough-
- That was an accident.
- And now the Larson killing.
A bullet in the back's no accident.
- Doyle, Sheriff.
- Counselor.
- Akins.
- Just to let you know,
I've requested a coroner's
inquest as soon as possible.
- Isn't that a little premature?
- Let's get in outta this killer heat.
(Doyle coughs)
You know, I've been
trying to sell this town
as a great place to live and do business.
(Doyle chuckles)
You couldn't make my job any
tougher if you put up a sign,
welcoming homeless hookers.
(Sheriff laughs)
- Well, whoever killed Larson did that
and I intend to find out
who killed him and why.
- What was he doing here anyway?
- Came to see an old friend.
- Yeah? Who's that?
- Archie Maddox.
- Archie Maddox? (laughs)
He was just a drunk who died in the fire
that he caused himself.
- What happened to his property?
- I bought it at public auction.
And I paid too damn much for it, too.
- You see the billboard
for the industrial park
outside of town?
- Archie's property.
- The whole town's gonna
benefit big time from that.
- It's funny how one man's life or death
could affect so many.
Whole economy of a town, in fact.
There's some poetry in there somewhere.
Thanks for the pop, Doyle.
(drill whirring)
(Martha gasps)
- Oo. (laughs)
Thought you might want
to join us for lunch.
- Next time could you please knock?
- Oh, I'm sorry, guess
I'm not used to guests.
(Eddie chuckles)
- [Linda] Eddie!
(Eddie growls playfully)
(car horn honks)
- Oo, amazing.
(slap cracks)
(car horn honks)
- That's probably Mr. Potter.
He's Eddie's boss.
- [Eddie] What's up?
- Get in.
What does she know?
- Oh didn't see nothin'.
She don't know nothin'.
- Akins thinks she does.
- Well he's shooting wild.
- You invite me to supper.
I'll find out what she knows.
- Mr. Potter has been
real good to his wife too.
I mean really gave us a break.
A little trouble and people run for cover,
but not the Potters.
- Well what kind of trouble?
- He's a great mechanic, like I said,
and Mr. Potter says that if he can-
- What kind of trouble, Linda?
- Eddie, knocked a guy
out and hit his windpipe.
They called it involuntary manslaughter
'cause it was an accident.
Hey, why don't you get dressed
and let's go into town.
I want to show you off, okay?
- Well, what is it like to
raise kids in a town like this?
- It's okay. I guess.
- And how are the schools?
- Mm, they're okay.
- Ever thought about private school?
- Martha, this isn't LA.
And besides, Eddie and I can't afford it.
- Well, I could.
- No, you couldn't.
I mean, it's sweet of you,
but since Eddie had it rough,
I mean...
Hi, Walt.
- Howdy, Linda.
- He just doesn't want the kids to think
that anything comes easy.
You know?
- You know that trouble
you said Eddie was in?
- Mm hmm.
- Did he ever hit you?
Dammit, Martha, why don't you like Eddie?
I mean, from the moment
you met him, I sensed it.
What, what is it about him?
I mean it's something.
And when he talks to you,
you barely speak to him.
It's not right. It's embarrassing.
- Can we just drop this right now?
- No, I will not drop it.
I mean, it's been 15 years
since we've seen each other
and we're all walking on eggshells.
It's not right.
Eddie walks in a room and you walk out
or you shut your door.
- I can't.
I can't talk about this now.
- Well what, are you gonna
wait another 15 years?
We're sisters and we used to be close.
But the longer you're here
the more distant you become.
It's not fair.
Martha, please talk to me.
(Martha sighs)
(gentle, yet tense music)
- Oh.
Eddie was the one I saw
kill that man, Larson.
- No.
No, how can you say that?
- I was there. I saw him do it.
- No.
- [Martha] Linda!
Linda please.
- Everything all right, Ms. Dubius?
- Yeah.
My sister and I haven't seen
each other in so many years.
We have a lot of
unfinished family business.
- Well, we were just
coming by to pick you up.
- Why?
- Need to ask you a few questions
about what you saw last night.
- Well, I told you everything that I saw.
I was here behind these crates.
And Larson was here.
and this, this is where
you saw the assailant?
- Well, his head was sort of half in
and half out of the light.
- Well I'm standing over the body
and I would be fully lit by that light.
How could you not see his face?
- I guess he was looking down.
- Larson was killed
what, about 10 past nine?
- That's right.
Gah, it's funny nobody saw anything.
Restaurant across the street
and there's a bar right here.
- [Martha] Everything was closed.
- Everything was closed.
But yesterday when Larson
was killed, wasn't a holiday.
Was it?
- When there's no business,
sometimes stores closed early.
- Uh huh.
All of them, including the bar?
- Maybe you should ask them
why they shut down early last night, hmm?
- Well, you can bet on it.
Come on, Ms. Dubius, I'll take you home.
(suspenseful music)
- I'm sorry I wasn't much help.
- Well, I got a feeling that
it'll all be a lot clearer
in a few days.
- What do you mean by that?
- When the shock wears off.
- Oh.
(thoughtful music)
- Thanks for your help.
Sorry it took so long.
- You told Sheriff Brand
and that prosecutor something, didn't you?
- No, I didn't.
- I know you think you
saw Eddie kill that man,
but you're wrong, Martha.
You know, I saw this program
about how much we really see.
And if we really remember the
things that we think we saw
and they had these
people look at something
and then close their eyes
and then describe what
they saw in a minute,
they didn't even get the colors right.
It was really crazy.
So what I'm trying to
say is it wasn't Eddie.
I mean, it may have looked like him,
but it was somebody else.
He didn't do it.
You were mistaken, Martha.
- I should never have told you like that.
I'm gonna pack up and go in the morning.
- Oh that's just great.
You accuse my husband of
murder and then you just leave.
- I don't want to leave you.
But if I stay, I can't help.
And if they keep pressuring me,
I'm gonna have to tell them what I saw.
- And I want you to admit you
could have made a mistake.
- I can't, Linda.
- I saw that man killed
and I saw Eddie do it.
(sad music)
- I've waited for years for this.
For you coming here.
- Oh I know.
I know.
- And I'm just afraid if you leave
I'll never see you again.
- So you'll call me when you get to LA?
- Yeah, maybe when things cool
down, you can come see me.
Bring the kids.
- Sure.
- [Man On PA] Hardy to track two.
Amtrak silver.
- Well, man says the train's on time.
- [Man On PA] Taylor, Waco, Waxahachie.
- Oh no.
- Sorry to do this to you, Ms. Dubius,
- You don't look sorry.
- What is it?
- Subpoena. Coroner's inquest.
- But you didn't see anything.
I mean, you told them that it was dark.
I heard you, you told them both.
I heard you!
- Eddie!
- I just don't get it.
- It's a subpoena.
It's not as if I asked to testify.
It's a court order.
You've heard of a court order?
Honey, go get her bag.
Please.
- I'll get a rental car and a room.
- No, you can't.
- I can't stay with him in the house.
- Please. For me.
(thoughtful music)
- Okay.
(ominous music)
Don't you think it would
be better all around
if I just got a room someplace?
- No, Martha, I need you to stay here.
- Why are you so frantic?
I mean, what are you afraid of?
- It's just this town.
I mean, if you move
out, there'll be gossip.
And if it gets back to Eddie-
- Eddie, it's always Eddie!
Why does everything revolve around Eddie?
Do you ever put yourself first?
Yes, it's what I want too,
I want you to stay here too.
- Now honey, honey listen,
it's gonna be okay.
Okay?
- What's going on?
- Hey honey.
I got a great meal plan for the Potters.
- Yeah baby.
What's the matter?
- I just heard some talk around a town.
Seems you got a lot of people worried.
- How so?
- Well, bad time for
this would be happening.
We got a lot riding on
Rocky Valley being seen
as a law and order town.
- Compared to Beirut, probably is.
- Big aluminum siding plant
deciding between Rocky
Valley and Temple City.
- Before you let Akin start scaring you,
when the prosecutor
gets himself a witness,
sometimes he tries to make you
start seeing all sorts of things.
- You being an authority on prosecutors?
- Don't get cute.
Say what you mean.
- No, thanks.
I've seen how you fly off the handle
when people say what they mean.
- No need to, 'til you came
along, that's for sure.
(Martha scoffs)
Listen.
- Stop it, Eddie!
Let go of her.
- You touch me again and
I'll tell them what I know.
- Really?
What do you know?
- I know that you shot that man Larson.
I saw you shoot him.
And the other man call you an idiot,
which is just about the nicest
thing I can say about you.
- She tell you this?
She tell you this lie?
- Yes.
- Well why didn't you tell me?
Why didn't you tell me?
- Because maybe every
time you raise your fence-
- You stay out of it.
- Please, Martha.
Ever since you come here
you've been looking down your nose at us.
And that's because you hate me
for not providing a smart life
for your sister like you got.
- Stop turning yourself into the victim.
- Look at her, honey.
How many times has she changed her story?
Huh? How many times.
Now how much could she have seen?
You know how dark those streets are
when all those stores are closed.
- I never said the stores were closed.
- It's a small town. People talk.
Everybody knows that.
Look at her.
Standing there, all smug
and sure of herself.
She don't know squat,
but she's got to convince you
that you can do better than me
because she hates it that you got a family
and all she's got is an empty bed.
You want to believe her, honey?
You just go ahead and believe her.
I don't even give a damn.
- Eddie!
Eddie!
Eddie, wait!
Look at me. Look at me.
Just tell me.
I'm your wife.
And whatever it is,
we'll piece it together.
But you have to tell me the truth.
Did you do what she said?
Did you kill that, man?
- She's lying, Linda, alright?
She's lying.
I didn't do it, I wasn't even there.
(thoughtful music)
You gotta believe me.
I don't know why she's doing this,
I don't know why she's doing this.
I don't know why.
- What we've got here is a
county prosecutor with an agenda.
While he's building
himself up in the press,
with all kinds of wild theories,
they're writing bad things about us
and the investors are leaving.
He's like all these politicians,
he's gotta build himself
up with headlines.
- Well, he's running out of time.
The inquest is tomorrow.
- I never know if this size
helps, but I do it anyway.
I think probably, you know,
ceiling fans do the most good.
- Well, we're saving up
for air conditioning.
Hey, kids are back.
- [Eddie] Good.
- Hey! Hi sweeties.
- Hey, kids.
- Hey, look who's here!
Look who's here.
Oh boy.
That's a great cap. Who won?
- We won.
- Oh good! Come here, you pretty thing.
- Do you have any children
of your own, Mrs. Potter?
- Not this small.
- What about Tina?
- Oh, well Tina wasn't mine, honey.
- Where is she now?
- With the angels, Emily.
Tina's with the angels.
- Hey, why don't we let the grownups
finish their dinner, all right?
Okay.
- What wonderful children.
(Doyle laughs)
- I understand you work
for a department store.
- Actually I'm a buyer for a
chain of department stores.
- I think women should work.
They get in so much trouble
with too much time on their hands.
- As opposed to men who
get into a lot of trouble
with so little time on their hands.
(Mrs. Potter laughs)
- You know, I always wanted to work,
have a career.
- Well you raised a family, didn't you?
- One son.
Actually...Eddie has
been more of a son to me
than that loser.
- Thank you, Mr. Potter.
- Our son went his own way.
- Thanks to your encouragement.
- I've always been grateful to our mother
for encouraging me to go my own way.
Some birds when they fly from the nest
don't land quite as good as you did.
- It's not the landing
that counts Mr. Potter.
It's the flying.
- What's that supposed to mean?
- That having the courage
to try to do something
is what's important.
Not how successful you become.
- (coughs) It's airy fairy crap like that
that losers tell each other
to keep 'em from getting discouraged.
(Doyle coughs)
- Oh, Linda, I'm so sorry.
- It's okay.
Here.
- [Eddie] Here, put that over there.
- [Linda] Thank you. (chuckles)
- Up.
- [Eddie] Watch your elbow
now, sweetheart, alright?
- Yeah, y'all be careful.
- Whoever fixed the chain
on this thing, I think one
side's longer than the other.
- [Linda] Yeah, kinda tween.
- Honey listen.
The man had a husky voice
and he used an inhaler.
How many men in this town does that fit?
- What are you doing?
You're not content in
destroying one family,
but you want to bust
up the Potters as well?
(Martha sighs)
- I just came in for a glass of water.
- Oh, Mr. Potter, it,
it's in the refrigerator.
- Oh, now I'll help myself.
- It's really nice having
you and Mrs. Potter here.
- Yeah, well we're really enjoying it.
You know, we don't get out very often.
Hilda is in rather delicate health.
You know I wouldn't trade Rocky Valley
for all the cities in the world.
- Oh, me either.
Eddie and I-
- Small town people know how
to pull together in a crisis.
You remember when the shops closed
during that oil glut?
- Oh yeah, and the food drive.
- Eddie had several strikes against him.
I hate to think what would
have happened to Eddie
if it hadn't been for you.
Without all of us for that matter.
You know, there's something
about a small town,
a kind of loyalty that
people in big cities
just don't understand.
But there's a price for
that fierce loyalty.
Betrayal is very ugly.
In a city if you betray your neighbor
you can always move to another suburb.
Sort of reinvent yourself.
But in a small town
you have to live with people you betrayed.
(Doyle sighs)
Thanks for the water.
- Now we know it was dark, Ms. Dubius.
Every shop in the area that night
for some inexplicable reason
had decided to shut early.
Innuendo is inappropriate
and suspicions are not
evidence, Counselor.
Those shop owners have testified.
Nothing inexplicably about closing early
when there's no business.
- Or why there was no
cab at the train station.
- That's your second
warning, Mr. Akins, Mr.
- Mr. Potter has already
submitted an affidavit
of repair on one cab.
And Mr. Ballou, the
driver of the second cab
had proof he was in Dallas that night.
- I'm sorry, Your Honor.
Coincidence is like common sense.
It's very uncommon.
I get suspicious when
a whole town shuts down
so that a man can get killed.
- Mr. Akins, unlike common sense.
Conspiracy theories are very common.
You're too smart to introduce
suspicions as evidence.
This is an inquest, not a trial.
Don't audition for us, you got the job.
(courtroom chuckles)
(gavel pounds)
- Alright. Alright.
So just what did you see Ms. Dubius?
- It was dark.
I didn't see anyone clearly.
- Larson fell right in front of you
under a street lamp.
The assailants crowded around
him, removed their masks.
And you didn't see them?
- Only one removed his mask.
- The one who was shot Larson.
He was the one under the light.
- He kept his head down.
I'm sorry, I didn't see
any of them clearly.
- So you can't identify him?
- No.
I'm afraid. I can't.
(unsettling music)
(upbeat music)
(crowd murmuring)
- Excuse me.
Excuse me. Can I get through?
Excuse me. Excuse me.
Beg your pardon.
Excuse me.
Hello, ladies.
- I hope this isn't
going to be unpleasant.
- No more unpleasant than
it was for me in there.
- It's over. Let us get on with our lives.
- Murdered by assailants
or assailants unknown
is not what I call satisfactory verdict.
Tomorrow I'm gonna serve
you another subpoena.
- She told you everything.
- I can speak for myself-
- You got no right hounding her like that.
- Eddie, please!
- Eddie!
- I told you what I saw.
- Well, you can tell me again
in front of a grand jury.
- (scoffs) I have a job
I have to get back to.
- Just remember Ms. Dubius,
that perjury is a serious
offense in a murder trial.
- If I'm not sure what I
saw, is it still perjury?
- No, but it is if you are sure
and just scared to tell the truth.
- He didn't believe you.
He didn't believe you.
- It's not her fault, Eddie.
It's not her fault.
- Come on. Let's go.
Get in the car.
- I'll walk, thanks.
- Come on, let's go.
Something else happens.
(tires peeling)
(chainsaw buzzes)
- Where's Linda?
- I don't know.
Maybe she's got a boyfriend.
- Gee, that'd sure top my wishlist.
(unsettling music)
- Your sister's at work.
Kids are at dinner with friends.
(chuckles)
Had you going there, didn't I?
Boy, I'll tell ya,
sure is hot.
I wish I could afford a swimming pool.
I bet you got a swimming pool.
You ever skinny dip?
(Martha scoffs)
- Are you afraid?
- Get out of here.
- Why do I know what you're
gonna say before you say it?
- I don't know. You tell me.
- Look at you.
Struttin' around like the town stud.
I don't know whether to laugh or cry.
- (laughs) You oughta be
grateful for the attention.
- Don't flatter yourself.
- Problem with you as you
never had a real man before.
(Martha gasps)
- Stop.
Stop! Stop!
Are you crazy?
Ow!
- Eddie! Eddie, what?
Eddie!
- Sorry.
Honey, I'm sor-
(slap cracks)
She come on to me.
- You stupid liar.
- She knew you's gonna
catch us here, honey.
She knew you was gonna come home
and that you was gonna catch us like this.
She set me up.
- You don't think she's
gonna buy any of that crap.
- Martha, stop it.
- You don't believe him?
- She's all talk, baby.
But talk ain't facts.
Fact is you know what we got.
You know, because you
can feel it right here.
- Eddie, leave us.
Please leave us alone.
- You don't believe him?
- I don't know what to believe.
- Oh, Linda.
- I just know that until you came here,
I was happy for the first time in my life.
- You blame me?
- I'm just telling you
I'm not gonna throw away what I have.
I may never find it again.
And I end up like you.
You're right, it's not
good with all of us here
under one roof.
There's a nice motel in town.
I'll call 'em for ya.
(thoughtful music)
- Hey, this is a great
spot for our picnic.
You guys go out and get
all set up, alright?
I'm gonna make a call and
then I'll come right out
and be with ya, alright?
Okay. Can you carry that?
You got that?
Good, sweetie.
Just go right in there.
See if you can pick out a spot.
Thanks, Emily.
Hello? Hi.
Yeah, Jane?
Hi, it's Martha.
Could I speak to Morgan?
Thanks.
Hi Morgan.
I'm gonna be here another couple of weeks.
I've been subpoenaed.
I know, but I'll talk to you soon.
Okay, bye.
Okay guys, let's get all
this stuff packed up.
- [Timothy] Boy, that was great.
Why aren't you living with us anymore?
- Oh sweetie, you know,
I just thought maybe it was
getting a little crowded.
- [Emily] We wish you'd come back.
- [Timothy] We like you living with us.
- You know what guys you're making me
feel really, really good.
Here you go, can you carry that?
- Yes.
- Alright.
- That's where me and Dad go shooting.
- [Martha] What do you shoot at?
- Just cans and stuff,
but Archie made us stop.
- Archie Maddox?
Is that his property?
- Yeah, he's real mean
whenever Tina was there.
- Tina?
- A little girl who would
come to visit Archie.
She acted real funny.
She looked weird too.
- Archie Maddox.
(phone rings)
(suspenseful music)
- I get to answer it.
- No, me.
(tense music)
- Kids? Timothy!
No!
Timothy!
(rattling)
(screaming)
- Texas. Snakes are everywhere.
- Well what about that four wheeler
that I saw stop next to my car?
- Mm hmm. Did you get a license number?
- Whoever killed Larson wants me dead too.
- If they killed Larson because
he suspected Archie's death
and the fire wasn't
accidental, then you're right.
They won't hesitate to kill you too.
Of course, if you didn't see anything
why would anyone want to kill you?
- Maybe it's what they think I saw.
- Okay. Okay.
I'll attach deputy to watch you.
- No, then they'll be
sure I know something.
- You won't let me help you?
My hands are tied.
- Well, you don't have any
answers at all, do you?
- That's right, I don't have any answers.
I may just have to subpoena
this whole damn town.
- I'm not gonna hang around
here waiting to be killed
while you fill out subpoenas.
- Now, what does that mean?
- Well if I'm stuck here,
I'm gonna make it pay off.
- Now hold on, hold on. Just wait.
No use start sticking your nose.
Oh, oh boy.
(suspenseful music)
- Well who's she talking to now?
Uh huh.
What kinda questions is she asking?
Okay, well keep me informed.
Eddie, get in here.
- Doyle?
- That sister-in-law of
yours is asking questions.
Questions about Archie's land.
About how strange it is that
I'm the only builder in town
who owns Archie's land.
- She's just making a pest
of herself, that's all.
I mean, ain't gonna do her no good.
- She's also asking (coughs)
about a little girl visiting Archie.
How do you suppose she put
together Tina with Archie?
You answer me that, huh?
- I don't know.
(suspenseful music)
(Martha gasps)
- Hotter than a whore's breath in here.
- Take your rustic homilies and get out
or I'll call the police.
Better yet, I'll call the FBI.
It's a federal offense
to intimidate a witness.
- You sit down and shut the hell up.
Just who do you think
you are coming in here,
messing around in our
business, disrupting our lives.
If you want to know
anything about Archie Maddox
or about who owns his land
you come to me.
You understand that?
- What about that snake,
was that supposed to scare me outta town?
Don't you get it?
If I try to leave town,
they'll throw me in jail.
I've been subpoenaed. I am stuck here.
- If you stay, you might
want to think about
what this town has done for
your sister and her family.
We don't like inquisitive
strangers coming in here.
You might want to think about that
before you testify again.
(door slams)
- Well, what brings you here?
- I just got a visit from Doyle Potter.
I'm not about to let some
redneck bully intimidate me.
- Feel better?
- Eddie was the one who shot Larson.
Potter was there too.
- What?
Oh, I didn't see his face,
but I recognized his voice
and he used an inhaler.
- You're sure.
- Yes. I'm sure.
Will that be enough to convict him?
- Well that's not your worry.
Besides, that's down the line.
First, the arraignment, then
the indictment against Eddie.
He'll pull the rest down.
- A favor.
- What?
- I need time to convince
Linda to leave Eddie.
- Can't promise that.
When Linda and the kids
are out of that house,
then you can have him.
Otherwise forget it.
- 48 hours.
Unbelievable.
- Look, there's something else.
- - What?
- Came from Linda's kids.
They used to play near
Archie Maddox's house.
- Yeah, the guy Larson came to see.
- Yeah, and Archie would chase 'em away
whenever a little girl came to visit.
- A little girl, who was she?
- Her name was Tina.
- When was this?
- About a year ago.
Hilda Potter used to
bring her to visit Archie.
And there's another thing.
- What?
- The kids said there was
something strange about her.
- What do you mean, strange?
I don't know. That's all they said.
(ominous tones)
(door rattling)
(door creaks)
Linda?
(ominous tones)
(electricity buzzes)
(Linda gasps)
- [Linda] Scared me to death.
- Me too.
- I just came into get a cup of coffee.
I'm doing books.
What are you doing here?
- Well, I think we should talk.
- [Linda] Would you like a cup of coffee?
- Oh, no thanks.
I'd like you and the kids
to come to LA for awhile.
- (scoffs) We can't do that.
I've got a job.
The kids are in school.
I can't-
- Just for a little while.
I mean, say you're taking a vacation.
Parents take their kids
outta school all the time.
They can make it up.
- And what about Eddie?
- This is not about Eddie.
(Linda sighs)
I'm sorry.
- What is this really about?
- It's about taking a break, you know,
from all that's happened.
Come on, you see the way Eddie's acting.
It's not good for you and
it's not good for the kids.
You know guys like Dad and Eddie,
well, they never think
of the consequences.
They're children and they're dangerous.
And they'll never grow up
because of people like...
(tense music)
Mother.
- And me.
Mother and me, that's
what you were gonna say.
You want us to leave town
'cause you're gonna testify against Eddie.
- Linda, honey.
Listen, it's time to think
about you and the kids.
- You are destroying my life, Martha.
Do you realize that's what you're doing?
I'll never forgive you, never.
(pool balls clattering)
(Linda gasps)
(ominous tones)
- Are you okay?
(Linda sobs)
Come on, I'll get us a beer.
- Thanks for coming.
I just didn't want to be alone.
- Your sister?
- Yeah.
- Come on.
I got some good news.
I've been doing some checking.
Archie Maddox did indeed
have a daughter named Tina.
Only the Hall of Records
claiming she died 10 years ago.
- But the kids said they
just saw her a year a go.
- Yeah, well, if that's true,
then obviously someone
fake the death certificate.
- Did Archie have any other relatives
who could have inherited his land?
- Nope, I checked.
And with Tina legally
dead, Potter was able
to buy Archie's land in a public auction
and he got it cheap.
- What about Tina?
- Well Mr. Potter's not gonna tell us.
- So I guess that means
we're on our way to see Hilda Potter.
- Mm hmm.
- Thank you.
- Thanks.
- I always add extra water,
it gets too sweet for me.
Whew, I can't bear this heat.
I can't imagine how you
think I can help you.
- Oh, you understand this is unofficial,
we're just trying to
tie up some loose hands.
- Well, I'm really not aware
of what goes on outside this house.
I uh, I, you know I do get out
of bit to see a few friends,
but my life is really my flowers.
These are from my nursery.
- Oh, they're beautiful.
- People say it's an ugly world.
Flowers remind me that
the blame lies elsewhere.
- Are those your sons?
- Yes.
- We understand that
you would occasionally
visit a young girl.
(door creaks)
- What are y'all doing here?
- Doyle, they just-
- You got no business here.
- Well, as I was telling your wife,
it's an unofficial visit.
- We've got a call first
policy in my house.
- Look, they didn't do any-
- Sorry for the intrusion Mrs. Potter.
That produced a whole lot of nothing.
- It produced a lie.
- What do you mean?
- Well at Linda's, Potter
said they only had one son.
She just admitted they have two.
There was a family picture with two sons
and then a class picture.
A school called Rosedale Hall.
- I've never heard of it,
but I'll check it out.
- Okay.
- We've got ourselves a real
potential problem here, Eddie
and you're the cause of it.
- Mr. Potter, I think I
got the situation in hand.
- You've got your life in
your hands is what you've got.
That bitch is gonna get
chatty to a grand jury.
- She ain't gonna say nothing.
I mean, she, she don't want-
- Shut up!
I've had some calls. I
know what she's gonna do.
Now, I've got an alibi.
And so have the boys.
We were playing cards together.
You're gonna take this
fall by yourself, Eddie.
- Yeah but you said, I mean,
I mean about friends
and sticking together.
- The bottom line, Eddie,
is we do what's right for Rocky Valley.
Now I'm bringing in jobs.
What are you bringing in?
Mr. Potter, me and Linda,
we owe you everything.
We wouldn't let anybody
cause you no trouble.
(Doyle laughs)
- Well, just keep that
sister-in-law of yours
from testifying, that's all, Eddie.
Goodbye, Eddie.
- Well she's gotta go.
You got to make her go
or they're gonna do something desperate.
- Eddie, why are you so upset?
Did somebody threaten you?
- I'm worried for you and the kids.
- Oh, they threatened us and
you're gonna defend them.
Who are they, Eddie?
- Honey, you know you are not
seeing the bigger picture.
Alright?
And your sister's ruining
everything for them, for us.
And we're the town too.
- No, they're the town.
You're the ex-con they helped.
And I'm the ex con's wife.
- They like us.
- As long as we're grateful.
We don't owe them anything.
- That's what Archie said,
look what happened to him.
(ominous tones)
- How do you know what Archie said?
You were there, weren't you?
- No, I wasn't there.
- What really happened, Eddie?
- I don't know. I told you I wasn't there.
- You were there. You know what happened.
And you've gotta tell me.
Eddie!
- All right. I was there.
All right? I was there.
But I was in the car.
I was driving for Mr. Potter
and I didn't get outta the car.
Old Archie got drunk,
knocked over a kerosene lamp.
You know the story, the
whole town knows the story
and it's the truth.
I swear it.
- And what about Larson?
Eddie, look at me.
Who shot Larson?
- I don't know. Now you leave me alone.
- It was you, wasn't it?
- It was supposed to be a warning.
I didn't mean it.
Listen to me.
I only wanted to scare him.
I didn't mean to hurt him.
Oh baby.
Oh.
- Eddie!
All your life, just
one mess after another.
- Thanks.
- You know I grew up in
a town like Rocky Valley.
Life like this.
I hated it.
- I like small towns.
I bet you don't even know
the name of your neighbor in the city.
- Yes I do.
Her name is 417.
- (laughs) Yeah, I know
you're being funny,
but I think you like it that way.
- I like knowing who I am
and making peace with that.
- That makes you happy?
- Makes me content.
- What would make you happy?
- To not be depressed by
the downside of my choices.
(Akins laughs)
- I gather you've decided
not to have a family.
- Apparently the same goes for you.
(sad music)
- My wife and boy were
killed by a drunk driver.
- Oh Brooke, I'm so sorry.
- I'm still not afraid to
start another family, though.
- You have a lot more guts than I have.
Success in life to me is
how well I handle plan B.
- So you're happier with the compromises?
- Only because the
unhappiest people I know
are the ones who are surprised
that life isn't fair.
I don't like surprises.
- Well, Ms. Martha, I like you.
Surprised?
- [Linda] Goodnight, Brooke.
- [Brooke] Goodnight.
(soft music)
(patrons conversing quietly)
- [Man] Get on outta here.
(man clears his throat)
- [Man] Bye bye.
- [Man] We better go back in.
My brother.
- Oh yeah.
- [Man] Alright.
(engine revs)
(tense music)
(Martha pants)
(crashing)
(Martha exclaims)
- (groans) I'm okay. Really, I'm fine.
- (sighs) Well what you described
is a four wheeler with light bars.
2/3 of the vehicles in this
town are four wheelers.
- Yeah, but this one had
a piece of a barn on it.
- Now will you allow me
to assign you a deputy?
- A local?
- No, I can get someone
from another jurisdiction.
- That'd take a lotta time.
Well, I'll get right on it.
And I'll get someone to
pick up your car too.
- Thanks, Brooke.
- Sure.
- Goodnight.
- [Woman] Come on. Now
you're getting the towel wet.
- [Girl] A little splash.
- [Woman] Oh good. Well come on.
- [Man] The suntan lotion.
- [Woman] There you go.
- I'm sorry about what happened.
I'm sorry.
Is there somewhere we can talk?
- [Man] Y'all stay where I can see ya.
- [Woman] That's good
honey, all the way across.
- Sounds like dad's old Plymouth.
(Linda sighs)
- It, it's just, I know everything now.
- I know that Eddie was there
when Archie Maddox died, and
I know Eddie shot Larson.
- Oh thank God.
Now you see why you and the
kids have to come away with me.
No, but Eddie told me what happened
and I know what he did is wrong.
- Don't finish that sentence, Linda.
- He's my husband, Martha, and
- How can I shake some sense into you?
Don't you see the pattern?
Mother never listened either.
Her death was an escape.
It was easier for her to
die than to face reality.
(tense music)
Linda, wait, please listen to me.
- You don't give people
any room do ya, Martha?
And if they take too much
time finding themselves,
you just dump 'em.
Eddie's right, you don't care about me.
- That's not true.
- You're selfish, Martha, you always were.
That's why you bailed out on me.
- I know the responsibility
I left you with.
I felt guilty my whole life.
- Oh, I'll make ya a deal.
I'll take your guilt if you
give me those years back.
I figure you owe me one, Martha.
- I do owe you.
- You want to help me and the kids?
You want to make things right?
- Yes.
- Then lie to the grand jury
and don't tell them about Eddie.
(explosion booms)
(women exclaim)
(Linda grunts)
- Oh, not necessary.
- Come on, get in.
It's hospital rules.
Thank you, I'll take her.
Your sister okay?
- Yeah.
- I'll put you up in my hotel.
They won't touch ya there.
You alright? You cold?
- Yeah.
I guess it's a delayed
reaction or something.
Thanks.
- There you go.
- Could we stop by Linda's
so I can get something else to wear?
- Yeah, sure.
- Okay.
- I have some interesting news.
That school photograph you
saw at the Potter's house.
- Rosedale Hall?
- Yeah. It's in Galveston.
It's a special school.
- [Martha] Special how?
- For impaired children.
I'll get the car.
Mrs. Potter.
- Are you all right?
- I'm fine.
- How is your sister?
I came to check on her.
- Well she's going to be okay.
Mrs. Potter, could I talk to you?
- I can't.
- Mrs. Potter, your husband
said that you have only one son.
At your house there were two
boys in the photo next to you.
Why did you lie?
- I had two sons.
One is dead.
The other is fine.
In spite of what his father says.
- May I ask how your other son died?
- No.
- Mrs. Potter.
I know about Tina.
I know she's Archie's
daughter and used to bring her
to visit him.
Now the secrets that are buried here
are gonna come out with or without you.
You're gonna have to face that fact.
- You're doing real well, Brenda.
Keep going now.
Yeah.
There.
There you go. Good.
That a girl, Brenda.
- This the same school
you saw in the picture?
- Well, it looks like it.
- [Woman] We could just go down the block.
- Alright.
- Down the corner.
- [Woman] Ready for our field
to look so much better now.
- Well, I think it was the flowers here
that convinced Hilda Potter
this should be the home for her son.
- How'd he die?
- Uremia, poor little guy,
one thing after another.
- Well, what was the matter with him?
- Galactosemia.
- What's that?
Disturbance in the
metabolism of milk, sugar,
retardation, underdeveloped physically,
large liver and spleen.
- Brooke?
The kids said that there was
something strange about Tina.
They could've meant retarded.
- [Nurse] That's odd.
- What?
- Mrs. Potter comes to visit a young girl
that she and Mr. Potter
brought us about a year ago
from an institution.
Her name is Katie Bass,
but she calls herself Tina.
A lotta these paintings
on the wall are Katie's.
(residents chattering quietly)
Hi, Katie.
Someone wants to talk to you, sweetie.
- Hi.
- Did you paint this?
- Yeah.
- Oh it's a sunset. It's just beautiful.
- Thanks.
- You have her records?
- Of course.
- I'll bet they're forged.
- I beg your pardon.
- We have reason to believe
Katie Bass' real name is Tina Maddox.
- But the Potters themselves
brought her to us.
- Did you paint this for me?
- Yeah.
- Oh, thank you, Tina.
- Tina.
(ominous tones)
- [Eddie] Come on.
What's going on?
- Eddie, we need to talk.
- You kids go on, get in the house.
Come on, get in there. Come on.
- Eddie, I think I figured
a way outta this mess
you got us into.
- Mr. Potter, me and Linda...
(Eddie panting)
- Eddie?
Eddie?
- Oh baby.
- What happened?
What happened?
- They took the kids.
There was nothing I coulda done.
- Timothy!
Emily!
They've taken my kids!
- They'll be returned after I testify.
- It says after you
testify you saw nothing.
- I'm gonna call the police.
- No, you're not calling the police.
No police, no Akins, no nothing.
For a change you're gonna
do what you're told.
You've caused enough trouble already.
These are my kids.
You do what it says.
Do you hear me?
- Listen, you stay by the phone.
I gotta get me some stitches.
- [Linda] Where are you going?
Martha!
(doorbell rings)
(knocking at door)
- Mrs. Potter.
Mrs. Potter.
Mrs. Potter who painted this?
- (scoffs) Well wasn't Gauguin.
- Tina Maddox only with forged papers.
She's registered at
Rosedale Hall a Katie Bass.
You visit her there under that name.
But you took her to see her father, Archie
under her real name, Tina Maddox.
Archie loved that little girl.
But he never told anyone about her.
He and his wife were divorced.
Tina lived with her mother until she died.
And Archie had to put her an institution.
They just soak up love
when they're like that.
My son was-
- I know.
I know. And I'm so very, very sorry.
But now that's over.
Your husband murdered Archie Maddox.
And he stole his land.
And if we hadn't found Tina,
he might've gotten away with it.
That land belongs to her.
- Archie's death was an accident.
- Maybe.
But the second one wasn't.
I saw Larson killed. I saw Eddie do it.
And your husband was
standing right next to him.
Now they've kidnapped
my sister's children.
- They've gone too far to turn back now.
- Stop it.
(Hilda gasps)
(glass shatters)
Two children you love are going
to die unless you speak up.
(tense music)
(ominous music)
- What have you done?
What have you done?
(gunfire pops)
- Dangerous man, Jake.
- Who the hell is that?
- You better go on outta here.
- Linda, no.
- Eddie!
Where are they, Eddie?
- Easy, there was never no danger.
It was just like a big game to 'em, honey.
Okay? Take it easy, sweetie.
- Mommy! Mommy!
- Eddie!
Take your family in the trailer, Eddie.
Get 'em on in there so we can talk.
- We're leaving now.
Linda, get the kids in the truck.
You too.
- Do what I tell ya, Eddie.
Not this time.
- Hold it right there, son.
- You know it's funny you
callin' me son like that.
'Cause I always looked at you as a father.
Even when you was gonna dump me.
You and the others gonna let
me take the fall for all of ya.
And still I looked at you as a father.
And them as my family.
- We were just trying to motivate you.
- Oh, you got me real motivated,
Mr. Potter, real motivated.
One question.
Being that I owe you and all,
was you gonna ask me to
kill my kids for you too?
- Don't do anything stupid, Eddie.
- I'm gonna do something
smart for a change.
In fact, it's gonna hurt you all the more.
'Cause it was dumb ole Eddie
Pick that done it to y'all.
(gunfire pops)
(all screaming)
- Daddy!
- Eddie!
(gunfire pops)
(Doyle yells)
(Martha exclaims)
(body thuds)
(tense, sad music)
(train horn blows)
- I guess she's not coming.
- Just give her time, Martha.
She's lost a lot.
- I know.
What's gonna happen to Eddie?
- He'll testify against
Jake and the others,
they'll be bargaining from
murder one down to manslaughter,
most likely, maybe if he's lucky.
But the town will be dead to him
and to your sister too.
She and the kids'll need
you now more than ever.
(gentle music)
- Can the kids and I come visit ya?
- Do you want to?
- That's what families do, don't they?
- Are we a family?
- Yeah, we're a family.
- We'll work this out.
This time I'll be there for you.
- I know.
- [Conductor] All aboard.
- Thank you.
- [Conductor] Watch your step, please.
Welcome aboard, ma'am.
(train horn blows)
- I love you.
- I love you too.
(hopeful music)
(train horn blows)
(suspenseful dramatic music)
(bright chiming)