[ Rain and thunder ]
[ Laughs ]
[ Siren ]
[ Crash ]
LILY, WE DON'T
PLAY WITH OUR FOOD,
YOU KNOW THAT.
IT'S NUTRITION DAY.
WE'RE SUPPOSED
TO DRESS UP
LIKE VEGETABLES.
YOU'LL MAKE A
GOOD STRING BEAN.
I'M A ZUCCHINI,
REMEMBER?
RIGHT.
DAD, WALK ME TO SCHOOL.
I HAVE TO
GET TO WORK, LIL.
MRS. THAYLER
CAN WALK YOU UP.
[ Sigh ]
HEY, YOU PROMISED TO GET
ALONG WITH THIS NANNY.
SHE DOESN'T
EVEN LIKE ME.
OF COURSE
SHE LIKES YOU.
WHO DOESN'T
LIKE YOU?
I'LL WALK
WITH MY FRIENDS.
GOOD.
YOU JUST BE
GOOD, HUH?
YOU SHIP ME
500 HAPPY HOLLY DOLLS,
ALL WITHOUT EYEBALLS.
WHAT CAN I SAY, HAL?
IT WAS AN OVERSIGHT.
OVERSIGHT?
HILARIOUS.
HOW COULD THIS HAPPEN?
I DON'T MAKE THE DOLLS,
HAL, I JUST MARKET THEM.
YEAH, BUT YOUR FATHER,
MAY HE REST IN PEACE,
WOULD HAVE
CHECKED THEM FIRST.
AND THIS STUFF
NEVER HAPPENED WHEN
YOUR BROTHER WAS AROUND.
SURE IT DID, HAL.
JAKE.
REMEMBER THE PLAY TIME
DOLL LAST SEASON?
TOTAL AMPUTEE.
RELAX, RELAX, WE'LL GET
TAIWAN ON THE HORN,
THEY'LL FIX YOU UP.
EYEBALLS FOR EVERYONE.
YOU'D DO THAT
FOR ME?
I'LL DO ANYTHING
FOR YOU.
THANK YOU, JAKE.
ONCE AGAIN HE SWOOPS IN
AND SAVES THE DAY.
WELL SWOOP OUT,
I'M BUSY.
EVIDENTLY NOT
BUSY ENOUGH.
YOU KNOW,
I READ THE FIGURES.
SALES
HAVE SLIPPED 28%.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING
READING MY FIGURES?
YOU DON'T WORK HERE
ANYMORE, REMEMBER?
BESIDES IF IT'S ANY
OF YOUR BUSINESS,
I'M HIRING SOMEONE
TO HELP OUT WITH SALES.
WHOA, WHOA,
YOU'RE REPLACING ME?
NO, TO DO THAT I'D JUST
GET PART TIME HELP.
OH, THAT'S REALLY
FUNNY, MICHAEL.
GOT SOME NEW
P.R. LINED UP.
SOME GUY FROM
PRESCOTT AND SACHS
WHO IS SUPPOSED
TO WORK WONDERS.
IT SEEMS LIKE
A REALLY GOOD IDEA.
I'M GONNA GO SAY "HI"
TO EVERYBODY.
[ Teacher: ]
GIRLS, DO YOU KNOW
WHAT THIS IS?
THAT'S RIGHT,
IT'S AN ALLIGATOR.
YES, VERY GOOD.
WHAT ARE YOU,
BRIAN?
I AM A YAM.
IT'S NICE.
IT STINKS.
I'M THE BEST FRUIT
IN THE CLASS.
YEAH, BUT YOUR
MOTHER HELPED YOU,
RUTH MURRAY TOLD ME,
AND WE WERE SUPPOSED
TO DO IT OURSELVES.
WELL, YOU HAD TO MAKE
YOURS YOURSELF.
YOUR MOTHER'S DEAD.
HER MOTHER'S DEAD!
[ Raspberry ]
CAN YOU HOLD
ON A SEC?
ATTRACTIVE.
DID YOU CALL TAIWAN?
OH, THE MUTANT
DOLL THING.
CAN I CALL YOU
RIGHT BACK?
DO ME A FAVOR, JAKE.
DON'T TALK TO MY CLIENTS.
LINDA, GET ME PHIL IN TAIWAN.
INCREDIBLE.
I COME BEARING YOUR
FUTURE HAPPINESS.
GWEN, MICHAEL.
I JUST PEELED THIS THING
OFF HER FACE THIS MORNING.
THIS IS WHAT YOU'VE
BEEN DOING?
THAT JUST HAPPENS
TO BE THE FACE OF
A BEAUTIFUL MODEL
WHO WANTS TO MEET
YOU TONIGHT.
I CAN'T, I'M SWAMPED.
BESIDES, SHE HAS
THE PERSONALITY OF A ROCK.
YOU KNOW, MICHAEL,
YOU'VE BEEN OUT TWICE
IN THE LAST 18 MONTHS.
MAKE MORE OF AN EFFORT
TO ENJOY YOURSELF.
OKAY.
GIVE ME A CALL WHEN
MY BROTHER GETS BACK.
[ Secretary: ]
Michael, Phil is one one
and Miss Costello on two.
WHO?
Lily's teacher.
MY NIECE IS IN
TROUBLE AGAIN?
HELLO, MISS COSTELLO?
YEAH.
AGAIN, HUH?
[ Sighs ]
TAXI!
[ Tires screech ]
DO YOU WANT
A RIDE OR WHAT?
23 WILLOW STREET.
DON'T SPEED AND DON'T
RACE THE LIGHTS.
[ Engine roars, tires screech ]
HEY, SWEETIE.
TALKED TO YOUR
TEACHER TODAY.
WE'VE TALKED
ABOUT THIS, LIL.
YOU'RE NOT
SUPPOSED TO HIT.
MIK SAID...
I KNOW,
IT WAS THOUGHTLESS AND CRUEL
AND SHE HURT YOUR FEELINGS.
BUT YOU KNOW
WHAT YOU DO?
IGNORE IT.
JUST TUNE IT OUT.
IS THAT WHAT
YOU DO?
YEAH, THAT'S
WHAT I DO...
OR I CALL
THE TICKLE MONSTER!
[ Giggles ]
COME HERE, YOU!
I AIN'T GONNA
FIGHT YOU.
I AM.
HEY!
KEEP AWAY FROM
MY LITTLE SISTER.
HEY!
SWEETHEART!
LET ME GO!
HEY.
HEY, YOU'RE BLEEDING.
WHY DON'T WE GET YOU
FIXED UP THERE, ROCKY.
ORDER'S UP.
YOU'RE EGGS
ARE READY.
WHAT IS THIS,
FIRST AID?
YOU HAVE CUSTOMERS.
THEY'LL WAIT, JERRY.
YOU WANT ANOTHER ONE?
NO THANKS.
I'M PROBABLY LATE
FOR SCHOOL ALREADY.
THANKS.
I'M LILY.
I'M FAITH.
SEE YOU, FAITH.
THANK YOU.
[ Music box playing ]
MR. BEDFORD.
GOOD MORNING.
I'M BRENDA HYATT.
FROM PRESCOTT AND SACHS.
RIGHT,
THE P.R. FIRM.
I WAS EXPECTING MARK.
I ASKED TO HANDLE YOUR
ACCOUNT PERSONALLY.
I HOPE YOU DON'T MIND.
NO.
I GOT HERE EARLY.
I LIKE TO WALK
AROUND FIRST,
GET A FEEL
OF THE PLACE
BY MYSELF.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
I THINK I SEE
GREAT POTENTIAL.
[ Kids yelling ]
HEY, COME BACK!
GIVE IT TO ME,
GIVE IT TO ME!
HEY, SLOW IT DOWN!
FRANK!
STOP BOTHERING PEOPLE!
HEY! CAN'T YOU GUYS
PLAY NICE?
SO, YOU FIGURE OUT WHAT
YOU WANT TO BE YET?
I MEAN A PERSON
GOES TO COLLEGE TO,
YOU KNOW,
BE SOMETHING, RIGHT?
YEAH, I WANT TO BE A TEACHER
AND WORK WITH KIDS.
YOU KNOW THAT, ROBERTA.
THAT'S GONNA MAKE
YOU HAPPY?
YEAH, IT IS.
FAITH. FAMILY, FAITH.
YOUR OWN KIDS.
THAT'S HAPPINESS.
HEY, STOP BEATING
YOUR BROTHER!
[ Horn fanfare ]
UNCLE RICHIE'S HERE!
WHO INVITED HIM?
I DID.
HE'S FAMILY.
NO, HE AIN'T.
[ Sigh ]
ISN'T!
RICHIE.
FAITHIE?
I TOLD YOU I GOT
A PAPER TO FINISH.
WHAT, THAT MEANS
I DON'T EAT?
HI, HANDSOME!
HEY,
BELLISSIMA MAMA, DAD.
I'VE BEEN SMELLING
YOUR CHICKEN
FOR 10 BLOCKS NOW.
I MARINATED JUST
FOR YOU, RICHIE.
MA!
WHAT?
I THOUGHT WE AGREED
TO COOL IT FOR AWHILE.
WHAT, IN THIS HEAT?
HOW COME HE CAN'T
COME IN, FAITH?
I WOULD, I CAN'T GET PAST
THE GATEKEEPER HERE.
COME ON, FAITH!
YEAH, FAITH,
WHY CAN'T I COME IN?
LOOK, I BROUGHT
YOU MELON.
JUST FOR YOU.
COME ON.
I DON'T BELIEVE THIS.
BELIEVE IT.
JUST DON'T
MAKE A MESS.
HEY, HEY!
GIMME THAT MELON,
YOU.
CAN I COME?
SORRY, LILY,
YOU COULDN'T KEEP UP.
STAY HERE AND PLAY
WITH MRS. THALER.
SO, HOW LONG BEFORE
THE DIPLOMA, FAITH?
I THINK WE'RE TALKING
NEXT CENTURY HERE.
COLLEGE IS NICE,
BUT CAN SHE MAKE
A GOOD PENNE?
SHE TOASTS A
MEAN POP TART.
WHAT IS THIS STUFF?
RECURRING MOTIFS.
DICKEN-SIGH-ON,
WHAT IS THIS?
LOOK IT SAYS
DICKEN-SIGH-ON.
IS THAT WHAT
IT SAYS HERE?
YOU WOULDN'T KNOW,
WOULD YOU, RICHIE?
I JUST WANT TO KNOW
WHAT YOU DO ALL DAY.
WHY DON'T YOU JUST
GROW UP, RICHIE.
WHAT DOES IT MEAN?
GIVE IT TO ME.
RICHARD!
WHAT'D I SAY?
DON'T GO, HONEY.
DON'T.
MA, I GOTTA GO.
I MEAN, I GOTTA
GET OUT OF HERE.
WHAT DID I DO, WHAT'S
THE MATTER WITH HER?
[ Panting ]
BRENDA.
HI.
WHAT A GREAT SURPRISE.
COOL DOWN?
YEAH.
DO YOU ALWAYS
RUN ALONE?
NOW I DO.
SORRY ABOUT
YOUR WIFE.
IT'S NOT A SECRET,
IS IT?
NO, OF COURSE NOT.
I HATE RUNNING
ALONE.
HEY, MAYBE WE COULD
MEET UP HERE AND GO
TOGETHER SOMETIMES.
MAYBE, BUT MY RUNNING
IS KIND OF SPUR OF
THE MOMENT RIGHT NOW.
SHHOOO
I'M SUPER GIRL.
REMOVE YOUR LEGS OR I'LL
SNAP THEM LIKE TWIGS
WITH MY SUPERHUMAN STRENGTH.
QUIET. PLAY QUIET!
"QUIET, PLAY QUIET!"
[ Sniffs ]
FIRE, THERE'S A FIRE!
I'M SERIOUS, COME ON!
FIRE!
F-FIRE!
[ Siren and horn honks ]
GET THAT LINE READY!
COME ON, HURRY UP.
WHERE DID THE FIRE
START, MA'AM?
[ Car honks ]
WICKED, WICKED CHILD!
WHAT HAPPENED?
LEAVE ME ALONE.
WHERE'S LILY?
OATMEAL-FLINGING BRAT!
LILY! LILY!
HI.
I THINK I BURNT
MY HOUSE DOWN.
OH, UH.
COME ON IN.
YOU OKAY?
I'M SORRY.
C'MERE, YOU!
WOW, MY NIECE,
THE ARSONIST.
HOW DID THIS HAPPEN?
I THINK SHE WAS TRYING
TO ROAST MARSHMALLOWS.
NOT THIS, JAKE,
NOT THE FIRE.
THIS, ALL OF THIS!
IT'S LIKE EVERYTHING
WAS OKAY.
EVERYTHING WAS SO GOOD.
AND THEN IN ONE SECOND.
WHY DIDN'T I DRIVE
THAT NIGHT?
BECAUSE A CAB WAS EASIER
AND IT'S TOO HARD
TO PARK DOWNTOWN.
PLEASE DON'T DO THIS TO
YOURSELF AGAIN, MICHAEL.
YEAH, BUT IT WAS
RAINING SO HARD.
AND THAT DRIVER.
HEY, HEY, IT'S OKAY.
I'M ALL RIGHT.
YOU KNOW,
IT'S OKAY NOT TO BE.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO BE
SUCH A TOUGH GUY
ALL THE TIME.
THANKS FOR THE
ADVICE, BRO.
I MEAN, I MEAN IT.
IT'S LIKE YOU'RE WALKING
AROUND ON AUTO PILOT.
IT'S BEEN A LONG
DAY, JAKE.
LET IT GO.
I HAVE, MIKEY.
I'VE LET IT GO FOR
OVER A YEAR NOW,
BUT YOU GOTTA KNOW
YOU'RE NOT FOOLING
ANYONE.
YOU THROUGH?
NO!
YEAH.
WHAT A MESS.
IN THE KITCHEN.
YES, SIR.
NO CHILD CARE
EXPERIENCE?
SEVEN BROTHERS AND
SISTERS, HONEY.
THAT'S CHILD CARE
EXPERIENCE.
SWEETHEART,
DON'T WORRY.
I LOVE KIDS!
BAKED WITH A
SIDE OF FRIES!
HA HA HA!
WAIT UP!
FAITH!
HEY, YOU!
YOU'VE GOT A LOT
OF STUFF THERE.
YEAH, NO MORE SCHOOL!
YEAH, FOR ME TOO.
[ Knocking ]
YEAH, YEAH!
LET'S CELEBRATE.
OKAY.
HOW ABOUT IF WE SET
YOU RIGHT THERE?
HOW ABOUT A MILK SHAKE?
OKAY, GREAT.
HEY, MACK!
WHAT, I HAD TO
PICK UP MY GRADES.
KNOW WHAT I GOT?
DO I LOOK
LIKE I CARE?
HERE'S YOUR APRON.
JERRY.
JERRY, I BEEN HERE TOO LONG
AND I'M TOO GOOD.
I AM NOT PUTTIN' UP
WITH THAT SCHEDULE.
I QUIT!
YOU CAN'T QUIT,
I JUST FIRED YOU!
C'MON, LIL,
LET'S GO.
DON'T EVEN THINK
OF COMIN' BACK FOR
YOUR LAST PAYCHECK.
B+, B+,
A-, A!
THAT'S WHAT I GOT!
I CAN'T BELIEVE
I'M DONE.
I DON'T HAVE
TO TOUCH ANOTHER BOOK
FOR THE WHOLE SUMMER.
I DON'T HAVE TO,
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT,
I WANT TO.
WHY?
I LIKE TO READ.
READING IS LIKE,
WELL--
IT'S LIKE A WHOLE
DIFFERENT WORLD
IN EVERY BOOK.
KIND OF LIKE TRAVELING,
ONLY CHEAPER.
HEY, I LIVE REALLY
CLOSE TO HERE,
YOU WANNA COME
PLAY AT MY HOUSE?
I CAN'T LIL.
I GOTTA GO.
YOU TAKE CARE
THOUGH, OKAY?
OKAY.
THANK YOU, PEARL,
THANKS FOR COMING.
YOU SURE YOU CAN MAKE IT
DOWN THE STAIRS?
GOOD. OKAY.
WATCH THE DOOR MAT.
DON'T RUN
ANYBODY OVER.
WELL, LOOKS LIKE IT'S
THE ONE WITH THE BOILS.
NO, NO.
I'LL GET NIGHTMARES
FROM HER.
COME ON, WHO'S
NEXT, MIKE?
I'LL BET
SHE'S THE ONE.
COME ON.
AMY KWAN?
FAITH ZACARELLI.
FAITH!
HEY, YOU!
YOU TOOK OFF AND LEFT ME
WITH YOUR BOOKS.
GOOD THING YOUR
ADDRESS WAS IN THEM.
DAD, FAITH FIXED
MY KNEE.
WHAT'S WRONG
WITH YOUR KNEE?
LILY--
COME SEE MY ROOM.
I'M MICHAEL,
LILY'S FATHER.
YOWZA! HOW MANY
PEOPLE LIVE HERE?
JUST US.
IT'S BEAUTIFUL.
THE WHOLE STREET.
THIS IS MY
BROTHER, JAKE.
JAKE, THIS IS FAITH,
LILY'S FRIEND.
COME UP.
HER, MIKEY.
I, UH, PICK HER.
EHHH...
AMY KWAN.
COME ON IN.
COME ON.
COME IN
THE DOOR.
COME ON,
THIS WAY.
IN THAT CHAIR,
RIGHT THERE, THAT'S IT.
I SEE YOU
LIKE TO COOK.
C...COOK.
COOK.
UMMM...COOK?
YOU'VE HAD
EIGHT NANNIES.
WHY?
WHY WOULD
THEY LEAVE?
MRS. THALER BECAUSE
OF THE FIRE, I GUESS.
AND I GAVE HILDA
A NERVOUS TIC.
AND ESPERANZA HAD ALL THESE
BOTTLES EVERYWHERE.
AND ALL THEY HAVE TO DO
IS LOOK AFTER YOU?
YEAH, AND HELP
COOK AND CLEAN.
HMM.
THANK YOU
VERY MUCH.
WONDERFUL INTERVIEW,
WATCH YOUR STEP,
TAKE CARE NOW.
WATCH THE STAIRS.
WELL?
I'M SORRY, LIL,
NO LUCK TODAY.
MR. BEDFORD, YOUR LUCK'S
ABOUT TO CHANGE.
LET'S TALK.
KEEP PUSHIN'!
SHUT UP!
FOR DIRTY LAUNDRY.
MA! SHE'S NOT MOVIN'
TO EUROPE,
MA, IT'S 10 MINUTES AWAY.
IT DON'T MATTER,
SHE'S LEAVIN'
AND ALL THE DREAMS
I HAD IN MY HEAD.
I ALWAYS THOUGHT MY
TWO DAUGHTERS WOULD
LIVE DOWN THE STREET,
MY GRAND KIDS
WOULD COME OVER,
I'D HAVE LOTS OF
COOKIES FOR THEM.
MA, I AM
STILL HERE,
I STAYED RIGHT
WHERE I BELONG.
I'M SORRY, WAS THAT
DIRECTED TOWARDS ME?
DID I SAY ANYTHING?
YEAH, I THINK YOU
SAID SOMETHING.
I AM NOT THE ONE
LEAVING TO PLAY HOUSE
WITH MR. RICH SNOB.
WHAT IS RICHIE
GOING TO THINK?
I'LL TELL YOU.
HE THINKS IT STINKS.
JUST WALK RIGHT ON IN,
WHY DON'T YOU?
THIS WHOLE THING JUST
DON'T SIT RIGHT WITH ME.
OH NO?
NO.
WELL YOU KNOW WHAT?
THIS JOB IS
PERFECT FOR ME.
I GET PAID TO TAKE CARE
OF A SWEET LITTLE GIRL,
AND WHEN SCHOOL STARTS
I WILL HAVE PLENTY OF TIME
FOR MY CLASSES.
BUT YOU'RE LIVIN'
WITH A TOTAL STRANGER.
RIGHT.
HE COULD BE DANGEROUS.
THE MAN SELLS TOYS.
YOU'RE MAKIN' A BIG
MISTAKE, FAITH.
I'VE BEEN PATIENT WITH YOU,
I LET YOU DO THE
LITTLE SCHOOL THING.
WAIT, WAIT, WAIT.
YOU LET ME?
YOU LEAVE NOW,
IT'S OVER.
THAT'S NOT TO SAY
I WON'T RECONSIDER.
JUST BACK OFF.
FOR NOW, HUH?
GIVE ME SOME SPACE
LIKE YOU PROMISED.
MA, I'LL CALL YOU.
OKAY.
WHAT DO YOU THINK
ABOUT SOME BOOGEYIN'?
NOOO!
OH, YES!
[ Music plays ]
LET'S GO.
COME ON, GIRLIE.
SPIN.
THERE YOU GO.
½ SOMETIMES THIS LIFE
CAN GET YOU DOWN. ½
½ DOWN AND DIRTY BABY. ½
½ FEELS LIKE YOU'RE
SPINNIN' ROUND AND ROUND. ½
½ OUTTA CONTROL NOW, HONEY. ½
[ Music continues
from upstairs ]
TAKE IT...
MICHAEL!
[ Music stops ]
MY OFFICE IS RIGHT
BELOW THIS ROOM.
OOH, SORRY.
LILY, GIVE US
A MINUTE, WILL YOU?
OKAY.
WHAT, WHAT'D I DO?
LOOK, FAITH,
I GOTTA TELL YOU.
YOU WALKED IN HERE
OFF THE STREET
WITH NO EXPERIENCE,
BARELY AN INTERVIEW,
NOTHING.
STILL, I WAS WILLING
TO GIVE YOU A CHANCE
BECAUSE LILY
LIKED YOU,
MY BROTHER LIKED YOU,
AND I WAS DESPERATE.
YOU ARE
SUCH A CHARMER.
LOOK.
JUST KEEP LILY
HAPPY AND SAFE,
WE WILL GIVE EACH OTHER
PRIVACY AND RESPECT,
AND I AM SURE THAT EVERYTHING
WILL WORK OUT JUST FINE.
[ Car door slams ]
[ Stairs creak ]
WATCH IT!
OH, I AM SORRY.
I, UM,--
I WAS LOOKING
FOR A BOOK.
OKAY, I WAS LOOKING
FOR YOUR SAFE.
LOOK, IT'S JUST
THAT YOU'RE NEW
AND YOU STARTLED ME.
I KNOW, I SHOULDN'T
HAVE COME IN HERE.
YOU KNOW, THE PRIVACY
RULE THING,
BUT I COULDN'T SLEEP,
AND YOU'VE GOT ALL
THESE BOOKS!
YOU'VE GOT DICKENS!
YOU LIKE DICKENS.
YEAH, I LOVE HIM.
DAVID COPPERFIELD?
UH...
BLEAK HOUSE?
DO YOU HAVE
GREAT EXPECTATIONS?
I DID.
OH, WOW, THESE BOOKS MUST
HAVE COST YOU A FORTUNE.
I GOT THEM AS
AN ENGAGEMENT PRESENT.
YOU GOT BOOKS?
I'D GET DISH TOWELS.
I MEAN, YOU KNOW,
IF I EVER GOT ENGAGED.
WHICH -- BOY,
THEY WANT ME TO.
WHICH, YOU KNOW,
I'M NOT.
WOW, SHE WAS BEAUTIFUL.
LILY GOT HER EYES.
I HOPE THAT HELPS
YOU SLEEP.
THE BOOK.
OH! I'LL BE UP
ALL NIGHT READING NOW.
AND I WON'T DISTURB
YOU AGAIN.
AND I'M SORRY ABOUT
THE LADDER THING.
[ Knocking ]
WORKING HARD?
JUST HANDS ON
PRODUCT TESTING.
THAT LOOKS LIKE FUN.
YEAH, BUT IT'S
NOT FOR US.
IT'S TOO COMPLICATED.
KIDS TODAY, THEY DON'T
HAVE THE PATIENCE,
AND NEITHER DO I.
I SET UP A LUNCH FOR YOU
WITH THE TOY CAMP PEOPLE.
THEY'RE LOOKING
FOR RACE CARS.
RACE CARS?
I HAVEN'T SIGNED
AN ACCOUNT YET.
TOY CAMP DOESN'T
KNOW THAT.
GET THEM HOOKED,
THEN SIGN THE CARS.
HOW ABOUT DINNER?
NO, LUNCH
WILL BE FINE.
NOT WITH TOY CAMP,
WITH ME.
YOU HAVE
EATEN BEFORE.
DAILY, YEAH.
I CAN'T FACE ANOTHER NIGHT
OF TAKE OUT ALL ALONE.
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
DINNER SOUNDS GOOD.
GOOD.
SO FRANK SAYS TO ME,
"I'M GOIN' BOWLIN'."
WELL, IT'S NOT
EVEN LEAGUE NIGHT.
SO I SAY, "SURE, FINE."
THEN I GO TO THE CLOSET,
THE BALL'S STILL THERE.
OH, ROBERTA.
SO, HE BOUGHT A NEW BALL.
SO WHAT CAN YOU SAY?
WELL, I HOPE HE BOUGHT
A NEW BALL,
BECAUSE HE'S GOT
SOMETHING ON THE WAY.
HEY, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
HELP!
HEY, HEY! LILY!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
WE DON'T HIT, LIL.
WELL ANTHONY--
ANTHONY WAS WRONG,
BUT YOU WERE
WRONG TOO.
NOW APOLOGIZE.
YOU CAN'T
TELL ME.
YOU HURT HIM, LILY.
I DON'T CARE!
SAY YOU'RE SORRY!
NO, YOU'RE NOT
MY MOTHER!
LILY, COME BACK!
HEY.
WOULD YOU LOOK AT ME?
YOU KNOW, I'D NEVER TRY
TO BE YOUR MOM, LIL.
I JUST WANT
TO BE YOUR FRIEND.
YOU MUST HAVE HAD
A WONDERFUL MOM.
YOU MUST MISS
HER A LOT.
WOULD YOU TELL ME
ABOUT HER?
WHAT?
WOULD YOU TELL ME
ABOUT YOUR MOM?
TELL ME WHAT
SHE WAS LIKE.
WHAT IS IT,
SWEETIE?
NO ONE EVER ASKS
ME ABOUT...
NO ONE EVER TALKED
TO ME ABOUT HER.
YOU CAN TALK
TO ME, LIL.
YOU CAN TALK TO ME
ABOUT ANYTHING.
[ Phone rings ]
KEEP STIRRING.
HELLO?
HEY, FAITH,
HOW'S LIL?
I'M GOING TO BE HOME
LATE TONIGHT.
BUT MICHAEL,
LILY AND I MADE SAUCE,
YOU KNOW, FRESH
FROM TOMATOES,
AND SHE REALLY
WANTS YOU TO...
--WON'T IT KEEP?
YOU WANT TEX-MEX
OR THAI?
SHE'S BARELY
SEEN YOU THIS WEEK.
SHE'S GONNA WANT
TO STAY UP.
SHE SHOULDN'T DO THAT.
She shouldn't
have to.
LOOK, I'VE
GOT TO GO.
LET'S TALK ABOUT
THIS LATER.
BYE.
HEY.
YOU KNOW WHAT THE
BEST THING ABOUT
THIS SAUCE IS?
IT TASTES EVEN
BETTER THE NEXT DAY.
KEEP STIRRING.
SO, I'M VERY,
VERY STILL,
AND I LOOK UP,
AND I SEE THREE
MOUNTED HEADS,
A LION, A BUFFALO,
AND A WILDEBEEST,
AND I THINK, "I HAVE GOT
TO GET OUT OF HERE!"
[ Laughs ]
WHAT'S THIS,
NO TIE?
IT'S SATURDAY.
THAT'S RIGHT, MICHAEL,
I'M OFF TODAY.
IS LILY EATING
THAT JUNK?
THAT WOULD BE MINE.
HAVE YOU EVER
TRIED IT?
IN THIRD GRADE.
OKIE DOKIE.
YOU KNOW, I THINK LILY'S
REALLY HURTING.
SHE HASN'T DEALT WITH ALL
THE STUFF ABOUT HER MOM.
SHE JUST NEEDS
SOME MORE TIME.
WHAT SHE NEEDS
IS HER DAD.
LOOK, THE ONE PERSON SHE NEEDS
TO TALK TO WON'T DO IT.
WHAT ARE YOU,
A PSYCH MAJOR?
ENGLISH.
AND I'M SORRY
IF YOU'RE INSULTED.
I'M JUST WORRIED
ABOUT HER.
FAITH, DO YOU WANT TO RIDE
ON THE BIKE PATH WITH ME?
FAITH'S OFF TODAY, LILY.
BUT NEXT WEEK, OKAY?
HEY, I DON'T KNOW
IF YOU REMEMBER,
BUT I'M JUST ABOUT THE
FASTEST DAD ON TWO WHEELS.
YOU'LL GO WITH ME,
LIKE WE USED TO?
LET'S ROLL, KIDDO!
EXCUSE ME.
YOU MUST BE JAKE.
AND YOU MUST
BE BRENDA.
I GUESS NO ONE TOLD YOU
THAT MY OFFICE IS TO
REMAIN EMPTY, SACRED.
LIKE A SHRINE.
BRENDA'S BEEN
INCREDIBLE.
I'VE MADE MORE CONTACTS THIS
MONTH, CLOSED MORE DEALS.
AND ON TOP OF EVERYTHING
SHE'S REORGANIZED MY ENTIRE
MARKETING DEPARTMENT.
REALLY?
I GOT A SOCK DRAWER
AT HOME THAT COULD
USE A LITTLE HELP.
DID I TELL YOU THAT
ASHLEY'S A DANCER
WITH MYTHOLOGIA.
MYTHOLOGIA.
I'D LOVE TO GO, BUT
SOLD OUT FOR MONTHS.
WELL, WHEN DO YOU
WANT TO COME?
I'LL GET YOU TICKETS.
YOU'RE WONDERFUL.
ASHLEY'S GREAT.
YEAH, SO WHAT ABOUT YOU,
YOU OKAY WITH THIS WOMAN?
YOU DON'T
LIKE BRENDA?
NO, I LIKE HER,
I LIKE HER.
I JUST THOUGHT YOU MIGHT
WANT SOMEONE WHO WOULD
LIGHTEN THINGS UP A BIT.
BRENDA IS AS LIGHT
AS A TRUCK.
WELL, SHE
MEANS WELL.
SALES ARE UP,
WE GOT A COUPLE
OF NEW LINES.
WELL, SHE'S GOOD
WITH THE BUSINESS,
BUT DO YOU LIKE HER?
WELL, WE HAVE
SIMILAR INTERESTS,
COMMON BACKGROUNDS.
[ Snores ]
JAKE, SHE HELPS ME.
WHAT DO YOU WANT
ME TO SAY?
THAT YOU LIKE HER!
LOOK, MIKEY, I JUST WANT
YOU TO BE HAPPY.
AS LONG AS BRENDA MAKES
YOU HAPPY, I LOVE HER.
HEY! WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
WHAT, DO YOU LIVE HERE
OR SOMETHING?
THAT'S RIGHT.
YOU'RE HIM.
YOU'RE THE GUY.
CAN I HELP YOU?
YEAH.
GIVE THIS TO FAITH.
TELL HER I FIXED IT.
TELL HER THE
R WORKS NOW.
AND TELL HER I THINK
SCHOOL'S OKAY.
WHO ARE YOU?
WHO AM I?
YEAH.
I'M THE GUY WHO'S GOING TO
BUST YOUR FACE IF YOU TOUCH HER.
CAPISCE?
SI.
OH, THE TYPEWRITER.
RIGHT.
LET'S SEE,
THE R WORKS NOW.
SOME CHAUFFEUR FIXED IT.
HE THINKS SCHOOL IS OKAY.
AND HE'LL BUST MY FACE
IF I TOUCH YOU.
THAT WAS RICHIE.
OH, RICHIE.
SURE.
HE'S UM..
WELL, WE'VE BEEN...
INVOLVED FOR SOME TIME NOW.
TANGLED UP
IS MORE LIKE IT.
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT,
FAITH?
ACTUALLY, NO.
THERE ARE ALL
THESE EXPECTATIONS,
YOU KNOW?
LIKE WHAT I WANT,
AND WHAT RICHIE WANTS,
AND WHAT EVERYONE
IN MY NEIGHBORHOOD WANTS.
AND THEY JUST
ALL KEEP SMASHING UP
AGAINST EACH OTHER.
SO I'M JUST A LITTLE
CONFUSED RIGHT NOW.
I'M SURE YOU'LL
FIGURE THINGS OUT.
I HOPE SO.
BREAKIN' IT OFF
WITH RICHIE...
THE PAST CAN HAVE
SUCH A HOLD ON YOU, HUH?
YEAH.
YOU KNOW, LILY'S BEEN TALKING
ABOUT HER, LITTLE BY LITTLE.
I THINK IT'S A COMFORT
IN A WAY.
YOU KNOW, THAT
TYPEWRITER OF YOURS
IS AN ANTIQUE.
WHY DON'T YOU TRY
THIS SYSTEM?
YOUR COMPUTER?
SURE, I'LL TEACH YOU.
NOW?
YOU GOT SOMEPLACE
ELSE TO GO?
ALL RIGHT, HAL,
LET'S TOUGHEN IT UP,
LET'S MAKE IT STERN.
GRR, I'M A TOY MAN.
DON'T TAKE MY PICTURE!
YOU JUST
NEED TO RELAX.
HAVE FUN.
OKAY.
RELAX!
YOU'RE LOOKIN'
GREAT.
HAVE FUN!
RELAX!
OKAY, MICHAEL,
HERE IT IS.
HEY!
EXCELLENT!
LOVIN' IT!
THAT'S IT, BEAUTIFUL.
THAT'S IT, MICHAEL.
BEAUTIFUL!
AWESOME!
EXCELLENT!
IT'S GREAT.
HE DOESN'T LOOK
VERY IMPOSING.
BRENDA,
THE MAN REPS TOYS,
NOT THE PENTAGON.
MICHAEL, WE'RE DONE.
HEY, COME HERE!
DADDY, ARE YOU
WEARING MAKEUP?
THIS PLACE, FANTASTIC.
MY NEPHEWS WOULD
DESTROY IT.
[ Singing: ]
I KNOW WHO THIS IS.
I'M BRENDA.
I'M A FRIEND
OF YOUR DADDY'S.
BRENDA HYATT,
THIS IS FAITH ZACARELLI.
NICE TO MEET YOU.
AND I THOUGHT NANNIES
HAD BLUE HAIR AND WORE
UNIFORMS WITH WHITE SHOES.
SOME OF THEM DO.
OH, SHE IS SO ADORABLE!
SO, WHAT ARE YOU
GUYS DOING HERE?
WE'RE GOING
TO THE PETTING ZOO.
WANNA COME?
WE'D LOVE TO!
GREAT!
IT'S SO SOFT!
COME ON IN, BRENDA,
THEY JUST WANT TO MEET YOU.
THEY WANT TO BITE
MY THUMBS OFF,
THAT'S WHAT THEY WANT.
OH, THEY'RE
REAL GENTLE. SEE?
I'M NOT EXACTLY
DRESSED FOR THIS.
BESIDES A HORSE ONCE
STEPPED ON MY FOOT,
AND I CAN'T STAND
THE THOUGHT OF HOOVES.
OH! HI THERE.
BRENDA, THEY AREN'T
GOING TO BITE.
SHOO, SHOO,
GET AWAY FROM MY FEET.
MICHAEL!
BREAK IT UP,
BREAK IT UP.
I GUESS THE GOATS
AREN'T YOUR THING.
LET'S GO, FELLAS.
YES!
YOU'RE VERY LITTLE,
BUT VERY SCARY.
OOO!
TRY THE DUCKS.
I LIKE THE DUCKS.
LILY, WANT TO FEED
THE DUCKS WITH ME?
I DID THE DUCKS.
DO THEM AGAIN!
I DON'T WANT TO!
[ Laughs ]
HEY, HEY!
OH!
MICHAEL, MICHAEL!
MICHAEL!
OH!
OH! MY SHOE!
COME HOME
WITH US NOW.
I'D LOVE TO, LIL,
BUT I'VE GOT A BUNCH
OF MEETINGS TODAY.
BUT SURPRISE ME
AGAIN SOON, OKAY?
PLEASURE MEETING
YOU, FAITH.
YEAH.
SORRY, YOU KNOW,
ABOUT YOUR SHOES.
MY FAULT, REALLY.
I SHOULD HAVE BEEN
SMART AND WORN RATTY
OLD SNEAKERS LIKE YOU.
AND AS FOR YOU,
I'LL SEE YOU SOON,
PUMPKIN.
I LIKE YOUR SHOES,
FAITH.
THANKS, LIL,
SO DO I.
WHO IS SHE?
SHE'S-- A FRIEND
OF YOUR DAD'S.
I GOT PEOPLE
FROM FOUR DIFFERENT
GALLERIES INTERESTED.
WOW, I'M IMPRESSED.
YOU KNOW,
ASHLEY IS REALLY GOING
TO BE DISAPPOINTED
IF YOU DON'T GO
SEE HER DANCE.
SO COME WITH ME.
NO, 12 TIMES
IS MY LIMIT.
I CAN'T GO ALONE,
IT'S DEPRESSING.
GWEN IS AVAILABLE.
I'LL GO ALONE.
BUT YOU'RE
STILL WATCHING LILY,
BECAUSE FAITH'S OFF.
TAKE HER.
FAITH?
YEAH, WHY NOT?
SHE'S GREAT, MICHAEL.
SHE'S THE NANNY.
OH, WHAT DIFFERENCE
DOES IT MAKE?
BESIDES, YOU SHOULDN'T
WASTE THE TICKET.
TAKE HER.
[ Computer beeps ]
WHATCHA DOIN'?
COMPUTERS FOR DUMMIES.
WHAT'S THAT?
IT'S JUST SOMETHING
I LIKED.
I SAW MY NAME.
WELL, MAYBE I'LL SHOW
IT TO YOU SOMETIME?
DO YOU NEED
YOUR COMPUTER?
NO, I JUST WANTED
TO SHOW YOU SOMETHING.
"I HAVE AN EXTRA
TICKET TO MYTHOLOGIA
TOMORROW NIGHT.
"WOULD YOU CARE
TO JOIN ME?"
FOR REAL?
WITH LILY?
JUST US.
JUST US?
AS FRIENDS.
WE'RE FRIENDS?
I SAY...OKAY.
HEY, WAIT,
DO YOU KNOW HOW
TO ERASE THIS?
[ Computer beeps ]
MMM.
GOOD NIGHT, SLUGGER.
THANKS, JAKE.
LILY REALLY LIKES
BEING WITH YOU.
I DON'T KNOW WHY.
FAITH, HOW DO YOU
PUT UP WITH THIS GUY?
HE PAYS ME.
CLEVER.
Michael...
WE CAN'T WATCH
A WHOLE SHOW LIKE THIS.
OUR NECKS WILL SPASM.
THERE ARE TWO SEATS
RIGHT DOWN FRONT.
FAITH, FAITH, IT'S
NOT A YANKEES' GAME.
WHAT?
IT'S AFTER 8:00.
THEY WON'T SHOW.
FAITH.
EXCUSE ME.
COME ON!
OH, I'M SORRY.
OH I KNOW THAT WAS
YOUR FOOT, I'M SORRY.
FAITH.
MICHAEL, COME ON.
OUR SEATS ARE RIGHT
DOWN THERE...B!
SORRY.
EXCUSE ME.
IT SAYS B, NOT P.
PARDON ME, SIR.
YOU CAN'T TELL ME
THIS ISN'T BETTER.
OH, YEAH, I'M MUCH
MORE COMFORTABLE NOW.
I'M GLAD TO SEE
YOU'RE ENJOYING THIS.
I AM.
GOOD.
ARE YOU?
YEAH.
REALLY?
YEAH, WHY?
I DON'T KNOW,
SOMETIMES IT'S HARD
TO TELL WITH YOU,
BECAUSE YOU'RE
JUST USUALLY SO --
SO WHAT?
I WORK FOR YOU.
NOT TONIGHT.
WHAT?
YOU'RE CERTAINLY
NOT THE LOOSEST
GUY IN THE WORLD.
I'M LOOSE.
I'M VERY LOOSE.
MICHAEL,
WE CHANGED OUR SEATS
IN THE THEATER,
AND YOU THOUGHT
WE'D GET ARRESTED.
I MEAN, COME ON,
YOU GOT TO ADMIT,
FOR A GUY
WHO SELLS TOYS,
YOU'RE PRETTY SERIOUS.
I'M SERIOUS
ABOUT SELLING TOYS.
YOU KNOW,
DON'T LISTEN TO ME.
I'M JUST USED TO
PEOPLE SAYING
EXACTLY WHAT THEY FEEL,
LOUD AND UGLY.
BUT YOU,
YOU'RE VERY CAREFUL.
YOU KNOW,
VERY THOUGHTFUL.
AND VERY
REPRESSED.
HOW ABOUT YOU?
ME?
WELL,
I'M NOT REPRESSED.
WELL, WHO'S TO KNOW?
I MEAN,
I DON'T KNOW A THING
ABOUT YOU OUTSIDE THE HOUSE,
EXCEPT FOR RICHIE.
YEAH, WELL RICHIE
IS NOT THE BE-ALL
END-ALL ANYMORE.
I'VE GOT TO STAY
FOCUSED ON SCHOOL.
WHAT DO YOU WANT
TO BE ANYWAY?
A TEACHER.
YOU'LL MAKE A
GREAT TEACHER,
FAITH.
I THINK SO TOO.
COME ON, MICHAEL.
THEY'RE GREAT!
[ Laughs ]
GO, FAITH!
C'MON, MICHAEL.
WHOO, MICHAEL!
HA HA HA!
[ Laughs ]
WELL, WE'RE HOME.
YEAH.
HOME.
WELL, LISTEN I...
THANK YOU, MICHAEL.
I HAD A GREAT
TIME TONIGHT.
ME TOO.
YEAH?
YEAH.
WELL, GOOD NIGHT,
THEN.
ARE YOU GOING
TO SLEEP?
YEAH.
GOOD NIGHT.
[ Stairs creak ]
[ Creaking again ]
ANYTHING GOOD?
OUCH.
YOU SCARED ME.
BAKING COOKIES,
HUH?
WHO SAID ANYTHING
ABOUT BAKING?
[ T.V.: ] The forecast, mostly
sunny skies today with brisk--
...fighting broke out over--
[ Changing channels ]
NOTHING BUT GILLIGAN.
WANT SOME HELP?
THANKS.
HURRY UP,
SLOW POKE!
I DIDN'T WANT
TO EMBARRASS YOU.
HELLO.
HI.
SO, LILY, YOU
STILL WANT TO GO
TO THE BLOCK PARTY?
YEAH!
OKAY,
GO GET CHANGED.
I'LL WAIT
FOR YOU.
GAME'S STARTING.
HUH?
YEAH.
I'LL GO MAKE
SURE IT DOES.
SO, YOU KNOW,
YOU CAN COME TOO.
YOU WANT ME TO?
WELL, YOU KNOW,
IF YOU WANT TO.
[ Sigh ]
HEY, QUIET DOWN,
FELLAS!
THE PRINCESS HAS ARRIVED
FROM HER PALACE.
PEASANT!
OUCH!
FAITHIE, COME ON!
DID SHE CALL
YOU A PEASANT?
HEY, FAITH, I AIN'T
WAITIN' FOR YOU, FAITH.
I AIN'T WAITIN'
FOR YOU FOREVER!
[ All talking at once ]
[ Talking and music ]
GET OUT OF HERE!
AH!
HEY!
DAD?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
ARE YOU
THE WATERMELON SNAGGER?
THAT WAS YOU,
WASN'T IT?
YES. IT WAS.
JOEY, YOUR MOM'S
LOOKIN' FOR YOU.
I GOT SOME ICED TEA
IF ANYBODY WANTS...
YOU MUST BE MICHAEL.
I'M SO GLAD
YOU COULD COME.
RUBY,
IT'S THE TOY GUY.
MA!
HONEY,
IT'S THE TOY GUY.
IT'S MICHAEL.
YEAH.
HI.
YEAH,
COME HERE,
I WANT YOU TO MEET
A FRIEND OF MINE,
MRS. LAMLIN.
OH MA, HE DOESN'T WANT
TO MEET MRS. LAMLIN.
SURE I DO,
I'D LOVE TO MEET
MRS. LAMLIN.
LAMLIN, RIGHT, RIGHT.
SHE WAS
AN OLYMPIC SWIMMER.
I'M TELLING YOU
SHE'S VERY INTERESTING.
FAITH!
IT WAS A FREAK
SWIMMING ACCIDENT.
YOU DON'T TELL ME
NOTHING NO MORE?
WHAT?
YOU KNOW, YOU
AND WONDER BOY.
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE
TALKING ABOUT.
FAITH, IT'S ME,
ROBERTA, YOUR SISTER.
THERE'S NOTHIN'
GOIN' ON.
RIGHT.
YOU KNOW WHAT,
JUST LEAVE
ME ALONE, OKAY?
FAITH.
FAITH. HI.
I, UM...
THINK WE NEED TO TALK
ABOUT LAST NIGHT.
LOOK, IT'S OKAY,
MICHAEL.
I MEAN,
IT'S NOTHIN'
SPECIAL.
[ Big band music ]
CHERRY'S THE BEST.
EXCUSE ME.
WE SHOULDN'T.
JUST DANCE.
HEY!
I TOLD YOU
TO LAY OFF HER.
RICHIE, WHAT
IS WRONG WITH YOU?
HEY, HEY!
I TOLD YOU, FRANKIE!
WHAT'S THE MATTER
WITH YOU?
GO HOME, RICHARD.
RICHIE, LISTEN
TO MY MOM.
NO!
MY NEIGHBORHOOD!
HE GOES.
YOU, YOU GO!
NO, MICHAEL,
YOU STAY.
WHAT ARE YOU CAUSING
TROUBLE FOR?
IT'S A PARTY.
MICHAEL, WHAT'S
GOING ON?
MICHAEL! MICHAEL,
I'M SO SORRY.
RICHIE, I TOLD YOU
TO GO HOME!
COME ON, WE'RE
GOING TO PUT A NICE
COLD CLOTH ON THAT.
ICE, GET ICE!
I CAME HOME EARLY
TO SURPRISE YOU,
AND YOU SURPRISE ME.
BRENDA,
HOW DID YOU
FIND ME HERE?
JAKE TOLD ME.
I LOVE MY BROTHER.
OW!
WHAT DO YOU EXPECT,
COMING TO THIS
NEIGHBORHOOD?
WHAT HAPPENED ANYWAY?
DADDY WAS DANCING
WITH FAITH,
AND THEN THAT GUY
STARTED HITTING.
LILY--
YOU WERE DANCING
WITH FAITH?
YEAH, AND THEN
THE GUY STARTED
PUNCHING AND EVERYTHING --
LILY,
WHY DON'T YOU GO
GRAB ME A PEPSI.
I'D FEEL A WHOLE LOT
BETTER, OKAY?
OKAY.
IT WAS A PARTY.
I WAS
BEING POLITE.
POLITE?
WE'RE IN FAITH'S
NEIGHBORHOOD.
YOU KNOW
HOW IT IS.
COME ON, BRENDA,
SHE'S LILY'S NANNY.
YOU'RE RIGHT,
I JUST...
YOU ALL RIGHT?
THANK YOU.
FAITH.
FAITH! WAIT!
DON'T!
I DIDN'T MEAN TO SAY--
YOU DIDN'T MEAN?
YOU DIDN'T MEAN.
WHY DID YOU
SAY IT THEN,
MICHAEL?
I WAS AFRAID--
AFRAID OF WHAT?
THAT YOU MIGHT ACTUALLY
FEEL SOMETHING?
YOU HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT I FEEL.
YEAH, WELL
NEITHER DO YOU.
LET'S JUST MAKE
IT SIMPLE, OKAY?
YOU TAKE CARE
OF MY DAUGHTER.
NOT ANYMORE.
GUYS, COULD WE
GO HOME NOW?
I'M TIRED.
HEY, LILY.
I'M GOING TO STAY
HERE WITH MY FAMILY
FOR AWHILE.
WHEN ARE YOU
COMING HOME?
C'MON, LIL.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
NOTHING.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING
WITH MY MOTHER'S
CLOTHES?
DON'T TOUCH THEM!
THEY'RE NOT YOURS,
THEY'RE HERS!
WHAT'S GOING ON?
MICHAEL, I --
LILY!
I HATE HER,
I HATE HER!
I'M SORRY, HONEY.
BRENDA DIDN'T
MEAN TO HURT--
NOT HER!
WHAT IS IT,
HONEY?
WHY DID SHE
LEAVE ME?
FAITH?
NO, MOM, MOM!
OH, SWEETIE.
MOM DIDN'T WANT
TO LEAVE US.
IT WAS
AN ACCIDENT.
SHE DIDN'T
WANT TO GO.
WELL, WHY DID
IT HAPPEN?
WHY DID IT
HAPPEN TO US?
I DON'T KNOW,
HONEY.
I ASK MYSELF
THE SAME THING TOO.
MOM LOVED YOU.
DON'T YOU EVER
FORGET THAT.
MOM LOVED YOU MORE
THAN ANYTHING.
BUT WHERE
IS SHE, DAD?
SOMETIMES...SOMETIMES
I MISS HER SO MUCH.
I JUST WANT
TO SEE HER AGAIN.
YOU KNOW WHERE
SHE IS, LIL?
SHE'S RIGHT HERE,
AND SHE'S RIGHT HERE.
AND THAT'S WHERE
SHE'LL ALWAYS BE
WHENEVER
WE NEED HER.
IT'S OKAY.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
I'M A TERRIBLE
SNOOP, MICHAEL.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT
YOU WERE THINKING.
[ Taxi honks ]
[ Faith: ]
"THOUGH THE RADIANCE
WHICH WAS ONCE SO BRIGHT
"BE NOW FOREVER
TAKEN FROM MY SIGHT,
"THOUGH NOTHING CAN
BRING BACK THE HOUR
OF SPLENDOR IN THE GRASS,
"OF GLORY IN THE FLOWER,
"WE WILL GRIEVE NOT,
"RATHER FIND STRENGTH
IN WHAT REMAINS BEHIND."
HEY.
YOU BUSY?
ALWAYS.
SALES ARE UP, THOUGH.
18 PERCENT.
YEAH, YOU COULD
DO BETTER.
WHAT'S UP?
NOTHIN', NOTHIN'.
I JUST FIGURED
IF YOU COULD USE
A HAND AROUND HERE,
I COULD HELP YOU OUT
IF YOU NEED ME.
WHAT, THOSE GALLERIES
TURN YOU DOWN?
NO, ONE OF THEM'S REALLY
INTERESTED, THANK YOU.
YEAH?
WELL, THEN WHAT
ARE YOU DOING HERE?
I JUST...
I WANT
TO COME BACK.
WHAT?
I WANT TO COME BACK,
MICHAEL.
I GOT ALL THESE
GREAT IDEAS.
WAIT, WAIT, WAIT.
YOU SAID THAT YOU
WANTED OUT FOR GOOD,
THAT THIS SCULPTING THING
WAS SUPPOSED TO BE
DIFFERENT.
IT WAS DIFFERENT.
FOR A YEAR.
LOOK, I CAN'T HELP IT,
I GOT TOYS IN MY BLOOD.
FORGET IT.
WHY?
BECAUSE I CAN'T TRUST
THAT YOU'LL BE THERE
FOR ME.
THAT IS REALLY
NOT FAIR.
I HAVE ALWAYS BEEN
THERE FOR YOU.
BUT YOU
WEREN'T HERE.
I NEEDED
YOU HERE.
YOU WALKED OUT
AT THE WORST
POSSIBLE TIME,
AND NOW I'M SUPPOSED
TO JUST LET YOU
WALTZ BACK IN
BECAUSE SOME LITTLE WHIM
OF YOURS DIDN'T PAN OUT?
THAT IS NOT WHY
I CAME HERE.
WELL THEN WHY
ARE YOU HERE, JAKE?
WHY?
I MISS YOU,
MICHAEL.
I MISS WORKING
TOGETHER.
I MISS...
I MISS THE
FAMILY THING.
I MISS US.
[ Sigh ]
YOU WANT BACK IN,
JAKE?
YEAH.
THIS TIME IT'S GOT
TO BE DIFFERENT.
THIS TIME IT'S MY TURN.
YOU UNDERSTAND?
YOU HAVE TO GROW UP,
YOU HAVE TO TAKE
MORE RESPONSIBILITY.
OKAY, OKAY.
DO YOU GET THIS?
BECAUSE I HAVE
TO KNOW.
I NEED MORE TIME
FOR LILY NOW,
AND MORE TIME
FOR ME.
I JUST WANT
MY BROTHER BACK.
YOU DO WHATEVER YOU
GOT TO DO TO FIND HIM.
WONDERFUL JOB, BRENDA.
THANK YOU.
TO BEDFORD INCORPORATED
AND YOU.
OFFICIALLY ON YOUR OWN.
NOT SO FAST.
YOU DON'T LIKE
THE BROCHURE?
THE BROCHURE'S TERRIFIC.
BUT WITH JUST
MY PICTURE ON IT,
IT'S ALREADY
A LITTLE OUTDATED.
WE CAN STOP THINKING
OF WAYS TO USE
JAKE'S OLD OFFICE.
I WON'T BE ON
MY OWN AFTER ALL.
ALL MY WORK?
NO, NO, IT'S FINE.
IT'S STILL GOING
TO BE BEDFORD, INC.
MY NEW PARTNER WILL HAVE
THE SAME LAST NAME?
SAME LAST NAME?
YEAH.
OH, MICHAEL.
OH, I THOUGHT
I RUINED EVERYTHING
THE OTHER NIGHT.
OH, YES!
YES!
OH YES,
IT'S WHAT I WANTED.
YES!
BRENDA, WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
PARTNERS, TRUE PARTNERS
IN BUSINESS AND
IN MARRIAGE.
CHAMPAGNE,
I'M GETTING MARRIED.
RIGHT AWAY,
MA'AM.
I'M GETTING MARRIED.
BRENDA,
LISTEN TO ME.
WHAT-WHAT-
WHAT-WHAT-WHAT?
I'M NOT PROPOSING.
SAY AGAIN?
I'M NOT ASKING YOU
TO MARRY ME.
I ASSUME I'M NOT THE NEW
PARTNER YOU WERE TALKING
ABOUT EITHER.
JAKE,
I'M TALKING
ABOUT JAKE.
JAKE'S
COMING BACK.
HOW COULD YOU
POSSIBLY THINK--
I JUST THOUGHT
WITH JAKE GONE
YOU'D SEE HOW MUCH
I COULD DO FOR--
WERE YOU AFTER JAKE'S SPOT
FROM THE BEGINNING?
NO!
NOT FROM THE BEGINNING.
I WAS AFTER YOU
FROM THE BEGINNING.
HEY, YOU AND YOUR BUSINESS
WERE DROWNING WHEN I MET YOU.
MICHAEL, WAIT.
LET'S TALK.
LET'S NOT LOSE
A GOOD THING HERE.
I DON'T LOVE YOU,
BRENDA.
I DON'T LOVE YOU, EITHER.
SO WHAT!
WE BOTH WANT THE
SAME THING, MICHAEL.
WE'RE BOTH JUST LOOKING
FOR A LITTLE HAPPINESS.
THAT'S NOT TRUE.
I'M LOOKING
FOR A LOT.
YOUR CHAMPAGNE,
MA'AM.
POP IT.
[ Whistles ]
452 HUDSON,
AND STEP ON IT.
AH, KEEP IT.
FAITH!
SHE AIN'T THERE,
SHE'S AT MY HOUSE.
WHO IS IT,
ANTHONY?
WRONG HOUSE.
MY SISTER HAD
HER BABY.
LITTLE GIRL.
CONGRATULATIONS.
THAT'S GREAT.
HOW'S LILY?
SHE'S WITH JAKE.
SHE MISSES YOU.
WE BOTH DO.
I GOT SAUCE
ON THE STOVE.
FAITH, WAIT.
WHAT?
I WAS DEAD
BEFORE I MET YOU.
IT WAS LIKE THE BEST PART
OF ME HAD DIED WITH SARA
THAT NIGHT,
AND I NEVER THOUGHT
I'D GET IT BACK AGAIN,
NOT EVEN FOR LILY.
NOT UNTIL I MET YOU.
DON'T DO THIS TO ME,
MICHAEL.
DON'T PUT THAT
ON ME.
I CAN'T HELP IT.
YOU WOKE ME UP, FAITH.
IT WAS LIKE ALL OF A SUDDEN
I REMEMBERED WHO I WAS.
YOU MADE ME LAUGH,
MADE ME FEEL ALIVE AGAIN,
AND I MISS THAT.
I NEED THAT.
I NEED YOU.
AND I WANT YOU
TO COME HOME.
MICHAEL,
I AM HOME.
I CAN'T LIVE
IN YOUR HOUSE
LIKE BEFORE.
I JUST WANT
TO SEE YOU AGAIN.
I'M TOO BUSY,
MY CLASSES START
NEXT WEEK.
YOU MAKE TIME FOR
WHAT'S IMPORTANT.
YOU TAUGHT ME THAT.
SCHOOL IS IMPORTANT.
YOU AND LILY,
YOU'RE GOING TO NEED
SO MUCH MORE FROM ME
THAN I CAN GIVE,
AND I AM NOT GOING
TO PUT MY LIFE
ON HOLD AGAIN.
NOT FOR RICHIE,
NOT FOR LILY,
AND NOT FOR YOU.
JUST GIVE ME
A CHANCE.
I'M GOING TO PICK UP
MY THINGS WHEN YOU'RE
NOT HOME.
[ Door locks ]
FIRST, I WANT TO THANK YOU
FOR COMING HERE
ON SUCH SHORT NOTICE.
WE'RE GOING WITH
THIS RIGHT AWAY,
BECAUSE YOU'VE BEEN
SO GOOD TO US,
I'M GIVING YOU FIRST LOOK.
THIS IS HOT OFF
THE LINE.
YOU KNOW, THIS SOUNDS
LIKE SOMETHING I'D LIKE.
BUT I'M NOT REALLY
SURE KIDS WILL BE
INTERESTED IN IT.
THAT'S MY CONCERN.
COME ON, I WANT TO
SHOW YOU SOMETHING.
C'MON.
THEY'RE HAVING
A LOT OF FUN.
THIS LOOKS LIKE
IT COULD REALLY SELL.
THAT'S GREAT.
THEY'RE INTERESTED.
THEY'RE JUST NOT
PUTTING THE STUFF DOWN.
IT'LL SELL.
"DEAR LILY,
I HOPE THIRD GRADE
IS WONDERFUL.
"THESE THINGS SHOULD
START YOU OFF.
"ALWAYS THINKING
OF YOU, FAITH."
COME ON.
HOW DO YOU KNOW
THIS IS THE
RIGHT SIZE POT?
I JUST DO.
SO WHAT
DO YOU THINK?
PERFECT.
EXCUSE ME, MISS.
COULD YOU HELP ME?
I AM LOOKING FOR
19TH CENTURY
BRITISH LITERATURE,
FROM BRONTE TO DICKENS.
I MEAN, I HEAR THE CLASS
IS PACKED,
BUT IF I PROMISE
NOT TO INTERFERE
WITH ANYONE'S WORK,
THEY SAID THAT MAYBE
I COULD AUDIT.
DID THEY?
YEAH.
WELL,
I HAPPEN TO BE HEADING
TO THAT VERY CLASS.
SO YOU LIKE DICKENS?
LIKE HIM?
I LOVE HIM.
I'VE GOT
"GREAT EXPECTATIONS."
YEAH? SO DO I.
CAPTIONS BY CAPTIONHOUSE
AND FAMILY FILMS
♪I DON'T KNOW HOW
TO READ MY HEART, ♪
♪ NEVER THOUGHT
WE WOULD DRIFT SO FAR. ♪
♪ BUT NOW I'VE WAITED
LONG ENOUGH, ♪
♪ ARE YOU WHO
I'VE BEEN DREAMING OF ♪
♪ ALL THIS TIME? ♪
♪ OH, I'VE LEARNED
HOW TO COUNT THE HOURS, ♪
♪ DON'T KNOW
HOW I FOUND THE POWER, ♪
♪ I'LL COME TO YOU, ♪
♪ I PROMISE TOMORROW, ♪
♪ I'LL BE THERE
THIS TIME. ♪
♪ IF I COULD
I'D CHANGE THE PAST, ♪
♪ LEAVIN' PAIN THAT
SHOULD NEVER LAST. ♪
♪ SAY GOODBYE
TO THE MOMENTS WE LOST, ♪
♪ ALL I HAVE IS
A BRIDGE TO CROSS ♪
♪ WON'T LET YOU DOWN
THIS TIME ♪
♪ IT'S BEEN SO LONG
AND WE'VE GONE SO FAR, ♪
♪ DOWN THE ROAD
WHERE WE REALLY ARE ♪
♪ I'LL COMFORT YOU, ♪
♪ I PROMISE TO HOLD YOU, ♪
♪ CLOSER THIS TIME. ♪
♪ SO MANY NIGHTS
I LIE WONDERING, ♪
♪ WHEN IS THE
SADNESS GONE? ♪
♪ AND THOUGH I SEE
HOW LOVE CAN BE BLIND ♪
♪ I KNOW I'LL STAY
THIS TIME. ♪
♪ I DON'T KNOW
HOW TO WALK AWAY ♪
HOW TO DO WHAT'S SAFE. ♪
♪ THIS TIME
I WON'T CLOSE MY EYES, ♪
♪ NOTHIN' LEFT
TO LEAVE BEHIND. ♪
♪ GONNA MAKE IT WORK
THIS TIME. ♪
♪ THIS TIME. ♪