[light music]
[gentle music]
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
[people chattering]
[upbeat music]
[heart beating]
[audience applauding]
[upbeat rock music]
[Camera Operator] Camera,
speed, and we are rolling.
[Interviewer] So, Jason,
how do you feel about your
first Oscar nomination?
I'm grateful for
the nomination,
and honored to be amongst
some of the most talented
people of all time.
But in all honesty,
I don't think any of
this really matters.
It's, it's not why I do it.
[Interviewer]
So, wait a minute,
are you saying you're not
happy about the nomination?
No, not at all.
But it doesn't make me any
better than anyone else.
I never wanted the
fame, even as a kid.
I was just never comfortable
with the attention
that came outside of the work.
I think it's sad
that people care more
about celebrities than
what's going on in the world.
[Interviewer] But
that's Hollywood.
You know how the business works.
Oh, I know exactly
how the business works,
and the business
needs to change.
- There he is!
- There he is! Jason!
[Announcer] The 1994
nominations for Best Actor are,
Jason Mast for...
[Reporter] Rumors
are circulating
after The Enquirer published
some damaging photos.
[Reporter] Well,
I guess it's just
another day in Hollywood.
[gentle music]
[phone ringing]
[Jason panting]
[upbeat music]
[Phone Answer Machine]
Hey. It's Jason.
I'm not here right now.
Leave a message, and
have an awesome day.
[Mother On Phone]
Oh, my god. You did it!
Sweetie, sweetie, pick up
the phone. It's your mother.
[Phone Answer Machine]
Hey. It's Jason.
I'm not here right now.
Leave a message, and
have an awesome day.
[Woman On Phone]
Jason, come on,
answer your phone. Dylan said...
[knocking]
[Celeste] It's Celeste!
I'm over this hermit shit.
You need to come out now,
everyone is here to see you.
The host cannot miss the party.
All right, I know
you hate this crap,
but you don't have to
stay out there for long,
you just need to
make an appearance!
[phone ringing]
[knocking] Hey,
dude. It's Ryan.
Open up. Come on, man.
[ominous music]
Jason Mast. You
talented motherfucker!
God, I've missed your ass.
Give me a break, Steve.
Just put her on the
fucking cover with Jason.
Heather Hayes is
the new it girl.
I'm telling you right now.
Well, if you don't,
you're not getting the interview
with Jason, and that would suck.
'Cause everyone
wants him right now.
He's nominated for a fucking
Oscar, for Christ's sake.
You know, I have to
go. Call me Monday.
Hey. Hey, Hey!
Let me see those
beautiful eyes, all right?
Not yours.
Come here, come here.
Come here. You look a
little tired, all right?
So fix yourself up a bit.
Okay.
Hey! I'm very proud of you.
This is your time, now go
out there and enjoy it.
[phone rings]
What?
I told you no! I mean it, Steve.
No cover, no interview.
You look thin.
It's the drugs.
Oh, shut up. I thought
you stopped all that shit.
I did.
Yeah, and what was the deal
with that boy's trip to Miami?
You see the pictures?
They're everywhere.
Do you want to keep
making the kind of money
you're making or not?
I'm gonna do what I do.
I don't give a
shit what you do.
Just don't do it in public
places where they can
take pictures and put it
in all those magazines.
Okay?
You know, you could've
gotten a supporting
actor nomination if you
had taken it all, mm,
just a bit more seriously
like I told you.
Mm-hmm... What?
[knocking]
You've gotta be kidding me.
- Who is it?
- It's Alyssa.
Not right now. Ryan!
What, am I not VIP enough
to party in your room?
No, no, no, no, no!
- I missed you, dick.
- [grunts] Okay
How long have I been telling
you this was gonna happen,
since you were what, like 16?
I'm so proud of you.
It's handled.
Marissa's sending the pictures
of you guys to the Enquirer.
Wait? That secret
engagement crap?
No, it's you and
Alyssa fighting,
making up, blah, blah, blah.
I told you I'd get you the
best publicist, did I not?
You know, it is all
gonna come out eventually.
And you embarrassed the shit
out of me with those pictures.
You didn't even tell me
you were going to Miami.
I don't have to tell
you everything I do.
Why are you such a
little bitch lately?
All right, you two.
No, I'm sick of his shit.
Hey. Hey, hey, hey!
Millions of people
buy tickets to see
Ryan Logan, their
hero cannot be-
- Oh, my God! I get it, Celeste.
Look, I wanna talk
to Jason alone,
can you give us a few minutes?
- We'll be right out.
- Fine.
Take your time, but hurry it up.
[phone rings]
What?
Yeah, I know. You've
told me multiple times.
I know. Yes.
Oh, I know...
Jason. Jason. Jason.
[voices whispering]
Why haven't you returned
any of my calls this week?
I, I called you.
I never got your messages.
You know I hate machines.
Whoa, hey, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Dude, take off your glasses.
- Why?
- Because I wanna look
- into your eyes, bro.
- What the fuck? What...
What's going on with you?
[phone rings]
Nothing.
[Phone Answering Machine] Hey.
It's Jason. I'm
not here right now.
Leave a message, and
have an awesome day.
[Mother On Phone] Jason,
answer your phone! Come on, baby.
I know we haven't talked
in a really long time,
but I want to see you.
Mommy's back on
the scene, huh?
Yeah, she's been
calling me non-stop, dude.
Don't let her
get to you. Okay?
You're an Oscar-nominated actor
now. You made this happen.
She didn't.
You should have
been nominated too.
You killed it up there.
This isn't about
me. This is about you.
Look, I know you
hate all this shit,
but let's just go out there
and have some fun tonight.
Huh?
Tonight isn't
about having fun.
Whoa, so you're still
going through with it?
Of course.
Are all the security
cameras set up?
They were tested this morning.
They're in every
room of the house.
Is Jack definitely coming?
Celeste said he was confirmed.
I'm not leaving this
room until it's done.
You know what this
is gonna do to Alyssa?
We'll get her through it.
Man, are you sure you want
to go through with all of this?
Yes. I have to do this.
I, I can't keep hold on to
it, man, it's killing me.
Man, can't you
just let it all go?
Can you?
- [knocking]
- Hey, bro. It's Dylan.
I'm holding down the fort,
but it is madness out here.
I'm coming back
in a few minutes,
and I will drag your
ass out if I have to!!
Hey, yo, baby, wait
up! What's your name?
Dylan doesn't know, so
don't say anything to him.
He's not going to be
able to handle it.
Okay. Hey, look at me.
No hard drugs tonight, right?
- I know.
- No. I mean it.
I know. You too.
Man, I told you in Vegas,
I'm done with all that shit.
I haven't touched it since.
[knocking]
[Celeste] Jason. Jack
Rossi just got here.
We have a surprise
for you. Come on out!
[Ryan] We'll be right
out! Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Hey.
Let's just go out there
for a little bit, huh?
Try to enjoy yourself,
just a little, will ya?
Do one round with me, hm?
One round with me,
then you can come back in
here and hide for the rest
of the night, okay?
Yeah? [laughs] Jason
Mast, everybody!
[Jack] Where's
the man of the hour?
[Voices] Jason. Jason.
Jason. Jason.
Jason.
♪ Clean my slate ♪
♪ Dip my hands in fire ♪
♪ Feel my eyes roll back
and my soul attack ♪
♪ Every thought I find ♪
♪ And I should paint my face ♪
♪ Before I go outside ♪
♪ I'm gonna bathe in salt
'til my teeth go numb ♪
♪ Devil in disguise ♪
[heart beating]
- [knocking]
- Hey. It's Alyssa.
Jason! Get the fuck up!
Okay! Oh, god!
It's a fucking party.
Are you seriously sleeping?
Jason! Heather just arrived.
She was looking for you.
Hey, girl. Don't
you look fabulous.
So do you! [laughs] I'm
so happy for you, babe!
- Congratulations.
- Thanks.
You're totally gonna win.
I love the new script changes
that you made, by the way.
I, I just, I keep reading
them over and over again,
and I just, I cry every time.
I mean, people know that
you are a great actor,
but when they realize
that you wrote this!
- Okay! [laughs]
- Oh, my God.
I, I'm really sorry.
It's cool.
I just really connect
to this part and I know
you're still looking
for the financing...
- Oh, no he's not.
- What?
I wanted to surprise you.
Jack Rossi has come on board.
He's fully financing
your project. It's done.
Why didn't you tell me
earlier? Uh, excuse me, please.
What the fuck?
Jack Rossi, really?
You wanted it done,
and I got it done.
You could be filming by summer,
and he's financing it himself.
You wrote it, you're
starring in it,
it's your movie and
everyone's gonna know it.
Whatever issues
you have with him,
let it go and take
the fucking money.
Jason doesn't want me
in the movie, does he?
He's gonna cast that
new Gwyneth girl,
or Cameron, or Winona, because
everyone just wants Winona.
Will you stop it?
Now, I can't leave the show.
So let's just tell Jack
that I'm signing on,
I'll do one more
season, or something.
I don't want to hear
another word about that show.
You are bigger than TV now.
Do you want to be a
movie star, or what? Hey.
How much do you
love your new nose?
I love it. I
feel a lot better.
Yeah, all right look.
I will handle Jack Rossi.
You just worry about Jason.
Don't leave his side tonight.
Like I told you,
Jason is all about chemistry
and I want him to feel
the chemistry between you two.
Now, go make him notice you.
Stand up, you're slouching.
Hey. I've been looking
all over for you.
You just left me. I
don't know anyone here.
I was standing there all
awkward, like an idiot.
People started giving
me drink their orders.
Why is he here?
Heather, I have told
you a million times,
publicly, you're single.
If you care about her career,
stay away from
her for the night.
Or you could just leave.
[phone rings]
You know, we have
work to do here.
What? No, no, I can
barely hear you.
Y'know, let me call
you from the landline.
So, do you wanna
go back to the party?
Or we could just
stand here staring
at Jason Mast all night.
[Heather] Brody, I told you
that tonight's all about work.
[Alyssa] Why are you here?
Alyssa, stop flirting with me.
God, you wish. Heather,
come to the bathroom with me.
I need to talk to
you for a minute.
Hey, man. I'm Brody.
I'm Heather Hayes' boyfriend.
Oh. Hi.
It's so nice to meet
you. I'm a big, big fan.
I've seen all your
movies. [laughs]
I watched "Boys of Summer",
like, 100 times in high school.
Me and my buddies quote
that all the time.
That's cool. Cool, cool.
[Brody] It's a great
place you got here, man.
Thank you for letting me come.
Oh, no problem.
[Brody] Great views.
Thank you.
Hey, I'm a writer!
Uh... Oh!
Okay.
Oh, um, y'know
actually, I have a script.
It's, um, it's a lot like
"Boys of Summer", a coming
of age story,
y'know, and uh, um...
That was so stupid...
I'm a writer, coming of age
story, like you give a shit.
How lame was that, huh?
Hey, giant movie
star, I'm a nobody,
let me tell you about
my awesome new script.
Shut-up, Brody. [laughs]
Bit of a nervous talker,
that's probably why
I'm a writer, huh?
Huh, huh?
I can see that.
I will see you...
Got a cigarette?
Sorry, I don't smoke.
Pft, that's lame.
So, you in the biz?
I feel like I've met you before.
Did we got wasted
together at Drew's house?
Never been to Drew's.
Oh! She's so sweet.
I know, it was backstage
at the Pumpkins show.
Yeah, I don't listen to them.
Oh, the Nirvana show?
Uh, I don't know famous
people, I hate grunge music,
and we definitely
haven't met before.
No, no, no, no. No!
No drinking and you are leaving
by midnight. Give me that!
A martini, really?
Where is your mother?
By the pool. She's
already wasted.
Figures. Did you
get a boob job?
Do they look good?
Pull this shit out.
You look ridiculous.
You told me that
flat chested only works
with modeling and I
would never get cast
with that heroin-chic look.
Right, and we will deal
with that when you are 18.
My mom already made
me an appointment.
And I'm canceling it.
I'm in charge of the business
that is Caley Miller, and
those tits are my business.
Fine.
Do you wanna meet Jason?
- Yes!
- Jason meet Caley Miller.
She's 16, just got to
L.A. a few weeks ago.
She's a model. I'm getting
her into acting now.
Isn't she gorgeous?
- Uh, she is.
- I'll be right back.
It's so nice to
officially meet you.
I love all your movies.
I used to have posters of
you everywhere on my walls
when I was a kid.
I was, like, totally
obsessed with you.
Oh, you're very sweet.
I hope you stay that way.
- Um...
- Huh?
- Get your ass over here!
We're gonna start your
night off with some shots.
My favorite boys!
Now the party starts!
Here, I'm good on
drinks, thank you.
Just like the old days.
But where's Logan's ass?
Who cares. I hate him.
- You hate everyone.
- No, not you.
Ooh.
All right. To my brother!
The best fucking
actor in this town!
Okay.
Plus I got some good blow.
So, get over here and put
this shit up your nose.
Okay, you first.
[upbeat, electronic music]
♪ With fingers on the trigger ♪
♪ And Nikes on my feet ♪
♪ Oh oh oh, oh oh oh oh ♪
♪ Oh oh oh, oh oh oh ♪
[group shouting in unison]
[Jason laughing]
Y'know, even after
all that trouble
in Vegas, he still took me in.
I love you so much, bro.
I'm so proud of you.
And I'm sorry I'm
such a fuck up.
Dude, you're not a fuck up.
Yes, you are, Dylan,
but we still love you.
Okay, no, no, she's
right, ok? I am a fuck up.
If I would have just done
what I was supposed to do.
But I couldn't, okay?
And you were always gonna
be better than me, anyway.
I think you could
have been a great actor.
He was. You were great in
all those cereal commercials.
I was, wasn't I?
Still, he wrote me a
part in his new movie.
It's a dope scene...
See, he just smiled at you.
Now, get Brody out of here,
and stop the slouching,
stop that slouching!
I'm starting my
own t-shirt line.
Really?
And that's why I wanna
be a vampire. [hisses]
Oh! Excuse us.
Your tits look
great by the way.
I know, right? They're new.
Hey, so are you ready to leave?
I know you hate this shit.
Yeah, we can go now,
whatever you want.
I can't go, but you
can totally leave.
Seriously?
'Cause Celeste wants me to go,
you want me to go? I get it.
You just wanna hang with
Jason Mast all night.
Brody. It's every day.
You're just obsessed with this.
I see the way you look at him.
Shit, I see the
way I look at him.
I'm not an idiot, Heather.
You're gonna sleep with
him tonight, aren't you?
I need you to stop being so
insecure. I have to do this.
I need this part
in his movie. Okay?
Hey. I love you.
Did you see that
Ryan Logan's here?
I did.
Why don't you go find him.
Tell him about your script.
Oh sure, yeah. Let
me just walk up to him.
Hey, buddy, I got a
great script and I think
it is perfect for you.
[laughs] Well,
I don't know him,
but I'll help introduce you.
Come on. Let's go.
No, but that's what you
have to do to win an Oscar.
You know what I mean?
Like, you have to play
a retarded person,
or a crippled person, or an
ugly person, or get really,
really fat, and I'm just
not willing to do any
of those things.
Like, I could.
I mean I know I have the
potential in me to do it.
I just need the
opportunity, you know?
Like, I need my breakout role.
No, you need a comeback role.
- Suck it, Dylan.
- Fuck!
I just need my "Pretty
Woman," you know?
My "Thelma and Louise."
Oh, I see rehab, did
you good, huh, buddy?
You know what? Suck it, Logan.
- Been there, done that.
- Fuck you.
- No, fuck you.
- No! Fuck you!
Dude!
I've been dying to mess
up that hair up all night.
♪ And it all occurs around me ♪
♪ And with all
that goes around ♪
♪ It's the gloaming
that'll haunt me ♪
♪ Ah, ah ♪
[men shouting]
Hey, your mom is
looking for you.
Ugh, so annoying.
She seems kinda wasted.
So embarrassing. I have to
deal with this every night.
I totally get it. Come on,
come to the balcony with me.
Hey. I need to talk
to you for a minute.
Come here.
Oh. I'll be right back.
Yeah, I'm cool.
[upbeat music]
Are you sure about my nose?
Oh, my god. Shut up, Heather.
Your nose is perfect, all
right? You're fucking hot.
Just relax.
[spits] Ugh!
Let's get outta town.
Celeste will kill us if
we took off for that long.
Oh, my god. Screw Celeste.
Okay? She works for you.
You don't work for her. She's
made enough money off you two.
They've all made
enough money off of us.
Oh, I can't. I
don't like that stuff.
I tried it once, it
messed with my head.
Oh, come on, your
career is taking off,
you're young, you're hot.
Now, just shut up and
do a line with me.
All right. Hey, girls.
[laughs] Hey, boys. Let's
get this party going, yeah!
All right, Caley.
Are you really gonna let
Jack Rossi finance your movie?
There you go. Your night
just got a whole lot better.
Hey! Go Caley!
Just go right up to him
and say, 2Oh, jeez, thanks,
Mr. Rossi, thank you so
much for funding my film.
You're best!
However can I repay you?"
Clean your pool?
Wash your Ferrari?
Your Rolls?
Wipe your ass?
Y'know, I used to dream
of torturing that fucker.
My entire life changed
after one season.
Yeah, and you'll be
even bigger next season.
God, it's crazy. I mean,
people know me everywhere I go.
Well, welcome to my life
since I was, like, nine.
Ok! Yeah!
Whoo! Yeah, girl.
I can't believe you're
finally gonna nail that son
of a bitch.
Wait, what do you mean?
Uh, Nothing, I just meant
we can do what we want now.
This lady came up to me
yesterday with her daughter.
The daughter said she
loved me, wanted a hug,
and then said she
wanted to be me.
I mean, I don't know, it
kinda, like, freaks me out.
Okay, I'll be back, lovers.
Hey, nice moves you got there.
Dylan Mast!
Maybe I could show
you some new ones.
Cool!
I worry about him.
Yeah, you worry
about everybody.
Yeah, cause we're
are all a fucking mess.
[laughs] Yeah!
I want you to stay right
here, okay? I'll be right back.
[soft rock music]
Mind if I join you?
Hey.
I'm sorry, I don't know
who the fuck you are.
Caley Miller, Alyssa Rossi.
You've seen her billboard,
it's across from Chateau.
No, I'm too fucked
up to see anything
when I'm at Chateau.
I'm a huge fan.
I used to make my mom tape
your show, when I was a kid,
so I could watch
it over and over.
Me and my friends
totally wanted to be you.
Really. That's so sweet.
When we thought you
died in that car accident,
and then Jesse confronts you
and Billy in the hospital
and he's all, "It's
either him or me,
Miranda, but know this."
[Booth] "I loved you since
the moment I saw you, baby!"
Oh! I love Jesse.
All my friends were
team Billy, but I was
just team Miranda.
Y'know, you're really
pretty. Sit down with us.
Here.
No! No, no, no.
She's 16.
- So, let her try it once.
- No!
You know what? I
do recognize you.
I have seen your billboard.
I totally fucked the model
in the photo with you.
Oh, really?
Yeah, I'm sorry, are
you sleeping with him?
[laughs] No.
Well, why not?
I don't know.
Shut up! Are you a virgin?
Really? Good for you.
Yeah, but I suck a
lot of dick though.
Did you see Jack out there?
Yeah, only for a minute. I
don't think he saw me, though.
Man, that fucker's put
on a bunch of weight.
Good.
You know you're gonna have
to talk to him tonight, right?
[tense music]
♪ Oh apricity, I
feel it in my bones ♪
♪ As you left me standing ♪
♪ Burning in the cold ♪
- You okay? Hey, we can just...
- Yeah, I'm fine.
I just need another drink.
No, you've been
drinking all night.
Stop trying to
fucking control me!
And he just made you
stand there naked and took
photos of you?
Yeah, he said all
the top models do it.
That's not okay.
Sure, it is.
You're a real great
influence, Alyssa.
Caley Miller, it's midnight.
Time for you to go home!
Wow, she really knows
how to break up a party.
I know, right?
Go find your mother.
I'll call you both a taxi.
You! You need to pull yourself
together and focus on Jason.
You are so close,
don't blow it doing drugs
with some has-been TV star.
She can't even get her
father to put her in a film
in this town.
Hey!
Alyssa Rossi is over,
and so is that show,
and it would already have
been canceled if you hadn't
come on last season.
Oh! And you have coke on
your nose, by the way.
Yeah. Stop the crap!
[phone ringing]
Stop the slouching! Oh what!
I know. I know!
Hey, guys. Jason, um,
this is a great party.
I, I really love the
sweater that you...
Oh. Thank you.
Excuse me.
- That went well.
- Sorry. Sorry.
Oh, my god, you were just
throwing yourself at him.
What are you doing?
Oh, my God! You
are so embarrassing.
Now, I want you to leave.
Way to go, big guy.
Ignore her.
Yeah, she comes
off like a bitch,
but underneath those
breast implants!
There's a big heart in there.
Hey, man. I'm Ryan.
I know. I'm Brody.
Sorry about all that.
Ah, no worries. Hey,
can I get you a drink?
Sure.
[Ryan] So, are
you an actor too?
No, worse. I'm a waiter.
Writer! I'm a writer.
Writers are cool,
so are waiters.
I actually have six
screenplays on my kitchen
table at home.
I haven't sold one.
Mm-hm.
Um. But, I was telling your
buddy, Jason, all about it.
And, it's um, it's actually, um-
- Hey! Did you see that
babe that was here earlier?
Y'know, tall, hot, legs.
She's friends with Drew
Barrymore and Kurt Cobain.
I, I don't think she's
actually friends with them.
I mean, she told me she
wants to be a vampire.
Who the hell is this guy?
He's cool. He's
Heather's boyfriend.
Oh, really? This guy?
Hey, man. What do you do?
I'm a writer.
Oh, really,
anything I've seen?
Um. Not yet.
- But I have this script-
- Me too.
Hey, I got some,
uh, y'know treats.
Just the three of us.
- How 'bout we-
- No, no, no, no.
II told you, I'm done
with all that shit.
And please don't give
anything to Jason either.
Don't be such a pussy, Logan.
I mean it, Dylan.
Nothing to Jason.
Hey, man! You're still
fucking standing there?
Did y'know you're sketchy
and starting to freak me out!
Hey, man, I'm sorry about him.
I will catch up with
you later, okay?
[Brody] Cool.
Nice to meet you.
Look, it's just like
the old days. Y'know.
When was the last time
we were all together?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah. I will think about it.
Okay, but before
the night's up. Okay?
Hey Jason, everyone's
gone. Can I come in?
[Jason] No.
C'mon man, open the door.
You know, I'm not trying
to control you. I just-
- [Jason] It's all good. It's
just, I just need a minute.
All right, well I'll come
back for you later, okay? Jason?
[Jason] Yeah, thanks.
[tense music]
[people shouting]
[phone ringing]
[Phone Answer Machine] Hey.
It's Jason. I'm
not here right now.
Leave a message, and
have an awesome day.
[Mother] Sweetie,
pick up the phone.
I love you and life is
too short for this crap.
I miss you, little man.
You know, family...
[soft music]
♪ Ima clean my slate ♪
♪ Dip my hands in fire ♪
♪ Feel my eyes roll back
and my soul attack ♪
♪ Every thought I find ♪
♪ I should paint my face ♪
♪ Before I go outside ♪
♪ I'm gonna bathe in salt
'til my teeth go numb ♪
♪ Devil in disguise ♪
[voices shouting indistinctly]
[Mother] Jason?
How'd it go?
I didn't book it. I
wasn't the right type.
Did you eat all of these?
No.
Lift up your shirt.
Disgusting.
Jason, you need to
stop eating like a pig
and start lifting weights.
I want you to take three
of these with every meal.
You can't book
anything if you're fat.
You're 15 now.
Which means you're gonna
start going out for all
the sexy roles.
You can't be a fatty.
You need to look like him.
That's what they want.
[heavy breathing]
[tense music]
Down.
Down! Give me 40.
Jason, you need
to book this role.
We all need this money.
It's just you, me,
and Dylan now. Okay?
We can't rely on your father
any more. He's not coming back.
Which leaves you as
the man of the house.
You can't be a
little girl any more.
- Do you understand me?
- Yes.
Keep going.
- My arms are tired.
- Keep going!
[Jason] Okay.
Now, I want you to walk
into that audition and knock
it out of the park.
That a boy. Keep going.
I love you, little man.
[heavy breathing]
Well, congratulations.
You know, I only
represent actors
that I think have
real potential.
And you? [laughs] You
got real potential.
We are gonna make
you a star. Deal?
- If you say so.
- I know so.
[heart beating]
[upbeat music]
♪ This medicine is
wearing thin now ♪
♪ We're bulletproof
until we bleed out ♪
♪ And even though
we always try ♪
♪ To hide our instincts
from our pride ♪
♪ In our struggle to survive ♪
♪ We keep the
warpath by our side ♪
- [knocking]
- Caley! Open up!
Caley, I saw you go in there.
Your mother is looking for you.
Your mother? How old are you?
I'm 19.
Then why is your mother here?
She just likes to tag along.
Caley, open this
door right now!
Hey, loser, you know
she's 16 years old?
You're 16?
[Celeste] Okay, Caley, I guess
I'll just have to
call your father,
and he'll ship your ass
right back to Idaho.
Please don't.
Let's go, let's go.
Go find your mother.
I didn't know she was 16!
When are you gonna
get your shit together
and stop leaching
off your brother.
You're gonna fuck up his career!
He's always cleaning
up your messes.
Jason would never tell you this,
but you are an embarrassment.
I don't care if you fuck
up your own life but don't
fuck up his life too.
No, go! Go, go now!
Now!
I'm a fuck up! I'm a fuck up!
You piece of shit! [panting]
Dylan? What are you doing?
Put down the gun, Dylan, no!
You're a loser.
Loser. A fucking loser.
- Maybe tonight's the night.
- What?
A fucking loser. Maybe
tonight's the night.
[Jason] What the
fuck is he saying?
Maybe tonight's the night.
Mom! You can't put
that on me, okay?
I can't force him to call you.
No, I'm not trying to start
anything with you, mom!
Oh okay, so now you
don't want to talk to me?
Okay, well fuck me then!
You booked it!
Yeah, your first film.
Now, it's a not a big
role, but it's a good one.
Good enough to get your face
out there. What did I say, huh?
It's all starting. [laughs]
See, Jason, this
is what happens
when you listen to your mother.
I'm not that bad,
am I? [chuckles]
And you, you might be
the best manager ever!
[laughs] Well, you
know, I do my best.
Go ahead, have a seat right
over there. Thank you very much.
Jason, what's wrong? I mean,
you don't seem so excited.
Is the, uh, is the role
not big enough for you?
No, it's not that.
It, hey, is there anything
in the movie for Dylan?
Nope. Not this time.
But you're still looking
for stuff for him, right?
Absolutely. Absolutely, Jen.
Uh, you know what?
How 'bout I take Dylan to
a ball game this weekend?
Y'know, give us some
time to be alone.
I can work with him
on some acting stuff.
I think this would
be great for Dylan.
- Hey, can I go too? Please?
- Oh!
No, buddy, not this time.
Just me and Dylan, okay?
I, I think we need some
bonding time. Okay?
But I am gonna make it
up to you. All right?
I promise. And you, mister, huh?
You... [laughs] You got
a lot of work to do.
Uh, Jen?
I need to talk to you
about some contract stuff
in the other room.
Jason, just sit tight.
- So, you know, I act too.
- You're an actress?
- Mhm.
- Wow! I did not know that.
[Mother] Yeah, well that's
actually why we moved out here.
[Paulie] Oh, that makes sense.
Do you have, huh,
a headshot? Resume?
Mom, stop! Why
are you saying that?
You know that's not true!
You know I love you, Mom.
I would never do that
and neither would Jason.
Mom, stop, Mom,
you're being crazy!
You screwed up
again! Jesus Christ!
I do everything for
you! Everything!
I went over that audition
with you again and again!
You were supposed to book this.
How could you screw those
lines up? You had them, Jason!
You had them! Get up!
Get up! Get over to the mirror.
Get over there. Look at you.
Huh? Why can't you be cuter?
Oh, cause you take
after your father!
And now I'm the one
stuck with you, huh?
Mediocre son with no talent!
Get up!
Sit down!
Dylan!
Get in here! This diva doesn't
think he has to do any work.
Oh, stop crying like
a little bitch, okay?
Only little girls cry, and
you are not a little girl.
You're not eating
dinner tonight, okay?
Dylan and I are gonna go out,
while you sit here
...look at me,
and go over the
script Paulie sent.
Okay?
I don't care if you have
to stay up all night long,
I want you off book
by the morning.
Understand?
All right, I love you. I
do, I love you, I love you.
Okay.
Dylan!
Get in here! Dylan!
Take it back.
Mom, take it back!
No, I, I really can't listen
to this any more. Okay?
So, I'm gonna hang up now. Mom!
- I'm hanging up now
- Mom, this is Jason.
If you call this
house one more time,
I'm calling my lawyers, and
you know what that means.
Dylan hang up the phone!
Are you sure that I don't
look fat in this dress?
I've barely been eating.
God, you have nothing
to worry about. All right?
Your body's perfect,
your hair is perfect,
and now your nose is perfect.
Do you really think so?
Heather, you're so
hot, it's ridiculous.
No, you're so hot [sniffs]
and you're so talented.
And you, like, [sniffs] nail
every scene that we're in.
I don't even know
how you manage to...
- Um...
- Are you into this?
I have a boyfriend.
Okay. Well, same sex hook-ups
don't count as cheating.
I've never been
with a girl before.
[Alyssa] Well, no guy can
please a girl like a girl can.
Sorry, boys.
That's some bullshit.
Oh, these are
perfect. I'm so jealous.
Well, they cost
my father a fortune.
Speaking of my father,
I feel like you've been
avoiding him tonight.
Just be honest, you're
not planning on re-signing
on my show, are you?
Don't lie to me.
Because I hate liars.
I want to, but Celeste
thinks that I shouldn't.
I know that my character
has helped boost the ratings
back up, and I told
her that I didn't want
to just abandon it.
Hey. I've been
looking all over for...
Are you doing coke?
This is a really big
night for me, like,
a really big night.
I'm under a lot of pressure
and you just don't seem
to get it.
I mean, everyone
is looking at me,
and you just keep embarrassing
me in front of Jason.
I'm embarrassing you?
Tell me the truth, are
you sleeping with him?
Oh, my god! You can't even
support me for one night?
I mean, I am doing
all of this for us.
Do you not realize how big
this could be for my career,
and for yours?
- Bullshit!
- You're just jealous.
Jealous of what?
Of these people?
Of this life that that you
once thought was a bunch
of bullshit too?
This is what you're
working so hard for?
You wanna be like her? Another
coked out, mediocre actress?
Alyssa doesn't have
to work for anything.
She's got daddy's
money to fall back on.
- You need to go home!
- No!
If this Jason Mast
movie is so important
and the only way you can
get the part is to fuck him,
then fuck him!
Go home.
No. We're leaving
together, or we're done.
Well it looks
like you're done.
Are you gonna go save him now?
Here.
This will make it better.
[soft music]
You got balls, man.
I don't think anyone's
ever said anything like
that to Alyssa.
At least not to her
face. You all right?
Yeah, I'm cool.
You want a cigarette?
I quit.
Yeah.
[knocking]
You cannot come in here.
But I thought you liked me.
Look, kid, you're
hot as fuck. Okay?
And when you're 18, if
I'm still alive, call me.
Okay, first off, don't
call me kid. I hate that.
It's condescending.
Okay. I'm sorry, I
didn't mean to offend you-
- And second off, you're
a kid, your room's a mess.
You're a total slob.
Okay, you're a sassy
little thing, aren't ya?
Do you have a cigarette?
That I can do.
But not in here.
Outside, where
everyone can see us.
No. We're not ready
to announce it yet.
But if everything goes the
way it's supposed to...
No, no, no don't worry.
I know how to handle Jack Rossi.
I don't know, man,
something about her's changed.
It could be the new nose.
I don't think
it's the new nose.
It might be, but
that's not what I mean.
Seriously, dude? Heather's
just doing what she has to do.
Look, she wants to
be in his movie.
It's a great part, it's
great for her career,
and Jason has no
interest in Heather.
Trust me.
And even if they did fuck,
it doesn't mean anything.
What are you taking about?
That would change everything.
Why? She loves you, dude.
It'll all work out.
You smoke pot?
Uh, not any more.
It makes me paranoid.
Well, tonight you do. Come on.
No, I mean it, Alyssa.
I, I really do love him.
I mean, look at you and
Ryan. You know how it is.
I'm not in love with Ryan.
Yes, you are.
No, I'm not. That's not what
our relationship is about.
Okay.
Well, I don't know that
much about you two,
but I see it every time
that you're with him.
It's all over your face.
You're kidding me?
You've been with Heather
since you were 15
and she's the only
one you've been with?
Yeah.
Then how do you even know
you're in love with her?
I don't know any
more. What about you?
Are you in love with Alyssa?
Uh, she's one of
my best friends,
and we fuck from time to time...
But no, I'm not
in love with her.
That whole thing about us
being a couple is just a cover.
[coughs] Cover for what?
[Heather] But you and
Ryan have sex, right?
Yeah, all the
time. But, so what?
We have sex with
a lot of people.
- Guys and girls?
- Yeah.
Ryan Logan has sex with dudes?
Sometimes.
Well then, he's gay.
No, he's not gay.
No gay man could do
what Ryan does to me.
Besides, I hook up with
girls, and I'm not a lesbian.
Yeah, well it's
different for girls.
No, it's not.
Everyone is bisexual,
girls are just man enough
to admit it.
You're not getting it dude.
It's not about the fucking.
I mean, you can fuck
night after night,
and it can mean nothing.
It's all about the connection
between two souls, you know?
What are you talking about?
Okay. I think we're
all just souls, man.
I believe a real connection
can be with a male or a female.
It's about getting
to that deeper level
where we're all just the same.
You know? No sexuality,
no religion, no judgment.
Even if you just hook
up for one night.
All right, if you're just
there with the other person,
looking into their eyes,
and touching them, y'know?
Soul to soul?
To me, that's love.
You gotta meet
Ryan. He's the best.
I love that guy.
Yeah, I can tell.
What does that mean?
I don't know.
It's just I saw you hitting
his ass earlier, you two were,
like, all over each other.
Seems pretty weird to me. No
guys in Idaho act like that.
Okay, well this ain't Idaho.
Well, I know that.
There's just something
different with all you guys.
We've been through a lot
of shit together. Okay?
Shit you wouldn't even believe.
I guess. But I do not
know how you do that.
I could never be with someone
who didn't want just me.
Look, what you have with
Brody might work for you,
but I don't need to be
tied down like that.
I can sleep with
whoever I want to, too.
Say whatever you want,
but I still think
you're in love with him.
Get real, Alyssa.
Oh, you want to get
real? Let's get real.
I don't believe you.
You've never had a
connection with a guy?
No! Why would I lie?
I have nothing to hide?
God, that must be nice.
Mm. What?
Not having anything to hide.
I feel like I'm always hiding.
Man, fuck what everybody says.
So what, if you're like,
attracted to souls, or whatever.
Oh, man. I like you, Brody.
You're a good dude.
You're different.
Different from what?
Different from
everyone in my life.
Answer the fucking
question, Heather!
You think I'm an idiot?
You fuck Jason, and he
puts you in his movie,
and then you don't need my show.
Right?
Right. Because you have
no fucking loyalty.
Well, what would you do?
I wouldn't have that
problem. Because I was born in.
You have to fuck your way in.
What the hell just
happened in here?
You know she could
blow this whole thing.
You go after her and fix it
before she talks to her father.
Let's go.
So, what?
You just believe everything
you read and you thought
I was gonna be
some asshole, huh?
No, no, not an asshole.
Just not this normal guy.
Well I mean, I guess
you're not that normal,
you've been famous since
you were a teenager.
God, that must have been a
nightmare for your parents.
Actually, I was emancipated
from them when I was 16.
It's their choice by the way.
Y'know that way I could
work longer hours and make
a lot of people
a lot more money.
That's pretty shitty.
I can't imagine
growing up that way.
But, but I guess none of
that matters now, now you can
have whatever you want, huh?
Why? Because I
have a lot of money?
Money can't get you
everything you want.
That's not what I meant.
Yes, it is.
You, god, you look at me
and you think I have it all.
Y'know, but everything
that I do gets blasted
out to the world
for everyone to see.
You have no idea
what that's like.
People thinking they know
everything about you.
Really they know nothing at all.
[soft music]
[water splashing]
[laughs] Hey, boys, come on.
No running around the pool!
What'd I say?
I'll come over there and
snap you right in the ass,
you little fuckers. [laughs]
So, you going in,
huh? It's pretty warm.
- I, I'm not sure.
- Yeah?
Well, I'm glad I convinced
your mother to let
you stay here tonight.
Me too.
You know, Jason, I think
you... I think you...
[laughs] You are
gonna be a big star.
- You really think so?
- Oh yeah. Oh yeah.
You're better than all these
little shits. Except for one.
Huh? Now, you see
that boy right there?
That is Ryan Logan.
You heard of him?
Yeah, of course.
He's got that TV show.
He's amazing.
That's right. He's
got a great career.
And I got the same
plans for you. Huh, huh?
[both laugh]
[Paulie] What happened?
Where's your sock, huh?
Didn't I tell you to always
wear a sock in there?
[Jason] I'm, I'm
sorry, Paulie. I forgot.
- Better?
- Oh yeah. See?
Much better. Much better.
You're still a sexy son of
a bitch, though, either way.
All right? So you are gonna
sleep in my wing tonight.
Yeah. Ryan's gonna be there too.
And Dylan, if he behaves!
[Caley] So, you just
didn't like acting?
No. I did like acting.
I loved it, actually.
But there were
just certain things
that they wanted me to do
that I just couldn't do.
Y'know, maybe I should've,
maybe things would
be a lot different.
There was just some stuff
that I wasn't willing to do.
Like what?
Hey Dylan, come
on now! All right?
Slow down! Be careful!
I don't want any of you
boys drowning on my watch!
Jason, come on,
man. You seem shy.
All right? Come on, let's
get the fun started, huh?
We gotta get you
out of your shell,
and get you in that pool.
- Okay.
- All right, good.
Now there, there's some
pool rules here after dark.
All right? Number one, you
always stick with a buddy.
Okay.
Number two, no
peeing in my pool.
[laughs] Okay.
And number three,
no suits after dark.
- Um, what?
- All right?
It just helps you to become a
better actor, more vulnerable.
Trust me. Take that.
Call your mother, tell
her you're gonna stay here
for the weekend.
[rhythmic music]
I'm still a virgin, Ryan.
I haven't even gotten my dick
sucked yet! Fuck you dude.
Yeah, yeah, I'm
still at Paulie's.
I'm staying here for a week.
I got auditions and
stuff to work on.
No, um,... it's just me.
Uh, Dylan left last night.
What are you talking about?
Well, I just got an
amazing call about you.
Yeah, I think this
could be your big break.
Now, it's a film called
the "Boys of Summer"
and it's produced by Jack Rossi.
Yeah, we got a meeting
in the morning,
Jack wants to meet you.
- Really?
- Yep.
- That's huge.
- [laughs] Yeah.
Y'know your mother, she's very
excited about this meeting.
Y'know she's very proud of you.
So she thinks it's best
that you stay here tonight
since you gotta be up so early.
Okay.
Y'know Jason, this
is a major game changer
for you and your family.
You seem nervous.
Am I ready for this?
[chuckles] Come on.
Let me help you relax.
All right? Come here.
You trust me?
Yeah.
There you go. [laughs] Yeah.
You know, we're
pretty close, right?
I mean other than being your
manager, we're buddies, right?
Of course, Paulie. You're,
like, one of my best friends.
Good. I'm glad
you feel that way.
Y'know, because trust
is very important
between a manager
and his client.
Okay? Yeah.
Yeah.
I mean, I've worked my ass
off for you, and tomorrow?
Whoo, tomorrow's gonna be
the biggest day of your life,
so far, all right?
I can't tell you how many boys
would want this opportunity,
to meet Jack Rossi and
make all their dreams
come true, huh?
Your buddy Ryan...
Your buddy Ryan's already
met Jack, and Ryan knows
how to make a deal happen.
Now, we were young and
we had all this money
just thrown at us.
I know that sounds really great,
but everything has a price.
Meaning?
You okay?
Yeah, man. I'm fine.
Let's go get a drink.
[Celeste] Jason!
Jack's leaving soon,
he's looking for you.
I'll bring him back here.
[tense music]
We have to bring
them down, Ryan! No!
No, I don't care what
kind of power he has!
No! It's not right.
You were shaking
the other night,
and Dylan couldn't even walk.
Fuck Jack Rossi, man!
[knocking]
Okay, I'll be
right out. Hold on!
[Jack] It's Jack.
[heart beating]
There's the man of the hour.
Come on, bring it in, man.
See, I deserve a
bigger hug than that.
Congrats on that nomination.
You earned it, huh?
Come on, man, make me a drink.
We got a lot to discuss.
You know what I like.
You must be flying
high about now.
Best actor nomination,
at your age.
[laughs] Personally, I
thought the film sucked,
but your performance
was solid, as usual.
I told you.
Told you the day you
walked into my office,
I was gonna make you a star.
♪ If I just had the confidence ♪
♪ I could claim, about this ♪
♪ Can't break my frustration ♪
Oh, finally.
I'm glad you two are
getting a chance to talk.
Find Heather. I want
to talk to you both.
Now. Ooh, that's feeling good.
You've been working out.
I'll go find her.
[Jack] [laughs] So,
I'm not even gonna
get a thank you, am I?
Thank you for what?
For financing your
movie. Come on, Jason.
You know we make a great team.
[soft music]
Hey, Daddy! I've been
looking all over for you.
You wanted to see Heather?
Well, don't you look gorgeous.
- Hello, Mr. Rossi.
- Oh, Mr. Rossi?
I think you'll be calling
me Jack again before long.
Where have you been hiding?
Hiding? What do you think
I've been doing all night?
Some people work, Alyssa.
I've had business to take
care of all over this place.
What are you eating?
There's no carbs
in this, Daddy.
Do you see Heather
eating that junk?
By the way, Heather,
you look stunning.
You see, that's what
a star looks like.
♪ I'm gonna have
once, type of thing ♪
♪ God bless these boys
and God bless these kids ♪
Hey, Jack.
Well, who is this
gorgeous lady? Hi, I'm Jack.
[Caley] I know. I'm Caley.
Well, it is nice to meet
you, Carly. [chuckles]
She said her name's Caley.
What are you hanging
out with this putz for?
He can't do shit for you.
It was nice meeting you.
Daddy, listen, I was thinking
about my birthday next week.
- What if we go together-
- Let's get her on the show.
Let's get her on the show.
So, big night for Jason.
I always knew he
was gonna be a star.
Same feeling I had about you.
You know I gave him
his big break, right?
A little film called,
"Boys of Summer".
You were 16 in that,
isn't that right, Jason?
♪ There's something creeping ♪
♪ Beneath my sleeping ♪
♪ There's monsters at home ♪
♪ I feel so alone ♪
Jason, hello.
Nice to finally meet you.
Paulie's been talking
about you for months.
He speaks highly of you, and
he knows how to spot talent.
That's nice of him.
Well, you know
I always bring you
the best, Jack, right? [laughs]
You want a drink? I
won't tell your mother.
Oh, I, I tried it before.
I don't like the taste.
[Jack] Be a man,
Jason, and have a drink.
Your buddy Ryan drinks
with me, and he's 16.
Yeah. Go ahead.
I can take it
from here, Paulie.
Whatever you say,
Jack. [laughs] Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
We're gonna do
a little improv.
I'll be the love interest
and I'm in danger.
And you're the hero. You ready?
- Yeah.
- Yeah? Action!
Help me! Help me,
please help me!
I'm here. What's going on?
Are you okay?
No, my arm! There's
blood everywhere.
He tried to kill me!
Well, what are
you just gonna do?
Just stand there? The
love of you life is dying.
Do something, for Christ's sake.
Take your shirt off,
wrap it around my wound.
Okay, okay, not bad.
Not bad.
We gotta do a little work
on the arms and the abs.
I'll get you a trainer.
That'd be awesome.
See, as far as the acting,
though? You're holding back.
Look, you wanna
be a leading man,
you gotta be comfortable
with yourself as a man,
you're not a little
boy any more.
You gotta be naked in
front that audience, son.
'Cause that camera doesn't lie.
Take off the pants for a second.
I need to see what
we're working with.
What?
Come here.
Closer.
Nah, you're still
holding back, Jason.
I mean, don't you want your
career to take off like
your buddy Ryan's?
Yeah?
Then be a big man and take
off the pants, and the boxers.
[surreal music]
- Isn't that right, Jason?
- What?
Hey Daddy, how
long are you staying,
because I think the three
of us need to have a talk.
About an hour.
I'm leaving for
Italy in the morning,
I haven't packed a thing.
Well, how long are you going?
A few weeks.
But, Daddy, my
birthday's next week.
And you promised that
we would go together.
Well, throw any party
you want, sweetheart.
Just send the bill to Maria.
I'll cover the whole thing.
No, forget it.
I'll just call Mom.
Like your mother's gonna do
something for your birthday.
You'll be lucky if she
remembers to call you.
Don't worry, we already
have something planned
for your birthday.
Daddy, please, just
talk to me for a second-
- That's enough!
You're embarrassing yourself.
This conversation is over.
I will deal with you later.
Hey. Hey, are you okay?
How's my new star?
- Hi, Mr. Rossi.
- You can call me Jack.
- I'm upset with you.
- Why?
Because you haven't
been in to see me yet.
[Caley] I'm sorry.
Celeste never told me
anything about a meeting.
Well, we didn't have one,
but we could have one now.
I got some projects I think
you could be right for.
You're not leaving
yet, are you Carly?
It's Caley. Actually,
my mom's here.
We're supposed to go home soon.
No, no, no, no, no. I'll
get a car for your mom.
You're a big girl now.
Come with me, we'll
go somewhere and chat.
Jason, I'll see you later.
Heather, we're speaking
before you leave.
Uh, Caley, where
are you going?
[Caley] Me and
Jack have a meeting.
Dylan, Dylan! Calm
down, calm down.
- Calm down! Hold on!
- I'm gonna go get Caley.
No! How could you
let him in this house?
We don't need that
fuck any more!
I swear, I'm gonna kill him!
I am handling Jack!
I just need you to go out
there and keep everything cool.
I'm not letting
him do it to her!
I know! Give me 'til
the end of the night.
Fine!
Dylan! Don't do
anything stupid!
Don't do anything
stupid! Dammit, Dylan!
♪ Oh, and I ♪
♪ Safe from you ♪
Dylan, what the
fuck are you doing?
Put the gun down. Oh my...
Fuck!
[Dylan panting]
No, don't worry about
a thing, Jack. Trust me.
I don't believe a word that
comes out of that kid's mouth.
Get your ass over here.
Dylan lies about everything,
so I don't blame you for not
wanting to work with him.
I will handle Jason.
I'm sure he's just going
along with his brother.
You have a zit! You need to
stay off the crafty, fatty.
Great. Well, I am so
glad we cleared this up.
In fact, you can just go
through me from now on.
I think it's time we
both move on from Paulie.
Mm-hm, exactly.
I'll be taking over
as Jason's manager.
Sounds good!
Take care.
Jack's sending you a car.
You two have a meeting.
I don't want to go.
I don't care. I'm
your manger now.
I say what Jason Mast does.
[tense music]
You little shit!
This is the thanks
that I get, huh?
See, I made you. I made you!
And I can end you. I
can fucking end you!
I could make you and
your brother disappear,
and no one would even
know that it was me.
'Cause that's the
power that I have!
What do you have?
What do you have, huh?
You got fucking nothing!
Who's gonna believe
a word that you say?
Your own mother
doesn't believe you.
It's your word against mine,
and who are they gonna believe?
Who they gonna believe. [laughs]
I just asked you a
fucking question.
Who the fuck are
they gonna believe?
You.
Me! Me!
So, keep your
fucking mouth shut!
What am I gonna do
with that mouth?
I should wash it out
with soap. [laughs]
I got a better idea.
Forget about your
mouth. Turn around, boy!
Turn around! Oh,
it'll be all right.
[somber music]
Jason? What's wrong?
Baby, baby, baby, what's
wrong? What happened?
No, no, no.
What happened? What happened?
Tell me, I won't be mad.
Baby...
Okay. Okay, don't tell me.
Don't tell, that's fine.
♪ When I heard the news ♪
♪ I was flying ♪
♪ I turned off the tube ♪
♪ And decided to go fishing ♪
[phone ringing]
[Phone Answering
Machine] Hey. It's Jason.
I'm not here right now.
Leave a message, and
have an awesome day.
[Lawrence] Hey
buddy, it's Lawrence.
Sorry to call so late,
I was stuck on set.
I'm so proud of you, man.
I know you don't think you
deserve this, but you do.
You are a true artist, Mr. Mast.
You followed your...
Jesus Christ. Cut!
Cut! Everyone just take five.
I'm sorry about that
last take, Lawrence.
What the fuck
is going on, man?
- I'm just a little out of it.
- You on drugs?
No, sir.
I just didn't get a lot
of sleep last night and...
Give me this. Don't
fucking lie to me.
This has been going on for a
while now. It has got to stop!
I don't know, I don't know
who the fuck you're hanging
out with, I don't know what
people are telling you,
but on my set, nobody
does drugs, all right?
That includes my actors.
So, go back to your trailer,
learn your fucking lines,
and come back in a half
hour ready to work.
All right?
[Jason] Yes, sir. I'm sorry,
it will never happen again.
Look, Jason, I know, I know
I'm hard on you, all right?
But that's because I
believe in you, man!
You're a great fucking actor.
You got something
really special.
You take this seriously,
you can go really
far in this business.
Just, you're 18 now,
man, don't fuck it up.
I'm really sorry.
And yes, sir.
I hear everything you're saying.
Good. Good.
Hey. Things, are
they better at home?
- Do you think I'm beautiful?
- Yeah.
Do you think I'm a star?
[Jason] Yes, I do.
You really think so?
[Jason] You're
really talented Mom.
I told you a gazillion times.
Oh, little man. [hiccups]
Little man, little man.
Do you think you're a star?
I guess.
Do you think you
have the looks?
What?
I think you need an operation!
What are you talking about?
I think you need a nose
job sweetie, it's too big.
You got the schnozz
from your father
and it's why you're
not booking. [hiccups]
[Jason] What are you
talking about, Mom?
I just did two huge movies.
Ugh.
I know baby, and
I am so, so, so,
so proud of you, but the phone
is not ringing and no one
is sending any other scripts.
So, what's next?
We have to think about
our future, now, okay?
So, we could just trim
a little right here...
Ow, ow, ow that hurts!
[laughs] Don't be such a baby!
You have to lighten up. [laughs]
Jesus, you are just
like your father,
so dramatic.
[Mother hiccups]
Uh, hey Lawrence.
Uh, it's Jason.
Remember that manager
you wanted me to meet?
I'm ready... Set up a meeting.
- [knocking]
- Jason, it's Celeste.
Well, I just wanted to
let you know that pretty
much everyone's gone.
Come on, open up. Jason!
Open this door right now or
I will have it busted down!
Hey, what is going on with you?
Why didn't you show
up to set today?
Oh uh, I'm uh, I'm just
uh, not feeling well.
Hey. Hey, hey, hey, come here.
Come here. Come on, come on.
All right, I'm just gonna take
off the glasses, all right?
Oh, my God. You look awful.
I'm pretty sick.
Bullshit. You're coming down.
Jason, you messed up big
time. Lawrence called.
He's done. He, he wants to
re-shoot all of your scenes.
What? No.
No, no, no look, I've... I've,
I've got it under control.
I'll, I'll get
clean. I, I promise.
Honey, no, no, no.
Honey, you don't!
All right? All right,
all right, listen to me.
I am not being your
manager right now.
I'm being your
friend. All right?
So now, I'm just gonna
go get your stuff,
we're gonna meet with Lawrence,
and you're gonna go into rehab.
What? I'm not going to rehab.
[Celeste] Yes you are!
I don't need to
listen to this shit.
Jason. Jason, wait!
Jason!
[knocking]
Jason?
Come on.
You know I plan on seeing
those eyes before I leave.
I'll be back.
Hey. I just want you to know,
I'm really proud of you.
I'm so proud of you.
This is not, look,
it's not easy,
a kid your age, to get clean?
That's amazing.
I owe it all to
you and Celeste.
- Well...
- I can't thank you enough.
Look, I'm so grateful for
everything you've done for me.
Uh, look, just, you did
this. Remember that, all right?
- Huh?
- I know. Thanks.
Come here. Come here, man.
All right. Get back
to work, all right?
Right back.
Hey, man! I never
thought I'd be doing this.
Doing, doing what?
I am drinking and I am
smoking with Ryan fucking Logan.
Man, I've seen every movie
you ever made. Twice.
And I think the film that
you did with Jason was
your best work yet.
That scene when you two
are by the campfire...
It's just a job, man. No, no!
It's just a job.
It is just like,
seriously, just like
- in "Boys of Summer" -
- Yeah.
When, when you two, it's just-
- Yeah, yeah, yeah. Enough.
Enough, enough...
How do you figure out how
to, you're so fucking real!
Dude, enough man!
Look, I'm not hanging out
with you because I need
another fan, okay?
Look, I, I have
enough fucking fans.
I am hanging out with you
because I think you're cool.
Why are you hanging
out with me, hm?
Because you want
your script read?
Because you think that I
can do something for you?
Because I am Ryan fucking Logan?
Man, I liked you
because you were real.
I'm sorry, but I'm a fan.
A big fucking fan, and
have been since I was 12.
And fuck you for
saying I'm not real.
I've been nothing but real
with you the whole night.
You know what? I do have
something I want to say to you.
You pick shitty fucking
movies. You're a great actor.
Shitty movies.
Last three you did?
Aside from the one with
Jason, sucked. No plot.
And, yeah, maybe I do want
you to read my script,
or something like it,
because you should be doing
something that matters!
Something that has
something to say!
- [knocking]
- Who is it?
It's me.
Where have you been?
Oh, looking for you.
[laughs] You again.
[Brody] Hey. Sorry I
was such a dick earlier.
I mean, I should go.
No one's going anywhere.
Oh yeah, Brody, please stay,
and tell me more about
what a great person I am.
I should, I should
probably go. Okay?
You want your script read?
That is messed up.
Come on, man, please
stay? I'll protect you.
Mm. Nope.
Dude, stay! I don't
do that shit any more.
Oh that's right. Well,
we'll see how long that lasts.
No, I should
probably go and find...
God, it looks like
you're not going anywhere.
I don't feel so well.
So, you were
discovered in a mall?
- Yeah.
- That's cool.
And now Jack Rossi
wants to put me in one
of his projects.
My friends back home
are gonna go crazy.
Maybe I could be on
yours and Alyssa's show.
He wants to bring
me in for a general.
When you go to meet with
him, bring your mother.
Can I please try some?
- No.
- Whatever, Heather.
I'll just find some random
guy to give it to me.
Okay! okay.
If you're gonna do it anyways,
I would rather
you do it with me.
But if you tell anyone
that I gave this to you,
I will deny it.
- Swear to God.
- I won't.
Just this one time,
our secret. Okay?
Promise.
[slow electronic music]
Dude, I feel like
I can't breathe!
- Dude, relax.
- Did I smoke too much?
I told you I can't
handle this shit.
Here, you're fine.
Just have another shot.
Dylan has some
pills you can take.
No, I took, I took
my fucking pills today!
- Well have some more.
- My god!
You're like, my little sister.
I gonna protect you.
Really? I never had a big
brother or sister before!
Well, now you do! It's me!
[both laughing]
Just chill, man.
I got you, okay?
I'll be right back.
No, where are you going?
Don't leave me...
Um. Here, come here.
Oh, god. Okay, just relax.
Of course I'm
gonna miss the show.
I love the show,
and I love working there and
everyone's so, so nice to me,
but I am getting
in Jason's movie,
and it's gonna be huge
and he's so talented,
he's like so amazing,
and I just, I just, I don't
even know how I could do
the show once I started
the movie and...
Oh my God! You could take
my place on the show!
I could like die in a car
accident or something,
and Caley, Caley?
Oh my God. Caley?
Baby? Caley.
Caley, please, please, please,
say something! Caley, Caley.
I love LA.
Still alive?
Barely.
You know, just been
embarrassing myself all night.
Sometimes I can
be a bit harsh,
especially when I'm busy
babysitting all of you.
Y'know, maybe you
need a babysitter.
That's not what I need.
I know what you need.
Are you flirting with me?
Maybe.
Meet me in your room in five.
Really?
Hurry up before
I change my mind.
Done!
I think I'm ready.
I'm gonna do it tonight.
I want Dylan to be my first.
Uh, you are not gonna lose
your virginity to Dylan Mast.
Yes I am. What's the big deal?
It's just sex.
Uh, it's a big deal.
But we have a connection.
No, you don't.
I was like in love with
him the moment I saw him.
Ooh, no, you weren't.
That's why I quit smoking
pot. I couldn't handle it.
It made everything
a little too real.
Oh, and the coke
makes the real go away?
I want you to know what you
said earlier messed me up.
What did I say?
You know what you said.
You said I was a mediocre,
coked out actress,
with a huge trust fund.
I'm so sorry. I, I, I didn't-
- No, it's fine!
It's fine. You were right!
No, and it made me
think and I hate people
that make me think.
Do you really think
I'm a mediocre actress?
- You all right?
- Uh. Yeah.
Uh, um, I'm, I'm just sweating.
Uh, we just disappeared
from the whole party.
- I'm gonna check on Jason.
- Hey! Just stay.
Okay. Just calm down.
Okay.
No! Never again.
Someone's awake.
No, it's fine.
Just go with it.
- Hey, baby.
- Eugh.
I'm so confused.
Don't be.
Get out of your head, man.
Stop thinking about
everything so much.
Hey. Just be here.
Believe me, I'd
love to, but I can't.
I can't.
Why? Because you're
in love with Heather?
I mean, do you think she
hasn't hooked up with anyone
else since you've been out here?
Because she made
out with me tonight.
[upbeat electronic music]
God, I needed that.
You are officially my boy toy.
But, I've gotta go,
there's still business
to handle tonight.
Don't you ever take a break?
I just did.
You know, lady,
you need more love in your
life cause I don't think
I've ever seen you smile.
Actually, you had a pretty
big grin on your face
about five minutes ago.
Eugh. You need to leave
while I get dressed.
Thank you very much.
Are you serious?
But we just has sex-
- Get out. Get out!
- This is my fucking room!
[Celeste] Get out,
boy toy! Get out!
What the, you're fucking crazy-
- [Celeste] Get the fuck out!
Go have your cigarette.
Stay away from Dylan Mast.
- I will.
- I'll meet you by the pool?
- Okay.
- There's my star.
- Hey, Jack.
I feel like you've been
avoiding me all night.
I haven't been avoiding you.
Don't think I don't know
what you and Celeste are up to.
What are you talking about?
Oh, you think I'm an idiot?
Celeste already told me you're
not re-signing on the show.
Well, I never
told Celeste that.
So, you are gonna
sign a new contract?
Would you stop the
bullshit, Heather.
You think you're gonna
get in Jason's movie,
then you don't need to re-sign
on the show cause you'll
be a big movie star.
And that, that's what you want
more than anything? Isn't it?
Isn't it. Isn't it?
Come on, Jack, make your move!
I could end your
fucking career.
Who even says I'm giving you
another season on the show?
Maybe I fire Heather
Hayes from the show 'cause
she's difficult on set,
or because of her
little drug problem.
Doesn't have to be like
that. Come on, beautiful.
I'm not your enemy. [laughs]
God, I can't do this.
Get off of me. Move out
of the way of the door.
- I want to leave.
- No.
This is not
gonna happen, Jack.
You mean it isn't
gonna happen again, Jack.
Get off of me!
I made you! Don't
you forget that!
You were nothing before my show!
Now you think you're
too good for me?
You fucked your way in,
and we both know it.
No!
Get off of me!
I made you! Don't
you forget that!
You were nothing before my show!
Now you think you're
too good for me?
You fucked your way in,
and we both know it.
That's not what
happened! Get off of me!
Shut the fuck up!
So the role is still
yours, if you want it.
Now you know what I want.
Busted. Fuck!
Fuck you Jack! You're going
down, you son of a bitch.
I got you. [laughs]
[Heather] Jason! I
need to talk to you.
Jason, please open up! Jason.
Jason! Open up! [panting]
Jason!
Jason, open up!
[knocking]
Jason, open up right now.
Jason, open up!
[knocking]
Jason, open up right...
What are these papers?
Who is this Celeste? You
made this woman your manager?
Are you fucking kidding me?
I am your mother, goddammit.
I am the one who got
your career started.
I gave up everything for
you and you are gonna leave
me with nothing?
Read your contract.
You get 10% of
everything until I die,
under one condition: you
stay out of my career,
and out of my life.
If you try to talk
to me or contact me,
that's a breach of contract,
and you get nothing.
Now, get out. We're done.
Baby, how can
you do this to me?
I am your mother.
No! You cared more about the
money than being my mother!
[Mother] No!
Baby, you're my son and I
just wanted you to be happy.
No, you wanted
me to be famous.
No, Jason. Baby, no.
No, this shit
won't work any more.
- Jason-
- Get out. Get out!
Get out of my house! My house!
Jason! Open up!
Let me in! Now!
- Jason, please open up!
- Hey!
- Hey.
- Are you okay?
I don't know.
Please, so I can talk to you.
Look, I, I want, I want
you know something, Heather.
I think you're beautiful
and you're very talented,
and I care about you.
But I would never cast you
in a role because I wanted
to sleep with you.
I want you in this
movie 'cause I think
you're an amazing actress.
I mean, all of this shit
you've been doing tonight,
come on, that's that's not you.
You are better than that!
This lifestyle. This
celebrity bullshit?
That's not why we do this.
People are gonna remember
you for something.
What's that gonna be?
[Both] Celebrity or an artist?
Jason, please.
Hey, are you okay?
Oh, yeah, I'm great! Now,
go find Brody, and go home.
I'll be in touch about
the script next week.
Oh, and don't worry about Jack.
I'm gonna take care of him.
What I say goes now.
[soft, upbeat music]
[Jason coughs]
♪ Another game ♪
♪ On a tie ♪
♪ It has a name ♪
♪ It's touched by, ooh ♪
Are you gonna stay and
hang out for a little while?
I can't drive right now.
Hey, we're good, right?
Yeah man, we're cool.
Alyssa?
God, you're gorgeous.
Shut up.
What's up your ass?
Just stop. I can't
keep doing this!
Wait, wait. Wait,
we had fun tonight.
That, that was, that
was good, right?
I need something more.
More from me?
No.
Come on, Ryan. Don't do this.
Come on. We got him.
Jason, my man! Oh,
was that hot or what?
Did the zoom work?
Fuck Alyssa, man!
I just wanna hang out with
you for the rest of the night.
I can't wait to see
that footage, man.
Nail that motherfucker!
Yeah, fuck him!
Fuck that guy!
You fucker!
You mother fucker!
Fuck you! [sobs]
You piece of shit.
Jason. Jason.
[knocking]
I'm shutting everything
down. I hope you're sleeping.
I'll check back before I leave.
[heart beating]
♪ Like the drone of ♪
♪ Silent moans it ♪
♪ Grows and grows 'til ♪
♪ Overblown and ♪
♪ Like the drone of ♪
♪ Silent moans it ♪
♪ Grows and grows 'til ♪
♪ Overblown and ♪
♪ Like the drone of ♪
♪ Silent moans it ♪
♪ Grows and grows 'til ♪
[tense music]
[surreal music]
And where have
you been hiding?
Have you been avoiding me?
I didn't know you
were looking for me?
I thought you were
looking for Heather.
Well, let me tell
you something, Carly.
I am always looking
for new talent.
Relax. We're just talking.
You know, the first time I
laid on eyes on you I knew
I'd seen that face.
You have that billboard
on Sunset. [chuckles]
I will bet there is not
a guy in LA that ain't
fantasizing about you.
I got to tell you, though,
you are even hotter
in person. [chuckles]
You're doing the right thing,
though, going into acting.
Modeling has a short lifespan.
That's exactly
what Celeste said.
She's right. You
should listen to her.
See, she knows what I like.
And she knows what it takes
to make it as an actress
in this business.
I've always wanted
to be an actress.
I even did all my school plays.
You did all your...
[laughs] Look at that face.
Do you know, I think you
have more star quality
than Heather Hayes.
Oh, no. She's so
gorgeous and so talented.
She's a fucking bitch.
Everybody knows it.
I wouldn't trust her if I were
you. She's got no loyalty.
And loyalty's everything to me.
Heather Hayes is finished
in this business.
- And do you know why?
- Why?
'Cause, I made her,
and I will end her.
Do you party?
- Of course, all the time.
- Good girl.
How would you like to be
the next Heather Hayes?
'Cause you're talking
to the right man.
I'm not comfortable.
Get off me!
What's the matter? Are
you not attracted to me?
I'm 16, you're, like,
old enough to be my dad.
Well that's not a very
polite thing to say, Carly.
It's Caley! Get off of me!
- Shut up!
- Get the fuck off of me!
Dylan! Dylan!
I feel so much better, man.
Tonight has been a great night.
Things are gonna
be different, okay?
I'm gonna make you proud of me.
You need a nose
job, sweetie. [laughs]
You got that schnozz
from your father.
- Hey. Jason?
- You look like shit, bro.
You're not gonna eat tonight.
Okay. Get over here.
Breathe. Breathe.
Okay? Take one of these.
Take one of these.
You'll feel better.
Okay? Just take it.
Just relax. Relax, okay?
I'll be back to check
on you. Just stay here!
I'll be back.
[Voice] No, no!
Fuck you!
Get out of my house! Get
out of my fucking house!
[Jason screams]
[Jason panting]
[voices shouting indistinctly]
Hey, I was looking
for you... Caley.
Caley?
Hey, you okay?
Caley, did something
happen with Dylan?
Caley.
Did something happen with Jack?
Just stay here and don't move,
okay? It's gonna be fine.
Caley. Caley!
[Jason coughs]
Caley. Come here. [coughs]
[Jason gasps]
Hey, man, I was
just... Oh shit!
- Holy shit!
- Dude, help me!
What are you doing?
Jesus Christ! Man, just
help me lift him to the bed!
- Hey Jason, Caley's-
- Heather! Hey!
I need you to find Alyssa
for me, right now, okay?
And see if Celeste is
still here! Hey, Jason.
Hey. Jason!
Can you hear me? Breathe man.
[Alyssa] Jason! Shut
that door right now!
I'm calling 911.
- No!
- What?
- You can't yet.
- Why?
Can you hear me? Jason?
Can you hear me?
- [knocking]
- It's Celeste! Let me in!
Oh, my God! There are
too many people in here!
- He's gonna die!
- He's not gonna die!
I'm calling an ambulance.
Oh, Brody, you're not
calling them. Give me that.
Get the fuck out of here!
What the fuck is
wrong with you people?
He's got to get to a hospital!
Brody's right!
We've got to get
him to a hospital!
Everybody needs to calm down.
I've dealt with this before.
I've got this.
Everybody calm down.
He's gonna be fine.
[Interviewer] So, how are
you handling everything?
I mean, you are everywhere now.
Your face is on billboards,
magazine covers,
it's like it happened overnight.
Is that weird for you?
It's cool, um,
I guess, y'know,
I'm not, I'm not sure I like it.
It kinda makes me nervous.
[Interviewer] You're
not sure you like what?
Being famous.
[soft music]
Jason?
[heart beating]
Jason, can you hear me?
Jason? Wake up!
- [knocking]
- What's going on in there?
Open the door!
- Oh shit.
- Don't open it!
- It's his brother!
- Open the door!
Where's Jason? Hey.
Hey, bro. It's me.
Jason!
- What did you give him?
- He was freaking out,
so I gave him something
to calm him down.
What was he on
tonight other than coke?
- Shit.
- Jesus Christ, Dylan,
- was he shooting?
- What!
[Dylan] I don't know.
Is there heroin in the house?
[Dylan] I'm not sure!
So he was doing
coke and heroin?
You gave it to him, didn't you?
- Wait, wait, wait!
- It's your fault, Dylan!
You killed him!
Um, wait! Wait wait wait.
[people shouting]
Celeste! Wait, wait, come on.
No! No, Jason!
My brother, he's convulsing.
We're in the Hollywood
Hills off Laurel Canyon.
I need you to send help. Shit!
Um, 10969 Mulholland. I am calm!
Just hurry!
Y'know, I'm just, I'm just
really excited about this film.
It's really saying
something, you know?
[Interviewer] I do.
But, what I'd really like
to talk about is the film
you're shooting now and
the rumors that have
been circulating in the
press about you missing days,
showing up late to set.
You know, I thought
we were here to talk
about my film that just opened.
[Interviewer] We
are, but my sources say
that you're about to be fired.
I thought you might
like to address that.
I don't.
[Interviewer] Okay,
and let me ask you this.
Is it true that you're about
to go into a rehab program?
You know what? This
interview is fucking done.
Fuck you! Fuck this!
You can fuck off!
[Interviewer] Jason!
[heart beating]
[siren wailing in distance]
[voices chattering indistinctly]
[slow, surreal music]
[Ryan] Dylan.
I didn't give him the heroin.
[Ryan] I know.
Give me the gun.
I'm his brother. I'm
supposed to take care of him.
You tried to keep him sober
tonight and I should've-
- Stop, Dylan.
Hey. Jason made his
own choices, okay?
Give me the gun.
It should be me. Not him.
- I'm the fuck-up.
- That's not true.
I didn't take care of him.
Hey! They did
this to him, okay?
Hey. Jason acted
like he was fine.
He was never fine.
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Hey! Hey!
Are you gonna let those
fucks kill you too? Hey.
Dylan, Dylan, Dylan! Look at me.
Look at me.
[Dylan sobbing]
What am I gonna do
without him? He...
I'm the fuck up. And
he's the strong one.
He's the strong one. [sobs]
Maybe he wasn't.
What are you both
still doing here?
Did you know how bad he was?
I didn't know he
was using again.
Did you see him tonight?
I thought it was
your job to know.
Excuse me? You
both need to leave.
The press is already
here and I have to go
out there and make a
statement and I don't want
them seeing you.
Is that seriously what
you're worried about right now?
I am trying to protect
you girls. It is-
- Oh, protect us? Did you
protect Jason tonight?
Did you protect her tonight?
What are you talking about?
I have been watching
her all night.
Did you see her with Jack?
What happened with Jack?
What did Jack do to you?
Tell me what happened...
Oh, you know exactly what
happened because you know
who Jack Rossi is.
Come on, Caley. You're
gonna come home with me.
Caley...
He did it to me, too.
The night that you sent
me to his hotel room
for that stupid TV show.
You're fired.
[Phone Answering
Machine] Hey. It's Jason.
I'm not here right now.
Leave a message, and
have an awesome day.
Hey. It's Jason.
I'm not here right now.
Leave a message, and
have an awesome day.
[tapping]
Hey.
You know, everyone's gonna
wake up today and think
they knew who Jason Mast was.
They have no fucking idea.
They're just obsessed with him,
because they think he has
everything that they want.
I wish everyone could be famous.
I wish everyone could get
everything that they ever
wanted so they could
fucking see it is not
what they think it is!
It is not what you think it is.
I know.
No, I knew him before
anyone even cared
who Jason Mast was.
He was the only
family I ever had.
[Ryan sobbing]
Hey.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm okay.
We're going home.
Caley's gonna come with us.
[Reporter] One of
Hollywood's finest young actors
is dead tonight.
Film star, Jason Mast,
died early this morning
at his house in the
Hollywood Hills.
[Reporter] It's a sad day in
Los Angeles as we regretfully
report the death of Hollywood
royalty, Jason Mast.
[Reporter] The cause of
his death is still unknown,
but the investigation
is looking into all
possibilities,
including suicide.
[Reporter] Jason Mast has
been most recently linked
to Hollywood's newest
sweetheart, Heather Hayes.
[Reporter] A 911 call came
from his Hollywood Hills home
at approximately
4:00 am this morning,
he was convulsing and
apparently having seizures.
The call came from his brother,
former actor, Dylan Mast.
[somber music]
[Camera Operator] Camera
speed, and we are rolling.
[Interviewer] So,
Jason, how do you feel
about your first
Oscar nomination?
Well, I'm grateful for
the nomination and honored
to be amongst some of the most
talented people of all time.
Um, but, in, in all honesty?
I don't think any of
this really matters.
It, it's not why I do it.
[Interviewer]
So, wait a minute,
are you saying you're not
happy about the nomination?
Oh, no, no. Not at all.
Um. But it doesn't make me
better than anyone else.
I never wanted the
fame, even as a kid.
I was just never comfortable
with the attention
that came outside of the work.
I think it's sad
that people care more
about celebrities than
what's going on in the world.
[Interviewer] But
that's Hollywood.
You know how the business works.
Oh, I know exactly
how the business works.
And the business
needs to change.
[Interviewer] So, then
why do you keep doing it?
Because I wanted
to be an artist.
You see artists...
Artists are like this lens
that we see life through.
They help us to think and
to feel in a more intense
and emotional way.
And that's, that's why we
fall in love with them.
Then we make them famous and
turn them into celebrities.
The money, the, the
greed, the power, uh,
the, the lies, that's what
kills the artist in us.
And, honestly, I think
we're all artists.
We're all, we're all
here to create something.
Think about that for a second.
You give a, a
two-year old a crayon,
and a, and a piece of paper,
and the kid knows
what to do with it.
They, they put the crayon to
paper and create something.
It's a natural instinct.
Art comes from the soul.
Um, sorry for rambling.
I just had to get that out.
[Interviewer] Well, I think
that was beautifully said.
I don't think this is the last
we'll be hearing from you.
No, definitely not.
[Interviewer] I wish you
great success with this film.
I think you've got a winner.
[soft music]
Thank you very much.
♪ Concrete calling ♪
♪ Screams aloud ♪
♪ Lights, too heavy to see ♪
[reporters shouting]
Over here!
♪ Capillaries crowd my veins ♪
[reporters shouting]
[Reporter] Well, 2019 is
off to an explosive start.
The recent sexual
allegations that rocked
Hollywood earlier this
year are about to be met
with another major controversy.
[Reporter] Some very
incriminating tapes have
recently surfaced online.
Confiscated from the home
of Jason Mast, on the day
of his death in 1994.
[Reporter] A secret
kept for 25 years.
[Reporter] The tapes had
quote, mysteriously disappeared.
[Reporter] Apparently, there
were cameras in many rooms
of the house the night
of Jason Mast's death.
Explicit videos...
[Reporter] Actress Heather
Hayes to give a statement
shortly about that night at
Jason Mast's house 25 years ago.
[Reporter] A recent video,
posted by Ryan Logan
has gone viral today.
[Reporter] In a new twist,
more and more men are coming
forward with allegations.
[Reporter] Jason Mast said
it in his last interview.
[Jason] I know exactly
how the business works,
and the business
needs to change.
♪ And cigarettes still
smell like cigarettes ♪
[audience applauding]
♪ I think I'd
rather just sleep ♪
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull