CAPTIONING MADE POSSIBLE BY
WARNER BROS.
DEAR LORD,
WE NEED A MIRACLE.
MAMA USED TO SAY THERE'S
2 THINGS WORTH BELIEVIN' IN--
GOD AND ATHENS FOOTBALL.
WELL, EVER SINCE
THE JACK SCHULER GAME,
PEOPLE AROUND HERE
HAVE HAD A HARD TIME
BELIEVIN' IN ANYTHING.
THIS TOWN'S GOT
ONE FOOT IN THE GRAVE.
IF YOU DON'T DO
SOMETHIN' SOON,
WE'RE GONNA LOSE
MORE THAN OUR SCHOOL.
Man: RACHEL!
WE GOTTA GO,
SWEETHEART.
SO, GOD...
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
IT'S ABOUT TIME
YOU SHOW UP AND...
SHOW OFF.
AMEN.
EVERY TIME
I TELL THIS STORY,
I START
WITH THAT SIMPLE PRAYER.
BUT THE STORY REALLY STARTS
12 YEARS BEFORE THAT DAY,
WITH ME AND MY DAD
AT THE HIGH SCHOOL
STATE CHAMPIONSHIP.
[BAND DRUMS BEATING RHYTHM]
ALL RIGHT, DOGS,
THEY'RE GONNA
EXPECT US TO PASS,
BUT WE ARE GONNA
LET THE BONE ROLL.
ALL RIGHT?
ALL RIGHT?!
1, 2, 3!
BREAK!
[CHEERING AND SHOUTING]
LISTEN, SON, I DON'T WANT
ANY FOOL HEROICS OUT THERE.
THIS TEAM NEEDS YOU NOW.
NOW, YOU'RE GONNA GO OUT THERE
AND BLOCK LIKE A BUICK.
ALL RIGHT?!
Announcer:
ROCK HILL, 28,
OUR CRUSADERS, 24.
WITH ONLY 8 SECONDS LEFT,
ATHENS IS 35 YARDS AWAY FROM
THEIR 17th STATE CHAMPIONSHIP.
COACH SCHULER
MIGHT HAVE TO RETHINK
HIS HATRED
FOR THE PASSING GAME.
BREAK!
DOWN!
SET! HUT!
[CROWD SHOUTING]
UHH!
[GAME-END HORN BLOWS]
Announcer:
THE GAME IS OVER.
ROCK HILL
HAS DEFEATED ATHENS,
BUT ALL EYES
ARE ON JACK SCHULER,
MOTIONLESS
ON THE ONE-YARD LINE.
Coach: JACK!
SON?
COME ON.
JACK.
Announcer: COACH SCHULER
IS KNEELING OVER HIS SON.
JACK HAS NOT MOVED
SINCE HE WENT DOWN.
COACH IS FRANTICALLY
MOTIONING FOR PARAMEDICS.
THIS DOES NOT LOOK GOOD.
WE'LL KEEP IT HERE
UNTIL WE KNOW MORE.
WHY DIDN'T YOU DO
WHAT I SAID?
WHAT I TOLD YOU TO DO?!
[SOBBING] JACK.
Rachel: WHEN COACH RETIRED
THE NEXT DAY AND LEFT TOWN,
PEOPLE BELIEVED ATHENS TRADITION
PRETTY MUCH LEFT WITH HIM.
HAVEN'T HAD
A WINNING SEASON SINCE.
SO WHEN THE RUMOR STARTED
THE COUNTY MIGHT
BE CLOSIN' THE HIGH SCHOOL,
NO ONE REALLY CARED,
THAT IS, UNTIL WE HEARD
THAT COACH WAS COMIN' BACK
FOR OUR LAST YEAR.
GUESS HE COULDN'T STAND SEEIN'
WHAT HE'D BUILT END THAT WAY.
ANYWAY, I MADE A DEAL WITH GOD
THAT IF HE'D DO HIS PART
TO KEEP THIS TOWN ALIVE,
I'D DO MINE.
RACHEL!
GOTTA GO, SWEETHEART.
SO, GOD,
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
IT'S ABOUT TIME YOU
SHOW UP AND SHOW OFF.
AMEN.
♪ WELL, I BEEN DREAMIN'
SINCE YESTERDAY EVENIN' ♪
♪ ABOUT A TIME AND A PLACE
WHERE I CAN BREATHE... ♪
Reporter:
ATHENS, ALABAMA,
ONCE THE FOOTBALL CAPITAL
OF THE SOUTH.
16 STATE CHAMPIONSHIPS
SINCE 1923.
BEAR BRYANT ONCE CALLED
ATHENS "THE MOTHER LODE
OF ALL-AMERICAN
FOOTBALL PLAYERS."
♪ NEAR THE EDGE
OF THE CROWD ♪
♪ I HEAR THE ANGELS ♪
♪ CALLING MY NAME
OUT LOUD ♪
DOZENS OF STUDENTS COME OUT
EACH YEAR TO TRY OUT
FOR THE ATHENS FOOTBALL TEAM
IN HOPES OF LANDING
THE JACK F. SCHULER
SCHOLARSHIP.
THE TOWN PROVIDES
A FREE RIDE
TO THE UNIVERSITY OF ALABAMA
FOR ONE STUDENT EACH YEAR
TO HONOR THE MEMORY
OF THE QUARTERBACK
WHO WAS KILLED IN
THE STATE CHAMPIONSHIP GAME
12 YEARS AGO.
♪ YOU'LL NEVER
TAKE ME DOWN ♪
BUT FOOTBALL IN THIS TOWN
HAS SEEN BETTER DAYS.
THEY HAVEN'T HAD
A WINNING SEASON
SINCE THAT INFAMOUS GAME,
AND COUNTY CUTBACKS
HAVE DOOMED THIS SCHOOL
FOR CLOSURE
AT THE END OF THE YEAR.
♪ IS GOIN' DOWN ♪
♪ NO NEED
TO HAND ME LIES ♪
TO SCRUTINIZE ♪
♪ 'CAUSE I KNOW THE WAY
THE WORLD WORKS ♪
♪ AND THE WAY THE EARTH
SPINS ROUND... ♪
BUT IF THERE WAS EVER
A GLIMMER OF HOPE
FOR THIS TOWN,
IT COMES IN THE NAME
OF COACH BUSTER SCHULER.
THE LEGENDARY COACH
WHO RETIRED
AFTER THE DEATH OF HIS SON
IS NOW RETURNING
FOR ATHENS' LAST YEAR,
AND WHEN A LEGEND
COMES OUT OF RETIREMENT,
THE FOOTBALL WORLD
TAKES NOTICE.
♪ YOU'LL NEVER
TAKE ME DOWN ♪
♪ OH, NO, NO ♪
♪ YOU'LL NEVER
TAKE ME DOWN ♪
♪ WELL, YOU CAN TIE ME UP ♪
♪ AND DRAG ME
TO THE EDGE OF THE WORLD ♪
♪ YOU'LL NEVER
TAKE ME DOWN ♪
YOU KNOW, I DON'T KNOW
IF WE HAVE ENOUGH.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND
WHY ALL THESE PEOPLE COME
JUST TO WATCH TRYOUTS.
ONE WORD:
SCHOLARSHIP.
2 WORDS:
NO LIFE.
SHOW 'EM WHAT YOU GOT, BABY.
LET THE BONE ROLL.
HI, MAMA!
SHE DRESS YOU THIS MORNING,
TOO, NATERS?
WELL, I'LL SEE YOU WHEN
WE DOIN' TACKLING DRILLS, HUH?
NONE OF Y'ALL
GONNA BE LEFT.
I'M GONNA WIN
THAT SCHOLARSHIP, BOYS.
WHOA, GIVE ME A LITTLE
PUFFY-PUFF ON THAT
BEFORE YOU THROW IT OUT.
MORNING, TEE.
MORNING.
YOU KNOW, I WAS JUST
THINKING THAT YOUR DINER
WOULD BE A GREAT PLACE
TO PUT THESE PAMPHLETS.
SWEETHEART,
IT'S A DEAD END,
AND I DON'T
WANT MY CUSTOMERS
TO HAVE A DAILY
REMINDER OF IT.
OH, COME ON, TEE,
YOU'VE BEEN HERE
A LONG TIME.
THIS TOWN
HAS GIVEN YOU A LOT.
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA
GIVE BACK?
THANK YOU.
[CHUCKLES]
Quarterback:
DOWN! SET! HUT!
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
Quarterback: LINE IT UP!
LINE IT UP. HUT!
VINCE LOMBARDI ONCE SAID,
"A GREAT COACH IS 50% TEACHER
AND 50% S.O.B."
I WANT TO THANK YOU ALL FOR
YOUR TIME AND YOUR SPIRIT.
BUT RIGHT NOW,
I WANT ANYBODY WHO IS
NOT WEARING A JOCKSTRAP
TO GET OFF MY FIELD.
THANK YOU FOR COMING,
NOW, BYE-BYE.
50%.
Man: COACH.
ALL RIGHT, YOU DOGS
THAT ARE LEFT...
YOU SMELL THAT?
WHAT IS THAT?
[SNIFFS]
YEAH, THAT'S IT.
THAT'S IT.
EVERYBODY ON YOUR FACES.
DOWN ON YOUR FACES!
OLD MAN'S CRAZIER
THAN WE HEARD.
NOW BREATHE DEEP.
DO YOU SMELL IT?
THAT, DOGS,
IS THE SMELL OF DEATH.
OVER A DECADE
OF DEAD HOPES AND DREAMS
BURIED RIGHT HERE.
THE CURSE OF INDIVIDUALISM
GROWS LIKE A WEED
ON THIS FIELD.
A CURSE THAT WE CALL
THE JACK F. SCHULER
SCHOLARSHIP.
I DIDN'T SAY
TO LIFT YOUR HEAD, SON.
KEEP YOUR FACE
IN THE GRASS.
IT FOSTERS
VISIONS OF GRANDEUR,
DREAMS OF PERSONAL GLORY.
IT GUARANTEES DISUNITY...
AND PRIDEFUL INDIVIDUALISM,
AND WORST OF ALL,
WORST OF ALL...
LOSING SEASONS.
HEAR THIS, DOGS:
I AM THE CURE
TO THIS CURSE.
[CHEERING AND SHOUTING]
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
SON, COME ON.
THANKS FOR COMIN' OUT.
BAND PRACTICE IN THE GYM.
[BLOWS WHISTLE]
JOHN, THANKS, BUT
UNLESS YOU CAN KICK,
I DON'T WANT ANYBODY
UNDER 165.
ALL RIGHT, THIS IS
5-A COMPETITION.
I WANT BOYS RAISED
ON MEAT AND POTATOES.
I LIKE MY STEAK RARE
AND POTATOES MASHED,
AND I'M 173.
SON...
DON'T EVER,
EVER STICK YOUR PAW
IN THIS CAGE.
YOU GONNA PAY
FOR THAT IN SWEAT.
HUT!
Coach Schuler: UP, DOWN.
UP, DOWN. UP, DOWN, UP.
[BLOWS WHISTLE]
ALL RIGHT.
YOU ALL RIGHT, SON?
THANKS FOR COMIN' OUT.
I HEAR THE SOCCER TEAM
NEEDS A LITTLE HELP.
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
All: ARRRRR!
DO YOU LIKE FOOTBALL!
MOVE THOSE FEET!
[ALL GRUNT]
DO YOU LIKE FOOTBALL?
124.
SORRY, SON. THANKS FOR
COMIN' OUT. STEP DOWN.
OHH.
YOU GOTTA BE KIDDIN' ME.
ELVIS JACKSON.
HMM.
171.
SCALE'S LIGHT.
YOU ARE.
WITHOUT A DOUBT.
SHERMAN NATERS.
SHERMANATOR.
[CHUCKLES]
ALL RIGHT.
165.
THAT'S RIGHT, BABY.
ONE SMALL STEP
FOR ATHENS FOOTBALL
AND ONE GIANT STEP BACKWARDS
FOR WOMEN'S RIGHTS.
MM-HMM.
OHH, OH, NO. NUMBER 40.
I MEAN, MANDATORY SWAP.
IT'S ARTICLE 3, SECTION 2
OF THE EX-BOYFRIEND MANUAL.
SO IT'S THE EX-BOYFRIEND
MANUAL AGAIN.
LISTEN, I TAKE A BACK SEAT
4 MONTHS OUT OF A YEAR
TO THIS VERY LAME
AND STUPID GAME,
AND I'M OVER IT.
HE'S A SCHULER.
THE MOMENT
HAS ARRIVED.
[ALL CHEER]
SETTLE DOWN,
HERE WE GO.
GASH. CATCH.
BE ABOUT THE ONLY THING
I CATCH THIS YEAR, HUH?
THAT'S THE WAY
THE BONE ROLLS.
SHERMANATOR.
WEAR IT WELL, SON.
THANKS, COACH.
SCHULER.
THANKS. I LOOK FORWARD
TO STARTING FOR YOU, SIR.
HEY.
WELL, WELCOME
TO ATHENS.
SEE, EVER SINCE
I WAS LITTLE,
I'VE BEEN
LOOKIN' FORWARD
TO SENIOR SEASON.
AND EVER SINCE
I WAS LITTLE,
I HAVE BEEN WEARING
NUMBER 40.
SEE, TRADITION IS,
WELL, IT'S
REAL IMPORTANT
AROUND THESE PARTS.
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA
WHO WORE NUMBER 40?
GALE SAYERS.
THE WAY I FIGURE IT,
THE FASTEST MAN ON THE TEAM
SHOULD HAVE NUMBER 40.
TELL YOU WHAT.
YOU UH, YOU PROVE
YOU DESERVE THIS,
YOU COULD HAVE IT BACK.
JUST HANG ON
FOR ONE SECOND.
SEE, NOW,
YOU'RE NEW. I'M NOT,
BUT I AM ONE
HECK OF A NICE GUY,
SO HERE'S
WHAT I'M GONNA DO.
I'M JUST GONNA GIVE
YOU A LITTLE BIT
OF FREE ADVICE, OK?
DON'T TUG
ON SUPERMAN'S CAPE.
I DON'T NEED TO.
I'M THE ONE
HOLDING IT.
I FORGOT
TO TELL YOU BOYS
MAKE SURE
THEY KNOW AT HOME
ABOUT THE DOUBLE-DAYS
ON MONDAY.
AND IF I HEAR ABOUT ANY
ALTERCATIONS IN THE RANKS,
TRUMAN DEALT MORE MERCY
TO HIROSHIMA...
NAGASAKI.
TAKE A SHOWER, SON.
OH, MY GOD.
IMPOSSIBLE.
CAN I JUST GET
A CUP OF HOT WATER?
THAT'S ALL. THANKS.
WE CLOSE DOWN
FOR FOOTBALL.
AHH.
SURE IS NICE
TO BE ABLE
TO LEAVE EARLY.
GOOD HAVIN' YOU
AROUND.
THANKS, TEE.
NOW, WHAT KIND OF MAMA
NAMES HER BABY ELVIS?
WHAT KIND OF MAMA NAMES
HER BABY SHERMAN NATERS?
WHOO.
LOCK IT WHEN YOU LEAVE.
[LAUGHS]
TEE?
TEE, ARE YOU HERE?
Elvis:
DECEMBER 12, 1965.
GALE SAYERS MADE
FOOTBALL HISTORY
WITH 6 TOUCHDOWNS
IN ONE GAME,
A FEAT
NEVER MATCHED SINCE.
[IMITATES CHEERING]
TOUCHDOWN NUMBER ONE
COMES IN THE FIRST QUARTER.
AN 80-YARD STREAM PASS.
HUT, HUT, HUT!
OH, YEAH!
TOUCHDOWN 2 IS A 21-YARD
TEAR THROUGH 4 DEFENDERS
AT LIGHTNING SPEED.
TOUCHDOWNS 3, 4, AND 5
ARE VINTAGE ELVIS.
JUKING, HIGH-STEPPING,
WHO'S YOUR DADDY?
LINING FEVER DREAMS.
YOU ARE, ELVIS.
OPEN FIELD.
THAT'S RIGHT.
IMPROV, BABY.
GALE SAYERS WITNESSES...
IN HIS PRIME.
WISHES HE COULD KEEP
WITH THIS WILD BUCK!
BUT THE SIXTH--
OH, BABY--
THE SIXTH
AND FINAL TOUCHDOWN
IS A THING OF BEAUTY.
AN 85-YARD PUNT RETURN.
OH, HE'S GOT IT.
OH, MY GOD!
TOUCHDOWN!
OH, YEAH! UH-HUH! UH-HUH!
BOOM! GRR!
GRR!
[GASPS]
I WAS JUST
LOOKING FOR TEE...
AND...DEFINITELY
NOT UNDER HERE.
I'M RACHEL.
YOUR F.C.A.
PRAYER WARRIOR.
NO. I KEEP
YOUR GAME HELMET
TILL FRIDAY NIGHT.
IT'S KIND OF
A VISUAL REMINDER
THAT I NEED
TO PRAY FOR YOU.
I DO OK ON MY OWN.
A GENTLEMAN
WOULD WALK ME HOME.
LET ME KNOW
WHEN YOU FIND ONE.
HEY, ELVIS.
I JUST WANTED
TO MAKE SURE
THAT THAT WAS
REALLY YOUR NAME.
CUTE.
SEE? I KNEW YOU HAD
A SENSE OF HUMOR.
YOU MIGHT AS WELL FACE IT.
YOU'RE STUCK WITH ME
FOR THE REST OF THE SEASON.
THAT IS,
IF YOU MAKE IT THAT LONG.
"IF"?
OH, I KNOW WHY
GUYS LIKE YOU
COME TO ATHENS.
HA HA.
I HATE TO BREAK IT TO YOU,
BUT BRIAN, THE GUY
WHOSE JERSEY YOU COMMANDEERED,
HE'S A SHOO-IN
FOR THE SCHOLARSHIP,
THE COACH'S NEPHEW.
EVERY ONE OF THE SCHULERS
HAVE GONE TO 'BAMA
SINCE BEAR BRYANT.
MAYBE THIS AIN'T
HIS YEAR.
SO...
WHAT SHOULD I PRAY FOR?
GREEN GRASS.
OK.
Coach Schuler: DOGS,
PASSING FOOTBALL
LIVES BY 3
OF GOD'S LOST COMMANDMENTS.
COMMANDMENT 1: THOU SHALT
RUN THE WISHBONE OFFENSE.
COMMANDMENT 2: THOU SHALT
NEVER FUMBLE MY BALL.
COMMANDMENT 3:
THOU SHALT DO IT MY WAY
ALL THE TIME!
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
YOU A CRUSHER, GO ON, MOVE!
[BLOWS WHISTLE]
WITH APOCALYPTIC FORCE!
TO THE NUTS,
DOGS!
THE MARROW
OF THE BONE!
[BLOWS WHISTLE]
AW.
[ALL LAUGH]
85!
21!
49!
40!
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
YOU ALL HEAR THAT, HUH?
THAT'S THE FIRST TIME
I HEARD
THE BIG BANG ALL DAY!
THAT'S THE SOUND
OF PERCUSSION!
YOU A TOUGH GUY,
JACKSON?
NO, SIR.
SAY AGAIN?
NO, SIR,
I JUST WANT MY TURN.
YOU FLOSS
WITH BARBED WIRE
AND GARGLE
WITH GASOLINE, BOY?
55!
21!
13!
TAKE HIM DOWN!
THAT'S 42!
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
ALL RIGHT, LADIES,
THAT'S ENOUGH.
Coach Schuler:
HEY, HEY!
BACK OFF! BACK OFF!
CLEAR OUT! CLEAR OUT!
CLEAR OUT!
HEY, IT'S OVER!
GET UP! GET UP!
WHERE'S
YOUR DISCIPLINE, SON?
IT'S OVER!
WHAT'S GOIN' ON HERE?
ANYONE WANT TO TELL ME
WHY TWO OF MY PLAYERS
IN A HEAD-ON COLLISION?
SIR, IT WAS ELVIS.
HE STARTED IT.
WHY, THANK YOU, SON.
YOU CAN GO HOME NOW.
YOU'RE OFF THIS TEAM.
GO ON, NOW.
ANYONE ELSE?
WANT TO TELL ME
WHAT HAPPENED?
COME ON, NOW, COME ON.
FESS UP.
I'LL MAKE YOU RUN
FROM HERE TO ETERNITY.
COACH?
BRIAN STARTED IT.
THANK YOU, SON.
THANK YOU.
YOU CAN GET OFF
OUR FIELD NOW.
WE APPRECIATE IT.
ALL RIGHT? GET OUT!
ANY MORE TRAITORS?!
COME ON, FESS UP.
OH, THAT'S HOW
IT'S GONNA BE, IS IT?
YOU KNOW,
SILENCE IS A LIE, DOGS.
IT'S A LIE OF OMISSION.
AND IN ALABAMA...
CRIMES GET PUNISHED.
♪ LEANING, LEANING ♪
♪ SAFE AND SECURE
FROM ALL ALARMS ♪
♪ LEANING, JESUS ♪
♪ LEANING ON
THE EVERLASTING ARMS ♪
HEY, SON!
YOU AND I BOTH KNOW
WHY YOU'RE HERE,
SO WHY DON'T YOU
JUST SAVE THE BOTH OF US
SOME TIME AND ENERGY
AND LIMP ON OUTTA HERE.
I CAME HERE
TO PLAY FOR YOU.
NO, YOU DIDN'T,
NO, YOU DIDN'T.
YOU CAME HERE
TO PLAY FOR YOU.
THAT'S WHY YOU VIEW
THIS TEAM AS A THREAT.
YOU GOT ONE THING
ON YOUR MIND:
PLAYIN' TIME.
I'M GONNA MAKE IT
CRYSTAL CLEAR FOR YOU:
YOU ARE NOT GONNA PLAY
ONE MINUTE FOR ME.
[HUSHED TONE]
COACH.
LISTEN TO ME.
NEPHEW OR NOT,
YOU GET TREATED THE SAME
AS EVERYONE ELSE.
C-COACH, HOW AM I
GONNA GET A CHANCE
AT THIS SCHOLARSHIP
IF I DON'T GET A CHANCE
TO THROW THE BALL?
NEVER MIND
ABOUT THE SCHOLARSHIP.
I--YOUR NAME IS NOT
MORE IMPORTANT THAN THIS TEAM.
IF YOU DIDN'T LEARN THAT
FROM YOUR COUSIN,
THEN YOU GOT PROBLEMS.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
I TOLD YOU.
I WON'T PLAY SECOND
TO FOOTBALL.
AND, UM, YOU'VE
MADE YOUR CHOICE.
NOW LIVE WITH IT.
YOU KNOW,
FORGET IT, OK?
JUST...[SIGHS]
[BELL RINGS]
YOU'D THINK THERE WAS
A FOOTBALL GAME TONIGHT.
[ALL CHEER]
Announcer: WELCOME TO ATHENS
HIGH SCHOOL FOOTBALL!
A CAPACITY CROWD SETTLES IN
FOR THE CRUSADERS
VERSUS THE BALDWIN BEAR CATS,
BUT THE REAL STORY HERE
IS THE RETURN
OF COACH BUSTER SCHULER
FOR WHAT COULD BE
ATHENS' FINAL SEASON.
[ALL CHEER]
LAST THING--
CRUSADERS RESPECT
THE MEN IN STRIPES.
THEY GOT A JOB TO DO.
[ALL CHEER]
HOW COULD YOU MISS
THE FACE MASK?
YOU ARE STILL
THE WORST REF IN AMERICA!
YOUR WIFE AND CHILDREN MUST
BE HIDING THEIR FACES IN SHAME!
OH, THAT'S GOOD!
THAT'S THE FIRST GOOD CALL
YOU MADE ALL NIGHT.
YOU ARE. WITHOUT A DOUBT.
[BLOWS WHISTLE]
HOLD ON!
THE GAME IS FOOTBALL!
LET'S ACT
LIKE WE KNOW IT!
WANT TO GO
TO THE SNACK SHACK?
[BLOWS WHISTLE]
OH, THIS AIN'T THE GAME
I BEEN WAITIN' TO SEE.
HUH. THE GAME YOU
BEEN WAITIN' TO SEE?
THERE AIN'T NO GAME
GOIN' ON OUT THERE, TEE.
Announcer: SCHULER'S
WISHBONE OFFENSE
OFF TO A ROUGH START,
BUT I'M SURE COACH
WILL INSPIRE THE TROOPS
HERE AT THE HALF.
[SHOUTING AND ARGUING]
WHY DON'T YOU
GET ON THE BALL?!
HEY, HEY! KNOCK IT OFF!
HOW MANY TIMES DID I
TALK TO YOU ABOUT DISCIPLINE?
THAT'S ALL RIGHT,
GO AHEAD.
YOU GO ON AND
FIGHT WITH EACH OTHER.
GO AHEAD,
FEED THE CURSE.
GO ON!
YOU ARE. WITHOUT A DOUBT.
I HAVE BLED
EVERY POSSIBLE
DROP OF SWEAT
OUT OF YOUR BODIES,
SO THERE'S ONLY ONE THING
LEFT TO DO.
I'M GONNA SHOOT STRAIGHT
WITH YOU.
YOU ARE A PACK
OF PATHETIC,
CURSE-INFESTED...
ME, MYSELF, AND Is,
AND YOU ARE GONNA
HAVE THE WORST SEASON
IN THE HISTORY OF FOOTBALL
UNLESS JESUS CHRIST HIMSELF
COMES DOWN ON A WHITE HORSE
AND SUITS UP!
♪ WORRIED ♪
♪ WORRIED AS A MAN CAN BE ♪
HOW COULD THEY OPEN
A HOLE THAT BIG?
CAN ANYBODY
TELL ME THAT?
ANYBODY ANYWHERE?
♪ BABY, WORRIED AS A MAN
CAN BE... ♪
CALL TIME-OUT.
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
SHERMANATOR!
TIME-OUT!
YOU'RE OFF!
♪ YEAH ♪
♪ I'M GONNA WALK
TO THE BUS STATION, BABY ♪
♪ WITH A SUITCASE
IN MY HAND ♪
♪ YEAH ♪
Announcer: THE CRUSADERS
ARE DOWN BY 20,
AND WITH 15 SECONDS LEFT,
IT'S PRETTY MUCH
PRACTICE TIME FOR BOTH TEAMS.
THE CRUSADERS WILL
START THE SEASON 0 AND 1.
COACH TOLD ME
TO COME IN FOR YOU.
RESURRECT.
DON'T GIVE UP, BOY.
RESURRECT!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
THEY SENT IN
THE CAVALRY.
RESURRECT.
READY?
All: READY!
READY!
[BLUES GUITAR
PLAYS LICKS]
WHAT IS JACKSON DOING
ON MY FIELD?
♪ YEAH ♪
PULL HIM!
GET HIM OUT OF THERE!
SHERMANATOR!
TIME-OUT!
HEY, SHERMANATOR!
PLAY SOME DEFENSE!
YOU NANCY MAMA'S BOY!
HIKE!
♪ YEAH ♪
NO, NO, NO,
NO, NO, NO!
♪ I GOT A COAL-BLACK MARE ♪
♪ OH, LORDY,
HOW THAT HORSE CAN RUN ♪
♪ I GOT A COAL-BLACK MARE ♪
♪ OH, LORDY,
HOW THAT HORSE CAN RUN ♪
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
Announcer: INTERCEPTION
RETURNED FOR A TOUCHDOWN
BY NUMBER 40,
NEWCOMER ELVIS JACKSON.
SPORTS FANS, I HAVEN'T SEEN
ANYTHING LIKE THAT IN YEARS.
MAKES YOU WONDER
WHERE HE'S BEEN ALL GAME.
WE LOST, IDIOT.
HEY.
GRASS LOOKED
PRETTY GREEN TONIGHT.
MAYBE YOU SHOULD
HOLD ON TO THIS.
WHOA! HECK OF A RUN,
40, HECK OF A RUN!
SHAZAM!
[KISSES HIM]
YOU THE MAN!
SHAZAM! YOU THE MAN!
SHAZAM.
WHO WAS THAT GUY?
WELL, MAYBE NEXT TIME
YOU WON'T HAVE TO SNEAK
INTO THE GAME.
YOU KNOW,
THE WAY I SEE IT,
WELL, SINCE YOU GOT
YOUR GREEN GRASS OR WHATEVER,
WHY, I THINK
YOU OWE ME A FAVOR.
REALLY?
I WANT YOU AT THIS MEETING
ON THURSDAY NIGHT.
NO EXCUSES.
♪ IT SLIPPED AWAY LIKE ICE
THROUGH MY FINGERS... ♪
NICE TRY, SCHULER.
IT BREAKS MY HEART,
ESPECIALLY ON
YOUR BIG RETURN AND ALL.
YOU SANCTIMONIOUS
LITTLE PISSANT,
WE'RE GONNA EAT YOUR GUTS
WITH A SPOON IN THE PLAYOFFS.
NOT WITH THAT
STONE-AGE OFFENSE,
YOU OLD BAG OF BONES.
AHH.
[OVERLAPPING
CONVERSATIONS]
SHH! SHH!
WE REGRETFULLY INFORM YOU
THAT THE MEMBERS
OF THE COUNTY SCHOOL BOARD
WILL BE UNABLE TO ATTEND
TONIGHT'S MEETING.
PLEASE ACCEPT OUR APOLOGIES.
[AUDIENCE GROANING]
YOU CAN'T JUST
LET IT END LIKE THAT.
I KNOW.
IF THE COUNTY'S NOT
GONNA SUPPORT YOU,
YOU GOTTA DO IT
YOURSELF.
OK.
YOU KNOW, IF...
IF THE COUNTY'S NOT
GONNA SUPPORT OUR SCHOOL,
WE HAVE TO DO IT OURSELVES.
[CHEERING AND APPLAUSE]
A LOT OF PEOPLE
HAVE BEEN LEAVING THIS TOWN
OVER THE LAST FEW YEARS,
BUT THE PEOPLE IN THIS GYM,
THE PEOPLE IN THIS GYM
LOVE THIS TOWN.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
AND THEY LOVE THIS SCHOOL.
AND THERE ARE
SOME OF US STUDENTS
WHO DON'T WANT TO BE BUSSED
TO SOME OTHER SCHOOL.
YOU KNOW, EVERYBODY
IS ALWAYS SAYING,
"PUT YOUR MONEY
WHERE YOUR MOUTH IS."
WELL, I THINK
THAT IF WE SHOW THAT WE
ARE WILLING TO DO OUR PART,
THEN THE COUNTY BOARD WILL
KNOW THAT WE ARE SERIOUS.
OH, BOY.
HERE WE GO,
YOU'RE SOUNDING
LIKE CHURCH, GIRL.
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
NO, I'M NOT ASKING
YOU FOLKS FOR A DIME.
WE HAVE ALREADY
GOT THE MONEY.
IT IS CALLED
THE JACK SCHULER
SCHOLARSHIP FUND.
AND THERE ARE THOUSANDS
OF DOLLARS IN IT
THAT WE COULD USE
FOR SAVING OUR SCHOOLS.
NOW--OH, COME ON, FOLKS.
COME ON, YOU HAVE GOT--
YOU'VE GOT YOUNGER KIDS.
I MEAN, DO YOU REALLY WANT
THEM GOING TO ROCK HILL?
WE CAN HELP 300 KIDS
INSTEAD OF JUST
ONE FOOTBALL PLAYER.
ELVIS.
I'M SORRY.
SAVE YOUR PRAYERS.
I DON'T NEED 'EM.
AND I DON'T WANT
A GROUPIE.
THE OTHER TEAM'S
NOT YOUR ENEMY.
THE SPIRIT OF DIVISION,
THAT'S YOUR ENEMY.
NOW HERE...
HERE'S A VISION OF UNITY.
ROCK HILL.
UNDEFEATED FOR 3 YEARS.
NOT EVEN OUTSCORED
FOR ONE HALF!
THIS TEAM
IS A WELL-OILED MACHINE.
MMM, MMM, MMM.
THIS IS DETROIT V-8
SCREAMING DOWN THE HIGHWAY
TO THE STATE FINAL.
THIS TEAM HAS MASTERED
THE FUNDAMENTALS,
BUT YOU DOGS HAVE NOT.
NOW...
SOME OF YOU MAY BE
JOINING THEM NEXT YEAR,
BUT UNTIL THEN, WE ARE
GOING TO DO THINGS MY WAY!
AND THAT MEANS...
WE START ALL OVER AGAIN!
GO ALL THE WAY BACK
TO THE BEGINNING
WHEN GOD CREATED FOOTBALL.
THIS...
IS PURE, GENUINE,
AMERICAN LEATHER.
18 OUNCES...
OF PIGSKIN AND AIR
SEWN AROUND A RUBBER SACK.
8 LACES ACROSS THE TOP.
THESE, THESE ARE
SHOULDER PADS!
THIS IS A KNEE PAD!
THIGH PAD!
HELMET!
EACH ONE OF THOSE THINGS
HAS ITS OWN
SPECIFIC FUNCTION!
AND YOU ALL ARE
GOING TO REDISCOVER
YOUR SPECIFIC FUNCTION
ON THIS TEAM!
I'LL SEE YOU OUTSIDE.
WE'RE GONNA START
WITH THE SHOULDER PADS.
FIRST, WE CRAWL,
THEN WE WALK,
AND THEN
WE WALK TOGETHER...
AND THEN WE RUN THE BONE.
LINE 'EM UP.
OFFENSE.
DEFENSE.
JACKSON, YOU COME IN
AT HALFBACK.
KENNEDY,
YOU SIT THIS ONE OUT.
YOU WANT IN THE GAME,
YOU'RE GONNA LEARN TO BONE.
WE'RE GONNA SKIP A STEP.
YOU'RE GONNA LEARN
THE OLD-FASHIONED WAY.
CRIME GETS PUNISHED
IN 'BAMA.
FORMATION: LEFT-39. ON ONE.
Quarterback:
READY?
All: BREAK!
DOWN.
1-18...1-18...
SET...
HUT.
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
NO, NO, NO, NO!
YOU JUST RAN
30 YARDS TO MAKE 5!
THOSE 7 DOGS OVER THERE
ARE WORKING
TO MAKE A HOLE FOR YOU.
YOUR JOB IS TO RUN UPFIELD,
AND WHEN YOU GET THERE,
TRUST THE HOLE'S
GONNA BE OPEN.
IF YOU IGNORE THEM,
THEY BECOME USELESS.
LET'S LINE UP,
RUN IT AGAIN.
TRUST YOUR BLOCKERS!
HERE WE GO.
LINE IT UP.
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
ONE MORE TIME.
HUT.
FORMATION: LEFT-39,
ON ONE.
UHH!
ON 2 THIS TIME.
I WANT YOU
TO RUN THIS WAY!
NOT THAT WAY...
THIS WAY!
DON'T RUN ON
GAIN AND MAINTAIN!
NOW RUN STRAIGHT!
HIT THE HOLE!
HUT.
UHH!
FORMATION:
LEFT-39, ON ONE.
Coach Schuler:
ONE MORE TIME.
TRY FOR FORMATION:
39-LEFT, ON ONE.
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
ARE YOU ON EMPTY, ELVIS?
IS THAT IT?
[BLOWS WHISTLE]
WATER BREAK.
NO, NO, NOT FOR YOU, DOG.
TILL YOU LEARN
TO TRUST YOUR TEAMMATES,
YOU AIN'T GOOD ENOUGH
TO DRINK WITH 'EM.
WHERE YOU LOOKING, DOG?
I'M STANDING RIGHT HERE,
RIGHT OVER YOU.
COME ON, SON.
I KNOW YOU WANT TO.
NOW YOU GOT A REASON TO.
AIN'T NOBODY IN THE WORLD
WOULD BLAME YOU.
THAT'S JUST WHAT I THOUGHT.
I DON'T NEED A QUITTER.
[GROANS]
THIS IS NOT OVER.
I AM NOT
OFF THIS TEAM.
YOU HEAR ME?
ONE MORE TIME.
[BLOWS WHISTLE]
LET'S GO HOME.
ELVIS.
WHAT HAPPENED?
TRADITION.
[NOW AND THEN PLAYING]
♪ I KNOW WHERE I'M BOUND ♪
♪ AND WHERE I'M SAFE ♪
♪ AND WHERE I'M LEFT ALONE ♪
♪ I KNOW NO WAY...♪
YOU'RE TRESPASSING.
NOW GO AWAY.
♪ AND I WANNA GO HOME ♪
♪ STAY WITH ME NOW...♪
WHAT ARE YOU
DOING HERE?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING
FOLLOWING ME?
I WAS AFRAID
YOU WERE HURT.
AH, LET ME GUESS.
YOU WANTED
TO PRAY FOR ME.
AS A MATTER OF FACT,
NO!
OUCH!
THAT'S WHAT
I WANTED TO DO.
I AM NOT TRYING TO STEAL
YOUR SCHOLARSHIP.
AND WHETHER OR NOT
YOU LIKE IT,
IT IS MY JOB
TO PRAY FOR YOU,
SO YOU MIGHT AS WELL
JUST GET USED TO IT.
WHY DON'T YOU JUST ADMIT
THAT YOU BETRAYED ME?
OH, WHY DON'T
YOU JUST ADMIT
YOU'RE ACTING LIKE
A LITTLE 3-YEAR-OLD?
ALL RIGHT.
I ACCEPT
YOUR APOLOGY.
WOW. THIS LITTLE GROUPIE
IS JUST OVERWHELMED.
WELL, SINCE YOU
APOLOGIZED FIRST,
I GUESS
I ACCEPT YOURS, TOO.
I'M ON YOUR TEAM, ELVIS.
LONG BEFORE
I LAID EYES ON YOU,
I THOUGHT THAT WE COULD USE
THAT MONEY FOR THE SCHOOL.
I DON'T WANT TO HURT YOU.
EXCEPT FOR MY ARM.
SO WHAT HAPPENED TODAY?
GOOD OLD
ATHENS TRADITION.
YOU KNOW, LAST TIME
COACH SCHULER WAS HERE,
OUR SCHOOL WAS
THE ENVY OF THE STATE.
HIS COMING BACK, IT...
GAVE ME HOPE AGAIN.
THINK YOU COULD LEARN
SOMETHING FROM HIM?
SO WHY ARE YOU UP HERE?
WHY ARE YOU UP HERE?
THIS IS
MY LAST SHOT.
I'M TIRED
OF FOSTER HOMES.
DON'T GOT THE GRADES
OR MONEY,
JUST
THIS PHONY ADDRESS
THAT COULD BE
MY TICKET OUT.
I'M SORRY, ELVIS.
THERE IS MORE TO YOU
THAN YOU THINK.
HEY.
I'VE NEVER MET ANYONE
WHO BELIEVES IN THINGS
THE WAY YOU DO.
WHAT IS IT WITH YOU?
[LAUGHS]
I'M A CRUSADER.
Announcer: WE'RE ALMOST
THROUGH THE FIRST QUARTER,
AND SCHULER'S OFFENSE
CAN'T GET ANYTHING
GOING TONIGHT.
FORTUNATELY, SHERMAN NATERS
AND THE DEFENSE
ARE HOLDING THE PIRATES
SCORELESS AS WELL.
JACKSON.
YEAH, YOU.
LET'S GO.
YOU LIKE RUNNING
THROUGH FENCES, SON?
NOW'S YOUR CHANCE.
YOU RUN
THROUGH THE HOLE, BOY,
OR YOUR NEXT PRACTICE
IS GONNA BE
ON A BED OF NAILS.
RIGHT?
FORMATION:
LEFT-39, ON ONE.
Asst. Coach: COME ON, BOY.
LET'S GO, LET'S GO.
HEY.
GUESS WHAT.
PEOPLE HAVE
BEEN ASKING ME
HOW TO GET
MORE PAMPHLETS.
I THINK YOU
STRUCK A NERVE.
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
HEY, HEY.
LOOKEE THERE,
IT'S THE NEW KID.
ONE MORE TIME.
Announcer: CRUSADERS
WILL BE FORCED TO PUNT.
EVEN JACKSON CAN'T FIND
A HOLE WITH THAT BLOCKING.
STAY DOWN!
FOOTBALL'S
DOG-EAT-DOG,
AND YOU'RE
MY BABY'S MILKBONE.
Announcer: ATHENS' DEFENSE
CONTINUES TO BEND,
BUT NOT BREAK.
LED BY SHERMAN NATERS...
OW!
MY BABY!
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
[GROANS]
OHHH, HAAAA!
AAAH!
HOW MANY HAVE YOU GOT?
ALL RIGHT, GRAB A LIMB,
WE GOTTA POP THIS NUT OUT.
OOOHHHH!
UHH!
[COUGHS]
HOW MANY YOU GOT NOW?
ALL RIGHT.
LET'S PLAY SOME FOOTBALL.
OLD SHAZAM GOT HIT
THAT WAY ONCE.
OH, YES, I DID.
HHHUUUHH.
HUHHHHH.
IT WAS FROM
A WOMAN, THOUGH.
Announcer: SCORELESS TIE,
HIDIN' THE FACT
THAT ATHENS' DEFENSE
HAS GIVEN UP 204 YARDS.
HELLO, CRUSADERS?
ANYBODY AWAKE?
CAN ANYONE EXPLAIN TO ME
HOW THEY CAN
CUT THROUGH OUR DEFENSE
LIKE A HOT KNIFE
THROUGH BUTTER?
ABEL, I REQUIRE A REPLY.
COACH, YOU TOLD US
THAT IF--
IF, IF, IF...
IF MY MAMA
HAD A 3-PIECE SET,
SHE WOULD BE MY DADDY!
WHY DON'T YOU GO
AND START RUNNING. YOU RUN.
HERE, TAKE YASH WITH YOU.
BUT, COACH,
WE'RE IN A GAME.
GO!
YOU ARE.
WITHOUT A DOUBT.
BRIAN, WHAT KIND
OF SPORT IS FOOTBALL?
IT'S A CONTACT SPORT,
SIR.
CONTACT SPORT.
EVERYBODY AGREE WITH THAT?
LET ME HAVE A SHOW OF HANDS.
CONTACT SPORT?
THAT'S WRONG. THAT'S WRONG.
WRONG! WRONG!
FOOTBALL IS--GOD BLESS IT--
A COLLISION SPORT.
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO BE
A LEADER ON THIS TEAM, SON,
AND YOU ARE
RUNNING OUR OFFENSE
LIKE A FAT MAN
ON A FROZEN POND!
NOW UNTIL I SAY OTHERWISE,
EVERY PLAY IS GONNA BE
A HAND-OFF TO JACK OVER HERE.
BRING 'EM OUT, COACH.
LET THE BALL ROLL!
[TAUNTING]
Announcer: BEHIND THE FEARLESS
RUNNING OF ELVIS JACKSON,
THE CRUSADERS ARE 7 YARDS
FROM THEIR FIRST
"W" OF THE SEASON.
TIME-OUT IS CALLED.
YOU GOTTA ASSUME
THE BALL'S GOING TO JACKSON.
COACH, THEY'RE
WAITING FOR THAT.
GIVE ME A KEEPER.
I CAN DO IT.
ELVIS UP THE GUT.
LET'S GO.
[BLOWS WHISTLE]
[SHOUTING AND CHEERING]
Announcer: AND THE CRUSADERS
ARE ONE AND ONE,
THANKS TO BRIAN SCHULER'S
HEADS-UP PLAY
IN THE FINAL SECONDS.
[WHISTLE BLOWING]
ARRRRR!
COACH SAID
TO STAY HERE, MAN.
OHH.
CRAP!
LET'S GO.
YO. YO.
HEADS UP.
WHAT'S UP, COACH?
I DON'T KNOW.
YOU, LINE UP OVER THERE.
YOU. YOU. YOU.
YOU, LINE UP THERE.
YOU, LINE UP.
YOU GET OVER THERE.
YOU...AND YOU.
LINE UP, YOU.
I DO NOT BELIEVE THAT
FIGHTING MAKES YOU TOUGH...
BUT I KNOW--I KNOW
THAT STANDING ON
THE SIDELINES WATCHING...
MAKES YOU A COWARD.
NOW, THE REST OF Y'ALL
DON'T KNOW WHAT IT MEANS
TO BE A TEAM.
I DON'T WANT TO SEE YOU
ON MY FIELD AGAIN.
GO ON, GO HOME.
GO ON!
YOU'VE GOT
TO BE KIDDING.
YOU FUMBLE MY BALL
ONE MORE TIME,
AND I WILL NOT GIVE YOU
A SECOND CHANCE.
I WILL NOT MOVE YOU
TO DEFENSE.
SEE Y'ALL MONDAY.
UNBELIEVABLE.
LET'S GO.
[LOUDLY]
SURE IS A DAMN LUNATIC.
YOU DON'T PUNISH PLAYERS
FOR NOT FIGHTING.
ESPECIALLY
SENIOR SEASON
WHEN COLLEGE
IS ON THE LINE.
PASS THE SALT.
THAT ASSISTANT COACH
IS SOFTER
THAN A GEORGIA PEACH
WITH RAIN ROT.
NO WONDER
HIS OWN SON--
AIN'T IT FUNNY
HOW THE DUMBEST PEOPLE
ALWAYS HAVE
THE MOST TO SAY?
MAYBE YOU OUGHT
TO TEACH YOUR OWN DAUGHTER
TO KEEP HER MOUTH SHUT!
MAYBE YOU OUGHT
TO WATCH YOUR MOUTH.
[SIGHS]
SIT DOWN NOW, SAWYER,
THIS IS NOT
THE PLACE FOR THIS.
YOU KNOW,
IF YOUR BOY
HAD THE FIGHT THAT
YOU HAD 25 YEARS AGO,
HE WOULD STILL BE
ON MY TEAM.
MY SON BELONGS
ON THAT FOOTBALL TEAM.
YOU JUST COST HIM HIS ONLY
CHANCE AT A SCHOLARSHIP.
OHH, NOW...
THERE IT IS.
THE TROUBLE
WITH YOU PEOPLE
IS THAT YOU SEE ME,
YOU SEE THIS TEAM AS
A GATE TO GREENER PASTURES.
BUT UNTIL
YOU SUCCEED RIGHT HERE,
YOU DON'T DESERVE
GREENER PASTURES.
YOUR BOY AND I
HAVE A DIFFERENT
DEFINITION OF SUCCESS,
AND I SEE
WHERE HE GOT HIS.
THIS IS WHY
I HATE FOOTBALL.
BOYS...
GIDEON WENT TO WAR
AGAINST AN ARMY OF THOUSANDS
WITH ONLY 300 SOLDIERS...
BECAUSE THEY WERE
THE ONLY MEN WITH THE GUTS
TO FIGHT AND WIN.
I CAN GO TO WAR
WITH EVEN LESS
THAN WHAT'S RIGHT HERE
IN FRONT OF ME.
SO IF ANY OF YOU ARE
AFRAID OF GETTING HURT
OR LOSING...
YOU CAN LEAVE RIGHT NOW.
YOU KNOW...
YOU KNOW, THAT'S
JUST WHAT I THOUGHT.
THERE IS NOT ONE
QUITTER ON THIS TEAM.
NOW THE LAST MAN
OFF THIS BENCH
IS GONNA RUN LAPS.
[CHEERING AND SHOUTING]
OUTSIDE LINEBACKER.
SAFETY.
SNOOT, COME HERE, BOY.
GRAB YOUR HELMET, SON.
OUTSIDE LINEBACKER,
WIDE RECEIVER.
YOU'RE SAYING
I'M GONNA PLAY?
I MEAN, DURING
THE FIRST 3 DOWNS?
YEAH,
IT'S TIME TO RUN
WITH THE BIG DOGS, SON.
BUT, COACH, I'M A KICKER.
I JUST KICK.
YOU LINE UP
ON THE OUTSIDE.
WHEN SOMEONE THROWS
THE BALL, YOU CATCH IT.
NOW GO.
SCRIMMAGE.
7 OFFENSE,
8 DEFENSE.
GET A CALL IN.
Quarterback:
CRUSADERS ON 3. 1, 2, 3.
All: CRUSADERS!
Announcer: ENTERING INTO
THIS THIRD GAME OF THE YEAR,
ATHENS' SEASON HAS TAKEN
A TURN FOR THE BIZARRE.
COACH SCHULER HAS CUT
THE TEAM TO 15 PLAYERS.
AND, UH, LOOKS LIKE HE CUT
THE ATTENDANCE AS WELL.
I'VE SEEN MORE PEOPLE
IN SOLITARY CONFINEMENT.
MAYBE COACH
WILL SUIT UP.
OH, HEY.
THIS CAME
TO MY ATTENTION.
FROM THE LOOKS
OF ALL THOSE NAMES,
I'M NOT THE ONLY ONE.
[CHUCKLES]
COME ON, BABY,
MAKE ME PROUD!
SOMEBODY! SOMEBODY!
COVER 3. READY?
All: BREAK!
ABEL, MAN,
THAT'S MY POSITION.
REMEMBER,
IT'S NOT THE SIZE
OF THE DOG IN THE FIGHT,
IT'S THE SIZE OF
THE FIGHT IN THE DOG.
COME ON.
I'M GONNA RIP YOUR HEAD OFF
AND CRAP DOWN YOUR NECK.
SET.
HUT.
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
UHH.
COME BACK HERE. I AIN'T
DONE WITH YOU YET.
Announcer: THE CRUSADERS
ARE SIMPLY UNDERMANNED, FOLKS.
OUR BOYS
SEEM LOST OUT THERE.
AND WITH MANY OF THEM
PLAYING NEW POSITIONS,
THE WISHBONE LOOKS BROKEN.
LET'S HOPE SCHULER'S
GOT SOME MAGIC WORDS
FOR THE BOYS AT HALFTIME.
[HIDE AWAY PLAYING]
♪ I'VE BEEN TRYIN' ♪
♪ TO HIDE AWAY... ♪
WE AIN'T NEVER GONNA
SCORE AGAIN.
BALLBUSTER'S BUSTED.
Announcer:
DOLPHINS TAKE A KNEE,
AND THE CLOCK WILL RUN OUT
ON THE CRUSADERS.
IN A BLOWOUT,
ATHENS FALLS TO 1 AND 2.
COACH SCHULER'S
GONNA HAVE A TOUGH TIME
EXPLAINING HIMSELF,
ESPECIALLY IN THIS TOWN.
TRY TO HAVE
A GOOD NIGHT, FOLKS,
AND SO LONG
FROM ATHENS STADIUM.
HELLO. SIR, WOULD
YOU LIKE TO SIGN THIS?
WOULD YOU SIGN THIS,
PLEASE?
NO? THAT'S OK.
EXCUSE ME.
SIR, WOULD YOU--WOULD
YOU LIKE TO SIGN THIS?
IT'S A PETITION
FOR OUR SCHOOL.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
RIGHT THERE, PLEASE.
THAT'S GREAT.
THANK YOU.
COACH!
YOU CAN'T JUST
WALK OUT ON THESE BOYS.
THEY WON'T LISTEN.
SO YOU'RE DONE?
I GAVE IT A SHOT.
IT'S OVER.
YOU'RE A COWARD.
[LAUGHS]
WHEN PEOPLE DON'T
LISTEN TO YOU, YOU QUIT.
YOU DID IT 12 YEARS AGO,
AND YOU'RE DOING IT
RIGHT NOW.
NOW YOU WATCH IT
NOW, SAWYER--
NO.
WHAT ABOUT
NOT MOVING ON
UNTIL YOU SUCCEED
RIGHT HERE?
WHAT ABOUT "THE
SPIRIT OF DIVISION
IS OUR ENEMY"?
YOU SEE, I BELIEVE
THESE THINGS.
THAT'S WHY
I'M STILL HERE.
[LAUGHS] YOU SHOULD
HAVE LEFT YEARS AGO.
LOOK.
NO, I DON'T
WANT TO LOOK--
WOULD YOU LISTEN TO ME?
LISTEN TO ME.
[EXHALES]
ALL I KNOW IS
WHEN YOU LEFT,
THIS TOWN DIED.
AND THIS TOWN,
THIS TEAM...ELVIS...
THEY NEED YOU,
AND YOU NEED THEM.
WELL, THEY DON'T
GET THE WISHBONE.
THEN TEACH THEM
SOMETHING ELSE.
I DON'T KNOW
NOTHIN' ELSE.
[BOTH LAUGH]
COACH, THIS TEAM'S
LIKE YOUR MUSTANG.
THEY'RE FAST AND QUICK.
YOU CAN'T
KEEP DRIVING THEM
LIKE THEY'RE
A 2-TON TRUCK.
WOULD YOU
JUST SLEEP ON THAT?
PEOPLE SAY IT WAS
MY FAULT, DON'T THEY?
FOLKS SAY
A LOT OF THINGS.
THAT DON'T MAKE IT
THE TRUTH.
YOU READY?
I CAN'T TELL.
COACH, THE BEAR
HIMSELF SAID,
"FOOTBALL CHANGES...
AND SO DO PEOPLE."
HMM.
HOPE GOD STILL
LETS ME INTO HEAVEN.
GO ON,
PASS 'EM AROUND.
BOYS, THE KEY
TO OUR NEW OFFENSE
IS THE WAY
THE RECEIVERS SPREAD OUT.
THIS WILL GIVE US
MORE WAYS TO MOVE THE BALL,
AND IT'LL GIVE
BRIAN A CHANCE
TO THROW
TO THE WHOLE FIELD.
Brian: THROW.
THROW.
THROW!
AS IN PASS!
[LAUGHS]
ABOUT 35 TIMES A GAME.
NOT A LOT OF PLAYS
FOR HALFBACKS.
WHAT HAPPENED
TO LOST COMMANDMENT ONE?
I PLAY THE HAND
I'VE BEEN DEALT.
YOU BOYS HAVE
5 DAYS TO LEARN
AND EXECUTE
EVERY PLAY
IN THAT BOOK,
SO I SUGGEST
WE GET STARTED...
NOW.
Sawyer:
LET'S GET FIRED UP!
DOWN IN THE END ZONE.
ALL RIGHT, Y'ALL,
THIS IS A Z-IN.
A Z-IN.
YASH, YOU'RE THE Z.
ON ONE.
All: HEY!
DOWN.
1-18...1-18...
SET.
HUT.
YASH, YOU'RE THE Z.
[GOSPEL MUSIC PLAYS]
♪ WHATEVER IT TAKES ♪
♪ I KNOW I CAN
MAKE IT THROUGH ♪
♪ I'M GOIN' THROUGH ♪
♪ I'M GOIN' THROUGH... ♪
BLUE, 32, PITCH. HUT.
ELVIS, TO THE SIDE.
ELVIS TO THE SIDE.
HERE.
DON'T SHOW UP
UNTIL YOU KNOW THE PLAY.
♪ I KNOW I CAN
MAKE IT THROUGH ♪
♪ WHATEVER IT TAKES ♪
♪ I KNOW I CAN
MAKE IT THROUGH... ♪
YELLOW GOLD 62.
HUT.
♪ WHATEVER IT TAKES ♪
♪ I KNOW I CAN
MAKE IT THROUGH ♪
♪ GOIN' THROUGH ♪
♪ I'M GOIN' THROUGH ♪
♪ I'M GOIN' THROUGH... ♪
CONCENTRATE.
IT ALL COMES DOWN
TO THIS ONE PLAY.
[WHISPERING]
Rainbow-46, go.
RAINBOW-46 GO?
DO I GO LEFT
OR STRAIGHT?
LEFT.
LINE PULLS RIGHT.
RIGHT.
RIGHT?
COME ON, BOYS, THIS TEAM
NEEDS OUR SUPPORT.
COME ON, LET'S GO.
IGNORE THE COLD.
COME ON!
COME ON, BOYS!
WAIT, WAIT, I THOUGHT
YOU WENT STRAIGHT
AND ELVIS BREAKS LEFT.
ON ONE.
READY...
All: BREAK!
MAN, IT'S A BIT
COLD OUT HERE.
I BELIEVE IT IS.
MAN!
Announcer:
SCHULER TAKES THE SNAP
AND ROLLS OUT.
I BELIEVE HE'S GETTING
READY TO PASS.
YES, AND HE'S GOT
JACKSON OPEN AT THE 30.
BREAKS A TACKLE,
TURNS ON THE SPEED
UP THE SIDELINE.
HE'S AT THE 20,
15, 10, 5...
TOUCHDOWN, CRUSADERS!
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
All: RAINBOW SCORED
A TOUCHDOWN!
Announcer: ATHENS
TAKES THE LEAD, 6 TO 3.
DID WE JUST PASS?
Announcer: ATHENS
WILL WIN THEIR SECOND GAME,
AND LOOK OUT, ALABAMA!
WE GOT A NEW OFFENSE!
[GAME-END HORN BLOWS]
[BLUES-ROCK MUSIC PLAYING]
♪ COME ON, PEOPLE ♪
♪ I WANNA TELL Y'ALL
SOMETHING ABOUT MY LIFE ♪
♪ MY LIFE'S BEEN HARD ♪
♪ EVER SINCE I WAS BORN ♪
♪ YOU KNOW WHAT? ♪
♪ I'M GONNA GO
HEAVY WITH IT ♪
♪ I TELL YOU,
I'M GONNA GO HEAVY NOW ♪
♪ YOU KNOW ♪
♪ I'VE BEEN DOWN AND OUT ♪
♪ I'VE BEEN WALKIN'
FROM DOOR TO DOOR ♪
♪ BUT NOW, I DON'T
GOT NOWHERE TO GO ♪
Reporter:
DO NOT ADJUST YOUR TV.
THE HALF-STRENGTH,
HIGH-SCORING
ATHENS CRUSADERS
ARE DEFYING ALL ODDS
IN STRIKING DOWN
ONE GOLIATH AFTER ANOTHER.
2 MONTHS AGO, WE REPORTED
THAT AFTER 12 LOSING SEASONS
THE FOOTBALL WORLD HAD
PRETTY MUCH GIVEN UP ON ATHENS.
WELL, DON'T TELL
COACH BUSTER SCHULER
AND HIS MIRACLE SQUAD
OF 15 PLAYERS.
IN THEIR FINAL SEASON,
THE CRUSADERS
HAVE THEIR EYES SET
ON THE STATE CHAMPIONSHIP.
PEOPLE IN EVERY CORNER
OF ALABAMA
ARE ASKING ONE QUESTION:
CAN LIGHTNING
KEEP STRIKING AT THIS FIELD?
All: YEAH!
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
♪ I WISH YOU
OUT OF THE WOODS ♪
♪ AND INTO A PICTURE ♪
♪ WITH ME ♪
♪ I WISH YOU
OVER THE MOON ♪
♪ COME OUT
OF THE QUESTION ♪
♪ AND BE ♪
THIS IS WHAT
I WANTED YOU TO SEE.
♪ IF THIS IS GONNA
RUN ROUND IN MY HEAD... ♪
AFTER MY MOM DIED,
I USED TO COME HERE.
I'D SPEND HOURS.
WHO ARE THESE PEOPLE?
DO YOU KNOW ANY OF THEM?
ONLY A FEW.
[CHUCKLES]
I WOULD MAKE UP
THESE STORIES,
YOU KNOW, ABOUT
WHO THEY WERE
AND WHY
THEY CAME HERE.
THIS IS INCREDIBLE.
LOOK AT ALL
OF THESE NAMES.
YOU KNOW, THIS USED
TO BE THE HEART OF ATHENS.
A TRAIN WOULD
COME IN HERE EVERY DAY.
PEOPLE COMIN'...
AND PEOPLE GOIN'.
THEN ONE DAY
THE TRAIN STOPPED COMING,
AND THESE 3 CARS
NEVER LEFT.
NOW THE TRACKS
ARE ONLY A BLOCK LONG,
AND IT'S
JUST LIKE EVERYBODY
JUST KIND
OF FORGOT ABOUT IT.
NOT EVERYBODY.
I WONDER IF THESE PEOPLE
EVEN REMEMBER COMING HERE.
A LOT OF MEMORIES.
YOU KNOW...
A GENTLEMAN
WOULD WALK ME HOME.
LET ME KNOW
WHEN YOU FIND ONE.
[LAUGHS]
Announcer: DOWN BY ONE
ON THE 45-YARD LINE,
YOU GOTTA THINK BRIAN
SCHULER'S THROWING DEEP.
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU.
THIS IS YOUR WHOLE
SEASON ON THE LINE.
WE HAVE GOT TO THROW
THE FOOTBALL, OK?
THAT IS EXACTLY
WHAT THEY ARE
EXPECTING US TO DO.
LISTEN, YOU GET THE BALL,
YOU GET OUT OF BOUNDS.
Assistant: LET'S
GO GET 'EM NOW!
SON, THIS TEAM NEEDS YOU.
NOW YOU BE A BUICK.
Man: LET'S GO,
BOYS, COME ON!
WE GOTTA PUT
THIS ONE IN THE AIR.
LISTEN UP.
BLUE 32. BLUE 32.
YOUR BUTT'S
ON THE LINE.
JUST WHERE
I LIKE IT.
ON 2. READY?
All: BREAK!
[SCHOOL BAND PLAYING]
32! 32! HUT!
ELVIS!
GET OUT OF BOUNDS!
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
[CROWD MOANS]
NO, NO.
Announcer:
AND ATHENS IS FORCED
TO USE ITS FINAL TIME-OUT.
AND JACKSON
IS NOT GETTIN' UP.
HE'S HOLDIN' HIS RIGHT ARM.
UHH!
[GROANING]
TAKE IT EASY, SON.
OHH!
WHY DIDN'T YOU
LISTEN TO ME?
UHH! I'M SORRY.
GET HIM UP.
LET'S GO, A LITTLE HELP.
LET'S GO!
A LITTLE HELP HERE!
WATCH THE ARM.
COME ON.
WHAT IS
SNOOT'S BEST KICK?
HALF OF THIS.
HMM. SNOOT!
STRETCH YOUR HAMMY.
SNOOT.
BAIL ME OUT.
Announcer:
AND ATHENS' DREAMS
OF GETTING TO
THE STATE CHAMPIONSHIP
RESTS ON THE LEG
OF 5'4" SNOOT NINO
WHO'LL ATTEMPT A 45-YARDER,
HIS LONGEST EVER.
HERE'S THE SNAP, THE HOLD,
THE KICK IS UP.
IT'S GOOD! AND
WE'LL SEE YOU NEXT WEEK!
I ALWAYS THOUGHT
THE FIRST TIME
I'D BE HERE,
IT'D BE UNDER
DIFFERENT CIRCUMSTANCES.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOUR DAD TRUSTS ME HERE.
OH, HE DOESN'T.
HE TRUSTS ME.
OK, HALFTIME IS OVER.
BACK TO 1782.
YOU'RE NOT THINKING
OF PLAYING?
MY SCHOLARSHIP'S
WITHIN REACH.
YOU MEAN
CHAMPIONSHIP?
RIGHT.
NO WONDER YOU DIDN'T
GET OUT OF BOUNDS.
A CHAMPIONSHIP DOES NOT
GET ME TO THE NEXT LEVEL.
I CAN'T WIN.
LOSE THE SCHOLARSHIP,
YOU'RE GONE.
KEEP THE SCHOLARSHIP,
ELVIS, WHY SHOULD I
HAVE TO APOLOGIZE
FOR SOMETHING THAT PEOPLE
ARE STARTING TO BELIEVE IN?
PEOPLE WANNA BELIEVE
IN SOMETHING.
MAYBE EVEN YOU.
I LOVE A GOOD FIGHT.
ELVIS.
HAVE YOU EVER
DARED TO THINK
THERE MIGHT BE
SOMETHING BIGGER THAN YOU?
[CLEARS THROAT]
HALFTIME IS OVER.
BACK TO 1782.
LOOKS A LOT DIFFERENT
FROM UP HERE.
YOU TRYIN'
TO PLAY FRIDAY?
DO YOU KNOW WHAT HAPPENED
ON DECEMBER 12, 1965?
THE GALE SAYERS
GAME.
MY DAD WAS AT THAT GAME.
THINK OF IT.
HE WENT TO ONE PRO GAME
HIS ENTIRE LIFE,
HAPPENED TO BE THAT ONE.
ONE OF MY ONLY MEMORIES
OF MY DAD WAS...
LISTENING TO HIM
DESCRIBE THAT GAME.
AND HE ALWAYS SAID
I COULD PLAY
LIKE THAT SOMEDAY.
I GOT ONE MORE CHANCE
TO PLAY LIKE THAT.
YOU KNOW, JACKSON,
YOU AND I ARE
A LITTLE BIT ALIKE.
WHEN I WAS A KID,
MY MOM AND DADDY
HAD TO CONSTANTLY...
KEEP AN EYE ON ME.
ONE--ONE TIME
IN THE WINTER,
I RUN ACROSS THE ROAD
TO A NEIGHBOR'S FROZEN POND.
AND THE ICE
COULDN'T HAVE BEEN MORE
THAN A COUPLE
OF INCHES THICK,
SO MY DADDY
HAD TO STAND AT THE EDGE
AND PLEAD WITH ME
TO GET OFF.
BUT SEEMED LIKE
THE MORE HE PLEADED,
THE MORE I WANTED
TO STAY ON THE ICE.
WELL, HE WAS
JUST LOOKIN' OUT
FOR MY BEST INTERESTS.
I DIDN'T KNOW THAT
AT THE TIME.
IT'S A LESSON MY SON
NEVER LEARNED, EITHER.
NOW, SON, I DON'T KNOW
WHY YOU'RE HERE.
WE ALL PLAY ON THIS FIELD
FOR DIFFERENT REASONS,
BUT I'VE NEVER SEEN
ANYBODY DO WHAT YOU DO.
AND IF YOU CAN LEARN
WHAT MY SON NEVER LEARNED,
WELL, YOU WON'T NEED
HIS SCHOLARSHIP.
I DIDN'T GET IT,
DID I?
THERE'S NOT A DIME
IN MY BOY'S FUND.
THE TOWN IS BROKE.
I JUST FOUND OUT.
I'M SORRY.
Announcer:
WHEN THE STATE CHAMPIONSHIP
WAS SCHEDULED
AT ATHENS STADIUM,
NO ONE EXPECTED
THE CRUSADERS
TO BE PLAYIN' IN IT.
BUT IT'S A BITTERSWEET DAY
IN ATHENS WITH THE NEWS
THAT TONIGHT'S GAME
VERSUS ROCK HILL WILL INDEED
BE THE LAST GAME
IN OUR HISTORY.
THE COUNTY REPORTS
THAT THE MONEY
SIMPLY ISN'T THERE,
AND STARTING NEXT YEAR
ATHENS STUDENTS WILL BE
TRANSFERRED TO ROCK HILL.
TONIGHT, THE ROCK HILL
FOOTBALL JUGGERNAUT
IS EXPECTED TO TOY
WITH THE UNDERMANNED
CRUSADERS
WHO HAVEN'T BEEN
TO THIS GAME IN 12 YEARS
AND WILL PLAY
WITHOUT INJURED STAR
RUNNING BACK ELVIS JACKSON.
BUT FOR ATHENS, TONIGHT
IS NOT A TIME TO MOURN.
FANS ARE EXPECTED TO COME
FROM ALL OVER ALABAMA
TO CELEBRATE
THE GREAT HISTORY
OF OUR FOOTBALL PROGRAM.
WHAT ARE YOU DOIN'?
DIDN'T YOU HEAR?
WE BOTH LOST.
BUT I'M NOT
LEAVING TOWN.
I DON'T HAVE
WHAT YOU HAVE.
BUT YOU COULD.
YOU'RE HERE.
AND IT IS ALL RIGHT
HERE IN FRONT OF YOU,
AND YOU ARE PART OF IT
BECAUSE
YOU'VE CHANGED IT.
WELL, I'M GLAD
I GAVE YOU
AND YOUR SCHOOL
ONE LAST GO-AROUND,
BUT IN THE END
I GOT NOTHING BUT USED.
BECAUSE YOU DIDN'T
GET THE SCHOLARSHIP?
IS THAT ALL THERE IS?
GET OUT OF
YOUR FANTASY WORLD!
AFTER THE CRUSADERS
GET DESTROYED
ON THAT FIELD TONIGHT,
THIS TOWN
WILL DISAPPEAR.
AND GOD, SCHULER,
AND YOUR SILLY
LITTLE PAMPHLETS
AREN'T GONNA CHANGE THAT.
I TELL YOU WHAT.
SUPREME COURT OR NOT,
I'M PRAYING.
SO ANYONE WHO WANTS TO,
TAKE A KNEE.
Stadium crowd chanting:
CRUSADERS! CRUSADERS!
Announcer:
THE 2 TITANS OF ALABAMA
HIGH SCHOOL
FOOTBALL HISTORY:
THE ATHENS CRUSADERS
AND THE ROCK HILL RAIDERS,
ARE MOMENTS FROM KICK-OFF.
A PACKED ATHENS STADIUM
IS READY
FOR ONE OF THE MOST
ANTICIPATED
STATE CHAMPIONSHIP
GAMES EVER.
SNOOT NINO, WHOSE MIRACLE
45-YARD FIELD GOAL
GOT THE CRUSADERS
IN THIS GAME,
KICKS OFF FOR ATHENS.
[STADIUM CROWD CHEERING]
ALL RIGHT, GOD,
YOU GOT SOMETHING
TO SAY TO ME?
I DIDN'T THINK SO.
ALWAYS NICE
TO BE NEEDED.
HOW DID YOU KNOW
I WAS HERE?
I WAS TIPPED OFF
'BOUT THE TIME
THE THIRD PIE
SHOWED UP.
AND WHEN
THE MAYOR CAME,
I WENT LOOKING.
I DON'T KNOW
HOW THIS GOT HERE.
PEOPLE IN THIS TOWN
TAKE CARE OF THEIR OWN.
I TOOK A CUSTOMARY FEE
AS YOUR LANDLORD.
[CHUCKLES]
Announcer:
AS MOST EXPERTS PREDICTED,
THE CRUSADERS LOOK HOPELESS
AGAINST THE ROCK HILL
MACHINE.
8 YARDS FOR THE RAIDERS...
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
TOUCHDOWN, ROCK HILL...
ROCK HILL 37, ATHENS 3
AT HALFTIME.
YES.
GOOD JOB, SON,
THAT WAS A BEAUTIFUL CATCH.
GOOD JOB.
SHERMAN...
YOU HIT LIKE
A TON OF BRICKS.
THAT QUARTERBACK
GONNA BE SORE FOR A MONTH.
SNOOT, GREAT KICK,
GREAT KICK.
YOU SENT IT INTO ORBIT.
GOOD JOB.
LISTEN UP, BOYS.
WE GONNA LOSE.
MAKE NO MISTAKE,
IT'S GONNA BE
THE WORST ROUT
IN THE HISTORY
OF ALABAMA PLAYOFF FOOTBALL.
BUT IT WAS WORTH IT.
YOU ARE FINALLY ONE UNIT.
FINALLY ONE BODY.
YOU RESURRECTED SOMETHING
THAT WAS LOST.
Elvis:
ARE YOU ON EMPTY, COACH?
IS THAT ALL YOU GOT?
YOU ALL STARTED
WITHOUT ME.
COACH?
LOOK, I THINK WE ALL KNOW
WHY I CAME TO ATHENS.
IT WASN'T FOR THE SCHOOL
OR EVEN THIS TEAM.
AND I NEVER THOUGHT
15 PLAYERS
COULD GET THIS FAR.
AND WE GET HERE
ONLY TO FIND OUT
THAT NONE OF US IS
GETTING THE SCHOLARSHIP,
THE SCHOOL'S
STILL GONNA CLOSE DOWN,
AND WE'VE GOT--
I MEAN, WE'RE PLAYING
A TEAM WE CAN'T BEAT.
DOESN'T SEEM WORTH IT.
BUT FOR SOME REASON,
THOSE STANDS ARE PACKED.
THE FANS ARE
STILL CHEERING, AND--
AND I'VE GOT ENOUGH
GET-WELL PIES
TO LAST ME A YEAR.
THEY'RE HERE
BECAUSE THEY BELIEVE
IN ATHENS TRADITION
AGAIN.
AND WE HAD SOMETHING
TO DO WITH THAT.
THAT'S SOMETHING
I'VE NEVER HAD BEFORE.
SO LET'S GIVE THIS TOWN
ONE LAST GREAT HALF
OF ATHENS FOOTBALL.
IN THE FUTURE,
WHEN THEY THINK
ABOUT FOOTBALL
IN ATHENS, ALABAMA,
LET'S MAKE 'EM THINK
OF THE NEXT 24 MINUTES.
WE STILL GOT
SOMETHING LEFT HERE.
HEY, ROCK HILL
HASN'T BEEN OUTSCORED
FOR A HALF IN 3 YEARS.
WE WIN THIS HALF,
WE GOT OUR PRIDE!
Player: COME ON!
THIS GAME STARTS
OVER RIGHT NOW!
Player:
YEAH! COME ON!
HEADS UP!
ACT LIKE JACKIE!
LISTEN UP, DOGS!
Y'ALL WANT TO PUT
ONE MORE DOWN IN THE BOOK?
YOU GONNA DO IT RIGHT.
SHERMAN NATERS.
I KNOW YOU'LL KEEP
THE PRIDE OF THIS JERSEY
ALIVE FOR ME, SON.
YES, SIR.
JACKSON.
WELCOME.
HEY.
THINK
I GOT YOUR NUMBER.
TRADITION'S REAL IMPORTANT
ROUND THESE PARTS.
ELVIS.
THIS ONE'S SEEN
A BIT OF WEAR,
BUT I THINK IT WANTS
ONE MORE GAME.
I JUST CAN'T--
TURN IT DOWN
IS WHAT YOU CAN'T.
MY BOY IS WATCHING.
NOW YOU GIVE IT
ALL YOU GOT, ELVIS.
GONNA GET BLOOD ON IT.
WELL, THAT'S
WHY IT'S CRIMSON.
DON'T GET FANCY.
HIT 'EM!
LET'S SHOW 'EM
SOME BARNYARD FOOTBALL!
1, 2, 3...
Team: CRUSADERS!
CRUSADERS!
[CROWD CHEERS]
Crowd chanting:
CRUSADERS! CRUSADERS!
PRAY FOR ME.
WHY ARE YOU
DOIN' THIS?
I'M A CRUSADER.
Announcer: DURING
OUR COMMERCIAL BREAK,
THE CRUSADERS
BURST ON TO THE FIELD
IN THE CRIMSON JERSEYS
THAT WERE RETIRED
12 YEARS AGO.
AND IN AN ODD TWIST,
THEY SET UP A CHALK BOARD
AT THE END OF THE FIELD.
I'M NOT SURE
WHAT THAT'S ALL ABOUT.
YOU CAN'T
CHANGE UNIFORMS
IN THE MIDDLE
OF THE GAME.
WELL, ACTUALLY THOSE
WEREN'T OUR UNIFORMS.
THESE ARE--
THESE ARE OUR UNIFORMS.
COME ON, JOHN.
IT'S THE LAST GAME
FOR THESE BOYS.
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
HEY, THAT SUCKER'S
GOT MY JERSEY ON!
OH, LOOK AT THAT.
YOU CAN STILL SEE
THE BEER STAINS.
Announcer:
THAT'S ELVIS JACKSON
BACK TO RECEIVE THE KICKOFF.
APPARENTLY, HE IS
GONNA GIVE IT A GO
IN SPITE OF
A BADLY SPRAINED WRIST.
HE TAKES IT AT THE 5,
HESITATES
WAITING FOR A WEDGE.
UP TO THE 15,
HE FINDS A HOLE AT THE 20,
AND HE'S OFF TO THE RACES!
ONE MORE MAN TO BEAT!
HE'S GOT A BLOCKER,
AND HE'S GONE!
NOBODY'S GONNA CATCH HIM!
WEARING JACK SCHULER'S
NUMBER 7,
ELVIS JACKSON SCORES
THE FIRST TOUCHDOWN
OF THE SECOND HALF.
[CHEERING]
[REFEREE BLOWS WHISTLE]
THE TEAM'S BACK.
[SHOUTING AND CHEERING]
[WHISTLE BLOWING,
CHEERING]
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
WELCOME TO ATHENS,
BABY! YEAH!
WHOO!
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
NOW YOU CALL
A TIME-OUT?
WE'RE UP BY 20!
I AM NOT GONNA GIVE THEM
THE SATISFACTION!
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
[CROWD CHEERS]
Brian: SET! HUT!
HIKE!
HUT!
1, 2, HUT!
Brian: 10...HUT! HUT!
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
OH, COME ON!
WHAT ARE YOU, BLIND?!
OH, GIVE US
A BREAK!
Announcer:
BRIAN SCHULER IS DOWN
AFTER TAKING A VICIOUS HIT
FROM CHRIS NORMAN.
HE'S GOTTA BE EXHAUSTED.
HE'S TAKEN A BEATING
THE WHOLE GAME.
WHERE YOU FEEL IT?
EVERYWHERE.
HELP ME UP.
NO, NO, NO, NO.
YOU PLAYED A GOOD GAME.
I'M PROUD OF YOU, BRIAN.
YASH, YOU SWITCH
TO QUARTERBACK.
COACH...
YOU'RE NOT TAKIN' ME
OUT OF MY LAST GAME.
I CAN'T THROW, BUT...
WE CAN RUN.
WHAT'S LOST COMMANDMENT
NUMBER ONE?
LET THE BONE ROLL.
LET THE BONE ROLL!
All: YEAH! COME ON!
Announcer: WITH THE CLOCK
WINDING DOWN,
ATHENS RETURNS
TO THE WISHBONE OFFENSE.
PERHAPS COACH SCHULER WANTS
TO GIVE THE CRUSADER FAITHFULS
ONE LAST LOOK AT IT.
THAT'S THE WAY
THE BONE ROLLS!
WE WILL NOT
LOSE THIS HALF
TO A TEAM
OF 15 PLAYERS!
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
Announcer:
AND ATHENS CALLS TIME-OUT
WITH THE BALL
ON THE 30-YARD LINE.
THEY HAVE TIME
FOR ONE LAST PLAY.
ALL RIGHT, GENTLEMEN,
LET'S GET IT GOIN'.
YOU READY TO WEAR
SUPERMAN'S CAPE?
[LAUGHS]
ON ONE.
READY...
All: BREAK!
[CHEERING]
WE'RE GONNA SEND YOU
HOME TO MAMA, BOY.
[ROARS]
[CHEERING]
DON'T YOU GUYS GET IT?
YOU LOST.
[LAUGHS] YEAH.
Announcer: ROCK HILL
HAS DEFEATED THE CRUSADERS
62-32,
BUT NO ONE IN ATHENS
CARES ABOUT THAT RIGHT NOW.
AND, IF YOU DON'T MIND,
THIS BROADCASTER'S
GONNA SHUT UP AND APPLAUD.
[CHANTING]
CRUSADERS! CRUSADERS!
GOTTA BE THE FIRST TIME
THE LOSING TEAM'S
TORN DOWN THE GOALPOST.
[LAUGHING THROUGH TEARS]
YOU BETCHA.
COME ON, WHAT ARE
WE WAITIN' FOR, TEE?
LET'S GO
GET A RIP ON 'EM!
GREAT JOB, BRIAN.
THANKS, COACH.
WELL...
WELL,
IT'S ABOUT TIME.
[LAUGHS]
I'M GLAD
YOU CAME BACK.
KEEP THAT JERSEY,
SON.
YOU WERE BORN
TO WEAR THAT.
ELVIS JACKSON?
I'M SO PROUD
OF YOU. [LAUGHS]
Rachel: GOD...
I KNOW MIRACLES
HAPPEN EVERY DAY.
JUST SOMETIMES
IN DIFFERENT WAYS
THAN WE ASKED.
WE DIDN'T SAVE OUR SCHOOL,
BUT YOU BROUGHT
TRADITION AND PRIDE
BACK TO ATHENS.
SO, THANKS FOR SHOWIN' UP
AND SHOWIN' OFF
IN ATHENS, ALABAMA.
AND WHEN THEY TALK ABOUT
THE CRUSADERS' LAST HALF,
COACH SCHULER'S
FINAL STAND,
THE SPEED AND HEART
OF ELVIS JACKSON,
LET 'EM REMEMBER...
YOU ARE, WITHOUT A DOUBT.
CAPTIONING MADE POSSIBLE BY
WARNER BROS.
CAPTIONED BY THE NATIONAL
CAPTIONING INSTITUTE
--www.ncicap.org--
♪ I WILL RISE ♪
♪ AND I WILL STAND ♪
♪ I'M GETTIN' OFF MY KNEES
AND MY HANDS ♪
♪ AND I WILL WALK ♪
♪ AS YOU LEAD ♪
♪ LOOK BEYOND
WHAT I CAN SEE ♪
♪ AND I WILL SPEAK ♪
♪ FROM MY HEART ♪
♪ NOT LET PRIDE TEAR
TRUTH APART ♪
♪ I WON'T FEAR ♪
♪ ANOTHER MAN ♪
♪ 'CAUSE HE IS DUST
JUST LIKE I AM ♪
♪ 'CAUSE IN THIS JOURNEY
WHEN THE NIGHT IS DONE ♪
♪ OH, I WILL SET MY FACE
TOWARDS THE SUN ♪
♪ I WILL NOT
LOOK BACK, NO ♪
♪ NO, I WILL NOT
LOOK BACK ♪
[NEW SONG BEGINS]
♪ KISS ME IN THE MORNIN' ♪
♪ WAKE ME WITH A SONG ♪
♪ DRESS ME IN YOUR AUTUMN ♪
♪ KEEP HOLDIN' ON ♪
♪ GENTLE WHISPER ♪
♪ IT SHAKES ME
FROM A DREAM ♪
♪ IT AIN'T LIKE
WHAT IT SEEMS ♪
♪ WHEN YOU'RE MILES AWAY ♪
♪ SINGIN' ♪
♪ OOH, OOH, OOH-OOH ♪
♪ HARMONY ♪
♪ OOH, RUNNIN'
THROUGH MY SOUL ♪
♪ OOH, OOH, OOH-OOH ♪
♪ HARMONY ♪
♪ OOH, RUNNIN'
THROUGH MY SOUL ♪
♪ IF I WERE TO TELL YOU ♪
♪ A TALE
OF NO TOMORROW... ♪