Give me the phone.
No!
No, no!
[Screams]
[Girl screams]
Man on phone: Have you had
a chance
to look over the spreadsheets?
Steven:
Yeah.
Those numbers look good.
Man on phone:
What about your flight?
Yeah, I'm on the 10:15
flight tomorrow morning.
You have me through the weekend?
Man on phone: Yeah.
Yeah.
Man on phone: Be ready.
Okay.
Man on phone:
It's gonna be a long one.
Hi.
Lookin' strong, kiddo.
Feeling strong, daddy-o.
It just stiffens up
on me sometimes.
Man on phone: Hey, be sure
to send over your report.
Steven yes, sir.
Jenny: Hey.
Hey.
Leg hurt?
Not as much as losing
my scholarship.
Are you rushing it?
Mom, I've been
babying it all summer.
If I'm gonna get
my scholarship back,
I have to start training again.
(Squealing) My baby's going
off to college. (Laughs)
Please don't gush.
Ah! Give me a hug.
Don't.
Come on!
I'm an empty nester now.
Gimme a break.
I love you.
Love you.
Let me help you pack.
Okay. I need it.
This is really beautiful, mom.
All my favorites.
We thought you'd enjoy
one last home cooked meal
before dorm food.
Absolutely.
To our brave
and beautiful Jen Jen.
We love you so much.
Scholarship or not.
You'll never disappoint us.
Now don't party too much and
flunk all your classes.
Um... like I flunked
stand-up comedy?
Kristen: What's wrong?
No, it's just
I'm nervous about the move.
30 miles.
You'll be home to do
your laundry on the weekends.
It's not the distance.
It's not even that it's my first
time being away from home.
It's dorms. Roommates.
What if I don't like them?
What if they don't like me?
I lived in the dorms in college.
I met your dad in the dorms.
Made friends.
Like Linda. It'll be great.
You'll see.
Here. Lemme get that.
Thank you.
Anything else?
No. That's it.
Oh! I'm gonna cry.
Please don't.
I'm gonna tell a joke.
Oh! Please don't.
Have fun.
You too.
Love ya, kiddo.
I love you.
Good luck.
- Bye.
- Have fun.
Let's go.
♪
So exciting!
Gosh, it's so big.
I'm gonna get lost.
You won't get lost.
We don't get a lot of new
students
after winter break,
but we're glad to have
some new faces.
This is our dining hall.
You'll spend a lot of time here.
(Kristen chuckles)
If you're used to
a high school cafeteria,
you'll recognize the abundance
of
starches and carbohydrates.
But don't worry,
every 5000 calorie meal
is topped off at the
all-you-can-eat
snack bar,
which I invite you
to partake of now.
Alright.
Did they have this
when you lived in the dorms?
Oh, yeah.
I gained the freshman fifteen.
Ice cream here,
and my campus job
is at the smoothie shop.
Forget it.
You'll be training again.
You'll need
all these scrumptious calories.
So, the tour guide.
Articulate with a hint
of sarcasm? Hmm?
Mom, don't "hmm" me
over every guy we see.
Okay, not every guy,
but what about that one?
Stop.
He's cute.
Okay, you're embarrassing me.
[Elevator rings]
Anyone for floor 11?
I'm also on 12.
Oh, penthouse.
(Chuckles) I'm the floor RA.
"Resident assistant."
The school feels
more comfortable
trusting the welfare
of irresponsible freshman
to equally
irresponsible grad students.
Just kidding. Sort of.
This is the bathroom.
What? You've never seen
a co-ed bathroom before?
No.
Everyone's a jokester.
Let's see where you are.
1227?
What?
Um... uh, nothing.
It's right down here.
That was weird, right?
Like my room leads
into a Stephen King novel?
No. No, no, no.
It was weird.
Uh, here it is. 1227.
Let me know
if you need anything.
[Knock on door]
Hello. 1227, a little bit
o' heaven. I'm Beth.
Come in.
Jenny.
Jenny Willis. And my mom.
Hi. I'm Kristen.
And that's sour Sarah.
Ignore her,
and she'll do the same.
She'll even ignore you
if you don't.
But don't worry,
I'm friendly enough
for the both of us.
That's your bed.
And your desk.
Not claustrophobic, are you?
Uh, not yet.
Right? The double rooms
are even smaller.
The triples are a trade off.
We get a little
extra floor space,
even though the bunk doesn't
take up that much more room.
Beth.
What? She's gonna
sleep in that bed
whether you like it or not.
What's wrong with her?
Sorry about her.
She warms up
once you get to know her.
Oh, wait... No.
She doesn't.
What made her so upset?
She was really fond
of our last roommate, Elaine.
But there'll be time
for all that later.
We have you now!
Where's all your stuff?
It's in the car.
- Let's go get it.
- Okay.
Okay, when you're done, let's
meet in the cafeteria.
Yeah, I usually just skip
this whole section
and go straight to the veggies.
Only thing worse
than the freshman fifteen
is the sophomore sixty.
Sixty?
Girls come in here
wanting to be models
and by Christmas
they're made out of Clay.
What's up, toppers?
Toppers?
Top floor.
Meet Jenny.
My new lower.
Hi.
You got Elaine's bed?
Everyone, stop.
You didn't tell her?
You have to tell her?
What? Tell me what?
Lot of returning students
had a party last week.
Last rager before classes start.
And Elaine
well, everyone was having fun,
but it was loud.
So, she went to the roof
to get some air and she...
She what?
She fell.
She fell?
She died.
Your last roommate
fell off the roof
and died at the party
last weekend?
And I'm sleeping in her bed?
[Cell phone rings]
Hey.
Steven: Hi.
Kristen (on phone) I love that
you're working so hard
to keep Jenny
in private school.
How's it going?
It's still going.
How's it going with you?
Horrible. I left her at 1:00,
and she still hasn't called.
Steven:
It's only 5:00.
Uh, yeah, I know,
but it feels like a lifetime.
Why don't you call her?
No.
I know you,
you're gonna worry
about her until you call her.
I don't want to bug her.
You're not gonna be able
to fall asleep
until you call her. Just call
her.
Alright, well, I gotta
get back in this meeting.
I love you. Okay? Bye.
If you believe she fell.
Michelle.
I'm just saying.
Elaine bombed last year.
Her grades went from like
A’s to C’s and D’s,
and there's a rumor going around
that she didn't
fall from the balcony.
She jumped.
She jumped?
Enough, Michelle.
[Cell phone rings]
Honey, what's wrong?
The girl who was in my bed
last semester died.
That girl died?
Are you kidding?
I know. It's so horrible.
I'm coming to get you
right now, okay?
No, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no.
You can't live in the dorms.
You can't.
You can commute.
An hour each way?
Yes, you can!
I know. But I can't just
run away on my first day.
Besides, I have to be on the
track in the afternoon.
I'm coming to get you.
Okay? A girl died.
Mom, it's okay.
I'm okay.
I'll call you later.
No, Jen Jen.
You have to come home.
Jenny:
You won't understand, mom.
Jenny?
Sorry. I-I didn't mean to...
Jenny: No!
I-I don't know why I'm so upset.
I mean, you guys
are the ones that knew her.
Because you have to sleep
in her bed.
Hey, babe.
Stop, Dane.
Dane! Seriously,
leave me alone.
That is not what you
were saying all last year.
That's right, last year.
So, by now you should accept
that it's never
going to happen again.
Never say never.
Hey!
I want my dorm room key.
Are you okay?
Should we call security?
Don't bother.
I'm sure it was Dane.
Dane? Whoever it was,
I got him really good
on the shoulder.
I gave him a key
back when we were dating,
and he never gave it back.
Said he'd keep it
for when I "came around."
I just never thought
he'd use it.
Probably trying to
steal my panties!
Take off your shirt!
I knew you'd come around
eventually.
Oh, god!
What is going on?
Someone broke into our room.
I cut his shoulder.
And you think that I’m...
Give me my key.
I was just hoping that we
would be able to...
Leave me alone.
I didn't go into your room.
I wouldn't do that.
You're both all right?
Anything uh, missing or stolen?
Only our sense
of safety and security.
You're doing
a bang-up job, "R.A."
First Elaine, now this.
I-I'm... I'm sorry.
I'll put in a req
to have the key re-lock...
The, uh, the lock re-keyed.
How long does that take?
(Sighs) A couple of days.
(Scoffs) We'll sleep
real soundly until then.
Kinda hard on him.
He's lucky
I didn't sting him harder.
Beth, the guy... The guy in here,
I mean, he was... He was looking
for something.
You know, I'm still not
convinced
it wasn't Dane.
He's got a whole...
No. He wasn't just
looking for panties, Beth.
I mean, he... He was really
looking for something.
Do you think
that it could have been
about Elaine?
Elaine?
I don't know.
Does she have any stuff
still here?
Her parents took it all.
It's just weird, you know?
A week ago, she dies
and now someone breaks in?
Maybe...
Maybe she didn't jump or fall.
Maybe she was murdered.
No. The police were here.
They questioned everyone.
There was twenty people
in the hall,
and no one saw anyone.
But you said it was a party.
I mean, no one was probably
paying attention?
Did anyone not like her?
Was there a guy that she dumped?
Everyone liked Elaine.
And I never even saw her date.
She wasn't killed, Jenny.
I mean, the police
said I it was an accident.
She fell.
And time to walk on eggshells.
I'm gonna take a shower.
Thanks for shopping at blush.
Thank you.
Have a nice day, ladies.
Died?
A student died?
Yeah.
And Jen is sleeping in her bed?
Can I make her move home?
Oh, I want her to move home.
At 18?
How's that gonna work?
I don't know.
And how does someone spend
two decades of their life
trying to keep their kid safe,
only to have them move away
and not be able
to protect them anymore?
I have two under ten,
and I cannot wait
until they're both
out of the house
and have to
keep themselves alive.
Oh, no, you say that now,
and then they're gone,
and all you can think about
is how you've totally
lost your purpose.
♪
Jenny.
Worst first night
in the dorms ever, huh?
Coulda been worse.
You could've been stuck in
a double only with Sarah.
Come on.
When the going gets tough,
the tough go shopping!
My treat.
[Elevator rings]
Do you like it?
I wouldn't be caught dead
in that outfit,
but I admire your fire.
I bet you're the first
to raise your hand
for every question, aren't you?
Jenny: Can we slow down?
Oh, my campus job.
Really?
Yeah.
Mangoberry is the best.
Come on. First one's on me.
Okay. Ow!
What's wrong?
Sorry, uh, hit a rock
on the road of life.
Okay. I'm good.
My leg is acting up today.
Coach Simmons: Not bad.
Coach Simmons.
You set a pace for about
a 17, 18 second 100 meter.
Great. That would've
gotten me
sixth place at the church
picnic.
Even a church picnicker
couldn't hit 18 seconds
with a torn acl.
I'm sorry
about the scholarship, Jenny.
It wasn't my call.
It's okay.
Gotta give the money
to someone who can run.
So, I'm gonna run, coach.
I'm gonna run my way
back into my scholarship.
When'd you get up,
two hours ago?
I didn't know
the first day of classes
was such a special occasion.
Every day is.
I feel my best
when I look my best.
Her grades were way
down last year.
College isn't for everyone.
How are you gonna
walk in those all day?
Beautifully.
Professor: I'll do it.
Honestly, Kyle, if your
assistance
is going to create
more hindrance than help,
I will find myself
another T.A.
Yes... sir.
Good morning.
Good morning!
This is American history 101.
If this is not the class
you're supposed to be in,
too bad you're stuck here
until I'm done in 50 minutes.
Where does
American history begin?
N...
This is a lecture, young lady.
Not a town hall.
The questions are rhetorical.
Kyle! Hey.
Jenny.
Yeah, I saw you in there.
You got a nip from old
Harrington.
Guess I asked for it though.
You didn't.
Ah, others are worse.
If you just let him
listen to himself talk,
you'll be all right.
How are you
after the other night?
Okay, I guess.
Sorry Beth was so hard on you.
She was just scared.
Hey, it's my job
to keep all the students
on my floor safe.
And I failed.
Twice now.
I asked for a rush
on that new lock.
Thanks.
[Thud]
You all jumped
when I came into the room?
Why?
Come on. This was in
your pre-term reading.
A loud noise startles you.
Is the reaction physiological
or psychological?
It's both.
Our brains instinctively
interpret loud noises
as potentially dangerous.
Then signal our bodies
to prepare for the threat.
By jumping out of your skin?
[Laughter]
Don't laugh. She's right.
Brain and body together
determine how we interpret and
react to our environment.
We want to examine
which is responsible for what?
What is instinct, as miss?
Willis. Jenny Willis. Jennifer.
Yeah. Jenny.
That's a lotta names.
As miss Willis has noted.
And what is a learned,
emotional response?
I am Dr. Davrow.
Welcome to my class.
Dr. Davrow: Thank you,
everyone.
We'll see you tomorrow.
Dr. Davrow (cont.) Miss Willis?
May I have a word?
Miss Willis?
Freshman? Very bold.
Most students would rather stick
their arm in a lion's cage
than in the air
on the first day of class.
I-I don't mind standing out.
University is more competitive
than high school.
Even the bold
have to up their game
if they want to stand out.
I look forward
to seeing your paper.
[Heavy bass music plays]
Hey.
Okay, that's enough.
Headphones off!
Look, I'm not gonna sleep four
feet
from you for the next semester
and never have you say hello.
Hello.
You don't even know me.
You have no reason
not to like me.
Well, stealing my book
and my phone
seem like pretty good reasons.
I didn't...
Okay, fine. Here.
I don't dislike you.
I dislike Beth.
Why? Beth's nice.
Beth is as fake as twenty
dollar Prada.
She wakes up every morning,
and she hides behind
those dresses
because she's too afraid
to succeed in this world
as what she really is.
I'm sorry for ignoring you.
Whatever, but I'm not going
to fake nice just because.
So I have to choose
between you two?
No, Jenny. I chose.
Kyle? What happened?
Uh... professor Harrington.
He, uh... Heart attack.
Thank you very much.
Everything okay, miss Willis?
Let's take a look at your paper.
My paper?
Yes. The assignment.
You completed it, right?
Yeah. Yeah, I did.
Here.
You're gonna have to work harder
than that to stand out.
Okay. Diagnostic and statistical
manual of mental disorders.
What was that?
Dr. Davrow.
Excuse me?
My students address me
as "Dr. Davrow."
Or "professor." It's an
honorific
that shows respect.
Well, you get respect
by showing it to others.
Hmm? Where'd you learn that?
Some book about the great
lessons
of kindergarten?
University is harder, Jenny.
Consider it a lesson.
In what, humiliation?
In rising to the challenge.
And you start by
putting yourself together.
This outfit, I don't know
what you call it.
Frumpy tracksuit?
You can do better.
How dare you!
I dare because I care.
You see, I can quote
pithy aphorisms, too.
So you're saying
you graded me down
because of my clothes?
No, I graded you down because
your paper was rushed,
ill-conceived and
subpar for my class.
And I'm pointing out to you
that going through life
looking like you slept
in an alleyway,
you'll find, repels rather than
attracts people
who might be in a position
to help you.
Which I could, if you show me
you're worthy.
He did it in front of everyone.
It was horrifying.
What, the paper or him
telling you to dress nicer?
Both!
Totally inappropriate!
What?
I don't know about the paper,
but as for the clothes,
I told you
I wouldn't be caught dead in...
Okay, "looking your best
to feel your best"
is different than dressing up
to get grades you should be
getting based on your work.
And if your work
can only get you so far?
I don't claim to be
a unicorn, Jenny.
I know my merits.
(Scoffs) Are you saying
that... To get grades?
Beth, why, why would you...
What? You've never
batted your lashes
at a traffic cop to get out
of a speeding ticket?
Jenny no!
Flirted with the bouncer to
get past the line at a club?
Whatever. It's not like
I was failing.
I wore a nice dress and heels
to Davrow's class
and got an "a"
where I might have gotten a
"B."
What about the girls
who don't have a nice dress,
or don't look
as good as you in one?
Should they suffer because they
won't
flirt with the professor?
Just because he marks me up
for playing along
doesn't mean he marks anyone
else down who doesn't.
He did it to me!
If he had given you an "a"
in front of everyone,
would you be complaining?
It's like my chemistry teacher
once said,
"if you've got it, flaunt it."
And somewhere
underneath that uh...
What'd you say he called it?
Frumpy tracksuit?
You've got it.
I don't want to get it
like that.
Oh, look. Kyle finally
made himself useful.
I cannot believe
neither one of you
told me someone tried to
break into our room.
You're not exactly
chatty with us.
Uh... Sarah?
Maintenance man new keys.
Thank you.
Now that we can sleep soundly.
All we have to do is find a guy
trolling the halls with a gouge
you put in his shoulder.
15.75 seconds.
Jenny: That's okay.
Jenny (cont.)
I'm gonna go home
this weekend.
You here for dinner tonight?
You're working overtime
for me, aren't you?
What?
You never
used to work this much.
Or go out of town
on the weekends.
No, kiddo. It's just this deal.
It's dragging me by the tail.
Worth every second though
to see you at Oldbridge.
You sure you don't want me
to transfer to state?
I'd rather have a hundred jobs
drag me around first. Okay?
Am I cooking,
or bringing something home?
Home cooked, please!
And no starches.
Well, I gotta go.
Love you, kiddo. Love you.
Love you, too.
Jenny: Love you, daddy-o.
And thanks.
You know...
I'm sorry about...
Ah...
Me too. I wish
I could... Meddle forever.
But, you're an adult now...
And you can make
your own decisions.
But not for being worried.
I will always be your mother,
whether you let me
meddle or not.
And a student dying at a
party...
I just can't turn it off.
Kristen: Linda wants
to do a makeover for you.
How beautiful is she?
Stop.
You're gonna have to
bat the boys away.
Or I could just go plain
and not have to worry about
them bothering me at all.
Oh...
Jen Jen,
having boy troubles already?
She's in college, Kris,
they're not boys anymore,
they're men.
All right,
are you having men problems?
No, I'm not.
How about the cute jock?
He's a jerk.
Oh, do tell.
Is he coming on too strong
or is he holding back too much?
I've only ever found
one or the other,
casual or confident.
Never one who's mastered
"casually
confident." (Laughs)
There's no one, okay?
No one I'm dating. No one
I'm interested in.
Jenny, I... I'm sorry I didn't...
Lin, it's not you.
Hi. Welcome to blush.
Welcome.
I'm sorry.
You know, we just got these in.
Too casual? Too confident?
You're the perfect blend
of both, you know.
What's going on?
Promise not to judge me?
I'll hold it in.
And I'm not moving home.
There's a rumor on campus
that some of the professors
will give a girl better grades
if she dresses up for class.
And how much truth
is there to this rumor?
Please don't make
a big deal out of it.
Jenny, it is a big deal.
If it's true,
you should report him.
Well, no one
actually told me to dress up.
Then what exactly
have they told you?!
Nothing.
I knew this was going to happen.
You've been stuffing down
your feelings
about that girl dying.
Mom, it's...
It's not just that.
What?
Jenny, what?
Mom! Mom!!
Get in the car.
I'm not moving home!
You are!
Mother!
Daughter!
Someone broke into your room,
and you've been
hiding it from me.
Lying to me about it!
I didn't lie about anything!
Sin of omission. Get in the car.
No!
Others are telling girls
to dress up for grades.
And a professor died!
He had a heart attack.
Get in the car!
I'm going back to school.
You're not.
You said yourself
I can make my own decisions.
Good ones!
Jennifer! Jennifer!!
Jenny:
Thanks, Beth, for picking me up
Jenny (cont.)
And showing me around town.
Hey, do you see this?
Someone was trying
to get back in.
Should we call security?
It's after midnight.
They won't get here til morning.
Maybe it was Sarah
trying to get in.
Lost her new key?
Well, I'm starving.
I'm gonna downstairs
and eat a snack.
Do you want to come with me?
I'm really tired.
Good night.
[Rattling]
[Noise]
[Jenny gasps]
Kyle, what the heck?!
I'm sorry I didn't mean...
I just saw you
and thought I’d...
Scare me half to death?
[Both laughing]
Um, I-I recommend
the protein bars.
Okay.
[Inaudible]
Thanks, Kyle.
I'm Ms. Kingsley, your new
American history teacher.
I can't even believe...
This is ridiculous.
Beth: Oh, come on.
A bunch of rich parents
just bribed their kids into
college.
You don't think any of them
wouldn't have jumped at the
chance
to just get them a new wardrobe?
Do you even hear yourself?
I mean, do you have any
self-respect at all?
Yes, enough to shower
and put on nice clothes
every day.
Where's your self respect,
Sarah?
In here, Beth!
In my heart,
where I protect it
with everything I've got
from disgusting,
degrading sell-outs like you!
Said you wanted to choose?
Choose.
If I don't keep my grades up,
I can't get my scholarship back.
She... seriously...
Don't.
What?
Don't make her wrong.
She's not wrong.
We are.
Oh, this is so exciting!
[Squeals]
Look at you!
Wow!
Excuse me.
Good morning, miss Willis.
Good morning, Dr. Davrow.
Okay, now you're just
kissing up.
Wouldn't think of it.
Let's talk about
psychopathology.
For those who can never
know what it's like
to be inside the mind
of a psychopath.
Where do we draw the line
between abnormality
and abnormally genius?
Beth:
Can I have a salad please?
Thank you.
I don't have to dress
for dinner, do I?
Don't act like I’m
twisting your arm.
Not you. Dr. Davrow.
Back up from "C’s".
Wonder what I have to do
to get the grade
I actually deserve in his class?
Stop wearing anything at all?
[Cell phone rings]
Everything all right?
I don't know.
I'm trying to let her
solve her own problems
but it isn't easy.
You can't hold her hand
all through college.
She's a smart kid, Kris.
You know, her way
may not be the same as yours,
but she'll find it.
I know.
Can I steer her
from behind a little bit?
Jenny:
I don't know if this
was a good idea.
Beth: It's gonna be awesome.
Beth: (Cont.)
It's totally legit.
Beth: (Cont.) Lots of
faculty,
male and female students, too.
Beth: (Cont.) They talk
about internships,
jobs after graduation,
Beth: (Cont.)
Make connections for you.
I can't believe the girl
who is fighting
with everything she has to get
her track scholarship back
is getting crushed so easily by
putting on a dress and heels.
Okay, fine. Let's go.
(Inaudible background chatter
and music)
I told you it was great.
Oh, good evening, ladies.
You both look radiant.
Beth...
The lady in the gold
sequin dress
is the fashion editor
for haute couture.
And Jenny...
The gentleman in the gray suit
books athletic endorsements
for running shoes.
Track, right?
Are you interested
in endorsements?
Uh, yeah.
Great.
Let me know
if I can make an introduction
for either one of you.
I'd offer you a drink,
but state law, university rules
and societal mores prevent it.
But do help yourselves
to some hors d'oeuvres
and mingle.
Okay, it's great.
Thank you.
Quite the soiree, isn't it?
Eric told me that he was
particularly interested
in having you here.
Eric?
Dr. Davrow.
He says that you have
great potential
as a psychologist.
Oh, I'm not actually sure
I want to go into psychology.
History, maybe?
Whatever field you choose,
be proud of yourself, Jenny.
The world needs
all of its young women
to grow up proud.
Will you excuse me?
I'll see you Monday morning,
8 A.M. the war of 1812.
Jackson and Lafayette
take on New Orleans.
Thrilling.
You got gray suit's card?
Is your face coming
to a cereal box near me?
Okay, first I have to
get back on the track team.
Before that, I have to
pee. Bathroom?
Upstairs. Oh, and don't miss
the study on the left.
The artwork is unbelievable.
Okay. Come with me.
Yeah. Sure.
Dr. Davrow:
Beth.
Oh, you'll be okay.
Dr. Davrow:
Someone I want you to meet.
Impressive collection, isn't it?
Yeah, um, whose is it?
I mean, whose,
whose house are we in?
Mine.
Oh. This is a really nice house.
Thank you.
Inspired by my travels. Italy.
Thailand. Borneo. Estonia.
Beautiful city of Tallinn.
All the buildings
are painted in pastels.
I didn't realize
teaching at public universities
was so lucrative.
They don't pay for the teaching.
They pay for the name.
I spent several years
building that, as well.
'66 chateau neuf de pape?
What happened to state law
and social mores?
I don't see either in here.
Cheers.
You don't like me, do you?
I... uh...
Why do you say that?
A man doesn't have to
travel the world
to discern when a
woman doesn't like him.
It shows in your eyes
every day in class.
It's because I suggested
you dress up.
And you think
I'm basing your grades off it.
You know, decades ago,
in the 60's,
it would be unheard of for
a woman to show up to class
in sweat pants
and a torn tee-shirt.
So should I get a pink
angora sweater
and a circle skirt
with a poodle on it?
You joke,
but it was the same for men.
18, 19, 20-year-olds
would show up to school
every day in a suit and tie.
White dress shirts, starched
collar
and polished black wingtips.
Same at the office. Any office.
It showed respect
for their institutions,
their colleagues, themselves.
At a university,
it showed an appreciation
for higher learning,
which, I am sorry to say,
is lacking in the halls
of academia today.
You can't deny that.
Is it too much for me to
ask you to show
a little appreciation?
Look, I appreciate the wine.
And the art.
And the party, thank you.
But I do wonder, where is the
line
between normal appreciation
and abnormally inappropriate?
Clever.
I-I was heading to the bathroom.
That way.
Thanks.
You dressed up for your "B,"
Jenny.
This is how you get your "a."
[Yells] You thankless ingrate!
Jenny! Hey, Jenny!
I'm sorry, Jenny.
I am so sorry.
Dr. Davrow never did
anything like that to me,
not all last year.
The dresses...
Yeah.
But kissing?
[Jenny sobs]
I guess he upped his game.
Monday morning. Conduct...
No! I don’t want to get
into a political war
with a professor
my first month at school.
Or ever.
I just want to study
and run track.
Can I please just do that?
I'm sorry.
13.2.
Not a church picnicker
who can do that.
(Chuckles) Thanks, coach.
What do I have to hit
to get on the team?
Shave a second off,
and I'll fight for you.
And the scholarship?
Still not my call.
Competition for money is...
It's even fiercer than the
fight for the finish line.
No... there's nothing like
fighting
for the finish line.
That's what I love about
running.
There's no pedigree.
Doesn't matter what your name
is, what you look like,
what you think, do, say.
It's just about your legs,
your breath, and your time.
That's all that matters.
Hi.
I prefer this look.
Me too.
You're gonna pay a price for it.
But at least you're not broken.
Andrew Jackson,
hero of New Orleans,
ending the English attempt
at taking back the colonies
they had lost
nearly half a century earlier.
Dr. Davrow:
Okay, I need a volunteer.
Miss Willis.
No, thank you.
Excuse me?
You asked for volunteers.
I'm not.
Participation is not optional
in my class.
When I call on you, you come.
Privilege of authority.
You won't break me.
I what?
Break you.
I hope everyone
is paying attention.
I need a volunteer.
Alexis.
Come on up.
I know what you're doing.
You don't know anything, Jenny.
If you did, you wouldn't be
doing this to yourself.
I'm not doing anything to
myself.
You're the one doing this to me.
You're just an arrogant,
entitled misogynist,
and if you don't start grading
according to my merit,
I'm gonna report you T...
To whom?
You clearly
haven't thought this out.
It doesn't matter who you go to.
My department chair.
The faculty conduct committee.
With any of them, it's the word
of a prestigious professor
against a freshman girl
who offered him sex
in exchange for better grades.
I have tenure, Jenny.
Do you know what that is?
They can't fire me.
They can't censure me.
They can't dock my pay.
But for you, win or lose,
how do you think that will go
for your track scholarship?
Or we can just put all of this
ridiculousness behind us
and give each other
what we want.
Jenny: You said he didn't
Mark
down girls who don't play along.
I didn't think he did.
But I it's not like we all talk
to each other about it.
I didn't know anybody
who didn't play along.
Until you.
He's right about
reporting him though.
Even if they believe you,
there's nothing
they can do to him,
and you'll suffer anyway.
Will you come with me
to report him?
Beth, please.
I'm guilty, Jenny.
He forced you.
Not like that.
He suggested, and I complied.
I'm sorry.
They wouldn't believe two
students
more than one, anyway.
Universities don't want to hear
about this kind of stuff.
Not from us.
But maybe from faculty?
Close the door, Ms. Willis.
Close the door!
She was so excited
to come to school.
She's been sullen since day one.
That poor girl in her room.
She said a professor died,
and there was a break in.
Jenny's not having trouble
with any faculty, is she?
Oh, no, no, no just the dorms.
Adjusting to her new roommates.
Unless you've
noticed something in class?
No. I mean, I can only
speak for myself, of course,
but I've found Jenny
to be a treasure.
Bright, confident.
Qualities she apparently
inherited.
Uh, would you uh...
I feel terrible even asking
this,
snowplow mom times a
thousand, but uh...
Would it be okay with you
if I checked in every now and
then,
just to see how she's doing?
Of course. Anytime.
Thank you... Eric.
Here's your orange passion.
Mom. What are you...
What are you doing here?
These are delicious.
You gotta start making them
for me at home. (Chuckles)
They're like 700 calories.
Well, worth it
for the ice breaker.
I'm sorry that I push you so
hard.
Sorry for pushing back harder.
- Your dad was...
- Dad was...
I uh, met one of your teachers.
Mom, I'm not
in fifth grade anymore.
Right. Professors.
Yeah.
He's very charming.
You talked to Dr. Davrow?!
He thinks you're wonderful.
Mom... I swear!
Stay out of it, please!
I am just trying to help!
[Door opens]
Sorry. I'll get out of your way.
You're not in my way.
I'm always in your way, Sarah.
What? Since the day I got here
you’ve made it very clear
you want me as far away
as possible.
Sorry you got stuck
with two fake roommates.
I shouldn't have said that.
Look, I know.
I know I've been mean.
But if you want to talk...
What's with the change of heart?
Do you want to go to the park?
Hey.
You two going somewhere?
Jenny: The park.
You want to come?
Sarah:
You know what? Actually, I
feel like
maybe I should stay back and
study.
Jenny: No, no, no, no.
You took the step. You're
coming.
Beth: He's cute.
Why don't you go ride with him?
If I wasn't as blond as I look,
I'd say you were trying
to get rid of me.
That didn't even make sense.
Sarah, please.
If you've had a change of heart
toward me,
maybe you can have one
toward Beth, too?
And you, the same.
Please, I really need
both of you right now.
[Loud noise]
Beth
code blue. What's going on?
Jenny
oh, my god. What was that?
Ride announcer (on speaker)
We're experiencing
some type of technical
difficulty.
Jenny seriously?
Sarah: Are we gonna die?
Ride announcer (on speaker) We
apologize
for the inconvenience.
I heard you guys.
About not wanting to get
into a political battle
with the professor.
Dr. Davrow.
You too?
Yeah. You fought him off?
Good for you.
'Cause I didn't.
And it was more than just
kissing.
Oh my gosh, Sarah...
You slept with him?
And you've been judging
me all this time?
Beth!
No! How dare you, Sarah!
How dare you point the finger
at me like I'm some...
You don't understand!
It was awful!
It was horrible!
I felt so... So dirty.
And so I stopped
and then when I did,
he didn’t just drop me
back down to the grades
I was getting before,
he-he failed me.
Like... like F’s.
And he had other professors
do it, too.
He had other professors
do it to me.
And Elaine.
Wait, what?
She was brave... Like you.
She was going to report him.
And then she just falls
from the dormitory roof.
Oh my gosh!
You think Dr. Davrow killed her?
And I just... And I just shut up.
Jenny, I am so sorry.
I should have
said something to you sooner.
I just... I have been so... Scared.
Dr. Davrow
couldn't have killed Elaine.
A faculty member
couldn't make it all the way
to the rooftop of a dorm without
getting recognized.
And during a party!
Okay, then someone's helping
him.
Or there's...
Or nothing.
Dr. Davrow shouldn't be
forcing girls to dress up
or anything else
for grades, I'll give you that.
But that doesn't mean he has
anything to do with Elaine.
There's no way.
Hey, look, it doesn't matter.
Whether he killed Elaine or not,
what he's doing alone is enough
that we have to report him.
Now you want to go to war?
I don't care about
my scholarship anymore.
I don't care if they kick me out
of school for making a scene.
I mean, he can't
keep doing this.
And if he did kill Elaine,
all the more reason.
He killed Elaine.
Or somebody did it for him.
But I... I can't say anything,
Jenny.
I'm finally getting
good grades again.
I...
It's too dangerous.
He'll kill me. He'll kill you,
too.
So he just gets away with it?
With all of it?
Maybe he'll forgot about you.
That's the best
you can hope for.
And Elaine?
Do we all just...
Forget about her?
[Ride engine starts]
A wide range of disorders
can experience
psychotic symptoms
from full blown schizophrenia
to more mild afflictions
like schizoaffective
and borderline
personality disorders...
Are you kidding me?!
Sit down, Ms. Willis.
Me... sit down?
How about you stand up?
And you!
Okay, what's more important, an
"a" in misogynistic psychology
or integrity for the rest
of your lives?
That's enough!
Yeah, it is.
One more word from you,
and I will drop you from this
class with an incomplete.
Word.
That is the perfect example
of borderline personality
disorder.
[Door slams]
I'm reporting him.
Are you guys coming with me?
(Scoffs) Whatever.
Wait.
[Door closes]
Are you scared?
Yeah. But I also feel
kind of free.
Tell me about Elaine.
Elaine was awesome.
She was smart.
Like really smart.
I was struggling in calculus,
and she made it seem so easy.
And she was really nice.
But like... an intuitive kind of
nice.
Like she would know
exactly what you needed.
[Screaming]
Sarah! Sarah!
Help! Someone help!
I got you. I got you.
Sarah!
Hi. How's she doing?
She's... breathing, but...
But not waking up.
Thank you, Dane.
You saved my life.
Yeah. Of course.
[Cell phone rings]
Honey? Are you okay? -
no, mom.
I messed everything up.
I dressed up for Dr. Davrow,
and then he attacked me...
And I think he killed Elaine
and he might have
just killed Sarah also.
Kristen (on phone)
Okay, I'm coming.
I'm coming. I'm coming okay?
Hurry up, just take it.
Kristen: Linda!
Manage the store for me tonight?
Of course.
Come on. Let's go.
Wait!
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Oh!
I'm fine. I gotta go.
Did you see him?
The guy that threw us
over the rail?
Was it Dr. Davrow?
Dr. Davrow?
No, I-I didn't see anybody.
I just ran to you.
Oh my gosh, Beth!
Hey.
Beth, are you okay?
Beth (on phone) I'm fine.
Stupid Dane came back and tore
through our room again.
No, what?
I told you I wasn't convinced.
He picked the lock.
Completely destroyed the place.
No, Beth, Dane's with me.
He's been with me all day.
Someone tried to kill me
and Sarah.
What? Are you okay?
Sarah's in a coma.
Alive, but the police are here.
Jenny, listen, whoever
attacked you,
whoever was here,
they're not done.
Whoever, Beth.
We know who it was.
Did you see him?
I... well, no, but...
Then it doesn't matter.
Whether it was him or somebody
else.
I can't believe I'm saying this,
but Sarah was right.
It's too dangerous.
I'm scared.
Jenny: The police are here.
So, you brought the victim
in from the clock tower?
She was attacked, too.
Can you identify the attacker?
No.
Can you think of anyone that
would want to harm you?
Please.
No.
I detest local news.
So, I was thinking...
Maybe we could go out tonight?
Dinner, a movie?
Is it really so bad
if anybody sees us out together?
There's enough gossip
on campus among the students.
We don't need to add to that.
Right. Okay. I agree.
I'm just going to...
[Sighs] Oh my god.
What?
Do you jog?
No, I...
I didn't know that you did.
I knew you were seeing
other people, but students?
The girls on the bridge, Eric?
What did you do?
What have you done?
Didn't I say I don't like to
be the subject of gossip?
What?
[Ms. Kingsley screams]
So, you think Dr. Davrow?
I think, but I-I can't prove.
Do you think it was the right
move
not telling the police?
Hey, are you okay?
Yeah, just tweaked it
after everything today.
Thank you, Dane.
You're welcome.
I mean, if you
hadn't been there,
I'd be in the ICU next to Sarah.
Or worse.
Um...
This is...
I don't want this
to sound the wrong way.
If your room isn't safe...
I mean uh, if you need
somewhere to stay tonight...
I'm gonna go home.
I mean, I'm gonna
move home, I think.
Leave school?
No. Just drive in.
Yeah, maybe dorm life's
not for me after all.
My mom's coming to pick me up.
[Elevator bell rings]
Hey.
Oh my god.
Are you all right?
Yeah. I'm just exhausted.
I'm gonna shower
then my mom's
coming to get me.
What?
You should come with me.
At least for a few nights.
It's not safe here.
Yeah. Okay.
Uh, you take a shower,
and relax,
and I'll pack some stuff.
- Okay.
Is that all they took?
Yeah. That's all.
I just need you
to sign this, please.
Okay. Can I go now?
Mm-hmm.
Thanks.
Hey, you got the store?
Hey. How are you doing?
I'm fine.
You should dress that leg.
It's fine. I gotta go.
[Water running]
[Phone rings]
Jenny, I'm so sorry. I'm just
leaving the store right now.
I'm racing to you.
Okay, I'll be there soon as I
can.
Okay, bye.
Call me when you get this.
Jenny!
[Gasps] Ugh! We have got to
stop doing that.
Oh, no. I'm so sorry.
I-I'll fix it.
Uh, it's-it's fine.
Beth said there was someone
in your room again?
I don't know. I wasn't home.
I'm just... I'm just tired..
Of course. Yeah.
Jenny! Jenny, wait!
Beth! Beth! Let me go!
Listen to me!
What is going on?
He broke into the room!
I saw his shoulder!
Wait.
- Did you kill Elaine?!
- No!
Why'd you break in?
Do you have a key?
Elaine gave me the key.
Why would she give you a key?
I loved her.
We were dating, all last year.
All summer.
Elaine never dated.
It's not allowed for R.A.'S
and undergrads
so we didn't tell anyone.
I loved her.
I want to find out
who killed her.
Bull!
Find out how?
What are you looking for in
here?
Elaine sent me a text
the night she died.
She was sending it
right when she was killed.
Elaine... fell.
In the middle of texting me?
What proof?
Pictures.
I'm not sure of what.
She took them on her phone
at one of those "dinners"
and printed them to make sure
they couldn't disappear.
Good thing, too, because
her phone got smashed
when she died.
But I don't know where
she put them.
Her parents let me go through
everything they took
from here but...
I-I think they're still in here
if you haven't found them yet...
I didn't do this.
I cut your shoulder.
That time, yes.
But you almost caught me,
and then the new lock...
Which you tried to pick.
I couldn't get in!
I didn't do this.
I’ll prove it to you if we
can find the pictures.
Just help me, please!
For Elaine.
Okay, where haven't you looked?
Almost everywhere.
I'd barely started.
Okay, we'll help you.
Let's start looking.
(Whispering) He's lying, Jen.
You even said,
a "guy she dumped."
He had a key.
He could have gotten in here
during the party.
He could have killed Elaine,
and no one would ever...
Okay, it doesn't hurt
to look, Beth.
Okay, search Sarah's bed.
Hey. I found something.
Beth? You?
But, if he forced you...
He didn't force me.
I love Dr. Davrow.
He's brilliant and beautiful.
A genius.
But you you told me
to dress up for him.
You told me about
the study with the art...
You delivered me to him.
I was trying to help you!
Get your grades up.
Get you your track scholarship!
But he was right,
you're so... Ungrateful.
And so was Elaine.
She was going to expose
the whole thing.
And not only ruin
Dr. Davrow's good name,
she was going to ruin mine!
I would have been kicked
out of school,
no college degree,
no future at all.
And so you murdered her?
I wanted to keep her quiet.
I wanted the pictures,
but she fought me, and she fell.
She fell!
Sarah didn't fall!
Sarah stayed quiet.
The whole thing had quieted down
until you came around
and stirred it back up again.
And you...
Breaking in here.
I suppose I should thank you.
I've been looking for those.
Phone too.
Time to delete that text.
Why didn't she just
text you the pictures?
I'd ask her,
if you hadn't killed her!
[Gunshot]
Kyle: Come on!
Wait, wait.
I'm not going to make it
down 12 flights.
- Yes, you are.
- I'm not fast enough.
Come on.
Beth: Hey!
[Growling]
You can't run! You can't hide!
Call Jenny!
Mom?
I'm on my way.
I'll be there as soon as I can.
Are you okay?
Where are you?
I'm coming to the dorms.
No, no, no! Not there!
Jenny, I can't hear you.
Mom?
Call Jenny! Call Jenny!
Where's the police station?
This way. This way.
Okay.
[Tires screech and squeal]
Kyle: Jenny!
Yeah. It's crazy
how this all went down, huh?
Kyle finds out
that the love of his life
is sleeping with Dr. Davrow..
To get her grades up,
and in a jealous rage,
throws her off the rooftop.
What are you talking about?
Beth: I'm talking about
how Jenny saw the scratch
she gave to the guy
who broke into our room
on your arm,
and you killed her.
It's just lucky that I
got here in time
to shoot you with your own gun
before you got away with murder.
No.
Again.
Beth, please, you don't
have to do this, Beth.
[Gunshot]
Are you crazy?
No, Jenny. I'm pissed.
Pissed that you just
wouldn't let it go!
You know, I liked you.
You were a way better
roommate than Sarah...
But at least she shut up!
Now look what you made Kyle do.
[Tires screech]
You are... Crazy!
Kristen: Jenny!
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
You're okay.
Kyle!
Kyle. Kyle. Okay.
Hey. It's okay.
Yes. We need help.
A student's been shot
outside the dorms.
At um.. Channing
and... and Telegraph!
Hey. Hang on.
Hang on for life.
Man's voice:
Is everyone okay?
No, we need help.
We need a doctor.
Man's voice: I'm a doctor.
Psychology. Does that help?
How'd he know where we...?
Beth told you that
Sarah and I were on the bridge.
He killed professor Harrington.
That old man
thought he was better than me.
Wanted to report me!
If he was thirty years younger,
he would have been thanking me.
You really did raise a fine...
Fine daughter, Mrs. Willis.
[Gunshot]
Aah!
I know.
[Police siren]
Hey.
You know what "R.A." Stands for?
"Really awesome."
Good enough to get
my scholarship back?
It is still not my decision.
It's the athletic director's.
[Squealing]
[Jennie squealing]
Don't do that!
[Group laughing]
Sarah, can I just say
how happy I am
that you're Jenny's roommate.
Mom...
What? Let me gush.
Hey, guys.
This is Lisa, your new...-
jenny/Sarah roommate!
Jenny: Welcome.
[Glasses clink]
[Laughter]