[menacing music playing]
[teenage girl] "It began as a prank
and ended in murder."
Fantastic choice.
I love this one.
It's trash.
Low-brow horror.
It's for my stepdaughter.
[sighs] That'll be $2.95.
Thank you for shopping at B. Dalton's.
[pleasant Muzak playing over speakers]
And have a nice night.
[man over PA] Attention, shoppers.
The Shadyside Mall is now closed.
["Closer" playing over store speakers]
♪ You let me violate you ♪
♪ You let me desecrate you ♪
♪ You let me penetrate you… ♪
[sighs]
[telephone ringing]
Hello, this is B. Dalton's. We're closed.
OK, since when do you work late?
Since my mom used her last paycheck
on scratch tickets
instead of the gas bill.
[line goes dead]
Hello?
Ryan?
Ryan? Are you there?
- Ryan? Hello?
- [dead tone]
Hello, Ryan!
[suspenseful music playing]
- [clanging]
- [gasps]
Night.
[relieved sigh]
- [falsetto] All alone now!
- Jesus Christ!
Woo-hoo! [laughing]
Ryan! What the hell, dude! [gasps]
Forgive me.
I do need a ride tonight.
That's what she said.
You are disgusting.
And, yes, I don't want to walk home alone.
Fine. Just give me and, uh… Jasmine here
15 minutes to close up.
You gave her a name.
Yeah, I thought, uh… "Big Tits"
was kind of deflating her ego.
[she scoffs]
- [whispering voice] Ryan…
- What?
I didn't say anything, weirdo.
[suspenseful music playing]
[shutter creaking]
[groans]
[ominous drumbeat]
[suspenseful music continues]
- [sighs]
- [distant bang]
[gasps]
[sighs]
[high-pitched shrill]
[gasps]
Hello?
[ominous music playing]
[relieved sigh]
- [object falls]
- [gasps]
[forcefully] OK. Very funny, asshole.
I'm spooked, OK? You win.
Ryan?
[ominous music playing]
[breathes deeply]
[she screams]
[she pants]
[screams]
[she grunts]
[shouting] Ryan! Ryan!
Help!
Ryan! [gasping]
Oh!
[panting]
[ringing tone]
[woman] 911, what's your emergency?
Hi, um… I'm in the Shadyside Mall.
- Um…
- [footsteps squeaking]
[woman] Hello?
[Heather pants]
Are you still there, ma'am?
Is someone hurt?
Ma'am, if you don't answer,
I'm gonna dispatch help.
[ominous music playing]
[gasps]
[breathing shakily]
[shouting]
[panting]
[she gasps]
[gasps]
[she breathes heavily]
[ominous music crescendos]
[doll hissing]
[Heather] Hey!
[Heather gasping]
Help! Help!
[Heather screaming]
[menacing music playing]
[screams]
Help!
[dramatic music playing]
[she screams]
Ah!
Ah, ah!
Ryan?
[crying] Please! It's me. It's me.
[gunshot]
[Heather gasps]
[officer gasps]
[dramatic music playing]
[female reporter 1]
More death in Shadyside
while Sunnyvale enters its 30th year
with no violent crime.
[female reporter 2] Killer Capital, USA,
as tragedy struck again.
[male sports announcer]
Sunnyvale football wins again!
[female reporter 3]
Christina Marlow and Jessica Van
were found in a house
in a residential area near Shadyside.
They've been identified.
[woman 1] That's Sunnyvale!
[man 1] Shadysiders seem to have
no desire to better themselves.
[man 2] Sunnyvale and Shadyside!
[male reporter 1] This just in!
More body parts found in the lake
between Shadyside and Sunnyvale.
[male announcer 1] Sunnyvale voted
Most Beautiful Place to Live!
[male reporter 2] Shadyside residents
are spending another night hunkering down
in darkness as…
[male announcer 2]
Find your new home in Sunnyvale,
where the sun always shines,
even when it's cloudy!
While the depression hit Shadyside hard,
the economy in Sunnyvale
continues to shine.
[female reporter 4] According to sources
with the Shadyside Police…
[indistinct news coverage]
[girl screams]
[crowd shouting]
[high-pitched shrill]
[woman screams]
["Only Happy When It Rains" playing]
♪ I'm only happy when it rains ♪
♪ I'm only happy when it's complicated ♪
♪ And though I know
You can't appreciate it ♪
♪ I'm only happy when it rains ♪
♪ You know I love it
When the news is bad ♪
♪ Why it feels so good to feel so sad? ♪
♪ I'm only happy when it rains ♪
[alarm bell ringing]
Shadyside, small-town America.
But among locals, a history of horror
has earned it another nickname,
"Killer Capital USA."
- And last night, tragedy struck again.
- Ugh, Dad!
I'm here with Sheriff Nick Goode.
Sheriff, what can you tell us?
Uh, there were seven victims,
uh, ages, uh, 16 to 42.
Uh, the perpetrator's also deceased.
[female reporter]
Shadyside sits just beside Sunnyvale,
one of the safest and wealthiest
communities in the country…
Josh!
What is it about Shadyside?
How do we end this cycle of violence?
[girl] Josh!
["Fear of the Dark"
playing over headphones]
- ♪ I am a man who walks alone… ♪
- [keyboard clicking]
♪ And when I'm walking a dark road ♪
♪ At night
Or strolling through the park… ♪
[chat beeps]
♪ When the light begins to change ♪
♪ I sometimes feel a little strange ♪
♪ A little anxious when it's dark ♪
- [music fades out]
- [suspenseful music playing]
[chat beeps]
[tense music playing]
[keyboard clicking]
- Dude! What the hell?
- This isn't yours, dillweed!
Oh, I get it.
You building a shrine or something?
Alright, you know what?
It's time for school. Get in the car.
- Let me finish this chat.
- [she tuts]
Deena, be careful with that!
Dad said you weren't allowed on this.
Know how expensive AOL is?
I'm stealing it. I'm talking to someone!
This internet bullshit
is exactly why you have no friends.
It's not bullshit.
It's a community dedicated to the truth.
Look, some guy went crazy and killed
a bunch of people at the mall last night.
Holy shit.
[Josh] It was all over the news.
Skull mask killer.
But, of course, the media won't talk
about the most important part.
[Deena] Josh, I am telling you calmly,
step out of your internet fantasy
nerd land and get in the car.
Step out your depressoid
"I'm gonna die alone" land,
and stop obsessing about Sam!
- Get in the car!
- [bangs desk]
[ominous music playing]
["Machinehead" playing]
[school bell rings]
[indistinct chatter]
♪ Breathe in, breathe out… ♪
See you later, Sir Silence.
♪ Breathe in, breathe out ♪
["Damn I Wish I Was Your Lover" playing]
Up, up, down, down.
Left, right, left, right, B, A, start.
♪ Damn, I wish I was your lover… ♪
[boy] Watch it, nerd.
["Sour Times" playing]
♪ 'Cause nobody loves me, it's true ♪
♪ Not like you do ♪
[girl] Jeez.
[indistinct chatter]
[random student shouts, laughs]
You see? It's the witch.
Sarah Fier's back.
Oh, Christ. Not you too.
[cheerleader laughs]
[school bell rings]
"She reaches from beyond the grave
to make good men her wicked slaves!"
- "She'll take your blood!"
- [Deena] Simon!
"She'll take your head.
She'll follow you until you're dead!"
Wow!
You guys are dicks.
- It's just fun.
- It's sick.
What? The dude was wearing
a Halloween skull mask!
How is that not fun?
People died.
Heather died.
The dude was probably just some sad sack
who hated his life, like the rest of us,
except he decided, "Hey,
why don't I get out of here for good?"
And, "Hey, why don't I take Heather
and a couple other mall rats with me?"
There's no angry dead witch
who made him go postal.
The only thing that made him go crazy
is this town!
Are you OK?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Seems like…
maybe you got a little witch in you.
[cheerleader laughs]
Dude, why are you even in here?
This is the girls' bathroom.
Candy store.
You know we don't believe
this witch shit, right?
It's just, like, fucked-up Santa Claus
or something.
[Simon] Ho, ho, ho!
- What's this?
- I need you to give this to Sam tonight.
- Yeah, uh-uh. No way.
- Come on, Kate!
No way, Deena.
I am not getting mixed up
in your ex drama. Do it yourself.
I'm not going to the game. I quit band.
- Since when?
- Since who gives a shit!
Was band the only extracurricular
you had left?
You still have your band uniform, right?
You just wear that shit one last time.
I've got something
that'll give you the balls to face Sam.
What? You're dealing again? I thought you
stopped after this dingus's brother OD'd.
[Simon] Timothy?
Wh… Uh… Timmy wasn't a real OD.
He didn't actually die.
They brought him back.
Ja-jing!
You're both morons.
Which one of us is valedictorian, again?
President of every club
this shithole has to offer.
I'm getting out of here. Off to claim
my place among the stars, bitch.
[boy] Woo! The witch lives!
Long live Sarah Fier!
Woo!
Yeah!
[students laughing, shouting]
[Simon laughs]
[coach] Before tonight's game,
out of respect
for last night's tragic events,
Sunnyvale will host
a candlelight vigil for the victims.
All player, cheer and band attendance
is mandatory.
[male student] Oh, really? Come on!
["Insane in the Membrane" playing]
♪ Don't you know I'm loco? ♪
[indistinct chatter]
[barking]
♪ Insane in the membrane… ♪
Didn't you quit?
♪ Insane in the brain… ♪
- [Simon growls]
- ♪ Insane in the membrane ♪
♪ Insane in the brain ♪
♪ Insane in the membrane ♪
♪ Crazy insane, got no brain ♪
["Creep" playing over headphones]
♪ You're so very special ♪
♪ But I'm a creep ♪
♪ I'm a weirdo ♪
♪ What the hell am I doing here? ♪
♪ I don't belong here ♪
♪ I don't care if it hurts… ♪
[music fades]
[uplifting music playing] ♪ Oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh ♪
[man 1 over speakers] This isn't
how I wanted to be here tonight.
I wanted to be here as a fan.
Our Sunnyvale Devils
and your Shadyside Witches
throwing down
some good old American football.
Instead I find myself here
as a husband,
a father, as a neighbor.
And, yes,
mayor of Sunnyvale.
And on behalf of all of the people
in my town,
I say all of Sunnyvale mourns with you.
Yeah, really looks like they give a damn.
The only Sunnyvalers who came
were the ones who had to.
The football team and the cheerleaders.
[mayor] Our hearts are broken with grief.
[melancholic music playing]
[lighter clinks]
Sam.
[breathes deeply]
[soft music playing]
I didn't think you were coming.
I thought you quit band.
Yeah, I did. Here.
What…
Is this my stuff?
Ding ding ding.
[dramatic music playing]
[man 2 over speakers] My family's been
in Sunnyvale for generations,
and now my brother is mayor
and I your sheriff.
We've prospered here.
And yet, I've seen you,
our neighbors in Shadyside,
suffer tragedy after tragedy.
It's easy in times like this
to drown in questions of why…
Why this happened.
But I know too well
there are no answers
that will provide relief.
There's no peace found in the past.
- Can we talk for a second?
- No.
You broke up with me! Remember?
So stop acting like I'm the bad guy.
Yeah, well, I'm not the one
who moved to Sunnyvale.
OK, you made the choice.
I just made it official.
My parents got divorced.
I didn't have a choice.
[Deena] Oh, come on!
You just couldn't wait to start
your new fake life with your fake-ass mom!
I am half an hour away.
It might as well be the goddamn moon,
and you know it.
I don't know anything.
[Deena] Yeah. Well, I do.
I know you were always too afraid
to tell anyone about us.
I know that.
And I know that douchebag out there
was squeezing your ass.
- You broke up with me.
- What's his name?
- You broke up with me!
- What's his name, Sam?
- The dude groping you.
- Stop. Stop!
- [Deena] Touching you!
- Peter!
His name is Peter!
We must not fall into darkness.
We must look to the light.
[scoffs] Yeah!
What we should do is light a fuse
and burn down Shittyside.
What'd you say?
- You don't get it!
- [Deena] No, no. I do.
There's not much of a future
in Shadyside with a lesbo.
Best case is what?
Dead on the mall floor
after a double shift,
or maybe, maybe if you're really lucky,
you're the one carrying the knife.
I said it ain't a tragedy
when it happens every week.
It's a joke.
Jesus. You're doing it again.
[Deena] Doing what?
- "Welcome to the suck!" "Shit is doomed!"
- Shit is doomed!
[Sam] It doesn't have to be.
- It's like you want to lose.
- At least I know who I am.
Stop being mad at me
for wanting a different future.
It's not your future
if you're pretending to be someone else.
Say that again, motherfucker!
[dramatic music crescendos]
[shouting]
[girls screaming]
[Nick] Stop!
[Simon screams]
You little green prick!
Come here, you little bitch! Come here!
Suck it in...
- Pieces of shit!
- [all] Yeah!
- They think they can do what they want!
- [all] No!
[Kate] They ruin our vigil,
then go waltzing back to their mansions,
like we're some reject pile
that they can step on!
[all] No!
Well, we are not the reject pile!
- [all] No!
- This shit ends tonight!
- [all] Yeah!
- What are we gonna do?
We're gonna go kill those preppy assholes!
[all] Yeah!
[chanting] Kate! Kate! Kate!
Kate! Kate!
[shouting] When I say Shady, you say side!
- Shady!
- [all] Side!
When I say Shady, you say side!
- Shady!
- [all] Side!
[Simon] When I say Shady, you say side!
- Shady!
- Side!
[chanting]
[car horn beeping]
[repeated beeping]
[students chanting]
[horn beeping]
[engine revs loudly]
Goddamn Sunnyvalers.
[boy] Yeah! Where are you going?
- Guys! Come here! Come here!
- [chanting]
- Shady!
- Side!
- Woo!
- [tires screech]
- You gotta be kidding me.
- Hey, isn't that, uh…
[engine revs loudly]
Sam.
[boy] Where are you going, you pussies?
Sunnyvale sucks!
- [Sam] Peter, stop! What are you doing?
- [Peter] Chill out!
[Deena] Open the door!
Open the door!
This is definitely a good idea, right?
Deena?
On three, OK?
- [Kate] Are you sure?
- One, two…
- [Kate] Deena!
- What?
[gasps] Your nose!
[tires screech]
- [loud crash]
- Stop! Stop the bus!
[horn blaring]
[Sam and Peter groaning]
[Peter] Whew.
[boy] Shit, are you alive?
[Peter] Yeah, I'm alive. Yeah.
[Peter] Sam! What… what are you doing?
- [Sam groans]
- [Peter] Sam!
[Peter] Sam!
[menacing music playing]
[indistinct voices whispering]
[sighs]
[gasps]
[groans]
[haunting music intensifies]
- [Deena] Sam!
- [Sam gasps]
[sighs]
Are you OK? Oh!
I'm so… I'm sorry.
Stay away from her, you bull dyke freak!
Sam, it's me. I'm here.
[breathing heavily] Did you… see?
What?
[menacing music intensifies]
Oh shit!
[Kate] OK, we should not be down here.
- Shut up, help me carry her!
- We need to leave, like ten minutes ago.
- We have to clear her airway.
- Quit it!
Hey! I got this. Chill out.
I got this.
- How many fingers am I holding up?
- Three.
See? She's fine.
- [Kate] Oh, my God!
- [Simon] Oh. Ugh!
- What the fuck?
- [Sam groans]
- [police siren wailing]
- [indistinct police radio chatter]
- [man] Deena Johnson?
- Yeah, two E's.
Wanna tell me what happened?
The car crashed.
Was it pursuing you?
Well, it was driving behind the bus.
Does that count as pursuing?
The driver said that before the crash
someone opened the emergency exit.
I don't remember that.
No?
He also saw you with the cooler.
Did anyone else see that?
Maybe you were just, um… goofing around.
Things got out of hand.
- Why don't you tell me what happened?
- [Deena] I don't know.
I guess…
Sometimes accidents just happen.
We lost control, sir.
Freak accident.
Suck it, pig.
It was just an accident.
Alright.
Well, if you do think of anything,
give me a call.
I'm on your side.
Yeah, totally.
My car is totaled.
Well, Daddy will buy you a new one.
- [Deena grunts]
- [Peter] Shittyside trash.
You are all fucking… dead.
[indistinct voices whispering]
[menacing music crescendos]
[screaming]
[dog barking]
[children laughing, playing]
[soft suspenseful music playing]
[gasping]
- I'm gonna kill you.
- [Josh] Yeah?
Do it before Dad gets here,
he's gonna murder you!
You know the cops called him at work
about some accident last night?
Please get out of my room.
You get out of your room.
You've been in your bed all day!
Get up!
[ominous bell rings]
[female reporter] I'm here
with Martin P. Franklin,
Shadyside Mall Janitor.
- Martin, what do you know?
- [Martin] He was a normal dude.
Always thought he would, like, just go
home and read a comic book or whatever.
He was chill, just snapped I guess.
[female reporter] A baffling development
as mall employee Ryan Torres
has been identified as the killer.
A recent graduate of Shadyside High
an ordinary guy who,
as those who knew him attest,
just seemed to snap.
- [ringing tone]
- [woman] East Union Medical.
Hi. Uh, Samantha Fraser's room, please?
- [rock music playing upstairs]
- [doorbell rings]
Josh! Get the door!
["More Human Than Human" playing]
♪ Man, I turn the world around
With a skeleton hand ♪
♪ Say I am electric head ♪
[doorbell rings]
- [woman] Hello?
- [Deena] Uh… Hi, uh, Mrs. Fraser.
I'm sorry. Uh, Miss… Ms…
- [doorbell rings]
- Hi, um…
- [doorbell]
- Is Sam there? I just…
- I wanted to see how she was doing.
- [Ms. Fraser] Deena?
Yeah. Hi.
I was just w… worried about her and...
[Ms. Fraser] You won't stop until you've
ruined her life completely, will you?
- She's fine. Don't call here again.
- [line goes dead]
[dead tone]
- [doorbell rings repeatedly]
- Josh!
♪ More human than human
More human than hu... ♪
Hello?
[menacing music playing]
[door creaking]
[ominous drumbeat]
Oh, hey, Peter!
See you got the full costume now!
[door creaking]
[menacing music crescendos]
- [timer buzzing]
- [Josh] Hey!
[gasps]
- Pizza ready?
- Oh, that ringing you heard.
What? [scoffs]
I have priorities.
Jeez.
- [buzzer stops]
- Shit! Hot, hot, hot!
[ominous music playing]
Sunnyvale prick.
Holy shit!
[Deena] Stay here.
You're pathetic!
[ominous music playing]
["Gz and Hustlas" playing]
[Kate] Four in each bag.
If you finish in an hour,
I'll let you watch
My So-Called Life with me.
And, uh, do not eat these.
These will make your little hearts stop,
you'll choke to death on vomit
and everyone will be so, so super sad.
Got it?
♪ Now back to the Gz ♪
♪ Freeze, at ease ♪
[man 1] Bob, easy with that blood.
It's our last can!
[Kate] What happened to sorting this?
Lights and darks,
and watch for stray socks.
- Remind me what's in it for me again?
- Nope.
You still wearing
the clothes from last night?
Did you wear that to the grocery store?
I had to work a double shift
and this was all I had in the car.
So, yes. Yes, I am.
- [pager beeping]
- Oh.
That's disgusting. You're disgusting.
- [man 1 on TV] Alright, kiddo?
- [man 2] There I was at ten…
Hey, lady-killer.
[Deena] Where are you?
Babysitting. Look out the window.
That prick Peter is screwing with me.
Sam's boyfriend? What the hell?
Yeah, he's creeping around our house
in one of those skull masks. It's fucked.
[sighs] I gotta go. Call you back.
Jesus! Put something on!
What? Make up your mind, woman!
[window smashes]
Stay here.
[low ominous music playing]
[glass smashing]
[glass smashing, banging]
[banging]
- [whispering] Maybe this isn't a good id...
- Shh!
Hey, creeper. What the f...
[haunting music playing]
- [quietly] Are you crazy?
- [Kate] It's just that Sunnyvale asshole.
[door creaks]
Thank you so much.
Oh, no. I'm so happy to have the company.
- [Kate] You're a lifesaver, Mrs. Lane.
- [Mrs. Lane] I used to be a nurse.
[menacing music playing]
Are you… you sure everything's OK?
Totally! I just have to run out and…
Kill that pervert!
Why would he break in there?
I just don't understand what he was doing.
He was acting all shifty and shit.
Like going through the laundry.
You need to get some groceries, man.
- We have an incredible sale at the store...
- He broke into the house! He had a knife!
Whoa! With the kids there? That's wack!
That's fucking right, Josh.
It is wack. Thank you.
There were kids there. OK, and what?
He thinks because he's balling Sam,
he can come and prank us on our own turf.
Hey, you know what?
You're right. Fuck this.
- Fuck Peter.
- [Kate] Hello?
Don't forget the most important part.
Fuck Sam.
Yeah, fuck her. She needs to get
her psycho boyfriend in check.
[Simon] Oh!
You coming or what?
[Simon] Hey, slow down, lover boy!
["Killing Me Softly with His Song" plays]
♪ Strumming my pain with his fingers ♪
♪ Singing my life with his words ♪
- ♪ Killing me softly with his song… ♪
- [bell dinging]
♪ Killing me softly… ♪
- Fill these out and take a seat.
- No, I'm just visiting.
Visiting hours ends at nine.
[clears throat]
Tell Nurse Beddy she has a patient.
["Your Woman" playing]
Beddy. Long time, how you been?
- Still toting around with this moron.
- She can't quit me, Beddy. Too pretty!
- [Beddy scoffs]
- Listen, we need your assistance.
I'm sure that you do, but there happens
to be a new security protocol.
We kept coming up short
on blueberries and bananas.
- So now I need a special key...
- I need to see a patient.
[ominous bell rings]
Blueberries and bananas?
Vicodin and Percocet.
You want anything from the machine?
I'm starving.
[suspenseful music playing]
[Deena] Cute sweatshirt.
- What are you doing here?
- What do you think?
I honestly have no clue.
Oh, Jesus. This game?
- What game? What are you talking about?
- [Deena] About your dipshit boyfriend.
- He threatened, "You're all fucking dead."
- That didn't mean anything.
Now tonight, he's stalking around,
messing with us.
He broke into the house
where Kate was babysitting.
No. Peter's been here.
You need to call him
and tell him to back off.
Good news. They're gonna transfer
you out of this shithole tomorrow.
Perfect timing, asshole.
Where's your stupid mask?
Yo, Si-Money. Cash me.
Don't look at me, dude.
I'm… I'm… I'm broke.
You got any change?
Oh, um…
Let me check.
Um…
Uh… Uh, no.
Uh, but I…
What do you want?
[Sam] He has been with me all night!
- Stop covering for him! He's a bad guy.
- You're out of control!
You put me in the hospital!
Now you're here yelling at me...
OK. No, that was an accident.
Look, I got a nosebleed.
- I didn't actually mean...
- A nosebleed? Stop making excuses!
You are total chaos!
And you have always been!
So don't blame me when you wake up
in ten years just like your dad!
Old and drunk and going nowhere!
OK, first, go to hell.
Second, yeah.
Congrats on getting out of Shadyside, Sam.
All you had to do was suck it up,
literally, and swallow some Sunnyvale...
You know what?
I never want to see you again!
Great. Have a nice goddamn life!
[Peter groans, gurgles]
[Deena] Oh my God!
[girls screaming]
- Where'd you learn how to do this?
- Oh, a lot of people trade hacks online.
[coughs] Nerd.
So, um… [chuckles]
…when'd you get into the fruit business?
What?
Um… The, uh… drugs.
Oh, that's just temporary.
Saving up to get out of here.
Take me with you.
[whistling]
- [imitates explosion]
- [girls screaming]
[Deena] Run!
Did they get back together?
[screaming]
[all screaming]
[TV host] Tonight's Unsolved Mysteries,
the story of a lonely housewife…
- Where are the keys? Do you have the keys?
- No!
Where… where are the keys?
Come on. The ambulance!
[glass breaking]
[breathing heavily]
[ominous music playing]
[Sam gasps]
[muffled sobs]
[whimpering]
- [Deena whispers] No!
- You can't wear that mask. What are...
[Deena gasps]
[screaming]
[Deena] Look out!
[girls screaming]
Come on!
[Sam grunting]
- [Simon] Come on! Let's go!
- [Josh] Come on!
What the…
[female reporter] Mall employee
Ryan Torres has been identified
as the killer in the mall massacre.
[Josh] Deena! Come on! Deena!
- [Simon] Deena! Hurry up! Let's go!
- [Deena] Go! Go!
- [Simon] We have to go now!
- [Deena] Hurry!
[tires screeching]
[Nick] You have access to the mall.
You are still employed there, correct?
I'mma tell you again.
Somebody planted that.
Those ain't my cans.
You're right, Martin. These…
are actually my cans.
Why would I tag my own place of work?
Come on, man!
Martin, around here,
people show a little respect.
They call me Sheriff Goode.
Sheriff Goode?
More like Sheriff motherfucking Evil!
[Deena] I'm telling you, it was him!
The psycho killer
my colleague shot dead, huh?
Yes! That's what we keep saying!
- What's wrong with you?
- [Nick] Officer Kapinski.
You told me to come to you.
We should not be this close to
the police station in a stolen ambulance.
We're hiding in plain sight.
Yeah, just like Bundy.
Ted Bundy, when he was stalking
his victims, I mean.
OK, didn't he get caught though?
- Well, no. Well, yeah, but...
- Figure this out. I'm gonna take a leak.
- [Josh sighs]
- Why do you know so much about killers?
Know thy enemy, right?
- You hang onto any of that candy?
- [Josh] Yeah.
Then his mask came off.
And you saw him?
Yeah. Yeah, the mall killer, Ryan Torres.
That's Ryan Torres.
[Deena] Yes!
Yes, that's him.
I know, but you guys must have made
a mistake or something. Look…
- I know what I saw.
- OK.
Let me get the right paperwork.
"Dead killer chasing…"
Would you say he was more, uh,
Dawn of the Dead
or Night of the Living Dead?
[Sam] Wait.
- You don't believe us?
- This was a waste of time.
We've had prank calls, we've had reports
of skeleton mask copycats all weekend.
Got a call from the hospital.
Lady sounded worked up.
[Deena gasps]
Uh… wait, I'll… I got it.
Take care of them.
[indistinct police radio chatter]
[Kapinski grunts, coughs]
[Kapinski grunts]
[police siren bleeps]
[engine revs loudly]
[zip closes]
[girl singing]
♪ You always hurt the one you love ♪
♪ The one you shouldn't hurt at all ♪
This is bullshit. There are bodies
at the hospital. You're gonna see...
Honey, we are so appreciative of this tip.
- The killer is still out there!
- We'll do our damnedest to catch him.
You're a monster!
You're supposed to protect us!
Hey, hey! Young lady, do not test me!
[panting] I'm so sorry, sir.
I have no idea what came over me.
Get out of here!
Go find your boyfriends!
Tell them you need to relax!
[girl singing] ♪ You always take ♪
♪ The sweetest rose ♪
♪ And crush it till the petals fall ♪
[Simon] Hey.
- ♪ You always take… ♪
- Are you OK?
Do… do you need help? What the…
- [Simon screams]
- [Sam] Deena, slow down!
- [Sam] What are you doing?
- [Deena] Just walk, fast.
We need to leave.
I think we should stay. We're safe here.
What if that psycho shows up again?
- Then we'll be ready.
- [Sam] What the hell?
Deena, what is that?
Is that the cop's? You stole a cop's gun?
Fuck yeah she did!
- You out of your goddamn mind?
- They didn't believe us.
We're on our own.
Where the hell is Simon?
["You Always Hurt the One You Love"
playing]
♪ You always hurt ♪
♪ The one you love ♪
♪ The one you shouldn't hurt… ♪
- [Simon screams]
[grunting]
[gasping]
[Simon yells]
[gunshots]
- Simon, come on!
- [Simon screams]
- [Kate] Come on!
- [Simon] Go! Go! Let's go!
[Simon] Go! Come on!
- Come on!
- [Simon] Sam! Come on! Run!
♪ You always… ♪
[Sam] It doesn't make sense.
It's… it's not possible.
- Bullets didn't stop her.
- Amazing observation.
- Who the hell was that?
- How the hell should I know? She…
She was hot! I don't know!
The bitch seemed normal!
I hate to break it to you,
but normal bitches
don't bleed black fucking blood!
Well, she was hot and normal
until she attacked me
with a fucking razor blade!
Wait. What… A razor?
Yeah, for like old-timey shaving,
or in this case, I guess, slitting her...
Wrists. She slashed her wrists.
Was she singing something?
Was she singing a song, like an oldie…
like an oldie song?
Jesus, Rain Man.
How the fuck do you know that?
This is Ruby Lane.
♪ You always hurt… ♪
- [Josh] The girl who attacked you.
- [Simon] Holy shit!
She sang as she murdered her boyfriend,
her friends, then she killed herself.
Slashed her wrists.
Jesus. Yeah, why didn't I see this
on the news?
Because it happened 30 years ago.
1965.
Ruby is one of Shadyside's killers,
just like Skull Mask.
[Heather] Ryan? Please!
[Josh] I mean Ryan Torres.
Look, 1978.
- [girl screaming]
- [Josh] Sixteen years ago.
- [Josh] "Masked psycho murders kids at..."
- [Kate] Camp Nightwing.
Yeah, my mom's sister was there.
That screwed my family up for a long time.
[Josh] 1950,
Harry Rooker,
local milkman slashes
a bunch of housewives.
1935, Humpty Dumpty Killer.
1922, Billy Barker.
1904, Grifter guts girls, and on and on.
It happens in Shadyside over and over.
Normal people turn into psychos.
[Simon] Jesus.
[indistinct voices whispering]
[Simon] Look at this guy.
That's the pastor, Cyrus Miller.
1666. He was the first one recorded.
He, um… killed kids
and cut out their eyes.
[retching]
[Deena] Sam?
I, uh, brought you…
- I always liked this sweater.
- Yeah, I know.
If you get blood on it, I'll kill you.
What's happening to us?
There are people trying to kill us.
Dead people,
if you believe my weirdo brother.
[scoffs]
That's not what I meant.
Yeah, I know.
Look, I know I always give you shit
for pretending you're someone you're not,
but it's…
It's not really easy for me to…
you know, be like us… either.
- Are you giving me a pass?
- [chuckles] No.
Fine. I'm not gonna say
what I was gonna say.
Say it.
[Sam sighs]
Maybe you're… you're right.
Maybe shit is doomed.
I mean, here we are.
We're together for one night and...
Dead people are trying to kill us.
[Josh] None of this is random.
It's Sarah Fier.
She's turning Shadysiders into killers.
Do you really believe that?
No one actually thinks
that this witch shit is real.
Yeah, it's something babysitters make up
to scare kids.
No, no. Just listen to me.
1666, Sarah Fier was hanged
for witchcraft, fact.
But ever since she was executed,
she's been possessing people,
turning them into killers,
to take revenge on the town.
- [Simon] It's like the nursery rhyme.
- [Josh] Yeah. Yeah.
[Simon] "Before the witch's final breath,
she found a way to cheat her death."
"By cutting off her cursed hand,
she kept her grip upon our land."
"She reaches from beyond the grave
to make good men her wicked slaves."
Yes, exactly.
Don't you see what's happening to us?
This is all proof.
Shadyside isn't just
some hotbed for psychos.
All these massacres are connected
to Sarah Fier.
The witch's curse is real!
Fine. Let's assume that the witch
has been possessing people
for some sort of messed-up vendetta.
This isn't the same as the mall massacre.
Something different is happening to us.
Something way worse.
OK, we have two of her killers after us
and both of them are dead.
Why is she so mad at us?
[Sam] I saw her.
Last night, I don't…
I don't know, you know.
I thought I hit my head…
It was…
It was her.
I saw the witch.
[ominous drumbeat]
[crickets chirping]
I can't believe you're wearing that.
Can't believe you're above it,
when we're in the middle
of the fucking woods
and dead maniacs are after us.
[sighs]
[high-pitched shrill]
OK, so I fell out of the car…
here.
I was crawling,
and my nose was bleeding.
And then…
- [metal clinking]
- I feel something.
[Kate] Chains?
Oh! Not just chains.
- [Kate] Holy shit.
- Oh my gosh.
- No way.
- Oh!
Fier. It's her.
It's her grave.
Oh no, no. No!
This is bad! This is really bad!
No wonder the witch is pissed at us.
I'd be pissed too.
Sam disturbed her grave.
[sighs] Now she's sending
her henchmen after us.
Henchmen?
As in every one of those sickos
on your wall is coming after us?
[twigs snapping]
Did you hear that?
[breathing heavily]
[Simon] Hold up. Hold up.
She's mad
because we disturbed her grave, right?
Yeah. So?
So, let's un-disturb it!
Just put the bones back, rebury them,
and put her to rest!
No, that's so stupid!
That's genius!
Yeah! In… in Poltergeist!
- [twigs snapping]
- [gasping]
Whatever.
Let's do it quickly so we can go.
[dramatic music playing]
[Simon] OK.
Deena, Deena!
Find something to wrap her bones!
[ominous music playing]
[gasps]
[woman] You! It's you!
[screaming] It's you!
[gasps]
Your nose…
[Josh] Guys?
I think there's someone in the woods!
[metal chains clinking]
[woman whispers] It's you!
It's you!
We need to hurry!
There, there.
We're sorry.
Did it work?
[breathing shakily]
[dramatic music playing]
[Josh grunts]
- [Simon] No!
- [woman screams] It's you!
- [screaming]
- [Deena] Go, run!
Run! Run!
Go! Come on, go!
Start the car! Go!
- [engine starts]
- [tires screech]
- That was the Camp Nightwing Killer!
- That was a bust!
Yeah, maybe because
it's not like the movies, OK?
It's not as easy as putting bones to rest!
- It should've worked. It always works!
- [Josh] Maybe it's her missing hand.
Who gives a shit? It doesn't matter.
Hey, how do I not die?
[Simon] We! How do we not die!
And I'm looking at you, witch nerd!
- I… I don't know!
- They're not coming for us!
- They're coming for me.
- What?
- I saw her again…
- [woman whispers] It's you.
The witch. She… I disturbed her grave.
- She wants me.
Yeah. Yeah, yeah.
Nightwing ran right by me.
I jumped out his way, it was like
he didn't even see me. He went for her.
Guys, no! Ruby attacked Simon.
Skull Mask came after us at home.
And while you guys were babysitting!
[brakes screeching]
No, he didn't.
Skull Mask didn't care about us.
He wanted this. Sam's blood.
- What the fu…
- Oh!
Yeah! From the crash
when Sam puked period!
It's Jaws, dude!
A shark smelling blood!
[panting] Kate's right!
When we found Skeletor,
he was all sniffy and weird with my shirt
like a perv in a pantie shop!
Yeah, but he came to our house too!
[Kate] Deena…
[Simon] Sam bled on her bones,
now the witch wants more of her blood!
OK, so what do they do in Jaws?
They didn't go skinny-dipping
with the goddamn bait.
She's not bait!
Yeah. She is.
Seriously, if we're right
and they're after her…
let's give these assholes what they want.
[sirens wailing]
[sighs]
[menacing music playing]
[Josh] Alright, we have to decontaminate.
You can't have any of Sam's blood on you.
Well, not much I can do about that.
Deena, you have to get clean too!
Not a single drop, OK?
[Simon] Rub-a-dub-dub time!
[Kate] Hey, wait.
I don't want to go in by myself.
[exhales slowly]
[whispering] Up, up, down, down.
Left, right, left, right, B, A, start.
Holy shit, your shoulder.
It's fine.
OK, well,
fine or not, we s… still need to cover it.
[soft music playing]
[humming]
[Kate] Do you really think
this is going to work?
I do.
[Kate] Josh…
Can you help me?
[dramatic music playing]
[Sam sighs]
This is all my fault.
I'm sorry.
When I went to Sunnyvale,
I ran away from you.
Because you were, like…
this reminder.
I was scared of this.
Of us.
Of me.
And, like, tonight's been the first time
I've felt like myself in…
months.
It's been so long.
I forgot what that… what that felt like.
You make me feel…
like me.
["Sweet Jane" playing]
♪ Anyone who's ever had a heart ♪
- ♪ Wouldn't turn around and break it… ♪
- [Kate] Make sure my back is clean.
Yeah.
- You're gonna have to look at me.
- ♪ And anyone who's ever played a part ♪
♪ Wouldn't turn around and hate it ♪
♪ Sweet Jane… ♪
[breathing heavily]
♪ Sweet Jane ♪
♪ Oh sweet, sweet Jane… ♪
I think you're all good.
♪ You're waiting for Jimmy
Down in the alley ♪
What if…
♪ You're waiting there
For him to come back home… ♪
What if tonight's it for us?
♪ Waiting down on the corner ♪
♪ And thinking of ways
To get back home ♪
♪ Sweet Jane… ♪
[both panting]
♪ Sweet Jane ♪
- ♪ Oh sweet, sweet Jane… ♪
- [Deena panting]
[both panting]
- ♪ Anyone who's ever had... ♪
- [banging]
Did you hear that?
[door creaks open, closes]
No!
[Kate] Calm down.
It was barely first base.
[Simon] Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Did you… all go to pound town?
Me too!
["Firestarter" playing]
Ready?
[Josh] The trap is simple.
We set the bait.
- ♪ Hey, hey! ♪
- ♪ I'm a firestarter… ♪
[Josh] The killers go to the blood.
Then…
Smile, you son of a bitch!
Are you sure you want to do this?
See you on the other side.
[door creaks]
[breathing heavily]
[Sam breathing heavily]
[ominous music playing]
[door bangs]
- [breathes shakily]
- [mop head slops]
[high-pitched shrill]
[menacing music playing]
[breathing heavily]
[Ruby Lane singing]
♪ You always hurt the one you love ♪
♪ The one you shouldn't hurt at all ♪
Dude! She's here! I saw her!
She was…
She was so sexy, but fucking crazy still!
She was doing it!
Following the blood trails!
It's working.
Skull Mask freak, three o'clock.
[Ruby Lane] ♪ You always hurt the one… ♪
Ruby.
♪ …you love ♪
♪ The one you shouldn't hurt… ♪
[Kate] This is so dumb.
If this doesn't work, I will murder you!
[door opens]
[ominous music crescendos]
They're all here.
[ominous music playing]
♪ So if I… ♪
[grunting]
Go, go, go, go, go!
[screaming]
[desperate screaming]
[loud explosion]
[screaming stops]
[Deena sighs]
Come back from that, motherfuckers!
[chuckling]
[Deena and Simon chuckling]
Oh!
[fly buzzing]
[ominous music playing]
Guys?
Holy!
Run! Run!
Go! Go!
[menacing music playing]
[rumbling]
Help me!
- They're coming!
- They're gonna keep coming!
We're fucked!
No, no! We are not fucked!
She's fucked. They're coming for her.
If we put Sam in the hall,
we end this now.
- You're a monster.
- I'm being reasonable!
We can't run anymore.
A bullet won't stop them, fine.
They're really strong.
But we just tried to goddamn explode them,
and that didn't work!
You're suggesting killing her.
I mean, that's not exactly
what she's saying.
Oh, you're on her side?
You'd let us all die to protect her.
Look at this.
OK, all of this.
Dead, dead, dead!
This is the way.
It's the only way.
Sam's gotta go.
Are you kidding me?
[inhales deeply] Kate's right.
I don't want you guys to die for me.
I'm going.
I'm ending this.
No, you're not.
Are you crazy?
No.
No, Sam!
Sam!
Let me go! Let me… Sam!
[breathing heavily]
[grunting]
[Deena] Let me go. Let me go!
Let me… Help me! Help!
[ominous music playing]
[breathing heavily]
[snorts]
[Deena] We're letting her die!
We're killing her!
[sobbing] Please!
[quietly] This is not your fault.
[Deena crying] Please!
Please!
[dramatic music playing]
[snorting]
[breathing heavily]
- [Sam screams]
- [he roars]
- [Sam] What… what… what is going on?
- [Kate] You're not doing this alone.
- [Josh] There's another way.
- [pounding on door]
- C. Berman.
- [pounding continues]
She's the key.
[Sam] Camp Nightwing. Summer of '78.
Group of campers, brutal massacre.
There was one Shadyside survivor,
C. Berman.
"The still traumatized girl claims that
amidst the carnage she saw the witch."
Yeah, just like you.
So, if she survived, I'm pretty sure...
There may be a way for me to live too.
[Kate] I got it! C. Berman!
9006 Brennan Way.
This has gotta be her!
Uh, 155-4747!
[ringing tone]
- No one's answering!
- [voicemail] The Berman residence.
- I'm not home right now.
- I need some help here!
- Please leave a message after the beep.
- No one's there!
Hello, my name is Deena Johnson.
I think you saw the witch.
[Simon grunts]
This shit is not gonna hold!
We need to know how you survived!
Hey! We're being attacked, alright?
There are killers here!
If you're there, please pick up!
Please answer!
- To record a new message, press one.
- Fuck! No!
- [Simon screams]
- [Kate] Help!
- [Kate] Help us!
- [Simon] Help!
[Josh grunts]
- [ringing tone]
- [Sam] She died.
[pounding on door]
She died.
What? No, she's alive.
That's the whole point.
Yeah, she… she survived, but…
but first she died.
[pounding on door]
[Deena] "C. Berman was found
in the woods."
"Her heart had stopped
but local boy performed CPR."
What if this is it?
What if that's how she survived?
Her heart stopped.
She survived by dying.
What is it? The fucking rhyme.
The fucking rhyme!
"She'll take your blood,
she'll take your head!"
- "She'll follow you..."
- "Until you're dead."
- [pounding continues]
- It's just like Kate said. OK?
The witch wants you dead.
So… we kill you.
And then, just like this C. Berman bitch,
we bring you back to life.
What are you saying?
[dramatic music playing]
Fuck it. I'm dying tonight
one way or another.
Let's try to bring me back.
[breathing heavily]
- [Simon] Let's do it!
- [Deena screams]
[ominous music playing]
Let's Timothy this bitch!
[tires screeching]
[soft menacing music]
[clicks pen]
[soft menacing music intensifies]
[menacing music crescendos]
[ominous music playing]
A few months ago, my brother Timothy
had an unfortunate experience
in which he ingested too much
of a certain substance.
He was dead for two minutes.
But…
we got him back!
[Deena] Kate.
It's time for your close-up.
You need to take these in order.
Pile one takes the edge off.
You're gonna feel like
you're being fucked by a unicorn.
Pile two is gonna bring
your core temp way down.
You may feel slightly sick.
You need to take a five-minute interval
between pile two and pile three.
That's really important, OK?
Pile three brings you down and out,
so take that "take five"
or it's all gonna go to shit!
- How many do we have?
- Tons. Like a thousand.
Wait. EpiPens?
Epinephrine, also known as adrenaline.
This is what brings her back.
This is Jesus!
[sighs]
[Deena] Sam's blood marks the spot.
Remember half an hour ago,
when you wanted to murder me?
You don't have to do this. You can leave.
Remember when you decided
to sacrifice yourself for us?
We're ending this together.
Die well, my friend.
We got back door patrol.
[Kate] Hey!
I'll run interference up here.
[ominous drumbeat]
OK, I got stock room.
You take the emergency exit.
Whoa! No, no, no!
Splitting up is not a good idea at all.
But, dude, listen to me.
I know that this is all fucked,
but… we gotta do this.
Kate,
she's a crusher.
She doesn't have time for most people.
I know.
She's being nice
because we're probably gonna die.
No! OK, well…
maybe we're gonna die,
but Kate is not nice.
She sees something in you.
- So?
- So, see that in yourself, dude.
We would not be this far
if it weren't for you.
Now we have to keep those psychos
away from Sam.
So go…
[slaps shoulder] …man up,
and check that exit.
[Sam] Deena.
Deena.
What if we fuck up and just kill me?
What if you can't bring me back?
[sniffles]
Listen to me.
When you left,
I saw it all.
My whole future,
my whole life in Shadyside.
A night shift, a day shift,
and a million empty beer cans,
just like my dad.
No way out.
But tonight, even though we are in hell,
I feel like I have
another chance with you.
And I'm not gonna lose you again.
Because you, and we,
are the way out.
When this is all over,
I am gonna take you on a date.
[both chuckling]
We're going to eat cheeseburgers
and listen to the Pixies,
and make out and have
the best night of our goddamn lives.
But right now, you've got to die.
Now, look at me. Look at me.
I am going to bring you back.
[sighs]
[Sam breathes heavily]
[metal clanging]
[eerie music playing]
[breathing rapidly]
[loud bang]
[Sam mumbling, groaning]
[Sam groaning]
[Sam croaks]
- Swallow it. Swallow it.
- [Sam groaning]
Swallow it. Swallow it.
[Sam groans]
[Ruby Lane singing in distance]
♪ You always hurt ♪
♪ The one you love ♪
♪ The one you shouldn't hurt at all ♪
♪ You always take ♪
[heavy footsteps]
[Deena] Oh, come on!
[panting] Come on!
[Deena panting]
[groaning]
[retching]
I'm so sorry.
- It's OK. It's OK.
- [crying] I'm so sorry.
[whimpering]
- [Sam] Look.
- Huh?
Look. Behind… behind you!
[screams]
Go! Go! Go!
Go!
[Deena] Oh!
[Sam] I need to die. I need to die.
[Deena] I'm gonna figure this out!
[ominous music crescendos]
Go, go!
[panting]
[gasps]
[breathing heavily]
[panicked breathing]
[screams]
[he grunts]
[bread slicer whirring]
[Kate screaming]
[Kate] No! No!
No!
[Kate] No!
Finish it.
[Kate screaming] No! No!
[Kate screams]
[ominous music playing]
[metal clanging]
[footsteps approaching]
- [monster roars]
- [Josh screams]
[panting]
[Deena] Do it! Do it! Do it! Come on!
[Kate screams]
[screaming]
[choking]
[Kate yells]
[Kate choking]
[Kate] No! No! No!
[Kate screaming]
- [bread slicer whirring]
- [Kate screaming]
No! No!
- Go! She's right behind me!
- [Josh gasps]
[Simon panting]
[panting]
[gasping]
[camp killer roars]
[Josh screams]
Come on, Sam!
[suspenseful music playing]
- [Deena] Come on, Sam!
- [Sam gurgles]
[panting, grunts]
[suspenseful music intensifies]
♪ You always… ♪
No! No!
[ominous music intensifies]
[high-pitched ringing]
- [electricity buzzing]
- [Deena sighs]
[Deena] Sam?
[electricity buzzing]
- [electrical thud]
- [Deena gasps]
[Deena gasping]
[Josh breathing shakily]
Josh, Josh! Come help me! Get the pens!
Get the pens!
Help me! Go get the EpiPens!
Come!
[Josh panting]
Come, hurry!
[Deena gasping] Sam!
Here, here, here!
Are you doing it right?
I don't know. I don't know.
[Deena grunts]
I don't think it's working.
It has to work! It has to.
It has to. Sam?
[Deena gasping] Sam?
[ethereal music playing]
[crying] Everyone's dead.
Simon…
Kate…
No. No, Sam!
I will not let you do this.
Come on!
[Deena grunting]
Come on.
Come on, Sam.
One, two, three.
[grunting] Come on, Sam.
Come on. Come on, Sam!
One, two, three, four.
[ethereal music intensifies]
[retching, coughing]
[coughing]
[Deena] It's over.
[gasping] It's over.
[sighs]
[Deena] It's OK.
It's over. It's over.
[Deena gasping]
[Nick] Interview with Deena Johnson.
Sunday, October 2nd, 1994.
Wanna tell me what happened?
We were picking up Sam's prescription.
And the lights went out.
It was pitch black.
I couldn't really see anything.
We ducked behind a counter.
We hid until it was over.
How'd you get that?
I fell on some glass.
[clears throat] Fell on some glass.
[Nick] You had 15 stitches
in your shoulder.
I fell on some glass.
Sam, you look like a ghost.
Like you just came back from the dead.
Shock, I guess.
I'll tell you what the facts tell me.
- [inhales deeply] The junkies...
- Kate and Simon?
They weren't junkies.
They were my friends.
They're to blame for everything.
That feels too easy to me.
But that's the story
this department will go with
unless you can help me
to see it differently.
Another Shadyside tragedy.
An underprivileged overachiever
with bright prospects.
A guy who's been supporting
his family alone since he was 15.
Both succumbing
to the quick cash of drugs.
Fits the narrative, right?
[inhale deeply] Nice and neat.
[Nick] You came here for my help.
I should have listened to you. I'm sorry.
I'm listening now.
But there's nothing else to say.
Do you want your friends
going down for this?
No.
But they're dead.
[indistinct police radio chatter]
[whispers] Hey.
[whistles] Urkel. Help me out?
Oh, OK.
So I'm a bad guy because I'm in here.
Then that makes you a bad guy, too,
little man.
[coughs]
Let's go.
[whispers] I owe you.
- [coughs]
- Anything comes to you, call me.
[prisoner sighs]
[Nick scoffs]
Prodigal son returns.
Man, you ain't my family.
[woman] Sam!
Samantha!
[Deena] So I guess I'll…
see you tomorrow?
[sighs]
No.
See you tonight.
[mother] Come on!
[female reporter 1]
More death in Shadyside.
A drug-fueled night of violence
leaves a trail of bodies.
Melissa, give us a recap.
[female reporter 2] There are
three dead at East Union Medical…
[Deena] I, uh… I wanted…
I wanted to give you this the other day.
- But, uh...
- [Sam] What is this?
Um…
- A mixtape?
- Yeah.
But you don't have to open it right now.
I knew it.
["Hey" playing over stereo]
♪ Hey! Been trying to meet you ♪
♪ Mmm-mmm-mmm ♪
♪ Hey! Must be a devil between us ♪
♪ Or whores in my head ♪
♪ Whores at the door ♪
♪ Whore in my bed ♪
- ♪ But hey! ♪
- [doorbell rings]
♪ Where have you been? ♪
[doorbell rings]
♪ If you go… ♪
[Deena] Josh, someone's at the door!
Josh!
- [Josh] What?
- [Deena gasps]
You ordered dinner?
Yeah, it's not a big deal.
Just some pizza.
[chuckles]
[Josh] Ah! Stop! Don't be weird!
[telephone ringing]
Hello?
Alright. Listen, asshole.
Don't call here...
[woman] You're still alive!
[ominous music playing]
Who is this?
- [whispering voice echoes] Sam…
- [woman] You called me.
Wanted to know how I survived
the Camp Nightwing Massacre.
C. Berman.
[C. Berman] Did you touch the bones?
Did you see her face?
- No. It's over.
- [C. Berman] Over?
Yeah, but, uh…
thanks for your prompt reply.
- [C. Berman] It's not over.
- [whispering voice] Sam…
[C. Berman] It's never over.
We ended it.
We stopped the killers.
[C. Berman] But you haven't stopped her.
You can't.
She makes the rules.
[ominous music playing]
Who?
[C. Berman] The witch.
[ominous music plays]
[C. Berman] She'll do whatever it takes.
[ritualistic chanting]
[C. Berman] You're not safe.
She'll find a way.
[ritualistic singing intensifies]
[C. Berman] She'll come for you.
[gasps, relieved sigh]
Sam.
[fly buzzing]
[gasps]
[chat beeping]
["The Day I Tried To Live"
playing over stereo]
♪ And gave it to the rich, yeah ♪
♪ The day I tried to win ♪
♪ I dangled from the power lines ♪
♪ And let the martyrs stretch, yeah ♪
♪ Singing one more time around
Might do it ♪
♪ Singing one more time around… ♪
[music fades]
- [dramatic music playing]
- [keyboard clicking]
[chat beeping]
[dramatic music stops]
["The Day I Tried To Live" continues]
♪ …the ones inside your head ♪
[loud banging upstairs]
[smashing]
[Deena screaming]
[Deena] Stop it! Get off!
Sam! Sam!
- [Sam grunting]
- Stop! Stop!
- [Deena screaming]
Sam!
Don't! It's me!
[Sam roars]
It's me! It's me!
["The Day I Tried To Live"
playing over stereo]
[ominous music playing]
[Deena gasping]
[ominous music intensifies]
[Sam grunting, roars]
What the…
[Sam grunting]
Sam's not feeling like herself.
We have to get her back.
I'm going to get you back.
[grunting]
[roars]
[rock music playing]
[ominous drumbeat]
[C. Berman] The witch…
The town curse…
I thought there was a way to end it.
But now I know
there is no end.
This is July 12th.
Summer of 1978.
The first day of camp.
A week later…
my sister was dead.
["School's Out" playing]
♪ School's out for summer… ♪
- [cheering]
- [groaning]
♪ School's out forever… ♪
[screams]
[screaming]
♪ School's out… ♪
- [explosion]
- [school bell rings]
[ominous drumbeat]
[screaming]
["More Human Than Human" playing]
♪ Yeah, I am the astro creep ♪
♪ A demolition style
Hell American freak, yeah ♪
♪ I am the crawling dead ♪
♪ A phantom in a box
Shadow in your head ♪
♪ Say acid suicide ♪
♪ Freedom of the blast
Read the fucker lies, yeah ♪
♪ Scratch off the broken skin ♪
♪ Tear into my heart
Make me do it again, yeah ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ More human than human ♪
♪ Yeah, I am the jigsaw man ♪
♪ I turn the world around
With a skeleton hand, say ♪
♪ I am electric head ♪
♪ A cannibal core
A television said, yeah ♪
♪ Do not victimize ♪
♪ Read the motherfucker
Psychoholic lies, yeah ♪
♪ Into a psychic war ♪
♪ I tear my soul apart
And I eat it some more, yeah ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ More human than human ♪
♪ Yeah, I am the ripper man ♪
♪ A locomotion mind
Love American style, yeah ♪
♪ I am the nexus one ♪
♪ I want more life fucker
I ain't done, yeah ♪
♪ More human than human ♪
[suspenseful music playing]