(jazzy music)
♪ Oh yeah
♪ Right here, baby
♪ Walk nasty
♪ Oh yeah
♪ Right here, baby
♪ Walk nasty
- So, Craig, what makes you think you need
to see a therapist?
- I'm as confused as an infant at a topless bar.
- Okay.
Okay.
What seems to be the source of all this confusion?
- Well, I know you might not get this, dude,
but I'm having a hard time with the babes.
- Women, yeah, that's very common.
You have a difficult time
relating with women, understanding them?
- You see, Doctor, I understand them,
they just can't understand me.
- Craig, I'm gonna cut to the chase right here.
Are you schizophrenic?
- No, I'm a standup comedian.
(jazzy music)
- Craig, you obviously create these characters
because you're uncomfortable with who you are.
- You're very good.
- Thank you.
(jazzy music)
- Now, how long have you been behaving this way?
- My entire life.
[Craig] I grew up with my sister,
my mother and my grandmother.
[Craig] There weren't exactly a lot of G.I. Joes around,
so I had to come up with unusual ways to entertain myself.
- Hey Suzie, hey Suzie!
Hey, Suzie, Suzie look, who am I?
- Get out you creep.
- Ruh-roh.
- Craig, give me those.
- I'm Astro Jetson.
- I said get out.
- Hey, hey Mom, hey Mom, Mom look, who am I?
- Not now, sweetie, I'm practicing.
- I'm the fly.
- Oh, precious (kisses)
Later, sweetie.
- Hey Nana, Nana, look, Nana, who am I?
I'll get you my little pretty, and your little dog, too.
- Come back in a little while, sweetie, I'm a tad busy now.
- I'm the Wicked Witch of the West.
- I'm as damp as a dishrag, what are you wearing?
- Craig, I wanna try and experiment here.
Just for once I'd like you to drop all these facades
and concentrate on just being you.
- Yeah, but that's the problem,
people don't want me to be me.
(jazzy music)
- Here we're going to explore your life, not your act.
- Well, you don't understand, my life is my act.
- Alright, then let's hear your act.
- Ladies and gentlemen here he is, the one, the only!
- [Announcer] Craig Shoemaker!
(audience cheers and applauds)
- Thank you, good to be here.
Woo!
Thank you, dang.
Alright.
(audience applauding)
You guys sound great, thank you.
Hey, would ye-.
Woo!
(audience applauding)
I could tell.
You're drunk, aren't you?
Oh, yeah.
I can tell, you get drunk, you become the woo people.
That alcohol hits that level,
"Woo!"
(audience laughing)
I'm fucked up.
It's the woo people.
That's a strange word, that word, woo,
means the same thing in any language.
Go anywhere, go over to China,
"Woo!"
"I'm fucked up."
(audience laughing)
So friendly, I was working in Brooklyn, New York,
not so friendly there.
They said, "Please welcome to comedy, Mr. Craig Shoemaker"
and they're all sitting there,
"Yo, hey, who is this asshole over here?"
"Hey, comedian, what are you doing?"
"Hey come on, make me laugh."
I said, "Listen, lady, what's your problem?"
"I'm doing my show up here, relax, will you?"
Renting' a car while I'm here.
I love renting cars,
they always give you a nice shiny car, it's great.
But they Armor All the seats, though.
It makes no sense.
You ever sit on Armor Alled seats?
Come around a corner, it's like, "Whoa!"
(audience laughs)
Rented a car once called the Astrovan by Chevrolet.
They're running out of names for cars.
It's named after The Jetson's dog.
It's a computerized car, it talks back,
you something wrong, this voice comes on,
(imitating Astro)
"You're lights are on, your lights are on."
(audience laughing)
You run out of gas, "Ruh-roh."
(imitates car engine)
They have other cartoon cars coming out this year:
The Droopy the Dogmobile will be out real soon.
"Oh boy, oh boy."
"I'm not gonna make it up that hill, you bastard."
(audience laughing)
Flew here on Southwest Airlines.
Ever fly that shit box airline?
(audience cheering)
(scoffs) Man.
I went up to the counter at the airport,
"How much do I owe you?!"
"Oh, chip it for gas."
"That'll be all right."
"If you wanna get out, pull the cord."
(audience laughing)
They always have a bird about that seat-back law,
they want it up for safety precautions.
You know, like there's this big difference
between this and this right here.
(audience laughing)
Boy, I'm living on the edge right now baby.
Check it out, I'm a man of danger. (chuckles)
Whoop, here she comes, safe and secure.
(audience laughing)
Some of these planes, the meat they give you,
I had this meat the other day on an airline,
I don't know what it was, I dropped it on my lap,
it started humping my leg.
(audience laughing)
Oh, you girls like that over there.
I saw you looking.
(audience cheering)
Come on, give me a dollar.
I just saw "Showgirls" baby, I got all the moves.
(audience cheering)
Oh, yeah.
(audience laughing)
Don't you laugh at me.
I'm the Lovemaster, baby.
(audience cheering)
Don't you laugh at the Lovemaster, yeah,
I could poke your eye out from right here, baby.
Yeah, come on, you hear that ringing?
That's a call on the bone phone, baby.
(audience laughing)
Yeah, answer the damn thing,
I ain't got call waiting, baby, I'm the Lovemaster.
Master of love, baby.
- What the hell was that?
- [Craig] It's the Lovemaster.
Now, him, the girls go crazy for.
(audience applauding)
Come on up here and walk nasty for me, baby.
Come climb the magic beanstalk.
(audience laughing)
Yeah, fee, fi, fo, fum,
lay on down and I'll make you,
you know what I'm gonna do for you, baby.
I'll love you so good, baby, you'll need an airbag.
(audience applauding)
Yeah, what you laughing at back there?
I'll stir your drink from right here.
(audience laughing)
Yeah, I got a drink, it's a Penis Colossus.
That's right, baby.
I'm the Lovemaster, master of love.
Yeah, I'm looking at you, baby.
Come on, tell Pinocchio a lie.
(audience laughing)
Yeah.
(raises pitch of voice) Oh, my God!
Where did that come from?
I am so sorry, just channeled through me.
Oh my God, a Penis Colossus, that was so gross.
(audience laughing)
Oh, my God, what a visual.
I'm sorry, it's gone now. (Craig chuckles)
Erase, erase, erase.
(deepens voice) Yeah, I'm back baby.
Yeah, don't worry we'll have safe sex,
go get me a Hefty Bag.
(audience laughs)
Yeah, I'll hit your G-spot,
H, I, J, K, L, M, N, O, P-spot,
I'll cover the whole damn alphabet, baby.
Come on up here and free Willy, get your ass up here.
Yeah, you don't look too well,
you need a shot of penis-cillin,
that's what you need, baby, yeah.
Don't you worry, yeah, I'm only two inches.
Yeah, from the ground!
(audience laughs)
Yeah, you believe in fairy tales?
Well, Puff the Magic Dragon, baby.
(audience laughs)
Ew!
I am sorry.
Puffy's gone now.
Erase, erase, erase.
(audience laughs)
Man, there's some people staring at me right now.
What the hell just happened to him?
Who's this Lovemaster, looks like John Boy
if you ask me. (Craig chuckles)
People tell me I look like John Boy all the time.
(audience laughs)
(audience cheers and claps)
"Hey, he does with the mole on!"
Yeah, you don't want John Boy, do you, baby?
Yeah, you're looking at Walton's Mountain,
that's what you-
(audience laughs)
Yeah, let's play connect the dot.
Sorry. (Craig chuckles)
Erase, erase.
(audience laughs)
Who's this right here, who's this?
Marsha Clark.
(audience laughs)
I checked that trial out, she's sexy, isn't she?
She's got those skirts on, I was,
yeah, I got your side bar right here, baby.
Yeah, come on, Marsha let me introduce you
to Johnnie Cochran.
(audience laughs)
Yeah, come on, baby.
Yeah.
I've got a hung jury waiting for you right here, baby, yeah.
Keep that big mouth open, I'll give you the gag order, baby.
Yeah, come on, Marsha, say O.J.
Yeah, you won't make it to the J, baby.
(audience laughs)
(Craig chuckles)
(raises voice pitch) I'm sorry.
Double erase.
(audience laughs)
Yeah, no.
I have no clue who I am anymore.
My therapist charges me a group rate.
(audience laughs)
I've been in therapy for a long time.
They always go back in your history
and they find out when it all went wrong.
- When did it all go wrong?
- It's when my mother belly danced
at high school graduation party.
- You're kidding.
- I swear.
She bought us a keg, she comes down the steps
with finger cymbals and bells.
- I've got a little treat for you and your friends.
- My friends are on the keg going, "Whew!"
"I'm fucked up and your old lady looks good!"
(audience laughs)
That's a true story.
I love my mother,
my mother raised us all by herself,
I'm proud of her for that, single mother.
Anyone else raised by a single mother?
(audience cheers) A few people, all right.
(audience claps)
I'm proud of my mother, that's right.
She had it tough, she had to play both roles,
you know, she'd come home from work,
"Wait 'til your father gets home."
(deepens voice) "I'm here."
(audience laughs)
I had no idea who's gonna greet me everyday.
It's like wash the dishes, pull my finger.
(audience laughs)
50/50 shot.
My mom was cool
and my mom did everything a dad would have done, you know?
Taught me how to play ball,
ended up throwing like this.
(audience laughs)
I was 19 till I figured out I'm right-handed.
My mother gave me my driving instructions too, that's right.
I can't drive worth a shit.
But I can change all my clothes at a stoplight.
(audience laughs)
Yeah, and I'm, that's right.
And I'm not afraid to cry
to get out of a traffic ticket either.
A cop pulls me over. (Craig cries)
Please don't give me a ticket,
I'm having a bad week, I'm bloating.
(audience laughs)
Hand-me-downs are a pain the ass in an all female household.
(mother knocks)
- Come on out, honey.
- [Craig] No, no way!
- Look, there is nothing wrong with hand-me-downs.
I wore hand-me-downs.
- [Craig] No, they'll kill me.
- Look, if your father would send me the child support,
I could buy you new things, but Craig,
I am doing the best I can.
(slow music)
What's the problem, you look adorable.
(audience laughs)
- Nothing like the first day of school in a halter top.
And they had those pants with the zipper in the back.
You know?
I mean, Mommy, which way do I tinkle?
(audience laughs)
(deepens voice) Hey, you just bend it on back there,
that's all you do, baby.
(audience laughs)
Yeah, look like a water fountain right there, yeah.
Come on Mommy, throw me a quarter.
(audience laughs)
(Craig chuckles)
(raises voice pitch) Gross.
Erase, erase.
(audience laughs)
Sex talk is different though when Mom gives it to you.
You know, my friends they would hear from their fathers
about the bees going
around flower to flower pollinating making new flowers.
What I heard from my mother was "All bees-
- Are scum.
(audience laughs)
Don't you laugh at that, baby.
Yeah, I'll come sting your ass, baby.
Big old king bee, boom, you're done.
(audience laughs)
Erase. Erase.
Here's something my mom used to tell me when I was a kid.
My mother used to say,
"Well, you're just gonna have to be our little man
of the house."
Man of the house?
I'm six-years-old,
I'm built like Barney Fife from Mayberry.
I'm trying to order my sisters around.
All right, all right, all right.
(audience cheers)
Somebody in here made a big old mess in the kitchen.
(audience laughs)
Now I came out here to have a cookie,
and there's dishes in the sink here little lady,
who's gonna clean them up, not me.
You better look out, look out!
These things are certified lethal weapons.
(audience cheers)
Thank you.
Man, you guys are into Barney there, aren't you?
I'll do Barney all night to kiss your ass, I don't care.
(imitates Barney) Come here baby, walk nasty
for the real Lovemaster.
Yeah, by God the bullet you're looking for.
This table's so young, you have no clue
who I'm doing right now do you?
They're looking at me, Barney, that doesn't sound
like the dinosaur, I'm sorry.
(audience laughs)
♪ I love you you love me
Now we're bonding, there you go.
Who's the youngest one over here, who's the youngest one?
You right there?
What year were you born?
- [Audience Member] 74.
- 74?
Ow, that hurt, damn that's young.
You don't even have a, "Where were you when?"
Some of us have a, "Where were you when Kennedy was shot?"
"Where were you when they landed on the moon?"
What do you have, "Where were you when Wham broke up?"
(audience laughs)
[Craig] That's young right there.
Damn, how old are you?
- [Audience Member] 21.
- 21, oh, me too.
(audience laughs)
Folded in half.
(deepens voice) Yeah, if you're good
I'll show you 42 there baby, yeah, little square root.
Sorry.
Erase, erase.
That's so cool, you know who Barney Fife is,
you have no clue, right?
Mr. Furley from "Three's Company" does that ring a bell?
Chrissy, the rent's due.
(audience laughs)
He's the same guy.
Barney Fife.
Tell me Barney wasn't wired on some sort of drug.
"Yeah, we're gonna, melt pile and do some cocaine!"
(Craig sniffs)
"And then we'll come down and smoke some Opie."
(audience laughs)
There were drugs in Mayberry, I'm telling you.
Floyd the barber was the dealer, I'm convinced.
(audience laughs)
They all hung out in that barber shop
and what drug was Floyd on?
(Craig mocks stuttering)
"Here try some of this Andy."
(audience laughs)
"Yeah, it'll get you high as a kite."
"Oh, yes, I'm toasted, Andy."
(Craig sniffs) "Bullshit."
"Well, that stuff you sold me was Maalox."
(audience laughs)
I do the whole cast of Mayberry.
A lot of free time as a kid.
- [Audience Member] Aunt Bee.
Aunt Bee?
"Andy, Andy, there are seeds in my marijuana, Andy."
Remember that episode?
(audience laughs)
Aunt Bee made those pot brownies.
"Mmm, that's a good brownie, Aunt Bee."
"Mm-mm, that's a good brownie right there."
(audience claps)
"Make some more of them things."
That was Matlock.
(audience laughs)
We got a thing going here.
Mayberry, man, they were all wasted in Mayberry.
Gomer Pyle, what the hell was he on?
Quaaludes if you ask me.
(audience laughs)
That's a drug in the 70's.
(Craig chuckles)
Gomer always had that singing voice
that had nothing to do with the show.
"Well, golly."
♪ Oh my papa
(audience laughs)
I like Barney the most, though,
Barney's my main man growing up,
I identify with Barney, right?
- So, Barney Fife, Barney Fife was your role model?
- I was built like Barney.
In high school I was five foot one, 92 pounds.
It was frightening.
Yo, Stiney, Stiney, hey, who am I?
(kid laughs)
That's damn good weed.
- That's funny, Shoe.
- Okay who am I now?
Mia, want prom date?
I'm Nicky no neck.
- Shoey
- [Craig] Can't touch my penis.
- Me what you get when cousins marry.
- It's Nate on the (indistinct).
- What?
- Hey, funny boy.
- I was like a wedgie waiting to happen.
- No, Nicky, come on, it's new underwear.
(students laugh)
- C'mon, Nicky.
[Craig] No!
(students laughing)
- [Craig] Okay, put me down. (clothes ripping)
Real funny guys.
(students laughing)
Come on I'm begging, guys.
Come on, put me down.
(audience cheer and laugh)
- Alright get it over with.
I was hyper like Barney from all that sugar I consumed.
I used to run to the store with all my allowance,
and get Penny candy.
Y'all remember Penny candy, remember that?
Now she's staring at me. (Craig chuckles)
What was it a buck
when you guys were growing up or something?
Remember Pixie Sticks, y'all had those right?
Pixie Sticks.
(audience cheers)
Right?
Diabetes in a straw, that was real healthy.
Some of the packaging they gave us.
What about that stuff on the calculator paper,
did you guys have that candy round here?
Those buttons, or dots, what was the deal?
They spot welded it to the paper,
I'm like a Gopher trying to eat this stuff.
(audience laughs)
(Craig spits)
I think I got a piece of candy that time.
(audience laughs)
What's this, for kids with a fiber problem?
Who invents these things?
Like the PEZ dispenser,
whoever came up with this must have been drunk on his ass.
Imagine just sitting around a corporate table,
"Any new ideas?"
"Alright, here's my idea."
"Okay, you got a big plastic head
with a thyroid problem."
"Now follow me."
"You pull it back, brick pops out of his throat."
"No arms, no legs, just a spine."
(audience laughs)
"It'll sell."
"We'll call it PEZ."
"Woo!"
(audience cheers)
"I'm fucked up."
Jawbreakers, did you eat those things, jawbreakers?
How do you eat something
that tells you the damage it's going to do to your body?
Here have a clogged colon while you're at it.
(audience laughs)
Wax candies and wax lips,
what in the hell was this?
I eat this, I'm shitting candles for three weeks.
I put it a wick in the toilet, I got a shrine.
(audience laughs)
Having services in my bathroom.
Some of the cereal we ate,
Captain Crunch, oh man.
(audience cheers)
I don't know how you ate that,
that was the hardest, sharpest cereal known to children.
They should call it Captain Fiberglass, this crap.
You had to soak it for four hours
before you could eat it safely,
otherwise I'd been injured walking round the neighborhood,
"I just had Captain Crunch this morning."
"That son of a bitch just peeled the roof off of my mouth."
"I got Bandaids on my tonsils."
"I think the toy was softer."
"I'm gonna shoot that son of a bitch."
Hey, nothing like a sugar buzz when your a kid though right?
Yeah, as adults we have a cappuccino in the morning,
coffees, kids you get the sugar,
I get a big bowl every morning,
big Jethro Bodine bowl, put in front me.
"Beverly Hillbillies," show in the 60s.
(audience laughs)
I filled it up with Cheerios and milk,
5 inches of sugar on top,
I would eat a layer, if I didn't see sugar I'd panic,
took a bowl of sugar, more sugar on top.
Layer, by layer, you take it down to the best part.
Oh, remember that?
That glucose quicksand that's sunk to the bottom?
(audience cheers)
Oh, that's a sugar high waiting to-
Fried my head for the week.
Few bowls of that I'm gone,
I'm walking round the neighborhood
like Reverend Jim from "Taxi,"
(Craig mimics stuttering)
"I'm cuckoo for Cocoa Puffs!"
"Cuckoo for Cocoa Puffs!"
They put so much money
into selling kids sugar when we were kids,
they actually had Pavarotti singing for cereal,
remember that commercial?
♪ No more Rice Krispies
♪ Run out of Rice Krispies
♪ My tears will not stop
♪ 'Til I hear snap or crackle
(audience cheers)
Oh stop!
Oh sto- Oh I feel the love I really do.
Oh, I'm embarrassed.
Oh, group erase.
(audience laughs)
Biggest applause is when I sing, it's a comedy show.
Now you're like my grandmother,
it's my grandmother's favorite part of my act.
She sits there, "I'm telling ya,
you should've been a singer, not a comedian."
"I don't like that Lovemaster, that you do."
Oh come on granny.
(audience laughs)
Yeah, you love the Lovemaster don't you granny,
come on, go walk nasty for me baby, yeah.
Get rid of that cane, I got something
for you to hold onto baby.
(audience cheers)
Yeah.
Come on granny, grab onto the guard rail.
Yeah, I'm as stiff as your hairspray, baby.
Yeah, you've fallen but you can't get up.
Ew!
That's his grandmother!
Don't encourage him.
(audience laughs)
That's it I swear, Jurassic erase.
(audience cheers)
I come from a weird family, originally.
(audience laughs)
Oh, shut up.
Some of you people, who are you, The Cleavers?
(audience laughs)
Show in the 50s.
I have a weird ethnic background:
part German, part Irish, part American Indian.
(Craig chuckles) No drinking in our family.
(audience laughs)
Came right out of the womb, "Woo!"
(audience cheers)
"I'm already fucked up."
Yeah, they cut the chord and found an olive.
(audience laughs)
It's a true story my first breathe was at 2.3.
Whole family's nuts.
I'm the normal one.
My grandmother, I'm not kidding you,
smokes and grows pot.
Now I quit smoking pot, it's kind of strange
when you quit before your grandmother does.
I'd visit her she gives me peer pressure.
(audience laughs)
"Come on lighten up will you?"
"Have a joint with your grandmother."
(audience laughs)
"What a pussy."
- Nanna I- I don't know what to do.
No one respects me the way I am.
- Sweetie, hold it up a little higher.
[Nanna] Stand on your tip toes,
That's good.
Now just hold it until Merv is over.
- I hate being puny.
- Oh that's nonsense, look at that Tommy Jones.
[Nanna] Who's he kidding?
He's short as hell, he wears heels like stilts,
[Nanna] and he stuffs his drawers with socks.
Hey you could be a singer, you've got a beautiful voice.
You could be on Merv.
- But Nanna, I don't know how to sing.
- Sure you do, you're very talented.
Come on, one song for your only grandma.
I could be dead by Tuesday.
- Okay.
[Craig] Nanna, who am I?
(Craig sings) - [Grandma] No, no,no.
Sing as you, don't be scared.
Be yourself for God's sake.
♪ Chances
♪ are
- Maybe not.
(audience laughs)
- [Craig] That's my grandmother.
You haven't lived 'til you've seen
your granny hoeing weed in the backyard.
(audience laughs)
"Oh, we got a bumper crop this year."
"I'm telling you, this shit will fuck you up."
(audience laughs)
"I'm as high as five people right now."
"Good to see all my grandchildren."
Well, it's just me Nanna.
(audience laughs)
"I'm stoned."
Hey Nanna, aren't you afraid
of the cops finding out about this?
"Fuck 'em."
(audience cheers)
"To hell with them."
"I tell them I've got glaucoma."
(audience laughs)
That's a true story.
Man, it's hot in here damn.
(audience cheers)
Yeah, I got a coat rack right there for you baby.
Yeah, say something nasty, I'll hang yours too baby.
Yeah, you want your wish, you gotta rub the lamp.
(audience cheers)
Yeah.
Come on Olga, get on the balance beam.
(audience laughs)
Russian gymnast in the 70s.
Oh yeah baby, I work out once a year.
(audience laughs)
January 2nd, when I joined a new club.
That's the last day they see me.
You've ever see these guys, they work out 2 months,
they get all these muscles,
but no flexibility, all walk around,
"Hey!"
(audience laughs)
"Hey, somebody get my dick for me, help me out."
"Come on man, I gotta pee, help me."
(audience laughs)
Hope none of those guys are here tonight.
(Craig chuckles)
"I'll show you flexible, how was that?"
(audience laughs)
And they do that posing thing, like that's attractive.
Who the hell you gonna meet like that?
"Excuse me, honey."
(audience laughs)
Oo, I want you vein man.
Can't work out in front of women,
ladies you look to good when you work out.
Yeah, you come in in those outfits,
you know those skin on sausage pants you all wear?
(audience cheers)
Yeah, when you get on those machines,
you look sexy on those machines.
This is the most distracting machine though ladies.
You know the one I'm talking about.
Yeah, don't get on this one anymore in front of me.
(audience cheers)
I live in front of this machine.
I have season tickets at the lat thing along the way.
I'm over there, "Oh my God!"
(audience laughs)
"Talk to me!"
This is taking fitness too far.
What do you need these muscles for?
"Honey you can't get that jar cap open?"
(pop)
"No problem!"
(audience laughs and cheers)
"I've got my new muscles."
(audience cheers)
"I can change that spare tire."
Tell you what ladies,
I found out the hard way what you need those muscles for.
Yeah, you don't want the guy going down there,
you put the clamp vice on his head.
(audience cheers)
Right, guys?
I'm down there, "Okay, you can let go now."
"Please, I can't hear the stereo anymore."
(audience laughs)
"Come on, we'll just kiss, I swear to God."
"You'll crack my head like a fucking walnut, please."
(audience laughs)
"Come on, if I was coal you'd make a diamond
out of me, stop it."
That's a true story.
My head just came back to normal this week.
Last week, I'm walking around,
"Just trying to give her some pleasure."
(audience laughs)
This is my favorite,
when you get on this machine, right?
Oh yeah.
I'm the stair master baby.
I'm the master and I'm staring.
- [Therapist] Craig, this is not a club
and I am not your fan.
Frankly, the Lovemaster frightens me.
- [Therapist] He's at the root of your problems Craig.
And I wanna know exactly where this guy is coming from.
- Yeah, from way down under baby.
- Are you through?
- Oh, sorry.
Erase, erase, erase, erase.
- Stop it!
- I wanna know when and where the Lovemaster began.
- It was 1990, I was watching television
with an old friend of mine, Debbie Mebbit.
[Craig] We'd known each other since high school,
but we'd always been buddies,
and I wanted more than that, you know.
[Craig] Geeze, look at the body on him.
Deb.
Who do you thinks hotter,
the "Solar Flex" guy or the "Easy Glide" guy?
- Oh the "Easy Glide" guy, his ass should be bronze.
- He didn't get that ass on "Easy Glide,"
believe me, he's a model.
- I don't care how he got it, I just know I like it.
- Hey, Deb.
What about me?
- What about you?
- Ever think about my ass?
(Debbie laughs)
- What are you saying, Shoe?
- What, what, what do you-
what do you think of my ass?
- I don't know, it's okay.
- You wanna see it?
- Would you stop.
- Oh Deb, haven't you ever wondered,
you know, what it would be like if,
you know,
you and me?
- No.
No, a- absolutely not.
- Loser table for one, loser table for one.
(audience laughs)
- Oh come on, Deb.
Let's just do it alright?
You and me right here, right now.
Lets ride the rodeo, shake the sheets,
take a ride on the Matterhorn.
I want you, you want me, lets just get it over with.
- What makes you think I want you?
- Oh, well the way your sucking on that water bottle,
you're checking out "Easy Glide's" ass.
- You started it with the, with the "Solar Flex" guy.
- Lets just do it.
- No.
We can't.
- Why not?
- Shoe,
I'm gay.
- You're a lesbo?
- Yep, yeah, yeah, that's right,
I'm, I'm a lesbo.
A vagitarian,
a lesbian,
a dyke.
A canyon yodeling, friend of Martinez.
- Wow, you're a lesbian.
All these years I had no idea.
- Well, well it's true so, there you have it.
You and I can't have sex.
- What about Donya?
- What about you and Donya getting it on while I watch?
- You're sick.
- I'm gonna call her.
- No, no!
- Why not?
- I-
I'm telling you, she's not my type.
I need a, I need a, I need a big,
big, earthy, Helga type girl, you know,
with, with hair on her back, and combat boots.
- What about Nina? Nina flips both ways.
- Big Nina from high school?
- Yeah, she was the shot putter on the men's team.
Jesus how big do you want?
What is her number?
- No, Shoe stop!
I'm not gay.
- You're not?
- No.
I was hoping it would turn you off.
- Why would you wanna do that?
- Oh, Shoe.
You're my buddy, my pal.
You're my friend I watch old movies
with when I don't have a date.
I can't have sex with you.
- You can't?
- You're too nice.
I need someone who's, a little more mysterious,
who's got a little bit of a edge to him,
little bit of nastiness.
- You mean an asshole?
- Exactly, that is the type of guy I go for.
- I'm mysterious.
I'm definitely mysterious.
I'm edgy.
And I'm hot.
I'm a sexy guy.
Yeah!
Walk edgy for the sexy guy.
Yeah, I do mysterious, mystery man.
Shake it mama for the mystery guy.
Mystery man, sex guy.
Master of sex.
Come on, give me a little, walking nasty for me.
Give it up for the, for the love mystery man, edgy guy.
Shake it mama, for the, for the...
Nasty guy.
The love guy.
Walk as bad as you nastily can myst-
Mystery.
Oh yeah.
(deepens voice) Oh yeah.
Oh walk nasty for the love guy.
Oh, oh.
Walk nasty for
the Lovemaster.
Oh yeah, I got what you want right here, baby.
Oh yeah.
I need some water, can you guys get me some water?
You guys got some?
- [Audience Member] Right here.
- No, no ice, I need some with no ice.
Oh she bringing me some?
Okay, just lay it right there baby.
(audience laughs)
Yeah, you better watch that smile, you could chip a tooth.
Yeah, that's right baby, yeah.
(audience cheers) Thank you baby.
Don't you turn around, you'll get a black eye there, baby.
That's me tapping you on the shoulder right now.
(audience laughs)
Yeah, go ahead leave the room,
I'll bend it around the corner there baby.
Yeah, lemme get that door for you back there, baby.
Yeah, (Craig chuckles)
These waitresses, they hate me here.
They all go back to the bar and they talk about me.
They're back there, "I bet you he's a fucking needle dick."
(audience laughs)
"Mr. Lovemaster, if he wants a drink
have him send his big dick back here."
(audience cheers)
I heard you, baby.
Yeah, I recorded it on the dickterphone.
(audience cheers)
Yeah, that's right baby. (Craig laughs)
Lovemaster doesn't work in real life,
believe me I've tried it.
I went to a dance club the other day,
I was like, "Come on baby dance with the Lovemaster."
She looks at me, "Fuck you, Forest Gump!"
(audience laughs)
Come back, Jenny.
(audience cheers)
Jenny.
I just wanna dance.
(audience laughs)
That's a true story.
Should've known she wasn't looking at me,
I was by myself, women will never look
when you're by yourself at a bar.
For some reason, if I'm with a date,
every women in the place wants me.
Like, you walk in with a date, right guys?
You with a date, you look around the room,
all the women are going, mmmm.
(audience cheers)
That's a true story.
(audience laughs)
If I go to bars, I go to piano bars.
I like piano, we like piano bars?
(audience cheers) Aren't they fun?
I go with my grandmother to piano bars.
I think it's great all the elderly people
surround the piano, know all the words
to all the old songs, sit there arm in arm,
swaying back and forth.
♪ You are my sunshine, my only sunshine. ♪
What the hell am I gonna sing
when I'm 89 sitting around a piano?
♪ Oh yeah whip it, whip it good. ♪
(audience laughs)
♪ Highway to hell!
Woo!
It's hammer time.
(audience laughs)
Those are our oldies.
Well maybe not your oldies.
You never had to endure "Muskrat Love."
On 8-Track.
That's a device in the 70s.
(audience laughs)
Put a little matchbook in there, for your skips.
- [Audience Member] Yeah!
You're dating yourselves.
Hey speaking of "Highway to Hell,"
how many of you know the group AC/DC?
Do you know the group AC/DC?
(audience cheers)
Oh cool, a lot of you great.
Great band.
Now, Brian, the lead singer, is an old friend of mine,
he actually came to my wedding, I was married,
and he gets up and he sings with the band.
- From AC/DC Brian Johnson, come on up.
(audience cheering)
(rock music)
(Brian sings)
(band plays)
(band sings in unison)
- But then he tries to blend in
by doing wedding tunes,
which sounds funny coming out of AC/DC.
♪ You put your right foot in
♪ And your left foot out
♪ Put your big titties in
♪ And your big titties out
(audience laughs)
See all my old aunts and uncles going,
"Oh my God."
"What did he say?"
Except my grandmother,
she goes up to him,
"You look like you party."
(audience laughs)
"How would you like a big fat doobie?"
"Let me give you a shotgun."
(audience laughs)
They're dating now.
I can't believe the wedding gifts
you get when you get married.
Women have a conspiracy going here, don't you ladies?
It's called registering, that's right.
You never register with the guys around,
and you never register like
Nevada Bob's Golf Shop, that doesn't happen.
Instead it's for all these foo foo gifts,
and what an acting job I had to do opening up these things
in front of people,
I open it up, "Woo, a bowl!"
(audience laughs)
"You don't know how much I have wanted a fucking bowl."
"Wow! Hey, you can mix stuff in there!"
19 bowls for our wedding, half of them filled
with something women go nuts for.
Potpourri.
Dead leaves in a bowl.
I said, "I'll rake the lawn if that makes you happy."
(audience laughs)
She goes nuts for this stuff,
"Oh potpourri, oh, put it
in the bathroom it'll smell so nice."
I said, "Honey, I've got news for you."
"When I go, nothing smells nice."
And nothing's gonna help called potpourri.
Yeah, you need something called,
"cuts through shit", that's what you need not potpourri.
(audience cheers)
Smells like I took a dump in the woods.
When a guy goes, a pine cone doesn't help.
Cause when a guy gets in there,
we camp out there, don't we fellas?
That's right, I got a sternal
and marshmallows going on in there.
I finish entire novels on the can, right fellas?
Hey guys, ever sitting there so long,
your elbows are on your knees,
and you cut off all the circulation in your legs?
Then you try to stand up
and going, "Oh my God, I'm paralyzed!"
(audience laughs)
"I shouldn't have finished that last chapter."
See the men are laughing now,
the women have no clue what I'm talking about.
You know how I know this?
I was married two and a half years,
my wife never shit one time.
(audience laughs)
I'm telling you, I investigated it.
(audience cheers)
She came out of that bathroom,
I ran in there.
(Craig sniffs)
She's gone on the lawn.
(audience laughs)
I don't understand it ladies.
We eat the same things you do.
And where does your gas go?
And how comes when it comes out of you it's called a fluffy?
(audience laughs)
No man ever let go of a fluffy.
Do you believe all my years I've never heard a female fart?
(audience laughs)
You know why?
My theory is-
where the hell you going?
(audience cheers)
Yeah.
Lemme open that for you, baby.
You like the way I parted your hair tonight there, baby?
(audience laughs)
(audience cheers)
Sorry, erase, erase, erase.
How come women have to have a possy piss when they go?
They couldn't just go by themself.
What do you do, hold hands under the stall
and sing "Kumbaya", what the hell goes on in that bathroom?
♪ Kumbaya my lord, kumbaya.
"Nice shoes."
(audience laughs)
You never see guys going together,
you ever see a guy go,
"Yo Ralph, I could take a dump, will you join me?"
"Come on now wipe my ass for me."
(audience laughs)
Never heard a female fart.
My theory is, women hold their gas for five years.
(audience laughs)
Right? Am I right about that?
'Til they really know the guy,
finally the guy comes home from work,
there's a mushroom cloud around the house.
(audience laughs)
"Hey look Al, she finally let go."
"Must be our five year anniversary."
(audience laughs)
See guys aren't that way, we hold it in for 3 months.
First 3 months are painful though, right guys?
You'll be driving along, you're trying to hold it in,
and your butt cheeks are scrunched together,
your sphincter flicking like a bunny's nose.
You could hold a dime for an hour in there.
Sitting there, "Oh my God, I'm gonna explode."
"Can't wait 'til three months is up,
she'll hear from me."
(audience laughs)
"Excuse me I gotta get out and check the tire right now,
there's something wrong with the tire."
"Oh yeah, there's a leak all right, I got it."
(audience laughs)
You get back in the car
and it follows you in every time doesn't it?
You think the door will cut it off,
it just seals it right in.
(audience laughs)
You're sitting there, "Oh boy (laughs),
that's catalytic converter acting up again."
(audience laughs)
"Ah, these damn new cars" (chuckles).
It's like a '72 Dart you're driving.
(audience laughs)
It's a car in the 70s.
Ah here, they come back again.
(audience cheers)
Come on in, come on in, we were talking about you.
(audience laughs)
Could you hear us, could you hear us in there?
Oh, we could hear you.
(audience laughs)
Yeah, you look a little uncomfortable baby.
I got a fold out couch
and two pillows waiting for you up there, baby.
Yeah.
Sorry, erase, erase.
Where's your partner?
- [Audience Member] She's still in there.
- She still Kumbayaing with somebody else?
(audience laughs)
See if guys go together,
we used to go together when we were younger.
We had sword fights with the wee wee, remember that guys?
I still do it.
I'm Darth Vader in my block.
(mimics Darth Vader's breathing)
Skywalker I've been waiting for you.
(mimics light saber sounds)
Chop Yoda's little head off.
(audience laughs)
Oh I see the force is strong in you.
Must have drunk a lot of beer.
Do females ever do that, you ever have sword fights?
You ever do that?
(audience laughs)
Come on, touche.
(audience cheers)
My whole life has been females.
I grew up with them,
and all this female influence
has been very good for me, though.
I'm the only guy I know who can fake an orgasm.
(audience laughs) (audience cheers)
Yeah.
Hey, applaud if you've heard this one before.
If females live together,
eventually their cycles will coincide.
Have you heard that before?
(audience cheers)
Uh, huh, you've all heard that.
It's true.
It happened to me.
(audience laughs)
[Craig] I never knew when,
I'd be playing basketball with my friends,
all of a sudden I get emotional for no reason.
(yelling over each other) (ball bouncing)
- [Man who fell] Foul!
- Foul? I didn't touch you!
- What are you kidding Shoe?
You just hacked the shit out of me.
- Oh go ahead, make a big deal out of it,
when you foul me I don't say a word,
but it's always about you isn't it?
You selfish bastard!
You have no regard for my feelings, my needs.
- What the hell's wrong with him?
- It's that time of the month.
- Hey Shoe, you okay man?
- Look, I'm sorry guys.
I've been feeling a little edgy,
and a little overwhelmed,
like, like, nobody really understands.
Look, let's not fight, just hold me.
- Maybe you've been overworking yourself, Shoe.
You need to take some time off, man.
- Don't try to fix my feelings, just listen.
- Alright, alright.
No foul you guys, it's Shoe's ball, okay?
- [Player] Yeah, alright.
- Shoe's ball.
Come on man, it's alright, come on.
(chattering)
- Oh go ahead, fine, fine, I'll go get the ball.
Guys, where are you going?
Are we playing or what?
(audience cheers)
Now you females are giggling
with that fix my feelings shit aren't you?
(audience cheers)
Ah huh, y'all read those damn books,
"Men are from Mars," "Women are from Vegas."
whatever that shit is.
(audience cheers)
Quit reading that stuff!
Fix my feelings?
We don't know what to say anymore.
She'll be over there, "Oh God,
you know I can't find a job."
Well apply for one.
(audience laughs)
Did I say the wrong thing?
(audience cheers)
Anybody married here? Anybody married?
(audience cheers) Few people married, yeah.
Cool.
You have to get used to stuff though,
when you get married,
like if they have pets, my wife had two dogs,
and they became my step-dogs.
(audience laughs)
No choice in the matter, one of them's a Dachschund,
you know what a Dachschund is?
A wiener dog.
I look real macho walking a wiener dog.
And she'll feed it too much,
it's now a kielbasa I'm walking down the street.
(audience laughs)
Got this big gut dragging on the ground,
"Hey get me off the cement this hurts."
(audience laughs)
"Put me on the grass, that tickles my belly."
"Look out for that speed bump!"
(audience laughs)
It got stuck on a speed bump.
Big, fat sausage.
And she's got this other dog,
it's half Pitbull, half Poodle.
Not much of a guard dog, but a vicious gossip.
(audience laughs)
After we were married a little while,
after the LA earthquake, there were a lot of stray dogs.
We got another dog, a stray dog, after the earthquake.
They're crazy from the earthquake.
This one follows my wife home, doesn't bark anymore,
it just goes (wheezily exhales).
(audience laughs)
(wheezily barks)
I said, "What the hell?"
Kick up a fur ball or something.
(audience laughs) (wheezes)
I said to my wife,
"What the hell do we need another dog for?
She says, "We need a watchdog."
'Cause all it's gonna do is watch.
(audience laughs)
Who's it gonna scare?
Hey, go get them!
(Wheezes)
Need an interpreter, "Hey get out of here burglar."
(audience laughs)
"We don't want you in here."
I've got the real solution though.
You install one of those mechanical voice boxes.
She wants to bark, she'll put her paw on the button.
(makes muffled barking sound)
That'll scare a robber off.
Imagine you're breaking into a house,
here comes a three-legged dog,
holding onto a button.
(muffled barking sound)
(audience laughs)
(audience applauds)
[Craig] It's robo dog.
(audience cheers)
My wife is always mad at me.
You can tell when somebody's mad at you.
A female is mad at you, they have a noise they do.
Only females can do this noise,
I'll try to duplicate it for you.
(Craig tuts)
(audience laughs)
She can do this thing so loud,
locusts would show up on our driveway.
(audience laughs)
(footsteps)
- Hi, sweetie.
- Think you'll be done with your writing soon?
You said we could go to the movies, right?
- Just a few more minutes.
[Craig] It's going a little slower than I thought.
(wife tuts)
- When she was real mad she'd follow with the f-word.
Yeah, the female f-word.
"Fine."
(audience laughs)
- Well we missed "Dawn of Love,"
but if we hurry we can catch "Time Orado", starts at 1:30.
- Time Orado? What the hell is that?
- Oh it's supposed to be excellent,
Gene Siskel gives it a thumbs up.
- Gene Siskel, oh gee, there's some incentive.
- I thought you liked Siskel.
- That's Schickel honey, Richard Schickle,
What does Siskel know?
You put subtitles on Rambo,
he'll call it the greatest foreign film of time.
- Well why don't we just not go to the movies then, fine.
- Guys, if you hear fine, you are fucked.
(audience laughs)
(audience cheers)
You've got no shot at survival.
- You always do this, you know that?
- Do what?
- Start an argument over the stupidest things
to get out of the plans we made.
- What argument?
- Gene Shallot?
- Gene Siskel.
- What?
- We were arguing over Gene Siskel, not Gene Shallot.
- So you admit you did start an argument?
- Huh.
- Then they have one more word,
you hear this one, you're in the biggest trouble of all.
"Whatever."
(audience laughs)
- All I wanted to do was go to the movies with my husband,
and you attack me with this Gene Shallot shit.
- I did not attack you, and it was Gene Shiskle.
- Siskel.
- Siskel, Shiskle, you know what I meant.
- You Dick Shickel.
- Shickle?
I said Shiskle but meant Siskle because you said Shallot.
- Then you said Shickel, after you started it with Siskle.
- And you thought Shallot.
- I never said Shallot.
- I'm telling you, you thought Siskle was Shallot.
- I would never confuse Shallot with Siskle,
it's Shickle, you're confused with Shiskle.
- Siskel.
- See it was Siskle.
- No, you just said Shiskle, you meant Siskle,
but you said Shiskle.
- I would never say Shiskle, because there is no Shiskle,
that's your invention.
There is only Shickel, Shallot and Siskel.
- What about Joe Siegel?
- Siegel? What's he got to do with it?
Stick to the issue.
- What issue?
- Shickel, Shallot and Siskel.
- And Siegel.
- There is no Siegel.
- He's on NBC.
- ABC.
- So you admit there is a Siegel.
- But not here.
- Where?
- In this argument.
- I'm not arguing.
- Fine.
Whatever.
(audience laughs)
- Evacuate, don't even pack a bag, you're done.
- [Audience Member] Yeah!
(audience laughs)
- You know what it is?
It's the Peter Pan thing, men are Peter Pan.
That's what, all the women write those books too.
Men are immature, I'm proud of being immature.
Anybody else proud of being immature?
(audience cheers)
Right on.
I wanna be a little kid when I grow up.
To this day, I go to the ball park,
I, I wear my glove on every pitch,
amusement parks, go on every ride,
favorite ride to this day is the bumper cars.
Yeah, you ever get in a bumper car ride as an adult,
you pick out a little kid and you pin them in a corner.
(audience laughs)
Come over here.
Come on get your little ass over here.
(imitates child voice) "Get away from me!"
(audience laughs)
(microphone hitting wall)
"Get off of me mister!"
"Come on, the ride's over."
"You're a jerk."
That's a lot of fun.
Here's a ride I went on.
I went on a ride one time, never forget this ride.
17 years old, me and my buddies,
drunk as skunks, got on a ride called the "Hell Hole."
You might know it as "The Roader."
And all it is, is a cylinder, right,
you stand inside the cylinder, right?
It starts spinning really fast,
900 miles and hour, the floor drops off.
We stay on the wall like dead guppies.
And this is all you do, the entire ride.
(audience laughs)
"This is a lot of fun."
"Woo!"
"Hey, I wonder what George is doing over-"
(audience laughs)
"Here!"
"He puked!"
"It's stuck to the side."
(audience laughs)
"It's coming towards me."
"I can't move."
(audience laughs)
"Stop this thing, please."
"I'll pay."
(audience laughs)
I'll never forget we all got on this thing.
It starts spinning, my fat friend Stiney,
he's too heavy for centripetal force.
The floor drops, he goes down with it.
(audience laughs)
I'll never forget his face over there,
"Whoa, whoa what's going on?"
(audience laughs)
"It's not working for me!"
He's down here, we're up there,
it's spinning around, his tits are pinned to the wall.
(audience laughs)
(audience cheers)
True story.
Stiney had great tits, I'll tell you that right now.
(audience cheers)
8th grade, those were the first tits I ever felt,
to tell you the truth.
(audience laughs)
- I've felt one before,
you've got the biggest ones in 8th grade.
- No, you're disgusting!
- Oh come on, just one.
- No, that's disgusting!
- Just, just a really quick feel.
- No, stay away you pervert!
- Oh come on Stiney, if I was fat I'd let you feel mine.
- I think I'm sharing too much with you people.
(audience laughs)
I'm like, I'm the only one
that felt a fat guys tits in 8th grade.
(audience laughs)
Come on help me out here guys.
Oh, you're full of shit!
(audience laughs)
Come on, you never wrestled a fat guy
and copped a quick feel, nobody in here?
(audience cheers)
You know what it is ladies?
It's because you're here.
That's right, guys keep secrets from you their entire lives.
We have guy's secrets, and that's one of them.
You know, yeah well you know what one of them-
you know, I'll give-
Oh no, we're not keeping it that way.
I'm telling you, I'm letting the ladies
in on another guys secret.
Wanna hear a good one ladies?
(women in audience cheer)
[Craig] Just for that.
[Craig] Yeah, that's right.
[Craig] Look at all the guys now.
"Alright, I felt a fat guys tits."
(audience laughs)
It's too late, you lying bastards.
Here it is ladies,
every guy in the room has done this.
At some point in their lives,
they have been naked in front of a full length mirror,
took their jewels, tucked them back by their ass,
tucked their legs in,
to see what they would look like as a woman.
(audience laughs)
[Craig] Every guy in here.
"Damn, I look good like a woman."
(audience laughs)
"I make a good looking chick, look at you."
(audience cheers)
"What's that back there?"
"A bowl of fruit."
(audience cheers)
"Oh walk nasty, Chiquita."
You got that one right.
Come on, hands up on that one fellas.
(men in audience laugh)
Hands up on that one.
(audience laughs)
You did it, right here?
Get the fuck out of here!
(audience cheers)
A man!
That's a real man, that's an honest man.
Give me some skin on that brother.
Yeah!
That's a man, that's a real man.
Can't believe you'd admit it in front of all these people.
(audience laughs)
I never went through it myself,
I think it's great that you'd admit it.
I saw it on "Silence of the Lambs."
(audience laughs)
That is so cool, when's the last time you did it?
You're looking at your fucking watch?
(audience laughs)
You did it tonight?
What the hell, is she shaking her head?
He did it for you?
How did that come up?
"Hey honey, got a little surprise for you."
Turn around, your thinking, "ring, roses."
"Check this out, notice anything different?"
(audience laughs)
"I'm vagina man."
"Check it out honey, I'm vagina man."
You better not turn around,
the whole place is trying to look at you right now.
(audience laughs)
Where is he? Hey vagina man!
(audience cheers)
You'll be a celebrity walking out of here, man.
You'll get recognized in a mall,
"That's him over there, we love you vagina man!"
(audience laughs) "I'm telling you that's him."
"Do it now! Do vagina man!"
"That's the last time I'm ever doing this,
I'm sorry I ever admitted it."
(audience laughs)
That is so cool.
Look at all the couples right now.
See all the couples?
All the women are going,
"Honey, have you ever done vagina man?"
(audience laughs)
"Do it for me tonight, do vagina man."
Alright guys, there's your assignment tonight.
I want you all to take your ladies home,
get naked, show her vagina man.
(audience cheers)
You, take a night off.
(audience laughs)
They're not gonna do it ladies.
They're gonna go home and try to be Lovemaster tonight.
(audience cheers)
Oh yeah, they're gonna be naked in the living room,
trying the voice,
"Come on honey, look it's a towel rack,
hang a wet wagon on it."
All the girls are gonna go,
"Alright honey, couldn't hang a washcloth on that thing."
(audience laughs)
"That couldn't hold up a dry Kleenex, put it away."
"Here's what I learned, erase, erase, erase."
(audience laughs)
(audience cheers)
That's what's gonna happen.
I'm telling you, I'm warning you guys.
Don't try it at home, my wife hated the Lovemaster.
- [Craig] Oh yeah.
[Craig] I'm feeling frisky, baby.
- Will you stop it, I'm trying to read.
- Yeah, I got a pop tent for you, baby.
Come and see the circus.
- Craig, I don't like that Lovemaster.
Save that for your little skit.
- Do Barney Fife.
- (sniffs) Alright, you asked for it.
Come on take it all mama.
(audience cheers) Take it all mama.
Come on, back up.
Back up!
Come on, I don't know how big this thing's gonna get.
Look out for that head bar.
(audience laughs)
(sniffs) Did you cum?
And that's why we're divorced today.
(audience laughs)
She showed the video tape in court.
In slow motion.
There I was, "Take it all."
(audience laughs)
"Baby!"
"Back up!"
"Did you cum?"
(audience laughs)
You know what I got outta that divorce.
A fucking bowl.
(audience cheers)
She took the potpourri.
- [Therapist] So what?
So your marriage was a bust?
It doesn't mean you can't ever find true love.
Well, I don't know, doc.
- Well you're not ever gonna know until you try.
Now I think it's time for you to start dating again.
- Doc, let's face it,
I don't think I'm destined to find someone.
- One date Craig, one date.
No masks, no Lovemaster, simply relax and be you.
(romantic jazz music)
- [Woman] Tonight was really fun.
- [Craig] Yeah.
- I didn't know you could dance like that.
- Well I learned it from my mother.
- Oh, was she a dancer?
- Yeah.
- Ballet?
- Belly.
- Oh.
(kisses cheek)
- What's wrong?
- Oh, can I be honest with you?
- Sure.
- Okay, Craig, I think you're a really nice guy.
It's just that, nice is not what I'm looking for.
- I don't understand, what are you looking for?
- Well.
When I saw your show,
I really wanted to meet you.
I, something about you really, turned me on.
- Ha, my sense of humor?
- [Woman] No.
- Boyish charm?
- Not exactly.
- My sensitivity towards women?
- The Lovemaster, Craig.
I want the Lovemaster.
- That's just a character from my act.
That's not really me.
- But you- I mean can you, I just wanna see-
- Uh, oh.
- Oh come on, the Lovemaster.
- You really don't want him.
- Oh, then you really don't want me.
Goodnight.
Thanks, anyway.
(doorbell rings)
Yes?
- It wasn't my hand that rang the doorbell, baby.
- Well, come on in.
- Oh, yeah.
- Oh you almost did it, you were so close.
- I just couldn't do it, doc.
She was like a dream, I couldn't pass it up.
I'm not that strong.
- Well you're gonna have to get stronger
if we're gonna get anywhere at all, okay?
Where can you go to meet someone?
Where you can feel safe, really free?
Some place you can just let everything go,
let it all hang out.
- I went to a nude beach to meet somebody.
(audience cheers)
Anyone here been to a nude beach?
- Shoe, look at all them, this is great!
Oh, boy.
Oh, boy, Oh, boy! - Alright Stiney, act cool.
Act cool! Act cool!
Hey, how you doing?
- How you doing, how you doing?
- Shoey, are you kidding me, Shoey!
Shoe, what are you doing it's a nude beach.
- Come on relax, I'm nude.
- [Stiney] Yeah, you're nude, I'm nude!
[Stiney] Come on, come on!
- [Craig] Wait up!
[Craig] Come on, slim, wait up!
- And my peepee's never been in the sun
for that long before.
I'm trying to be inconspicuous
putting sunblock on my wiener
in the middle of broad daylight.
This isn't bad enough, they make it out of white cream.
(audience cheers)
These people think I'm spanking the monkey
in the middle of the beach out here.
(audience claps)
People look at me, "Is he clearing a snorkel over there?"
It's not the same as doing your back
or handing it to someone like,
"Hey, can you do this for me?"
"Yeah, sure, I'll help you out with that thing, yeah."
(mumbles)
"Ah yeah, you're all set there."
"Hey, go take a walk!"
Take a walk?
I gotta smoke a cigarette.
Then I go for my first nude walk,
made a big mistake, went into the cold water.
You know what happens then, right guys?
Shrinkage.
- Shoe!
Shoe!
- [Craig] I don't care who the hell you are,
it's an acorn in that cold water.
- Shoe!
- This is a true story.
I came out of the water, I made a beeline for the towel.
[Craig] "Hoo, no, they're not gonna see me like this."
Three gorgeous women intercept me.
They recognize me from the show the night before.
They start talking to me, they're nude.
My weiner looks like button on a fur coat.
- We saw you the other night at the club.
You were great!
I mean jaw is still hurting from laughing so much.
Do it, Tina. Do it.
(mimics Craig's joke)
- [Nude Woman] I thought I was gonna die!
And you know what?
You don't look a thing like John Boy,
you are much sexier.
- [Craig] Oh, thank you.
Whole time they're talking to me,
I don't hear a word they're saying.
I'm standing there like,
"Please grow, please grow!"
"Make him grow!"
I'm trying to hit it real casually.
"Aw, you like that show, that's good."
"Just great."
"Lemme hear uh..."
Your-your favorite part of the show.
- Please, the Lovemaster! (girls moan in unison)
I mean when you're out there just going,
"C'mon baby, talk nasty for the Lovemaster."
I get so excited,
I just wanna jump up on stage and, "Ruff!"
You know?
Look girls, he's doing his act for us right now.
He's doing vagina man!
- I'm not doing vagina man, right now!
- You're not?
- Let's get out of here.
(Craig sighs)
(audience laughs)
(audience cheers)
- I was Flipper.
(dolphin trills)
Dolphin at his own show in the 60s.
I got other impressions.
You guys like impressions?
- [Audience] Yeah!
- I can do some impressions for you.
Alright, here's my impression of the Cowardly Lion
from the Wizard of OZ on a motorcycle.
(imitates motorcycle engine and the Lion sobbing)
(audience cheers and claps)
[Craig] I've got another one!
I've got some more!
My whole life, I always wondered what it would be like
to be somebody else.
We're gonna take that back and see what it would be like
to be born as a celebrity.
These are my impressions of the birth of celebrities.
Celebrities that are being born,
starting with Jack Nicholson.
We'll take you to the hospital room now with Mrs. Nicholson.
Alright, Mrs. Nicholson.
Take it easy now.
Now breathe deep.
Come on bear down and push Mrs. Nicholson.
Push!
(audience laughs)
(audience cheers and applauds)
Here's Johnny!
Wow, we're on a roll here now.
Here we go.
From "60 Minutes," Anne Derune.
Did you ever look in the inside of a uterus?
Kinda cramped in here.
Rambo.
(moans repeatedly)
Rocky.
(moans again)
"Cliffhanger."
(repeats moaning)
Hey, I'd like to buy a consonant!
(audience laughs)
Hey, you got that one, eh?
More births.
Pee-Wee Herman.
Okay, miss.
What if I don't feel like coming out?
Ala-la-la-la.
Looks like you're gonna have to come in and get me.
Mike Tyson.
Excuse me, doc.
Try to spank me and I'll slap the shit out of you.
(audience laughs)
(audience cheers)
Jimmy Stewart.
(speaks indistinctively)
Hey, would you look at this!
I'm outta here!
(audience laughs)
Mick Jagger.
(audience cheers)
And the Lovemaster.
Come here, nursie baby.
It's the umbilical cord you see coming out of there, baby.
Aw, yeah! Birth of celebrities!
Thank you!
Woo!
(crowd cheers)
I'm glad I came here.
I live in Los Angeles, you know?
- [Audience Member] Woo!
- Don't boo.
I have to live there for show-biz purposes.
You think I'm gonna get discovered
in a shopping center in Phoenix?
(audience laughs)
Everybody in LA is in show-biz.
Everybody you meet.
The people in drugstores, grocery store,
waiters, waitresses, they're all frustrated
screenwriters, directors, actors.
Even the policeman who stops me for drunk driving.
He's a frustrated choreographer.
Instead of me walk the line,
he wants me to follow after him.
"Here we go."
"And, follow me!"
"Step, kick, ball change, step right,
step, step, step,
kick ball change, step, smile pretty!"
"Shuffle!"
(sings)
"Someone missed a step!"
"Bitch, don't get me pissy!"
"I am in a mood."
[Craig] Yeah.
You know why I like coming here though?
It's- everybody's cool around here, you know?
In Los Angeles, the whole show-biz thing is ridiculous.
You know where it's really bad?
If you go to a ball game out there,
the people that sing "The National Anthem."
You cannot sing along with them
because they think it's their big audition piece.
They know producers are in the audience,
they're thinking they're gonna get a record deal
out of "The National Anthem."
This is what it's like if a guy has his big break
in front of Dodger Stadium.
It goes something like this.
Alright, let's say Lovemaster has his big shot
at singing "The National Anthem."
(audience cheers)
[Craig] At Dodger Stadium, it goes something like this.
♪ Whoa, whoa.
♪ Say
(holds note)
(holds note) (audience cheers)
♪ Whoa, whoa.
♪ Say
(holds note)
♪ Whoa, whoa.
♪ Oh say, can you see.
(dramatically holds high note)
(holds note) (audience cheers)
(continues to hold note)
(pauses)
(continues the same note) (audience roars)
♪ You see it, baby?
(crowd laughs)
♪ By the dawn's early...
♪ 'ight
♪ What's so, what's so proudly we ha-yeah-yeah-ail ♪
♪ At the twi- gleaming
♪ Who's broad stripes
Who brought 'em baby?
Who brought the stripes and bright stars?
♪ Through the perilous
♪ 'ight
♪ Oh the ramparts
♪ I have no idea what a rampart is ♪
♪ Were so gallantly streaming
Yeah let me here you say, "Yeah!"
- [Audience] Yeah!
♪ And the rockets red glare
♪ The bombs were bursting right there in thin air ♪
Yep! Mhm!
♪ Gave proof through the night
♪ That our flag, our own flag
♪ My good friend, Betsy Ross' flag ♪
♪ Was still there
Come on, Betsy.
Walk nasty for the Lovemaster.
I got your flag pole, run it up.
- Stop it!
Why don't you sing as yourself for God's sake?
- No one wants to hear that, Nanna!
- Don't be scared, sure they will!
- Go for it, Shoe!
- Come on, honey!
- Don't be a wimp!
- Go for it, Shoe!
- It's now or never, Craig.
- Nah.
- Do it!
- Alright, bring it home!
♪ Oh say
♪ Does that star-spangled
♪ Banner yet
♪ Wave
(holds note)
(audience cheers)
♪ O'er the land of the free
♪ And the home of the brave
(holds note)
(audience cheers)
(audience claps)
You've been a great audience!
Thank you!
(jazz music) (audience cheers)
(jazz piano)
(audience cheers)
(audience continues clapping)
(jazz piano)
- Hey, you're the waitress with the water.
I was just clowning around.
It's all just a part of my act.
You did great.
Hey, you wanna go out for a cup of coffee?
- Sorry, Lovemaster but my boyfriend's coming to pick me up.
- Oh.
[Craig] Hey, anybody here want to uh-
[Craig] Alright, no problem!
- Uh, excusez-moi!
Uh, can you tell me how to get to this?
"Murphy's Tavern."
- I wish I could help but I'm not from around here.
- Aw, me neither.
- What brings you to Arizona?
- I'm traveling.
And you?
- Business.
- Oh.
- I'm a therapist.
I'm here on like,
a therapy convention, therapy, type of thing.
- Oh, that's very interesting.
What is your specialty?
- My specialty?
It's love.
Love and laughter.
They combine the two, it's like a new type of therapy.
(fangirls in French)
- So you love to laugh?
Well, uh, I love to laugh.
(Craig chuckles)
- Well, French is the language of love.
You are French, aren't you?
- Oui.
(both chuckle)
Do you speak?
- Oh, Oui!
Je parle un peu français.
- [French Woman] I'm impressed!
(rambles in French)
- I speak it, but I don't understand it.
Not a word.
I heard like, "visite," I figure that's visit or something.
(French woman laughs) (Craig rambles on)
- You are very funny, no, it's good!
- Well, thank you.
Hey, have you ever heard of the Lovemaster?
- Uh.
What is this?
- Never mind.
My name is Craig.
- Nice to meet you Craig, I am Molly.
- I was just going out for a cup of coffee.
Feel like joining me?
- Oui.
(agrees in French)
I think I would like that very much!
(Craig comments in French)
- That's French!
- I know!
That's all I know though.
Don't ask anymore.
(woman giggles)
- [French Woman] You are very funny.
(chuckles in unison)
- (imitates Lovemaster) Oh yeah.
(voices drift off in the distance)
(woman giggles)
(jazz music)
- [Therapist] Craig, I'm just so darn proud of you.
- I gotta thank you, doc.
I feel great!
- You know, there's a question I've been meaning to ask you
for quite some time now.
- [Craig] Hey, I'm an open book.
Fire away.
- Great.
Uh, I don't want to sound unprofessional or anything
but just how big is your "schmekle" anyway?
(jazz instrumentals)
♪ Oh yeah
(upbeat music)
♪ Baby
♪ I can walk nasty for the
♪ Walk nasty for the
♪ The master
♪ I got
♪ I got what you want right here, baby ♪
♪ The master
♪ I got
♪ Oh yeah
♪ Cum on me
♪ Erase, erase
♪ Oh yeah
♪ Baby
(percussion)
(upbeat music)
♪ I got
♪ I got what you want right here, baby ♪
♪ Walk nasty for the
♪ The master
♪ I got
♪ I got what you want right here, baby ♪
♪ The master
♪ I got
♪ Oh yeah
♪ Cum on me