[funky guitar music]
[car engine idling]
All right I'm here,
Montel, what now?
Montel, this is
Towers, what now?
DAVID MONTEL: Come on in, Phil.
I'm waiting inside.
[gun shot]
[ominous music]
Do you like the decor?
I did it all myself.
[ominous music]
[eerie music]
Good boy.
I see you found the entrance.
Well?
Don't just stand there.
Come and play.
SGT. PHIL TOWERS (DREAM
VOICE): It's me Towers.
Don't go in.
It's a trap.
DAVID MONTEL: No guts,
no glory law man.
SGT. PHIL TOWERS (DREAM
VOICE): It's a trap.
Get out.
Save yourself before-- before
it's-- before it's too late.
DAVID MONTEL: But
it is too late.
[motorcycle engine revving]
[rapid gunfire]
[ominous music]
Please.
Who is he?
DAVID MONTEL: See for yourself.
[ominous music]
Montel, I'm
taking you to trial.
How can I testify if I'm dead?
Ha, ha, ha, ha.
Ah, ha, ha, ha, ha.
[evil laughing]
[ominous music]
Ah.
Oh, God.
Oh.
Oh, sonofabitch.
[funky guitar music]
[birds chirping]
Hello?
Is anybody here?
Yeah, I'm here.
Oh, hi sugar.
Morning sweetheart.
You working by yourself?
Yeah, everyone
went hunting today.
You want some eggs?
You bet.
I'm about to starve.
Coming right up.
Thanks.
[TRAFFIC NOISE AND BIRDS
CHIRPING]
[music playing]
How are the eggs?
Great, I'm already finished.
Are you and Alec
going hunting today?
Yeah, I'm fixing to meet
him down at the junk yard.
Now, you're not going
to disappear for two
weeks in the woods are you?
You promised to take me
dancing tomorrow night.
I didn't forget.
Date's still on.
Good.
Now, you come in the kitchen
and see what I made for dessert.
Dessert?
LORI: Yeah, come check it out.
[guitar picking]
I'm not much in the habit of
having dessert after breakfast.
[funky guitar music]
Maybe you could
make an exception.
Maybe I could at that.
[funky guitar music]
Oh, fuck.
All work and no play
makes for a grumpy boy.
Come on, cousin.
It's time to go hunting.
Yeah, I'm ready.
I just got to
finish pulling this.
Look, this can wait.
We're going to go have
a few drinks at the bar
and then go nail down
a couple of bucks.
The bar?
Jesus, I haven't even
had breakfast yet.
You know, is there any time
of day you don't drink?
Yeah, when I'm sleeping.
Come on.
Besides I already had
breakfast and dessert.
Dessert?
Never mind.
Come on, let's go.
This can wait.
OK.
But I do want you to
help me get the school
bus over here tonight.
Damn think again?
This town definitely
needs a new school bus.
Hey, no big deal.
Just a brake job.
Harvey left the part by the bar.
At least it's convenient.
I'll tell you what,
we'll get drunk,
then we'll drive the
thing off a bridge.
Then they'll have
to get new one.
You know, keeping that school
bus running is a major source
of income for me.
If you so much as
lay a hand on it,
I'm going to have
to kick your ass.
I'm sure you mean that
in a figurative way.
I'll tell you what, game of
pool, best three out of five,
if I win, we drive the
thing into the river.
And if I win, which I
will, you buy the beer
for the next three months.
Hey wait a minute.
Oh.
[birds chirping]
[music playing]
[pool cue cracking balls]
Yes, that's two in a row.
Man, you got lucky.
Half those shots
were squirrel shots.
Yeah, maybe you're right.
So I don't suppose
you want to play
another one, double or nothing.
Ha, ha, and don't worry, I'm
not feeling lucky anymore.
Don't be an asshole.
You want another beer?
Oh, why not We're
buying it with my money.
I know.
Hey Sarah.
Sarah?
Damn, that's heavy.
Well, baby, if
I've told you once,
I've told you a thousand
times, if you just marry me
you wouldn't have to
work in this dump.
I'd have to work just
to pay for your bar tab.
Besides what would Lori say?
Oh, yeah.
I guess you've got a point.
Well, maybe won't you
give me another round?
See what I mean?
Hey, why are you
guys still in town?
I figure you'd be out hunting
with the rest of town.
JAKE: Well, you know,
it's obvious we're
trying to beat the rush.
We're going to
wait about an hour.
Oh, did you ever
buy a gun or are you
still trying to hit something
with that bow of yours?
Ew, Miss NRA.
I'm telling you--
- Ahem.
It's the way to go.
You ought to try it.
You know, a guy could
die of thirst around here.
Oh, well, here you go.
I wouldn't want you
dying on me now.
If I could die on
someone, I'd pick you.
Are you ready to play?
Yeah, I'm ready to play.
Are you?
- Later.
- Break it up.
I'd hate to have to throw
cold water on you two.
Jesus.
Hey, what can I say?
Lucky at pool, lucky at love.
You know, sometimes
you can be real prick.
Yeah?
That's what makes our
friendship so special.
Special my ass.
[music playing]
DETECTIVE WEST: Hello?
Hello?
Anybody here?
SHERIFF: I'm coming.
I'm coming.
What can I do for ya?
Ah, good afternoon, sir.
We're looking for the sheriff.
Sheriff John J.
Roberts in the flesh.
DETECTIVE WEST: It's a
pleasure to meet you.
My name is Detective West.
This is Detective Carter.
We're here on a witness
protection assignment.
And we would
appreciate your help.
SHERIFF: Well sure.
But what's it all about?
Sir, you understand we have
to have your full support.
Our witness will be coming
through here in the next three
or four hours.
DETECTIVE WEST: And you must
tell no one, absolutely no
one, not even your own men.
How many men
are on duty today?
Actually just me.
But I don't understand
what you want me to do.
Ah, sheriff, are there
usually more men on duty?
Well, there's Emmett.
He's gone hunting.
The season opened today.
It is very important that
no one, and I repeat, no one
find out about this.
Yes, you see
we're transferring
this witness to Los Angeles
under top secret orders.
Well, you don't have
to worry about me.
What's mine is yours.
Good.
We appreciate that.
Yeah, well, thank
you very much.
SHERIFF: Hey, where you
fellas going be in case
I have to get a hold of you?
Oh, well, ah don't
worry, Sheriff.
We'll be around.
[suspenseful music]
SGT. PHIL TOWERS: Want a smoke?
DAVID MONTEL:
Well, sure why not?
When are we going to
get something to eat?
Soon.
Come on.
I'm tired of this shit.
Well, that's just
too bad, isn't it?
Fuck.
Quit your whining.
There's a town about
20 miles ahead.
We'll get something there.
Whatever happened to
three square meals a day?
Great.
[candy wrapper rattling]
Oh, man.
You better have a beer.
I do.
Last one.
Looks like we're going
to have split it.
ALEX: I always have
a back up, Jake.
JAKE: You're nuts.
And you talk about me.
Hey, come here, I want
to show you my new baby.
What is this time?
Ah, just wait and see.
You ready for this?
No, but let's see it anyway.
[crows cawing]
Jesus Christ.
Where's my bow?
Here.
Today you're using a gun.
And this is nothing.
I got something
else to show you.
[birds chirping]
Well, what do you think?
I think you're nuts,
that's what I think.
Jesus.
Why do you collect
all this shit?
Because I like it.
Look at these.
You know what's going
to happen when I pump
these through that 50 caliber?
Yeah, you're probably going to
go to jail for about 10 years.
Oh, listen Mr. Bow and
Arrow, you hunt your way,
and I'll hunt mine.
Hunt?
What are you going to
shoot, elephant and buffalo?
Don't worry, I'll save
a buffalo or a rabbit
or two for you.
You're not serious.
Well, of course I am,
however, I'm not dumb.
[birds chirping]
Hey, let's go hunting.
[crows cawing]
[eagle screeching]
[music playing]
Can I help you?
Well, you sure
can, sweetheart.
Well?
DETECTIVE WEST: Give
us a couple of drafts.
Coming right up.
What a town, huh?
First day of hunting season and
everything stops for the day.
Jeez, we're-- we're back
in the 18th century.
Yeah, it's a beautiful
thing, isn't it?
Besides it makes our lives
all that much easier.
Here you go.
That'll be $1.50.
DETECTIVE WEST: You're kidding?
You're not from
around here are ya?
Sweetheart, where
I come from, $1.50
doesn't even pay for the ice.
Where's that?
Nowhere.
We travel around a lot.
If you say so.
[music playing]
You keep that.
You know, it's hard to
believe this town is so quiet.
Yeah, it's nice and
peaceful around here.
If I can get you anything
else, just let me know.
We sure will.
[music playing]
Cheers.
JAKE: Oh, God.
Look at this weather.
It doesn't look like we're going
to get much hunting done today.
Oh, Don't worry about it.
It'll clear up.
You know how it is.
One minute it's bad,
and then I'll clear up.
It'll be great.
I hope so.
You know what, as
much talk as we
do about how this place sucks,
I don't think I'd ever leave.
Yeah, it does
have its moments.
Yeah.
Remember when we
took the Callaghan
sisters up to Northridge Point?
Oo hoo.
- Oh, ho, ho.
Remember it?
That was a good time.
Best shot Alex.
Shit, dream on.
Yeah, but I remember
their brothers.
Oh my God.
I thought their brothers
were going to kill us.
Don't even remind me of that.
Oh.
Those were the days, partying,
girls, Budweiser, more girls,
more Budweiser, Springsteen.
Trojans.
Yeah, Trojans,
couldn't forget those.
How about getting those?
You remember that?
No, remember we used to
try to get good old Pete
to buy those for us?
Oh, man, Pete.
Whatever happened to him?
Oh, he's probably
still in Hollywood trying
to do these low budget
movies, you know,
trying to be a big movie star.
Imagine that.
Oh, at least that's one guy that
got the hell out of this town.
Yeah, I got to give him that.
He did have balls.
Yeah.
Oh, hey, what are those
two guys doing over there?
Beats me.
Let's pull over and ask'em.
[birds chirping]
How's it going?
Oh, just fine.
How about you?
Not bad.
You guys ah all right?
Broke down or something?
No, no, just
enjoying the fine air.
Where you guys from?
We're just passing
through town,
thought we'd take a few
minutes to come out here
and appreciate the countryside.
Ah, you're a little off the
main road, wouldn't you say?
ROBERTSON: Yeah, well, we
just figured the scenery would
be a little nicer out here.
Hm.
Well, you figured right.
Well, we'll be seeing ya.
Y'all have a good day.
You too.
Thanks for stopping by.
Hey, no problem.
See ya.
[birds chirping]
Stupid fucking hicks.
I hate this fucking town.
Come on, let's get on with it.
[birds chirping]
How long will this take you?
Oh, two or three
minutes a line.
Good.
But just do it so we can get
out of the fucking place.
[birds chirping]
You know, that was strange.
What?
Well, they just didn't
seem like the type to go
out of their way for a view.
Well, you never know, man.
Poor bastards are
probably from New
York, never seen a tree before.
They're used to seeing
faggots and pimps.
Yeah, but that's my point.
You know, guys like that
don't do anything that doesn't
put money in their pockets.
And besides, how the hell would
they know where this road is?
Yeah, don't you
think you're getting
a little out of hand, Alex?
You want to turn around and
make a citizen's arrest or what?
ALEX: All right, all right.
So I've got an
active imagination.
It's all those damn detective
magazines you've been reading
and those guns and shit.
Oh.
I don't know.
You know, something
is strange about guys
dressed in suits sitting
in the middle of nowhere.
[loud thumping]
Jeez.
What the hell now?
[birds chirping]
Shit, man, I don't believe it.
That was a brand new tire.
Well, now it's
old and fucked up.
Great, what should we do?
We can't go hunting now.
We can either leave the
car here and go hunting.
Or we can go back and try to
catch a ride with those guys.
Shit, man we can't
go hunting out here.
We're not far
enough out of town.
And the only thing
we're going to get here
is rabbits and squirrels.
And I can't hunt them
in my own backyard.
Look, dude, then let's
leave the car here and go
catch a ride with those guys.
Oh, great.
Come on.
We'll lock the car up.
Nobody's going to
bother our stuff.
And we'll go back down there.
Ain't nobody going
to bother it here.
No, in a town this
small, we'd know
who did it in five minutes.
Come on.
Damn it.
[birds chirping]
Five more miles and
you get your second meal.
What do mean, second meal?
That candy bar,
that was your first.
You're a real
asshole, you know that?
Yeah, that's
what they tell me.
Why do you treat me
like a piece of shit, hm?
Probably cause you
are a piece of shit.
You know, I make
my money in one hour
than you make in a year?
Not anymore.
I could set you up, Phil.
Let me go, and you'll
never have to work
another day in your life.
Yeah.
You know the way
I got it figured,
in, prison you oughta make
about, oh, $0.18 cents a day.
Are you as stupid as you look?
Don't you get it?
You're nothing.
You're more expendable than me.
And how do you figure that?
Simple.
The FBI and DEA want
me alive at all costs.
And if that cost just
happens to be you,
well, another cop dies
in the line of duty.
We4ll, I guess if that's
the way it's gotta be,
that's the way it's gotta be.
My offer still stands.
I don't take blood money.
I never killed any
skunk that didn't
damn well deserve to die.
I just helped a
skunk kill the skunk.
What I do is public service.
Oh, you're a sick fuck.
[traffic noise]
[birds chirping]
Oh, damn, not
the phones again.
Hey, hey guys, wait a second.
Hey.
[ominous music]
What's wrong?
Did the stupid hicks get
lost in their own back yard?
You ask too many
questions, you know that?
[gunshot]
Man, what the hell
did you do that for?
Fun.
I hear it's hunting season.
I hear it's hunting
season, boys.
I hope you don't mind if
I didn't bring my license.
Ain't exactly what you'd
call a thriving metropolis.
Who cares as long
as they've got food.
Well, what do you want?
Come on.
Let's go in and eat.
I'm going to ask you one
more time, what do you want?
I have to take a
shit, for Christ's sake.
God, you're a pain in the ass.
Put up your hands.
Damn, that feels good.
I'm glad I could
make you happy.
You got an attitude problem.
Tell my therapist about it.
[funky guitar music]
[dogs barking]
Hi.
I'm Lori.
I'll be your waitress today.
Where's your bathroom?
Down to the left.
You guys are eating, aren't you?
Of course we are, sugar.
Come on, move it.
We'll be back in a minute.
[funky guitar music]
Do you have to stay in here?
It's a little hard to take
a shit with an audience.
It's was a real
thrill for me too.
I'll try not to applaud.
Oh.
Shit.
What is it now Montel?
There's no goddamned
toilet paper in here.
Am I going to have
to come in there
and wipe your ass for you?
There's none in here either.
I'll go get the
waitress to get some.
[ominous music]
Montel, let's go.
Let's go?
Get me some toilet
paper for Christ's sake.
Montel let's go, now.
[suspenseful music]
Shit, they're gone.
Check outside.
Move.
[suspenseful music]
You going somewhere?
What the hell are you doing?
Hey, you didn't think we'd
let'em take you to jail,
did ya?
DAVID MONTEL: Christ,
what took you so long?
You ah-- you didn't tell
those police anything did ya?
What kind of question is that?
Of course not.
Good, good.
That's real good.
Can we get the
hell outta here now?
Well, now I wish
we could, but ah--
I'm afraid you're
not going with us.
[suspenseful music]
You kidding me?
You sonofabitch.
I saved your life once.
Oh, sorry.
[gunshot]
Don't get any ideas.
Let's go.
[suspenseful music]
Shit.
Jesus Christ.
[ominous music]
What's going on?
You tell me.
It's not what you think.
The mob doesn't work like this.
This is bullshit.
If they want you.
They can have you.
[suspenseful music]
[dogs barking]
We lost'em.
Why don't you go
check around back, OK?
Now.
[birds chirping]
What the hell
is going on here?
Don't worry about it.
Everything's under control.
AGENT CARTER:
Under control, my ass.
Now you talk to me, now.
Sheriff, I need you
to go back to your car
and call for backup.
Find as many men as
you can, all right?
Oh.
[jazzy music]
That's a good way to die.
Where are they?
There's nobody back there.
Damn.
[music playing]
Somebody's gonna pay, man.
Somebody's gonna pay.
We lost'em.
All right, later.
Let's find a-- a doctor
in this hick town.
Come on.
[suspenseful music]
You know, I thought
you were dead.
Yeah.
Thanks for checking, asshole.
AGENT CARTER:
ROBERTSON: I hate to break
this little party up boys.
But we got business to do.
First business we got
is to get me to a doctor.
Oh, it's nothing.
The guy winged you.
Hey, how about
I wing you, man?
I'll be right back.
Asshole.
What the hell are we doing?
If we don't find
these assholes soon,
we're going to have 100 red
necks showing up in town
and fully armed.
Don't worry about it.
We'll get'em.
What the hell is this?
It's a first aid kit.
It's all we've got.
- Where's the doctor?
- He's hunting.
The doctor is hunting too?
I don't believe this town.
[engine revving]
How you doing?
Huh?
This hurts.
This isn't my idea of fun, man.
Hey, it's not my
idea of fun either.
But we've got to get into town.
Those guys are still after us.
We gotta get to the sheriff.
Can you hang on?
- Yeah.
OK, let's go.
[birds chirping]
[door squeaking]
Hello?
[music playing]
Freeze.
Don't move.
I'm a police officer.
And I'm the President.
[music playing]
Looks real.
So what are you doing
sneaking around my bar?
Put down the gun, and
we'll talk about it.
I'll keep the
gun and you talk.
You a cop too?
No.
I'm a killer.
Listen lady.
I just want to get out
of this town alive.
This man is a hitman
for the mafia.
And I'm trying to transport
him cross-country.
Apparently his friends
don't want that.
They want him dead.
So put down the gun now.
Lady, I'm not kidding.
Put it down now.
[intense music]
Come on.
Have you seen any strangers
from out of town today?
[music playing]
Yeah, a few minutes ago, a
guy who was in here earlier
came in and asked
for a first aid kit.
What do you do?
Well, I gave it to him.
He had blood all over his shirt.
But I think his friend
was the one who was hurt.
We're dead.
There's no way we're going
to get out of this alive.
These guys are nuts.
They'll kill anyone.
- You have a telephone?
- It's out of order.
The lines are dead.
So are we.
By the way, you got
any toilet paper?
I've got some unfinished
business to attend to.
Let's take a short
meeting fellas.
All right, all right,
we'll set up here, guys.
With the Sheriff out
of the way, this has
got the best view of the town.
We can catch any
of the dispatchers
that are coming in and out.
Now, ah-- Carter,
you take Thompson
and have a look around.
I'll stay here with Roberts.
Let's do it.
Be careful boys.
Do you want to check the radio?
[birds chirping]
[suspenseful music]
Jesus.
[funky guitar music]
Give me the radio.
Are you locking it up?
Yeah.
Close it up.
Repeat, close it up.
[funky guitar music]
Jesus Christ, what's going on?
I'm not sure.
Lori?
Alex, where's Lori?
She was working today.
She's dead.
What?
She's dead, man.
Oh.
Sarah.
What is going on?
Who's-- who's doing this?
That's what we're
trying to figure out.
Now, look Sarah--
What?
Lori's dead.
No.
Oh, my God.
JAKE: Sarah, why are you here?
There are these
guys at the bar.
One says he's a cop.
He told me to go
get the sheriff.
He said if he's seen outside
he'd be killed in a second.
ALEX: Well, who is they?
I don't know.
He said some guys with the
mafia were trying to kill him
and some other guy, a
prisoner or something.
Look, whatever
is going on here,
we're going to need some
serious fucking help.
SARAH: I went past the
year sheriff's office,
but I didn't stop because
there were guys in the window.
Ah, Sarah, are these
guys still at the bar?
Yeah.
He said he'd wait
as long as he could.
Oh, my God, Jake what happened?
Look, just forget about it.
We're going to need to go.
SARAH: Where?
I guess back to the bar.
Wait, wait a minute.
He said-- he said
he's sure they'll
be watching my every move.
If we go out together,
it'll look suspicious.
ALEX: Man, this is crazy.
So what do we do?
OK.
Sarah, just go back to the
bar as fast as you can.
Don't cause any suspicion and
don't stop for anyone, OK?
SARAH: OK.
ALEX: How's the arm?
Can you make it a little longer?
It still hurts,
but I'll be fine.
ALEX: OK.
After Sarah goes, we'll go
out the back through the woods
down along the creek.
Will be at the
bar in 20 minutes.
Sounds good to me.
Be careful.
ALEX: We'll see you there.
[soft music]
Jesus Christ, what
are we going to do?
We can't take these guys on.
Yes we can.
I'm getting the sheriff's gun.
[gun cocks]
We're gonna fight back.
Come on.
Man, I'm gonna kill somebody
for what they did to her.
[barking]
[birds chirping]
That's your last beer, Montel.
Where the hell is she?
She's dead, pal.
And so are we if we
don't get outta here.
Well, do you have a
better idea, genius?
You could give me a gun.
Yeah, that's all I
need, you with a gun.
I'm a pro.
If anyone can get us
out of this, it's me.
You know that.
But what's to stop
you from killing me?
What's the difference?
You're going to die
one way or the other.
You're a real asshole.
I'll make you a deal.
I don't make deals
with pieces of shit.
Don't be an idiot.
Look, I help you get outta
this, and you set me free,
even exchange, a
life for a life.
Nobody has to know.
Come on.
It's your only chance.
It's my only chance.
Do you really
think I'd kill you?
I told you, I only
killed the scumbags.
I never touched an
innocent person.
Well, I don't want
to make me your first.
[traffic noise]
[gunshots]
Get the fuck in the car.
Relax, I wasn't gonna hit her.
I was just having some fun.
Well, you pull any
more shit like that,
and I'll cut your
fucking heart out.
Huh.
[loud country music]
Get out you stupid bitch.
Get out.
Now, you're coming with us.
[birds chirping]
[music playing]
[pool balls clicking]
Oh, shit.
She should have been
back here by now.
I'm telling you,
man, she doesn't
stand a chance with these guys.
With what guys?
So do I shoot first and
ask questions later?
Put down the gun.
I'm a police officer.
But where's Sarah?
She should be here.
DAVID MONTEL: I'm
telling you, she's dead.
She better not be.
Because if she is,
then you are too.
Oh, I'm not impressed, kid.
Shut up, Montel.
Now listen, I'm going
to reach into my pocket,
and I'm going to
pull out my badge.
Just do it nice and slow.
[soft music]
So if you're a cop, why
are people being killed?
Listen, I don't
have time to explain
all the details to you guys.
We don't have much
time, all right?
So either pull the trigger
or put the gun down.
Look, you said we
didn't have much time.
Time for what, goddammit?
SGT. PHIL TOWERS: Time
before our little friends
get over here.
Looks like you've
already met them.
These guys are professionals.
They work for the mob.
And this guy is a witness.
And all I want to do is
get him to court alive.
Look, I don't care
who he is or you, just
get the fuck out of this town.
It's too late for that, kid.
They know we're here.
And they ain't gonna
leave without us.
Well, what if
we get them first?
Come again?
I mean, what if
we go after them
instead of sitting
like ducks on a pond?
You have no idea
what you're in for.
These guys are pros and
probably outman us five to one.
Do you think they
really still have Sarah?
Yeah.
but I wouldn't worry.
They won't kill her right away.
They'll have some fun with her
first, then they'll kill her.
You sonofabitch.
[gunshot]
You can't get away.
We got ever road
out of town blocked.
[eagle screeching]
So ah-- so why don't you
just be good fellas, eh?
Send that Montel out.
[eagle screeching]
Shit, we gotta get outta here.
Give me a gun,
man, I can help.
Look, why don't you
just throw him out front?
It's him they want, not us.
Well, maybe we can
slip out the back.
Not likely.
Well, I think
Sarah's got a couple
more guns stashed somewhere.
I'll find them.
OK.
See now, you're so sure
we're going to die,
I guess this won't
hurt anything.
Now you're thinking.
Look, well, Jesus Christ,
what the hell are you doing?
This guys' a killer.
A killer is exactly
what you need right now.
Here, stop your
bullshitting and go help
your friend find some guns.
[gun cocking]
[birds chirping]
What's it gonna be?
You want me to blow up
this whole town or what?
All right hotshot,
show us what you got.
DAVID MONTEL: Go to the
window and cover me.
I've got an idea.
[suspenseful music]
Hi guys.
It's me.
[MULTIPLE GUN SHOTS AND COUNTRY
MUSIC]
Well, that was a hell
of a plan, asshole.
We've got to move fast.
That school bus, does it run?
Yeah.
I'm supposed to fix the brakes.
- You work on that thing?
- Yeah.
- You got the keys?
- Yes.
Give'em to me.
- What?
Do what he says.
I'm tired of playing
games with you, Montel.
Well, you think he's dead?
If he ain't he will be.
What are you giving up
your life to Montel for, huh?
That Montel's
nothing but a killer.
Come on out, boys,
with your hands up.
We'll let you go.
Cover the windows and
stand by for action.
[music playing]
Holy shit.
Guys, I'd say we got about
10 seconds to fucking live.
Holy shit.
Fuck.
Ready?
Ready.
[multiple gunshots]
Shit.
What are you waiting for?
Fire that damn thing.
[funky guitar music]
Oh,
Shit.
[gunshots]
[FUNKY GUITAR MUSIC AND GUN
SHOTS]
Kill him.
[funky guitar music]
[cars exploding]
Bastard.
West.
Over.
DETECTIVE WEST: What?
You missed.
No shit.
You missed your target and
they're heading for the woods.
[guitar twang]
Dodge?
Dodge, are you there?
Oh, Christ.
Come on, let's get Montel.
Something's wrong.
Shut up.
Just shut up.
I'm very disappointed.
I thought you guys
were better than that.
You sonofabitch.
You're Here dead man Montel.
You hear me?
You're a dead man.
[birds chirping]
Come on.
Well, looks like
we're going to need
a new school bus after all.
Yeah, but you're
still buying the beer.
Yeah.
Come on, let's go.
Face it.
He got away.
He'll be here.
Come on.
We gotta move.
Was there anyone back there?
No.
They probably already left.
Well, come on, let's go.
Where you going?
My house.
It's about a mile that way.
[gunshot]
Run little bunnies.
Have your fun.
[ominous music]
Well, what's going on?
Not only did we miss Montel,
but they've multiplied.
There's four of them now.
They picked up two punks
I ran into earlier.
Which way did they go?
Due south.
Now come on.
We'll go and head'em off.
No, we'll pick
up the girl first.
What for?
Trust me.
Let's go boys.
[eagle screeching]
[engine starting]
So you ever pose
for any pictures?
You know, if it was up
to me, I'd let you go.
Why are you doing this?
Because it's important to us.
But you-- you kill
innocent people.
No one is innocent as
far as I'm concerned,
Well, then why
would you let me go?
Because you're
cute, not innocent.
Maybe later what's up?
Grab the girl.
Let's go.
Come on.
You heard the man.
Let's go for a little ride.
[HEAVY BREATHING AND RUNNING
FOOTSTEPS]
Alex, I'm going to need
a doctor for this wound.
It's getting pretty bad.
Hey, help him out.
There's a first aid
kit under the sink.
So what didn't you run?
I will.
It just isn't time yet.
What if you don't
get another chance?
I'm willing to take that risk.
You like this kind
of shit, don't you?
DAVID MONTEL: I live
for this kind of shit.
Well, I guess if you
can get out of this
you can get out of anything.
You said it, not me.
Do I have to do
this myself or what?
Shut up and hand
me the first aid kit.
So ah-- so you don't know
where they might have went,
huh, Sunshine?
I bet I could get her to talk.
I bet I could get her to moan.
What do you say West?
We'll find those guys.
What do you say we have
some fun before we go.
[birds chirping]
Maybe later.
Right now we work.
Listen up.
I want every available
man except the road blocks
to head due north through town.
Over.
[suspenseful music]
I found something to eat.
How can you think about
food at a time like this?
He's a pro, remember?
No, I'm just hungry.
I've got a plan.
Oh, I'd say so.
How much of this
stuff do you have?
Don't worry, he's got a
for a whole fucking army.
Good.
Because I've got a feeling
that's exactly what
we're up against.
ALEX: Follow me.
[suspenseful music]
Holy shit.
What is all this stuff?
Heaven, baby, heaven.
So what's your plan?
ALEX: Well, this is it.
We load up and go blow
the hell out of them.
Ah, it's a pretty shitty plan.
ALEX: Hey, you're the one
that pulled the kamikaze stunt
with the bus.
We're alive now, right?
Listen, no matter how
many guns we've got,
we can only take two a piece.
And that's not
going to be enough.
Look, they we're tracking
us, which means they're
probably on their way here now.
Exactly.
So we dig in here.
We can use the 50
caliber to hold'em off.
Well, let's get it.
Put a gun and a
whole box of shelves
next to every window
in the house in case
we have to retreat there.
And what are you going
to be doing, cowboy?
I'm going to make
sure they find us.
And how do you think
you're going to do that?
I'm a pro, remember?
Yeah.
Just be ready for'em.
Oh, we'll be ready.
I hope so.
ALEX: Hey, here's a flare.
That should get some attention.
I suppose you have
a tank in your garage.
Not yet, but
I'm working on it.
[birds chirping]
[suspenseful music]
DAVID MONTEL: Mr.
West, there you are.
I could drop you right now.
But that would be much too easy.
[suspenseful music]
DETECTIVE WEST: Did
you see anything?
AGENT CARTER: There's
a house and a junkyard
about a mile up the road.
DETECTIVE WEST:
Well, Sunshine, is
that where your boyfriends are?
SARAH: No.
ROBERTSON: Her mouth says no,
but her eyes say yes, yes, yes.
DETECTIVE WEST: For the
first time in your life,
I think you're right.
Take us there.
OK, everybody, listen up.
This is where we're going.
[suspenseful music]
[birds chirping]
AGENT CARTER: Look,
there's a flare.
ROBERTSON: It must be them
trying to signal for help.
So let's go help them.
That's too soon.
Something's wrong.
Hey Alex.
Alex.
- What's up?
It's too soon.
He shot the flare off.
He's not calling them.
He's calling us.
- What?
They must be
right on top of us.
You got that thing ready?
Yeah, I got it.
So what's the deal?
The party's about to start.
Let's go.
[funky guitar music]
DETECTIVE WEST:
Pearson you move East.
Larson you go West.
Move in around the back.
The rest of you
boys come with me.
[twangy guitar picking]
[birds chirping]
[suspenseful music]
You want to come
with us, sweetheart?
[suspenseful music]
DETECTIVE WEST: Spread out boys.
ROBERTSON: There they are.
Up the hill by the trailer.
[suspenseful music]
These hicks will be dead soon.
Well, don't be so sure.
These hicks ain't as
dumb as they look.
I'm shaking in my boots.
Yeah, well, maybe
you should be.
You already
missed'em once today.
Makes the hunting
more exciting.
What makes you think Montel
is even still with these guys?
Yeah, he's still here.
He wouldn't miss
this for the world.
Neither would I.
[suspenseful music]
Jesus.
How many do you
think there are?
There's no way of telling.
I used to hate these things.
Well, don't worry.
It's going to be your
best friend real soon.
[suspenseful music]
Bring the girl out.
Every good card
player keeps an ace.
[suspenseful music]
There's no one in the house.
They're all up there.
Get her over there
where they can see her.
Oh, shit, they got Sarah.
Hey, they got Sarah.
Shit.
It's Sarah.
They've got Sarah.
What are we going to do?
We just want
what belongs to us.
[birds chirping]
You give us Montel.
We'll give you the girl.
Shit.
He did it.
He did what?
Don't you see?
He set this up perfect.
He left us here alone to
kill each other while he's
on his way out of town.
Oh, God, how could
I be so stupid.
Look, they've got Sarah.
So what are we going to do?
We're just going
to have to bluff.
We're going to have to
say we got Montel up here.
And then what?
I don't know.
We'll just deal with
that when the time comes.
I know you boys are up there.
So why don't you make it
easy on all of us, huh?
Can't get away.
Let the girl go.
Now, that's more like it.
Now you send Montel out first.
No, you let the girl go
and come up the hill alone.
Then we'll give you Montel.
Well, I'm sorry I--
I can't do that.
But I can do this.
[suspenseful music]
Cut her.
[rifle shot]
[guitar rock and rapid gunfire]
[birds chirping]
[soft suspenseful music]
[gunshot]
[guitar rock and rapid gunfire]
Well now, if it
isn't hillbilly Bob.
Didn't anyone ever tell
you to watch your back?
I only winged you before.
Like a good hunter, I've tracked
you down to finish the job.
You guys are fucking crazy.
You're never going to
get away with this.
Well, you're half right.
I'd say we're
all the way right.
You have the guts
to pull the trigger.
I'm not going to have to.
[rapid gunfire]
Where's the girl?
I thought Thompson had her.
This is just right.
These guys are
fucking killing us.
Do they have a
fucking army in there?
Come on.
It ain't over till it's over.
Well, maybe it's over.
[birds chirping]
Go get the rocket launcher.
Right.
[birds chirping]
[rapid gunfire]
[grenade explosion]
Cover me, I'm going in.
Go.
[rapid gunfire]
[fire crackling]
[shotgun fire]
[rapid gunfire]
[suspenseful music]
[shot gun cocking]
[rifle shot]
[twangy guitar music]
[birds chirping]
Level that damn place.
Alex.
Yeah?
We gotta move now.
[birds chirping]
[large explosion]
How many do think are left?
I don't know.
But we better watch
the back of the house.
Well, let's go.
No, you stay here.
Watch the window.
Let's go.
[suspenseful music]
[loud thump]
They must be in the house.
I'll go check it out.
OK.
[suspenseful music]
[door squeaks]
No, no, don't shoot.
ALEX: Oh, God, Sarah.
Come on, somebody's
in the house.
Let's go.
- Shit.
Well, what about Alex?
- I don't know.
Let's go.
Oh, how touching.
He's not here.
The guy you're looking
for is not here.
I'd say it's going a little
past that, wouldn't you?
Let's take a little walk.
[birds chirping]
Hey bubs.
Now why don't you boys
put those guns down.
Tell me where Montel is.
- He escaped.
[birds chirping]
[gunshot]
Ah, ah, ah.
Oh.
Why don't we try
this one more time?
Ah, ah.
Where's Montel?
[gunshot]
[ominous music]
[birds chirping]
Here I am, West.
What now?
[birds chirping]
What do you say we
make a deal, all of us.
[birds chirping]
Like what?
You come over here unarmed.
And we fight man to man.
The winner walks away clean.
[birds chirping]
[crows cawing]
What do you say, Phil?
You really don't have
much of a choice.
You're a crazy
sonofabitch, you know that?
Let him go.
Let's settle this like men.
[ominous music]
[birds chirping]
[crows cawing]
[suspenseful music]
[birds chirping]
[crows cawing]
[suspenseful music]
Let's do it.
[birds chirping]
[suspenseful music]
What the fuck is this?
You trusted a
professional assassin?
You're dumber than you look.
[birds chirping]
Whatever happened to honor?
The only honor in a
game like this is winning.
[gunshots]
[birds chirping]
Freeze Montel.
Oh, ho, ho.
You've got to be kidding.
I wish I was.
[crows cawing]
I'm going to turn and
walk out of this town.
And you're going to let me.
Don't make me
shoot you, Montel.
You won't.
That's the difference
in me and you.
You've got a badge and oath
that keeps you from shooting
a man in the back.
I wish at times I did.
[music with drums playing]
I'll be seeing you.
Shit.
[music with drums playing]
Well, I got you off the
hook on the weapons charges.
You have to get a
collector's license, though.
Thanks Phil.
SGT. PHIL TOWERS: No problem.
So what's next for you?
I guess I'm going to
have to go after Montel.
Well, just as long as you
do it in some other town.
Well, hey, you keep that 50
caliber loaded just in case.
I'll see you guys.
Take care.
Bye bye.
Something tells
me he's not kidding.
I suppose you still want
to go hunting, don't you?
Alex, just shut
up, just shut up.
[music playing]
[birds chirping]
[dogs barking]
[music playing]
[MUSIC - RON DI
IULIO, "ARMED FOR
ACTION"] Running to
the edge of tomorrow
with nothing to hold on to.
I'm hoping to be
the lucky one doing
what they said I couldn't do.
If anyone tries to hold
me back, well, it's
not going to work this time.
No, I won't stop and I
won't give up fighting
till I cross that line.
I'm armed for action,
it's a fatal attraction.
Got to keep on going
till I take a fall.
I'm armed for action,
it's a deadly attraction.
I won't slow down
till I give it my all.
I'm armed for action.
There's just no way that
you could slow me down.
Cause I'm leaving a trail
in this old lonely town.
You can talk all you want,
and you can give it a try.
But I won't give up
until the day I die.
In this time of twisted games it
takes so much to stick it out.
But I'm ready for anything
and no time to live in doubt.
I'm leaving the past behind
me and moving to another day.
I'm reaching for a desire
that you say is wrong.
Won't you listen to what I say.
I'm armed for action.
It's a fatal attraction.
Gotta keep on going
till I take a fall.
I'm armed for action
it's a deadly attraction.
I won't slow down
till I give it my all.
I'm armed for action.
JAKE: Jesus.
ALEX: Hey, what can I say?
I'm lucky at pool,
lucky at love.
JAKE: You know sometimes
you can be a real prick.
ALEX: Yeah.
[music playing]
DETECTIVE WEST: We're here on a
witness protection assignment.
We'd appreciate your help.
SHERIFF: Well, sure.
Ah, what's it all about?
AGENT CARTER: Sir,
you understand.
We have to have
your full support.
Our witness will be coming
through here in the next three
or four hours.
DETECTIVE WEST: You must
tell no one, absolutely no
one, not even your own men.
AGENT CARTER: Ah, how many
men are on duty today?
SHERIFF: Actually just me.
But I don't understand
what you want me to do.
[music playing]
LORI: Hi, I'm Lori.
I'll be your waitress today.
SGT. PHIL TOWERS:
Where's your bathroom?
LORI: Down to the left.
You guys are eating aren't ya?
DAVID MONTEL: Of
course we are, sugar.
SGT. PHIL TOWERS:
Come on, move it.
We'll be back in a minute.
[music playing]
[MUSIC - RON DI
IULIO, "ARMED FOR
ACTION"] I'm armed for action.
It's a fatal attraction.
I'm armed for action.
It's a deadly attraction.