- [Narrator] Tonight's
film is a dramatization
of private investigator
Kim Paris' account
of events surrounding
an actual murder case
and is based on her
recollections,
personal interviews, and
police reports.
Some composite characters
have been used
for dramatic purposes.
(tense music)
(gun firing)
(dog barking)
- Grandma, Grandpa!
(screaming)
(upbeat music)
- [Man On Radio] Kim?
Kim?
Paris, are you there?
- What?
- [Man On Radio] Nothing,
just checking to see
if you're awake.
- I'm awake, I'm ready,
and I'm waiting.
- She just left.
Okay, give it 10 minutes.
- 10 minutes?
No way.
I'll go nail him now.
- Kim, you've never done
this kind of thing before.
It's a $100,000 claim.
I got you the job.
If you blow it, I get the blame.
Damn it, Kim.
You gotta listen up.
- That's what I needed,
just what I needed.
If it isn't one thing
with cars, it's another.
I just had the carburetor,
whatever that is, rebuilt
and now I've got a flat tire.
Could that be connected?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Look, I just got a flat
tire and I'm on my way
to a modeling appointment
and I'm gonna be late.
Can I go in and use your
phone, call the service guy,
have him come out and
fix my tire?
- Why don't you
change it yourself?
I'd do it for you only
I hurt my neck.
I hurt my back, too.
- Oh, that's too bad.
- You're a model, right?
- Mm-hmm.
- Uh, hmm.
- Hell, but men are dumb.
- Okay, you just show
me what to do
because if I'm told what to
do, I can do mostly anything.
- Yeah?
Well, that's quite a thought.
(both laugh)
- There it is.
- You're gonna need a jack
and a lug wrench, too.
- It's pretty complicated,
isn't it?
- Nah.
Okay, just stand back.
It'll be a lot easier
if I just do it for you.
- Oh, are you sure?
What about your back,
and your neck, and all?
- Well, sometimes for a lady,
you gotta make a little
sacrifice, hmm?
- I am gonna watch and
see exactly how to do it.
(camera shutter clicking)
- Hell, I think a sight
like that's enough
to cure a fella of more
than whiplash.
You say she used to be a
topless dancer?
- She wasn't much use at that.
- Well, everybody likes
different things.
- She can't dance.
She doesn't have any rhythm.
- Is that a fact?
Oh, well.
So, that's that.
What else you got, Posey?
Tom, get me a pack
of cigarettes.
- Well, I think we ought
to draw a line
under the Campbell account,
Clyde.
We haven't come up with
anything in a month or more.
- I know how long we've been
taking their money, Posey.
I told them when they came to me
that murder cases
were slow movers.
It's been two years since
somebody shot the Campbells.
Houston Police Department
haven't come up with diddly.
- I spoke with Dan Halsey at the
police department the other day.
They're waiting for the
estate to get settled,
see where the money goes.
- [Clyde] Halsey couldn't find
his butt with a flashlight.
I thought you were
onto this fellow.
The boyfriend of Cindy Campbell.
What's his name?
- David West?
He gave Cindy her alibi.
- Where's the coffee?
- You didn't ask for coffee,
Clyde.
No problem, I'll get it.
- Campbell had some
pretty scuzzy clients
in his line of lawyering, Clyde.
It could've been one of them.
- Not what the family thought.
They think their little
sister Cindy did it.
- They think she killed
her own parents
with her two kids right
there in the room?
- That's why they hired us.
- Well, we can't get
anywhere near Cindy.
She's a recluse.
Never comes out.
- Cindy's holed up.
Is this David West
holed up with her?
- Uh-uh.
They split up.
- You could try Kim on it.
She's kind of flaky, you
know, but she's plenty smart.
- His name is David West.
This could be good.
He's some kind of gun freak.
You know, a survivalist.
Into that
bodybuilding macho stuff.
I'm gonna create a whole
new style just for this gig.
Yes, he won't know what hit him.
- I don't know.
I don't like the
sounds of this guy.
I mean, what's he supposed to
have done, murdered somebody?
(upbeat music)
- His ex-girlfriend's
parents got blown away.
Could've been anybody.
Maybe even a professional hit.
They just think he knows
something about it.
Once I fix my hair,
it'll be perfect.
(tense music)
- All right, it's the
white house.
He's not home, so you
might have to wait a while.
And remember, Kim.
It was me who suggested you for
this, so don't be too weird.
Now, you have to
remember everything
so that it doesn't trip
you up later.
Keep to the facts about
yourself as much as you can.
Where you were born, what
your father does, all that.
Don't...
Don't fantasize.
(Kim laughs)
You can tell him about
being in the Navy,
you can tell him about being
an air traffic controller,
and you can tell him
about the topless dancing,
and about the time you
were raped, if you have to.
- I don't wanna do that.
Why would I wanna do that?
- Yeah, well chances are, Kim.
- Call me Theresa.
Theresa McNeil.
- Yeah, right, Theresa.
Chances are, he's gonna
come onto you, right?
So, you're gonna want
to keep him off
without completely chilling him.
- Well, you know I know
how to do that.
- Yeah, okay.
But David West might be
as easy going as I am.
So, something like
what happened,
can explain why you're
not hot to trot.
- Last guy I told about that
dropped me like a stone.
Don't worry, Tom.
Theresa McNeil can take
care of herself.
(tense music)
- How is she?
- Think Clyde'll blame me
if she blows it?
- If she blows it,
what Clyde thinks will be
the least of our problems.
She's on her own out there.
- She'll be okay.
(car engine starts)
- Oh, I was in the Navy
for four years before this.
Were you now?
Yes, I was.
It's what brought me to Texas.
Corpus Christi, mainly.
Yeah, it's a fun town.
Air traffic controller.
Yep.
Yep, I was one of those.
Only woman among 50 guys.
You better believe I
got to know men.
No, I'm not anti-man,
I'm just tired of these
add-water-and-stir
relationships.
Love.
Love, love, love, love.
Love, have I ever been in love?
This is kind of a
personal question,
don't you think right
off the bat?
No, I'll answer it.
I'm just saying it's
kind of personal.
No, I've never been in love.
I love people, but in love?
No.
What's the difference?
(engine revving)
I don't know, but I bet
you when it happens,
you sure can tell.
(uptempo music)
- [Woman] Hey, let's party!
- Hi, I'm Theresa McNeil.
I'm Theresa McNeil.
(exhales sharply)
Hi.
- Hi.
- Is Charlie home?
- No.
- No?
You know when he'll be back?
- I don't think I
know any Charlie.
- [Kim] No?
Do you live here?
- (laughs) Yeah, I live here.
Charlie doesn't.
- Oh.
This is 3031 Franklin?
- [Man] That's right.
- Damn, I must've got the
address wrong.
Charlie Lockwood?
- I never heard of him.
- This is a real drag.
I drove all the way
across Houston.
You have a phone?
- (chuckles) I think so.
- Yeah, can I come
in and use it,
maybe save myself a wasted trip?
- Yeah, absolutely.
- Yeah, I'm here now.
Yeah.
Well, are you sure you
gave me the address right?
I'm telling ya.
No.
Never heard of Charlie Lockwood.
All right, it's 555-8624.
All right.
I can't sit here all night.
Yeah, bye.
- So, any luck with Chuck?
- I tell you, making a
decent connection's
a real hassle these days.
It was no problem at all when
I was down in Corpus Christi.
Great place.
- [Man] Yeah?
- [Kim] This yours?
- [Man] No.
I just got a room here.
The guy that owns it,
it's his trip.
- He some kind of Vietnam vet?
- He wishes.
He's into the whole, um...
I don't know, he's just
into thinking about
all that kind of stuff.
So, what are you
trying to score?
- Weed.
They're gonna call me back
if they can locate Charlie.
You mind if I wait here?
- Oh, no.
But I gotta go out in a minute.
I gotta hook up with Dave.
- [Kim] Oh, hey, I
don't wanna hold you up.
- Oh, no.
Listen, if you're
looking to score,
I can probably put you
in touch with somebody.
How much you wanna buy?
- Depends on the price.
- Of course it does.
So, you wanna come with me?
- No hassles, right?
- No, no hassles, right.
Jeez, I'm just gonna hook up
with Dave for his birthday.
- Oh, hey, that's great.
You can say I'm his present.
- Yeah, right.
(lighter flicking)
(people chattering)
(uptempo country music)
♪ Happy Birthday to you ♪
♪ Happy Birthday, dear David ♪
- [Man] Yeah, David!
♪ Happy Birthday to you ♪
(people cheering and applauding)
(uptempo country music)
(people chattering)
- So, you were an air traffic
controller in the Navy?
- Mm-hmm, two years.
I never lost a plane.
- You must've been just a kid.
- Yeah, well, I left
St. Louis when I was 17.
Ran away.
Joined the Navy so I
could get taken care of.
- So, what do you do now?
- Oh, I'm kinda between
gigs as they say in showbiz.
I live with my sister
Sammi and her old man.
My overhead's pretty low.
- You in love with anybody?
- That's kind of a personal
question, isn't it?
- Prefer that I ask you
impersonal questions?
Like, can you give me
a ride home?
- What, you don't have a car?
- I have a Trans Am, but it's
got a busted transmission.
I got a job that doesn't pay
enough for an oil change.
- Yeah?
Well, maybe your luck's
about to change.
- I don't believe in luck.
- Hey, how about that?
Neither do I.
- I have to talk to Steve, okay?
(engine revving)
- So, how come you don't
believe in luck?
- I just think everything
that goes to the trouble
of happening was inevitable.
I mean, you come up to
something in your life
some big decision you know
is gonna alter everything.
You think you made a choice,
but when you look back on it,
you see you did the only
thing you could've done.
- So, everything's
decided in advance?
That's what you're saying?
That's not much fun.
- Well, when you read a book,
see a movie,
everything's decided in advance,
but it's fun while
you're finding out.
Hey, turn here.
(tires squealing)
(car horns honking)
You drive like I think.
- I'm a great driver.
- That's what I said.
So, how come you left home
when you were so young?
- I was a difficult kid.
My father kept
getting on my case.
- Oh, tell me about it.
- Well, I remember the
night I left.
I was terrified, but I kinda
got myself backed into a place
I couldn't get out of, you know?
I'm like that.
Anyway, he was downstairs
watching television,
60 Minutes it was, and I brought
my bags down one at a time.
I pile 'em in front of
the front door, you know.
Last of all, I go get
my Snoopy dog.
I stick him right on
top of the pile.
I keep thinking he's gonna
turn around, you know,
and see it and say, Kim,
don't go.
- [David] Kim?
- He always called me by
my middle name, Kimberly.
I hate it.
- Well, that's probably why.
- Probably.
Anyways, he never did
turn around,
not even when the taxi came.
He just kept
watching 60 Minutes.
- Hey, it's hard going
up against Andy Rooney.
(laughs)
This is my street.
- Here?
(tires squeal)
There you are.
You're free to go.
- So, what's this all about?
- What's this all about?
Haven't you ever picked
up a girl in a bar before?
- I'd have said it was
you who picked me up.
- [Kim] So, are you saying
that's never happened to you?
- Often enough to know it
doesn't feel like this.
- I'm not into these
just-add-water-and-stir
relationships.
- Neither am I.
Am I gonna see you again?
- How about same time,
same place tomorrow night?
- Well, we're gonna have
to be more straightforward,
Theresa, if this
relationship's gonna work.
Tomorrow.
- Tomorrow.
- So, do you have to sleep
with him or anything?
- Undercover doesn't mean you
have to get under the covers.
- Yeah, but don't you have to,
like,
taunt him with your
body until he confesses?
- Who says he has
anything to confess?
- Well, how come they're
paying you to date him then?
- I'm not dating him.
- I thought you were
seeing him tomorrow night.
- Mm-hmm.
Same time, same place.
- Hmm.
Sounds like a duck to me.
Now, come on, Kim.
Is he cute?
- Ask Theresa McNeil.
- [Sammi] Who's Theresa McNeil?
- [Kim] That's the
name I'm using.
- Now, wait a minute.
I thought you was
calling yourself...
Who's that girl,
Denise something?
That girl from the
insurance scam.
- Denise Donnelly was
totally helpless.
She couldn't change a flat tire.
Denise Donnelly is not the type
David West would be
interested in.
- What is the type David
West would be interested in?
- Well, now there's the trick,
Sammi.
First, I have to find that out.
Then, I have to become her.
(laughing)
(people chattering)
(uptempo country music)
- Excuse me, I'll be right back.
Kim?
Kim Paris.
Billy Curtis.
Corpus Christi?
Launch commander's office.
Don't you remember?
Hey, it's me.
Hey, we went out and got
drunk that night.
We had a great time.
You remember, Billy Curtis.
- Would you get your
hands off me, huh?
I mean, that's enough, you know?
God.
- You all right?
- Yeah, that guy
just grabbed me.
- Come on, let's go.
- Hey, wait a minute.
- I think a minute
would be too long.
- I just wanted to say hello,
okay?
- Consider it said.
- Yeah.
Yeah.
- Oh, put it out of your mind.
Let him deal with it.
- Maybe I overreacted.
- Don't apologize for
how you feel.
Don't look for trouble,
but don't walk away.
Some people see something
they don't like and they say,
that's wrong, and they
look down at their feet,
and shuffle 'em around,
and walk away.
I don't do that.
- You're a pretty tough
dude then, huh?
- No, I just see things through.
- I need a beer.
Can I have a beer?
The reason that I was
late is that Sonny,
my sister Sammi's husband,
he's kind of strict.
I couldn't tell him I
was coming to see you.
- Now, why's he strict with you?
You're not his wife.
- He's possessive.
You know, it's that
family kind of thing.
- Sounds like he's mafia.
- You must be clairvoyant.
He is kind of mixed up
in that kind of thing.
Does that bother you?
- No.
I had a girlfriend whose
father was a lawyer
for all kinds of lowlifes.
He didn't like Cindy going out
or having a life of her own.
Just like your sister's
husband Sonny.
- Well, he was her father.
Maybe he cared about her.
- Yeah, maybe.
- Sonny's not that bad.
Sometimes it helps to
have a man look after you.
How does your friend and
her father get on now?
- He got killed in a car crash.
Mother, too.
- Oh.
- So things worked
out just fine.
- [Kim] Oh, that's awful.
- The Campbells were
nicer people dead.
- David, what a
terrible thing to say.
- Yeah, it is.
But the Campbells were
terrible people.
All of their kids got
severely screwed up by 'em.
- Even your friend?
What was her name, Cindy?
- Oh, especially Cindy.
Cindy almost didn't make it.
- Was she in the car
when it happened?
- No.
No, I was with her when
she got the news.
- Are you and she still close?
- No.
No, after Cindy lost her
parents, things changed.
We don't see each other anymore.
It's all in the past.
I want you to know that.
- Hey, if you say so.
- No, I want you to believe me.
- I do.
I do believe you.
- Good.
Good.
I want things to be straight
between us, Theresa.
- [Kim] You may have to find
your own way home, okay?
- [Sammi] Oh, all right.
- [Kim] Now remember,
you and Sonny are only
married six months.
- [Sammi] His name is Sonny?
- [Kim] Yeah, he's very
old fashioned about stuff.
- [Sammi] What does he
care whether my husband's
old fashioned or not?
- [Kim] I told David he won't
let me get calls from guys
because I don't want him
to have my telephone number
and know that we live in
the same area.
I told him I live all the
way across town.
- What happens if you run
into him at the laundromat?
- I'm gonna take our clothes
to one of those places
where they do 'em for you
and then I'm gonna put
it on my expense account.
- You can do that?
- Deep cover costs, kid.
Now remember, don't blow it,
okay?
'Cause my name is Theresa.
- You think I am so stupid
I can't remember a name.
- Hey, cut down the Texas draw,
okay?
You're supposed to be
my older sister.
- I am not older than you.
- Don't be confused.
It's just a cover story.
- I'm not the one who's
getting confused.
- So, how come you
didn't run away from home
and join the Navy?
- Couldn't stand all that
yes, sir, no, sir stuff.
- Sammi was always
Daddy's favorite.
He taught her how to play pool.
- Dad's a real hustler, huh?
Amazing the way parents
operate on kids
and kids on each other.
Seen a lot of those
kind of games,
putting one kid
against the other.
- A dollar she makes it.
- You're on.
- Do you mind?
- $2.
- You're on.
- Oh.
Nah, I put her off.
She's really good.
Daddy used to make us play
all the time for money.
- I feel like I know him
without ever having met him.
- Kim exaggerates everything.
(suspenseful music)
- How come you still call her
by your father's pet name?
Suggests to me you
haven't accepted Theresa
for who she really is.
Want a little bet on this one,
Sammi?
Remind you of childhood.
- Five bucks a game,
best of 10, loser breaks.
- It's what Daddy liked to bet.
- Shoot pool, big sister.
(pool balls clacking)
You hustled me, didn't you?
- Well, kind of.
You mind?
(both laugh)
- You're pretty smooth.
I like that.
You take care of Theresa,
can't you?
- [Kim] Yeah.
- You're not looking for
somebody else to do it for you.
- Is that how it was with Cindy?
- Something like that.
(engine revving)
(subdued music)
- Of course, if you don't
want to talk about it.
- You coming in?
- David, I'm not ready
for a physical thing.
It's not you.
It's something that happened.
- You don't have to explain.
It's okay.
You don't have to worry.
I don't want what you
don't want to give.
- [Kim] Some place.
You a survivalist, or what?
- [David] (laughs) Well,
I'm surviving so far.
- And that's enough for you.
- Hey, don't knock it
till you try it.
You go from home, to the Navy,
to living with your sister.
That's not taking too
many chances.
- And you, too.
- I live every day like
someone's sneaking up behind me.
So, I practice every day
sneaking up behind them.
Cheers.
- So, were you very
much in love with Cindy?
- Whoa, you don't give up,
do you?
- [Kim] No, sir.
- I created Cynthia,
or I tried to.
I was in love with what
she was gonna become.
- [Kim] Doesn't
sound too loving.
- When I first met Cindy,
she weighed about 200 pounds,
had greasy hair, complexion
like a glazed donut,
and a nose like Pinocchio.
She hated herself.
I didn't blame her.
- [Kim] So, why were you
attracted to her?
- 'Cause I could feel the
pain coming off her in waves.
She was like
radioactive with it.
And I was interested in
why this ugly, fat chick
was just so totally screwed up.
- [Kim] Did you ask her?
- Sure.
I said, how come a fat,
ugly chick like you
is so totally screwed up?
- [Kim] What did she say?
- Well, she said a
lot of things,
but in the end it all
came down to one thing.
Somebody was putting her down
and that person was Cindy.
- [Kim] You said her father was
terrible to her or something?
- Her mother wasn't much better.
But you can't blame
everything on your parents.
It just doesn't solve
your problems.
I told her, quit complaining.
You're just giving away
your power to the past.
So, I got her to stop
eating the crap she ate
and got her to start
exercising, reading books,
you know, to clean out her mind.
Put her in touch with her gift.
She was a natural psychic.
She didn't know it.
She knew stuff before
it happened,
but she never figured why.
I even got her to get
her nose fixed.
Turned out pretty good.
- [Kim] And were you
in love with her then?
- I was trying to make her
into somebody like you,
but I just didn't have
the blueprint.
- Well, there's only one
of those and I have it.
- I know.
I know.
(subdued music)
- David is a person of
deep feelings
and considerable sensitivity.
He has expressed a remarkable
degree of affection for me
and indeed may be in the process
of falling in love with me.
Now listen.
This is the one time, first
and last, I'm telling you.
This client isn't paying
for you to get
jugged up every night with
some sleazeball
that's so hot to trot that
he tells you he loves you.
If you think he's keeping
something hidden
about the Campbell
killings, that's one thing.
But I don't wanna hear
anything more
about this Dear Abby soap opera.
(hand slams)
- Aw, to hell with them
and their agency.
I survived before this,
I'll survive after it.
They're all so damn scared
of the old tone, you know?
They all think they're the ones
who know how to handle this.
I am the only one who could've
got this close to David.
Don't they get that?
- You love it.
You just love it.
All this playacting.
Miss Undercover, USA.
- What is your problem?
- You love making up lies.
You love believing 'em.
- You're supposed to
be my friend.
I don't need this from you.
- I am your friend
and I know you
which is more than you
do right now.
You're getting involved
with this creep, aren't you?
- How do you know he's a creep?
You hustled him at pool,
that's what you know.
You don't know what it's
like being somebody else,
being seen as somebody else,
feeling like somebody else.
- Answer the question, Kim.
- You promised to
call me Theresa.
- Answer the question, Theresa.
- That's the way it works
for me and it's working.
I'm getting close to him.
- You slept with him yet?
- No, I haven't.
And he hasn't pushed me, either.
He--
- Oh, respects you.
- Yeah, as a matter of fact.
I think he does.
- Aw, sweet.
(tense music)
- David?
David?
David, you here?
David, it's me.
(knocks on door)
(dramatic music)
- Bang-bang.
(Kim yells)
- Damn it, David.
Don't do that.
Don't ever do that.
- You didn't hear me coming,
did you?
- I think that sort
of thing sucks.
- I'm not gonna hurt you.
- How do I know that?
- Why?
Why do you think I
might hurt you?
- I...
It's not you.
- Well, who is it?
- You scared me, okay?
Fine, all right?
You scared me.
- There's something you're
not telling me, Theresa.
You can tell me anything.
- About a year ago, I was raped.
It was partly my fault.
(subdued music)
I ran out of gas, and I
was walking to get some,
and a car came by.
It was kind of in the country.
Two guys were in it.
They asked me if I
wanted a lift, I said no.
They said it was a couple
miles to the next gas station.
He said, "What's the
matter, don't you trust us?"
I said it wasn't that,
but I'd walk anyway.
I was too close to the car.
He grabbed my wrist and
they drove off.
I had to run alongside.
After a bit, I fell down.
They stopped the car and
pulled me inside.
- Well, that wasn't your fault.
- I don't know.
Dumb of me.
- To run out of gas?
- Yeah.
I'm always doing dumb
things like that.
- Rape isn't a punishment for
running out of gas, Theresa.
Not even in Texas.
- Then why?
Why did it happen?
(Kim sobbing)
- Because it is an awful
world we're in.
I won't ever let that
happen to you again.
Never.
Never, never, never.
- [Man] George, give me five
of these, will you please?
(coin clanks)
- I want a tuna melt on
rye and some iced tea.
The money...
(fist pounding)
Gummit.
The money's in my coat.
- I'm buying.
- Well, well.
If it ain't Sam Spade
come a slummin'
in his 500 buck threads.
Tell me, Posey.
How is the private enterprise
law enforcement business?
- Well, it's up to taking
you to lunch, Halsey.
- Yeah?
Well, ain't that nice.
I can't help it, Posey.
I'm just not very partial
to private detectives.
- That include me?
- Oh, no.
You know I got a
little soft spot
in my heart for you, Posey.
I guess it's on
account of that name
you had to grow up with.
Posey, Posey.
How come you never changed it?
- [Posey] You play the
cards you get, Dan.
You play the cards you get.
- No, don't give me that bull.
Next thing you'll tell me
is it made a man out of you.
- Oh, no.
I wouldn't go that far.
(both laugh)
Dan, we've been working
on the Campbell case.
I suppose you heard?
On behalf of the family.
- [Dan] What's that
costing the sucker?
- Well, they thought the
Houston Police Department
had kind of quit on 'em.
- Hey, hey, hey.
You get a guy that
that many people
got a motive for killing,
you either get lucky
or you either get slow.
- Yeah.
Well, we're working the
David West angle.
- David West.
Good luck, Posey.
I spent a long time trying
to break that alibi.
- Yeah, well, we've
got a girl next to him.
Her name's Kim Paris.
She's, well...
Well, she's kind of flaky,
but she's got her
hooks into West.
The only thing is, Clyde
doesn't take her seriously.
- So?
- Well, you know the case.
You know West.
I thought maybe you
could talk to her
and see if you could
figure out what she's got.
She's kind of exposed out there.
- What's in it for me?
- Apple pie.
- A la mode?
- One scoop.
All right, bring her by.
- All right.
Louise?
- Okay, now I recommended
you with the agency.
You're gonna have to tell me
if you're getting anywhere.
- Listen, listen.
I got a great idea.
David is a believer in
psychic stuff.
Cindy was psychic.
- Nevermind about the psychic.
Just tell me if you're
getting anyplace.
- Will you just listen to me,
Tom?
Okay, I'm gonna tell David
that I've had this dream,
like he's in danger, you know?
And then the next time
that I go and pick him up,
you drive by and you fire a gun.
Not at us, but I mean
like in the air, okay?
And then he'll think I
have it, really have it.
- This is crazy.
This is...
This is really crazy.
You didn't put this in
your report, did you?
- Hey, it was just an idea.
I'm just trying to be creative.
- It sounds like you're
desperate to me.
- Maybe I should be taping it.
(horn honks)
- Theresa.
- David.
It's David.
You play along with me,
all right?
Hi.
- How are you?
Hey, look at you.
- I look awful.
- You do not.
- This is my
brother-in-law Sonny.
- Well, hello, Sonny.
Theresa told me about you.
- Oh, yeah?
Yeah, she mentioned you.
- Great.
Hey, how about you and your
wife having dinner some night
with me and Theresa
over at my place?
- Oh, Sammi would love that.
You know how she loves to
go out, Sonny.
- I fix a pretty good
Mongolian lamb.
How about Saturday?
- Saturday?
Uh.
- I think Saturday
would be fine.
- [Tom] I don't know.
- [Kim] I'll work on him.
- Saturday.
Hey.
Well, good.
Nice to meet you.
Saturday it is.
(engine starts)
- [Kim] Bye, David!
See you Saturday!
- Damn it, you are careless,
Kim.
We should not have
been out here.
- I thought that worked
out pretty good, Sonny.
- What is this
brother-in-law crap?
- That's what I told him why I
can't invite him to my house.
I live with this pig of
a brother-in-law Sonny.
You'll be perfect, huh?
- No, no.
No, I am absolutely not
going to dinner
pretending to be some hood.
- You gonna blow my cover, Tom?
Is that what you want, huh?
If I tell Clyde that
you can't pull it off,
he won't let you fetch
his cigarettes anymore.
(Kim laughs)
- [Tom] Kim.
- Don't forget, Sammi.
You're different when
you're around Sonny.
You're quiet, subdued.
- Where'd you come up
with this mafia?
What was the idea of that?
- Well, didn't you say that
the Campbell murders were like,
you know, executions,
like professional?
- Yeah.
- Okay, so maybe Cindy had
somebody hire some hitmen.
Maybe David is the one who
did the hiring.
Did you ever think of that?
- This is crazy.
It's absolutely crazy.
Crazy, Kim.
- Theresa, Theresa.
You gotta remember to
call her Theresa.
- Hey, would you watch your
mouth when you're talking to me?
You're gonna end up
with cement shoes.
(laughing)
- This is never gonna work, Kim.
I mean, Theresa.
This is never gonna work.
(laughs) No.
- I don't believe in free will.
I mean, it looks like you
have a choice,
but when you examine,
really examine it,
you see one thing leads to
another the only way it could've.
I mean, all history's inevitable
'cause it goes through
the trouble of happening.
May sound kind of fatalist.
- [Tom] Sounds dumb.
That's what it sounds like.
- You believe in free will then?
- Oh, nothing's free,
including this dinner.
- Now, what price do
you see yourself
paying for this dinner?
- Well, I gotta sit here
and listen to you go on
about all this stuff you
don't know nothing about.
Why don't you two broads
go powder something?
- [Sammi] Sonny.
- [Tom] Go on, beat it.
- You certainly have a way
with the ladies, Sonny.
- West, don't use
sarcasm with me.
It ain't gonna work.
What I want to know
about is what you
have in mind with my
sister-in-law.
- I intend to marry Theresa.
I respect your position,
your feelings,
and how you're
protective about her,
but I'm gonna take care of her.
Now, this house is my
property and I can fix it up
and get a very good price.
Theresa and me didn't have any
choice but to meet each other
and we have no choice but to
keep on knowing each other.
I don't know how it is
with you and Sammi,
but that's how it is with
Theresa and me.
- We'll be out in the car, okay?
Oh, and thank you, David.
Goodnight.
Theresa will join us
in a moment.
That guy's nuts.
He did it, I really
think he did it.
- Uh-uh.
No way.
- What do you mean no way?
- Oh, he's out to lunch all
right, but not that way.
Want to know what he told me?
- What?
- He wants to marry her.
- Oh, my god.
- Oh, yeah.
You wanna know what else?
- What?
- They have no choice, he says.
- No choice.
- David, shouldn't you
have asked, well,
spoken to me before you
spoke to him?
- I don't think I did
anything wrong.
I love you, Theresa.
- I know, but what I'm saying
is shouldn't you have--
- Do you?
Do you really know?
Do you really know I love you?
I wanna marry you.
When I have to, I can
get things done.
I do not intend to
deliver blueprints
for the rest of my life.
Take this house, fix it up,
and sell it.
We can do whatever we
want to do with the money.
Have a life, family.
You and me.
(water rushing)
- He asked me to marry him,
Sammi.
Isn't that something?
I mean, a lot of guys
have hit on me,
but the first time I get the
white picket fence proposal
and I'm pretending to be
somebody else.
- Kim, why don't you just
forget this whole thing?
- What, tell him I changed
my name to Kim Paris
and you got divorced from Sonny?
- You don't have to
tell him anything.
Not a thing.
We could just split.
I'm not exactly
doing great here.
- Mm-mm.
- You're getting serious about
this guy, aren't you, Kim?
Aren't you?
- Kim isn't.
I'm not so sure about Theresa.
(people chattering)
Excuse me.
Watch it.
(metal banging)
Do you know where
Sergeant Halsey is?
Halsey.
- Halsey, he's banging on
that typewriter over there.
That's right.
You're quite welcome.
- [Dan] Piece of junk.
- Sergeant Halsey, Kim Paris
from the Clyde Wilson Agency.
How do you want me, sitting,
standing?
- I don't know if I
want you at all.
All right, all right.
What do you got on David West?
- I think he knows a
lot about Cindy Campbell
and about her parents.
- Well, no kidding.
That couldn't be because
he was shacked up with her
for two years, now could it?
- He lied to me about the way
the Campbells were killed.
He said they were
better people dead.
- Did he tell you who shot 'em?
- [Kim] No.
No, he didn't say
anything like that.
- Well, what do you think?
What do you think?
- Me?
- Yeah, you, Miss Private Eye.
What is your
professional opinion?
- I don't know.
I don't think that David.
- Well, let me ask you this.
How long have you been
shacked up with David West?
- I'm not shacked up
with David West.
- I hear tell that he
wants to marry you.
Now, why would a weirdo
like David West
want to marry you, Ms. Paris?
- I think he's in love with me.
- Oh, in love.
Oh, well sure.
Now, I see.
In order to prove his
love to you,
he's gonna confess to
the Campbell murders.
Is that it?
Okay.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Okay, okay.
So he's not sleeping with you.
You're not sleeping with him.
Why not?
- Because I don't want to.
- [Dan] Oh, and what does
he have to say about that?
Wait a minute.
Has he got you pegged for some
kind of virgin or something?
- I don't know why you're
talking to me like this.
- Oh, you don't.
- [Kim] No.
- Well, I'll tell you why,
darling.
Because I'm a cop and
I don't trust
private detectives in general
and I don't trust Clyde
Wilson in particular.
And I especially don't like
it when he sticks some bimbo
out on the street who thinks
that all she has to do
is flash a little skin and
she can get a confession
out of every punk that
she comes across!
- [Man] Go, go, yeah.
(people applauding)
- Well, that'll teach her, Dan.
Coming in trying to
cooperate with the police.
- [Dan] Butt out.
- Hey, hey.
You don't need this
stinking job.
I mean, it's Looney Tunes.
You don't even know
what your name is.
Quit the case.
- Well, what am I gonna
do about David?
I can't just run out on him.
(pan clatters)
- Run out on him?
What is the matter with you,
Kim?
You'd be doing him 50
different kinds of a favor
if you ran out on him.
You've been lying to that boy
since the day you met him.
- That's not true.
That's not all true.
God, Sammi.
What am I gonna do?
- How about tell him the truth,
Kim?
What would be wrong with that?
(subdued music)
- [David] I talked to a real
estate lady about the house.
She said with a little fixing up
I could get maybe 60,
65 grand for it.
Hey, what's wrong?
Look at me.
Talk to me.
You can talk to me.
- David, I have to go
away for a while.
- [David] I think we should.
I think we should go to Mexico.
The way the peso is, we could
live there good a long time.
I know guys who've done that.
- No, I mean on my own.
- [David] Why do you
have to do that?
- I just do.
I have to get things straight.
- What's not straight?
Is this about Cindy?
I told you there's nothing
between Cindy and me.
It is over.
Oh, trust me.
There are a lot of things
I wanna talk to you about
and have you understand.
But I need you to, you know,
make some kind of a commitment.
- No, I can't.
Not now, not yet.
I need time.
- But what if you go away and
I never hear from you again?
- You will.
I wouldn't do that.
- I love you, Theresa.
Why do you have to go away?
- David, you have to believe me.
I'm all confused about things.
My feelings, who I am,
all kinds of things.
I gotta get things straight.
I just, I have to.
- All right.
All right.
Well, when you're
figuring all this out,
just remember I love you.
(subdued music)
- And I love you.
- Oh, then why do you
have to go away?
- I don't know.
I don't know.
- So, did you do it?
Did you tell him?
- I said...
I said that I loved him, Sammi.
I couldn't help myself.
- Well, you better start,
Kim, 'cause you got company
and I don't think
they're here to help you.
- So, how come all of a
sudden this jerk believes me?
- [Posey] Well, Sergeant
Halsey was just
testing you first time, Kim.
- No, he wasn't testing me.
He was insulting me
and he was enjoying it.
- Yeah, I was a little
rough on you, Ms. Paris.
Just one of those bad days,
you know?
- Ms. Paris.
- Thing is, Kim.
You're the best thing
they've got.
The Campbell case has
been on hold--
- No such thing.
We've been waiting for the
Campbell will to be probated.
Now, as soon as they
divide up the estate,
we'll follow the money, see if
any of it goes to David West.
- Which could take a
year or more.
In the meantime, you are
the only thing they've got,
no matter what
Sergeant Halsey says.
And the reason he's here now,
is that he can set you
up with a wire.
See what you can get
out of David.
- You want me to record him?
- Well, as I recall,
you thought that you
could get West to talk.
You know, on account of
him being in love with you
and you never having
slept with him.
- Kim, don't let him talk
to you that way.
- Most likely be a waste
of your time and mine, too.
Unless you really got
something going with this guy.
Course, you're the only
one who'd know about that.
So, do you or don't you?
Tell me you do.
I'll believe you.
- Yeah, I got something going.
- [Dan] Okay, now you gotta
push both of these down
for it to record.
- [Kim] Mm-hmm.
- Are you listening to me?
You gotta push both of
'em down, all right?
Now, here.
You gotta make sure the
microphone stays in the clear.
All right, all right, let's go.
Say something.
- Sergeant Halsey is a pig.
- How's that?
- [Man On Radio] Repeating,
Sergeant Halsey is a pig.
- All right, let's go.
Come on.
Now remember, it's no good
if you do all the talking.
He can't just sit there
and yes and no ya.
You understand?
It's gotta come out
of his mouth.
It's gotta be in his words.
- Of course.
Do you think I'm trying
to frame him?
- I'm just explaining.
- Kim, we'll be here
just in case.
- In case of what?
I don't have anything to
fear from David.
He's the one that's in danger.
(subdued music)
(car horn honks)
(car horn honking)
(tires squealing)
- Remind me to have her license
revoked after this is over.
This is Halsey, you
guys hanging in?
- [Man On Radio] Hanging in,
Sergeant.
Hanging in.
(exhaling rapidly)
- Hey, Dave.
What's the idea behind all
that stuff you're doing?
I mean, I see these old
Chinese guys on the TV
going after it and they just
look like they're trying
to hack their way through
some kind of imaginary jungle.
- That's exactly it, Steve.
System for getting
through the jungle.
And this teaches you
how to stay in the now.
The big now, no past, no future.
That's how you survive
in the jungle.
- [Steve] Wow, man.
That's pretty deep.
You ought to write
fortune cookies.
Hey, Theresa.
- [David] Theresa.
- [Steve] You should've
been here, man.
It was a real
learning experience.
- It's so good to see you.
I didn't know when you'd
get it straightened out.
- David, we have to talk.
- What's wrong?
- I'm in the big now, man.
- [Dan] Jimmy.
- Hey, man.
Signal's clean.
- Okay, good.
Sit over here.
- What's wrong?
Tell me what it is.
- David, why did you lie to me?
- What about?
- About Cindy's parents.
They weren't killed in
a car accident.
- How were they killed?
- [Kim] They were
shot in their bed
in front of their grandchildren.
Shot three times each
by two people
who've never been arrested.
- She's got some guts.
- [David] How did you
find that out?
- I checked in the newspapers.
It took a lot of looking,
but it was there.
- Oh, what made you do that,
Theresa?
- [Kim] I didn't believe
what you told me.
- Why?
- Because you lied to me.
- How'd you know I lied to you?
- I don't know how I knew.
I can't explain
everything like you can.
I don't know.
Is just something I could feel.
I never thought I'd find out
that they'd been murdered.
- The way they died
doesn't change the fact
that they deserved to.
I didn't lie about that.
- I don't care about them.
I don't know them.
It's you I know.
Now, you say you want us
to be together.
You say you want me
to trust you.
How is that gonna happen
if you're gonna
lie to me about
something like that?
- You have really good
instincts, don't you?
I mean, I kept asking
myself why you went
on and on about Cindy.
You weren't picking up any
kind of interest from me.
- We've become very close,
David.
Now, there was something
and I could sense it.
I thought it was about
you and Cindy.
I knew you weren't telling
me everything about her.
I thought maybe you were
still involved with her.
Maybe.
- Oh, no, no.
- Then what was it?
What made you tell me that lie?
You don't have to lie to me,
David.
- Cindy got a bad deal.
A real bad deal.
By the time I met her, she
was all lost and gone to Hell.
And I went there, too, to
try and bring her back.
Sounds kind of melodramatic,
doesn't it?
I went to Hell to
bring her back.
But it's the truth.
Where Cindy lived was Hell.
Her father...
had been molesting her
since she was a child.
The family knew and
nobody did anything.
I guess, while he was
doing it to Cindy,
he wasn't doing it to them.
You'd think they'd be on her
side, but they hated her.
But she hated herself.
She blamed herself.
(subdued music)
It's like when you
ran out of gas.
Oh, I'd get her to agree
to stop seeing him,
but there was always some
excuse why she couldn't stop.
She'd just lie there.
So, what could I do?
What could I do?
Oh, you have any idea how
angry that can make you
when somebody you care
about is dying
and they won't try to get well,
won't even want to get well?
- Why didn't you leave her?
- I couldn't do that, Theresa.
When you go into
something like that,
you have to see it through.
I told you I was that way.
When I commit, it's
the whole way.
- But you got her to stop.
Stop with her father, right?
Right?
- Well, I took her away
from all that,
but I didn't take all
that away from her.
You see, it gets to be
a part of you.
How you feel, how you are.
Cindy never got away
from the way she felt.
She put it onto me.
You know what I'm saying?
Um...
She didn't want me
to punish her.
I would and then I'd have
to forgive her.
Well,
I got a picture in here
that comes in my head.
Like somebody switched on
a light and I can see her
and I can see him doing
what he wants.
Anything he wants.
- [Kim] Oh.
- [David] You know what
I'm saying, don't you?
- Why didn't you get
her out of there?
- You ever been any place
you just didn't
know who you were, Theresa?
- David, I think you
should leave.
- I did, I did leave.
I got out, she got out.
We had to.
You understand that, don't you,
Theresa?
(knocking on door)
- Hey, y'all.
I got some nose candy.
- Steve, get out!
Get out!
- I'm just offering some blow,
man.
- Where are you going?
- I have to get out.
- It's 'cause of what
I told you, isn't it?
- You didn't tell me anything.
- It's about Cindy and me and
you hate me because of it.
- I don't hate you, David.
- Oh, but you don't love me.
- You.
- I can see it in your face.
- You don't know me.
You don't know
what's in my face.
- Cindy, wait a minute.
You want me to trust you?
I want you to trust me.
That's why I told you.
- It doesn't matter about trust.
Who am I that you should
want me to trust you?
- You're Theresa and I love you.
Theresa.
- She chickened out.
- [David] Theresa, wait.
- The broad has chickened out.
- Theresa, where are you going?
- I don't care about Cindy, I
don't care about her father.
- Or me, or us.
You don't care about us.
You asked me to tell you
about Cindy, so I tell you,
and all of a sudden you
just don't wanna know.
- David, let go of me.
- [David] No, wait.
- Where are you going?
- [Posey] I think
she's in trouble.
- Shh, shh, shh.
- What are you waiting for?
- Sit your butt down.
- [Posey] We've gotta
get her out of there.
- Listen, just listen.
- He's in the car with her.
- I know he's in the
car with her.
Shut up.
- I didn't know what it
was between you and Cindy.
I mean, I didn't get it,
about the thing about
her parents being killed and
found her dead in the car.
It doesn't even matter because
I'm just sorry for
Cindy and for you.
- Okay, Theresa.
- I'm sorry for us, for me.
- Theresa.
- David.
- I killed them.
- You shot 'em?
- The only thing I could do
for her after everything else.
She was still the same Cindy,
she just looked different.
She was chained to herself,
her old self.
I broke it.
- You?
You yourself?
- Well, she couldn't.
You couldn't expect her to.
- [Kim] No, she couldn't.
- Well, I'll be.
- She did it.
She did it.
(David breathing heavily)
- I told you.
I told you.
Oh, tell me.
- [Kim] Yes.
- Just tell me it'll be--
- Yeah.
Yeah, it's gonna be all right.
It's gonna be all right.
David.
(subdued music)
(Kim sobbing)
I have to go.
- No, just don't go right now.
- No, come on.
It's okay.
I have to...
I have to think
about everything.
Okay?
- I can't believe I told you.
I love you.
I couldn't have told you.
- I know.
I know, but it's a lot, David.
It's a weight and I
have to let it sink in.
- It's gonna drive you away.
- No, it isn't.
- I love you.
- I love you, too.
- I've given it to you, my life.
You know that, don't you?
(car engine starts)
(tense music)
Drive safe.
(tires squealing)
(retching)
(people chattering)
- DA's in with the grand
jury playing the tape.
Won't be long after that.
Once they hear him say it,
that's it.
(subdued music)
- I don't have any time
for this right now.
- You did it, kid.
They indicted him.
Hey.
Hey, hey, I wanna tell
you something.
For what it's worth,
you were good.
Better than good.
I've never seen it done better.
- Yeah, think I can
make a career out of it?
- I think you could do
just about anything
you set your mind to.
- Since when did you
start giving compliments
to bimbos from private
detective agencies?
- Hey, hey, hey, hey.
You caught me on a bummer
that first time.
My old lady walked out on me
just a couple days before.
- I don't know the old lady,
but she made the right choice,
Halsey.
- Well, if Kim is finished here,
I'm gonna bring her back
to the office.
Clyde wants to see you.
- In a minute, in a minute.
- Hey, you got your case.
Ease up.
- I really need to talk to you.
- Thanks, Tom.
- We'll see you at
the elevators.
- What is it, Halsey?
You wanna get together for
drinks and discuss my prospects
now that the old lady
walked out on you?
- The DA wants you to see
David again with a wire on.
- You just said that the
grand jury indicted him.
- No question, got him cold.
- So?
- So, we can't indict Cindy,
not with what he said
on those tapes.
- But with what you have,
you can get him to tell
you the rest.
- Sure, we can.
And then the second he
gets a lawyer,
he'll plea bargain his
testimony against Cindy.
- Plea bargain for what?
- For not getting the needle.
(subdued music)
- They want the death penalty?
- Two counts capital
premeditated for-gain homicide.
Now, that gets you the big
ticket in Texas, honey.
- He didn't do it for the money.
- Hey, we don't know that.
We don't know why he did it.
All we know is what he told you.
And most of what he told you,
Cindy told him and she
lies about everything.
We got no proof that her
father ever laid a hand on her.
(tense music)
You, uh...
You never did see
what little David
did to those people, did ya?
- I'm sure we can get
this thing on Crackdown.
She's coming in to see me
and I'll explain everything
she needs to know.
- [Man On Phone] Clyde,
you gotta get her--
- Oh, I understand.
Just so you understand
when the time comes,
I wanna make the announcement
about the agency's involvement.
Yeah, sure.
I'll take care of this
and I know you'll take
care of your part.
Yes, thank you.
Well, sit down.
Take the weight off those
lovely legs of yours.
- What do you wanna see
me about, Clyde?
- Well, I wanted to tell
you you did a hell of a job
and I'm real pleased.
- I'm pleased you're pleased,
Clyde.
- Well, the thing is,
we got a little end or
two left untied.
Seems they need for David
to really place Cindy
at the scene of the crime
before they bring
either of them in.
- So, they can get the
death penalty for David.
- Well, yeah.
They wanna kill
somebody for this.
Cindy would be a hard one being
a woman and all with kids.
Law's kind of sexist that way.
- What if I won't do it?
- Hell, that's just talk, yeah?
You'll do it.
This is your case.
It's not complete.
- Feels pretty complete to me.
- David fooled you, Kim.
Had you thinking he was a
pretty nice guy.
- What does this have to
do with anything?
- Hell, you sounded more upset
on those tapes than David did.
I didn't even
recognize you on it.
- I caught him, didn't I?
Does it matter how I sounded?
- Well, not to me, not to
the HPD, not to the DA,
but how about to you, Kim?
How about when you meet
David in court
and you're sitting there
looking at him
and those tapes are
saying you love him?
- I had to say that.
I don't love him.
- That's what you wanna
be sure about.
Seems kinda to me like
you fell for the guy.
That's the way it sounded.
Listen to those tapes.
Listen, I'll tell you what, Kim.
I think you'd do yourself
a power of help
if you went back in
there cold as ice
and tied a ribbon on this case.
It sure would impress the hell
out of just about everybody.
Might even make you feel
better about yourself.
- Well, I'll just have
to see how much
better about myself
I wanna feel.
- Yeah, and I want
you guys ready.
Why don't you go ahead and
get in your cars, all right?
(people chattering)
- How's she doing?
- How should she be doing?
- Did you call him yet?
You know, we're gonna
be right there.
No more than 10 seconds away.
You stay in public places.
You don't go back to his place.
That's a no-no.
You give us a code.
Something you'll say
that'll let us know
you want to get out.
We'll be there.
You understand?
- Yeah, I understand.
All right, just leave me alone.
- Right.
(door closes)
(tense music)
- [David On Phone] Yeah?
- David.
- [David On Phone] Oh, I
thought you weren't gonna call.
God.
Do you have any idea how
long a day is?
- It's been a pretty long
day for me, too.
- [David On Phone] I
wanna see you.
- I thought we should talk.
- [David On Phone] I
think we should do
more than talk, Theresa.
I'm not expecting sex, Theresa.
Just...
Just some ears.
I need that.
Some ears.
- Trick or treat, right?
- Oh, Kim.
I don't want you to do this.
You've done enough.
More.
- He so much as makes a
move towards me
and the cops will be
all over him.
(uptempo music)
- We need to know
where Cindy was.
We want her exact location
at the time of the shooting.
Was she in the room, was
she waiting in the car,
did she offer him money?
All that kind of thing.
Now, if you think
he's suspicious,
if you think anything
is wrong, you just say--
- I'll say I don't
want one of these
just-add-water-and-stir
relationships.
That's a pretty good line.
- Yeah.
Yeah, okay.
Kim, one more thing.
You don't go back to his
place no matter what.
When you leave the restaurant,
that's it.
Whether he's told you about
Cindy or not, that's it.
- You really care about
me, don't you, Sergeant?
- I'm just doing my job.
And my job is to see to
it that this punk
doesn't kill anybody else.
You leave the restaurant,
you turn into a liquor store,
say you need a pack
of cigarettes.
You get out of the car,
walk away.
Don't look back.
- [Waiter] Smoking or
non-smoking?
- [Kim] Smoking.
Thank you.
- Well, this is the
yuppie rip-off joint.
- What, are you ashamed to be
seen in public with me, David?
- Yeah.
Of course not, no.
I just hate this kind of
pretentious dump.
- [Waiter] Would you
care for anything
from the bar before you order?
- [Kim] We'll have a bottle of
dry white wine, a Chardonnay.
- [Waiter] Very good, thank you.
- Well, hey.
You're making decisions tonight.
I like that.
Long day today.
Boy, it was a long one.
I kept thinking, what
have I done?
What have I done?
I promised myself when
this business went down
I wasn't gonna get put away.
I'd check out first and
here I am handing my life
over to this person that I love.
I don't really know.
You scared me, Theresa.
I don't mind telling you.
- Poor, dumb bastard.
- You must've been scared
when Cindy knew.
- Why?
What was Cindy gonna do?
- I guess not.
Her being there and all.
Was she?
- Take it easy, Kim.
Take it easy.
- It's really all right, is it?
I mean, you've accepted it,
that I did it.
- What was that you once said?
Things are inevitable
once they've gone
through the trouble
of happening.
- Right.
Yes, right.
I think I found my
first disciple.
- Wasn't Cindy your first?
- Oh, Cindy never knew
what I was talking about.
She wasn't smart like you.
- She was smart enough to get
you to do what she wanted.
- Something like that.
Something as big as that's
gonna change your life.
Nothing's gonna be the same.
You don't let anybody else
make those decisions for you.
- You mean, it was your idea?
- No, I'm saying...
I did it as much for me
as I did for her.
I take responsibility
for my actions.
If I ever have to live this
life again, I got no complaints.
It's my philosophy, stay
in the now and no regrets.
- Yeah, but whose idea was it?
- Cindy begged me to
do it and I wanted to.
I saw it was the only thing
that could set her free.
So, I made sure she was
right there beside me
so it was hers as well.
It was like I was her arm.
I pulled the trigger, but
she planned it.
- The girl's a genius.
We got 'em both.
- And her kids didn't
recognize her?
- No, she'd run out the
door and had a mask on.
I didn't know they were
gonna be there.
When you start on
something like that,
you've got nothing but
nerve to see you through.
I was in my soldier mode.
You have no idea how it feels.
To be able to talk about it.
- Did Cindy offer you any money?
- Yeah.
That was the bit that
really bugged me.
- [Kim] How much?
- A lot.
It bothered me a lot.
- I mean, how much money?
- 25,000.
It just confused things.
Made it not clear why I
was doing it.
I had to think about it,
keep things separate.
- How much did you get?
- Nothing, I didn't
get any money.
It's all tied up in the estate.
I'm not gonna touch it.
I mean, it just makes
things different.
I didn't do it for the money.
Anyway, the cops will be
waiting for that.
Money talks.
I think I'll feel a
lot better about myself
if I forget about the money.
- You're right about this place.
Let's get out of here.
- Where do you wanna go?
- There's only one
place for us now, David.
- Jimmy, where's the driver?
- He's right outside.
- Get him, get him.
Let's go.
We're gonna stay right with her.
- I gotta get some cigarettes,
I'm out.
- We'll stop at the
liquor store on the way.
- Yeah.
- You know Friedrich Nietzsche?
Well, he got blamed for
all sorts of stuff
like being a Nazi philosopher.
Well, he wasn't.
He saw some things
really clearly.
He had this theory called
the Eternal Return.
He said you had to live your
life and be willing to live it
again exactly the same,
no changes.
And that was the
difference between
truth and falsehood,
Heaven and Hell.
Sometimes things make
sense suddenly
that you thought made
sense before.
You missed the liquor store.
- Yeah, next one.
- Well, you gotta have
some in here.
- No, I don't.
- [David] How can you tell?
You could have a box of Havanas.
- 'Cause I just smoked them all
and I know what I have in there.
- Wait a minute, let me look.
- Move in closer!
Driver, move in closer!
I think he found the mic.
- [Kim] Just give me the purse,
David.
Give me it.
- Okay, okay.
Here's your purse.
(car horn honks)
What is it?
- Nothing.
- Well, hurry back.
(subdued music)
(door clattering)
- Get your hands in
front of you!
Get 'em out now!
- [David] Okay, okay.
- Get out, out, out!
- Cuff him.
Get him up.
David West, you're under
arrest for the murders
of Virginia and James Campbell.
Anything you say can
be taken down
and used as evidence in
a court of law.
- Theresa!
Theresa!
- You don't know her name,
David.
But it isn't Theresa.
- Theresa?
Theresa!
- [Police Officer] That's
it, let's wrap it up.
- Theresa!
Oh, Theresa!
- [Tom] You don't have to
acknowledge him.
- I do.
Yes, I do.
- Theresa!
Why?
(subdued music)
Theresa!
(car engine starts)
(subdued music)