Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
["Follow You" by Christopher
Norton Ayer Kyle Robert McCammon] ♪
♪
How about Moose on the loose?
Sam, this is a police blog,
not Green Eggs and Ham.
I know.
Um, okay.
How about Moose saunters
down Main Street,
causing no traffic jams
'cause there's no cars
on the road?
[scoffs]
I don't know. This is kind
of the dumps.
I just need to finish
my OP ED
so I can get a real
writing job.
At least you're getting paid
for this one, right?
Mm, kind of.
I mean she's paying me
in banana bread.
[doorbell jingles]
Sam, you promised you'd get paid
for the article this time.
I know, but at least
it's a job.
Jess: I'm not sure it's a job
if you're not getting paid.
[sighs]
What am I going to do
with you?
Sam: Well at least my notary gig
pays the bills for now.
Woo, hot guy alert.
[laughs]
I don't think I heard
you correctly.
Sam: There aren't any
hot guys here.
Jess: Well that moose had
a nice caboose.
[laughs]
You just rhyme with me,
smoosh.
Coming round the corner.
Hop on Doctor Seuss.
You just rhymed with me again,
baba ganoush.
Is this going to be
all morning?
Maybe.
Because I like freshly squeezed
orange juice.
[groans]
["Follow You" continues]
♪
[laughs] Home sweet
tiny home.
Protest posters
here we come.
["Follow You" continues]
♪
Fire in the hole!
[gun shot]
[applause]
All right, good.
[bell rings]
Brunch is served.
Oh yeah, ooh...
everything looks good.
Hand those over here.
Pass them down.
Ooh, I want some
coffee cake.
Yum.
Peterson Maple can
singlehandedly destroy
Vermont's maple syrup industry
with their fancy technology.
They're like a big bully
on the playground.
You know, I heard
Peterson spent
a quarter of a million
on one evaporator.
We should bring
our baseball bats
and smash it as it comes
out of the truck.
Peaceful protest, dear.
We're not stooping
to their level.
You know, Sam's going to start
off her OP ED piece
at the protest.
I am so proud of you
for taking this on Sam.
It's kind of a big
undertaking for me,
but I'm really excited.
Suzie.
Writing an article is an example
of peaceful protest.
I am still packing my bat.
That's my girl.
[laughs]
Peterson thinks that they can
just march in here
and start mass producing.
They have clearly never
met Vermonters.
- True dat.
- Yeah.
Definitely not.
Oh. Speaking of which,
we stopped by
the family farm.
Hell yeah.
Pass me the sweet stuff.
[baby talk] Look who wants
some sweet stuff?
Look who it is everybody,
it's Gonzales.
[truck horn honks]
[protesters yelling]
[chanting]
Save our farm!
Oh come on, I just want
to dent it.
I just want to dent it.
You see that giant
gray factory?
That should be
on your label.
Not a sugar shack!
[yelling]
Yeah!
[chanting]
Save our farm!
[siren blares]
Hey folks.
Hello Rita.
I hate to tell you, but you got
to move it on home.
[annoyed chatter]
Clarence, you had better be
playing for the home team.
I am, Rita.
But the law's the law.
Come on folks.
You know you're
all trespassing.
Don't make me get out
my ticket book.
Come on.
Okay everybody, you heard
the constable.
Everybody to the bar.
First round's on Clarence.
All right.
Hey Alice.
Carrie.
Tell your mother thanks
for the muffins.
Gwendolyn, how are you?
Oh, Sam help.
Yeah.
Oh, hurry Sam.
I have to pee.
I'm trying.
My bracelet's caught.
Agh!
Sam, that's tighter.
Okay, you're free.
Oh, but we're not.
[groans]
♪
So the only reason
that the GMO law passed
is because I led
the rally.
And I didn't give you a ticket
for that one either.
I have a first
amendment right.
But you can't do it on
other people's property.
I heard he's had a crush
on her since high school.
And the one time
he gave her a ticket,
he ended up paying
for it himself.
Himself!
[laughs]
Oh, he's so good to me.
Yeah.
Don't press your luck.
[laughs]
Hey.
Can I get a good neighbor and
for these two ladies as well?
Oh, that's all right.
We're fine.
Um, thank you so much.
That's really sweet.
I'm Jessamine.
Landon.
I'm Sam.
Apparently I won't be saying
no to a free drink.
So what's this all about?
There has to be a good
story here.
Oh yeah.
We were actually just protesting
this horrible corporation
that's trying to take over
the Vermont maple industry.
Horrible huh?
Pure evil.
That's pretty harsh now.
No.
[laughs]
We actually know
what we're talking about.
I'm actually writing an article
about it right now,
so I've been doing
a lot of research.
Hmm.
I heard they were creating
demand for maple internationally,
which will drive demand
for Vermont maple.
But they're taking over family
farms with a cold steel factory.
Factories are more
energy efficient.
[laughs]
Okay, um...
Something tells me you're not
from around here.
I did just move up here
from Connecticut.
[spits]
You work for Peterson Maple?
As a matter of fact I do.
As a matter of fact, I don't
need to take this beer from you.
Listen. If you want an insider
interview for your article,
I live on my boat
on Lake Champlain.
I'd love to speak
with you ladies further.
Of course you live on Lake
Champlain and have a boat.
Like all of the rich
out-of-staters.
Would you like my card?
Um, thanks.
How about tomorrow
for the interview?
Um, I think
that sounds great.
Yeah.
You know what? I think
it's time to go, so...
Sam, stop it.
Thank you.
Come on, shackle buddy.
Nice to meet you.
Oh um, thanks
for the beers.
Yeah.
- Nice to meet you.
Bye.
[whispers]
Stop it!
Do you know those two?
No.
Don't know them,
don't know you.
Oh.
Okay.
♪
Slow down, I'm coming.
You have to stay
next to me.
[doorbell jingles]
Rusty, help!
Rusty!
I can't believe you want me
to interview that guy.
Come on Sam, it's
just an interview.
You're a reporter.
It's your job
to be objective,
and this is the perfect
opportunity
to get the opposing
perspective.
There you be.
- Thanks Rusty.
- Thank you Rusty.
[laughs]
All right, now we need a fix.
You better be paying in cash.
The regular?
- Always.
Coming up.
[giggles]
I really like that name.
Landon.
Please.
You with the flatlander.
I can't.
Oh, flatlander?
Whatever.
At least he's a flatlander
and not from New Hampshire.
Ugh, agreed.
[shudders]
New Hampshire.
Two maple creamy.
I got it.
No, I got it.
No, you paid last time.
Don't let her pay.
My bills are bigger.
She just paid?
They're dripping.
[laughs]
Hmm, yum.
This is the best.
Rusty always has the best
creamies of all time.
Mm-hmm.
Do you remember when
we were kids
and it used to snow six feet
by Christmas?
Yes.
We used to jump off the roof
into giant piles of snow
wearing purple snowsuits and
knitted mittens I think.
We need another winter
like those.
These warm spells
are killing us.
I know.
50 gallons less than
last year is rough.
Yeah.
Dad and I have enough
to worry about
without Peterson Maple
moving in on our industry.
Tell me about it.
They are the worst.
Oof.
How's your OP ED coming?
Hmm.
It's pretty challenging.
You are Vermont's
Erin Brockovich,
the voice of the people.
[laughs]
So have you decided
which magazine you're going
to submit to yet?
I mean the dream is
the Vermont Times.
Honestly, I'm a little nervous
to be taking on
such a huge topic
for my first OP ED.
But I really want to do
something that matters, you know?
Maybe it'll even lead to
a real writing job?
I would love to
stop freelancing,
stop that stupid
notary gig.
Have an office
with a desk.
Be a real person.
A real writer.
Ah, there's my girls.
Oh Dad, don't get up.
Hi Mr. Burr.
Hmm.
Okay, farm stand's all set
and I'll be back tomorrow
to do the receipts and I'll get
you some groceries on the way.
Sneak some peace pops
into the bag.
[whispers] Only
if I can have one.
Deal.
You know I can
hear you, right?
[giggles]
- Love you Dad.
- Love you.
I'll see you later.
- Bye Mr. Burr.
- Sam.
No peace pops in between.
Oh, come on.
♪
[typing]
Hmm.
Tea is cold.
Time for bed.
Mine is empty and I just
finished my paragraph.
Thanks love.
Perfect timing.
Mm-hmm.
♪
Love you, goodnight.
Love you. Night.
Don't forget we're interviewing
Landon tomorrow.
[birds chirping]
[doorbell jingles]
What can I get you ladies?
You seem like cappuccino girls.
Oh sure.
You know what?
We're actually good.
Thank you.
[chuckles]
Okay.
Sam. Don't be rude.
Free drinks.
Nothing's free.
Wow. That's so pretty.
Oh, yeah.
Rusty's the best at creating...
Okay, so just jumping right
into the interview,
here's our first question.
Uh, why are you on a mission
to destroy the Vermont
maple industry?
[laughs]
Wow, you get right in there,
don't you?
Thanks for starting
with an easy one.
[laughs]
Oh.
All right.
I don't see us as destroying
the maple industry at all.
I see us enhancing it.
How do you figure that?
Well maple is not a flavor
all over the world.
The way Vermonters manufacture
maple is traditional
but it's expensive.
If we want to give maple
a global presence,
then we have to use new
technologies to keep costs down.
We plan to create an
unprecedented demand for syrup.
Then the family farms
will have more sales
than they know
what to do with.
But how are people going
to know the difference?
You're falsely advertising
that your syrup
is made the Vermont way.
If you want to do something like
that then we need to come up
with some sort of labeling
system that allows people
to see if their syrup was made
by a farmer or a factory.
It's a valid point
and I'm sure something our
company would consider.
Really?
Yes. We want to work
with Vermont, not against.
[laughs]
You guys are feisty.
[notification alert]
[sighs]
I have to go notarize
a cattle sale.
So um, interview's over.
Oh.
I can do the interview.
No, that's okay.
It's over.
We really got
what we needed.
No, I got it.
It's fine.
Bye Sam.
[clears throat awkwardly]
So you say you want to work
with Vermont,
not against us.
So does that mean you're not
going to be buying family farms?
Because I have a sugar farm
that's been in my family
for four generations and I want
to make sure it's protected.
The intention of Peterson Maple
is not to buy up family farms.
So yes, I promise your farm
will be safe.
Now. My turn to ask
a question.
Do you like sailing?
["Life Is Rosy" by Tim
Myers, Jessica Penner] ♪
♪
Honey, I'm home.
Hey.
Best interview ever.
Longest interview ever.
I... I texted you like
a million times.
Oh sorry, spotty service.
Mm, it smells like
split pea soup in here.
Oh yeah, it was delicious.
Um, so.
You spent the whole day
with him.
He's really great Sam.
And I told him more about
your labeling idea
and he was really open to it.
Please.
I mean, I kind of doubt that.
I don't know, I don't really
trust his flashy watch
or really anyone who pays
with a $100 bill. I mean...
I don't even know
why you like this guy.
I mean he, he doesn't
even seem like your type.
I don't know.
There's just something
about him.
Don't be so judgmental Sam,
we should welcome him
into the community
like good Vermonters.
Okay, Little Miss Welcome Mat.
I'm just a little careful
about what kind of foxes
I invite into the henhouse.
Okay. I will be careful.
But I think this could be
a great opportunity
for him to work with us and,
you know, his company,
and maybe everybody
could be happy.
He's not a Vermonter!
Period!
Whew.
I'm really tired.
I'm going to go to bed.
Love you.
[sharply] Okay, that's fine.
Yeah, me too.
Love you.
Goodnight.
You know, I had so much fun
sailing with you the other day.
You are a natural.
I had a great time too.
But for a second date I thought
I'd bring us onto dry land.
[laughs]
So what looks good?
Should we start with oysters?
Ooh, I love oysters.
You know, I never get to have
them 'cause Sam hates them
and we usually
share everything.
Right.
Great, well since
Sam isn't here,
oysters it is.
You know, Sam actually
had a good question.
Mm-hmm.
Why are you making Vermont
maple syrup?
You know, I think Peterson
Maple offered me
a leadership opportunity
that I couldn't pass up.
Right?
I was really excited about
helping to build a business
from the ground up.
It's the whole reason I went
to business school.
You take a concept and you
bring it out to the world,
and it's challenging,
and it's invigorating...
Oh, I'm boring you.
No, not at all.
I, I think it's great that
you're so passionate
about what you do.
I mean, you move
to a place
where you don't even
know anybody?
I've hardly ever even been
out of Vermont.
Well I think it's very brave
that you went
on a second date
with a flatlander.
[laughs]
Right? I'm catching on.
Okay, so now I get to ask
a question.
What's the deal
with you and Sam?
Because you have already
mentioned her
four times this evening.
I mean it seems like you guys
are kind of close.
Well yeah, I mean she's
practically like a sister to me.
We've been inseparable
since we were little.
And she's always looked
out for me.
You know,
been my protector.
Ah.
She's like the yin
to my yang.
Hmm.
So if I wanted to do
something spontaneous,
would you have
to ask Sam first?
It depends on what it is.
No.
I don't think we need to ask
permission for that.
Cheers.
["Sweet Nothing" by Will
Cookson, Amy May Ellis] ♪
♪
[laughs]
[donkey brays]
♪
Woah!
Woo!
Hard to go back.
All typed up for you.
Banana bread?
This is udderly ridiculous.
[moos]
[laughs]
You're udderly dorky.
Thanks Rusty.
["Sweet Nothing" continues]
♪
Take care.
[whistling]
So tell me.
Who do you look more like?
Your mom or your dad?
Well, I don't really remember
what my mom looks like
except from pictures.
She died in an accident
when I was little.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
It's okay.
Luckily my amazing dad
raised me.
Hmm.
The accident's why he doesn't
walk that well.
Oh.
He still likes to pretend he can
do everything just fine.
You know, it's tough
for an ex-naval officer
to not be able to run
his own ship.
Hmm.
My dad says I look exactly like
my mom and I have her voice.
Do you still have memories
of her?
She used to sing all the time
and we used to sing together.
And that's her guitar.
Then you have to play
something for me.
- No!
- Yes!
- No.
No.
It's the weekend.
Come on, you have no excuse.
[scoffs]
Okay fine.
But you have to turn around,
you can't look at me.
Are you serious?
I'm serious.
You're not serious.
You're se...
[clears throat]
Turn around.
["Broken Before" by
Stephanie Sarah Lynn] ♪
♪
Wow.
That was incredible.
Thanks.
I'm serious, that was
really good.
You should play
for other people.
Have you ever thought
about pursuing it?
No.
I could never do that.
You know, I have to run the farm
and take care of Dad.
Yeah.
Well, I'm, um, I'm really happy
you let me hear it.
Because it just, it makes me
love you even more.
[romantic guitar music]
♪
Did you just say
you love me?
I think I did.
'Cause I love you too.
[laughs]
[fiddle music]
♪
I'm engaged!
Huh?
What?
Landon asked me to marry him!
Who's Landon?
Sam, come on.
I have coffees and bridal
magazines.
Get up!
Hold on.
I just found like,
the best one.
I gotta show you.
This is so pretty.
Oh, Sam, they're just like
all so pretty.
So you and Landon
are serious?
Yeah, Sam.
He proposed to me on his boat
last night with like,
the worst slash cutest poem
of all time.
Oh my god, you have to watch
this video, it's so cute.
Hold on, ready?
Okay watch, ready?
J is for jubilant,
which you always are.
E is for everything,
which you are to me.
SS is for shooting star,
because you're my shooting star.
[laughs]
Okay wait, ready?
I got a ring!
[laughs]
Wow.
What, you don't like
the ring?
Uh, well, it,
it's so fancy.
Wow.
[excited squealing]
I just, I'm not, I'm not really
sure that that's, that's you.
I mean, really?
This guy?
He's the one Sam.
You've only known him
for two months, okay?
As your best friend I just have
to make sure
that you're not rushing
into something
you're maybe not ready for.
I'm not.
It feels right.
I heard screaming and I came
as fast as I could.
[screaming]
[laughs]
Congratulations.
Oh.
I was wondering when you two
would make it official.
Oh no, no, no, no.
Rita, my boyfriend Landon
proposed last night.
Ohh.
Who wants muffins?
Hey.
Mwah.
So did you hear
the news?
Come here future
sister-in-law.
Oh.
I'm sorry, I didn't know
you had somebody here.
I'm Landon.
I know who you are.
Landon, this is Rita.
The best landlady in the State
of Vermont.
Well it's very nice
to meet you.
I will share my muffin
with you.
I have something for you.
Wait here.
You're my favorite muffin.
[smooching]
Ooh, oh, I got coffees
for every...
Oh good.
Sam, green tea for you.
And cappuccino
for me and Landon.
Thank you.
Jess, you always drink tea.
Oh well, Landon has this really
amazing cappuccino maker.
So I've been getting really
into it.
Really?
Mm-hmm.
Well, sounds good.
I'll, I'll try a cap then.
Oh, here, I'll share mine.
[clears throat awkwardly]
I have a pair of flannel
pajamas.
Cool.
Here you go, honey bunny.
Thank you.
Ooh, cappuccino cheers.
Cappuccino cheers.
Okay so I really
want you guys
to get to know each
other better.
So we want to take you on
our boat tonight to celebrate.
Already finishing
each other's...
...sentences.
Hmm.
[giggles]
Ugh.
Yeah sure, boat ride
sounds great.
Good.
Here.
Hand these flyers out
to your friends.
Jess.
I just have to say something
right now. I just...
Sam. I need your help
in the garden.
Okay. But I...
Now!
Okay, we'll see you later.
See you later.
[growls]
Jess is completely wack.
Good.
Feel your feelings.
I can't believe she literally
just got engaged
to someone she's known
for two seconds!
I'm watching her change
who she is for this guy,
you know?
And you're supposed
to be yourself
with the person you love.
They're supposed to love you
for you, right?
[sighs]
And why the sudden rush
to get married?
I mean we're just still trying
to figure out
what we want to do
with our lives.
Oh.
So you don't want to be
a notary forever.
It's not very funny.
Hon, I don't disagree with
you about this guy,
but you have to let her
figure it out for herself.
Maybe it's because we both
have big birthdays this year.
People tend to make very
rash decisions around this age.
That's right, you're turning...
Don't say it.
But people totally freak out,
right?
On the eve of our third decade,
my girlfriends and I made a deal
that we were each going
to buy convertibles.
Damn front wheel drive
didn't make it
up the driveway all winter...
Hold on, Rita.
Jess and I made a silly
pact once
about getting married
at the same time.
Sam: We were 12 years old and at
the annual Sugar on Snow Party,
there was this really mean boy
there that Jess really liked,
but he was talking
to this other girl
and Jess got
totally emotional.
Oh, my gosh.
You know how she is.
Jess, this is not right.
Sam: Anyway, I was trying
to make her feel better
and I came up with
this crazy idea.
I'll never get married
unless you get married.
Let's make a pact.
[spits]
Gross, Sam.
You're such a hippy.
Both of our husbands are
going to wear Carhartt pants,
chop wood, and at least
listen to Brad Paisley.
- You're my best friend.
Oh, let's make it official!
I'll sign here...
and you sign here.
Okay.
Sam: We signed the pact
and I still have it.
It's hanging on the bulletin
board in the tiny house.
Boom sauce, our pact
in writing.
Always and forever.
All I have to do is remind her
of this pact,
and then that will stall her
until she wakes up from
whatever love daze she's in.
Darling, why don't you focus
your energies
on helping people
who want to be helped?
Come down to the community
centre.
We always need volunteers
for the baked bean suppers,
and you clearly
have free time.
Sure.
I will totally do that,
whatever,
I just, I really need to go
talk this pact with Jess.
[playful music]
♪
I know what you're thinking.
There's no rush setting
any date.
You have plenty of time to get
to know Landon better
because you can't get married
unless I get married.
Remember?
Uh...
And I am single!
[hums]
Really?
Mm-hmm.
Well, then let's fix that.
Oh.
Yeah.
I love playing matchmaker
and there's all these great
dating apps now.
I can help you
set up a profile.
[awkwardly]
Yes. Definitely. No problem.
Great. I'll see if Landon
can set you up
with someone for tonight.
Great.
I'll go put together an outfit.
Perfect.
We can start planning
our weddings together.
I'm so glad you reminded me
about the pact.
[crows cawing]
So this is the outfit
you put together?
- What?
- Seriously?
I like it.
Oh, my god.
It's BO Brad.
Jess: I can't believe
you survived
that eighth grade dance
with him.
He was so stinky.
Sam: Don't remind me, Jess.
[giggles]
Quiet!
I was just trying to be nice.
I mean no one else
was asking me.
He was my last option.
Look how sparkly
it gets in the sun.
Oh, here's Landon's boat.
Sir Docks-a-Lot?
Come on, that's clever.
If it was anyone
other than Landon
you would think
that was funny.
Ahhh.
You made it.
Welcome aboard.
- Baby.
- You look nice.
Thank you.
- I missed you.
- I missed you too.
I...
Oh. Okay.
Hey, go down below.
I've got some hors d'oeuvres,
the champagne's on ice.
Ooh, sounds good.
Welcome to my humble abode.
Here's a little caviar to try.
Wah, no thanks.
Jess and I are more
like fish food girls,
know what I mean?
Oh.
Mmm.
Oh my god.
Ahoy mateys.
[laughs]
Howdy neighbor.
Brad and I are thinking
of teaming up
for the regatta next spring.
Brad, this is uh...
Jess Burr and Sam Templeton.
Hi Brad.
Brad, how are you?
I should've known, everyone
knows everyone in Vermont.
Hey.
So what have you been up to?
I'm teaching fourth grade.
That's amazing.
Wicked.
What have you ladies
been doing?
Just taking care
of the farm.
And writing songs.
Jess is a very talented
musician.
Oh, no way.
Wanda, the after school
music supervisor,
just went into early labor
and we're scrambling to find
a replacement.
That be something you'd be
interested in?
Oh wow, thank you so much.
I, I'm just really busy
at the farm.
That's too bad.
Well, if you think of anyone
let me know.
Well if you need a writer,
Sam is incredible.
She's actually working on her
first big OP ED piece right now.
Mm-hmm.
Sam. That's wicked.
Yeah, totally wicked.
Brad, grab some champagne
and caviar.
Ah, no thanks, man.
I'm not big on fish eggs.
More into fish food
if you know what I mean.
[laughs]
That's so funny.
Sam just made
the same joke!
[laughs]
Uh, dude, you got
any brewskis?
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
help yourself.
In the fridge.
Thanks man.
You know what?
It's actually feeling
really cramped in here
and I'm not feeling well.
I'm just, I'm going
to grab some air.
Oh. Okay.
Who loves Pictionary?
I like Pictionary.
You guys start.
I'll... I'll be right back.
[sighs]
[playful music]
♪
Hey.
You're feeling sick?
What?
I mean people grow up,
and he's really nice.
You know, just 'cause
someone's nice
doesn't mean
you marry them.
Okay.
Forget about Brad.
Look, Sam.
I think we should just rethink
this whole pact thing.
I mean, Landon thinks
it's a little ridiculous.
Landon thinks it's ridiculous?
Really?
Ridiculous like, I don't know,
getting engaged
after two months?
[sighs]
Look.
It doesn't matter if Landon
doesn't get our pact, okay?
We do.
We agreed, Jess, to never break
promises to each other.
I know, but don't you think
it's kind of one of those things
you just say but you
don't really mean?
Like I don't know, we're always
saying we're going to volunteer.
Yeah.
And I am volunteering,
with Rita at the community
centre tomorrow.
Yep.
Upholding my promise.
Wow Sam, that's amazing.
I'm really proud of you
for doing that.
You know, a promise
is a promise.
Yeah.
Okay, you're right.
All right, so maybe this date
didn't go so well.
But I bet you the next one's
going to be perfect.
Great.
The next guy just can't
be anyone
from middle school, okay?
Deal.
All right, now let's go
finish celebrating.
I'll slip a Dramamine
in your champagne.
[groans]
Come on.
Let's go.
♪
So I think you are going to have
a great day here Sam.
There's wonderful people
who volunteer...
Sam.
Come on.
It's going to be great.
These are our volunteers.
Hey everybody.
And we serve 65 guests
so you'll be very busy.
There's your apron,
there's your glove,
we will get you a tres
chic hairnet.
Have fun, darling.
It'll be great.
[sighs]
[loud crashing]
Never uh, wore a trash bag
before huh?
[uncomfortably] Can't
say that I have.
Can I help you out
with that?
No.
I am an expert.
- Teamwork.
- I got it.
[yells] I think I can handle
my own trash bag!
Team. Team bag.
Nope. Up through the top.
Okay.
And... there we go.
- Okay. I got it.
- Ok.
Thanks.
I'm Colin.
I'm Samantha. Sam.
Sam, meet bread.
Bread, meet basket.
Got it.
Cool.
So.
DUI or breakup?
Huh?
Uh, people usually only
volunteer here
if they are required by law
or they are escaping something.
Um, I guess kind of
a breakup,
but I don't really want
to talk about it.
Oh. Yeah, no.
I totally get it.
I mean, she's totally
being impossible.
Oh, she.
I'm the only one who's ever
protected her.
You know?
Ever since her mom died, I'm
the one looking out for her.
And now you know,
we're basically not even in each
other's lives at all.
And when we are in
each other's lives,
Landon is there.
Just lurking in the shadows,
making everything un-fun.
Uhh...
How long have the two of you
been together?
Uh, since we were like, five?
Wow.
We're best friends.
Oh!
Yeah, got it.
[laughs]
- Sam?
- Mm-hmm?
You're a natural when
it comes to bread.
Oh, thank you.
Therefore you are
on bread detail.
Ooh.
This is your weapon.
There are many like it,
but this one is yours.
Wicked.
Honey, I'm home.
Day one of my commitment.
Wow.
Green looks good on you.
Right?
Look what I brought.
Both: I'm just a girl,
standing in front of a boy.
Asking him to love her.
[laughs]
I'm just going to shower off
this bean juice
and then we can totally watch.
[toilet flushes]
Hey Sam.
Oh.
Landon's here.
Babe.
I thought we were going
to watch Rambo.
I mean, I still can't believe
you haven't seen it.
I think it's a classic
and that Stallone should've
won the Oscar.
Um, I actually was hoping
for some girl time tonight.
You know, you really wanted
to set up that dating profile
for me,
and I think we can all agree
that Julia would be a much
better inspiration.
Okay... but...
We can watch both.
It'll be a double feature.
We'll work on Sam's profiles,
it'll be good to have
a guy's opinion.
And then Sam can make her
famous cheddar shake popcorn.
Jess, I don't know
if I want a dude here
while I'm trying to do something
that's very intimate.
[stammers]
Okay. I really want us all
to hang out together, okay?
Hand me the DVDs, I'm going
to do a blind pick,
we'll figure out which one
to watch first.
DVDs?
Who has a DVD player?
I was just going to rent
it online.
[laughs]
We are totally
watching Julia.
[hums happily]
You know it's Vermont.
We can watch Rambo tomorrow.
Tomorrow.
All right.
Excuse me. This is
my favorite spot.
Can you just move?
Wait, wait. Agh!
You know this is
my favorite pillow.
Okay, um.
I'm sorry, but I just
don't need,
like, a million people
in my way.
[groans]
It's very sweaty over here.
You're kind of sweaty.
This is my...
Oh my god, honey,
are you okay?
Oh, my god.
Eyes closed,
eyes closed.
Okay open.
Okay, what's the surprise.
Why are we at my old school,
and why are you carrying
my guitar case?
Don't kill me but I told Brad
that you could teach
the music class.
No Landon, I can't do that.
Yes, you can do it.
It's only temporary and you're
going to be great.
Now you better hurry inside
because a classroom full of kids
needs supervision.
[groans]
[laughing]
Up, up, up, up, up, up, up.
I love you.
You're going to be great.
[various instruments playing]
Class, as promised, this is
the new teacher today.
This is Miss Jessamine, okay?
Thank you.
[yelling]
Hi!
I'm Jessamine.
[instruments jangling loudly]
What are your names?
Um, do you guys like songs?
A song?
No? Okay.
Um, I'm kind of terrified
to play in front of people,
but you're not really full
people yet, so...
Here goes.
[crash sound]
[class laughing]
♪
[knocking at door]
Samantha, you're just in time.
Okay. Miss Peterson.
You will sign this page
right here.
Okay.
And then again here.
Mr. Hopper.
You will sign right here.
Oh.
Okay.
If you would notarize this,
Samantha.
Good. And that completes
the sale.
It's a pleasure doing business
with you.
Wonderful.
I'll show you both out.
[sighs]
I knew it.
[phone buzzing]
[phone dinging]
♪
How can you be so blind
to this?
Landon said that's not
what they're doing,
and I believe him.
But I saw his boss at
the bank with a farmer
and a bill of sale.
Well there must be some
other explanation.
I can't believe you.
Well, I can't believe you.
He's my fiancé.
Can you please lay off?
[goat bleats]
So is this girl a dime?
Like a 10?
Two fives?
Ten ones?
Half a twenty?
Oh, she's much more
than a dime Dave.
Landon's bringing someone
for you to meet, okay?
He's really trying.
Can you please try
for me, Sam?
Yeah, of course.
I mean I want to get married
just as badly as you do.
Hey.
Oh, an 11.
Sure.
Dumbbell Dave, seriously?
Jess, I said no one else
that we know.
You said no one else we know
from middle school.
Dumbbell Dave transferred over
sophomore year of high school,
remember?
What, are you backing out?
Definitely not.
Oh, he just started working
for Landon.
Great, a double whammy.
I'm so pumped for this.
♪
Let's get ready to rumble.
[class exhales]
[inhaling]
[laughs]
If you want me to show you
how it's done,
I'm happy to help.
I'm kind of like
an expert at this.
Baa.
[sighs angrily]
Ooh, somebody's qigong is out
of alignment today.
[sighs]
Jess is a metaphor for what's
happening to maple in Vermont.
She's being corrupted.
Why don't you channel some of
this energy into your writing?
Oh, I am.
My OP ED is going
to be scathing.
Ugh, I'm the only person seeing
what's happening to Jess.
What is new with you lately?
Rita, this is about me, okay?
Jess is my best friend.
Well, I hear you've been
on a few dates lately.
Any new beaus?
Rita, 1943 wants its word back.
No one says beau.
This is Vermont.
It's always a little
bit 1943.
[sighs]
I mean, tomorrow afternoon
Jess set up a horseback riding
date with Rancher Steve, 007.
He sent you his license
plate number?
What?
No, no Rita.
He's from...
Oh, don't you say New Hampshire.
Dog, please.
Not even Jess is
that desperate.
Good.
I still don't want to go.
Oh honey, it'll be fine.
Ow.
You know, I would've put you
on bread detail
without faking an injury.
Yeah, well, apparently
horses go really fast
when you say "giddy up."
[chuckles]
Another fake date?
Yeah, it's complicated.
I just, I feel like I can't
give up now, you know?
Jess has to think that
I'm making an effort, right?
Right?
Sure. Yeah.
Whatever you say.
That's what I said.
Okay. You're the boss.
Am I on bread?
[bells chiming melodically]
Sam, I don't really get it.
That sounds like
a lot of work.
Well yeah, it is a lot of work.
But I'm the only one
looking out for Jess.
I've got to save her
from this guy.
Well, if you need another date
to suffer through,
I can set you up
with my friend
who's an Ultimate
Fighting Champion.
[laughs weakly]
Ouch.
I'm so excited to eat here.
We haven't had lunch at our spot
together in like, forever.
It's just nice to have
some alone time with you.
Ugh, oysters.
Don't get mad, okay?
Keep an open mind.
I actually have to go.
I'm teaching music class
this afternoon.
But I set you up
on four dates
with the best bachelors
in Vermont.
What?
You'll really like them, okay?
♪
- Hi.
- Hey.
So good to see you.
Okay, have fun.
Jess, you can't leave
me with him.
[angrily]
He has a man bun!
Konnichiwa.
How are you?
I am not interested in dating
at this time.
You know, I'm the type
of person
that goes into something
head first.
Good day my lady.
Prithee, what be thy type?
A little known fact,
Vermont actually does have
a coast guard.
We monitor the international
waters.
If I wanted to destroy
an enemy ship,
that's something you could
help me with?
I'm not a pirate, ma'am.
I'm looking for somebody
that I can really connect with.
You know what, this
whole vibe is just,
I'm just not
really feeling it.
You have a great
sense of humor.
[laughs]
[singing poorly] ♪ Sam like a very
tasty, tasty ham. ♪
[imitates pan flute]
Is that a literal cannon,
or a metaphorical cannon?
You and I could be one.
That's when I saw the dragon.
I was going to need a helm
of plus 20 fire resist.
[singing poorly] ♪ The one that I
want, just like you ♪
Hi yes,
we're going to have two
orders of the pork ribs,
extra bacon please.
[sobs]
Meat is murder!
My loins are a fire for you.
[sobbing]
How are you feeling
about us?
Jump ship.
Jump ship right now.
Yes ma'am.
Just jump ship.
Game over.
Will I see you anon?
Ah-no.
Ah.
Great.
God that was weird.
[snapping fingers]
["Be Who You Are"]
♪ You gotta be ♪
[class singing]
♪ who you are ♪
♪ No matter what they say ♪
Good!
♪ Be who you are ♪
♪ No matter what they say ♪
That's great you guys.
Okay now everybody go grab some
instruments and bring them back,
and we'll keep going.
[giggling]
Hey Tita, I noticed you
weren't singing.
Papa told me I'm no good
at singing,
and that singing is silly.
Well, do you think singing
is silly?
No.
I think you have
a beautiful voice,
and I think it's really
important to listen to yourself
and to do what you love.
No matter what they say?
No matter what anyone says.
Well, I love singing.
Well then let's sing!
How about you go get
the biggest drum?
Jess, you're really
good at this.
Aw. Thanks.
It's been fun.
Wanda decided not to return
after maternity leave,
so there's a full-time position
with your name on it.
[sighs]
I wish I could, but the farm
is my full-time job.
Okay.
Bummed, but I understand.
[kids playing instruments]
I'll go break out
the maracas.
All right, you guys
ready to jam?
[laughs]
Yeah!
["The Game" by Rick Reddington ]
♪ It's been a long winter ♪
♪
♪ Summer's much the same ♪
[cheering]
I can't take any more
screaming.
Do you want to go home?
We could totally go.
Hey, can I get the cheque?
No, no, no, come on.
I want us all to hang
out together.
We're going to find you a man,
going to dance with my man
Cheers to the hottest girls
in The 802.
Oh, I'm not doing beer.
No, I don't drink beer.
What? You drink beer
all the time.
Not when there's whiskey.
Come on Sam,
come dance with us.
No, that's okay.
You guys go.
Whiskey, can I get a double?
Ooh, out of my head
["The Game" continues]
♪
♪ Playing this game ♪
♪ Cause you all like to do ♪
Can I get two more shots,
please?
♪
No buddy, I do not think so.
Mm-mm.
♪
♪ And the cost of living ♪
♪ It's insane ♪
♪
You guys, shots!
[laughing]
Thank you.
Ooh, sorry.
I totally thought
you were drinking beer.
Oh, okay...
I said no.
I told you no!
[laughing]
Oh, oh, okay.
Sam, come pee with me.
Okay.
You've been rejecting
every cute guy.
I feel like you're not even
trying to meet someone.
What do you mean?
I have been on so many
dates, okay?
It's not my fault they've
all been duds.
You haven't been on
a single second date.
That is not true, okay?
I have a second date this week
with a horseback riding guy.
Giddy-up.
Look, Jess.
Give me more time, Jess.
Okay? I just need
a little bit more time.
Well there's no more
time, Sam.
Landon found us a place.
What?
[sighs]
Look, we need to talk about
giving our 30-day notice.
Oh, that happened
all of a sudden.
Sam, we're engaged.
Well, so be engaged then,
okay?
Just, it doesn't need
to be so rushed.
I'm not rushing.
I'm just thinking about
wedding dates and...
[yells] You can't set a date.
We have a pact, remember?
[toilet flushes]
[groans]
I haven't forgotten,
but I'd like to.
Well, you know what?
You can't move out, okay?
I'm sure I will meet
someone great,
and then it will be great,
and then we can figure out
the 30-day notice.
[toilet flushes]
Yo, when's your place
available?
It's not!
Yes it is.
[scoffs angrily]
[country music playing]
Out.
♪
Tequila, no lime.
[laughing]
♪
Enough of this bluegrass!
I'll show them real music.
Coming through.
♪
What is she doing?
That's enough!
Enough! Enough.
Give me a beat, drummer.
[plays hip hop beat]
♪
["Mother Trucker" by Alexandra
Case] ♪ Won't say hi to buddy ♪
♪ Now she's a duddy
I don't understand ♪
♪ when the waters
got so muddy ♪
♪ It's not funny ♪
♪ Have a friend always
there not be there ♪
♪ Who cares? ♪
♪ Out-of-staters beware ♪
♪ I'm coming for you ♪
♪ Mother truckers
get scared ♪
♪ Go back to Connecticut! ♪
Woah!
[cymbals crashing]
Oh boy.
[mooing]
You know, I'm trying
to be supportive,
but this pact is
becoming ridiculous.
Hey come on, it's
important to her.
Look, this whole thing
is really hard,
but I made a promise and
I can't break a promise.
Didn't it happen
a long time ago?
Like when you were 12
or something?
So what, in 17 years this
isn't going to hold up?
I just wish she could be happy
for you.
She's just being protective.
She doesn't trust you with
the whole Peterson thing.
You know?
There's no reason
not to trust you, right?
I do want to make sure
everything's clear
between us and there's
a conversation
that I've been wanting
to have.
[vomits]
[groans]
Alright.
[squelching sounds]
Okay. If I don't look at it,
I won't feel sick.
Hey, hey, hey.
Woah, stop spinning.
Rough night?
They're moving in together.
What?
Who's moving in together?
Oh my god, I gotta
do something.
I gotta do something.
What do you got to do?
Ugh, 30 days is like,
tomorrow.
Okay. You lost me.
I have to figure
something out.
I am just going to let you
talk out loud
to yourself and clearly
not to me.
You know what I could do?
You know what I...
Hey wait!
What if I create the worst
breakup of all time,
and I'm so beyond destroyed
that Jess can't leave?
Oh my god, I'll invent
the perfect relationship
and then have it blow up and
she won't be able to move out.
[gasps]
You can play him.
You can play my imaginary
boyfriend.
Imaginary, huh?
Yeah!
Come get your t-shirts for
tomorrow's rally everybody.
And the local sap rally.
Hello, perfect.
I mean I'll be
there interviewing
for my article anyway,
and everyone will be there.
So you can come as
my big imaginary date.
You can meet Jess,
you can meet everybody.
Nah, I don't really
want to get involved.
Why not?
But I get it.
Change is hard.
[sighs]
You know what Colin?
You don't get it, okay?
I don't need you.
I can handle this on my own.
[melancholy music]
♪
Jess?
I think I just met
my soul mate.
[peppy bluegrass music]
♪
Oh yeah!
♪ Oh, yeah man. ♪
♪
♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
Yeah!
[cheering and applause]
Thank you.
The guys are good,
aren't they?
Hey listen.
It's an honor for all of us
to be here
with a bunch of local saps.
[cheering and applause]
Supporting our Vermont pride,
the maple industry.
[cheering and applause]
So thanks a lot for fighting
the good fight
and for not being afraid
to stand up to the man.
[cheering and applause]
Patrick?
This one is for Vermont maple.
Yeah.
[peppy bluegrass music]
♪
Oh yeah.
I hear they won't let anyone
on the property
who isn't an employee.
What do you think
they're hiding?
Well they actually lured me
into a meeting,
and then they strong armed me
into a conference room
and tried to bully me
into selling my farm.
Well an inside source told me
that Peterson Maple
has a policy against buying
family farms.
We don't want
flatlander money.
We want our traditions.
Jess, stop scaring away
my interviewees.
Sam, you're not
being impartial.
You're just egging
on negativity.
I'm just trying to uncover
the truth.
Wow Jess.
You really have changed
your perspective.
Yeah, you really have, hon.
I'm just trying to encourage
Sam to write the most
inclusive article.
Really?
Doesn't seem like it.
Agreed.
[sighs]
[piano music]
♪
[phone ringing]
Hey.
Hey. I really wish
you were here.
I've been trying hard to
advocate on your behalf,
but people here really need
to see your face
and hear that you actually care
about the community.
Of course I do.
I'm sorry babe.
I'm just, I'm
swamped here.
I'll make it up to you, okay?
I promise.
Okay.
All right, love you.
Talk to you later.
[sighs]
Mrs. Peterson, can I speak
with you for a minute?
One minute.
I've been thinking
about our strategy.
And it was never to buy up
single family farms.
It was to benefit everyone and
create international demand.
We are benefiting everyone.
These old farms
are falling down.
We're giving these people
more money
than they've seen
in their entire life.
These falling down farms
are the brand.
They're the exact brand that
we're trying to bring to market.
Landon, look.
You have a good heart, okay?
But this is business.
If they are selling,
we are buying.
End of discussion.
But...
[sighs]
[chattering]
Hey.
Sam was just telling us about
her hunk-a hunk-a burnin' love.
Mm-hmm.
I knew you two
would hit it off.
Sounds like a cool dude.
I think it's so cool
that you met volunteering.
Yeah, right?
I mean he's there basically
every day
because his parents
own the place.
You guys, they are such
good people.
I mean like instant family.
He has such a big heart.
Well I'm really excited for you,
Sam.
Thanks, yeah.
He's um, he's also a pilot,
and he could take us all for
like a weekend getaway, right?
Well we need
to meet him ASAP!
I know you guys,
I'm so bummed.
He couldn't make
it here today.
He flew to Boston
for this like,
really big super
important meeting.
There's my heart.
Oh my god, baby.
Yeah.
Hi, your flight got cancelled,
wow.
Yep.
Pilot got the flu.
Oh.
Well, he means his co-pilot.
Goofball.
Can't fly without him.
Thanks for showing up
to support.
You know, honeybuns, there is
a perfect spot to put that sign,
um, right over there.
So um...
- Nice to meet you.
- Come on.
[playful music]
♪
Did you tell them
I'm a flight attendant?
A pilot.
Flight attendant?
[laughs]
Yeah. Cause that's
the crazy story.
Lookit, Colin, I am so glad
that you're here.
Me too.
We need to stage
this breakup ASAP.
We just started dating.
Yeah well,
it's already over.
Come on-
[cheering]
Yeah!
Hey.
[yells]
Ahhh!
I can't believe you just
said that.
That is such a sexist comment.
You know what?
Both men and women can both
be winners in my book.
I cannot date someone
who thinks like that.
Yep. You're right babe.
I don't believe in winners
and losers.
I believe that everybody
is equal in my book.
Crowd: Aww.
Your book and
your schedule.
Everything's always
about you!
Yep.
My book, my schedule.
The only thing it says in them
is Samantha.
Crowd: Aww!
You're not listening to me.
You never listen!
[grits teeth] This is not
what we talked about
in the corn maze.
Sorry babe. I wasn't listening.
I was composing a poem
for you in my head.
Crowd: Aww!
Haiku.
What?
Come here!
That was good.
Ooop!
Did you hurt yourself?
I like him better than Samantha.
Sometimes.
Ugh.
Colin. What are you doing?
I don't want to break up.
This is serious, okay?
I'm trying to save Jess
and you're screwing it up.
I'm screwing it up?
What is that supposed
to mean?
Look at what this is doing
to you.
I mean, is this really
who you are?
You know what?
You are not being a very
good friend right now.
Wow. Okay.
I think you need to look up the
definition of the word "friend"!
Colin, just leave me alone okay?
I never should've done
community service!
What?
[zany music]
♪
Ah!
No! No! No!
Get out of here!
It all looks the same.
♪
My mother always warned me
don't go into a corn maze
with a girl you don't know.
♪
Ugh.
Come on!
[grunts]
That way!
♪
[typing furiously]
Argh!
Take that Peterson!
[exhales]
I printed out enough copies
to send to every paper
in the state.
I will also need stamps
and envelopes please.
[whistles]
That's some title.
Yeah, well sometimes you have
to burn the trash, Rusty.
So I guess this is
our 30 days' notice.
I'm sorry I didn't give you
more of a heads up.
Just, you know, with Sam...
Oh, I know.
Poor Samantha.
What is she going to do?
I don't know.
It's really stressing me out.
Rita: I know.
She's having a hard time
right now.
Jess: Yeah.
I don't know if she's
the marrying kind.
She's so unhappy.
But I have to tell her
I gave you notice.
I can't lie.
Hang in there.
It'll all come out
in the wash.
♪
Colin broke up
with me!
[sobbing]
What?
What happened?
He got back together
with his ex,
a flight attendant.
Apparently they weren't
even officially broken up.
[sobbing]
Why does it hurt this much?
I'm so so sorry.
Okay here, I'll clear
my whole day, okay.
We can watch a Julia movie
and shoot the potato cannon.
Yeah.
Having some alone time with
you actually sounds really nice.
Okay love.
[explosion]
Woah.
[laughing]
That's crazy.
That was amazing.
Nice one.
[sighs]
That was exactly
what I needed.
I know.
Since when did life get
so stressful?
Hmm, well, I mean, I can
think of a catalyst or two.
[laughs]
You know what, Sam?
All I want to do is tell you
what I'm going through
and what I'm thinking,
and I feel like I can't.
I finally find the guy
of my dreams
and my best friend
hates him.
Well, maybe that means he's
just not the guy of your dreams.
See? I can't talk to you.
You're so closed-minded
about him.
I miss my best friend.
Well, I miss my
best friend too.
Ready, ready, ready?
Happy engagement!
[cheering]
Let's get drunk.
Ah, thank you, sir.
So, if we could all
gather around,
I would love to make a toast
to my beautiful bride-to-be.
I cannot wait to spend
the rest of my life with you.
- I love you.
- Aww, I love you.
Yeah!
- We love you.
- Cheers.
Landon: For the honeymoon,
I'd love to get her over to Nantucket..
Rita: Woah.
Suzy: I'm sure she'd love
that too.
[laughs]
I'm going to work these off
later with a little goat yoga
if you want to come with.
Uh, I'm actually allergic
to goats.
So no, thank you.
Oh. That's a shame.
Hey congrats.
Congrats on the big news.
Come on, how much you guys
pull in?
Half a mil?
Two quarters?
Four eights?
Five hundos?
[laughs]
I heard yours was our biggest
farm sale yet.
What?
[furiously] You bought
Jess's family farm?
You syrup usurper!
[gasps]
Woah, woah, woah.
Why would you do that?
Jess!
I didn't know, I swear.
[tearfully] You told me that your
company wasn't buying family farms.
Please, let me try to explain.
Let you explain?
That is the one line that
every liar says in every movie.
I have been defending Peterson
Maple to the entire community.
Listen. I was trying
to make it better.
If you really loved her,
you wouldn't lie.
Sam, stop hating on him.
You've been attacking him
since the beginning.
This doesn't involve you.
Of course it involves me, okay?
I'm protecting you
like I always have.
I don't need you
to protect me.
Fine, fine.
Then enjoy your life
with liar liar pants on fire
and his evil corporation.
Come on Sam.
This can't be, this
can't be happening.
I was just upholding a pact
like any good friend.
Well I've been doing nothing
but fight for the stupid pact
because I'm a good friend!
Ugh.
Ugh!!!
Sam's right.
I shouldn't have fallen for
somebody that I barely know.
If I can't trust you,
I can't be your family.
No.
And I don't think I can be
your family anymore either!
[angry groaning]
[slams door]
Okay. Can we stop
with the slamming?
- No!
Why couldn't you just
let me be in love?
You're supposed
to have my back.
Yeah, we are supposed to
have each other's backs.
Just cause you need some guy
to be happy doesn't mean I do.
Okay. You girls have nothing
but each other's backs.
So guess what?
I'm leaving.
You know, marry
whoever you want.
I don't need you, Jess.
Well...
Well, I don't need you either!
[grunts]
Fairy tales say that everything
works out
when you meet the guy of your
dreams, but it doesn't!
[yells]
Argh!!!!!
Ooh. Careful.
Because the prince
is really the villain
and your best friend shattered
your glass slipper.
Argh!!!
I'm going to be plenty warm
this winter.
♪
Hello Samantha.
[angrily]
What?
Just want to let you know
your mailbox is overflowing.
Oh.
[doorbells jingle]
[groans]
[frustrated groan]
Okay, some good news.
["Life carries on without you" by
Lena Anderssen, Niclas Johannesen] ♪
♪
[laughing]
[grunts angrily]
[phone rings]
["Life carries on without you"
continues] ♪
Hello?
♪
What?
What happened?
♪
Stop staring at me.
Dad.
I was so worried about you.
You had a really bad fall.
We have to take this seriously.
I'm going to be fine.
Don't worry.
Okay.
We'll get through
this together.
You just sounded exactly
like your mother.
[laughs]
I love you sweetheart.
I love you too, Dad.
You're the only family
I have left.
Where's Sam?
We're not speaking.
Where's that nice fiancé
of yours?
Also not speaking.
Are you not talking to Landon
because of the farm?
I wish I'd been the one
to tell you first.
We've been going under
for years.
When they came to me
with an offer,
I was more than happy
to take it.
I have had my eye on a lakefront
assisted living facility.
I already put my name in
for the cribbage tournament.
Dad.
Honey.
You have been taking care of me
and the farm forever.
I want you to feel free
to choose your life.
Speaking of which.
How's that music class
of yours?
It's actually going
really well.
I really like teaching them.
[chuckles]
Excuse me, this is
private property.
Rita, it's me.
Sam?
Honey, I thought you were
a homeless person.
What's the matter?
[teary]
Everything's the matter.
Everyone hated my article,
I lost my best friend,
and I am homeless.
Honey, let's go get
some cheddar soup.
Come on.
[acoustic guitar music]
♪
I can't believe Jess
didn't appreciate
everything that I did
for her.
Are you sure what you did
was for her?
I was really happy
how everything was.
I guess, I never really tried
to meet anyone
'cause Jess was just
filling that space.
And now I am alone.
Who wants to date a girl
who's friendless and homeless?
Hopefully somebody.
[laughs]
Honey, you are
a rare bird.
It's going to take a special guy
to keep up with you.
And when you meet him
you will hear church bells.
That's not a thing.
No one hears church bells.
In the meantime what's wrong
with a little alone time?
In order to be able to fly
with someone else
you have to be able to fly
on your own first, right?
Which brings me
to your article.
Honey, that was more of
a hate note than an OP ED.
That's not
the Sam I know.
How about a rewrite
with a little less rage
and a little more heart,
hmm?
[playing xylophone poorly]
♪
♪ Old MacDonald
had a farm ♪
♪ Ee I ee I oh ♪
♪ And on that
farm he... ♪
Nobody?
Hi you guys!
[cheering]
Hi you guys,
I missed you.
[laughs]
Hey, if that full time
position's still available
I'll take it.
Definitely.
Okay you guys,
let's get in a circle.
Circle time.
Okay ready?
[drumming]
♪ Going through the jungle ♪
♪ What do we see? ♪
Sam: Change is hard.
But it is inevitable,
as all Vermonters know.
I look outside to see a maple
tree standing full of pride
and endurance.
A maple tree holds strong
through all four seasons.
Well, five if you count
mud season.
It can withstand because it has
found a perfect balance
between changing to adapt
and maintaining strong roots.
♪
Miss Peterson.
I think you need
to read this.
Sam: Like a maple tree,
Vermonters need to evolve with
the maple sugaring industry,
accepting each new season
as it comes
and making room
for Peterson Maple.
At the same time,
Peterson Maple
should respect
and build off the strength
of our Vermont roots.
[church bells playing
Hallelujah]
[laughs]
[applause]
♪
Crowd: Aww!
[applause]
♪
[crowd chattering]
Hi.
Hey.
He is wearing a flannel.
Really great.
I am so proud of you, hey?
Thank you.
Nice sign, Kayla.
Hey Harry, how are you?
Okay everybody,
let's quiet down.
Thank you all for
coming out today.
I could not be prouder
of this unique community
we have here in Vermont.
Now this community has very
strong values.
They take great pride
in the beauty of the state
and its traditions,
and they also take
great pride
in the inclusiveness
of everybody's opinion.
So we've heard some great points
from the community today
and from the mayor.
So it's time to hand over
the floor to Peterson Maple.
[crowd groans]
Hello Vermonters.
Thank you for the floor.
Um, hmm.
I had uh...
I had planned what I was
going to say but forget it.
I, um, I've been here
just a couple months,
and it just took me a few
minutes to see how
special this place was.
To understand that Vermonters
have each other's backs.
And along the way I learned
a lot about myself,
about corporate responsibility,
and I learned about just doing
the right thing.
So we here at Peterson Maple
are going to have your backs.
We're going to do
the right thing.
We don't want to tear down
what you've built,
we want to add to it.
So from this point forward,
we will only tap
unused maple trees.
And furthermore,
and most importantly,
we will no longer purchase
family farms.
[cheering and applause]
As an added assurance,
Peterson Maple has agreed
to the proposed label
which clarifies where
our syrup is being made.
We will no longer use
the picture of a sugar shack
in our branding.
[cheering and applause]
[sighs]
Permission to enter
enemy territory?
Sure.
[laughs uncomfortably]
Two cappuccinos.
Oh.
Thanks Sam.
So, um...
I'm here today because
I am redefining
my definition of being
a good friend.
Hmm.
What you said at the meeting
earlier today was commendable.
Oh.
I didn't know they had purchased
her farm,
but I should've done more
to stop it.
I misjudged you.
Look.
Jess has always kind
of been, um,
she's kind of like my person.
And I'm not close
with my parents.
To be honest, I'm not really
close with most people.
Mm.
It felt like you had just
taken her away from me.
And I realize now that just
because things change
doesn't mean that they end.
You are a pretty tough act
to follow.
All Jess talks about is
how great you are.
And it's hard because I want
to be her perfect person,
but you already are.
I mean you guys are already
married on Facebook.
There's room for Jess
to have a love of her life
and a best friend.
Mm-hmm.
I can let you be
the best friend.
[laughs]
Oh, um...
What's this?
[laughs]
Thank you.
Well, asking Jess's dad for
his blessing was customary.
But now I realize who I really
should've asked.
So Sam, I would like
to ask permission
to take your best friend's
hand in marriage.
Permission granted.
Cheers.
- Mm!
- What do you think?
Cappuccino's not as bad
as I thought.
It grows on you, right?
Kinda does, yeah.
♪
Hi.
Packing up the farm, huh?
Yeah.
Saw your article.
Did you like it?
I loved it, Sam.
Good.
Because so did
the Vermont Times.
I have an interview with them
next week.
For a job with a desk?
For a job with a desk.
[laughs]
Yeah.
How's, um, how's
your dad doing?
He's doing better.
Well, that's good.
A lot of boxes.
A lot of memories
in this kitchen.
Yeah.
Speaking of memories,
um, do you remember
that summer
we went swimming
at Red Rocks
and we hiked up
the 40-foot cliff?
Well, when we got
to the top,
you all tried so hard
to get me to jump.
You were coaching me,
bribing me,
I think someone even offered
to hold my hand.
Anyway, you all jumped
and I didn't.
And I remember just being
so incredibly mad at you
for leaving me
all alone up there.
You know, I had to scoot
back down
all the way in Harry's
super ugly Tevas.
[laughs]
Anyway, I'm telling you this
because that's just sort of
been my life, you know?
Me not jumping and being mad at
everyone else because they did.
God. We're turning 30 this year,
and I guess part of me
just still feels all alone,
stuck on the top of Red Rocks
in really ugly Tevas.
Jess, I just want
you to know
that I'm really sorry
for everything.
I'm really sorry too.
[laughs]
Now.
For my first duty
as Maid of Honor...
[sings fanfare]
Ta-ta-ta-ta!
Huh? Huh?
Woah!
First off, no-go
on the dress.
Where did you even get
that thing?
It's cute.
And secondly, no-go
on the groom.
We haven't spoken.
Okay look.
I have to show you
something.
And furthermore,
and most importantly,
we will no longer purchase
family farms.
[applause]
He's a good one, Jess.
And I'm sorry it took me
so long to see it.
I really love him, and I
really love you too, Sam.
I know you do.
Which is why we're going to go
get us a groom!
[police siren blaring]
♪
Thanks for the ride
Constable Johnston.
There's no law
when it comes to love.
Next stop, Peterson Maple.
I think you need
one final touch.
[sings fanfare]
Ta-ta-ta-ta!
[laughs]
You are officially banned
from the thrift store.
Okay come here,
hold still.
[police horn honks]
I love doing that.
[laughs]
[whispers]
Oh, my gosh.
Okay, he doesn't know
we're here yet.
[giggling]
[whispers]
Hi Mrs. Peterson!
Good to see you.
Perfect timing, he's heading
this way now.
Okay.
[sighs happily]
Are you ready?
Go get 'em.
[gasps]
Oh!
["Something Inside" by Barrie Gledden,
Jason Pedder, Jessica Greenfield] ♪
♪
24th and then by the 25th
Give me a second.
♪
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I got caught up in the pact
and everything got crazy.
No one can ever
replace Sam
but no one can ever replace
you either.
You make me really happy,
Landon.
You put this ring
back on my finger,
I promise I'll never
take it off.
["Something Inside" continues]
♪
Come here.
I love you maple nut.
[laughs]
[applause]
♪
By the power vested in me,
I now pronounce you
husband and wife.
You may kiss the bride.
[applause]
[cheering]
[laughs]
Guess what you guys?
Colin and I are going to start
our own community centre.
We're moving to Maine!
But we have a pact!
And we promise to always
live in the same town.
Always and forever.
[spits]
Sam!
[laughs]
["True Love" by Terrie
Devine-King, Steve Levine] ♪
♪
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
♪
["Do It All Again" by Graham
Colton, Maggie McClure] ♪
♪