( typewriter keys
clicking slowly )
( typewriter dings )
SHIT, MAN.
YOU SCARED THE HELL
OUT OF ME.
TAKE IT.
I HAVEN'T GOT TIME
TO PLAY WITH YOU, PHIL.
YOU SEE ALL THAT WORK
I GOT?
YOU'RE BACK ON.
WHAT?
IT WASN'T EASY.
JENNINGS FOUGHT ME
EVERY INCH OF THE WAY,
BUT YOU'RE BACK ON.
MAYBE HE'S RIGHT, MAN.
NO, HE'S NOT.
NEVER WAS,
NOT ABOUT ANY OF THAT SHIT
THEY TALK ABOUT YOU.
I'M COOL.
I LIKE IT DOWN HERE.
( laughs )
RIGHT.
WE NEED YOU, PARTNER.
YOU KNOW THE O.C. PLAYERS
BETTER THAN ANYBODY.
YOU'RE BACK ON, JACK.
( distant siren wailing )
I OWE YOU, MAN.
YOU DON'T OWE ME
ANYTHING.
( siren wailing )
( crash )
TONY.
- YEAH?
DID I EVER TELL YOU
ABOUT THE TIME I WAS
IN BOARDING SCHOOL?
NAH, YOU DIDN'T.
IT WAS DURING NAP TIME.
OH, BABY.
IT WAS SO HOT,
I'VE DOZED OFF.
OH, YEAH.
YOU KNOW
HOW I DOZED OFF?
HOW?
I WAS NAKED
UNDER THE SHEETS.
OH, YEAH?
THAT'S THE WAY I LIKE YOU.
WHAT HAPPENED?
WELL, THEN
MY LITTLE HAND
DROPPED DOWN
AND IT ACCIDENTALLY
BURST MY SCHOOL RING
- BETWEEN MY THIGHS.
- OH, YEAH.
AND THEN YOU KNOW
WHAT HAPPENED?
Tony:
What happened?
Woman:
I was in the perfect
place
between sleeping
and dreaming.
I slowly felt
your hands
stroking me,
caressing me gently...
Then...
ARE YOU MAINTAINING
TONIGHT, PARTNER?
HMM?
OH, YEAH, I'M FINE, MAN.
I'M FINE.
JUST TURN IT UP
A LITTLE BIT.
WHAT, ARE YOU
A PERVERT?
THIS IS LIKE SOME BAD
PENTHOUSE LETTER.
IT'S PERFECT IF YOUR
BOYFRIEND'S A CHEESEBALL
LIKE TONY D.
HEY.
( honks horn )
( muffled gunshot )
WHAT WAS THAT?
SHIT.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
I DON'T BELIEVE THIS.
CALL FOR BACKUP.
( Tony and woman moaning )
( woman screams )
( rapid gunfire )
MAKE IT FAST.
( tires screech )
POLICE!
- ANYONE ELSE IN HERE?
- HUH-UH.
- NO?
- NO.
TONY FUCKING D.
SIX MONTHS
DOWN THE DRAIN.
COME HERE.
SIT DOWN.
YOU ALL RIGHT?
- I THINK SO.
- GOOD.
FACES-- WHAT DID THEY
LOOK LIKE?
FACES, YOU KNOW?
YOU'RE NOT GOING MUTE
ON ME, ARE YOU?
LOOK, IT WAS A PERFECT DATE.
I THINK I'LL ORDER PIZZA.
YOU MUST BE THE SENTIMENTAL
TYPE, HUH, ALMA?
SO YOU KNOW MY NAME.
YOU KNOW WHAT IT MEANS?
NOT A FUCKING CLUE,
BUT I KNOW TONY OVER THERE--
HE PAYS FOR THIS PLACE,
DON'T HE?
SO YOU'VE BEEN
WATCHING ME.
THAT'S CREEPY.
YOU PUT ON
SUCH A NICE SHOW.
HE PAID FOR YOU TOO?
HOURLY OR WEEKLY?
HEY, JACK, EASE UP.
HEY, PHIL.
MEET ALMA.
BE VERY GENTLE WITH HER.
SHE'S QUITE UPSET.
Jack:
HOW DOES THIS GET TO BE
MY FUCK-UP?
YOU WERE
SITTING ON YOUR ASS
20' AWAY, JACK.
WE WERE THERE
TO MONITOR ONLY.
IT'S NOT OUR FAULT
IF TONY DOESN'T TAKE
POLICE PROTECTION.
I DON'T CARE.
BOTTOM LINE IS,
WE GUARANTEED TONY WOULD
TURN STATE'S EVIDENCE
AND SOME HITTER
TAKES HIM OUT RIGHT
UNDER YOUR NOSE.
AND NOW THE MAYOR,
THE D.A.
AND THE FUCKING F.B.I.
ESPECIALLY
ARE ALL OVER MY BACK.
ARE YOU READY, PHIL?
- ALL SET.
- F.B.I.?
THAT'S WHAT WE'RE DOING THIS
DOG-AND-PONY SHOW FOR--
BILL KEENAN?
THAT'S RIGHT.
- WHY?
WHY?
BECAUSE HE WANTS IT.
BUT THAT'S BULLSHIT, MAN.
I HAVE BRIEFED THIS GUY
AT LEAST A DOZEN TIMES MYSELF.
LISTEN, THE MAYOR'S
ASKED THE F.B.I. TO RUN
THIS TASK FORCE.
KEENAN HAS THE AXE
OVER YOU AND OVER ME.
IT'S TIME TO PUCKER UP,
JACK.
SORRY WE'RE LATE.
DOES EVERYBODY KNOW EVERYBODY?
SPECIAL AGENT IN CHARGE
BILL KEENAN.
AND, BILL, THIS IS HEAD OF
THE ORGANIZED CRIME SQUAD
FRANK JENNINGS
DETECTIVE PHIL KELLY
AND DETECTIVE JACK VALENTINE.
'MORNING, COUNSELOR.
Phil:
THE NUMBER-TWO MAN
IN THE MASSINO FAMILY,
A.K.A. TONY D,
SICILIAN, A REAL
OLD-SCHOOL KNEE-BREAKER.
WHOEVER TOOK TONY OUT
HAD TO BE AN INSIDER.
NO ONE KNEW
ABOUT THE GIRL.
RIGHT NOW
THE BIG QUESTION IS
WHO ON THE INSIDE
SENT THOSE HITTERS
TO WHACK OUT TONY D.
IS THAT THE GIRL?
SHE'S BEAUTIFUL.
IS SHE COOPERATING?
SO FAR JUST NAME, RANK
AND SERIAL NUMBER.
STANDARD ARM PIECE, I'D SAY,
DOES SOME MODELING AROUND TOWN.
YEAH, WELL, WITH ALL DUE
RESPECT, KEENAN,
- I THINK SHE'S A LITTLE
MORE THAN THAT.
- YEAH? HOW?
WELL, IN THAT SITUATION
STANDARD ARM PIECE GOES
CATATONIC.
THIS CHICK-- SHE--
SHE HARDLY BLINKED.
WHAT'S ON THE TAPES?
A LOT OF SEXY STUFF,
OOH-ING AND AH-ING.
TONY REALLY HAD IT
FOR THIS GIRL.
LET'S FORGET THE GIRL
FOR A SECOND.
SHOW US THE SUSPECTS.
WHO DO YOU THINK
ORDERED THE HIT?
Phil:
JOE MASSINO,
ALSO KNOWN AS JOE BUDDHA,
HEAD OF THE BUFFALO FARM TEAM
FOR THE CRIME FAMILY
IN NEW YORK CITY.
AS BUFFALO'S UNDERBOSS,
HE WAS THE ONLY ONE
WHO HAD THE AUTHORITY
TO ISSUE THE HIT
ON TONY D--
THAT IS,
IF THE HIT WAS OFFICIAL.
JOE BUDDHA HAS INTENSE
CONVERSATIONS WITH PARKING
METERS IN LITTLE ITALY.
I THINK HE NEEDS HELP
PUTTING ON HIS PANTS
IN THE MORNING.
YOU THINK SO?
I DON'T.
HE STILL WEARS THE HAT.
MAYBE HE FOUND OUT
TONY WAS GONNA TURN
STATE'S EVIDENCE.
YEAH?
AND HOW'D HE DO THAT?
HAS TO BE A LEAK.
WHO ELSE YOU GOT?
Phil:
WELL, BESIDES JOE,
THE OTHER FAMILY INSIDER
WHO MIGHT HAVE SENT
THE HITTERS AFTER TONY D
IS MICHAEL NOCERA.
MICHAEL NOCERA,
A.K.A. THE YUPPIE DON.
A REAL GENERATION GAP
BETWEEN HIM, TONY AND JOE.
WORD IS, MICHAEL IS ITCHING
TO TAKE JOE BUDDHA'S PLACE
AS HEAD OF
THE MASSINO FAMILY. JACK.
MICHAEL IS
LIKE THE POSTER BOY
FOR UPWARD MOBILITY.
HE WENT TO PRINCETON...
- TILL THEY KICKED HIM OUT.
...DEVELOPS REAL ESTATE,
HAS A PIECE OF A
RECORD COMPANY,
PULLS IN A COUPLE
EXTRA MILLION A WEEK
FOR JOE BUDDHA
AND THE LATE TONY D
IN THE GASOLINE TAX SCAM.
THE COUNTY, STATE AND FEDS
ALL COLLECT TAX
ON GASOLINE.
NOCERA RUNS 300 MILLION
GALLONS A MONTH THROUGH
FIVE STATES.
COLLECTS THE TAX,
CLOSES IT DOWN AND
KEEPS THE TAXES.
SHELL COMPANIES
WITHIN SHELL COMPANIES,
REGISTERED BACK TO SOME GUY
NAMED JUAN IN PANAMA--
YESTERDAY'S NEWS,
OLD HAT.
MAYBE TONY HAS A BEEF
WITH SOMEBODY IN NEW YORK
OR LAS VEGAS.
LIKE WHO?
YOU GOT NOTHING,
GENTLEMEN.
YOU'RE GRASPING AT STRAWS.
EXCUSE ME, KEENAN,
WEREN'T YOU THE ONE THAT WANTED
O.C. SHOW-AND-TELL DAY?
WHAT I WANT TO KNOW
IS WHY A DETECTIVE
WITH VALENTINE'S HISTORY
WAS TAKEN OFF A DESK
FOR SOMETHING THIS BIG.
ALL DUE RESPECT,
IT'S WHERE HE BELONGS.
JACK'S THE ONE
KNOWS THESE GUYS.
HE'S GOT ALL
THE RELATIONSHIPS.
YEAH, PLUS
HE'S A GOOD COP.
WELL, HE USED TO BE,
SURE,
BUT I NEED SOMEBODY WHO'S
HITTING ON ALL CYLINDERS.
IF JACK MAY SPEAK
FOR HIMSELF FOR A MINUTE,
KEENAN,
THAT'S ALL HISTORY.
IT TOOK YOU
SIX GODDAMN MONTHS
TO SET UP TONY D.
- YOU'VE ONLY GOT TWO WEEKS.
- FOR WHAT?
TO GET ME SOMETHING
TO ROLL THESE GUYS UP.
YOU KNOW,
YOU GLIDE UP IN HERE
THREATENING PEOPLE.
YOU THREATEN FRANK.
AND NOW YOU START
THREATENING ME.
JACK.
I'M COOL, MAN.
TWO WEEKS, THAT'S IT.
WHAT DO YOU SAY, JACK?
- I SAY WE FIND THE LEAK.
WHERE DO YOU START?
TONY D'S GIRL IS
AS GOOD A PLACE AS NAY.
THAT'S A WASTE OF TIME.
WELL, RIGHT NOW, KEENAN,
THAT'S ALL WE GOT.
OKAY.
BUT DON'T COME BEGGING
FOR YOUR JOB BACK
WHEN IT DOESN'T
WORK OUT.
GENTLEMEN, COUNSELOR.
DETECTIVE VALENTINE,
COULD I HAVE A WORD WITH YOU?
THANK YOU,
DETECTIVE KELLY.
WELL, THAT CERTAINLY
WAS FUN.
WHAT IF KEENAN COMES BACK
FOR HIS BOW TIE?
I DON'T CARE ABOUT KEENAN.
I CARE ABOUT YOU.
YOU LOOK LIKE YOU'VE LOST
A LOT OF WEIGHT.
WELL, THE NICE THING ABOUT
A LITTLE ANXIETY
IS YOU LOSE WEIGHT WITHOUT
HAVING TO DO ON A DIET.
AND YOU LOOK LIKE YOU'RE NOT
GETTING ENOUGH SLEEP EITHER.
ARE YOU STILL HAVING
THOSE DREAMS?
- YOU MEAN THE NIGHTMARES?
- MM-HMM.
A TRIPLE FEATURE
EVERY NIGHT.
YOU KNOW, YOU SHOULD
LET ME COOK YOU DINNER
LATER ON IN THE WEEK.
I THOUGHT WE WEREN'T
DOING THAT ANYMORE.
JACK, IT'S JUST DINNER,
NOT YOUR HAND
IN MARRIAGE.
THINK ABOUT IT.
OH, HI, SUGAR PIE.
NOW WHAT ARE YOU DOING
BACK DOWN HERE?
WELL, I MISSED YOU.
AND I WANTED TO GET
A LITTLE INFORMATION.
WHAT DO YOU NEED?
- A WOMAN NAMED ALMA ANSON.
- OKAY.
NOW SHE'S A WITNESS
IN THE TONY DENISIO
MURDER CASE.
WHAT DO YOU WANT
TO KNOW?
ANY LITTLE TIDBIT
YOU CAN GET ME.
♪ WHEN THEY TURN
THE LIGHTS OUT ♪
♪ THE FACE IS
IN THE SHADOW... ♪
WE'RE FINE.
- HEY, HO, HO.
- HEY, JACK.
- YOU LOOK GREAT, MAN.
- HOLY SHIT. WELL...
- HEY, A DRINK, COME ON.
- NO, NO, NOT RIGHT NOW.
NO, NO, I--
- HEY, TOMMY, TOMMY.
- WHAT?
LET ME TALK TO YOU A SECOND.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
ABOUT WHAT?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
ABOUT TONY.
OH, FUCK, IT'S CRAZY.
IT'S NUTS, MAN.
NO, NO, NO, NO,
TOMMY, TOMMY,
NOW HOW'S YOUR
BROTHER DOING?
GREAT.
VINCENT'S DOING GREAT.
THAT'S GOOD, 'CAUSE, YOU KNOW,
IT SEEMS MAYBE YOU FORGOT
- I HELPED HIM OUT
WITH HIS EARLY PAROLE.
- HEY, I AIN'T FORGOT.
YOU WERE GREAT, DETECTIVE.
YOU WERE A BIG HELP, OKAY?
OKAY, THEN HELP ME OUT.
TOMMY, GIVE ME SOMETHING.
I KNOW YOU'VE SEEN
THIS KIND OF SHIT BEFORE.
TELL ME ABOUT TONY.
YEAH, I THINK IT'S
ONE OF THOSE THINGS,
YOU KNOW--
YOU'RE NEVER GONNA
FIND OUT WHO DID
ALL OF THIS.
LIKE MAYBE 20 YEARS
FROM NOW, YOU KNOW,
YOU MIGHT FIND OUT THAT--
TOMMY, TOMMY,
I AIN'T GOT 20 YEARS.
TELL ME SOMETHING.
WHAT ABOUT THAT TALL,
SKINNY BLOND GIRL
HE WAS SEEING?
I'M BEING
HONEST HERE, JACK.
WHAT CAN I TELL YOU?
I GOTTA GO.
- TOMMY.
- CALL ME, CALL ME.
( crows cawing )
- ( speaking Latin )
( camera shutter
clicking )
HEY, HEY, LOOK WHO'S PAYING
MICHAEL NOCERA A VISIT.
YEAH, TONY D'S
NUMBER-ONE GUYS.
HE SEEM HAPPY ABOUT IT
TO YOU?
IT'S A FUNERAL, JACK.
HE'S NOT SUPPOSED TO
LOOK HAPPY.
NO, MAN, THAT'S BULLSHIT.
THEY'RE LEANING ON HIM, MAN.
THREE-TO-TWO IT'S 'CAUSE
NO ONE KNOWS FOR SURE
WHO KILLED TONY D.
WHAT, YOU THINK NOCERA?
HE'S NOT THAT STUPID.
Jack:
HEY, MAN, HOLD ON NOW.
HEY, LOOK WHO
SHOWED UP.
GOD DAMN.
- YOU BITCH.
- UH-OH.
YOU BITCH.
WHORE!
HOW DARE YOU?
WHO DO YOU THINK
YOU ARE?
HEY, WHATEVER YOU'RE
THINKING, DON'T DO IT.
PHIL, THEY KNOW WE'RE HERE.
I'M JUST GONNA RATTLE
THE CAGE A LITTLE BIT.
- WHAT THE HELL FOR?
- TO PISS OF THE WILD ANIMALS.
- NOW TRUST ME ON THIS.
I KNOW WHAT I'M DOING.
- JACK.
SON OF A BITCH.
OH, SORRY,
I'M A LITTLE LATE.
A GUY IS DEAD.
NOW THIS IS ALL BULLSHIT.
YOU ARE OUT OF ORDER.
WAIT, WAIT, WAIT,
JOEY, JOEY, TECHNICALLY
I HAD A RELATIONSHIP
WITH TONY TOO.
I CAN'T PAY
MY LAST RESPECTS?
WHAT DID I SAY?
JUST LEAVE US
THE FUCK ALONE.
ALL RIGHT.
I CAN SEE WHEN
I'M NOT WANTED.
OKAY.
MICHAEL, FELLOWS.
( sighs )
THE GUY GIVES ME
A LARGE PAIN.
YOU KNOW THAT MAN?
A LONG TIME AGO,
FROM THE NEIGHBORHOOD.
IS THAT ALL?
HE USED TO BE AROUND
ALL THE TIME,
ALWAYS POKING
HIS NOSE IN.
YEAH.
HOW GOOD DO YOU KNOW HIM?
JUST ANOTHER HUMP
WITH A BADGE, JOE.
YOU SEE ANYTHING IN THERE,
ANYONE YOU RECOGNIZE?
HUH-UH, SORRY.
IT ALL HAPPENED
TOO QUICKLY.
( through speaker )
I didn't get a good look.
Okay.
WHAT SCHOOL
DID YOU GO TO?
ST. MARY'S, BOSTON,
TILL THEY KICKED ME OUT
FOR TALKING BACK
TO THE NUNS.
MM. FAMILY?
DOES IT UPSET YOU IF I ASK
YOU ABOUT YOUR FAMILY?
YOU CAN'T UPSET ME,
DETECTIVE.
GOOD.
IF YOU MUST KNOW, MY MOTHER
DIED WHEN I WAS FIVE.
MY FATHER DIED
WHEN I WAS EIGHT.
How long have you
known Tony D?
- ONE MONTH.
- WHERE DID YOU MEET?
WHERE THE GIRLS
MEET THE BOYS--
AT SOME PARTY.
DID IT MAYBE BOTHER YOU
WHO HE WAS?
THAT THAT WITNESS
GOT KILLED--
THAT LADY YOU WERE
SUPPOSE TO PROTECT?
DOES IT UPSET YOU
WHEN I ASK YOU ABOUT
YOUR PAST, DETECTIVE?
WHY DON'T WE JUST STAY
FOCUSED ON YOU?
YOU'RE UPSET,
but you can't show it.
JUST ANSWER
MY QUESTIONS.
WHY DID TONY D COME
TO YOUR HOUSE THAT NIGHT?
WHY DID YOUR WIFE
LEAVE YOU?
COUNSEL, YOU WANT
TO TELL YOUR CLIENT
TO QUIT PLAYING GAMES
AND ANSWER
MY QUESTIONS?
( whispers )
MEN LIKE TONY DON'T TALK
TO WOMEN LIKE ME
ABOUT BUSINESS.
AND WHAT DID YOU THINK
TONY'S BUSINESS WAS?
DO I LOOK STUPID
TO YOU, DETECTIVE?
I KNEW EXACTLY
WHAT TONY WAS.
HE WAS GOOD TO ME
AND TIMES ARE TOUGH.
SO IF YOU'RE GONNA
CHARGE ME WITH SOMETHING,
YOU GO RIGHT AHEAD.
OTHERWISE I WOULD LIKE
TO LEAVE.
GO AHEAD.
I'M THROUGH WITH YOU FOR NOW.
THANK YOU FOR YOUR TIME.
( gasps )
OH, YOU SCARED ME.
- HOW DID YOU GET IN?
( music playing )
I STILL GOT MINE.
OH.
FLOWERS--
OH, THEY'RE BEAUTIFUL.
- HI.
LET ME DO THIS
FOR YOU.
GO AHEAD.
WAS THERE TRAFFIC?
NO, IT WAS COOL.
GET YOUR JACKET?
( sighs )
WOULD YOU LIKE
SOME WINE?
NO, SHIT.
YOU KNOW, THERE'S SOMETHING
ABOUT A MAN IN THE KITCHEN
THAT REALLY
TURNS ME ON.
REMEMBER WHAT WE SAID?
NO, I DON'T REMEMBER.
JACK.
LET'S GO UPSTAIRS.
HEY.
JACK?
YOU KNOW, YOU'D BETTER
QUIT BLAMING YOURSELF.
OKAY, SO YOU GOT TOO CLOSE
TO A WITNESS-- NOT SMART.
BUT YOU DIDN'T PULL
THE TRIGGER.
ARE YOU GONNA SEND ME
A BILL FOR ALL THIS
FREE ANALYSIS?
NO, SHE KNEW IT WAS
DANGEROUS TO WEAR A WIRE.
SHE WANTED TO DO IT.
IT WOULD PROBABLY BE BETTER
IF WHEN YOU CAME HERE
YOU WERE READY
TO BE HERE.
THE SEA LION'S
GONNA GET YOU.
IT'S GONNA GET YOU.
( applause )
♪ Rainy days
and lonely nights ♪
♪ I feel... ♪
♪ All my affection
I gave onto you ♪
♪ Your smile
brings me joy ♪
♪ Your love makes me
happy ♪
♪ You know
that wherever I am ♪
♪ I'll run to you ♪
♪ For you are
my love, you ♪
♪ 'Cause you bring me
sunshine ♪
♪ In the rain ♪
♪ You bring me joy
when I feel in pain ♪
♪ When I am down ♪
♪ And feel alone... ♪
THANK YOU.
EXCUSE ME.
( knocks )
HEY.
REMEMBER ME?
OH, WHO ARE YOU
GONNA CALL?
MY ATTORNEY.
WHO DO YOU THINK?
OH, YOU DON'T NEED
TO DO THAT.
THIS IS AN UNOFFICIAL
VISIT, IF THAT'S OKAY.
WELL, I BELIEVE I'VE ANSWERED
ALL YOUR QUESTIONS ALREADY.
I HAVE ONE MORE.
OKAY, WELL, I'VE GOT
ONE QUESTION FOR YOU TOO.
- ( clicks )
- YOU FIRST.
WHAT'S WITH THE RECORDER?
PROTECTION.
I ALWAYS LIKE
TO BE PROTECTED.
RIGHT, QUESTION:
WHY WOULD WHOEVER KILLED
TONY D LEAVE YOU ALIVE?
SO YOU THINK
I'M IN DANGER?
WELL, I THINK
THERE'S A GOOD CHANCE
THAT THEY'RE GONNA COME
PAY YOU A VISIT, YEAH.
WELL, I'M NOT
THAT WORRIED.
WELL, I JUST THOUGHT
YOU MIGHT THINK
IT WAS A GOOD IDEA
TO HAVE A FRIEND
THAT WAS A COP.
WHAT EXACTLY DO YOU MEAN
BY "FRIEND"?
FRIEND-- I TALK, YOU TALK,
THAT KIND OF STUFF.
WELL, FRIENDSHIP IS
SOMETHING YOU FEEL.
IT'S SOMETHING
IN YOUR SOUL.
IT'S NOT AN EXCHANGE
FOR A PAYOFF.
ARE YOU STILL WATCHING ME,
DETECTIVE?
I THINK YOU HAVE
SOMETHING A LITTLE MORE
INTERESTING IN MIND
THAN JUST FRIENDS.
YOU KNOW, THIS--
THIS MIGHT COME
AS A TOTAL SURPRISE,
BUT I DON'T FIND
YOUR TALL, LANKY ASS
IRRESISTIBLE AT ALL.
LOOK, BOYS AND GIRLS
IS THE SUBJECT I'M NEVER
WRONG ABOUT.
ME,
DO YOU?
NO, I DON'T KNOW YOU
PERSONALLY,
BUT THE WORLD'S FULL OF MEN
THAT WANT TO BE MY FRIEND.
ALL RIGHT.
IF YOU CHANGE YOUR MIND
AND YOU DECIDE
YOU CAN USE ONE MORE
MAN FRIEND
IN THE WORLD OF MEN
THAT WANT TO BE
YOUR FRIENDS,
MY NUMBER'S
IN THE BACK.
THANK YOU
FOR YOUR TIME.
OH, ONE MORE THING:
UH, HOW DID YOU KNOW
THAT PERSONAL STUFF
ABOUT ME?
YOU, YOUR WITNESS,
YOUR BREAKDOWN--
COME ON, JACK,
IT WAS ALL IN THE PAPERS.
OKAY.
WAIT, I DIDN'T GET
TO ASK YOU MY QUESTION.
DID IT BOTHER YOU
THAT TONY DIED?
I'VE SEEN A LOT OF PEOPLE
DIE A LOT OF DIFFERENT WAYS.
WELL, THAT'S NOT
AN ANSWER.
ARE YOU HAPPY
THAT THEY SHOT HIM?
I THINK YOUR BOYFRIEND WAS
A LOW-ON-THE-FOOD-CHAIN
PIECE OF SHIT
AND THE WORLD IS PROBABLY
BETTER OFF WITHOUT HIM.
HMM.
JACK VALENTINE,
- A MAN OF FIRM OPINIONS.
- ( clicks )
HEY, LINA.
HEY, JACK.
YOU GOT ANYTHING FOR ME
ON THE ALMA ANSON THING?
WELL, I CHECKED
MEDICAL,
INTERNAL REVENUE,
COLLEGES.
- AND?
- THERE'S NO RECORD OF HER.
THERE'S NO ST. MARY'S
IN BOSTON.
I MEAN, SHE REALLY
DOESN'T EXIST.
I DON'T KNOW.
MAYBE SHE'S USING
AN ALIAS.
THANK YOU.
( insects chirping )
( camera shutter clicks )
A WEIRD DAMN THING, MAN.
YOU KNOW, SHE'S GOTTA BE OUT
BY THE END OF THE MONTH.
TONY D'S WIDOW
MADE SURE OF THAT,
CANCELED
THE GOLD CARD TOO.
POOR LITTLE LAMB.
PARTNER,
YOU KNOW, MAYBE WE'RE
CHASING OUR TAIL HERE.
NO, MAN, WE SHAKE
EVERY FUCKING TREE
TILL SOMETHING
FALLS OUT.
COME ON, ALMA,
SHOW US WHAT YOU GOT.
( playing piano )
( camera shutter clicks )
( static hissing )
- PHIL, WHAT'S THAT STATIC?
- I'M WORKING ON IT.
Hello.
It's me.
SHIT.
WHAT'S GOING ON, MAN?
THE PHONE'S DEAD--
THE BUG.
- WELL, FIX THE DAMN THING, MAN.
- WELL, WHAT DO YOU THINK
I'M DOING?
YOU'RE THROWING
A PARTY TONIGHT
AND YOU DON'T INVITE--?
WHO IS SHE TALKING TO?
I DON'T KNOW.
I DIDN'T HEAR.
IT CUT OUT JUST AFTER
SHE PICKED UP.
YOU DID, BUT I JUST WANTED
TO HEAR YOUR VOICE.
IS THAT SUPPOSED
TO BE ON?
NO, THAT'S FINE, OKAY?
JUST LEAVE IT ALONE.
I CAN'T GET ANYTHING.
I CAN'T GET HIM.
GOOD.
SHIT.
PHIL, YOU GET OVER THERE.
YOU REDO EVERY BUG
YOU'VE GOT WITH THE BEST
SHIT YOU'VE GOT, MAN.
- I WANT HER ANSWERING MACHINE
BUGGED-- EVERYTHING.
- ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
I'M GONNA TAIL HER, MAN.
DAMN IT.
( engine starts )
♪ Oh ♪
♪ I never meant
to hurt ♪
♪ The one I love ♪
♪ Listen ♪
♪ Looking back on times
when I ♪
♪ Was living a lie ♪
♪ Reeling with
the things of my past ♪
♪ Many times I tried
to face it ♪
♪ But I just ran away,
my fears were so great... ♪
WHAT THE HELL
ARE YOU DOING HERE?
I SAID WAIT TILL I GET
IN TOUCH, DIDN'T I?
MICHAEL, I MISS YOU.
NO, NOT HERE,
FOR CHRISSAKE.
COME ON.
EXCUSE ME.
- YEAH?
- I NEED TO SEE
YOUR INVITATION.
- OH, WHO ARE YOU?
- I'M MICHAEL'S PUBLICIST.
MICHAEL WANTS PUBLICITY?
YEAH?
YEAH, I DO A VERY
GOOD JOB.
- YEAH.
- YEAH, YOUR INVITATION.
OH.
HERE, IT'S MY V.I.P. CARD,
MASTER SHIELD.
I NEVER LEAVE HOME
WITHOUT IT.
( music continues
in distance )
MM, GOD, I MISSED YOU.
WAIT.
OH, YOU GOT TIME
TO TALK TO ME?
- LOOK, I WANT TO EXPLAIN.
- NO, NO, THERE'S NOTHING
YOU HAVE TO EXPLAIN.
- I KNOW YOUNG LOVE
WHEN I SEE IT.
- NO, NO, YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND.
WHAT?
WHAT DON'T I UNDERSTAND?
I WORK OUT EVERY DAY.
I LOVE MY WIFE.
I LOVE MY FAMILY.
MICHAEL, LOOK,
YOU ARE IN GREAT SHAPE
AND YOU JUST GOT AN UNUSUAL
WAY OF SHOWING YOUR LOVE.
NO, NO, LOOK, LOOK,
YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT
SHE'S LIKE, ALL RIGHT?
THE WOMAN IS OBSESSED
WITH ME.
WELL, THAT'S TOO BAD,
BECAUSE YOU JUST BECAME
MY NUMBER-ONE SUSPECT
IN THE TONY D MURDER.
I THINK MAYBE
YOU TOOK A WRONG IDEA.
ALMA IS TONY'S GIRL.
WE'RE JUST FRIENDS.
MICHAEL, YOU NEED TO TAKE
YOUR HANDS OFF ME.
- SHE GOT YOU ACTING
KIND OF CRAZY, MAN.
- OH, IS THAT RIGHT?
- YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
- WELL, I'VE SEEN YOU
LOOKING AT HER TOO.
HERE'S THE DEAL:
YOU TURN STATE'S WITNESS,
I'LL GET YOU SOMEWHERE SAFE.
- REALLY?
- MM-HMM.
FUCK YOU.
NO, FUCK YOU.
SEE, YOU FUCKED YOURSELF.
YOU'D BETTER HOPE
YOU CALL ME BEFORE YOUR
UNCLE JOEY CALLS YOU.
YOU PAWN.
YOU PIECE OF SHIT.
HEY, EXCUSE ME.
BACK UP, BACK UP.
FIVE-OH.
- CARRY ON.
- THANK YOU.
GIVE ME A LITTLE SPACE.
( car horns honking )
( people shouting )
SO SHE WAS BANGING
NOCERA AND TONY D
AT THE SAME TIME?
I'M TELLING YOU,
SHE WAS SEEING THEM
BOTH, MAN.
THIS CASE IS STARTING
TO COME TOGETHER,
PARTNER.
YOU KNOW THOSE WEIRD
CAT STATUES SHE HAS
IN HER APARTMENT?
THEY'RE LIKE
CHINESE WISH DOLLS,
LIKE BIRTHDAY CANDLES,
LIKE WHEN YOUR
WISH COMES TRUE,
YOU PAINT THE EYE IN.
- SO?
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN, SO?
SO HOW MANY
STATUES SHE GOT?
THREE.
HOW MANY HAVE THE EYES
PAINTED IN?
NEVER REALLY LOOKED.
ONE.
WHAT IF THAT ONE EYE
WAS FOR TONY D?
I DON'T KNOW, PARTNER.
I THINK YOU'RE KIND OF
STRETCHING IT NOW.
NO, NO,
NO STRETCHING, PHIL.
THIS IS COMING TOGETHER.
HEY, JOE, JOE,
- YOU WANT TO CROSS
THE STREET?
- HUH?
OH, KNOCK IT OFF.
YOU NEED A LITTLE
HELP HERE? COME ON.
- HELP I DON'T NEED.
- OH, YES, YOU DO.
EVERYBODY KNOWS YOU'RE STILL
RUNNING THE SHOW, JOE,
EXCEPT FOR MAYBE
MICHAEL NOCERA.
NOW THAT'S AN AMBITIOUS
YOUNG GUY, MAN.
OH, YEAH.
YOU KNOW, HE WIPED OUT
YOUR FRIEND TONY D
RIGHT UNDER OUR NOSE.
JOE, THERE'S NO LOVE LOST
BETWEEN MICHAEL NOCERA
AND TONY D.
NOW MAYBE TONY WAS GONNA
FLIP STATE'S EVIDENCE,
MAYBE NOT.
MAYBE THAT JUST GAVE
MICHAEL THE EXCUSE
HE NEEDED, HUH?
I DON'T KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
I'M TALKING
ABOUT TONY'S GIRL.
MICHAEL'S DOING HER--
YOU KNOW, THE TALL
ONE AT THE FUNERAL.
I SAW IT WITH MY OWN EYES.
YOU DON'T FIT INTO NOCERA'S
VISION OF THE FAMILY
ANY MORE THAN YOUR FRIEND
TONY D DID.
BUT THE F.B.I.--
THEY GOT TWO PLACES.
THEY GOT
NEW MEXICO AND ARIZONA.
YOU LIKE THE SUN?
HEY, BOSS,
EVERYTHING OKAY?
GO FUCK YOUR MOTHER
IN NEW MEXICO.
JOEY, I COULD BE
YOUR RETIREMENT PLAN.
- ( phones ringing )
- ( people chattering )
NOW MICHAEL NOCERA
DIDN'T ACTUALLY PULL
THE TRIGGER ON TONY D,
BUT HE DID
MAKE IT HAPPEN.
AND HE DID IT WITHOUT
UNCLE JOE'S BLESSING.
YOU THINK YOU CAN
SQUEEZE HIM?
HEY, I THINK HE'D RATHER
FLIP FOR US AND GIVE UP
HIS WHOLE DAMN CREW
THAN FACE A SHOWDOWN
WITH JOE BUDDHA.
IF YOU CAN MAKE THIS
AIRTIGHT IN EIGHT DAYS,
GREAT.
TONY AND I GO BACK
A LONG TIME.
UNDERSTAND?
THE GUY HAD PROBLEMS.
HE WAS TURNING
STATE'S EVIDENCE, JOE.
YOU DID THE RIGHT THING.
NOBODY'S SAYING DIFFERENT.
ARE YOU FUCKING
LISTENING TO ME?
I'M NOT THE ONE
WHO ORDERED THE HIT
ON TONY D.
THERE'S A WAY TO DEAL
WITH PROBLEMS LIKE THIS.
AND NOBODY DOES ANYTHING
UNLESS I SAY SO.
UNDERSTOOD?
UNDERSTOOD.
TONY WAS A GOOD FRIEND.
HE'S A BACKDOOR STUGOTS,
A POTENTIAL RAT,
A FUCKING YELLOW DOG,
BUT I DEAL WITH IT,
NO ONE ELSE.
MAYBE IT WAS CARLUCCI
FROM VEGAS, HUH?
YOU KNOW,
SOME PEOPLE THINK
I'M READY FOR
A PARK BENCH.
- ( chuckles )
- NOBODY THINKS THAT, JOE.
WHAT ABOUT YOU, MIKEY?
YOU THINK YOU'RE READY
TO DRIVE THE TRUCK?
NOW LET ME TELL YOU,
IT'S A VERY FAST
FUCKING VEHICLE.
ANOTHER THING
THAT BOTHERS ME--
THAT GIRL TONY D
WAS GOING WITH
GIVES ME A BAD FEELING,
VERY BAD.
( tires screech )
- ( tires screech )
( horn honks )
Tony.
Yeah?
Did I ever tell you
about the time I was
in boarding school?
Nah, you didn't.
It was 102 in the shade.
( knocks on door )
Oh, baby.
It was so hot...
- YEAH.
Alma:
IT'S ME.
- ALMA?
- YEAH.
You know how
I dozed off?
How?
I was naked
under the sheets.
( turns off player )
COME ON IN.
YOU WERE RIGHT.
I DO NEED A FRIEND.
I DON'T KNOW, JACK.
YOU SURPRISE ME.
YEAH, WELL,
IT'S A SUBLET.
HAVE A SEAT.
A DRINK?
GOT A GLASS?
NOT A CLEAN ONE.
I'LL PASS.
( turns on player )
And then
a little hand
dropped down...
( turns off )
YOU'RE A HELL OF
A STORYTELLER.
DID YOU MAKE THAT SHIT UP
OR DID YOU LIKE READ IT
IN A BOOK OR WHAT?
ACTUALLY IT WASN'T
A BOARDING SCHOOL.
IT WAS AN ORPHANAGE.
NOW YOU'RE TRYING
TO PLAY ME, HUH?
YOU ADD SOME
VIOLINS IN THERE?
TRYING TO PUSH
MY BUTTONS?
I GOT NO BUTTONS
LEFT TO PUSH.
WANT TO BET?
SEE, NOW MICHAEL AND TONY--
THEY MAY LIKE ALL THIS,
BUT ME-- YOU NEED TO FIND
YOURSELF ANOTHER SUCKER.
WHAT, ARE YOU AFRAID
OF ME?
YOU CAME BY HERE
TO TELL ME SOMETHING.
WHY DON'T YOU
CUT TO THE CHASE?
WHAT IF YOU DON'T LIKE
WHAT YOU HEAR?
LIKE WHAT YOU TOLD
MICHAEL NOCERA TO GET HIM
TO KILL TONY D?
YOU'RE GIVING ME
TOO MUCH CREDIT, JACK.
THEY'RE JUST
NATURAL PREDATORS.
SO WHAT WOULD MICHAEL
THE NATURAL PREDATOR
THINK OF YOU
WITH ME RIGHT NOW?
IT'S OVER.
HE'S IN THE PAST.
WHY DON'T I
BELIEVE YOU?
BECAUSE YOU'RE A COP.
IT'S YOUR JOB.
( phone ringing )
( answering machine
clicks )
Hi. This is Jack.
Please leave a message
after the beep.
( machine beeps )
Woman:
Jack, I know you're there.
Pick up, come on.
We need to talk.
SOUNDS LIKE SOMEBODY
NEEDS TO TALK TO YOU
PRETTY BAD.
Jack, pick up.
- EXCUSE ME A MINUTE.
Jack, I'm not
gonna hang up.
Pick up.
Come on, we need to talk.
Jack, pick up the phone.
YEAH.
NO, NO, I JUST RAN
THE PHOTO.
CAN I CALL YOU BACK
IN FIVE MINUTES?
RIGHT, YEAH,
I'LL CALL YOU
IN FIVE MINUTES.
RIGHT.
ALMA?
Jack:
THIS GIRL'S READY
TO TALK.
NOW WE'VE GOT
A BREAK HERE.
LET'S ROLL WITH IT.
WHAT BREAK? SHE COMES
TO YOUR HOUSE. SHE SAYS
SHE WANTS TO HAVE DINNER.
WHAT, ALL OF A SUDDEN
SHE FINDS YOU A WITTY
CONVERSATIONALIST?
JESUS.
IS THERE SOMETHING GOING ON
BETWEEN YOU AND THIS WITNESS
THAT I NEED TO KNOW
ABOUT, JACK?
NO.
I'M CULTIVATING
AN INFORMANT, THAT'S IT.
OKAY.
LOOK, JACK WILL BE
WEARING A WIRE.
I'LL BE IN THE TRUCK.
WE'LL GET EVERY WORD
ON TAPE.
I MEAN, IT'S WORTH
A SHOT.
Keenan:
ALL THIS GIRLFRIEND SHIT
IS MARGINAL.
TONY WAS SERVING US JOE
ON A PLATTER. HE FOUND OUT
ABOUT IT AND ICED HIM.
- IT'S REAL SIMPLE.
- IT WAS MICHAEL NOCERA.
- REALLY?
- REALLY.
LOOK, ALMA ANSON
IS NOT EVEN A REAL NAME.
SHE IS DYING
TO GIVE ME SOMETHING
I CAN USE TO SQUEEZE
MICHAEL NOCERA WITH.
I FEEL IT.
LET'S JUST GET IT
ON TAPE.
NOCERA WOULD
SELL OUT HIS GRANDMOTHER
TO AVOID GOING TO JAIL.
WE PUT A LITTLE
PRESSURE ON HIM, I THINK
HE'D GIVE US JOE BUDDHA.
YEAH. YOU KNOW,
I THINK I LIKED
THESE GUYS BETTER
WHEN THEY HAD
THE CODE OF SILENCE.
( chuckles )
NO SHIT.
OKAY, I'LL GO WITH IT,
BUT I WANT EVERYTHING
OFFICIAL AND ON RECORD.
AND I'M THE ONLY ONE
WHO CUTS A DEAL.
SO TELL ME A LITTLE BIT
ABOUT THIS TONY FELLOW.
TONY CAME INTO MY LIFE
AT A TIME WHEN I REALLY
NEEDED SOMEBODY.
Tony was a very
controlling man.
He had to know where
I was all the time.
So he was
a control freak.
( chuckles )
He was a control freak,
yeah.
SO YOU STARTED AN AFFAIR
WITH A CONTROL FREAK'S
BUSINESS PARTNER.
WELL, IT WASN'T SMART,
BUT I THINK
YOU OF ALL PEOPLE
SHOULD UNDERSTAND THAT.
( chuckles )
NO, LET'S LEAVE JACK
OUT OF THIS.
I'M THE LAST ONE TO PASS
JUDGMENT ON ANYBODY.
MM, SOUNDS LIKE
THE KIND OF GUY I NEED.
WHY? YOU GOT
MORE TO HIDE?
CURIOSITY KILLED
THE CAT, JACK.
BUT WHO KILLED TONY D?
DID YOU TELL NOCERA
THAT HE WAS GONNA TURN
STATE'S EVIDENCE?
DON'T BE SUCH A COP.
I-- I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
( static hissing )
JACK, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
( sighs )
( static stops )
- NO.
- HEY.
- GET AWAY.
ALMA, WAKE UP.
IT'S ME.
WHAT'S WRONG?
YOU DON'T WANT TO KNOW.
LOOK, IT WAS
AN INCREDIBLE NIGHT, OKAY?
LET'S JUST LEAVE IT
AT THAT.
( water running )
OH, SHIT.
HOW IS HE FEELING
THIS MORNING?
HE JUST WOKE UP.
THIS IS
THE THIRD NIGHT THIS WEEK
HE DIDN'T COME HOME.
YOUR PARTNER'S HERE.
( clock chiming )
GOOD MORNING.
YOU WANT SOME COFFEE?
YEAH, THAT'D BE GREAT.
HERE.
HELP YOURSELF.
I'M HAVING
HERBAL TEA.
- ( dog squealing )
- GO ON.
GO FIND YOUR MOTHER.
SO HOW ARE YOU
FEELING?
HOW AM I FEELING?
WELL, I WAS ON A LISTENING
POST LAST NIGHT
AND SOMEBODY MESSED
WITH MY GEAR.
YEAH, WE NEED TO TALK
ABOUT THAT.
COME ON.
YOU FORGOT ABOUT THE BUG
ON HER CELL PHONE, JACK.
YOU HEARD, HUH?
EVERY LAST WORD.
JUST ERASE
THOSE DAMN TAPES.
JUST-- JUST TELL THEM
THE EQUIPMENT MALFUNCTIONED
LIKE IT DID FOR US
THE OTHER DAY IN THE VAN.
THEY'RE NOT GONNA BUY THAT.
TWICE IN ONE WEEK?
COME ON.
THIS IS MY JOB.
PHIL, I'M YOUR PARTNER.
YOU KNOW I'D DO
THE SAME FOR YOU.
I'D BACK YOU UP.
CAN YOU GIVE ME
A LITTLE BREAK?
I GAVE YOU A BREAK, JACK.
I WENT TO THE MATS
FOR YOU.
YOU KNOW,
AND NOW IT'S BACK
TO THE SAME OLD SHIT.
( footsteps )
YOU SAID YOU'D MAKE
BREAKFAST FOR RUPERT.
( sighs )
IN A SECOND,
HONEY, OKAY?
I'LL GET IT.
I DON'T
BELIEVE THIS, MAN.
( chuckles )
FIRST TIME OUT OF THE BOX
IN OVER A YEAR AND, WELL--
I JUST HOPE
SHE WAS WORTH IT.
SHE WAS WORTH IT, MAN.
YEAH, WHY DON'T YOU JUST
SHOOT YOURSELF IN THE HEAD
AND SAVE EVERYBODY
THE TROUBLE?
HERE.
ARE YOU GONNA WORK
WITH ME OR NOT?
( sighs )
ALL RIGHT.
THANKS, MAN.
( phone ringing )
HELLO.
WHERE WERE YOU
LAST NIGHT?
COME ON,
YOU'RE NOT GONNA
START THAT AGAIN,
ARE YOU?
YOU KNOW, JOE'S GOONS
TOOK A SHOT AT ME.
WHAT?
MICHAEL, I'M NOT
WORRIED ABOUT ME.
I'M WORRIED WHAT
THEY'LL DO TO YOU.
EH?
FREAKIN' VIOLETS--
THESE PURPLES ONES
ARE BEAUTIFUL, BEAUTIFUL.
- I WANT SIX FLATS OF THESE.
- SIX OF THOSE.
- YEAH, I WANT THIS COLOR.
- YEAH.
AND THIS TOO.
GO RING THEM UP, EH?
OKAY, I'LL COME BACK
FOR THE REST LATER.
( dings )
( groaning )
( sirens wailing )
JOE, JOE, MAN,
I GOT ONE WORD FOR YOU--
ARIZONA.
GET HIM INSIDE.
EASY, EASY.
AND THEY DIDN'T SAY
WHO THEY WERE FROM?
Man:
NO, MA'AM.
THANK YOU.
HEY.
HMM?
WHY DON'T WE
GO AWAY SOMEWHERE,
GET AWAY
FROM ALL THIS,
START AGAIN TOGETHER,
START CLEAN?
AND I'M GONNA WEAR
A BIG T-SHIRT
SAYING
"JACK THE FUCK-UP."
HAVE YOU EVER BEEN
TO MEXICO?
NO.
WE COULD FLY
INTO OAXACA,
SPEND A FEW WEEKS
ON A BEACH
AT ESCONDIDO,
BUY A CAR CHEAP,
DRIVE TO YUCATAN,
MAYBE TRY COSTA RICA.
SOUNDS NICE.
MAYBE IN SOME OTHER
LIFETIME.
SWEETHEART,
WE ONLY HAVE THIS ONE.
- HEY, GEORGE.
- GOOD EVENING, SIR.
- SEE YOU, JOE.
- GOOD NIGHT, SIR.
GOOD NIGHT.
( jazz playing )
LET NOBODY SAY
ME AND VINCENT EVER
FORGOT A FAVOR.
YOU HELPED OUT
WITH THE PAROLE.
WE AIN'T FORGOT.
THAT'S GOOD, TOMMY,
BUT WHO'S EMMA DUCKWORTH?
YOU WAS ASKING AROUND
ABOUT ALMA, RIGHT?
SO THIS EMMA DUCKWORTH'S
HER GRANDMOTHER.
APPRECIATE THAT.
- THANK YOU, DEAR.
- YOU'RE DOING GREAT.
MISS DUCKWORTH,
DO YOU RECOGNIZE
THIS LADY RIGHT HERE?
OH, YES.
THIS IS MARIAN.
YOU KNOW,
WHEN SHE WAS YOUNG
SHE HAD A BEAUTIFUL
DOLL COLLECTION
AND SHE COULD PLAY
WITH IT
FOREVER AND EVER.
AND IT WAS REALLY--
EXCUSE ME, EXCUSE ME,
NOW WHAT DID YOU SAY
HER NAME WAS?
MARIAN HAMILTON.
YES, THIS IS MARIAN.
I WAS RIGHT THERE
IN THE CHURCH
THE DAY SHE WAS
CHRISTENED.
WHAT ABOUT
THIS GENTLEMAN HERE?
DO YOU RECOGNIZE
THAT FELLOW?
HMM, YES.
THIS IS FRED HAMILTON--
MARIAN'S FATHER,
VERY INTERESTING.
HE COULD READ
A BOOK THIS THICK
IN A DAY.
- PROLIFIC.
- YEAH.
WELL, LET ME ASK YOU
A QUESTION:
IF THIS IS HER DAD,
DID MARIAN SPENT ANY TIME
IN AN ORPHANAGE?
OH, FOR HEAVEN'S SAKES, NO.
BUT SHE SPENT TWO YEARS
IN A HOSPITAL.
WHAT KIND OF HOSPITAL?
AND SHE STILL IS
A BIT UNSTABLE.
POOR MARIAN,
SUCH A LOVELY GIRL.
( playing piano )
I'VE BEEN TRYING TO
REACH YOU ALL DAY SO I COULD
FIND OUT WHAT THE GIRL SAID.
BUT THEY SAID YOU TOOK
A FOUR-HOUR LUNCH. AND NOW
YOU EXPECT ME TO BELIEVE
THAT $150,000 WORTH
OF HIGH-TECH EQUIPMENT
JUST STOPPED WORKING?
YEAH, WELL, THESE THINGS HAPPEN.
IT HAPPENED TO ME AND PHIL
THE OTHER DAY IN THE VAN.
- IT HAPPENED LAST YEAR.
- ( phone rings )
VALENTINE.
YEAH.
SHIT.
( siren wailing )
AS YOU CAN SEE BEHIND ME,
THE POLICE ARE COMBING
THE AREA.
THEY'RE STILL WAITING
TO RELEASE THE IDENTITY...
- WHERE IS HE?
- IN THE CAR.
WHAT HAPPENED?
MULTIPLE STAB WOUNDS,
ABOUT A DOZEN,
FOR STARTERS.
( sighs )
YOU SHOULD HAVE CALLED,
MICHAEL.
IT'S A GAMBLE WE TOOK
AND WE LOST.
WHAT?
JOE GOT TO NOCERA
BEFORE WE COULD.
THE BAD NEWS IS,
WITHOUT NOCERA,
THE ONLY GUY LEFT
ON YOUR LIST THAT CAN
CRACK THIS FAMILY OPEN
IS JOE BUDDHA HIMSELF.
THE GOOD NEWS IS--
RECOGNIZE THIS?
IT'S ALMA ANSON'S SCARF,
JACK.
I SURE AM GLAD HER SLIPPERS
BED.
- YOU'RE EARLY.
- ARE YOU COMPLAINING?
- NOPE.
- ALL RIGHT.
KNOCK YOURSELF OUT.
- STAY WARM.
- ALL RIGHT, PARTNER.
( door opens
and closes )
( receding footsteps )
( knocks on door )
( gun clicks )
WHAT ARE YOU
DOING HERE?
WE NEED TO TALK,
MARIAN.
DON'T EVER
CALL ME THAT.
WELL, OF THESE NICE CATS,
YOU SEE, THE SHORT ONE
MUST BE FOR TONY D.
THAT WOULD MAKE THIS ONE
FOR MICHAEL NOCERA.
YOU REALLY DID A JOB
ON THOSE GUYS, HUH?
I DIDN'T NEED TO.
THEY LIVE IN A CRUEL WORLD.
THEY DID IT TO THEMSELVES.
SO YOU KEEP TELLING ME.
WHAT'S THIS FOR?
LOOK, I KNOW YOUR DAD
WAS AN ACCOUNTANT
FOR SEA LARK--
JOE BUDDHA'S LITTLE
GAS SCAM.
SO WHAT DO YOU KNOW
THAT GOT THESE GUYS
TO TURN ON EACH OTHER?
JOE BUDDHA DOESN'T DESERVE
TO LIVE AND BREATHE.
WHAT DID HE DO TO YOU?
HE KILLED MY FATHER.
Alma:
MY DAD WAS AN ACCOUNTANT,
AN HONEST ONE.
HE MADE THE MISTAKE
OF TAKING ON
THE SEA LARK BOOKS
FOR JOE BUDDHA,
MICHAEL NOCERA
AND TONY D.
BY THE TIME
MY DAD REALIZED
WHO HIS REAL
BOSSES WERE,
HE WAS IN TOO DEEP.
( gunshot )
YOU NEVER TOLD ANYBODY
WHAT YOU SAW?
OF COURSE I DID.
YOU THINK
THEY BELIEVED ME?
THE COPS SAID
IT WAS SUICIDE.
SOMEBODY GOT PAID OFF.
YOU'VE BEEN CARRYING THIS
FOR 15 YEARS.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO
ANYMORE.
DO YOU REALIZE
YOU'RE PROBABLY THE ONLY
LIVING WITNESS
THAT'S EVER SEEN JOE BUDDHA
COMMIT A MURDER HIMSELF?
YOU COULD FORCE HIM
TO TURN STATE'S EVIDENCE.
THIS COULD BE
THE BUST OF THE CENTURY.
THE U.S. ATTORNEY'S OFFICE
COULD HAND DOWN
DOZENS OF INDICTMENTS
RIGHT ACROSS THIS COUNTRY.
JOE BUDDHA'S GONNA WALK?
THAT'S JUSTICE ALL RIGHT.
JOE BUDDHA
IN WITNESS PROTECTION
IS A SMALL PRICE TO PAY
FOR PROSECUTIONS
ON THAT SCALE.
ALMA, YOU WANT TO NAIL
THESE GUYS?
YOU FUCKING REALLY
WANT TO NAIL THEM?
YOU COULD ROLL UP
HIS ENTIRE FAMILY.
WASTING THAT
SON OF A BITCH
WOULD FEEL
A WHOLE LOT BETTER.
YOU'RE NEVER GONNA GET
NEXT TO JOE WITH A GUN,
NOT NOW.
YOU NEED ME
TO GET TO HIM.
I CAN WORK IT OUT SO THAT
I'D BE THERE WITH YOU.
I WOULD BE THERE
TO PROTECT YOU.
LIKE YOU WERE THERE
WITH THAT OTHER WOMAN--
THE ONE
THAT WORE THE WIRE?
YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT.
FORGET I ASKED.
YOU WANTED TO SEE ME?
( Alma's voice )
Look, it was an incredible
night, okay?
Let's just leave it
at that.
( Jack's voice )
We'll have a lot
of nights like that.
( turns off player )
WHAT'S THE MATTER, JACK?
IT GETS BETTER.
YOU'RE SLEEPING
WITH A KEY SUSPECT
IN THE MOST IMPORTANT
O.C. INVESTIGATION
IN 20 YEARS.
AND WHAT'S WORSE, I THINK
YOU'RE PROTECTING HER.
EVERYONE WHO GETS MIXED UP
WITH THIS WOMAN
ENDS UP ON A SLAB
AT THE MORGUE.
DO YOU WANT
TO BE NEXT?
SALLY, I--
I AM SO CLOSE
TO GETTING SOMETHING.
YOU KNOW, WHAT'S TRAGIC
IS THAT THERE'S A PART OF ME
THAT WANTS
TO BELIEVE YOU.
I'M GONNA
HAVE TO HAVE JENNINGS
TAKE YOU OFF THE CASE.
AND THEN I'M GONNA HAVE
TO CALL I.A.D.
THERE'S GONNA BE
AN INVESTIGATION.
THIS IS A MESS.
LISTEN, I CAN DELIVER
JOE BUDDHA
IN 48 HOURS,
READY TO TURN
STATE'S EVIDENCE.
IMPOSSIBLE.
IF I DON'T DO THIS,
I'LL GIVE YOU MY BADGE
AND MY GUN
WITH PLEASURE.
- HEY, MOTHERFUCKER, YOU GOT
SOME 'SPLAINING TO DO.
- HEY, MAN, FUCK YOU.
YOU GO BEHIND MY BACK
AND GIVE THOSE TAPES TO
SALLY CLAIRE? WHY, PHIL?
I DIDN'T TELL CLAIRE
ANYTHING, ALL RIGHT?
SHE ALREADY KNEW
ABOUT YOU AND ALMA.
IT WAS EITHER
HAND OVER THE TAPES
OR LOSE MY FUCKING JOB.
SO YOU COULDN'T
TELL ME YOURSELF?
LOOK, JACK,
I'M SORRY, MAN,
BUT I NEED THIS JOB,
YOU KNOW?
I GOT A WIFE
THAT DEPENDS ON ME.
COME ON.
I WAS GONNA TELL YOU.
LOOK, YOU'D BETTER
TAKE IT EASY, YOU KNOW?
YOU LOSE IT AGAIN,
THEY'RE NOT JUST GONNA
GIVE YOU YOUR DESK JOB.
THEY'RE GONNA KICK YOU
OFF THE DAMN FORCE.
( knocks on door )
- YEAH?
IT'S ME.
OKAY, I'LL DO IT
YOUR WAY.
YOU WOULD HAVE LIKED
MY DAD.
I KNOW I WOULD HAVE.
DO YOU KNOW HOW BLUE
THE SKY IS IN MEXICO?
HUH-UH.
HOW BLUE?
IT IS BLUE LIKE
YOU HAVE NEVER SEEN.
AND I KNOW A PLACE
WHERE THE SAND ISN'T WHITE,
IT'S PINK.
PINK SAND?
I LIKE THAT.
Tommy:
...A MINIATURE STEINWAY,
RIGHT?
AND THE GENIE SAYS,
"I'M SORRY, LADY.
I THOUGHT YOU MEANT
A 9" PIANIST."
CUTE.
TOMMY, LET ME SEE YOU.
COME HERE.
HEY, JACK,
HOW IS IT GOING?
GOOD. LET ME
SEE YOU, PLEASE.
EXCUSE ME, GENTLEMEN.
SURE. WHAT'S HAPPENING?
LISTEN, I NEED TO GET
A WORD WITH JOEY B.
CAN YOU HOOK THAT UP
FOR ME?
JESUS, JACK, FUCK.
I'M GRATEFUL AND
EVERYTHING,
BUT YOU'RE PUTTING ME
ON THE FUCKING SPOT HERE.
TOMMY, ONE LITTLE
CONVERSATION.
PLEASE SIT DOWN.
SIT DOWN.
ONE LITTLE CONVERSATION,
THAT'S ALL I NEED.
AND YOU CAN DO THAT.
YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND,
DETECTIVE.
TWO BIG GUYS ARE DEAD.
NOBODY KNOWS WHERE
JOE IS EVEN.
ARE YOU SAYING
HE'S SCARED?
JOE? HE AIN'T BEEN SCARED
IN 30 YEARS.
HE'S WHAT YOU MIGHT CALL
CONCERNED, ALL RIGHT, BUT--
I'M CONCERNED.
EVERYBODY'S CONCERNED.
I'M JUST TRYING TO GET
THE MAN SOME USEFUL
INFORMATION.
OFFICIAL OR UNOFFICIAL?
I WANT TO HAVE DINNER
WITH THE GUY,
COMPLETELY OFF THE RECORD.
CAN YOU SET THAT UP?
I CAN'T BELIEVE
KEENAN AGREED TO THIS.
WELL, HE DIDN'T
ACTUALLY AGREE.
WHAT, YOU MEAN
HE DOESN'T KNOW?
NO, NOT EXACTLY.
WAIT, WAIT, WHAT THE FUCK
DO YOU MEAN, NOT EXACTLY?
KEENAN FINDS OUT THAT
WE'RE RUNNING OUR OWN
PERSONAL BLACK OPS HERE,
HE'S GONNA SHITCAN
THE BOTH OF US,
GOD DAMN IT.
PHIL, PHIL, LOOK,
JUST WORK WITH ME
ON THIS ONE, OKAY?
NOW YOU'RE THE ONE
THAT PIMPED ME ON THE TAPES
TO SALLY CLAIRE.
I PIMPED YOU?
YOU'RE THE ONE THAT GOT
INVOLVED WITH A WITNESS, JACK.
YOU'RE THE ONE THAT'S GOT HER
WEARING THE WIRE.
DOES THIS SOUND
FAMILIAR?
PHIL, ALL YOU GOTTA DO
IS SIT IN THIS LITTLE VAN,
PRESS "RECORD"
AND HOPE THIS SHIT WORKS.
CAN YOU PLEASE DO THAT?
HOW IS THIS GIRL
GONNA GET JOE B
TO TURN ANYWAY?
LET ME WORRY
ABOUT THAT, OKAY?
GET THE FUCK
OUT OF HERE.
OH, JESUS CHRIST.
DETECTIVE, MY PEOPLE
TELL ME
YOU'RE A VERY
COMPASSIONATE GUY,
AN ODDBALL,
BUT VERY KIND INDIVIDUAL.
AND I LIKE THAT.
WELL, I APPRECIATE
THAT, JOE.
OF COURSE
YOU'RE COMPASSIONATE
SO FUCKING MOPES TAKE YOU
INTO THEIR CONFIDENCE.
( chuckling )
AND THAT'S VERY IMPORTANT
IN YOUR LINE OF WORK.
WELL, PEOPLE SKILLS
CAN BE HELPFUL, YES.
( knocks on door )
( door opens )
WHAT'S THIS, DETECTIVE?
I THOUGHT WE WERE GONNA
DINE ALONE.
Well, Alma here
is a friend of mine.
She's been dying
to meet you.
And I think you're gonna
want to hear her out.
Sit down, sweetheart.
Now Tommy said you had
some information for me?
Well, actually
Alma's the one
with the information.
SO WHAT'S ON YOUR MIND?
I HELPED MICHAEL NOCERA
KILL YOUR PAL TONY D.
I TOLD MICHAEL
THAT YOU AND TONY
WERE SKIMMING HIM
ON THE GAS TAX SCAM
THAT HE INVENTED.
AND THEN I MADE YOU
KILL NOCERA
BY MAKING SURE
THAT YOU KNEW THAT
THE TWO OF US WERE TOGETHER.
WHO IS THIS LADY?
SHE'S CRAZY.
MARIAN HAMILTON.
YOU REMEMBER
A COMPANY CALLED
THE SEA LARK
COMPANY, JOE?
SEA LARK?
SEA LARK-- THAT'S A NAME
I HAVEN'T THOUGHT OF
IN A LONG TIME.
THAT'S BECAUSE
IT'S BEEN A LONG TIME
SINCE YOU KILLED
FRED HAMILTON.
HE WAS THE ACCOUNTANT
FOR YOUR GAS STATIONS--
MY FATHER.
FRED HAMILTON.
HE WAS A NICE MAN.
HE WAS TOO HONEST.
THAT WAS HIS PROBLEM.
SO YOU KILLED HIM.
MARIAN HAMILTON--
EYEWITNESS TO THE MURDER
OF FRED HAMILTON.
NOW SHE SAW YOU
KILL HER FATHER, JOE.
Now you can die in jail
serving out a life sentence
for the murder
of Fred Hamilton,
OR WE CAN MAKE A DEAL.
- A DEAL?
- THEY'RE GONNA GET YOU
SOONER OR LATER, MAN.
MAKE A DEAL WITH ME NOW.
IT'S GONNA BE ARIZONA
OR NEW MEXICO.
( knocks on door )
( door opens )
Man:
MR. VALENTINE,
YOU HAVE A PHONE CALL.
Jack:
NOT RIGHT NOW.
Man:
IT'S A MR. KEENAN, SIR.
IT'S URGENT.
THE F.B.I.?
I THOUGHT THIS WAS UNOFFICIAL.
JOE, I LIED.
IT HAD TO BE THIS WAY.
I'M SORRY.
WE'RE WIRED.
THIS PLACE
IS SURROUNDED.
HAD TO BE THAT WAY.
DON'T DO
ANYTHING STUPID.
( line beeping )
- HELLO. HELLO.
- HELLO?
( gunshots )
( people screaming )
EXCUSE ME.
COMING THROUGH.
ALMA.
GOD DAMN IT.
- JACK.
- I'M RIGHT HERE, BABY.
I'M RIGHT HERE.
WHAT DID YOU DO IT?
I--
I DIDN'T.
( distant siren wailing )
( Joe's voice )
The FBI? I thought
this was unofficial.
( Jack's voice )
Joe, I lied. It had to
be this way, I'm sorry.
We're wired.
This place is
surrounded.
Don't do
anything stupid.
Sweetheart, I'm sorry.
I wasn't happy--
what happened to
your father.
( Alma's voice )
Neither was I.
( Alma screams )
What the fuck?
( gunshots )
WAIT A MINUTE.
PLAY THAT PART AGAIN
AFTER SHE SAYS,
"NEITHER WAS I."
( Alma screams )
What the fuck?
( gunshots )
WHAT'S THE MOMENT OF SILENCE
AFTER THE FIRST SCREAM?
WELL, THE D.A.D.
PROBABLY CRASHED
INTO THE HEADROOM.
MEANING WHAT?
IN ENGLISH, PHIL.
WELL, ON A REGULAR
ANALOG TAPE RECORDER,
IF THE SOUND'S TOO LOUD,
IT'LL RECORD DISTORTED.
BUT WITH DIGITAL,
IF THE SIGNAL'S TOO HOT,
THE SOUND JUST DROPS OUT
ALTOGETHER.
WHY DO I HEAR
THE OTHER GUNSHOTS?
WELL, AFTER THE FIRST ONE
I KNOCKED DOWN THE GAIN
SO THE OTHER ONES
WOULDN'T DROP OUT.
FOR WHAT IT'S WORTH,
SHE FUCKED US BOTH.
( woman speaking
indistinctly )
( continues speaking
THIS IS ALL THE EVIDENCE
YOU GOT ON THE JOE BUDDHA
CASE, RIGHT?
- IT'S ALL I GOT, JACK.
- OKAY.
- THANKS A LOT, MAN.
- I'LL SEE YOU.
( clicks )
Sweetheart, I'm sorry.
I wasn't happy--
what happened to
your father.
Neither was I.
( Alma screams )
Phil? What the fuck?
( gunshots )
( rewinds )
( Alma screams )
Phil? What the fuck?
( gunshots )
PHIL?
( rewinds )
PHIL? WHAT THE FUCK?
YOU JUST COULDN'T LET IT GO,
COULD YOU, BUDDY?
HOLY SHIT, MAN.
WELL, IT'S REALLY
PRETTY EASY.
YOU HAD JOE COLD,
WHICH MEANT YOU HAD ME
AND EVERY OTHER COP
ON HIS PAYROLL.
I WANTED TO BRING YOU IN
ON IT, JACK,
SHARE THE WEALTH,
YOU KNOW?
YOU BROUGHT TOO MUCH
ATTENTION TO YOURSELF
WITH THAT GIRL,
MESSED IT UP
FOR EVERYBODY.
WHY ME, MAN?
WHAT WOULD MAKE YOU THINK
I'D DO THIS?
I FIGURED IF ANYBODY
COULD USE A LITTLE EXTRA
INCOME, IT'D BE YOU.
A COUPLE HUNDRED DOLLARS
A WEEK TO PUT YOUR LIFE
ON THE LINE--
IT'S A LOUSY GIG, JACK.
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA
DO NOW, PARTNER?
ARE YOU GONNA TAKE ME OUT
RIGHT HERE?
I DON'T KNOW.
A GUY GOT FIRED,
WENT POSTAL.
THANK GOD THAT BRAVE OFFICER
WAS THERE TO TAKE HIM OUT
BEFORE HE BLASTED HIS WAY
THROUGH THE WHOLE STATION.
BACK ME UP.
- Jack: FREEZE!
- ( men yelling )
PUT THE RECORDER DOWN.
HE'S DESTROYING STATE'S
EVIDENCE.
- FOR CHRISSAKE, TAKE HIM OUT.
- NO, HE'S A FUCKING MOLE.
HE'S ON BUDDHA'S PAYROLL.
PUT IT DOWN, PHIL.
PUT THE TAPE RECORDER
DOWN, MAN.
PUT IT DOWN.
I'LL PUT MY WEAPON DOWN.
PUT IT DOWN, PHIL!
PUT IT DOWN.
( people chattering )
( siren wailing )
( police radio chatter )
( camera shutters clicking )
GET THAT CAR
OUT OF THE WAY.
GET OUT OF HERE.
COME ON.
OH MY GOD.
EXCUSE ME.
I'M SALLY CLAIRE WITH
THE U.S. ATTORNEY'S OFFICE.
- IS HE GONNA BE OKAY?
- HE'S SHOT UP
PRETTY BADLY.
JACK, IT'S SALLY.
PHIL DIDN'T MAKE IT.
AND I HEARD THE TAPE.
YOU WERE RIGHT
TO TRUST ALMA.
- GO AHEAD.
- Man #1: WATCH IT.
- Man #2: GOT HIM.
- Man #1: LET'S GO.
( siren wailing )
( rustling )
( Alma's voice )
"JACK,
IF YOU'RE
READING THIS,
I'M NOT AROUND
ANYMORE.
LIKE I SAID,
YOU WOULD HAVE LIKED
MY DAD.
HERE'S SOMETHING HE LEFT ME
A LONG TIME AGO.
I WANTED YOU
TO HAVE IT.
THE BOOKS SHOW
A TRAIL OF NUMBERS
THAT WILL LEAD YOU
TO THE BOSSES
IN NEW YORK
AND KANSAS CITY.
MAYBE IT'LL HELP.
MAKE SURE YOU GO, JACK,
FOR THE BOTH OF US.
LOVE,
MARIAN."
( song playing )
♪ YEAH, I WANT TO DEDICATE
THIS SONG ♪
♪ TO THE ONE
THAT I LOVE ♪
♪ OH ♪
♪ I NEVER MEANT TO HURT ♪
♪ THE ONE I LOVE ♪
♪ LISTEN ♪
♪ LOOKING BACK ON TIMES
WHEN I ♪
♪ WAS LIVING A LIE ♪
♪ REELING WITH
THE THINGS OF MY PAST ♪
♪ MANY TIMES I TRIED
TO FACE IT ♪
♪ BUT I JUST RAN AWAY ♪
♪ MY FEARS WERE
SO GREAT ♪
♪ BUT I KNEW SOMEDAY
MY TEARS WOULDN'T LAST ♪
♪ YOU SEE, GROWING UP
IN A HOME ♪
♪ WHERE NO LOVE
IS SHOWN ♪
♪ AFFECTS HOW YOU FEEL ♪
♪ ABOUT YOUR SELF-WORTH ♪
♪ SO AT THE TIME
THAT YOU CAME INTO MY LIFE ♪
♪ I WAS LIVING LIFE
ABATING ALL MY HURT AND ♪
♪ I'M SO SORRY ♪
♪ FOR WHAT I'VE DONE
TO YOU ♪
♪ PLEASE DON'T HATE ME,
DON'T HATE ME, BABY ♪
♪ FOR ALL
I'VE PUT YOU THROUGH ♪
♪ I'M SO SORRY,
I'M REALLY SORRY, LOVER ♪
♪ FOR WHAT I'VE DONE
TO YOU ♪
♪ PLEASE FORGIVE ME,
I'M BEGGING YOU, PLEASE ♪
♪ FOR ALL
I'VE PUT YOU THROUGH ♪
♪ OH, I'VE HAD SO MANY WOMEN
IN MY LIFE ♪
♪ BECAUSE I DIDN'T FEEL
THAT I WAS GOOD ENOUGH ♪
♪ CONSTANTLY SEARCHING
FOR APPROVAL ♪
♪ OH, NEVER REALIZING ♪
♪ THAT IN THE END
I'D JUST BE HURTING MYSELF ♪
♪ I NEVER PLANNED TO GO ON,
RUN AND FIND MYSELF ♪
♪ ANOTHER LOVER ♪
♪ MY AFFLICTIONS
AND MY INSECURITIES ♪
♪ WAS WRITTEN IN STONE
INSIDE MY SOUL ♪
♪ AND AFTER MY ABUSE
I HAD GIVEN UP ALL CONTROL ♪
♪ I LOST CONTROL ♪
♪ SO, BABY, WHEN YOU CAME
INTO MY LIFE ♪
♪ I HONESTLY TRIED
TO CHANGE ♪
♪ BUT I JUST COULDN'T,
I FELT I SHOULDN'T ♪
♪ I ONLY KNEW I HAD
TO SURVIVE, BABY ♪
♪ I'M SO SORRY,
SORRY, BABY ♪
♪ FOR WHAT I'VE DONE
TO YOU ♪
♪ PLEASE DON'T HATE ME,
DON'T HATE ME, NO ♪
♪ FOR ALL
I'VE PUT YOU THROUGH ♪
♪ I'M SO SORRY,
CAN'T YOU SEE IT IN MY EYES? ♪
♪ FOR WHAT I'VE DONE
TO YOU ♪
♪ PLEASE FORGIVE ME,
YEAH ♪
♪ FOR ALL
I'VE PUT YOU THROUGH, OH ♪
♪ HEY, BABY ♪
♪ I REALLY, TRULY, HONESTLY
DO LOVE YOU ♪
♪ BUT PLEASE LISTEN TO ME,
THIS THING THAT I'M
TRYING TO SAY ♪
♪ BRING IT BACK ♪
♪ MY HONEST INTENTIONS
ARE WORDS ♪
♪ THAT GIVE YOU
MY LOVE ♪
♪ WELL, NOW I REALIZE
MY LOVE IS WEAK ♪
♪ BECAUSE I NEVER LOVED
MYSELF ♪
♪ I WAS ROBBED AS A CHILD,
LEFT ALL ALONE ♪
♪ ABANDONED AND
NEGLECTED... ♪