(YEARNING MUSIC PLAYS)
(YEARNING MUSIC CONTINUES)
ALLISON: Throughout the long summer
and crisp fall days
before my mother's trial,
I'd overheard
much more than my parents realised,
and understood
more than they would have liked.
I think we're alright, Sibyl.
Really, I do. There's no way
they can find you guilty.
(TELEPHONE RINGS)
You're the lawyer, Steven.
Tell her.
Well, I think we have cause
to be optimistic.
Hello.
Alright. The jury's back.
(TELEPHONE HANGS UP)
The Jury's back.
They've only been out four hours.
Is that good?
It's best not to read
too much into it.
But, we should go.
I'll go get Connie.
I never liked this time of year.
The leaves have turned
but there's no snow yet.
Sibyl, whatever happens...
It's that in between time, you know.
Everything Grey.
No colour.
And it's cold.
ALLISON: I heard you could tell
what the jury
had decided the minute they walked
into the courtroom by the way
they looked at the defendant,
or, refused to look at her.
Steven told us that was nonsense.
Just another one of the great myths
of litigation.
But it made sense to me.
(DOOR OPENS)
Look at her.
Look at her. Please.
Please.
(COUGHING)
Look at my mum.
All rise.
Be seated.
Oh, god, please.
Please look at her.
Look at her.
Have you reached a verdict?
We have, Your Honour.
No!
(SCREAMS)
Push. Keep trying to push.
That's it, Wanda, you can do it.
Come on, a little more.
Oh, I love you. Keep pushing.
A little more.
A little more, come on.
Good girl. Good girl.
Come on, the baby's coming.
Keep pushing. Keep pushing.
You're doing great. Almost there.
Ah! God!
Oh, Caleb!
Here, honey. Here.
We're never doing this again.
Do you understand? Never again.
Don't worry, honey, Mummy says
silly things when we have a baby.
We? When was the last time
you pushed something the size
of a watermelon out of...
Oh! Oh, Sibyl.
You can do it. You can do it.
This is the one.
Now, ready. That's it.
Good girl. Here it comes.
Push. Good girl.
OK, pant.
ALLISON: The summer before I started
high school more than a year earlier,
the trial was still a lifetime away.
And the tragedy
that took over our lives
would have been impossible
to imagine.
(CRYING)
OK. Here's your baby!
Oh! Oh!
Oh, she's a beautiful girl.
ALLISON: Since the late '60s,
my mother had been one of a dozen
independent lay midwives in Vermont.
But it was no job,
it was her greatest joy.
Hey, Sweetie,
come here and meet your baby sister.
(CRYING)
Oh, Hannah,
say hi, hi to your sister.
Do it again.
(LAUGHTER)
Oh.
(DOOR OPENS)
I thought I heard you come in.
How did it go?
Oh, Rand, you should have seen her.
What a little beauty.
What time did this one weigh in?
4am. They named her Julia.
4am? The baby came at 4am?
Rand, I had to get
everyone settled in.
I had to make sure Julia was nursing
and that Wanda was up and around.
Is there any more coffee?
You're not going to bed?
No. Elizabeth Anderson's going to be
here soon for her prenatal.
Sibyl, you've been up all night.
I don't care.
I couldn't sleep now anyway.
But I will think I'll have
a cup of coffee and your bagel.
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYS)
I'm leaving.
Hmm?
I was thinking maybe,
umm, outer Mongolia.
Well, send my regards
to Genghis Khan.
I'm busy, not deaf, Connie.
Hey, where are you going?
The Weston's to ride.
Well, you look pretty dolled up
for some old horse.
I'm babysitting
Foogie Bedford at 4pm.
Mr Bedford's so funny.
He plays with Foogie
like they're both five years old.
And Mrs Bedford's really sweet.
Bedford? That's the preacher
and his wife, right?
The ones who moved
up here from Alabama?
Mum, I've only been babysitting
for them all summer.
What do you write
every day in those books anyway?
Not every day.
I make notes on my patients and...
just observations
on life in general.
I like to keep
a record of each birth.
You'd be amazed
at how different they are.
Mum, I get it.
Why don't I drive you over
to the Bedford's this afternoon.
We can visit on the way up.
OK. Thanks, Mum.
(TENDER MUSIC PLAYS)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Hi, Connie.
Hi, Tom.
After you.
(HORN HONKING)
Sorry, Sweetie,
I can't take you after all.
Lilly Lambert's baby's coming.
But I called Dad and he's rearranged
some things so he can take
you to the Bedford's.
Oh, and I took some hamburger
out of the freezer. Do you mind
making dinner for the two of you?
I guess not.
Anything you need before I go?
A foster mother.
I'll see what I can do.
Maybe it will be
a short labour this time.
Maybe.
Give me kiss.
Have fun.
So, what's with you and Tom Quartz?
Who?
Oh, you know, 6 feet, 140,
blonde, blue...
Green.
Excuse me, green eyes.
15 years old.
Smokes cigarettes.
Do you pay your spies or is strictly
on a volunteer basis?
He's not your type.
I'm 13, I don't have a type yet.
13.5. He's a delinquent.
He writes poetry.
And comes from a long line
of garage mechanics
who buy beer with food stamps.
Oh, the dream life.
If you keep
your tetanus shots current.
Good one, Dad.
You know, I love how you take
my advice to heart.
I'm sorry I'm not going to be able
to babysit for you much longer.
You must be excited
about starting high school.
A little nervous to tell the truth.
Oh.
Mrs Bedford, are you OK?
I'll be alright.
Oh, look who's here.
Connie!
Oh.
Hi, Foogie. Hello, Reverend Bedford.
Hello, Connie. Glad to see you.
Are you ready, honey?
I just have to get my purse.
Oh.
Oh, go get your colours, Sweetie.
You could draw
a picture for Connie.
I've been meaning to ask you,
is your mum really a midwife?
Sure. She's delivered
about a million babies.
Charlotte, going to be late.
Are you...
I'm fine now, really.
We shouldn't be too late.
Help yourself to whatever you want
in the fridge.
Thanks.
Bye.
ALLISON: That fall,
Mum was busier than ever.
But by October, Tom and I were
boyfriend and girlfriend.
And the need for my mother's
attention had all but vanished.
(ENGINE REVS)
We need to talk about Connie.
What about her?
Well, you've been running from one
delivery to the next for months.
Rand, she's 13.
The last thing in the world
she wants is me hovering.
It's not what she wants,
it's what she needs.
I thought we agreed...
I know what my daughter needs.
Fine. You're right, Sibyl.
You're always right.
Look, I've been thinking
about getting a new apprentice.
Would that help?
You tell me.
Rand, I'm here for you
and for Connie, you know that?
You know, even when you're here,
you're distracted.
Do you spend any real time with her?
Yes, I do.
Look, I know you're nervous
about this boyfriend thing,
but she's a sensible girl.
Never mind. You don't know
what I'm talking about.
I know
exactly what you're talking about.
And it has nothing to do
with Connie.
Hey, why don't we go out to dinner
next week, just the two of us?
Because you can't plan
a week ahead.
Somebody might go into labour.
I would have come
to you but with one car,
he needs to travel all over and all.
Well, anyway, I sure appreciate
you coming over.
Oh, it's nothing. I had to come
out this direction anyway.
A lot of questions here.
Well, I do need
a complete medical history.
Now, tell me about your diet.
You getting plenty of protein?
Charlotte?
I just don't know
how I'm going to manage.
Oh. A home birth
is an incredible experience.
You'd be amazed
at what your body can do.
Oh, it's not that.
Foogie was an easy baby.
I had him at home, too.
It's just, well, I don't know
what Asa is going to say.
Well, I'm sure he'll be thrilled.
Connie tells
me he's a wonderful father.
Oh, he is.
It's just we're not situated yet
and...
well, I've never even seen snow.
Asa doesn't have
a regular congregation.
We don't have any friends.
We don't even have
any neighbours out here.
Well, I bet we can put together
everything you need for this baby.
Lots of people around here have
had babies and you know how fast
they grow out of everything.
I guess God didn't put
anything on us we can't handle.
Everything's going to be
just fine, Charlotte.
And you're going to love the snow.
Thanks.
Gloves, sterile gauze.
Oh, and we need some more Betadine.
Mum?
Oh, Connie, this is Anne Heston,
my new apprentice.
Hi.
My daughter, Connie.
Can I get a ride into town.
It's too cold to walk.
Well, do you want to go with me?
I'm headed that way.
Great. Thanks. I'll go get my coat.
OK.
This should be enough.
Great.
Thanks, Mrs Danforth,
for taking me on.
It's Sibyl.
I can't wait to deliver a baby.
Well, it will be
a while before you can do that.
There's a lot to learn.
I'll work very hard
and I'm a fast learner.
Good.
Come on, Foogie,
I'm late for my appointment.
You little monkey.
(OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYS)
Come on now, honey.
You testified that you asked
someone to bring you a knife.
That's right.
A sharp knife?
I don't think I would have asked
for a dull one.
"The sharpest knife in the house."
Were those your words?
They may have been.
- (BARKING)
- (HORN HONKING)
ALLISON: Charlotte Bedford went
into labour with her second child
on Thursday, March 13th.
Phone records later showed that she
had called her husband at 1:30pm,
spoke for three minutes,
then called my mother at 1:40pm.
Someone they know from town came
for Foogie and I've had Charlotte
walking some, resting some.
Good.
What about her vitals?
BP, 130 over 85. Pulse, 90.
It's all so amazing.
Well, let's see how she's doing.
How you feeling?
Excited.
There's new snow on the mountain.
Did you see it?
How about you, Asa,
you ready for a new baby?
You bet.
That was a good one.
What'd you get, Anne?
20 seconds.
Foogie took about nine hours.
Second one's usually less, isn't it?
Hmm, usually.
But you never know.
I'd like to offer a prayer.
Dear Holy Father,
we ask that you help your child
Charlotte through this time.
Give her the strength
and the courage to endure.
We ask that you protect
her and the baby from harm
and be with us during this joyful
occasion so that we might serve you
in Christ's name. Amen.
Amen.
Did Mum say how long she'll be?
Hmm, you know, you can't predict
when a baby will be born,
so she's figuring around 9:47pm.
(TICKING)
(SLOW EXPECTANT MUSIC PLAYS)
8cm. You're doing great.
Almost there.
(PANTING AND GROANING)
(RAIN FALLS)
(CLOCK TICKING)
(PANTING)
I can't do this!
You're doing fine.
No, I can't. Oh, god!
I know it's hard,
but you can do it, Charlotte.
You're fully dilated.
You can start pushing now.
No, this is different!
It's not like the last time!
Something's wrong!
Please, help me!
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYS)
(SCREAMS)
The Lord is my shepherd,
I shall not want.
He maketh me lie down in green
pastures, he leadeth me...
110 over 70.
Just leave it on.
In spite of this, you still saw
the delivery as normal?
Yes, it was difficult,
but not life-threatening.
And the baby was fine.
So you continued to encourage her.
Yes.
Urge her on?
Yes. OK, Charlotte, big push now.
(GRUNTING)
Is that when you noticed the blood?
No. It was later, just after 1:30am.
And how long had she been
labouring by then?
About 15 hours, more or less.
Ooh!
You're doing great.
It's great. It's great.
(SCREAMS)
Anne?
Oh, Asa.
80 over 50.
It's alright. It's alright.
Pulse 130.
Baby's at 90.
Is that alright?
Is the baby alright?
Charlotte, don't push. Just try
to breathe through this next one.
(GROANING)
(PANTING)
60 over 40.
Charlotte, I think it would be
in your best interest
and the baby's to go
to the hospital.
You may be bleeding inside.
Oh, god. Let's go.
I'll just call
an ambulance to take her there.
I think that would be the easiest.
(PHONE RATTLING)
Anne, can you go check
the phones downstairs.
Just hang in there,
Charlotte, don't push.
Our Father who art in Heaven,
hallowed be Thy name,
Thy kingdom come,
Thy will be done on earth
as it is in heaven.
Give us this day our daily bread...
The phones must be down.
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYS)
Well, we'll just take
her ourselves.
Anne, will you get some blankets.
Asa, you stay here with Charlotte
while I go warm up the car.
Charlotte, just hang
in there and don't push.
Asa?
The record shows that the rain
had turned to ice at 11:45pm,
two hours earlier.
Weren't you concerned
that the roads were icy?
I didn't know that.
(GRUNTING)
You were calm.
Yes.
But you were afraid for the baby?
(TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES)
(ENGINE STARTS)
(ENGINE REVS)
You knew you wouldn't be
going anywhere.
Yes.
And that no-one would be
coming to help.
You were trapped.
Yes.
Speak up, Mrs Danforth.
We were trapped.
I want to try again.
OK. When the next one comes,
just give it everything you've got.
OK, I think
this is going to be the one.
(GROANING)
Good girl. Good girl.
A little more. A little more.
(SCREAMS)
Keep going.
I can see the top
of the baby's head.
(SCREAMS)
A little more.
(GASPS)
Charlotte?
Charlotte? Charlotte?
What's happening?
What is it?
(OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYS)
What is it? Is she alright?
One.
Two. Three. Four. Five.
Sibyl, is she going to be alright?
One. Two. Three. Four. Ten.
One. Two. Three.
4. 15.
Charlotte?
One. Two. Three. Four.
Oh, dear god, please.
Five. One. Two. Three. Four. Five.
Is she going to be alright, Sibyl?
Please.
(OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES)
One. Two. Three. Four.
Come on, Charlotte. Come on.
Come on, Charlotte.
One. Two.
Don't give up.
Come on, Charlotte, please.
One. Two. Come on. Fight.
Two. Three. Four. Five.
(OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES)
One. Two. Come on, Charlotte.
Come on, Charlotte, fight. Come on.
Charlotte, please!
(MUSIC FADES)
Oh, god, Asa, I can't get a pulse.
She's gone.
No.
I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry, Asa.
Oh, god. No. No.
No. My Charlotte, no.
Oh, no.
Get me a knife.
The sharpest one in the house.
And you did as she asked?
Yes.
Did you know
what she was going to do?
Um... I thought maybe try
and save Charlotte.
With a knife?
Mrs Danforth was in charge,
I wasn't.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYS)
Can you tell me, Anne,
how many births you had assisted?
This was my fourth.
Why did you go
with Reverend Bedford
instead of staying with Mrs Danforth?
Charlotte...
I believed Mrs Bedford was dead.
It was...
I didn't want to be there.
Oh, Charlotte.
We've got to hurry.
What are you going to do?
I'm going to try to save your baby.
We don't want them both to die.
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYS)
You didn't ask
Reverend Bedford's permission?
No.
It was his wife.
His baby.
If he'd said no,
I would have done it anyway.
I had to try to save the baby.
And you thought you could?
I didn't think about it.
I just did it.
I had no choice.
Had you ever done
a C-section before?
No, of course not.
But you proceeded anyway?
Yes.
(TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES)
OFFICER: I don't remember
it snowing like this in March.
Not in the last ten years anyway.
We'll do the autopsy
as soon as we get back to Burlington.
Alright.
Standard procedure.
Nothing to alarm you.
Excuse me.
They're taking
the baby to the hospital.
North County in Newport.
Check him over.
(CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKING)
Are you alright?
You did just fine, Anne.
Don't worry.
We'll talk later.
The room was very quiet.
Even the ice and snow had stopped
banging against the window.
(EERIE MUSIC PLAYS)
I didn't want to hurt the baby.
I told myself I just had to be
incredibly careful.
(DOORBELL RINGS)
Can't this wait until tomorrow?
I'm sorry, Sir, it can't.
But I promise
it won't take too long.
Connie,
maybe you better go upstairs.
Why don't I finish cooking dinner?
No, that's alright, Sweetie.
It's OK.
Please, come in.
Please, sit down.
Thank you.
I am sorry to bother you,
Mrs Danforth. We just need
an account of what happened
while it's still fresh in your mind.
I...
ALLISON: I heard it all.
How Mrs Bedford had died.
How my mother saved the baby.
Every detail
of what they all had endured.
If you could just read this over,
check it for accuracy.
And then just sign it right there.
I don't think
that's such a good idea.
It's OK, Rand.
I want to help in any way I can.
Thanks.
Thanks for your cooperation.
Years later my father would still
believe he might have changed
everything that happened
if he'd insisted on having
a lawyer present that night.
I keep thinking of Asa
and those motherless little boys.
I know.
(ENGINE STARTS)
I couldn't save her.
I tried,
but I just couldn't save her.
(FORLORN MUSIC PLAYS)
Mum?
Oh, Connie,
what are you doing up, honey?
I was thirsty.
Are you OK?
I'm a little sore. But I'm fine.
Dad's gonna take
me to get my ankle x-rayed
tomorrow over in Burlington.
And we're going to check out
some lawyers while we're there.
Why?
Well, in case there's a lawsuit
or something.
But you saved the baby.
Well, Dad just wants
to be prepared.
Mum, what do you think happened?
I'm not sure.
Charlotte had some kind
of a seizure
or cerebral aneurysm probably.
You know, stroke.
There wasn't anything I could do.
Why don't you go on to bed now.
Try not to worry.
Everything's going to be OK.
Alright.
Good night, Mum.
Good night, Sweetie.
(TENDER MUSIC PLAYS)
ALLISON:
I sensed the pretence even then.
And I wondered how long
she could keep up the strong front.
She was lost
and she didn't know it yet.
That quality she had,
part confidence,
part optimism, part joy,
that sometimes seemed
to fill whole rooms when she entered
had vanished.
As if a light had simply gone out.
(TELEPHONE RINGS)
VOICEMAIL: Hi. You've reached
the Danforths.
Leave us a message
and we'll call you back.
(LONG BEEP)
Hello, I'm looking
for Sibyl Danforth.
This is Joe Meane
with 'The Sentinel.'
I'll call back later.
I got three names,
but everybody tells me
that this Steven Hastings
is the best lawyer in Vermont.
Really smart.
Handled some very tough cases.
We've probably seen
him on the news.
(DOORBELL RINGS)
Connie, it's me.
(TELEPHONE RINGS)
(LONG BEEP)
Good morning.
This is Maggie Fresher with
'The Burlington Street Press'...
I want to get all Mrs Bedford's
prenatal records,
bring in an investigator,
that sort of thing.
Meanwhile, don't talk
about this to anyone. Not a soul.
Don't tell me everything, either.
I'll ask you what I need
to know as we go along.
Mr Hastings, no offense.
I know this is your job, but aren't
you overreacting a little bit?
Please. It's Steven.
You know, the fact is a woman died
under unusual circumstances.
And my guess
is they'll look to blame someone.
From what you've told me so far,
the State could charge
you with involuntary manslaughter.
Stemming from recklessness
or extreme negligence.
State's Attorney might make some
noise about it being intentional.
Not that that means anything.
He just has to act tough.
I did what I had to do.
She saved that baby's life.
And as far as I'm concerned,
the State should damn well give
you a medal.
But I think we should be prepared.
Look, the list of things
that can go wrong
in child birth is frightening.
And it's endless.
And what this tragedy proves
is that women should have
their babies in the safety
of a hospital.
Dr Demond, as an obstetrician,
do you think Mrs Bedford would have
died had she been in a hospital?
At this point, I don't know.
What I do know
is that she wouldn't have had
her stomach ripped open
with a kitchen knife.
What I do know is that she
would not have had to endure
a C-section without anaesthesia.
Oh, my god.
The State Attorneys office
is investigating,
but sources tell us it may take
some time to decide
whether there's basis
for criminal charges or whether
it's merely a civil matter.
What's with these idiots?
..have to wait
for the autopsy report
to answer the question
on everyone's mind.
It's on every channel.
Turn the damn thing off.
Reverend Bedford,
do you have a comment, Sir?
Yes, uh, I'm grateful to be blessed
with another child. Thank you.
Steven's right.
They are going to find
a way to blame me for this.
Oh.
(DOORBELL RINGS)
Hi, Rand.
Cheryl, what are you doing here?
Stuff from the midwife's co-op.
Insurance companies, law firms,
articles. All sorts of good crap.
I got here as soon as I could.
Are you alright? I wouldn't be.
Pisses me off, I tell you.
So, listen to this. A study
from the university of...
Who is that?
Cheryl Fisco, midwife militia.
..patients cared for by physicians.
They don't know
what they're talking about.
I say bull crap.
The medical establishment
is just using this tragedy
to promote their cause.
I mean, come on.
They all know damn well women labour
more effectively at home.
And I...
Should we offer
her some coffee or something?
Are you crazy?
The woman never shuts up as it is.
We'll be lucky to get
her out of here by 10pm.
Maybe it will help Mum.
Mark my words,
tomorrow's headlines...
Could you tell me where I could find
Sibyl Danforth?
I'm her lawyer.
You don't look like a lawyer.
Well, what's a lawyer look like?
I don't know.
Nerdy. Boring.
Thanks, I think.
Steven Hastings, Attorney at Law.
I'm her daughter. I'll show you.
Sibyl, they're not going to come
after you
just because a lot of doctors
don't approve of midwives.
They already are coming after me.
That's just the media.
It's the State's Attorney
who decides
whether or not to press charges.
Here.
How's that?
Good.
Thanks.
He's been looking to make
a name for himself.
He'll be all over
an emotional issue like this.
You let me worry
about Tanner, alright?
Sorry I'm late.
Set up over here, would you?
I don't want her to have to move.
Brought some iced tea.
Oh, my god.
They're just going to take pictures
of my skinned knees, sweetie.
You're in ninth grade, Connie?
Uh-huh.
Union High School?
Yeah.
You know Darrin Royce?
Mr Royce? He's my biology teacher.
We were in the military.
In the Army.
Next time you see him...
(OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYS)
Hello. How are you, BP?
ALLISON: In the nine years
that BP Hewitt
had been my mother's backup doctor,
the records would show
that out of 463 deliveries,
there were 28 times
my mother had transferred
a patient to the hospital.
And only 11 where Dr Hewitt
had surgically removed the infant.
Have you finished your homework?
Almost. I just was going to get
something to drink.
OK. Come in. Come in.
Can I get you something to drink?
ALLISON: One time
a baby was stillborn.
All agreed it would have been,
even in a hospital.
Never once did a mother die.
So, you got yourself a lawyer?
Yeah, we hired a lawyer a week ago.
Just in case. Why?
But you haven't spoken to Anne yet?
No, not since the birth.
I've been leaving messages for her,
but she hasn't called back.
I'll see her tomorrow, though.
We have prenatals all afternoon.
I don't think so, Sibyl.
I think she's avoiding you.
Why would she do that?
How long has she been
your apprentice?
For three or four months.
You two get on OK?
Oh, sure.
You're stalling, BP.
What's going on?
I was interviewed today
by a couple of state troopers.
It seems that when you made
that incision into Mrs Bedford,
Anne says she saw blood spurt.
She says she saw
it a couple of times.
And she and Asa both saw it.
At least that's what she told
the State's Attorney's Office.
Blood spurt?
What are you talking about?
Blood only spurts
from a beating heart.
They're saying that when I operated
Charlotte was still alive?
Yes.
(OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYS)
There's no way. I don't care
if they both say they saw it...
They don't think I know
if somebody's alive or dead.
Sibyl, you're the best midwife
in three states.
You could never make
that kind of mistake.
There must be some reason Anne
would make something up like this.
A grudge or something.
This is insane?
What was I supposed to do,
let the baby die?
Well, what do you think
I should do?
I see.
I understand.
No, I'll tell her. Thanks, Steve.
He says that whatever they saw
or think they saw doesn't matter.
He says that Asa is a distraught
and grieving husband and that Anne
is a young girl who panicked.
He says we wait
for the autopsy report.
He's right. That will put
an end to this nonsense.
Mum?
They released the autopsy report.
No sign of stroke or seizure.
According to the Medical Examiner,
she was alive when I took the baby.
He says she bled to death.
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYS)
What?
I was just thinking
about how grown up you are.
Thanks.
So, tell me about your boyfriend?
Dad doesn't like him.
Oh, he's your father,
that's his job.
But you know, Connie,
these are the years you'll define
what it means to be a woman.
Oh, no, this isn't gonna be
another sex talk, is it?
We've been having those
since I was two.
I think my first word was vulva.
That was your second.
Seriously, Honey,
I know we've talked
about the physical part,
but it's an emotional step, too.
It can be very confusing.
I'm not confused.
I'm not even thinking about it.
Good.
That's good.
It's just that things aren't always
as predictable as we like to think.
They can change so fast.
I just wanted to be sure I had
a chance to tell you these things.
Are you going somewhere
I don't know about?
Hey, you are stuck with me
for at least
the next thousand years.
At some point there could be
some talk about a settlement.
Anything from pleading
to a lesser charge,
reduced sentence,
maybe even probation.
The important thing is no jail time.
No jail time?
You've got to be kidding?
We'll delay as long as we can...
I don't want to delay.
The longer we delay,
the greater the chance
they'll move
on to some real criminals.
I don't care, Steven.
I want this over with.
I want my life back.
I know. Look, I'm sorry.
I shouldn't be bothering
you with all this.
I'm just being an attorney.
You know how we are.
No, actually, I don't know.
You're the only one
I've ever met, thank god.
No offense.
You just never needed one before.
That's good?
Yeah, that's good.
So, I'm your first.
You're my first, so to speak.
I'm flattered.
I'm surprised
you're not sick of me by now.
I spend more time
with you than I do with my husband.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Hi, Sweetie.
Hi, Connie.
Mr Hastings brought good news.
It's over?
Well, not that good.
But at least they don't think
your mum's a murderer.
They just think
I'm a lousy midwife.
Sibyl, that's not what they think.
Oh, excuse me.
They just think I can't tell
if a woman's alive or dead.
They think you made a mistake.
A gross mistake.
A reckless mistake.
Anyway, if this mess
ever comes to trial,
it won't be a murder trial.
And that's the good news.
Then what will it be?
Involuntary manslaughter.
Which means they think
it was a mistake.
Where's Dad?
He's at work. Why?
I'll be right back.
Connie, what's the matter with you?
Why does he have
to be here all the time?
He's my lawyer.
He acts like he's you're boyfriend
or something.
Don't be silly. He's a friend.
So now he's your lawyer
and a friend?
Connie, you know
I love your father very much.
But I need Steven too right now.
Can't you understand that?
Does Dad?
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYS)
No.
He has to do that.
He doesn't have
to put those on. Come on.
She's not a criminal.
She came out willingly.
It's OK, Rand.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC CONTINUES)
(ENGINE STARTS)
Your Honour, a midwife
is by nature an outlaw.
Someone who puts women and babies
at risk for no reason
other than a mindless and backward
distaste for modern medicine.
Mr Tanner, "outlaw?"
I can do without the hyperbole.
A tragedy brought us here
and we've got a long road ahead.
Let's get on with it.
The State believes that Mrs Danforth
poses a significant flight risk.
And we request that bail be set
at the amount of $35,000.
That's ridiculous, Your Honour.
Sibyl Danforth has lived
here all her life.
She has a child
in the local high school.
Her husband has a successful
architectural practice...
And she's facing
15 years if convicted.
It's absurd.
That's enough.
I see no reason to impose
a monetary condition for release.
There are, however,
other conditions.
In the first place,
you may not leave the state.
If you have an emergency
that requires you to leave,
your lawyer will first have to...
(FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYS)
..and lastly that Mrs Danforth,
will suspend her practice
until the conclusion of the trial.
Do you understand
these terms and conditions?
Yes.
What about your mothers?
I'll have to refer
them to other midwives,
or doctors,
if that's what they want.
People are going to say
some awful things about your mum.
I don't care. They're idiots.
I have time to look
into that foster mother for you now.
That's OK.
I think I'll keep the one I've got.
(SOMBRE MUSIC PLAYS)
Sibyl?
Thank you.
You know, I was just thinking,
I haven't seen
Vale since he was born.
Well, I hear he's doing fine.
Good. I'm glad for that.
I can't help but wonder
if he'll grow up to hate me.
If he'll blame me, too.
Blame you for what?
For killing his mother.
You didn't say much at dinner?
You sure you want to go tomorrow?
I'm sure.
You seem to be handling this well.
I guess I can't help but worry
that it's all wounding you
in some way that I can't see.
I'm fine. Really.
I'm sorry, Sweetie.
Things are supposed
to be simple at your age.
Mum, nothing's ever been
simple for me. Not once.
You're the one that always
had it figured out, not me.
Sounds like I had us both fooled.
I love you.
I love you, too.
Sleep well, Honey.
Connie, what are you doing up?
I couldn't sleep.
Is that work?
This? No.
They're some of the cases
Steven researched
while he was putting
your mum's defence together.
Do you think he's a good lawyer?
I do.
Your mum's lucky to have him.
She's lucky to have you.
She knows that.
And she knows
when this is all over, I'll be here.
Come on.
We could both use some sleep.
Do you think
they'll find her innocent?
Oh, yes.
If they don't, we'll appeal.
You talked about that?
It's come up.
With Steven, yes.
Why does he have to be her lawyer?
Because he's the best.
Listen, Connie,
this is hard on us,
but it's harder on your mum.
Now, we may want to charge
in there to protect her,
but the best way we can take
care of her right now
is to be here when she needs
us and let Steven do his job.
You're pretty cool, Dad.
Try to get some sleep.
Ladies and Gentlemen,
Charlotte Bedford is dead
for one reason.
Sibyl Danforth killed her,
pure and simple.
Now, the defence will tell
you that Sibyl Danforth
is a remarkable person,
an excellent wife and mother.
That's irrelevant.
What's relevant
is that her criminal recklessness
resulted in the death
of a 29-year-old wife and mother.
And her cavalier use
of a kitchen knife
means that a baby will never know
the woman
who should have raised him.
Now, the facts will show that from
the first moment that Charlotte
and Asa Bedford first sat down
with Sibyl Danforth she behaved
with this sort of
incomprehensible negligence
that could only result in tragedy.
Did Mrs Danforth consider
that a labouring woman
might be trapped in an isolated house
if something should go wrong? No.
And in the early hours
of March 14th,
when she did realise
that Charlotte Bedford was in trouble
and trapped miles and miles
from the help she needed,
what did she do?
She had her push and push and push
hours beyond what any doctor
would have allowed.
Without anaesthesia.
Without pain killers.
She had her push so long,
she thought she'd killed her.
But she hadn't.
The fact is,
Charlotte Bedford didn't die
from her agonising ordeal.
She bled to death
because Mrs Danforth took a ten-inch
kitchen knife and cut her open.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(GAVEL BANGS)
Ladies and Gentlemen,
women have been having babies
at home since the beginning of time.
And they've been tended
by knowledgeable,
tireless and loving midwives
like Sibyl Danforth.
The State wants to talk facts?
OK. Let's do it.
Statistics show that today a planned
home delivery is every bit as safe
as a hospital one,
for mothers as well as for babies.
Statistically, Sibyl Danforth's
babies did every bit as well
as the ones born
in North County Hospital.
And the mothers did better.
That's right. Better.
The fact is that in all these years
of delivering hundreds of babies,
tending to hundreds of mothers,
one woman died.
Charlotte Bedford.
And don't misunderstand me,
that is a terrible tragedy.
And one that Sibyl Danforth
will mourn for the rest of her life.
But the fact is
that she did not act recklessly
and she did not kill anyone.
She saved someone.
Sibyl did what any decent
and courageous person
would do faced
with the same horrific choice.
Two deaths or one?
She rescued that baby
from his dead mother.
Ladies and Gentlemen,
that is not criminal negligence.
That's courage.
(MURMURING)
(GAVEL BANGS)
So, Dr Gerson, as an OB-GYN
and formerly a midwife,
how would you assess
Charlotte Bedford
as a candidate for home birth?
A tragedy waiting to happen.
She was frail, underweight,
anaemic and she had a history
of high blood pressure.
Thank you.
Would you say that pregnant
women are often anaemic?
Perhaps, to some degree.
And, as a doctor,
how would you treat that condition?
Iron tablets.
Ferrous sulphate, usually.
You reviewed Sibyl's records.
What did she do?
She gave her iron tablets.
And did her condition improve?
Yes, but...
Thank you.
I have a form detailing
Mrs Bedford's medical history.
Do you see the words,
"high blood pressure", circled?
No.
So, there's no indication
that Mrs Bedford confided
her history
of high blood pressure to Sibyl.
But she had it.
And bottom line, Counsellor,
no responsible person,
midwife or doctor,
would have allowed
Charlotte Bedford to labour at home.
Dr Gerson, you began as a midwife.
Why did you become a doctor?
Because I felt, as a midwife,
I wasn't adequately trained.
And do you feel that most midwife's
are inadequately trained?
Yes.
Do you feel that they should be
banned from delivering babies?
Yes, I do.
And so now you finally have
the chance to get rid
of at least one midwife, don't you?
Objection.
Withdrawn.
Now, Miss Heston,
did Mrs Danforth check
Charlotte for a pulse again
before she did the C-section?
No.
Did she do anything to confirm
Charlotte was dead?
No, Sir, not that I saw.
Thank you.
Miss Heston, prior to March 14th,
had you ever been
in an emergency situation?
Like what?
Anything? Car crash.
A man with a heart attack.
A train wreck?
No, nothing like that.
Nothing. Do you know CPR?
A little bit. Uh, a few days
after Charlotte died...
Have you had any CPR training?
No.
Have you ever seen an operation
prior to March 14th?
Uh, pictures...
Miss Heston, had you seen one?
(REPETITIVE TAPPING)
No.
So, you've never seen blood spurt
from a living or a dead body,
have you?
No.
No again.
So, what in your background led
you to make the wild assumption
that the blood you saw that night
was coming from a living woman?
It was the way that it spurted.
I didn't ask
what you thought you saw.
What in your background
lead you to believe
that based on the bleeding,
Mrs Bedford was alive?
You didn't see it, if you...
Your Honour,
would you instruct the witness
to answer the question, please.
Miss Heston, just answer
the questions as they are asked.
Proceed.
What in your training or experience
led you to believe
that Mrs Bedford was alive?
(REPETITIVE TAPPING)
I don't recall.
Ah.
So, Miss Heston...
(REPETITIVE TAPPING)
..your conjecture was made
on the basis of no training
and absolutely no experience at all,
is that correct?
Oh, god, Sibyl. I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry, but I had to do it.
I had to call.
You know you killed her.
Objection, Your Honour!
I demand that that outburst
be stricken from the record.
So ordered. The jury will disregard
Miss Heston's last statement.
Court is in recess.
I'm so sorry and I know
you didn't mean to,
but we both know
that you killed her.
(MURMURING)
Miss Heston, that's enough.
(GAVEL BANGS)
Mrs Danforth told you
your wife was dead?
Yes.
What did you do?
Nothing. I went to the window
and looked outside.
When she operated,
you were standing at the window?
Yes, but I turned to look.
What did you see?
Reverend Bedford?
Um, I saw the...
When she first cut her,
I remember seeing blood spurting.
I remember seeing
my Charlotte bleed.
Thank you, Reverend Bedford.
No further questions.
Mr Bedford,
I'm so sorry for your loss.
Thank you.
I won't keep you very long.
There's just
something that confuses me.
In your statement you say that you
were standing by the window.
Was the sun up?
Umm, I'm not sure.
It was still dark from the storm.
So, the main light on the bed
would have been
from the bedside lamp?
Yes, but it was bright enough.
I could see Charlotte.
And you believed she was dead?
Yes, at the time.
You loved your wife?
Oh, god, yes. Very much.
You must have been devastated.
Yes.
Was it in that frame of mind
that you thought you saw
the blood spurt?
Well, yes.
So, it was dark,
you were across the room,
you were distraught with grief.
Are you absolutely positive
that you saw blood spurt?
Mr Bedford,
is that your sworn testimony?
Umm, I'm not sure.
I thought I saw it, but...
I'm not sure now.
Thank you.
So, Dr Tierney,
as County Medical Examiner,
what did you find when you examined
Charlotte's reproductive organs?
She'd had a placental abruption.
But it had started to clot over.
So, that isn't what killed her?
No. But it left her weakened.
In Sibyl Danforth's statement,
she said that Charlotte appeared
to have had a stroke.
Is that the case?
No. The brain would have shown
significant changes. It didn't.
So, apart from this placental
abruption, what did you find?
In my opinion, Mrs Bedford vagaled.
Would you elaborate?
Yes, of course.
Right here in the back of our heads
is a pair of cranial nerves
called the vagus nerves.
In layman's terms,
they help carry information
from the heart to the brain.
And in a particularly long labour,
and I'm speaking here
of hours and hours
of very deep breathing,
very, very hard work,
the brain can eventually go hypoxic,
sort of shut down
from lack of oxygen.
The heart will slow down,
it could even stop,
and you pass out.
Some doctors say you vagaled out.
Can you die from this?
Yes, of course,
if it's not treated.
Was this lack of oxygen to the brain
the cause of death?
No. I think Mrs Danforth's CPR
actually brought her back.
What do you base this opinion on?
There were close to 750ml
of blood in the abdomen.
With such an extensive
loss of blood,
the heart would have had
to be pumping.
So, would it be correct to say
that Charlotte was alive
when Mrs Danforth cut her open
and that she subsequently
bled to death?
In my opinion, yes,
that's what I stated in my report.
Thank you.
Dr Tierney,
you think Sibyl revived her?
She must have.
There was too much blood.
Do you have anything to support
this opinion?
Nothing else is necessary.
Dr Tierney, if you wanted
categorical proof
that a woman died
during a C-section,
how much blood would you expect
to find in the abdominal cavity?
Categorically, perhaps 1,000ml.
But you didn't find
that much, did you?
No.
So, your opinion is based
on a flawed hypothesis.
Objection.
Withdrawn.
I have nothing further.
Dr Tierney, in this case,
considering all of your findings,
was 750ml enough blood to convince
you that the Caesarean
was the cause of death?
Yes. Most certainly.
Thank you.
The State rests, Your Honour.
Mr Hastings, you may begin
your defence after lunch.
Court will recess until 2pm.
(GAVEL BANGS)
So, Dr Hewitt,
you have no doubt
that Charlotte Bedford was dead
when Sibyl operated?
None whatsoever. It's absurd
to even ask the question.
I've worked with Sibyl Danforth
as her backup doctor
for close to a decade.
She is an exceptional midwife.
And if she tells me the woman
was dead, then she was.
Unfortunately, I've had to perform
autopsies on several women
who've died from Caesareans.
And I've never seen
less than 1,100ml of blood
in the peritoneal cavity.
That's more than Dr Tierney found
in Mrs Bedford.
Yes. Significantly.
A full pint, in fact.
So, is it your opinion then, Doctor,
that Mrs Bedford died
of lack of oxygen to the brain?
It is.
And that she was already dead
when Sibyl saved the baby?
Absolutely.
Thank you.
SYBIL: I keep thinking
about what I wrote
that day Charlotte died.
I'm drawn to it.
I reread it a thousand times.
Every detail.
And still, that night's become
some vague haunting thing
like a nightmare
from years ago.
Tomorrow I'll just have to find
it in myself to be cool
and confident on the witness stand.
That's what I have to do
for my family.
(ENGINE STARTS)
(TENDER MUSIC PLAYS)
And you were certain she was dead
when you saved the baby?
Absolutely. Yes.
What made you so certain?
I checked her. I felt for a pulse.
I checked her heart.
There was nothing.
Did Miss Heston and Mr Bedford
see you do this?
No, they were downstairs.
So, they couldn't know
that you checked Mrs Bedford again?
No.
But you did.
Of course. Yes.
Sibyl,
you had never done a C-section.
You had no surgical training.
Why did you do it?
I knew the baby would die, too.
I couldn't bear to let that happen.
(CRYING)
Yes. Talk to him, Asa.
Say something to your son...
(CRYING)
Shh. It will be alright.
He's such a beautiful baby.
It will be alright.
Sibyl, there's one thing
I'd like to clarify.
If you knew
that Mrs Bedford was dead,
why did you sew up the body?
I couldn't leave her like that.
It wouldn't have been fair to her,
or her son.
The way we come into this world
means more than any of us realise
and I just wanted
to make sure he had an image
of how incredibly pretty
and peaceful she was.
I don't really remember turning
out the lights when I was through,
but I looked at my diaries
the other day and I saw that I had.
Your medical notebooks?
No, my personal notebooks.
Your Honour, may we approach?
Yes.
What diaries?
Mr Hastings?
(MURMURING)
Your Honour, this is...
I should be read to use them first.
No. I have already ruled.
Step back.
I want all Mrs Danforth's personal
diaries from March forward
in my hands by the end
of the lunch break.
Court will be recessed
until I can determine
if they contain information
that is relevant to this case.
(GAVEL BANGS)
(MURMURING)
(INAUDIBLE DIALOGUE)
They're in my office.
I don't think you'll have
any trouble finding them.
Sure. I'll get them.
I'll go with you.
I know right where they are.
Good.
I'll just be a second.
Alright.
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYS)
I don't know.
If he admits the notebooks,
we'll have to ask
for a continuance so I can evaluate
what's in them.
Is this everything?
Yeah.
I'll take them to the Judge
and we'll get some lunch.
This could take a while.
All rise.
Be seated.
The notebooks in question
are a personal account
of Mrs Danforth's life.
There is nothing in them
that is relevant to her testimony,
specifically or to the case
in general.
Therefore,
motion to admit the notebooks
into evidence is denied.
ALLISON: The closing arguments
were anticlimactic.
Both lawyers recalled the testimony
of their expert witnesses.
The prosecution contending
that Sibyl had revived Charlotte,
then killed her by operating.
Steven insisted that the defence
experts had made it perfectly clear.
Charlotte had vagaled and died
and Sibyl had not been able
to revive her.
She had, in fact,
taken heroic measures to save
the baby from its dead mother.
Steven reminded the jury
of my mother's excellent record
and reputation as a midwife.
Bill Tanner reminded them
of Anne Heston
and Asa Bedford's accounts.
But Steven countered that neither
one of them was in a position,
emotionally or otherwise,
to make a judgment.
When it was all over,
it remained anybody's guess
as to what the verdict would be.
The only question left
was whom would the jury believe.
The burden of proof was on the State.
And for the first time in a week,
I would believe
they would acquit her.
(FOOTSTEPS)
ALLISON: If I hadn't heard the myth
about the jury looking at her,
I'm sure I would have believed
they would acquit
her until the very end.
Please, please look at her.
Look at her, please.
Please. Please, look at her.
Look at her.
(DOOR OPENS)
All rise.
Be seated.
Please look at her.
Look at her.
Have you reached a verdict?
We have, Your Honour.
No!
Will the defendant stand?
How say you?
On the charge
of involuntary manslaughter,
we find the defendant...
not guilty.
(CHEERING AND APPLAUSE)
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
You are free to go.
Court is adjourned.
Thank you, Steven, for everything.
I should have told
you about the diaries.
I just didn't think about it.
Well, it doesn't matter.
There's nothing damaging in them.
Look, Sibyl...
Why don't you come
back to the house.
I don't think so. But thank you.
I couldn't have endured
this without you.
I won't forget you.
And I won't forget you.
('RESPECT' BY ARETHA FRANKLIN PLAYS)
# What you want
# Baby, I've got it
# What you need... #
Here they are.
# ..You know I got it... #
The troops decided to bring dinner.
# ..For a little respect
# Just a little bit
# Mister, just a little bit... #
It's OK. Connie, it's alright.
It's over. It's OK. It's over.
Honey?
Oh, I was just thinking,
maybe I should redo this room.
You know,
maybe some nice wallpaper.
Maybe irises.
Lots of blue irises.
There's nothing like it, you know.
One miracle after another.
A little human being struggling
to get into the world.
It was my life.
What do you mean, "was?"
I don't think I can do it anymore.
Of course, you can.
You saved a life. Be proud of it.
What if I don't have the courage
to do it again?
What if I just freeze up?
You won't. I know it.
You'd never let somebody die
if you could prevent it.
All these years I thought
I took care of you and Connie.
That you've needed me.
But I'm the one that needs you.
I know.
(FOOTSTEPS)
Hey, you two, save the mush
for later. It's party time.
You go on.
I'll be there later.
You can't hide up here.
Everyone wants to congratulate you.
I can't...
Oh. Oh, Connie.
"The room was very quiet.
"Even the ice and snow had stopped
banging against the window.
"I didn't want to hurt the baby.
"I told myself I just had to be
incredibly careful.
"I don't think
anyone but me saw the body flinch.
"At the time, I just thought
it was one of those horrible
"post-mortem reflexes, so I went on.
"And I believed
it still when I saw that blood.
"And it just kept flowing.
"I had checked for a pulse
and a heartbeat.
"There hadn't been one.
I knew she was dead.
"I was absolutely sure of it then.
"But now, a day later...
"after I've gotten some sleep...
"I just don't know.
"Whenever I think of that flinch,
I just don't know."
(PARTY CONTINUES DOWNSTAIRS)
I don't know
if what you did was brave or stupid.
Or both.
I want you to know
I love you either way.
But it was wrong.
I know.
But I would do it again.
I understand how you feel, Connie,
and I believe in trusting
your instincts. It's what guides us.
But you need perspective, too.
Don't be so sure of yourself.
You go ploughing through life
believing you're always right...
you can make mistakes.
What do you think
now of what I did?
I'm glad you saved the baby.
ALLISON: We both understood
that it was the question
that mattered.
That was the thing that made it clear
that our lives as mother
and child were in some way over.
I was 14 years old
and I knew my mother's worst fear.
Why don't you come
in and get something to eat.
I'll be in in a minute.
OK.
(CHEERING AND APPLAUSE)
(TENDER MUSIC PLAYS)
ALLISON: Years later,
I became a doctor.
An OB-GYN.
In some level it was simply a desire
to be around the miracle
of mothers and babies.
A legacy from my mother, perhaps.
But the reasons go deeper still.
I need to know,
without doubt or reservation,
exactly when someone is alive
and when they're dead.
As for the trial
and all that happened,
we never spoke of it again.
A few months later, she stopped
delivering babies for good.
I'm sure some people thought
it was because of Charlotte's death.
And maybe it was,
but not in the way they thought.
She had lost her confidence.
Without that she knew her mothers
and their babies could be at risk.
And for them
she would give up anything...
even her greatest joy.
Captioned by Ai-Media
ai-media.tv