MAN: TROOP!
ATTENTION!
BY THE LEFT!
QUICK MARCH!
LEFT, RIGHT, LEFT...
MAN'S VOICE:
THERE'S EVIDENCE
THAT SOMEONE THEY CALL
"AGENT VIRGIL"
MAY BE A CONVERT.
THE MAIN SOURCE OF THE LEAKS
IS SOMEONE
WHO WORKS INSIDE THE
FOREIGN OFFICE IN LONDON,
AND HIS K.G.B. CODE NAME
IS "HOMER."
MI6 HAVE MODIFIED
THEIR ORIGINAL LIST OF SUSPECTS
AND PUT GEORGE QUENNELL
RIGHT AT THE VERY TOP.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
I THINK LONDON'S RIGHT.
[PHONE RINGS]
YOU THINK WE SHOULD ARREST HIM?
MMM, NOT YET.
LET'S MAKE ABSOLUTELY SURE
FIRST, SHALL WE?
THANK YOU, DICK.
MAN: GOOD MORNING,
MR. QUENNELL.
[WHISPERING]
I'LL MAKE ALL THE ARRANGEMENTS
FOR YOU TO JOIN ME
IN MOSCOW.
[SNIFFLING]
[CLOCK CHIMING]
WHAT'S THIS OTHER CASE?
MINE.
I'M GOING, TOO.
DOES STANLEY KNOW?
YES, HE ORDERED IT.
NEWS REPORTER:
BRITISH AUTHORITIES
HAVE NOW LEARNED
THAT GEORGE QUENNELL
AND ANGUS PETHERBRIDGE,
THE TWO DIPLOMATS WHO
FLED ENGLAND ON MAY 25TH, 1951
AND LATER SURFACED IN MOSCOW,
HAD BEEN SOVIET SPIES
SINCE THEIR RECRUITMENT
AT CAMBRIDGE UNIVERSITY.
THE LENGTH OF THEIR DECEPTION
AND THE EASE OF THEIR ESCAPE
WOULD INDICATE THAT THE K.G.B.
HAS PENETRATED
BRITISH INTELLIGENCE
AT THE VERY HIGHEST LEVEL.
[CHATTERING]
[HEN CACKLING]
SALLY!
COME AND JOIN US
FOR LUNCH.
OH, I JUST CAME
TO PICK UP MY MAIL.
ALL OF US CAME TO BEIRUT
WITH SOME OTHER PURPOSE
IN MIND, DEAR.
HOW HAVE YOU BEEN?
WE'VE MISSED YOU,
SALLY!
YOU BECOME A RECLUSE
EVERY TIME PAUL GOES
"BYE-BYE."
WOULD YOU LIKE
A DRINK?
OH, IF I MUST.
THE ONLY DIFFERENCE
BETWEEN ME
AND THAT BUGGER
T.E. LAWRENCE
WAS I HAD THE BALLS
TO BECOME A BLOODY MUSLIM.
WHO'S THAT?
THAT'S OLD
RANDOLPH CAUFFIELD.
YOU MET HIS SON,
LEO?
MIDDLE EAST STRINGER
WITH THE LONDON TIMES.
LEO!
COME AND MEET THE MOST
BEAUTIFUL WOMAN IN BEIRUT!
OH, GOD.
LEO,
THIS IS SALLY TYLER.
PLEASED TO MEET YOU, SALLY.
AND YOU, LEO.
LEO'S A BIT OF A LONER,
SALLY,
BUT WE STILL THINK OF HIM
AS ONE OF US.
WELL, TO BE IN SOCIETY
IS SIMPLY A BORE,
BUT TO BE OUT OF IT
IS MERELY A TRAGEDY.
AT LEAST HE'S NOT LIKE THESE
YOUNGER JOURNALISTS OUT THERE.
THEY ARE SO N.Q.O.C.M.D.
"NOT QUITE OUR CLASS,
MY DEAR."
PLEASE, PETER.
I'M SURE SALLY GREW UP
BLISSFULLY UNENCUMBERED
BY D.P.L.T.O.C.
"DREADFUL PHRASES LIKE THAT,
OLD CHAP."
[ALL GIGGLE]
PETER'S A LITTLE LECHEROUS
AND OPINIONATED
OLD BASTARD, ISN'T HE?
HE'S ONE OF MY
CLOSEST FRIENDS.
WHICH, OF COURSE,
ARE BOTH DEEPLY ADMIRABLE
QUALITIES IN A MAN.
BUT NOT THAT CLOSE.
I KNOW.
MR. CAUFFIELD: AND WHO BROUGHT
THE AMERICANS TO ARABIA
IN THE FIRST BLOODY PLACE?
I DID.
I SUPPOSE I SHOULD
GO AND RESCUE MY FATHER
BEFORE HE FALLS DOWN.
IT WAS NICE TO MEET YOU,
SALLY.
AND YOU, LEO.
[ARABIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[WOMAN SINGING]
WOW,
I DIDN'T RECOGNIZE YOU.
YOU LOOK FABULOUS!
I NEED MY BEST FRIEND AROUND
TO HELP ME
GET THROUGH THESE THINGS.
OK,
WHERE'S PAUL THIS TIME?
OH, CAIRO.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
HOW WELL YOU MANAGE
WHEN HE GOES OFF
ON HIS ASSIGNMENTS.
OH, I'M USED TO IT.
OH, YOU KNOW ME,
I GET LONELY GOING
TO THE BATHROOM ON MY OWN.
[GIGGLES]
WHERE ARE THE TWINS?
OH,
I JUST GOT THEM INTO BED.
GO UP AND SAY
GOOD NIGHT TO THEM.
THEY WOULD LOVE
TO SEE YOU!
YES, GO ON.
I'D LOVE TO.
OK.
"CAPTAIN BIGGER'S EYES
"WERE COLD AND HARD
LIKE PICNIC EGGS.
"IT'S THE CODE, SIR.
THE CODE.
"THAT'S A BIG WORD
WITH THE MEN
"WHO LIVE ON THE FRONTIERS
OF EMPIRE."
[DEEP MAN'S VOICE]
AYE, MATEY.
OH, HELLO.
JOAN OF ARC'S ARRIVED.
[GIGGLING]
CHILDREN ARE GENERALLY
MUCH NICER THAN GROWNUPS,
AREN'T THEY?
I MEAN, THEY NEVER COMPLAIN,
THEY NEVER CRITICIZE.
AND IF THEY GET CROSS--
IT JUST BLOWS OVER.
I JUST GET ALONG
WITH CHILDREN
SO MUCH BETTER
THAN ADULTS.
I REALLY MISS MY OWN.
THEY'RE IN ENGLAND RIGHT NOW
WITH THEIR MOTHER,
TILL I GET
SORTED OUT HERE.
MY WIFE AND I
HAVEN'T SLEPT UNDER
THE SAME ROOF FOR MANY YEARS.
OH.
HOW DO YOU KNOW FAY AND GLEN?
OH, I'VE KNOWN FAY
FOR YEARS.
I MET HER
WHEN I WAS AN ART CONSULTANT
FOR AN AMERICAN COMPANY
IN TURKEY.
OH, YOU'RE AN ARTIST?
WELL, NOW AND THEN.
I JUST CAN'T SEEM
TO DISCIPLINE MYSELF
BODY AND SOUL.
[CHUCKLES]
DO YOU WANT TO DANCE?
NOT REALLY.
OH, THANK GOD.
I HATE DANCING.
TELL ME ALL ABOUT YOURSELF.
I MEAN,
WHEREABOUTS IN AMERICA
DO YOU COME FROM?
THE NORTHWEST, NEAR SEATTLE.
AH, SEATTLE.
IT'S RATHER LIKE ENGLAND,
ISN'T IT? I MEAN--
WELL, THE CLIMATE, ANYWAY.
THAT'S GREAT.
NOW WE'RE TALKING
ABOUT THE WEATHER.
[SIGHS]
I KNOW.
AND WE MADE SUCH A PROMISING
BEGINNING.
I'M SORRY.
IT'S MY FAULT.
I'M A LITTLE NERVOUS.
WHY?
BECAUSE...
EVERY TIME I'M AROUND YOU,
I HAVE TO KEEP REMINDING MYSELF
THAT I'M MARRIED.
[CHUCKLES]
IT WAS NICE
SEEING YOU AGAIN.
WHO ARE YOU TONIGHT?
LOUIS PASTEUR.
WELL, HE WAS VERY PERSISTENT.
SO WAS JOAN OF ARC.
[SHOUTING IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
SALLY!
UM...
WOULD YOU LIKE A DRINK?
A TEA, PLEASE.
TEA, PLEASE.
I'M GLAD YOU'VE COME. I...
NEEDED SOME HUMAN CONTACT.
I'VE BEEN LIKE A HERMIT
SINCE CHRISTMAS.
ME, TOO. PAUL'S AWAY AGAIN
ON BUSINESS IN LIBYA.
THANK YOU.
CAN I ASK YOU A QUESTION?
I MEAN, DON'T ANSWER ME IF YOU
THINK IT'S NOT MY BUSINESS.
ARE YOU HAPPILY MARRIED?
HAPPILY ENOUGH.
PAUL AND I ARE COMFORTABLE.
PAUL'S A GOOD HUSBAND
AND FATHER.
I'M SURE HE WISHES
HE'D PICKED SOMEONE
WHO WAS A LITTLE BIT MORE
EFFICIENT IN THE KITCHEN
AND SOMEONE WHO WOULD KEEP
THEIR OPINIONS TO THEMSELVES.
MAYBE HE SHOULD HAVE MARRIED ME.
I'M VERY GOOD IN THE KITCHEN
AND I KEEP MY OPINIONS
TO MYSELF.
WELL, IF HE EVER DECIDES
TO CHANGE HIS MIND,
I'LL HAVE HIM
GIVE YOU A CALL.
DID THAT ANSWER YOUR QUESTION?
I RAN INTO
AN OLD ACQUAINTANCE TODAY
I HAVEN'T SEEN FOR YEARS.
BRITISH WRITER
NAMED LEO CAUFFIELD.
YOU HAVEN'T COME ACROSS HIM
ON THE CIRCUIT
SINCE I'VE BEEN GONE,
HAVE YOU?
YES.
I ALWAYS LIKED LEO.
OH, MATTER OF FACT, I INVITED
HIM OVER TO DINNER NEXT WEEK.
PAUL.
HMM?
HAVE YOU THOUGHT ANY MORE
ABOUT TAKING THAT OFFER
TO RUN THE BUREAU IN PARIS?
WHY?
I JUST THOUGHT IT MIGHT BE A...
GOOD CHANGE FOR US.
I ALREADY TURNED IT DOWN.
THERE'S NOTHING MUCH
OF INTEREST
HAPPENING IN PARIS
THESE DAYS.
SALLY, DID YOU KNOW THAT
LEO HERE WAS AWARDED AN O.B.E.
BY THE QUEEN HERSELF?
WHAT DID YOU GET IT FOR?
I WAS WORKING FOR
BRITISH INTELLIGENCE.
I WAS THE HEAD OF A THING
CALLED "SECTION NINE."
THE BRITS' COUNTERINTELLIGENCE
DIVISION, SALLY.
LEO: MAY I HAVE
ANOTHER CUP OF COFFEE?
IT'S ABSOLUTELY DELICIOUS.
PAUL: I'M OFF ON ANOTHER TRIP
NEXT WEEK, LEO.
LEO:
REALLY?
I THINK SALLY GETS A BIT MOODY
WHEN I'M GONE.
PAUL: WOMEN DON'T LIKE TO BE
LEFT ALONE FOR TOO LONG.
IF YOU HAVE ANY TIME,
YOU SHOULD KEEP HER COMPANY.
HAVE YOU THOUGHT OF
TAKING HER WITH YOU?
[BOTH CHUCKLING]
CAN I GET YOU A BRANDY?
OH, NO, THANKS.
I'VE GOT TO BE GOING SOON.
I PROMISED MY FATHER
I'D PICK HIM UP
AT ST. GEORGE'S
AFTER DINNER.
EXCUSE ME, WAITER,
THERE'S A BEAUTIFUL WOMAN
IN MY COFFEE.
I HEAR THE AMERICANS
ARE TRYING TO LAUNCH
THEIR OWN SPACESHIP
NOW THAT THE RUSSIANS
HAVE SENT UP SPUTNIK II.
LEO: YES.
I GATHER IT'S CALLED
"THE VANGUARD."
[MARKET BUZZING]
WOMAN:
HOW MUCH WAS IT?
[LAUGHING]
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
I WANT TO KNOW
WHY TIME STANDS STILL
WHEN WE'RE TOGETHER.
MAYBE YOUR WATCH BROKE.
PROBABLY.
EVERYTHING ELSE I VALUED
BEFORE I MET YOU
SEEMS WORTHLESS NOW.
[SALLY MOANS SOFTLY]
I CAN'T DO THIS.
SALLY...
WE DON'T HAVE TO BE
IMPRISONED
BY THE CHOICES WE MADE
IN THE PAST. HMM?
DEEPER AND DEEPER...
I DON'T HAVE THE--
OH...
LEO, I DON'T HAVE THE COURAGE
TO TEAR MY WHOLE LIFE APART.
[BOTH BREATHING HEAVILY]
[INDISTINCT VOICES]
PAUL, WOULD YOU PLEASE
SAY SOMETHING!
I'M...
JEALOUS.
OF LEO?
OF YOU.
I WISH I COULD HAVE FELT--
COULD FEEL LIKE THAT
ABOUT SOMEONE.
OH, PAUL!
[DOORBELL RINGS]
PAUL...
IF I COULD HAVE FALLEN
FOR ANYONE IN THE WORLD
OTHER THAN SALLY,
I SWEAR I WOULD HAVE DONE IT.
I WON'T FILE FOR DIVORCE MYSELF
BUT I WON'T STAND IN YOUR WAY,
EITHER.
YOU KNOW I INTEND TO MARRY HER
AS SOON AS IT'S FINAL.
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA, WHOA!
SO GOOD. [GIGGLES]
TEA, DARLING,
ON THE TERRACE?
THIS IS THE FIRST THING
I'VE DONE IN YEARS.
I GUESS I'M THE OPPOSITE
OF A TORTURED ARTIST.
I CAN ONLY DRAW OR PAINT
WHEN I'M AT PEACE WITH MYSELF.
THERE IS NOTHING MORE PLEASING
TO THE EYE
THAN A PICTURE
OF WOMEN'S BREASTS.
IT'S A BOWL OF FRUIT.
REALLY?
"REALLY?"
I'VE ALWAYS PREFERRED
SUNRISES TO SUNSETS.
SUGAR?
YEAH.
PRIEST:
LEO ANTHONY CHARLES CAUFFIELD,
DO YOU TAKE SALLY TO BE
THY LAWFUL WEDDED WIFE
TO HAVE AND TO HOLD,
FOR RICHER AND FOR POORER
IN SICKNESS AND IN HEALTH
TILL DEATH DO YOU PART?
LEO:
I DO.
MR. CAUFFIELD: NOW,
THE SECRET OF A HAPPY MARRIAGE
IS COMPROMISE.
AND I SHOULD KNOW, 'CAUSE
I'VE HAD A FEW WIVES MYSELF.
[LAUGHTER]
WELL, ANYWAY,
WHEN LEO'S MOTHER AND I
FIRST GOT MARRIED,
WE MOVED INTO
A SMALL HOUSE
WITH A SMALL GARDEN
AND A TINY FLOWER BED.
NOW, I WANTED TO PLANT DAFFODILS
AND SHE
WANTED TO PLANT RHUBARB.
SO WHAT DID WE DO?
WE COMPROMISED.
WE PLANTED RHUBARB.
[LAUGHTER]
ANYWAY, HERE'S A TOAST
TO THE HAPPY COUPLE.
HAPPY COUPLE.
WHERE DID YOU FIND
THE OLD SCHOOL SCARF?
I LOST MINE YEARS AGO.
I'VE ALWAYS HUNG ON TO IT.
IT BRINGS ME GOOD LUCK.
THIS IS THE REAL THING, ANDY.
I MEAN, I DIDN'T REALIZE
HOW LONELY I WAS
UNTIL I MET SALLY.
I COULDN'T BE HAPPIER FOR YOU,
OLD CHAP.
BUT I HOPE YOU'LL STILL
SPEND SOME TIME WITH OLD CHUMS.
OF COURSE.
CATHERINE AND I
HARDLY KNOW A SOUL IN BEIRUT.
BEIRUT?
I'VE JUST BEEN POSTED OUT THERE.
I DIDN'T THINK THE MIDDLE EAST
WAS QUITE YOUR BAG.
I'VE RATHER FELT LIKE...
NEW CHALLENGES.
BUT MORE IMPORTANTLY,
DO YOU?
[SCOFFS]
[FAY LAUGHING]
YOU LOOK RADIANT, HONEY.
I JUST HOPE
YOU'LL BOTH BE OK.
WE'LL BE FINE.
MY BIGGEST CONCERN WAS JEN,
AND SHE SEEMS TO BE
MORE THAN OK WITH IT.
I THINK KIDS ARE HAPPY
WHEN THEIR PARENTS ARE.
BY THE WAY,
I'M ASSUMING THAT YOU KNOW
THAT BEFORE LEO
WAS A JOURNALIST,
HE WAS KICKED OUT OF
BRITISH INTELLIGENCE.
HE WASN'T KICKED OUT, FAY.
HE RESIGNED.
I COULDN'T GIVE A DAMN
EITHER WAY, HONEY.
IF YOU'RE HAPPY,
I'M HAPPY.
[FAY CHUCKLES]
[GIRL'S DISTANT VOICE]
STOP THROWING BALLOONS!
YOU ARE IN BIG TROUBLE NOW,
MISTER!
SALLY:
HELLO.
HI, MOM.
OLIVER...
WHY CAN'T YOU PLAY
WITH THE OTHER KIDS
INSTEAD OF TERRORIZING
THE ENTIRE NEIGHBORHOOD?
WELL, YOU'RE LOOKING
VERY PLEASED WITH YOURSELF.
I HAVE JUST BOOKED A TABLE
AT "LUCULLUS"
FOR OUR ANNIVERSARY DINNER
TOMORROW NIGHT.
OH, MY GOD!
I THOUGHT
YOU HAD TO BE KNIGHTED
OR HAVE THREE HYPHENS IN
YOUR LAST NAME TO GET IN THERE.
LISTEN, I MAY BE JUST
ANOTHER BRITISH JOURNALIST,
BUT I DO HAVE
MY CONNECTIONS.
WELL, YOU BETTER TELL ME
WHO THEY ARE
AND I'LL SEND THEM
A THANK-YOU NOTE.
CAN WE GO SAILING TOMORROW, DAD?
AYE-AYE, MATEY.
IF THAT STORM THAT'S A-COMIN'
'AS ALL CLEARED UP, HAR-HAR.
YIPPEE!
WAS THAT
"YIPPEE, THERE'S A STORM COMING"
OR
"YIPPEE, WE'RE GOING SAILING"?
BOTH, I GUESS.
I HAVE AN APPOINTMENT.
OH... WELL,
I HAVE SPAM.
SO THANK GOD WE'RE GOING TO THE
TOLLANDS' HOUSE FOR DINNER, OK?
I'LL BE BACK AT SIX.
OK.
[CHILDREN TALKING INDISTINCTLY]
I NEVER THOUGHT I'D SEE THE DAY
WHEN BOTH MY DAUGHTER
AND MY STEPDAUGHTER
ENDED UP IN JAIL.
WHAT DID I DO WRONG, EH?
I'M JUST VISITING, DADDY.
SALLY: HEY! DON'T FORGET
YOUR COAT AND UMBRELLA.
THEY'RE FORECASTING RAIN LATER.
LEO.
[HUMMING]
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
SALLY:
SOMEBODY GET THAT?
HELLO?
OK, I WILL.
BYE-BYE.
IT WAS DADDY. HE SAYS
HE'S GONNA BE A BIT LATE.
HE'LL MEET YOU AT THE TOLLANDS
AROUND EIGHT O'CLOCK.
OK. THANKS.
[DOORBELL CHIMES]
[THUNDER CRASHING]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
THANK YOU.
HI.
CAT'S AND DOGS, HUH?
LEO'S BEEN HELD UP,
BUT HE'LL BE HERE PRETTY SOON.
WELL,
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
EVERYBODY'S HAVING PROBLEMS
WITH THIS WEATHER.
CHAMPAGNE, PLEASE.
OH!
THANK YOU.
FAY WILL BE GLAD TO SEE YOU.
MAN: EXCUSE US.
ARE YOU SURE
YOU DON'T WANT US TO WAIT?
OH, POSITIVE, FAY.
I'M SURE HE JUST HAD TROUBLE
GETTING A CAB.
ALL RIGHT.
LET'S EAT THEN. COME ON.
FAY:
PLEASE SIT DOWN.
[CHATTERING
IN VARIOUS LANGUAGES]
[THUNDER CRASHING]
SALLY?
WOULD YOU LIKE TO CALL HOME,
SEE IF HE'S GOT BACK YET?
OH, YES.
THANK YOU.
SALLY: DAD'S NOT HERE.
HAVE YOU HEARD FROM HIM?
NO. HE HASN'T RUNG
OR STOPPED BY.
[THUNDER CRASHING]
ALL RIGHT.
DO YOU THINK MAYBE
IT GOT SO LATE
HE JUST DECIDED
TO GO STRAIGHT THERE?
I'LL CALL YOU BACK, HONEY.
DON'T WORRY.
[RAIN POURING]
OLIVER: CAN I SLEEP
IN YOUR ROOM ALL NIGHT
IF DADDY
DOESN'T COME BACK?
OF COURSE.
HE PROMISED TO
TAKE ME SAILING TOMORROW.
HE'LL BE BACK.
WHEN DID GLEN TOLLAND
SAY TO CALL THE HOSPITALS?
NOT TILL MORNING, HONEY.
BUT IT'LL BE OK.
OH, ANDY!
I'M SORRY TO CALL YOU SO EARLY.
IT'S JUST, YOU KNOW,
YOU'RE HIS CLOSEST FRIEND.
I'M REALLY WORRIED.
DON'T WORRY. DON'T WORRY.
YOU'VE DONE THE RIGHT THING.
I KNOW. I JUST--
IS IT ALL RIGHT IF I TAKE
A QUICK LOOK AT HIS STUDY?
SURE.
OF COURSE. OK, GOOD.
IS THERE ANYTHING MISSING?
TYPEWRITER?
I DON'T THINK SO.
DOCUMENTS?
NO.
ANDY:
NEW PASSPORT.
WAS HE PLANNING ON
GOING ANYWHERE?
I DON'T THINK SO.
FOR THE TIMES?
NO.
SALLY,
I'M GONNA CALL THE POLICE
AND FILE
A MISSING PERSON'S REPORT.
SALLY:
OK.
[EXHALES]
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
ANDY: HELLO?
YES, YOU HAVE.
ARE YOU SURE?
YES.
THANK YOU.
THE BODY OF AN
UNIDENTIFIED WHITE MALE
HAS BEEN FOUND
WASHED UP NEAR THE HARBOR.
[SOBS]
IT'S NOT HIM.
NO.
[DOOR BANGING]
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
[KNOCKING]
MRS. CAUFFIELD?
SECURITY POLICE.
SECURITY POLICE?
MAY WE TAKE A LOOK
AROUND YOUR APARTMENT?
WAIT A MINUTE...
SALLY: WHAT THE HELL
DO YOU THINK YOU'RE DOING?
AHMED!
ANDY?
ANDY:
SALLY, THIS IS DENNIS ACWORTH,
MY SUCCESSOR AS S.I.S. CHIEF
HERE IN BEIRUT.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
WHY ARE THE POLICE
TEARING OUR APARTMENT APART?
MRS. CAUFFIELD,
THE WARRANT IS OUT
FOR THE ARREST
OF YOUR HUSBAND.
THE LEBANESE AUTHORITIES
BELIEVE
HE MAY BE WORKING
FOR THE SOVIET UNION.
IS THIS SOME KIND OF SICK JOKE?
ESPIONAGE IS NOT SOMETHING
WE AT MI6
REGARD AS A SOURCE OF HUMOR.
SALLY, I UNDERSTAND HOW
YOU MUST FEEL ABOUT THIS, BUT--
OH, NO, ANDY.
YOU DON'T KNOW HOW I FEEL.
YOU COULDN'T POSSIBLY KNOW
HOW I FEEL, ANDY,
OR YOU WOULDN'T BE
ABLE TO JUST STAND THERE
WHILE THIS STUCK-UP PRICK
TELLS ME THAT
THEY THINK MY HUSBAND IS WORKING
FOR THE GODDAMN RUSSIANS!
ANDY?
[SOBS]
[DOOR SLAMS]
SORRY.
[LUCY SOBS]
[WHISPERING]
ALL RIGHT.
OH... OH...
[SOBS]
OLIVER:
I'M GOING TO THE BEACH.
SALLY:
ALL RIGHT.
RECEPTIONIST:
...MERCI BEAUCOUP.
HELLO.
I'M SALLY CAUFFIELD.
MY HUSBAND LEO CAUFFIELD
AND I
USED TO HAVE AN ARRANGEMENT
TO PICK UP OUR MAIL HERE.
ARE THERE ANY LETTERS
FOR HIM?
NO, MRS. CAUFFIELD,
I'M AFRAID NOT.
BUT THERE'S A LETTER FOR YOU.
LEO'S VOICE:
MY DEAREST SAL.
I'M SO SORRY
I DISAPPEARED SO SUDDENLY
BUT I HAD TO LEAVE TOWN
ON A VERY IMPORTANT STORY.
PLEASE, PLEASE DON'T WORRY,
DARLING.
EVERYTHING IS FINE.
INSIDE YOUR STUDIO,
YOU'LL FIND SOMETHING FROM ME.
THERE SHOULD BE ENOUGH CASH
TO PAY ALL THE BILLS.
YOU'LL ALSO FIND SOMETHING
TO REMEMBER
OUR VERY SPECIAL DAY THIS WEEK.
I HAVEN'T FORGOTTEN YOU
OR THE KIDS,
OR EVERYTHING
YOU ALL MEAN TO ME.
AND I BELIEVE NOW, AS
PASSIONATELY AS I ALWAYS HAVE,
THAT WE WILL ALL SOMEDAY
BE LIVING IN A BETTER WORLD
THAN THIS.
AND I MISS YOU
AND LOVE YOU MORE THAN EVER.
GIVE THE KIDS A BIG HUG
AND A KISS FROM ME.
LOVE, LEO.
[GIRLS LAUGHING]
[GIGGLING] OH!
MOM?
[REPORTERS CHATTERING]
REPORTER #1:
HAS HE BEEN KIDNAPPED?
REPORTER #2: IS HE WORKING
FOR BRITISH INTELLIGENCE?
REPORTER #3:
HOW MUCH WERE YOU AWARE OF?
AS I HAVE ALREADY TOLD
THE POLICE...
AND THE BRITISH EMBASSY...
REPORTER #3: MRS. CAUFFIELD,
THIS ISN'T THE FIRST TIME,
IS IT?
...MY HUSBAND IS AWAY
DOING A STORY FOR THE TIMES.
UNFORTUNATELY, SOME PEOPLE
HAVE CHOSEN TO JUMP
TO THE WRONG CONCLUSION.
REPORTER #4:
ARE YOU YOURSELF IN ANY WAY--
REPORTER #2:
THE POLICE HAVE BEEN IN THERE?
THANK YOU.
IT'S A LITTLE STRANGE
THE WAY HE LEFT,
YOU'VE GOT TO ADMIT THAT.
PEOPLE THOUGHT A LOT OF
STRANGE THINGS WHEN HE LEFT MI6,
BUT THEY WERE WRONG.
I HAVE LESS REASON
TO TRUST LEO THAN ANYONE
BUT IF IT'S ANY CONSOLATION,
I DON'T BELIEVE
HE'S A RUSSIAN AGENT.
THANKS FOR THE VOTE
OF CONFIDENCE.
YOU KNOW,
IT'S POSSIBLE
HE DIDN'T ACTUALLY
WRITE THAT LETTER.
I DON'T WANT TO BE
AN ALARMIST,
BUT AS A FORMER BIGWIG WITH
BRITISH COUNTERINTELLIGENCE,
STILL DOING WORK FOR THEM
ON THE SIDE
HE'D BE SOMETHING OF A CAPTURE
FOR THE K.G.B.
OH, THAT MAKES ME FEEL
A LOT BETTER.
OH, LISTEN, SALLY,
I'M SURE EVERYTHING'S
GONNA BE FINE.
BUT UNTIL THINGS
SETTLE DOWN AROUND HERE...
I THINK JEN SHOULD
COME BACK WITH ME TO NEW YORK.
EVEN IF HE IS JUST ON A STORY,
PEOPLE ARE GONNA BELIEVE
WHATEVER THEY WANNA BELIEVE.
AND UNTIL HE SHOWS UP SOMEWHERE,
IT'S GONNA BE A CARNIVAL.
COME HERE.
OK.
"THE ENCLOSED IS TO BUY
TICKETS TO LONDON
"FOR YOU AND
THE CHILDREN.
"JUST WRITE THE DATE
OF YOUR DEPARTURE IN CHALK
"ON THE WALL
AT THE END OF OUR STREET.
"ALL MY LOVE."
I GUESS HE COULD BE
WORKING ON SOMETHING
THAT REQUIRES
THIS DEGREE OF SECRECY.
IT'S A LITTLE OVER-THE-TOP,
ISN'T IT?
SO EITHER HE'S BEEN ABDUCTED
AGAINST HIS WILL,
OR IT BOILS DOWN TO WHETHER
OR NOT I TRUST MY HUSBAND.
TRUST AND LOVE AREN'T ALWAYS
MUTUALLY INCLUSIVE, DARLING.
[CHALK SCREECHING]
[KNOCKING]
MAN:
MRS. CAUFFIELD?
WHO IS IT?
I HAVE COME FROM LEO.
SALLY:
HOW DID YOU GET UP HERE?
THE DOORMAN HAS STRICT ORDERS
NOT TO LET ANYONE UP HERE.
COME WITH ME NOW!
PLEASE.
I WILL MAKE
ALL THE ARRANGEMENTS.
I CAN'T.
[STUTTERING] I'M TAKING
MY CHILDREN TO ENGLAND
AS SOON AS THEY
GET HOME FROM SCHOOL.
PLEASE. I MUST COME IN.
GET AWAY!
[SCREAMS]
I'LL CALL THE POLICE!
I HAVE ONLY COME TO HELP.
YOU MUST BELIEVE THAT.
WHY DIDN'T YOU WRITE
A DEPARTURE DATE ON THE WALL
LIKE LEO ASKED?
WHERE IS HE?
ARE YOU HOLDING HIM SOMEWHERE?
EVERYTHING IS FINE.
PLEASE, MRS. CAUFFIELD,
COME.
[SALLY SCREAMS]
OH...
GO TO YOUR ROOMS!
I TOLD YOU
TO GO TO YOUR ROOMS RIGHT NOW!
[AIRPLANE PASSING]
ANDY: SALLY.
WELCOME BACK TO LONDON.
LET ME HAVE YOUR CASE.
THANKS, ANDY.
HOW ARE YOU?
OK.
LUCY.
HELLO,
MR. DARCY.
GOOD TO SEE YOU,
OLIVER.
YOU, TOO.
SALLY:
THE KIDS ARE GOING TO BE STAYING
WITH THEIR COUSIN IN WILTSHIRE.
I WANT THEM OUT OF
THE SPOTLIGHT IN LONDON.
AH, YES?
YES.
SALLY: OK, DARLINGS,
I'LL SEE YOU SOON.
AND WHERE ARE YOU STAYING?
I'M STAYING WITH
LEO'S SISTER, CYNTHIA,
IN ISLINGTON.
SALLY, DID LEO EVER
MENTION THE NAME
DICK MADSEN TO YOU?
WELL, THERE WAS A FELLOW
HE CALLED "LIMP DICK,"
IF THAT'S WHAT
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
AH...
HE WAS RATHER HOPING
YOU'D COME AND MEET WITH HIM
AT HIS OFFICE.
WELL, I'LL TRY NOT TO
CALL HIM THAT TO HIS FACE.
IF I CAN.
WOULD YOU LIKE
A BELGIAN TOFFEE?
I HAVE THEM SENT
FROM BRUSSELS EVERY MONTH.
NO, THANK YOU.
TELL ME...
DO YOU BY ANY CHANCE
RECOGNIZE THIS FELLOW,
MRS. CAUFFIELD?
IS HE THE CHAP
WHO TRIED TO PERSUADE YOU
TO LEAVE BEIRUT WITH HIM?
MM-HMM.
WHO IS HE?
HE'S TURKISH.
WELL,
THAT'S HELPFUL.
THIS PHOTO OF HIM
WAS TAKEN LAST NIGHT.
HE WAS FOUND BY THE SIDE OF THE
ROAD, NEAR THE SYRIAN BORDER.
WHO DO YOU THINK DID IT?
K.G.B., C.I.A.
WHO KNOWS?
MAYBE EVEN THE TURKS THEMSELVES.
ANDY: SALLY, IS THERE
ANYTHING YOU CAN REMEMBER
ABOUT LEO'S BEHAVIOR BEFORE
HE DISAPPEARED THAT WAS UNUSUAL?
WELL,
HE WAS DRINKING MORE THAN USUAL.
WELL, THAT'S UNDERSTANDABLE,
IF HE WAS PLANNING AN ESCAPE.
THAT WASN'T WHAT WAS HAPPENING.
LEO'S FATHER WAS STAYING WITH US
AND HE HAD A HEART ATTACK.
YOU KNOW, LEO AND HIS FATHER
WERE VERY CLOSE.
DID YOU KNOW THAT
BEFORE THE WAR,
RANDOLPH CAUFFIELD TRIED
TO MAKE A DEAL WITH HITLER
WHICH WOULD HAVE
GIVEN THE GERMANS
AN UNLIMITED SUPPLY OF OIL?
WE HAD TO ASSIGN AN AGENT
TO KEEP US UP-TO-DATE
WITH ALL HIS ACTIVITIES.
WHY ARE YOU TELLING ME THIS?
BECAUSE THE AGENT WE ASSIGNED
WAS HIS OWN SON, LEO.
FORGIVE ME FOR ASKING,
MRS. CAUFFIELD,
BUT, MOST OF THE
UNDERGRADUATES THE K.G.B.
RECRUITED FROM CAMBRIDGE
WERE HOMOSEXUAL.
I WAS WONDERING
IF LEO'S ALLEGED PENCHANT
FOR THE OPPOSITE SEX
WAS ACTUALLY A FRONT?
WOMAN:
IF THEY'RE WHAT PASSES FOR
BRITISH INTELLIGENCE
THESE DAYS,
WE MUST BE THE STUPIDEST
BLOODY COUNTRY IN THE WORLD.
I NEVER UNDERSTOOD WHY LEO
HAD ANYTHING TO DO WITH THEM.
OH, YOU LOOK EXHAUSTED.
I'LL LET YOU GET SOME REST.
THANK YOU.
[INDISTINCT MUTTERING]
SOME COFFEE, ANDY?
THANKS, SALLY.
SURE.
HEY.
IT WAS THE PROUDEST MOMENT
OF MY FATHER'S LIFE
WHEN I GOT THE O.B.E.
I SUPPOSE I WAS A BIT OF
A DISAPPOINTMENT AFTER THAT.
OH, I DON'T THINK THAT'S TRUE.
WHEN MI6 ASKED ME TO RESIGN
THEY TOLD ME I WOULD HAVE BEEN
THE NEXT CHIEF
IF THE PETHERBRIDGE AND QUENNELL
BUSINESS HADN'T HAPPENED.
SURELY THEY DON'T BLAME YOU
FOR ALL OF THAT.
ACCORDING TO A MESSAGE
INTERCEPTED BY THE C.I.A.,
THE ESCAPE OF K.G.B. AGENTS
HOMER AND VIRGIL
WAS SET IN MOTION
BY SOMEONE CALLED AGENT STANLEY.
A THIRD MAN.
SOMEBODY MUCH HIGHER UP
IN BRITISH INTELLIGENCE.
THE AMERICANS MADE A BIG DEAL
ABOUT PETHERBRIDGE AND QUENNELL
AND I ALL BEING AT CAMBRIDGE
AT THE SAME TIME.
[SCOFFS]
THEN DICK MADSEN
JOINED THE BANDWAGON.
WHY DID MI6
TRY TO TO RECRUIT YOU AGAIN?
WELL, POSSIBLY
BECAUSE I WAS CLEARED
BY THE FOREIGN SECRETARY
OF ANY INVOLVEMENT.
OR?
OR THEY WANTED TO
TRY AND TRAP ME.
BUT FOUR YEARS LATER,
THEY STILL HAVEN'T MANAGED.
BOTH.
I HAD A DREAM
THAT I WAS SEPARATED
FROM YOU AND
THE CHILDREN.
IT WAS HORRIBLE.
OH...
MAN:
EXCUSE ME...
[GIRLS GIGGLING]
SALLY,
WE'VE HAD SOME NEWS ABOUT LEO.
MADSEN: MRS. CAUFFIELD,
WE'VE JUST BEEN INFORMED
THAT YOUR HUSBAND
HAS ARRIVED IN MOSCOW
OF HIS OWN FREE WILL.
WE CONSIDER THE TERM "TRAITOR"
RATHER MELODRAMATIC
WITHIN THESE WALLS.
IN INTELLIGENCE VERNACULAR,
YOUR HUSBAND HAS CHOSEN
"A DIFFERENT LOYALTY."
HOWEVER, HE IS AN
ACTIVE COMMUNIST AGENT,
AND IT IS IMPERATIVE
THAT YOU DON'T, ON ANY ACCOUNT,
CONSIDER JOINING HIM
IN THE SOVIET UNION.
IF YOU DO YOU'LL NEVER
BE ALLOWED TO RETURN.
THE ONLY THING I INTEND TO DO
IS TO GO TO NEW YORK
TO VISIT MY DAUGHTER.
WHERE I PLAN TO GO OR
WHAT I INTEND TO DO AFTER THAT
IS OF NO CONCERN TO YOU.
[GLASS SHATTERS]
HI!
OH!
OH.
YOU LOOK SO BEAUTIFUL!
LET ME TAKE THIS.
THERE SHOULD BE TWO MORE
IN THE TRUNK.
FOR WHAT IT'S WORTH,
SALLY,
I'M SORRY
ABOUT WHAT'S HAPPENED.
LEO HAD A LOT OF PEOPLE FOOLED.
I CAN'T SAY I WAS
ENTIRELY SURPRISED MYSELF, BUT--
[LAUGHS WEAKLY]
WELL, IF THERE'S
ANYTHING I CAN DO
TO MAKE THINGS
EASIER FOR YOU...
WELL...
I WOULD LIKE JEN
TO SPEND SOME TIME
WITH LEO'S CHILDREN IN ENGLAND.
THEY GOT REALLY CLOSE
WHEN THEY WERE IN BEIRUT.
WELL...
WHY DON'T YOU
BRING THEM OVER
AND STAY
UP AT THE LAKE HOUSE?
YOU KNOW
I CAN'T AFFORD THAT.
I CAN'T LET JEN GO BACK
TO EUROPE WITH YOU, SALLY.
WELL, IT'S NOT LIKE
I'M GONNA KIDNAP HER
AND TAKE HER BACK TO MOSCOW.
[DOOR SLAMS]
[LAUGHTER]
JEN: OH, WOW,
I MISSED YOU SO MUCH.
I'M SO GLAD TO SEE YOU.
SALLY:
OH, ME TOO, HONEY. ME, TOO.
JEN: IT'S SO WEIRD
TO THINK ABOUT ALL THE THINGS
THEY'RE SAYING ABOUT LEO.
SALLY: YEAH.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT
ANYTHING IS ANYMORE, HONEY.
I DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHO I MISS ANYMORE...
THAT WITTY, CHARMING MAN
WHO EXPRESSED HIS LOVE MORE
HONESTLY THAN ANYONE I EVER MET
OR THAT WITTY,
CHARMING CON ARTIST.
MOM...
YOU KNOW HOW MUCH
I LOVE DAD, RIGHT?
YEAH.
BUT THE ONLY REASON I HAVE
ANY IDEA OF WHAT LOVE REALLY IS
BETWEEN TWO ADULTS
IS BECAUSE I LIVED
WITH YOU AND LEO.
LEO'S VOICE:
DEAR SAL,
I KNOW WHAT YOU MUST
PROBABLY THINK OF ME NOW.
BUT I NEED YOU TO KNOW
THAT YOU HAVE ALL MY LOVE,
MORE THAN EVER.
I'M SURE THAT
THERE ARE MANY PEOPLE
WHO ARE SAYING
TERRIBLE THINGS ABOUT ME,
BUT THE TRUTH ISN'T ALWAYS
WHAT IT MIGHT SEEM TO BE.
I BEG OF YOU WITH ALL MY HEART
TO AT LEAST VISIT MOSCOW
AND HEAR MY SIDE OF THE STORY.
YOU'D BE FREE TO COME HERE
AND LEAVE AT ANY TIME.
JUST CALL THE RUSSIAN EMBASSY
IN LONDON
AND EVERYTHING CAN BE ARRANGED.
I CAN'T STOP THINKING ABOUT YOU
OR EVER GIVE UP HOPE
OF SEEING YOU AGAIN.
ALL MY LOVE, AS ALWAYS,
LEO.
DON'T WORRY.
I'LL BE FINE.
ARE YOU SURE?
YES. YES.
OK. WHATEVER I DECIDE,
I PROMISE I'LL BE BACK
FOR YOUR BIRTHDAY.
JUST DO
WHAT YOU NEED TO DO.
OH.
I LOVE YOU,
SWEETHEART.
LOVE YOU, TOO.
SO MUCH.
HAVE A SAFE FLIGHT.
OK.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
DADDY'S NOT VERY GOOD
AT COPING ON HIS OWN.
HE'S HOPING TO FIND A WAY
FOR YOU TO VISIT HIM
DURING YOUR
SCHOOL HOLIDAYS.
BUT I WANT TO LIVE IN MOSCOW
WITH HIM ALL THE TIME.
DON'T BE SILLY, OLIVER.
YOU KNOW YOU CAN'T.
SALLY:
IT'S NOT GONNA BE EASY,
BUT HE'S TRYING TO FIND A WAY
TO GET YOU YOUR VISAS.
I DON'T WANT TO GO TO RUSSIA!
LUCY:
IT'S A BLOODY DUMP!
I'M THE PERSON FROM
THE RUSSIAN EMBASSY
YOU SPOKE TO ON THE PHONE.
GOOD LUCK,
MRS. CAUFFIELD.
SO...
WHERE WILL YOU BE
THIS TIME TOMORROW,
MOSCOW OR MANHATTAN?
I DON'T KNOW.
PART OF ME IS SO MAD AT HIM,
I CAN'T EVEN SEE STRAIGHT.
AND THE OTHER PART?
WELL, YOU KNOW,
WITH LEO I NEVER TOOK THE PATH
OF LEAST RESISTANCE.
BUT THERE'S A PART OF ME
THAT FEELS LIKE
IF I DON'T AT LEAST SEE HIM,
I WON'T BE ABLE TO
GET ON WITH MY LIFE
WITH OR WITHOUT HIM.
[KNOCKING]
[WHISPERING]
SALLY!
OH, ANDY.
HELLO, CYNTHIA.
SALLY, I WAS JUST ON MY WAY
AROUND THE CORNER
TO AN EXHIBITION WITH MY WIFE.
KNOWING YOUR INTEREST IN ART,
I WAS WONDERING
IF YOU'D CARE TO COME ALONG.
MAN:
WOULD YOU EXCUSE ME?
CATHERINE.
ANDREW,
HOW LOVELY TO SEE YOU.
SALLY, THIS IS
SIR MICHAEL STRICKLAND.
MICHAEL,
SALLY CAUFFIELD.
OH, YES. I REMEMBER
YOUR HUSBAND AT CAMBRIDGE,
MANY MOONS AGO.
WHO WOULD'VE GUESSED,
EH?
DO HELP YOURSELF TO DRINKS,
AND I HOPE YOU'LL ENJOY
OUR LITTLE COLLECTION.
EXCUSE ME.
OH, LADY MARKHAM'S WAVING AT ME.
I'LL BE BACK IN A TICK.
ANDY:
YOU KNOW...
I'LL NEVER FORGET THE MOMENT
WHEN I FINALLY HAD TO ACCEPT
LEO WAS GUILTY.
IT WAS WHEN I WORKED OUT WHY
THE HUMPS ON THAT DAMN PHOTO
OF MOUNT ARARAT
WERE THE WRONG WAY AROUND.
LEO:
I FOUND HIM IN THE DESERT,
ALL ALONE
WITH NOBODY IN THE WORLD.
A DESERT RAT, EH?
THEY'RE VERY MISUNDERSTOOD
CREATURES, RATS.
SECOND ONLY
TO MAN'S BEST FRIEND
AS THE MOST LOYAL
AND RESPONSIVE OF PETS.
I'M GOING BACK TO LONDON
TONIGHT, OLD FRUIT.
REALLY?
THE YANKS HAVE HANDED
GOLITSYN OVER TO US.
I THOUGHT THE C.I.A.
COULD NEVER MAKE UP THEIR MIND
IF HE WAS A TRUE
K.G.B. DEFECTOR OR NOT.
OH, NO. HE'S PROVED
HE KNOWS HIS STUFF.
SOMETIMES
I CAN'T HELP WONDERING
IF THE METHODOLOGIES OF
AMERICAN DEMOCRACY AND COMMUNISM
AREN'T VIRTUALLY
INDISTINGUISHABLE.
PERSONALLY, I ALWAYS THOUGHT
COMMUNISM WAS RATHER LIKE ACNE.
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO
GROW OUT OF IT, AREN'T YOU?
I DON'T KNOW.
I NEVER HAD ACNE.
[LAUGHS]
AH,
THE OLD TWO-BACKED BEAST.
YES, I TOOK THAT WHEN
I WAS STATIONED IN ISTANBUL.
I THOUGHT THOSE OLD
TOURISTY SHOTS
THAT WE USED TO STICK IN OUR
GEOGRAPHY BOOKS BACK AT SCHOOL
HAD THE SMALL HUMP
ON THE RIGHT.
I EXPECT THE PRINT WAS MADE
WITH THE NEGATIVE REVERSED.
SMART FELLOW.
GOLITSYN HAS THE DIRT ON EVERY
SOVIET SPY IN THE WEST, LEO.
HE'S TOLD US YOUR ENTIRE HISTORY
IN THE K.G.B.
I'M AFRAID WHAT YOU'VE BEEN TOLD
HAS NOTHING TO DO WITH REALITY.
WE CAN MAKE A DEAL
IF YOU RETURN TO LONDON
AND TELL US EVERYTHING.
I TOLD YOU EVERYTHING I KNOW
THE LAST TIME I WENT
THROUGH THIS CHARADE, ANDY.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO GO
AND ROT IN MOSCOW
FOR THE REST OF YOUR LIFE,
LIKE THE OTHERS.
THEY'RE OFFERING
TOTAL IMMUNITY.
THINK ABOUT IT
FOR A FEW DAYS.
ANDY: THE PHOTOGRAPH
HAD THE HUMPS BACKWARDS.
IT WAS TAKEN FROM
THE RUSSIAN SIDE OF THE BORDER.
INTELLIGENCE IS JUST
A GAME YOU ALL PLAY
LIKE OVERGROWN SCHOOLBOYS,
ISN'T IT?
YOU HAVE TO MAKE SOMEONE
THE ENEMY,
OTHERWISE THEY'D CALL YOU
ALL IN OFF THE PLAYGROUND.
IN ANY GAME,
THERE ARE ALWAYS CERTAIN RULES.
YOU LET HIM ESCAPE, DIDN'T YOU?
BECAUSE HE WAS YOUR BEST FRIEND,
OR BECAUSE MI6 WAS TOO
EMBARRASSED TO BRING HIM BACK?
WHAT RULES OF THE GAME
ARE WE TALKING ABOUT NOW, ANDY?
THEY WANTED HIM BACK
AT ANY PRICE.
IT MAY END UP COSTING ME
MY CAREER,
BUT IF LEO HAD RETURNED
AND TESTIFIED,
I COULDN'T HAVE REGARDED HIM
AS ANYTHING OTHER THAN
A DEVIOUS OPPORTUNIST.
HIS CHOICE...
HIS CHOICE TO DEFECT
AT LEAST SHOWED THAT HIS FAITH
IN COMMUNISM WAS UNERRING.
YOU AND I MAY REGARD THAT
AS HONORABLE
OR JUST BLOODY FOOLISH.
BUT EITHER WAY,
IT'S SOMETHING I,
AND I SUSPECT HE, TOO,
CAN LIVE WITH.
CYNTHIA:
OH, GOD!
[MAN COUGHING]
MAN: WELCOME TO THE SOVIET
UNION, MRS. CAUFFIELD.
[DISTANT SHOUTING]
LEO:
IT MAY NOT BE THE RITZ,
BUT IT'S MORE THAN COMFORTABLE.
HAVE A WONDERFUL EVENING.
THANK YOU, ALEKSI.
I KNOW IT TOOK A LOT OF COURAGE
FOR YOU TO COME HERE, SAL.
EVEN THOUGH I...
THOUGH I WANTED YOU TO COME
MORE THAN ANYTHING...
I WOULD HAVE UNDERSTOOD
IF YOU HADN'T.
SO THIS IS WHAT YOU
ABANDONED YOUR FAMILY FOR?
I WASN'T INTENDING TO
LEAVE YOU PERMANENTLY, SAL.
WELL, YOU WEREN'T
INTENDING TO COME BACK.
AND YOU WON'T BE COMING BACK
ANYTIME SOON.
THAT SEEMS PRETTY PERMANENT
TO ME!
[TIRED LAUGH] YOU HAVE
EVERY RIGHT TO BE ANGRY.
WHAT HAPPENED WAS--
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA
HOW IT FEELS
TO FIND OUT THE PERSON
YOU LOVED WAS A SHADOW?
THAT EVERY WORD
OUT OF THEIR MOUTH WAS A LIE?
THAT HE USED YOU JUST LIKE
HE USED EVERYBODY ELSE?
IT MAY BE HARD TO BELIEVE, SAL,
BUT I WASN'T LYING TO YOU.
IT'S WHAT I DIDN'T TELL YOU
THAT I'M GUILTY OF.
A THOUSAND TIMES OVER!
I HAD TO KEEP THINGS FROM YOU,
FOR YOUR SAFETY
AND FOR THE CHILDREN.
DON'T GIVE ME THAT BULLSHIT!
IF YOU CARED ABOUT OUR SAFETY,
YOU WOULDN'T HAVE LEFT US THERE.
I DIDN'T PLAN TO, SAL.
THINGS DIDN'T HAPPEN
THE WAY YOU THINK.
UH!
GOLITSYN HAS THE DIRT ON EVERY
SOVIET SPY IN THE WEST, LEO.
ANDY:
WE CAN MAKE A DEAL.
IF YOU RETURN TO LONDON
AND TELL US EVERYTHING.
ANDY'S VOICE:
THINK ABOUT IT FOR A FEW DAYS.
LEO: THEY HAVE GIVEN ME
A FEW DAYS TO MAKE UP MY MIND.
THAT'S IF THE C.I.A.
DON'T GET ME FIRST.
GOT A LIGHT?
DON'T WORRY.
I'LL WALK
PAST YOUR APARTMENT
EVERY THREE HOURS,
EACH DAY.
IF YOU SEE ME
CARRYING A NEWSPAPER,
I ONLY WANT TO TALK TO YOU.
IF I'M CARRYING A BOOK
IT MEANS EVERYTHING IS PREPARED
FOR YOUR DEPARTURE.
MY DEPARTURE?
WE CANNOT ALLOW YOU
TO GO BACK TO LONDON
UNDER ANY CIRCUMSTANCES.
[SIGHS]
JEN:
OH, GOOD.
OOH!
LEO:
I NEVER THOUGHT I'D SEE THE DAY
WHEN BOTH MY DAUGHTER
AND MY STEPDAUGHTER
ENDED UP IN JAIL.
WHAT DID I DO WRONG, EH?
LUCY:
I'M JUST VISITING, DADDY.
SALLY: HEY! DON'T FORGET
YOUR COAT AND UMBRELLA.
THEY'RE FORECASTING RAIN LATER.
LEO!
YES, BUT YOU SAID IT WOULD
ONLY TAKE A COUPLE OF DAYS.
YOU KNOW,
I DO NEED SOME NOTICE.
EVERYTHING IS READY NOW.
THEY ARE WAITING FOR US
TO LEAVE.
WHAT?
BUT YOU DON'T HAVE
A BOOK IN YOUR HAND.
OH, MY GOD.
I'M SO SORRY.
I FORGOT ALL ABOUT IT.
I CAN'T JUST LEAVE NOW,
YOU KNOW.
I HAVE TO MAKE ARRANGEMENTS.
I HAVE TO MAKE SURE
MY FAMILY IS LOOKED AFTER.
I HAVE TO SAY GOODBYE.
I HAVE TO MAKE SURE
THEY'RE ALL RIGHT.
YOU CAN TELEPHONE THEM.
TELL THEM
YOU'LL BE BACK LATE.
I MEAN, YOU MUST HAVE KNOWN
WHEN YOU FIRST GOT INTO IT.
HOW COULD YOU POSSIBLY THINK
IT WOULD END HAPPILY EVER AFTER?
I ALWAYS KNEW
THE DAY MIGHT COME.
AND I WAS DESPERATELY WORRIED
ABOUT THE CHILDREN.
I ALWAYS BELIEVED
I COULD SURVIVE LONG ENOUGH
FOR THEM TO GROW UP,
BECOME INDEPENDENT.
WHAT CHANGED EVERYTHING...
WAS FALLING IN LOVE.
I UNDERSTAND WHY YOU THINK
I DECEIVED YOU,
BUT THE TRUTH IS YOU WERE
THE ONLY PART OF MY LIFE
WHERE THERE WAS
NO PRETENDING.
EVERYTHING I SAID, I MEANT...
FROM THE BOTTOM OF MY HEART.
THEY SAID I COULD GET A FLIGHT
BACK TO LONDON OR THE STATES
AS EARLY AS TOMORROW MORNING
IF I WANT.
I KNOW YOU CAN PROBABLY
NEVER FORGIVE ME...
BUT I WANT YOU TO KNOW
I LOVE YOU MUCH MORE NOW
THAN I EVER DID.
LEO: ANGUS WAS THE LIFE AND SOUL
OF EVERY PARTY IN LONDON
BUT POOR OLD AGENT VIRGIL HAS
NEVER BEEN ABLE TO FIT IN HERE.
LEO:
ANGUS...
A.K.A. VIRGIL.
CAUFFIELD.
YOU OLD BUGGER.
THIS IS MY WIFE, SALLY.
SALLY.
I'M AFRAID I HAVEN'T BEEN
AS GOOD A FRIEND TO LEO
AS HE'S BEEN TO ME, SALLY.
OH, FOR HEAVEN'S SAKE, ANGUS.
[COUGHS]
I... I SUSPECT THE KREMLIN
WILL BE SOMEWHAT RELIEVED
TO GET RID OF ME.
WE'VE HAD A BIT OF A FALLING OUT
SINCE I GOT DRUNK AT ONE OF
THEIR DREARY COCKTAIL PARTIES
AND URINATED IN A FIREPLACE.
IT WAS VERY BAD BEHAVIOR.
BUT OF COURSE IT WAS,
OLD LOVE.
[SPEAKING RUSSIAN]
ANGUS PETHERBRIDGE
WAS AN INTELLIGENT,
GIFTED AND COURAGEOUS MAN,
WHO SACRIFICED HIS LIFE
TO THE CAUSE
OF MAKING A BETTER WORLD.
[PLAYING SOFTLY]
HIS ASHES ARE
BEING BURIED IN ENGLAND.
THAT'S WHAT HE WANTED.
MR. CAUFFIELD:
I MISS ENGLAND...
BUT NOT THE ENGLISH.
IT'S ACUTELY PAINFUL TO SEE
THE COUNTRY OF ONE'S BIRTH
CONTROLLED BY A SUCCESSION
OF PETTY ADMINISTRATIONS
ALL INTENT IN DESTROYING
WHAT THE EMPIRE EVER STOOD FOR.
I SUPPOSE WE ALL WANT A BETTER
WORLD TO LIVE IN, FATHER.
GOOD YOU LEFT
THE FOREIGN SERVICE
WHEN YOU DID, LEO.
JUST LIKE ME.
SAME AGE, HUH?
I COULDN'T GO ON
WORKING FOR THAT LOT.
THEY'RE ALL THE SAME LOAD
OF WANKERS, THE LOT OF THEM!
I'LL TRY
NOT TO LET YOU DOWN, FATHER.
I DIDN'T RAISE YOU TO PEN
HALF-BAKED GOVERNMENT PROPAGANDA
WITH THE TIMES, LEO.
HOW ARE YOU FEELING?
FUCKING BORED.
[AIRPLANE PASSING]
MAGNIFICENT,
ISN'T IT?
WE DIDN'T NEED THE V.I.P.
TREATMENT, GEORGE.
I SPENT
MY WHOLE BLOODY LIFE
FIGHTING AGAINST
THE NOTION OF PRIVILEGE,
AND WHERE AM I?
I TELL YOU WHAT.
I CAN LIVE WITHOUT
THE ROYAL FAMILY
AND THE SNOBBERY
IN THE SUBURBS,
BUT AFTER 12 YEARS
I REALLY MISS ENGLISH SAUSAGES.
OXFORD THICK-CUT MARMALADE AND
LEA AND PERRIN'S SAUCE FOR ME.
SALLY? THERE ARE SOME
WONDERFUL NEW SHOPS IN MOSCOW.
I'LL SHOW YOU AROUND
IF YOU LIKE.
GEORGE: MAYBE SALLY'S
NOT AS INTERESTED IN SHOPPING
AS YOU ARE, LESLIE.
ALL WOMEN ARE INTERESTED
IN SHOPPING, GEORGE.
LET'S GO ONE AFTERNOON
NEXT WEEK,
WHEN THE MEN
ARE WORKING LATE,
AND THEN WE COULD HAVE
AN EARLY DINNER TOGETHER.
THAT WOULD BE NICE.
OK.
SALLY: WHERE ARE YOU FROM
IN THE STATES, LESLIE?
LESLIE:
CHICAGO.
I CAN'T UNDERSTAND WHY ANYONE
WOULD WANT TO
LIVE IN AMERICA THESE DAYS.
MAYBE THAT'S BECAUSE
YOU DON'T HAVE A CHOICE, GEORGE.
IN A WAY...
YOU HAVE TO ADMIRE
WHAT OUR HUSBANDS HAVE DONE,
THOUGH.
THEY REALLY BELIEVED IN IT,
THE BRITISH ONES.
AND THEY NEVER GOT PAID A CENT.
CAN YOU IMAGINE
AN AMERICAN SPY EVER DOING THAT?
THEY FOLLOW YOU EVERYWHERE.
CAN I ASK YOU SOMETHING,
SALLY?
WHAT'S LEO LIKE IN BED?
GEORGE DOESN'T SEEM INTERESTED
IN ANYTHING THESE DAYS.
AND I JUST ALWAYS--
WELL, I JUST IMAGINED THAT
LEO WOULD BE A TERRIFIC LOVER.
[SALLY SPEAKING RUSSIAN]
I'M LOOKING FOR THE MUSEUM
AND ART GALLERY?
[SPEAKING RUSSIAN]
UH, THE ART GALLERY?
WHY IS IT SO DIFFICULT
TO DO ANYTHING HERE?
WELL, WHAT DO YOU NEED?
I MEAN,
ALEKSI IS ALWAYS AVAILABLE
TO HELP YOU, DARLING.
CHRIST ALMIGHTY, LEO,
IS THIS WHAT YOU
SACRIFICED EVERYTHING FOR?
HOW CAN YOU LIVE LIKE THIS?
PEOPLE WATCHING YOU
ALL THE TIME.
WONDERING WHAT YOU CAN SAY
IN YOUR OWN HOME.
WHAT, ARE YOU WAITING
FOR IT TO BE YOUR TURN
TO HAVE YOUR ASHES
SENT BACK TO ENGLAND?
WE DON'T ALL HAVE
YOUR DEDICATION, LEO.
THIS IS NOT MY WORLD.
I'M GOING TO LOSE YOU,
AREN'T I?
[SPEAKING RUSSIAN]
THIS IS MY FAVORITE SPEECH
IN SHAKESPEARE.
LEO: "COME,
LET'S AWAY TO PRISON:
"WE TWO ALONE WILL SING
LIKE BIRDS I'THE CAGE:
"AND WHEN THOU
DOST ASK ME BLESSING,
"I'LL KNEEL DOWN,
AND ASK OF THEE FORGIVENESS:
"SO WE'LL LIVE, AND PRAY,
"AND SING, AND TELL OLD TALES,
"AND LAUGH AT
GILDED BUTTERFLIES."
[RUSSIAN CONTINUES
IN BACKGROUND]
YOU MUST FEEL AT LIBERTY TO SAY
ANYTHING, SALLY, GOOD OR BAD,
ABOUT WHAT YOU'VE SEEN HERE.
THE ONLY THING
WE DON'T WANT THEM TO KNOW
IS LEO'S RUSSIAN NAME
OR WHERE HE LIVES.
IT WOULD PUT HIS LIFE IN DANGER.
ANGUS LEFT ME SOME MONEY
IN HIS WILL.
WOULD YOU...
WOULD YOU GIVE IT
TO THE CHILDREN FOR ME?
HERE.
TELL THEM...
TELL THEM I LOVE THEM
VERY MUCH, AND...
I'M SORRY.
MAN:
REMAIN IN YOUR SEATS.
MRS. CAUFFIELD,
PLEASE COME WITH ME.
I HAVE BEEN TRAVELING
FOR 18 HOURS!
I'VE BEEN WAITING IN HERE
FOR ANOTHER TWO!
WOULD YOU MIND TELLING ME
WHAT THIS IS ALL ABOUT?
MAY I HAVE YOUR
RIGHT FOREFINGER, PLEASE?
WHAT?
IF YOU'RE COOPERATIVE,
YOU'LL BE ABLE TO
LEAVE HERE A LOT FASTER.
MRS. CAUFFIELD,
I'VE BEEN ADVISED BY
THE SECRETARY OF STATE
TO INFORM YOU THAT
IN VIEW OF YOUR MARRIAGE
TO LEO A. CAUFFIELD
AND YOUR RECENT ACTIVITIES
IN THE SOVIET UNION
AGAINST THE INTERESTS
OF THE U.S. GOVERNMENT,
YOUR PASSPORT
IS BEING WITHDRAWN.
MY ACTIVITIES AGAINST
THE U.S. GOVERNMENT?
I JUST WENT TO VISIT
MY GODDAMN HUSBAND!
IF YOU DECIDE
TO LEAVE THE ADDRESS
YOU'RE STAYING AT
IN THE U.S. FOR ANY REASON,
YOU MUST LET US KNOW.
FAILURE TO DO SO
MAY RESULT IN THE ISSUE
OF A WARRANT FOR YOUR ARREST.
WHAT?
WELCOME TO THE U.S.A.
I DON'T KNOW WHY THEY ALL
HAVE TO BE SO DAMN PARANOID
ALL THE TIME.
DAD SAYS THE C.I.A.
AND BRITISH SECRET SERVICE
HAVE PRETTY MUCH
HAD TO DISMANTLE
THEIR ENTIRE OPERATIONS
AND START OVER 'CAUSE OF LEO.
WELL, THERE IS THAT.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
I'M LAUGHING ABOUT THIS.
IT'S NOT FUNNY.
THANKS FOR A GREAT BIRTHDAY,
MOM.
YOU ARE SO WELCOME, HONEY.
FAY!
SALLY,
I THOUGHT YOU WERE--
LISTEN, HONEY,
I'D LOVE TO TALK
BUT WE'RE IN A TERRIBLE RUSH.
[CHUCKLES]
MRS. CAUFFIELD.
ART YALLOP, C.I.A.
THIS IS KEN RIEDLER.
MRS. CAUFFIELD.
RIEDLER: I KNOW THIS IS
A VERY INAPPROPRIATE TIME,
BUT I WAS WONDERING IF YOU
COULD SPARE US A FEW MINUTES.
WELL, WE'D LOVE
TO TALK TO YOU
ABOUT YOUR EXPERIENCES
IN THE SOVIET UNION.
WILL IT HELP ME
GET MY PASSPORT BACK?
WOULDN'T HURT.
FINE.
THIS WAY.
[POLICE SIREN BLARING]
EXCUSE OUR ACCOMMODATION.
WE ASKED THE AGENCY
TO PUT US UP AT THE PLAZA,
BUT THEY WOULDN'T GO FOR IT.
[SHORT LAUGH]
SMOKE?
NO, THANKS.
I DO BELIEVE YOUR HUSBAND
WILL ONE DAY BE REGARDED
AS THE MOST SUCCESSFUL SPY
OF THIS CENTURY.
I DIDN'T COME HERE
TO DISCUSS THAT.
WOULD YOU SAY THAT
YOU WERE GENERALLY WELL TREATED
BY THE RUSSIAN AUTHORITIES?
YES. IN FACT,
BETTER THAN...
I WAS TREATED BY
THE AMERICAN AUTHORITIES
WHEN I GOT BACK HERE.
HMM. CAN YOU TELL US
WHERE YOU STAYED?
NO.
[WHISPERING]
I UNDERSTAND.
EXCUSE ME A MOMENT,
MRS. CAUFFIELD.
TAKE A LOOK AT THOSE.
GO AHEAD.
THEY'RE RECENT
INTELLIGENCE PHOTOGRAPHS
OF LOCATIONS IN THE SOVIET UNION
CARRYING ATOMIC WEAPONRY.
WHAT'S THAT GOT TO DO WITH ME?
WELL, IT WASN'T LONG AGO
THAT WE WERE
THE ONLY NATION ON EARTH
THAT HELD THE SECRET
TO ATOMIC WARFARE.
NOW, HOW DID THE RUSSIANS
GET AHOLD OF IT?
YOU HAVE NO RIGHT
TO KEEP ME HERE.
WE DON'T NEED TO GET THE TRUTH
BY VOLUNTARY MEANS ANYMORE.
THE ADVANCES OF MEDICAL SCIENCE
MADE OUR JOB A WHOLE LOT EASIER.
DO YOU REMEMBER THE ROSENBERGS,
MRS. CAUFFIELD?
[SOBS]
IT WAS OFTEN CLAIMED
THAT ETHEL ROSENBERG
KNEW NOTHING OF WHAT
HER HUSBAND WAS DOING.
BUT WE PROVED OTHERWISE.
NOW, JUST TELL US
WHERE HE IS IN MOSCOW
AND NO HARM WILL COME
TO YOU OR YOUR DAUGHTER.
HER NAME'S JEN, RIGHT?
NO!
OW!
ALL RIGHT!
THAT'S IT!
BITCH.
PIG.
MRS. CAUFFIELD.
YOU'RE FREE TO GO.
MOM!
YOUR PASSPORT'S HERE!
CYNTHIA:
LUCY'S BEEN VERY WITHDRAWN
AND OLIVER GOT INTO A FIGHT
WITH A BOY AT SCHOOL
WHO TOLD HIM
HIS FATHER WAS A TRAITOR
AND DESERVED TO BE HANGED.
I THINK THEY NEED
A PARENT WHO'S AROUND,
SOMEONE THEY CAN COUNT ON.
OH, I'M SORRY.
THAT WAS UNFAIR OF ME.
NO.
BELIEVE ME,
I AGREE WITH YOU.
IF I HAD MY WAY,
THEY'D HAVE TWO PARENTS.
I KNOW.
SALLY!
SALLY! I DIDN'T REALIZE
YOU WERE IN LONDON.
I'D HEARD
YOU'D GONE BACK TO AMERICA.
I HAVE A PROPOSAL.
YES. YES, OF COURSE,
BUT SHALL WE--
I WANNA BRING HIM BACK.
COME WITH ME.
SALLY:
WHERE'S LEO?
ALEKSI:
IN THE CAR.
HE HAS A TOUCH OF THE FLU.
[COUGHS]
TEA?
I HAVE A PRESENT FOR YOU.
OH, SPLENDID.
WE CAN DRINK TO YOUR
MOST UNEXPECTED RETURN.
LEO, WHAT DID YOU DO?
OH...
A DISAGREEMENT
WITH A GLASS DOOR
AFTER A COUPLE DRINKS.
WELL, OTHER THAN
GETTING SICK
AND WALKING THROUGH
GLASS DOORS,
WHAT ELSE
HAVE YOU BEEN DOING?
I HAVE A NEW OFFICE
AND A SECRETARY.
AND PRETTY SOON,
THEY'RE GONNA GIVE ME
SOMETHING REALLY IMPORTANT
TO DO.
MMM!
I CAN ARRANGE A MEETING
WITH ANDREW DARCY.
THEY'D GET YOU OUT
AND FORGET ABOUT EVERYTHING
IF YOU'D JUST
COOPERATE WITH THEM.
BUT, SALLY, DARLING,
THE RISKS INVOLVED WOULD
BE ENORMOUS. I DON'T EVEN--
HASN'T EVERYTHING
WE'VE EVER DONE BEEN A RISK?
GOD!
"WE DO NOT HAVE TO BE IMPRISONED
"BY THE CHOICES
WE'VE MADE IN OUR PAST."
THE KIDS NEED YOU, LEO.
I NEED YOU.
I NEED YOU TOO, SAL.
I WAS NEVER HAPPIER
THAN WHEN WE WERE IN BEIRUT.
IT COULD BE LIKE THAT AGAIN.
WE DON'T HAVE TO BE SEPARATED
FOR THE REST OF OUR LIVES.
I NEED TIME TO SORT
SOME LOOSE ENDS OUT.
HOW MUCH?
A WEEK.
TEN DAYS.
WHATEVER YOU DO,
DON'T SAY A WORD TO LESLIE.
I HADN'T INTENDED TO.
BY THE WAY,
SHE AND GEORGE HAVE SEPARATED.
LESLIE!
SALLY, YOU DON'T KNOW
HOW HAPPY I AM
TO HAVE SOMEONE
TO GO SHOPPING WITH.
LEO.
AND I'VE GOT TICKETS FOR
TRAVIATA AT THE END OF JUNE.
I HOPE YOU CAN BOTH COME.
SPLENDID.
ANYONE FOR DRINKS?
SALLY:
I CAN'T IMAGINE
THIS IS HOW LENIN THOUGHT
COMMUNISM WOULD TURN OUT.
I CAN'T IMAGINE
THIS IS HOW ANYONE
THOUGHT COMMUNISM
WOULD TURN OUT.
YOU KNOW, WHEN I WAS
AT CAMBRIDGE IN THE '30s,
WE HAD TWO ALTERNATIVES:
FASCISM AND SOCIALISM.
THERE IS A DIFFERENCE
BETWEEN
BECOMING A SOCIALIST
OR A COMMUNIST,
AND GOING TO WORK FOR
THE RUSSIAN SECRET SERVICE.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
BUT A LOT OF US,
ADMITTEDLY FROM PRIVILEGED
AND EDUCATED BACKGROUNDS,
WERE SICK AND TIRED
OF OUR GENERATION
GOING ON ABOUT
CHANGING THE WORLD
AND DOING NOTHING ABOUT IT.
SO WHEN I WAS ASKED
TO JOIN A CELL,
I THOUGHT I'D MAKE
MORE OF A DIFFERENCE THAN BY--
I DON'T WHAT, CHANGING MY ACCENT
AND MARCHING
WITH THE TRADE UNIONS
OR GOING OFF TO DIE
IN THE SPANISH CIVIL WAR.
BUT YOU MUST FEEL DIFFERENTLY
ABOUT COMMUNISM TODAY
THAN YOU DID BACK THEN.
THE TROUBLE IS,
THE WRONG PEOPLE
ARE TRYING TO IMPLEMENT
THE RIGHT DOCTRINES.
BUT, TO ME, IT'S ALWAYS
BEEN LIKE A GOOD MARRIAGE.
MY COMMITMENT WAS NEVER
BASED ON ROMANCE...
PASSION ALONE.
SO WHEN THE FIRST FLUSHES OF
EXCITEMENT AND FRENZY WERE OVER,
I STILL ALWAYS BELIEVED IN
THE BASIC PREMISE OF MARXISM.
I KNOW IT HASN'T TURNED OUT
THE WAY IT WAS SUPPOSED TO,
BUT I STILL BELIEVE IT CAN, SAL.
I REALLY DO.
AFTER YOU WENT BACK
TO THE STATES,
HE WAS IN TERRIBLE SHAPE.
WORSE THAN YOU CAN IMAGINE.
I'VE NEVER SEEN
LONELINESS LIKE THAT IN A MAN.
HE WAS RESIGNED
TO LOSING YOU, SALLY,
AND HE TRIED TO BLOT OUT
THE PAIN ANY WAY HE COULD.
YEAH, WELL,
I'M BACK NOW.
I THOUGHT WE WERE
STAYING HOME TODAY.
SOMETHING CAME UP AT WORK.
I WAS GONNA
MAKE US SOME LUNCH.
NO, I'LL PROBABLY BE BACK
A BIT LATE.
[WHISPERING]
LEO!
YOU SAID IT WOULD BE A FEW DAYS.
IT'S BEEN MORE THAN A MONTH NOW.
YEAH, I'VE STILL GOT
SOME UNFINISHED BUSINESS.
IT'S TAKING A LONGER
THAN I THOUGHT.
YEAH, WELL... HAVE YOU
CONTACTED DARCY'S MAN YET?
I'LL TRY TODAY.
[COUGHS]
[DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES]
[LEO COUGHS]
I'M SORRY I'M LATE.
I WAS BUSY.
DID YOU CONTACT HIM?
SALLY...
SALLY, YOU KNOW,
IT ISN'T QUITE AS EASY
AS YOU THINK.
OH?
THIS IS BIGGER
THAN JUST YOU AND ME.
THIS IS ABOUT MY LIFE'S WORK!
REALLY?
WHY DON'T YOU TELL ME SOMETHING.
IN ALL THESE YEARS
THAT WE'VE BEEN TOGETHER
WHICH IS MORE IMPORTANT TO YOU,
ME OR THE COMMUNIST PARTY?
HUH? HUH?
NO! WAIT!
GET OFF ME!
HUH?
ANSWER ME!
[LEO COUGHS]
SALLY: OH!
I HATE YOU!
[LEO COUGHS]
LEO!
LEO? LEO?
YOUR HUSBAND
HAS VERY SEVERE PNEUMONIA.
WE HAVE DONE
EVERYTHING THAT WE CAN
BUT THE NEXT 48 HOURS
WILL BE CRITICAL.
[MAN SPEAKING RUSSIAN
OVER RADIO]
BROUGHT YOU
SOME NEWSPAPERS.
I HAD SOME VISITORS FROM
THE GOVERNMENT THIS MORNING.
IT APPEARS I'VE BEEN AWARDED
THE ORDER OF THE RED BANNER.
[CHUCKLES]
IT'S THE HIGHEST THING
THEY'VE GOT--
I MEAN, IT'S THE EQUIVALENT
OF A KNIGHTHOOD.
YOU KNOW,
YOU'VE GOTTA GIVE IT UP, LEO.
IT'S KILLING YOU.
YOU DIDN'T CHOOSE THIS LIFE,
SAL.
I REALIZE IT'S NOT FAIR TO YOU.
I COMPLETELY UNDERSTAND IF--
I DON'T WANNA
LEAVE YOU, LEO.
BUT IF YOU WANNA BE WITH ME,
YOU BETTER MAKE UP
YOUR GODDAMN MIND!
[MAN WHISPERING]
A DACHA IN KARELIA
HAS BEEN BOOKED
IN YOUR RUSSIAN NAME
FOR A WEEK
STARTING ON SATURDAY.
YOU WILL TAKE THE AFTERNOON
TRAIN TO LENINGRAD ON FRIDAY.
YOUR WIFE WILL TAKE THE FLIGHT
TO LONDON.
WHEN YOU GET TO LENINGRAD,
YOU'LL MISS YOUR CONNECTION.
IN YOUR COPY OF THE TIMES
TOMORROW,
THERE WILL BE A CODED MESSAGE
IN THE OBITUARIES
WITH INSTRUCTIONS HOW TO
GET TO VASILEVSKY ISLAND
AND BOARD A FISHING TRAWLER
FOR FINLAND.
GOOD LUCK.
[SHIVERING]
HELP!
HEY, THERE.
THERE, THERE.
LEO: I'LL HAVE TO ATTEND
A MEETING AT THE KREMLIN
BEFORE I GO TO LENINGRAD.
[WHISPERING]
IT WAS ARRANGED WEEKS AGO, SAL.
[IN NORMAL VOICE]
LET'S MEET AT OUR FAVORITE SPOT,
AND IF OLGA'S THERE
I'LL BUY YOU AN ICE CREAM...
[DOOR BELL BUZZING]
...BEFORE YOU GO TO THE AIRPORT
AND I GO TO THE STATION.
IT'S A BEAUTIFUL MORNING.
I'M SORRY YOU HAVE TO
RETURN HOME SO SOON,
BUT I HOPE
WE'LL SEE YOU AGAIN
AND THAT LEO WILL BE
COMPLETELY HEALTHY BY THAT TIME.
ALEKSI.
DO THEY KNOW?
IT DOESN'T MATTER
WHEN THEY FIND OUT, SAL.
HERE, FINLAND, LONDON.
K.G.B. HAVE A SAYING...
"ANY FOOL CAN COMMIT A MURDER
"BUT IT TAKES A REAL ARTIST
TO STAGE A NATURAL DEATH."
THEY'VE ALREADY
KILLED YOU, LEO.
WHAT KIND OF LIFE
WOULD IT BE, ANYWAY?
I'D STILL BE THE PARIAH
WHO DEFECTED TO MOSCOW
AND YOU'D BE THE WIFE
OF A RUSSIAN SPY,
WHO CHANGED HIS MIND
WHEN IT SUITED HIM.
I'M GETTING
ON THAT FLIGHT, LEO.
AND I'M NOT COMING BACK
TO MOSCOW.
WE CAN STILL BE TOGETHER.
YOU KNOW WHAT I WANT, LEO,
AND IT'S NOT ABOUT THAT ANYMORE.
I MADE A DECISION
BEFORE I CAME BACK HERE
AND I'M KEEPING
OUR FAMILY TOGETHER.
IF YOU EVER DECIDE
THAT'S WHAT YOU WANT...
YOU KNOW WHERE TO FIND US.
SAL...
DEEPER...
AND DEEPER.
LEO'S VOICE:
"COME, LET'S AWAY TO PRISON:
"WE TWO ALONE WILL SING
LIKE BIRDS I'THE CAGE:
"WHEN THOU DOST ASK ME
BLESSING,
"I'LL KNEEL DOWN,
AND ASK OF THEE FORGIVENESS:
"SO WE'LL LIVE, AND PRAY,
AND SING, AND TELL OLD TALES,
"AND LAUGH
AT GILDED BUTTERFLIES."
[DISTANT LAUGHTER]
GOTCHA!
CAPTIONS: BROADCAST TEXT
WWW.BROADCASTTEXT.COM