(dark electronic music)
(sentimental music)
♪ Love's an ocean ♪
♪ And each wave that whispers ♪
♪ Runs across the sand ♪
♪ So take my hand ♪
♪ Like the sun ♪
♪ You pour into my life ♪
♪ And fill the corners of my heart ♪
♪ With who you are ♪
♪ Suddenly ♪
♪ My love ♪
♪ I knew all at once ♪
♪ You were the one ♪
♪ Just for me ♪
♪ No more tears now ♪
♪ Joy's replaced the fears ♪
♪ And in this silent bliss ♪
♪ I find your kiss ♪
♪ And the shores will lead us evermore ♪
♪ Though footprints softly fade away ♪
♪ I'm here to stay ♪
♪ Suddenly ♪
♪ My love ♪
♪ I knew all at once ♪
♪ You were the one just for me ♪
- Was it all real?
Did it all happen so fast?
How did my life become my life?
I was living in a quiet
place at a quiet time
when out of the blue, heaven
and hell seemed to fall
upon me with such force.
That I was swept away on a tide of events.
(Mario sings in foreign language)
- So I'm not Pavarotti.
Hey, look, Rudyard Kipling.
There is an example of a poet warrior.
- Hans Christian Anderson.
- Hans Christian Anderson?
He wrote fairytales.
- You are so easy to tease.
- Oh, you're flirting
with me again, aren't you?
Senselessly flirting. You
are right, though, you know.
A man can be warrior and a poet.
He can be strong.
Yet sensitive at heart.
Take me for example.
- Mario, you are lovable.
- Lovable?
What does that mean? I'm
a wuss, a wimp, a weenie?
- You know how I feel about you.
- Yeah. Like a friend.
You know, one day you will realize
how you really feel about me.
I'm the one who will always be here
when all those so-called poet
warriors have come and gone.
- So what, are you going to propose again?
- Oh, speak again bright
angel for thou art as glorious
in my head as a winged
messenger of heaven.
Say yes and get it over with.
- Get it over with.
Oh, so that's how you see commitment
and spending the rest of
your life with someone?
Getting it over with.
(hiphop music)
♪ It's a Friday night ♪
♪ As I steps in the club ♪
♪ Looking at the honeys ♪
♪ As they show me love ♪
♪ It's time to get my groove on ♪
♪ And it's all the way live ♪
♪ I hit the dance floor ♪
(Joe knocks)
- Just a minute.
- Miss Antasio?
- Oh, Mr. Kirkman, I'm so glad you came.
Thank you.
Now see. I told you how bad it was.
And I called him three times.
And no one has come.
- And that's it?
You call three times and
you and your neighbors
just continue to let this sewer grow?
- But he's a slumlord.
I mean, look at this
place. It is his fault.
- No, Miss Antasio.
Rigdon didn't haul this
trash in here to fester.
You and your neighbors
did that to yourselves.
You're as much the problem as he is.
- What are we supposed to do?
- Clean the trash and filth
from your halls, Miss Antasio.
Then you call me. I'll make
damn sure Rigdon does his part.
But don't call me when
you're the co-creators
of your own horrible living conditions.
Please, Miss Antasio, get
this place cleaned up.
I'll take care of Rigdon.
Okay? Okay, Miss Antasio?
- Okay.
- Thank you.
- Today.
- Okay.
- Ladies and gentlemen, let's get started.
(stately music)
We don't care about third
world government policy.
We make policy.
We, money, capitalism, make
the only policy that counts.
Now, Rita.
- Yes, sir?
I want you to take the corporate jet
and a suitcase full of cash
and fly down to San Duarte
and tell Colonel Delgado
to have a nice vacation
in The Bahamas.
Something on your mind?
- I have my concerns, sir.
- Well, let me hear them.
- You know, Agricultural
Department Secretary Battis
recently met with all the union
leaders from South America
on his trip.
- And this concerns you.
- Yes, sir, it does.
- It's your job to stop errand boys
from getting in the way of commerce.
- Do I do what I have to do
in order to keep them from
asking any more questions?
(somber music)
Are there any particular rules, sir?
- Yes. Mine.
- [Linda] Hey MW.
I've got it. Yes, I've got it.
I'm going to nail his slimey
butt to a stone cross.
- [Man] Sharon, this is your boss.
I'm on my way to meet Linda
at the Sheraton in San Pedro.
Forward all my messages there.
- Okay. Thank you.
- Good morning.
- Hi. How are you?
Thank you.
Hey, Mr. Newspaper man. You
looking for a hot story?
- Oh my goodness. Linda.
- You are still the best
looking man I never seduced.
- What are you doing here?
- Oh.
Just a little vacation time
that I thoroughly deserved.
- Linda, this is Joe you're
talking to, okay, come on.
You're the one who told me,
LA is the only place in the world
where you can have a good time
without enjoying yourself.
- Did I say that?
- Yes, you did.
It's a story, right? Something big.
- And I'm not telling you
a damn thing about it.
- That's okay. That's fine.
This is my place now. I
just want to know one thing?
- What?
- Why ain't you ever seduced me?
- Because you were a pup back
then and I like wolfhounds.
Besides, I was too busy making you
the second best investigative
reporter on this planet.
- And that you did.
- Yes, I did.
Mmm, thank you. I did a good job. (kisses)
So you're taking me out to lunch?
- Absolutely.
- Okay.
- I need an hour. Can you give me an hour?
- Yeah, I can give you an hour, where?
- Lighthouse.
- You can afford it now?
- The Lighthouse, one hour.
- In an hour. See ya.
- Mel Rigdon, please.
- Joe Kirkman from the Washington Post
to the New Times just to
harass property owners.
- Is that what you call yourself,
Rigdon, a property owner?
You're nothing but a loud
noise, but I'ma prove to you
I'm even louder and starting today,
I'ma urinate on your
already tarnished image
in every issue until you bring every one
of your raggedy buildings up to code.
And if you think I'm playing
by the time I'm through
typesetting your ass,
you won't be able to breathe in this town.
I'm warning you, Rigdon.
(sinister music)
- Why didn't you tell me he was out here?
That guy's trouble for us.
(sinister music)
- Linda.
(Linda laughs nervously)
Okay. What's going on?
- Joe, if you hear from me?
(smooth music)
- I get it.
You come around my office,
acting all mysterious
as only Linda can do.
What exactly are you and that
old charm school reptile Marty
up to this time?
- Just forget I said
anything. Just forget it.
Come on. Let's talk
about the good old days.
- That's what I thought we came here for.
- Yeah, yeah.
You remember that time we
stuck it to Sir Anthony Mallon.
Ooh, darling.
(Joe laughs)
- How could I forget?
- There I was in my very short skirt
so that old sleazeball
could get a real good look.
Excuse me, the conversation is up here.
- But your legs are down there.
- You keep on looking down
there, your eyes'll go blind.
- I'll lose one eye.
(Linda laughs)
- Hey, you remember how
mad Marty introduced us
to that thief?
What was his name is?
- Robert Adam Chickle.
- Chicklets, that's it.
Chicklets, Robert Adam Chickle, ma'am.
You remember how Ward flew him to London
and you and I wined and dined Sir Anthony?
Chickle broke into his house
and stole his crown jewels.
- Everything.
- Yes, baby,
which gave us all the
proof we needed to prove.
- That Sir Anthony, Deputy
British Minister of Defense.
- Yes.
- And also pillar
of English society was actually spying
for Saddam Hussein during the Gulf War.
- Oh, was that good or what?
- Absolutely.
- Oh, we were a great team.
Yes, the best.
You were the best.
- No, you brought the best out of me.
- Oh, thank you. Thank you.
Wanna know something?
If I had been just 10 months
younger then, just 10 now,
I'd have seduced you.
- You wanna know something?
- What?
- You coulda been 10 months
older and still seduced me.
(Linda laughs)
- Mmm, I love you.
- I love you.
- You happy here? I mean, really happy?
- Yeah.
This is my home, Linda.
This community needs me.
I belong here.
(gentle music)
- You're right.
(sinister music)
- Who is he?
- We'll find out.
- You think he's in it?
- It doesn't matter.
He wants it cleaned, we'll clean it all.
- Oh, you're up early.
- I got to hand in this
dissertation outline this afternoon.
- You were restless last night.
- How would you know that?
- Because I checked on you when I came in
and I stole your purple
sweater to wear today.
'Cause I knew if I'd asked you today,
you'd be too grouchy to lend it to me.
(woman growls)
So how's that bookstore Romeo of yours?
- He proposed again.
- He proposed again. Oh
my God, I am shocked.
I'm so confused. I'm absolutely flummoxed.
Have you ever been flummoxed?
God, is that fun.
Especially if the flummoxer
is absolutely gorgeous.
- Hey girl.
- Hey Sondra. How are you?
- Good, how are you doing?
- So are you still
looking for Mr. Right, eh?
- That's me.
I know my Knight in shining
armor is out there somewhere.
Maybe a little chipped, a little rusted
but he's out there, unconditional
love or no love at all.
- Yeah. I know what you mean, girl.
Hi.
- How you doing?
(romantic music)
I happened to overhear you
guys' conversation, and,
you know, you really don't want much.
- (laughs) Well, I want it all.
- How about we start with dinner tonight?
Rex, eight o'clock.
- See you later, Sondra. Bye, Sondra.
- Okay, but go.
- Excuse me. Everything okay here?
- Yeah, yeah.
- Good.
- You know, I could be married
or engaged or something.
- No, not married or
engaged. Something maybe.
- And you don't care.
- No, I don't.
So you'll be there?
- Well, that's kind of fast.
I mean, who are you anyway?
- Joe, Joe Kirkman.
- Joe Kirkman.
Is that name supposed
to mean something to me?
Do you read that?
(romantic music)
- You're that Joe Kirkman? Oh yeah.
Yeah. I read that.
I like your work. It's very committed.
- Some people say I should be committed.
(Patrice laughs)
- Depends on your point
of view and you are?
- Patrice Summers.
- I like that.
- So Rex at eight, did you say?
- That's right. You'll be there.
- And if I'm not?
- I'll have to come back and get you.
Eight o'clock.
- Here's your change.
- Bring it to me tonight.
(romantic music)
- You okay?
- Yeah.
- Need to take a cold shower or something?
Why do you do that in front of me?
- Mario, my life is my own.
- You know how I feel about you.
Doesn't that mean anything to you?
- Do we have to do this every day, Mario?
- He's a love him and leave
him type if I ever saw one.
Yo, honey, I got to go off to war now
so I can make the whole world better.
You know what I mean?
A real man is the one who stays at home
and deals with whatever
it has to be dealt with.
With all the little things in your life.
Like your, your dreams,
your disappointments.
He's not the type.
- Cut it out. And I mean it.
- Okay.
- Mmm, mmm, mmm, Joe Kirkman, huh?
- Joe Kirkman.
- Ooh, I got a friend over at the Weekly
and she's telling me he is very tasty.
- In a word.
- Ooh, sparks?
- Roman candles.
- Look at you, finally
maybe your warrior poet.
Because Mario certainly isn't.
- Mario is a very decent kind man.
- But.
- Hush just.
- Okay, all right, all right.
Enjoy, get unlucky.
- I have something that
belongs to you. Your change.
(Joe laughs)
(romantic music)
- Mmm. Had to find a way to get you here.
(Patrice laughs)
(romantic music)
- So that book by Dumas that you got,
it's not exactly a bestseller.
- I figured that.
That's why I called ahead
to make sure you had a copy.
- Hmm so you know about Dumas?
- That he was black.
That his father was a general
in Napoleon's army. Of course.
- Okay. I'm embarrassed.
- Not much faith in black men, right?
- No, not much faith in men of any color.
- (laughs) Now is that going
to be tonight's subject?
- (laughs) No.
- Okay.
I notice your necklace
there. It's very beautiful.
- It's my mother's wedding
ring. My father's wedding ring.
They were killed in a car crash
when I was a freshman in college.
- Oh, I'm sorry to hear that.
I lost my mom to cancer a few years ago.
- So tell me about your
journalistic career.
How did you get started?
- At St. Alban's Review
in Queens, New York.
Actually, I was only 14 years old.
Reporting on the quality
of lemonade stands
around the neighborhood.
- Were you an impartial critic?
- I couldn't be, my sisters had a stand.
Would you like something to drink?
- Yeah, that'd be great.
- Waiter?
So eventually I decided to leave the Post
because I realized the stories
that matter the most to me
were the ones right here
in my own community.
- [Patrice] Oh yeah, I understand that.
- [Joe] Well, little lady,
you've got your hands full.
You're about to get
your doctorate candidacy
on the future of democracy
in central American politics.
And you happen to be a super
whiz kid at computer science?
(laughs) That's a bit much for one woman.
I never told you I barely
got through journalism school
with a C average, did I?
- [Patrice] Well, we
can't all be brilliant.
- [Joe] Or humble. My God.
- Thanks for the ride.
- It's my pleasure.
You sure your roommate's
not gonna be worried
about you, though?
- [Patrice] No, I told
her I'd give her a call
if I needed a ride.
- [Joe] Oh, let me get the door for you.
- Yeah, thanks.
Thank you.
- You tell her
Whenever you go out with Joe
Kirkman, you never need a ride.
Okay?
- I will do that.
- Make sure you do. You understand?
I had a great time.
- So did I.
- I'll see you.
(romantic music)
- Good night.
- Goodnight.
- See you tomorrow?
- Okay, yeah.
- I'll call you.
- Okay, night.
- You take care.
(romantic music)
- Bye.
- Yes!
(romantic music)
- Bang zoom?
- Bang zoom. Yes!
- Really? I don't believe it.
Do you realize that Mario's gonna know?
Tomorrow when he sees
you, he's going to know.
- Mario already knows.
- Oh, ouch, poor Mario.
Ever the romantic dreamer
where you were concerned.
So what about Mr. K? Okay,
does he know? (laughs)
Yes, of course he knows.
Gosh, I envy you.
Do you realize that your next sex
is just going to record shattering?
- He's the one, Carolyn.
All that frustration, all that waiting.
And it's him. I knew it
the moment I looked at him.
- You realize I'm going to have
to melt from sheer jealousy, right?
- [Linda] Nope, no, no, no, no.
Not on the phone.
No. Listen, meet me under crane
six on the San Pedro pier.
All right. Ciao.
(sinister music)
(Linda screams)
- Good morning.
- Good morning, Patrice.
- Good morning, Mario.
- Look who decided to come in today.
Must have been a late date.
- Mario.
- Are you going to go out with him again?
- Yes I am.
(Mario sighs)
And that's going to be the
end of this conversation.
- Do you know how much this is hurting me?
- You have no right to say that.
- I think three years gives me the right.
- Do you want me to quit?
- Just get to work.
♪ I want to know ♪
♪ All about it ♪
- Well, have you come to humble yourself
for the great sacrifice
I'm making in going out
with Philip tonight so
you can cook for and with
your new babe-alicious?
- Some sacrifice.
You've been wanting to wrinkle his sheets
ever since you met him.
- Oh, please, they're already wrinkled.
- You are such a slut.
- Look who's talking.
At least I've known him
for more than 12 minutes.
- Oh, what makes you think I'm
going to sleep with Joseph?
- Well, who am I some
bumpkin from cupcake?
- Yes. You're a Norwegian bumpkin slut.
- You know, if you weren't my best friend,
I'd really take that personally.
And I bet you anything that your sheets
will be sweaty before Phillip's.
- Just shut up and taste this.
(suspenseful music)
- Important men like you should be careful
about places like this.
- Men like me never worry about anything.
- Took care of that little errand.
- Nice and neat?
- You know Ward's here.
- Of course I do. He's an annoyance.
Just like the woman. Watch him.
- What about that other
annoyance that showed up?
- Let's make sure first.
- You're the boss.
- That's something that you
don't ever want to forget.
(romantic music)
- It's okay, Joe.
I know it's okay. All right, I know.
All right, Kirkman, Kirkman, Kirkman.
48 hours ago, you were
a confirmed bachelor.
Now. You're like a teenager in love.
But it's simple. It's real simple.
Even though it's pressure.
You're feeling pressured.
I know all that.
I know, but it's simple.
Either you come across
a single greatest moment
of your life, (laughs)
ah, or you need serious psychiatric help.
Let's see which one it is.
(doorbell rings)
(romantic music)
- Hi.
- Hi. How are you?
- I'm fine. How are you?
- Okay.
- Oh, roses.
It's my favorite. Thank you.
It's a good guess.
- Thank you.
- Karma?
- A lot of research.
(romantic music)
- Mm, smells wonderful around here.
- Let's hope it tastes that way.
- You have any doubts?
- Actually none.
- I didn't think so.
(romantic music)
- It's beautiful.
- Thank you.
- Your place looks nice too.
- That's very gallant of you, Joseph.
You do like Middle Eastern food?
- Yes. Matter of fact, I do.
I spent some time there, you know.
- Yeah, I know.
The article you did on the children
and the post-war conditions
in Baghdad was outstanding.
Yes. I read you when you
were at the Post too.
All right, now see, that's not fair.
You been holding out on me.
You didn't say a thing
about that last night.
- Well, last night was last night.
Tonight is tonight.
(romantic music)
A little at a time, Mr.
Kirkman, a little at a time.
- You're beautiful.
Extremely smart.
And a great cook.
I'm not leaving.
(Patrice laughs)
So where's your roommate?
- She's out playing.
She'll either be back
very late or very early.
So why don't we go sit on the couch?
(romantic music)
- So hard to quarrel with perfection.
- You know, I never pass up flattery.
- You shouldn't.
(both laugh)
- Listen.
I was in Syria and Lebanon
and I just love their music.
And their dancing.
It's just this urgency
that the rhythm conveys.
(romantic music)
Come on, dance with me.
- I have two left feet.
Don't worry, I'll teach you.
(romantic music)
I won't believe you if you tell me that
what's happening is only happening to me.
- I couldn't do that. That would be a lie.
- I'm not a child, Joe.
And I'm not a fool, and I'm not desperate.
But I love you.
There's no doubt in my mind.
- I know.
I knew it the moment I saw you.
My soul's been searching
for yours forever.
(romantic music)
♪ All my life I wished for you ♪
♪ To share in everything I do ♪
♪ Be by my side night and day ♪
♪ To kiss and caress my troubles away ♪
♪ This golden glow I feel inside ♪
♪ There's no way it can be denied ♪
♪ You got to make me yours ♪
♪ Just like I have made you mine ♪
♪ Golden lady ♪
♪ Golden girl of my dreams ♪
♪ You made me such a happy man ♪
♪ And to you I forever sing ♪
♪ Golden lady ♪
♪ My golden girl to be ♪
♪ I need you ♪
♪ Desperately ♪
(downbeat music)
- [Martin] Joe, this is Martin.
I just arrived at the
Sheraton in San Pedro.
Give me a call when you get in.
- Mmm.
Oh, Marty, I knew it wouldn't
be long before you showed up.
Operator, can I have the
Sheraton in San Pedro, please.
- I want every stone unturned.
I don't care whose feathers
we ruffle. You understand?
No, you're not hearing
me. This is priority.
You tell all our people on the coast.
- [Man] You're right. He's
talking to his office.
- [Martin] Now leave a
message at the hotel.
- He thinks she left
what she knows somewhere.
So where do we start looking.
Ward's in the dark and
she's that thorough.
The only contact she made here is.
- Let's go.
(suspenseful music)
- Ward's prowling.
He's convinced the dead
bitch left a package.
- Kirkman.
I don't like unknowns.
Have you found a way in?
- Yeah, I found it.
- Get in, and get answers.
- And if he's a player?
- Step on his neck, step on it hard.
(suspenseful music)
- Listen, baby, take
that gum out your mouth.
Everybody has their water, okay?
All right. Ooh, Joe Kirkman.
Boy, where have you been keeping yourself?
And who's this pretty young thing you got
holed up close to you, my goodness?
- Lanetta, this is
Patrice. And she's the one.
- Well, bless my soul, honey.
Now when did all this come about?
- Recently, it wouldn't matter
if I met her outside your
door five minutes ago.
- Oh, and don't I know it.
Because I told you, Joe, that one day
lightning was going to hit you smack right
between those baby brown eyes.
Now didn't I tell you that?
- Yes you did.
- Didn't I?
Ooh, child, you got yourself
a fine man here, honey.
You better hold on to him
tight. Now you hear me?
- Oh, don't you worry, Miss Lenetta.
I'm holding on real tight
- That's a girl. Oh, Joe,
I can see right away.
She's special.
- Yes she is, one of a kind.
I'm supposed to be meeting
two friends of mine here,
Martin Ward and Linda Cray,
anybody been looking for me?
- Mmm, well, you know, there's
a down in the mouth white man
sitting over there at
the bar all by himself.
Joe, looks like he seen a
ghost. Is that your white man?
- That's Martin. Martin?
How you doing man?
- How are you?
- Good to see you.
- All right. Patrice, this is Martin Ward.
International editor of
Washington Post, my former boss
and former friend and all around louse.
- Well, it's nice to be dining
with Joe's close friends.
It's nice to meet you, Martin.
- Pleasure to meet you, Patrice.
- Lenetta, do you have a table for us?
- Ooh, honey, if you want to do right
by this special child right here,
you all can sit at my table.
You all go on over there
and enjoy yourselves, okay?
- Thank you, Lenetta.
How you been, man?
- I've been okay, Joe. I've been okay.
(downbeat music)
- So where's Linda?
- Joe, can I talk to you for a second?
- I get it. She's going
to burst in any moment.
Talking about the story
trail's getting hot.
I told you, baby. Don't start
today, Martin, where is she?
- Joe, there's something
that I want to tell you.
And I don't think you want me
to say it in front of Patrice.
- What do you mean?
You can say anything you want to say to me
in front of Patrice.
Come on. Don't start today,
all right, where's Linda?
- Joe. I want to talk to you alone.
- Martin. I just told
you, this is Patrice.
You can say anything you want
to say to me in front of her.
- Linda's dead.
(downbeat music)
- What?
- She's dead.
- What the hell you mean?
I just saw Linda yesterday.
- Somebody slit her throat.
(downbeat music)
- No. No, Martin, no, no!
All right, Martin, listen,
what's going on here?
What are we really dealing with?
- I know in my heart, she was murdered
by the people she was investigating.
- Do the police know that?
- Yes. I told them my suspicions.
- Well, did they believe you?
Do we have anything to back them up?
- Only what she suspected.
You know how Linda worked.
She loved the high drama.
You know, she loved to tell you
the whole story all at once.
She didn't get a chance this time.
And we certainly don't have enough
to confront a prominent CEO
on a murder charge, do we?
But I'll tell you, Joe, he killed her.
That rotten son of a
bitch Markham killed her.
Or he had her killed.
- Well, it's a police matter now.
You two need to grieve
over the loss of a friend.
- She was more than a friend.
- I know you're hurt, Joe.
- You're damn right I'm hurt.
- Look, I got to go.
I'll call you tomorrow.
Pleasure meeting you, Patrice.
- Yeah.
- Kirkman, I've been looking for you.
Someone left this on my desk.
- Thanks, Kelly. Linda's handwriting.
- How many times have you
called him, about six now?
Look, I know you're concerned,
but he hasn't called you back once.
- Oh Mario, just don't say any more, okay?
Don't risk what you and I have as friends.
- Okay.
- [Linda] It's all about rubber, Joe.
Markham is raping the San
Duarte forest and bringing it
on the sly through the
ports of Los Angeles,
not paying a dime in
tariffs or import duties.
He's got to have somebody in the port.
I mean, it's got to be a bigwig.
Someone who can move container ships
full of stuff unnoticed.
My guess is Sea and Shoreman's
union boss, Harry Pesco.
Joe, if you're listening to this,
maybe I'm not there with you.
So close it out for me, my
friend, for old time's sake.
(downbeat music)
- Can I come sit next to you?
Come on, go over there.
- No, he wants to be alone tonight.
- No he doesn't.
How close were they, him and the woman?
- Very close, like family.
- And it didn't really hit him until now.
You see, that's the delay.
If it's someone you really care about,
the denial lasts 24 hours.
Do you really love this guy
you met just a week ago?
- Yeah, Carolyn, I really do.
- Then go over there and be needed.
Patrice, I know how
long you've been waiting
for this to happen.
Maybe even longer than you've known it.
Don't back away because
of what's happened.
No matter how terrible it is.
Don't back away.
- I'm not backing away.
Okay, I get it.
You're not backing away,
but you're backing up.
Come on. He needs you.
And you are the only person
I know with strength enough
to be needed by those who love you.
You know. Come on.
Sometimes guys are just too
chicken to reach out, right?
But if he's all you say he is,
he's gonna grab you when he
sees you and hold on tight.
- Hold on tight.
Hi.
- Hi.
I thought maybe you
would like some company.
But maybe you don't.
- No, listen.
- Want any company.
- Listen. I think Martin was right.
I think Linda was murdered by
people she was investigating.
- How can you be so sure?
- Come in.
- [Linda] Unnoticed, my guess is
Sea and Shoreman's union boss Harry Pesco.
Joe, if you're listening to this,
maybe I'm not there with you.
So close it out for me, my
friend, for old time's sake.
- So what are you going to do with it?
- Well, you heard Linda.
I got to close this thing out for her.
- Joe. This is a job for the authorities.
You're a reporter.
- No Patrice, you don't understand.
I'm an investigative
reporter. This is what I do.
- You said that these kinds of stories
weren't important to you
anymore, that your life
and your focus was going
to be on the community.
- Important? Somebody just
murdered my best friend.
That's not important enough?
- I'm sorry. That's not what I meant.
- Look, this is getting personal.
Markham and his thugs killed Linda.
- And what can you do against
powerful people like that?
- Expose them.
This is not what I had planned for us now,
but I got to do this.
- And what is it that I'm doing?
I'm just sitting at home,
waiting for you to decide
to restart our lives together?
- Honestly, I didn't think about that.
Not today.
- Think about it now.
- Look, I love you,
but this thing is
getting way too dangerous
and I won't have you hurt.
- That gallantry again. But
this time it's misplaced.
You're about to risk your
life for your friend.
Joe, look at me.
You think I can't handle
it or that I don't want to?
Which means you have not looked
deeply enough inside of me.
- No, that's not it.
Look, I won't take
chances with you close by.
- I guess you don't want company after all
- Kirkman.
- Hey Kelly.
- Diane, will you make sure
Paul gets that? Thank you.
- Kelly, you've been working
the harbor beat down there.
What's up with Harry Pesco?
- Pesco? Why the sudden interest in him?
- I just been knocking around a story
in my head about the waterfront unions.
- JK, be careful out there in the Harbor.
You ask anything negative about him.
You are liable to get one of those hooks
right in your gazoikas.
- Thanks, Kelly.
(sinister music)
- Hi.
- I'm kind of new in the neighborhood.
I thought that maybe you could tell me
where the nearest grocery store was at.
- Just go two blocks down, make a right.
- Thanks. Hey, San Duarte.
I was there on vacation once.
Is that where you're headed?
- No, I'm just doing research on it.
- Well, hey, it's a great place.
If you ever need anybody to talk
to you about the place, you know?
- Okay. Well thanks.
Gotta go.
- All right.
- Thanks. Thanks a lot.
You're right.
She's all over that San
Duarte shit. What now?
- We do what Markham sent us to do.
We find out what these
two know and take 'em out.
(sinister music)
- Back to work, yeah come on,
what do you think this is?
(foghorn blares)
- Mr. Pesco.
- Yeah, who wants to know?
- Joe Kirkman, New Times Weekly.
- What can I do for you?
- I'm interested in doing a profile
on you and the port activities.
Everyone says you're the
man to keep things moving.
- And all of a sudden you
want to make me the cover boy
on some paper that most
people read in public toilets?
I'm underwhelmed.
- Maybe you are, but we're
going to do the article.
And if you cooperate,
it'd go a long way with
getting the story right.
- Oh yeah. How about this?
How about you write
about endangered aardvarks in Santa Monica
and stay the hell away
from my docks and my men.
- You got something to hide, Mr. Pesco?
- You see that?
You see how easy it is not
to like you press monkeys?
Let me give you some friendly advice, Joe.
Don't come around these ports.
You're not welcome here.
- Two PM Saturday.
- Hi Joe.
- Hi.
- It seems Colonel Delgado,
that San Duarte dictator,
has been on a very expensive
spending spree lately.
- Hold on.
- He's also had his
interior ministry flunkies
inform the world bank
that there's been a blight
on the country's rubber trees
and that he will be unable to
meet his European commitment
for deliveries this year.
Of course, no one's been allowed
to confirm this disaster.
It's all here. Read it.
- Patrice!
(sexy music)
♪ I'm a bad, bad woman ♪
♪ Baby, yeah, yeah, yeah, woman ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, woman ♪
♪ I'm a bad, bad woman ♪
♪ Looking for a good good man ♪
♪ I'm a bad bad woman ♪
♪ I'm looking for a good good man ♪
♪ Looking for a good good man ♪
♪ I'm a bad bad woman ♪
- Whoo! Encore.
(Carolyn laughs)
Well, somebody's feeling very happy today.
- Bang. Zoom, eh?
- Bang zoom?
- Yep.
- Really? Really.
- Phillip?
- Come on. Don't be
ridiculous, I met him today.
- Okay, who is he? What does he do?
- Don't know, don't care.
- Oh, Carolyn, come on.
- No judgment calls, remember?
I'll let you have your bang zoom.
You let me have mine, right?
- Hi.
- Hi. Going out?
- Yeah I'm going to
meet Carolyn at a club.
She's got a blind date.
She wants my approval.
- You think she'd approve of me?
- I don't know, why don't you
take a break and find out?
- Okay. Mind if I drive?
- No, not at all.
- Okay.
I want to thank you for everything.
- You don't do humble very well either.
I like that.
So what's your take on the
Delgado world bank scam?
- Well, it's like you found out.
He screams poverty, gets a huge loan.
Pays off the farmers dirt cheap.
He delivers the rubber to Markham
and puts millions in his pocket.
Markham sells his tax-free
import duty free rubber
at a huge profit.
- So getting the rubber into the country
and past the customs people,
that's where Harry Pesco comes in.
Well, they must have an outlet
for selling the rubber right?
- Absolutely.
They have a subsidiary
right here in Santa Monica.
Pan-American Resources.
It's the perfect front.
- Well, if everything
that you suspect is true,
and Markham did have your
friend Linda murdered,
then he must be desperate.
Plaxcom must be in trouble.
- Not necessarily. You know what they say?
Greed is greed.
(sinister music)
- Wait here for me.
- Yes sir.
(sinister music)
- Why all the sneaking around?
- A reporter showed up with a fish story
about writing me up in this local sheet.
The New Times. I don't like coincidences.
- I don't either. What did you tell him?
- What do you think? I
told him to get lost.
Now you know something
you're not telling me?
- What does that mean?
- It means I got a lot at stake here
and I want to know who's
at the table with us.
- Kirkman.
- That's the guy.
What's going on, Markham?
- It's being handled.
- So, mister, I'm about to introduce
the best roommate I ever had.
I'm beginning to see what
the fuss is all about.
- So how am I doing so far?
- Oh, you're better
looking than your picture,
but are you honest, forthright, sincere?
Ah, who cares, you're better
looking than your picture.
- I told you about her.
- Yes you did. She also
told me you're from Norway.
Oslo Accord. Last story
I did for the Post.
- You should have called me.
I would have put you onto some great lox.
- That's it. I'll have to go back.
- So where's your fella?
- Fella? It's not exactly how
anyone would describe him.
He looks like the best
looking wanted poster
in the post office.
- Hence the attraction. Carolyn
loves the dangerous type.
- Are you dangerous, Joe?
- In a pinch.
I guess I could be pretty irritable.
- I like him.
- The ultimate blessing.
Or a curse.
- You made it.
Oh, this is my roommate Patrice
Summers and Joe Kirkman.
- John Smith.
- Pleasure.
- John Smith? Come on,
is that really your name?
- I'll change if you like.
- Careful, John, she might ask.
- I'm familiar with your work.
I used to live in Washington.
Are you here in LA on a story?
- Is that what my roommate was
doing today, working for you?
I saw that stuff from some
guy named Colonel Delgado.
- Carolyn.
- Alexio Delgado?
Yeah, the San Duarte strong
man. I hear he's bad news.
- Pretty well-informed, Mr. Smith.
- I try to keep up with what's happening.
It helps in my business.
- What business would that be?
- Personal security.
- Personal security?
Sounds exciting.
- Is it?
- Nah, it's dull most of the time.
- Guarding anybody interestingly lately?
- If you consider corporate
types interesting.
- Some of them can be.
- Not my clients.
So Joe, tell me about
this Delgado situation.
- Nah, that's a boring subject.
- I'm sure. Pardon me, Smith.
- It's me.
He's getting awfully annoying.
- I noticed.
- Where are you?
- I'm at a club with some friends. Yeah.
- You know what you have to do?
- Yes I do.
Sorry.
- Business?
- And pleasure.
- Ooh, I'm jealous already.
- I'm going to powder my nose.
Come with me to the ladies room.
- Don't want to.
- Come on.
- Okay, I'm coming. Be right back.
- You might as well.
- Might as well.
- Okay, what's on your
mind, little mother?
- I don't trust him.
- Who, Joe? Please, he's a boy scout.
- Don't be funny. You know I mean Smith.
- I think you're jealous.
Maybe you picked your super
honey a little too soon.
- There's something about him.
- Mmm, yes, isn't there?
- So you're not with the Post anymore.
- No, I'm not. How about yourself?
How'd you get into your line of business?
- I'm just naturally good
at keeping certain people
from being disturbed.
- Imagine it pays pretty well.
- The bigger the disturbance
that needs eliminating,
the bigger the fee.
- Pretty dangerous too, I guess.
- Can be for them.
- God he is hot. My panties are soaked.
- Do you have to be so obvious?
- Yeah. Look who's talking?
Coming home tonight?
- I don't know what's going to happen.
- Come on. He came to
apologize then, didn't he?
You cannot let the poor boy suffer.
- Okay. I'm serious.
I think you need to watch out for this guy
because he seems like he
could be really dangerous.
- Yeah, well, I hope he's deadly.
- No, I mean it.
- Come on, Patrice, you're
judging, you're judging me.
- Okay, okay, okay.
- No, it's not okay.
- Oh, just, I love you
and I worry about you.
Mostly I worry.
She is so, so.
- So what?
I assume you're talking about Carolyn.
- Never mind. What'd you think of her?
- I liked her. She's real.
- What about John Smith?
- Oh, the tough guy, in his
business, I assume that's a plus.
- I did not like him.
- Well, would that matter to her?
You said she wanted your approval.
- Yeah, only if it agrees with her.
(Joe laughs)
So what do you think, you
wanna take a walk on the beach?
I think he's going to be invited in.
- Sure.
(romantic music)
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Baby ♪
♪ I know I told you we should be friends ♪
♪ But no matter what, till the end ♪
♪ You and me ♪
♪ And let no one come between us ♪
♪ Don't let them tell you things ♪
♪ That you don't want to hear ♪
♪ Holding your body tight ♪
♪ Saying things you want to hear ♪
♪ I want you right here with me ♪
♪ 'Cause you know what I need ♪
♪ Who would of thought it would be you ♪
♪ Who'd make me change my ways ♪
♪ To fall in love again ♪
♪ Girl, you know I was afraid ♪
♪ But having you here with me in my life ♪
♪ It's deeper ♪
♪ Deeper than it's ever been ♪
♪ Deeper than before ♪
♪ Sure is deeper than before ♪
♪ Deeper than it's ever been ♪
♪ And it's deeper baby,
deeper baby, deeper baby ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ It's Deeper ♪
♪ It's deeper than it's ever been ♪
♪ It's deeper than before ♪
♪ And it's deeper, baby,
deeper, baby, deeper, baby ♪
♪ 'Cause every time I close my eyes ♪
♪ I think of you ♪
♪ No matter what the season is ♪
♪ I still love you, oh ♪
♪ It's deeper ♪
♪ It's deeper than it's ever been ♪
♪ Said it's deeper, deeper ♪
♪ It's deeper than before ♪
♪ Than it's ever been, yeah ♪
♪ Said it's deeper, baby ♪
♪ Deeper, baby, deeper,
baby, deeper baby ♪
♪ It's deeper baby ♪
♪ It's deeper than it's ever been ♪
♪ It's deeper than before ♪
♪ Said my mind is made up, oh ♪
♪ It's deeper than it's ever been ♪
♪ 'Cause it's deeper baby, oh ♪
♪ It's deeper, baby ♪
♪ Deeper baby ♪
(sinister music)
- John?
What are you doing?
- That's not a toy you're holding.
- I asked what the hell you're
doing at Patrice's computer.
- Give me the gun.
- Stay away from me.
Stay away from me.
(both grunt)
(sinister music)
- You shoulda stayed in bed.
Now write.
(sinister music)
(Carolyn whimpers)
(Carolyn screams)
- Too bad this was business.
You're a great lay.
(Carolyn screams)
(sinister music)
- Well, according to the
international ship registry,
a big freighter left the port
of Harango in San Duarte,
four days ago, was supposed
to haul bananas to Chile.
It never arrived at Santiago
and nobody seems to care.
- That has to be it.
- I think so too.
The ship's called the Colombian,
it's Liberian register,
the ship's a drench
at 460 foot 84 tons.
Let me make some calls,
see what else I can dig up.
You know something, Joe?
I know you don't believe it
but I used to be a pretty good reporter.
- I heard about you, Marty.
(somber music)
- Hey, what's wrong?
- Carolyn left me this note.
Pats, John swept me off
my feet and swept me away.
We're off to a secret
hideaway in the Caribbean.
I'll call you when we come up for air.
Doesn't that sound strange to you?
- You still worried about Carolyn?
Well, has she done
anything like that before?
- Well, yes, occasionally.
She likes adventure.
- So what's the problem?
- I'm worried about her.
- You read the note.
When she comes up for air,
she'll give you a call.
You'll tell her she picked
the wrong man again.
It all will be fine. Cool out.
- Yeah. I guess.
- Listen, I got to go out.
- Where are you going?
- To the Harbor.
- Well then I'm going with you.
- No, you're not, Patrice,
it could be dangerous
and a lot of trouble.
- You're going to have
a lot of trouble with me
if you don't take me.
I'll drive you down there.
I'll stay wherever you want me to stay.
And you'll have somebody
to tell all the details to
when you get back.
- No you're not going.
And I'm very serious.
- So am I.
(foghorn blares)
- What?
- She always leaves me
her messages in my email.
She likes to send me little
jokes and she knows my password.
And she sends me no email,
no jokes, no nothing.
- I doubt very much if that's
what she had in her mind
if she was packing for the Virgin islands.
(sinister music)
- Okay, that's it, that's the Columbian.
All right, keep the engine
running. Lock your doors.
If you see anyone coming, just go.
- If you find those containers
are full of raw rubber,
can't we just call customs?
I mean, that will accomplish
what you're trying to do, won't it?
- No, I want Markham.
I want Markham and the
proof he killed Linda.
- You want it all.
Be careful.
(somber music)
- Lock the doors.
(suspenseful music)
- As long as Michael is free
then the Lakers got no shot.
- Yeah, but he's not coming back.
(sinister music)
(men grunt)
- Hit him, Gus.
(men laugh)
- Come on, come on, come on.
(men grunt)
Come on, finish him off.
- Crack you like a rotten
fucking egg. (laughs)
Get ready to bleed scoop.
(men grunt)
(sinister music)
- Motherfucker, I'm going
to kill you so dead.
(men grunt)
(suspenseful music)
- All right, come on.
He ain't gonna be coming
back this way anymore.
(phone beeps)
She's in.
(engine revs)
(sinister music)
- [Patrice] Oh my God. What happened?
- [Joe] I'm all right, let's
get the hell out of here.
What happened? Why the hell'd you leave?
- [Patrice] This black van was chasing me,
and you hadn't-
- A black van?
(somber music)
(Joe whimpers)
- Joe, you need to go to the hospital.
- No, I ain't got no
time for that shit now.
You see what I mean? I can't
have you involved with this.
You could have been hurt or even worse.
- Doesn't matter now. They know about me.
And you're stuck with me.
- I just lost my best friend.
I'm not gonna lose you too.
- You're never going to lose me.
- You're pretty tough for
a little girl from Encino.
- You have no idea.
What next?
- My father always said,
when you want something done,
you gotta go straight to the source.
(sinister music)
I want to see Markham.
- Can I help you?
- I want to see Markham.
- One moment.
Miss Allen, there's a gentleman
out here to see Mr. Markham.
- Now.
- And he's insisting.
Yeah. Okay, thanks.
She'll be right with you.
- Thank you.
- May I help you?
- I want to see Markham.
- Mr. Markham is busy. Did
you have an appointment?
- Just tell them it's Joe
Kirkman from the Washington Post.
- Oh, I see Mr. Kirkman.
Well, I'm afraid Mr. Markham
rarely gives interviews.
Perhaps if you leave your
card, he'll get back to you.
- Where is he?
- He's in conference.
- Well, I suggest you go in conference
and tell him I'm here.
I want to talk to him now.
- Mr. Kirkman, you cannot
just barge right in here
and speak to Mr. Markham.
- Lady. Do you like your job?
- Excuse me?
- If you do, I suggest you go in there
and you tell them I
want to talk to him now
or we talk on the deck of the Colombian
in front of 50 cameras.
Trust me. He'll want that message.
- Well, wait here and
don't touch anything.
We have security cameras everywhere.
- Just get Markham.
(sinister music)
Guys have any idea who you
work for? I didn't think so.
- Do you have that contract,
that Blackwell contract?
Right.
- Mr. Markham will see you now
- Thank you.
- Mr. Kirkman. I am a very busy man.
I have no time for you.
- Save the bullshit. You knew
I was in that dock last night.
And I know what you and that
slimey ass Pesco are up to.
- All right. No bullshit.
But you don't know who
you're fucking with.
I don't know what you think you know,
but you don't know shit.
Now you came here to threaten me.
I have been threatened by men
who eat their own children.
Now I'm going to tell you
what you are going to do.
You are going to stay the
fuck out of my business.
If you don't, I'm going to put a bullet
right in your fucking head.
- Oh, similar to the way you slashed
Linda Cray's throat, huh?
Oh yeah. I know a lot more
than you think I know.
And she was onto your big game too.
And let me tell you something.
You don't know who you're fucking with.
I'm taking you down, Markham.
I'm watching your ass burn.
You killed my best friend
and I'm taking you down.
- Get the fuck out of my building.
- You're going down, Markham.
I know my way outta here.
(sinister music)
- So you've been busy.
- Listen, to hell with Markham.
It's time we pulled the cover off his ass.
- Oh, is that right? And
what about the story?
The exclusive. I thought
you wanted that for Linda.
- The longer we wait,
the more people are going to be destroyed.
Somebody like Markham has to be stopped.
- And then what, you and Patrice run off
and live happily ever after?
- Don't patronize me.
- Hey, you know me better than
that. That's not my style.
You want to go public?
Make a lot of noise.
Fine. You'll inconvenience
the guy a little bit.
So instead of bringing the
rubber here, he'll port it out
in new Orleans and his trucks
will have a longer drive.
The minute you accuse
him of Linda's murder
without a shred of evidence, guess what?
You'll become the bad guy.
- You got a better idea? Spit it out.
- Yeah, I do. Remember Bobby Chickle?
- Chicklets, Linda and I
were just talking about him
before she was killed.
He's doing 18 years at Marion.
- No, he's not, Joe. He's
out and he's on his way here.
- What, are you getting
daring in your old age?
- Did you forget? Linda was
your mentor at the Post.
Who do you think was hers? Me. (laughs)
(sinister music)
- Joe.
- What's going on?
- Kirkman.
- Joe Kirkman.
- Yeah, I'm Joe Kirkman. What's going on?
- I'm Detective Cogan. This
is Detective Hail, LAPD.
About two nights ago, you
went out with Ms. Summers
and Caroline Thomasson, her roommate.
She was on a blind date with a guy
by the name of John Smith.
(Patrice sobs)
- Oh my God, Carolyn.
- We have a very strong
description of this John Smith.
And we're going to catch him.
Is there anything you can add?
- No.
- Well then we'd like for you
to come down to the station
and look through our mug file.
- I can't, I'm busy today.
- What's that about?
You're not interested in catching the punk
that did your girlfriend's roommate?
- Take it easy, Hail.
So does this mean that
you're not going to cooperate
with our investigation?
- I said I'm busy today. Excuse me.
- Okay. Mr. Kirkman.
- How could you put Patrice in danger?
I bet you had something to
do with poor Carolyn as well.
- I'm going to find
out what happened here.
- You do that and then
keep her out of your life.
- I don't know you, but I can
see how you feel about her.
- I don't care what you know.
I know that a week ago
she was content and happy.
You walk into her life
and it's a living hell.
- That's about as much
of your petty jealousies
I'm going to take.
- Petty jealousy. You son of a bitch!
- Stop it. Both of you.
I want to talk to Joseph alone.
- Patrice, if Linda and
Carolyn's death are connected
and John Smith is
responsible, I'll find out.
- Yeah, you probably will.
But what is that going to do?
They're not going to magically reappear
because you find out who
the killer is, are they?
But you're just going to go
ahead and pursue the answer
until they finally just kill you too.
- I don't have a death wish
but I need to do something
for Linda and Carolyn.
- Like what?
- At first, I thought it was vengeance.
But the proper way to honor
them would be to find justice.
- And when you find justice
and if you're not killed, then what next?
- I can't answer that for you.
- I guess you can't.
Mario, I want to go home.
- Do you want me to drive you?
- No.
- Kirkman, I may not be the
poet warrior she always wanted
but I never would have
risked her life for my ego.
- You know what, Mario? Fuck you.
- [Man] You wanted me, sir?
- Yes. We have a hundred
tons of rubber at the plant.
So call the buyers
and tell them to expect
delivery next week.
- Certainly, sir.
- Yo editor man.
Yeah, I already been to the Plaxcom baby.
I took the 50 cent tour.
Because that's my business.
Of course you can't do the job.
Man, that's why you brought me here.
Yeah. I'll see you boys tonight.
Look, I got to go. I
got some shopping to do.
None of your business, man.
Look, editor, just have a big wad of money
waiting for me, okay?
Later.
- Yeah. It's him.
Rick said you look like a hawk.
- Damn, so you're Rick's new delivery men?
- I ain't nobody's nothing.
- How come Rick didn't come himself?
- None of your fucking business.
- Hey, baby. I ain't mad at you.
All right, let's do some business.
(suspenseful music)
- Rick says you just got out.
- That's right, baby. Is
everything here I asked for?
- You got first secure
9100 with a code blocker
and auto override.
VG clamps, B meter, cold
sale, two burn sticks.
- Yeah. Rick's the best
outfitter in the west.
And you two look well equipped.
- You have no idea, Hawk man.
- You tell Rick everything is cool.
Wish I had time, baby.
- Come on, girl. Let's go.
(sinister music)
- I'm very sorry about your loss.
- And you know who has done this?
- Yes I do.
- I'm simple man, Mr.
Kirkman, from simple place.
All the time on the plane, I
am thinking parties unknown.
I cannot accept that.
Now I have the truth.
It is not parties unknown.
- No, sir. It is not.
- And now. I see in you a
young man filled with anger.
And this anger will be
satisfied with what?
- What I need is justice.
- My anger will fade
with time and grieving.
Yours, I think, will need something more.
Now I would like to be
alone with Carolina.
We have much to talk about.
(somber music)
- Your password has been violated?
Oh my God, Smith, oh my God.
(sinister music)
- Hey man, hey. Hey, the money.
- You got a nasty habit of
sneaking up on people, Joe.
- Probably the only person in the world
who could sneak up on you.
- That's cool.
- Last time I saw you, brother,
was through the glass at Marion, you know.
- Things change.
- Hey, Martin's back at
my place, waiting for you.
- Is that right? Hey Joe,
I'm sorry to hear about Cray.
She was a nice lady.
- Yeah, she was.
Listen, Chicklets, we're
gonna skin us a rattlesnake.
- Look, rattlesnakes are
known to have a nasty bite.
- That's exactly why we called you.
- Let me go up and change. I'll
meet you back at your crib.
(doorbell rings)
- Chicklets, my man.
Oh, Patrice, I was expecting someone else.
Listen. I'm sorry about your friend.
- Where's Joseph?
- I don't know, but I got a bad feeling.
Markham's having a dinner party tonight
over at the Ritz for his business cronies.
I think Joe went after them.
Hey, Patrice!
(sinister music)
- Now my friends, I
have some positive plans
for Plaxcom's future,
especially among the medical community.
But first I have to tell you
that this was a banner year
for Plaxcom and you're
all going to be very happy
with your Christmas bonuses.
Now let me tell you what
we have been up to lately.
- I'll tell you what
he's been up to lately.
He's been killing innocent women,
trying to cover up his
crooked business dealings.
- Who is this crazy lady?
- You know who I am, you animal.
You killed Linda Cray and my
friend, Carolyn Thomasson.
And your assassin was John Smith.
- You fuck with her, it'll be
the last check you ever cash.
- I should've known.
I'm going to have your guts for garbage.
Get them out of here.
You take them out of
here and call the police.
Come on. Let's have a party.
Everybody, drink up and
be merry, like before.
Great, for Plaxcom.
Where the fuck have you been?
- I had to clean something up.
They're out, Ward posted bail.
- Get rid of them, all of 'em.
Take 'em out somewhere and
turn 'em into fertilizer now.
- Done.
(sinister music)
(Patrice screams)
- It's okay, honey. This is Chicklets.
- Nobody was here. So I let myself in.
(quirky music)
- That's cool, brother.
You know I understand.
Listen, I think it's time that
you got this thing started.
- We gotta go.
- We got trouble.
That system at Plaxcom
is state of the art.
And you've been out of touch.
- I keep up.
- Keep up how?
You been in the joint.
- What do you think they
have prison libraries for?
That's why I liked the federal joints.
They got everything there
a guy in my profession
needs to keep up to date.
You think they incarcerated
me just to let me out
to work at Wendy's?
- Jesus.
- Yeah, Jesus.
He was in the joint,
but we didn't hang out.
I was busy studying.
- I saw that damn black
van outside of jail.
When you bailed us out.
- [Bobby] A black van
with painted windows?
- Yeah.
- You brought home company, baby.
- Shit.
- What the hell is
that? Hey wait a minute.
Your record never mentioned guns.
(gun cocks)
- Systems change, times change.
- What is going on?
- We're going to break
into Markham's office.
- You think there's material
there that could expose him?
- For God's sake, Joe, leave
her out of this, will you?
- Martin, I trust her completely.
If there's records,
there's a good chance
they're at his office.
- A Chippy, we got complications.
- Who are you?
- Robert Adam Chicklet, sister,
pleased to make your acquaintance.
- I assume you are the
skill part of this outing.
Burglar, generic thief?
- No, Patrice, Chicklets is the best.
- A brainy chick. Man, we
got even more problems.
- And you are a hacker as well?
- I specialize.
- I'll take that as a no.
Did Joe tell you that I have a
master's in computer science?
- [Joe] No, Patrice, not after that.
- After what? He murdered
Carol and he murdered Linda.
- Listen, you're not going.
- Try and stop me.
- Guys. Give me a minute,
I need to speak to her.
Come over here, please.
What is wrong with you?
- I'm not in the mood for a lecture, Joe.
- Have I done that?
- No, but you're about to.
- Things have gotten out of hand.
- I've realize that.
- All I ask you to do is
stay here where it's safe.
Let me do what I have to do.
- Where is safe, Joe?
In a world where Markham and
his thugs exist, where is safe?
Is love safe? I don't think so.
- I'm not talking about love.
I'm talking about breaking
into Markham's office.
- Then don't do it. Do
what I told you before.
Just give it to the authorities
and let them handle Markham
the way they handle these things.
But no, you won't do that.
- I have to avenge Linda
and Carolyn's death.
I know that may be wrong or twisted
or tinged with a bit of evil itself.
But it's me.
- Well, if it's you, then it's me too.
We've been through too much together
for it to be you and I.
It's either us or.
- You're right. Your right
Guys, she's in. She knows computers.
She can help us down there.
- What about the van?
- Okay, look, you handle
her. I'll handle the van.
(exciting music)
- Shit, fuck, we lost him.
How in the hell are we
supposed to do them tonight
if we can't find them, son of a bitch.
We're never going to find them.
- What's wrong with this picture?
(sinister music)
- Hey, you okay?
- Can I be now?
- I guess not.
(door clicks)
- Yeah.
- Brother, you still
got the touch. Good job.
- Hey, what about lobby guards?
Shouldn't they be making rounds?
- Hey, good point. In
case we get interrupted.
I'll holler when I get in.
(somber music)
- Hurry up, Chicklets, we
don't have much time, man.
(somber music)
Oh, shit.
(sinister music)
- Okay, brainy lady.
Welcome to the world
wide web superhighway.
The computer is all yours.
- Did you ever think of
writing a book, Mr. Chickle?
Because you have very colorful phrasing.
- Not now, guys, not now, come on.
- If we get interrupted,
act like you mean it.
Let's do the do.
(sinister music)
- Ain't that the broad's car? You think?
- You don't?
(sinister music)
- Got the safe.
- Good job, man.
Let's get it open.
Anything yet?
- No, not yet.
- You know I'm proud of you, don't you?
- Aren't you supposed
to be watching the door?
- Yeah.
- Gin, I'm in.
Bunch of junk, but you
can tell your editor
that I've been paid.
(sinister music)
(silenced guns fire)
- Joe!
- That's it. Numbers, dates,
records, the whole damn thing.
Get that on this disc and
get the hell out of here.
(suspenseful music)
(Patrice screams)
- Fucking amateur. Put the gun down.
- Come on. Let's do them right here.
- No, Markham likes it nice and neat.
- What about this sack of shit?
- Let the burglar explain it all.
Okay, everybody. I don't feel
like carrying bodies tonight.
We're going to take a little
walk. Boyd, get the girl.
Hey. Come on, get up.
Let's go.
Hey bitch, your roommate
makes great fish bait.
(sinister music)
- You bitch.
- Patrice, get the disc!
(sinister music)
(silenced gun fires)
(glass shatters)
(men grunt)
- Joe?
- You guys okay? Where's the disc?
- I got it.
Hey, you're bleeding all over.
- Don't worry about that. I'm okay.
- Now we have to call the police.
- And tell them what?
That we broke in and stole
evidence of conspiracy?
Bad idea.
We get on the horses and
you do what you gotta do.
- What about him?
- Let him explain how he
got here and got shot.
By that time, if you know your business
the package will be wrapped.
- Patrice is right. You
are colorful, brother.
(men mutter)
- Step back from the car, please.
- Step back from the vehicle, please.
(men mutter)
(eerie music)
- Mr. Markham. I'm Detective Cogan.
This is Detective Hail. I have
a warrant for your arrest.
Sir, stop right there.
- Where is security?
- Stop right there.
- Where is my security?
- Stop right there, turn around.
- What the hell am I being arrested for?
- How about two counts of murder.
One count of conspiracy.
And one count of illegal
trafficking. Come on.
- And Ms. Allen, you need to come down
to the station for questioning.
Walk with me, please.
(sinister music)
- Mr. Markham, what about Plaxcom?
- Mr. Markham, your comments please, sir.
- Mr. Markham, would you like
to make a comment at this time?
- You think it's over, reporter?
You haven't seen hell yet,
but I'm gonna show it to you.
- I won't be hard to find.
- Neither will I.
- I'll be looking for you too.
- Let's go.
- Two decent human beings
died, and for what?
- You were right when
you left the paper, Joe.
The real stories are the closeup ones.
But now I want you to come
back and work for me again.
Not writing about scum like Markham,
but writing about Linda and Carolyn.
I want you to tell the
world that no good life
is worth the story.
- Hear, hear. Thanks Martin.
Give me some time to
think about that, though.
- Take all the time you need, buddy.
- My friend, I owe you another one.
- You call me to testify
and I ain't going to show up
and then we'll be even.
- I thought we were supposed
to putting the bad guys away.
Not ourselves.
- Hey look guys, let me
know if you need anything
for the wedding.
(romantic music)
- May I please have your hand?
This belonged to my mom.
But now it's meant for you.
Will you please do me the honor?
- It's beautiful, Joe.
(romantic music)
And this belonged to my dad.
I want you to have it.
(Joe and Bobby hum "Wedding March")
- This calls for a toast.
Hey waiter, champagne.
(somber music)
- I see you got your annual
birthday card from Mrs. Antasio.
You're never gonna tell me
who this secret admirer
of yours is, are you?
- Been telling you for 12 years.
She's just someone who
decided to take responsibility
for her own circumstances.
Still living in that same building.
- Excuse me. What was
that, husband of mine?
- Oh, nothing.
- You know what, let's teach
dad how to do that dance.
I know I never could.
(romantic music)