♪♪
-Man: Emily!
-Woman: Mom?
-[knocking on door]
-Woman: Mom!
Mother!
-Mom!
-Man: Emily?
Emily!
Emily?
[door crashing]
Mom?
[shuffling papers]
Man: Emily?
What are you doing?
It's all right, Richard, just...
It's time to go, Mom.
I know.
Emily?
Man: It's getting dark.
Judy?
Now, Judy, I know
you're angry at me,
but I can't let you
into the house today.
You know what you'll do, hmm?
[dog whining]
[sighs]
Now, try to eat something, dear.
I'll let you in tonight,
after they're all gone.
Judy, please, eat something now.
Judy?
[telephone ringing]
-[glass shattering]
-[gasps]
[telephone ringing]
-Hello?
-Woman: Hi, Mom.
How ya doin'?
Happy Easter.
Woman: They're fine.
They're doing their
morning constitutional...
shooting hoops.
[shouting]
Boy: Come on, Dad.
No, no.
No, no, we're just
running a little bit late.
We went to the Dean's house
last night for a party
and we didn't get home 'til one.
Actually, it was after one.
Mom.
Mom, listen to me.
They're dropping hints
about making Richard
the chairman of the
Philosophy Department.
Yes!
-Hey, Mom.
-Good morning.
Eric made the Honor Roll again.
Now, speaking of rolls...
Fill your sink with hot water
then, set the bowl
with the dough in it.
Now, if that doesn't work
well, just cuss at it.
-I...
-Janet...
Janet, I spoke to your
brother this morning.
I'm worried about him,
he sounded so glum.
See if you can dig
it out of him today.
Uh huh.
[car horn]
Oh, my. There's Henny already.
Oh, that woman.
She'll be 15 minutes
early to her own funeral.
[laughs] Bye now dear.
Hi!
Where is your Easter bonnet?
Oh, hold your horses Henny.
You're getting
worse than Gladys.
[tisks]
Glady, don't you
dare sell your house.
You won't be in that retirement
place more than one week
before you'll be begging
them to let you come home
and you won't have
anywhere to go.
Stay at home, Gladys.
We'll chain you to the
bedpost if you get loony.
[chuckling]
I know you, Glady.
You think you're gonna
meet a man in that place.
[laughter]
She's got her hearing
aid turned down on purpose.
[laughter]
[church bells ringing]
Happy Easter, Emily.
Oh, same to you, Charles.
Oh, Em, you ought to marry him.
That old gold digger?
Don't mind her, Gladys.
She's just jealous.
[classical music plays]
Honey, it's getting late.
I'm really gonna miss this mess
when you get that thing
published, you know.
Seriously, I'm, I'm...
Give us a kiss.
Hey, the Easter Bunny
came this morning.
Thanks Mom.
Son: Here we go.
Cool, Grandpa's watch.
-Mother: Looks good on you.
-Son: Yeah.
Father: Yes it does.
Thanks Mom.
Okay, we better get moving.
-Let's go.
-Honey, would it violate
your principles if I asked
you not to wear jeans today?
Son: Why?
Well, your mother wants
your Grandmother to think
that we went to church today.
Okay, I'm weak. Okay?
That's why I admit it.
Listen Mom,
I have a chemistry
test tomorrow.
Would it be all right
if I stayed home
from Grandma's this once?
-No.
-[sighs]
Son: Why do we always
have to go to Grandma's
on holidays anyway?
Because we do.
All right, don't get hyper.
I just asked.
Mom: Get dressed.
♪ Over the river
and through the woods ♪
♪ To Grandmother's
house we go ♪
Will you stop?
Come on, stop.
You promised. You promised.
Yeah okay, we'll stop if
you turn off that Muzak.
It's not Muzak, that
is Simon and Garfunkel.
[laughter]
That's Muzak.
Boy are you dealing
with troubled waters.
[water running]
[humming]
Emily: Rob, your sister's here.
Coming.
Couldn't he wait till after
dinner to run the washer?
I never saw so much laundry.
Look how much Eric is
starting to look like Dad!
I can't believe it.
I gave him the
watch this morning.
-He's very excited.
-He didn't wear it did he?
-Janet: Yeah.
-He wore it?
He wore it.
Rob was asking about it.
I didn't know what to say.
Dad wanted Eric to have it.
I know, but Rob is so touchy.
Mom, he got so many
things when Dad died.
How could he possibly
feel slighted?
I wish you wouldn't be
so hard on your brother.
I'm starting my
PhD this summer.
I thought you were
going to Europe.
No. Not if Eric's
going to college.
When your father retired
he wanted me to stop
teaching and travel with him.
I kept saying,
"Just one more year."
"We need the money."
"Next year."
Well, next year never came.
I want you and Richard
to see Amalfi together,
to see Palermo together.
We'll get there.
[laughter]
The ham is wonderful, Emily.
I'm glad you like it.
Eric: Yeah, it was great.
Richard: As usual.
-You forgot the cloves.
-Emily: Oh please.
Come on, have some eggs.
That's sugar, Honey.
Be careful.
Emily: Your grandfather
gave that to me
when he asked me to marry him.
He couldn't
afford a wedding ring then.
It was the Depression.
[chuckles]
My poor mother, she
wanted me to marry money.
Rob: Oh money.
I remember one Easter Sunday
your mother's Easter
basket was full of goodies
and mine had a calculator in it.
Now, Dad made the special trip
to Marshall Fields in Chicago
to get you that calculator.
You were flunking math and
Dad was pulling his hair out.
I flunked math anyway.
Now I teach math in high school.
Isn't this interesting
family stuff?
Anyway, after she went to
sleep I snuck into her room.
Sneaked.
Crept silently into her room
and I ate every
goodie in the basket.
He was so sick, I didn't
have the heart to punish him.
Janet: And I was so
angry the next day at school
I let all the air out
of the bicycle tires.
Rob: You did that?
You little brat.
I gave Buster Thompkins
a bloody nose for that.
I know you did.
That's why I made Tracey
Johnson swear in blood
she would never tell anybody.
[laughter]
Is that Dad's watch?
Uh, yeah.
Looks nice doesn't it?
I had it cleaned.
Yeah it really does.
It's very valuable.
Take good care of it.
It's really the only thing
of Dad's he has, you know.
I wasn't asking for it.
I think I better
check the dryer.
Excuse me.
Listen, if Uncle
Robert really wants it,
I mean, it was his dad's.
Janet: Uncle Robert
just needs to grow up.
Something else is bothering him.
Mother, he's always been
a little jealous of Eric.
-You know that.
-What a thing to say.
Janet: You know
how Dad adored Eric.
We all adore Eric but Robert
is your one and only brother.
Janet, please stop this.
Eric, try another one
of your mom's rolls.
Go ahead, we have
dental insurance.
Ha ha ha.
Eric: Actually they're
not too hard, Mom.
Here you are.
Why don't you come in and
visit with us for a while?
Oh, they were watching
television so I...
-We'll turn it off.
-No, it's okay.
Oh goodness, look at
the weeds in this yard.
Dad would have a stroke, huh?
Remember when he used
to make us pick weeds?
We were always picking
weeds, pulling weeds.
Yeah.
Does Mom seem a
little fuzzy to you?
Mom? Mom's fine.
She'll outlive us all.
The house is so dusty.
It isn't like her.
She'll have her
big spring cleaning
and the whole
place will glisten.
You were thinking about going
to grad school a while back.
-Are you still?
-No.
You could knock off
your masters in no time.
Maybe teach college,
still have your summers.
Teach college?
Like you and Richard?
Yes.
It's funny, I thought
when Dad died
I wouldn't have to
hear that anymore.
You know, Eric was really
happy to get that watch.
Would've meant
a lot to me too.
I guess Dad didn't
want me to have it.
Rob, I know you and Dad had
your moments and it wasn't fun
but don't you think it's
time you let go of it?
For your own sake.
It's not the watch.
It's the principle.
How do you think
that made Eric feel?
All right, all right.
[sighs]
That woman you're
dating, Mary?
I like her.
Yeah, I like her too.
She's getting married.
Well, there's a
lot more fish in...
Jan, I know you're
trying to be helpful.
I'd rather you
wouldn't meddle, huh?
Okay.
It's a little cool
out here, anyway.
I'm going to go in.
[crowd on TV cheers]
TV Announcer: Forty, fifteen.
[Emily snoring]
TV Announcer: Forty, thirty.
[crowd cheering]
[whispering]
Mom.
Oh. What time is it?
After five. We have to go.
-Where's Rob?
-He's out in the back.
You come and go so fast.
I'll have to start making lists.
I'll be remembering things
I wanted to tell you
for two weeks.
Well, you know
our phone number.
I hate to see you go.
Emily: Bye.
Bye, bye.
-Janet: Eric?
-Eric: Bye.
Richard: So long. Thank you.
You bet.
Bye.
You avoided your sister the
whole time they were here.
She's got her family.
I want you have each other.
We have each other, Ma.
Mom, my car needs an overhaul.
Could you let me have 500?
Well, yes of course, dear.
But uh, this will have
to be the last time.
I don't want to strain you.
No, no.
There's no strain.
You must learn to be more
careful with your money.
Yeah. I will Ma, honest.
Want to take some food with you?
No, no, no.
Do you want some coffee?
No, no, I'm fine.
I'll call you through the week.
No, you won't.
[Rob laughs]
Bye!
Oh, Rob!
You forgot the cake.
It's your favorite.
Keep your eye on the ball.
Attaboy Rob, hmm?
Father: Don't stand
on the plate.
And get that bat
off your shoulders.
Ready?
I don't wanna play.
We've been out
here long enough.
Okay, if he doesn't practice
he won't make the team.
But you make him feel so
bad every time he misses.
Look, I don't care if
he isn't Joe DiMaggio
I just want him to try.
He won't try.
Robbie?
Come on, let's give
it another shot, okay?
-Get down.
-I don't want to.
All right, stay
up there and pout.
Come on, Janet.
My turn.
Something wrong?
Uh, no, I was
watching the sunset.
I'll be with you in a minute.
Well, be quick about it.
We gotta pick up Gladys.
Now, where's that purse?
[car horn]
What do you suppose
is taking her so long?
I'll bet you a doughnut
she can't find her purse.
[screams]
Henny: Hi.
Em.
You're okay, Mom.
They pinned your hip.
You're as good as new.
I fell.
So far.
You were very lucky.
That's a long stair.
Hit my head.
Then the lights...
went out.
Kept...
falling.
Falling.
Into darkness.
I thought I'd died.
And the light came back.
Here I am.
Well you can
quit trying to die.
The doctor says you're fine.
Judy.
Oh, did anyone feed Judy?
No. We've been here night
and day, waiting for you.
How are you feeling?
Well, I'm still here.
[laughs]
Mom, I have to
go see the doctor,
and then I will go
by and I'll feed Judy
and I'll be right back.
I promise.
No. Henny can do that.
You go home.
Don't be silly.
[Emily groans]
Henny.
Where's Rob?
He was here.
We sent him home
to get some sleep.
You can get that gerbil
food out of here.
I brought her supper.
Don't look at me like that.
My mother-in-law
built this hospital
and my husband was chief
of staff for 34 years.
[laughter]
Doctor: Janet, the broken hip
wasn't the result of the fall.
In all likelihood the
fracture occurred naturally
and caused your mother to fall.
Naturally?
She twisted her
hip and it snapped,
before she fell.
Her bones are pretty brittle.
Most Caucasian women her
age suffer from osteoporosis
to some extent.
How soon will she
be able to walk?
I mean really walk?
It's impossible to say.
Now, barring complications,
I can let her out in a week
providing she responds well
to physical therapy
and assuming you plan to
provide some help at home.
Oh, certainly.
Good.
She's probably going to need
some degree of home care
from here on in.
From here on in?
A mother falls down the stairs
and all of a sudden she's old?
Intercom: Doctor Kankay
please call the operator.
Doctor Kankay please
call the operator.
She's coming to my house.
It's all decided.
Oh no, Mom.
You're gonna come home with me.
No, no.
You have classes to
teach, a husband, a son.
I don't want to
burden you that way.
Not only that, you'll spoil her.
-I know what she needs.
-[laughs]
I've already made arrangements
to take next week off.
Emily: No, no.
This is easier all
the way around.
I took Judy to the vet.
She hates that vet.
The Gustavsson boy,
he can feed her.
The Gustavsson boy got
married and moved to Maine.
We went to the wedding.
Mom, Judy's sick and the
vet wants to put her to sleep.
Oh, no.
No, no, no, no.
Janet: It'll be all right.
It's really the best
thing for her, you know.
Right. Fine, fine.
Try and get some sleep.
Janet: Good night.
Henny: See you tomorrow.
[Emily dreaming] But I don't
want a puppy, Arthur.
Somebody dumped the poor thing
in the alley behind
the drugstore.
I couldn't just leave her.
There'll be hair
all over the place.
It'll ruin the upholstery
and I don't have time
to train a puppy.
But you'd have her if
anything happens to me.
Nothing is going
to happen to you.
Em, I've already
had one heart attack.
I may not be so
lucky the next time.
Please, don't be so morbid.
I don't want a puppy.
We'll keep her till
I can find her a home.
Well, then put her
down in the basement.
[dog whimpers]
Aw.
Aw, she's trembling.
Aw, I'll give her some milk.
Make sure it's warm.
I'm calling her Judy.
[laughs] Judy.
Oh, Judy, Judy, Judy.
[bell dings]
-Woman: We've got you.
-Man: Are you ready?
All the way up now.
Woman: Easy.
-Man: Push on my hand.
-[Emily gasps]
Man: Good.
Emily: It's too soon.
I can't.
Get out of that chair!
Who let her in?
You stop feeling
sorry for yourself
and get out of that chair.
Take my hand, come on.
Up.
Come on. Good.
Let her go, she can do it.
-It hurts.
-Oh, sure it hurts.
I feel the same every morning
when my arthritis kicks in.
Man: Come on, all the way.
Good.
Don't baby her.
She'll eat it with a spoon.
I will not.
Man: Take a step.
One more.
[laughs]
Man: Straighten
up just a bit more.
Henny: Yahoo!
She'll be jitterbugging
by the fourth of July.
Oh, throw her out.
That damn doctor.
Making us sit around till noon.
I'll cancel my hair appointment.
Oh no, you go ahead.
I'll get Mama something to eat.
What about Eric's track meet?
Well, I've already
missed it, Mom. Here.
Wait a minute,
let us help you there.
They showed her what
to do in the hospital.
[Emily gasping]
Here.
One, there.
Sit down for a minute.
It's so nice out here.
Why don't I just bring
your lunch out here?
We could have lunch
on the porch, huh?
-[gasping]
-Sound good?
[gasping]
What am I gonna do, Henny?
Don't blubber in front of her.
I've heard you blubbering.
You've done your
share of blubbering.
You might as well enjoy this.
I fully expect you
to wait on me hand and foot
if I ever decide to get old.
Get me a tissue from my purse.
Get it yourself.
What a mean old snake.
When I get rid of this cane
I'm going to kick you
from here to the corner.
[laughs]
You call me if
you need anything.
-Anything.
-Yes.
All right now, go ahead.
Go.
Why don't you take a
couple bites before I go.
-I'm not a child.
-I know, I just want you to eat.
All right.
I'm eating.
Now go.
Okay.
Why don't I bring the phone out?
Would you like me to bring
the phone out here for you?
Please. Go.
I love you.
Jan!
I dropped my fork.
Well, I'll just have to take
it in and rinse it off, then.
Hi.
-Eric: Hi Mom.
-Hello, Honey.
They kept us waiting for
hours at that hospital.
And then Mom was so depressed
I just couldn't leave her.
So who won the track meet?
-We did.
-Janet: Congratulations.
Thanks.
[laughter]
What's going on?
Well hey, if you'd
been there you'd know.
What?
I broke the school
record for the 400.
Eric, that's wonderful!
That's great. Congratulations.
He was beautiful.
And now he has to go and
have his picture taken
for the newspaper.
Right.
Mom, you should've been there.
It was something.
-I'm so proud of you.
-Thank you.
Okay, I gotta go.
We'll see ya.
-Richard: Have a good one.
-Eric: Thanks!
Janet: Aunt Henny went
off to get her hair done
and Mom started crying.
Richard, I've never
seen her like this.
She's really a mess.
Do you have any
idea how your son felt
when he realized you
weren't there today?
It's simple physics,
I mean, I can't be in
two places at one time.
I know. I'm sorry.
It's just that ever
since your mother fell
you been so wrapped up in her...
We miss you.
I miss you.
Yeah.
Well, at least now she's
out of the hospital.
If anybody's going to get her
up on her feet in record time,
it's going to be Aunt Henny.
So, Jonathan comes home from
the war sporting a mustache
and my mother-in-law
says to me,
"I can't stand that
boy's mustache."
Well, I looked her
straight in the eye
and said, "Well, Ethel,
I can't stand yours either."
[laughter]
Oh!
My trick.
[jeering]
You dirty underhanded dog.
-Where did you hide that trump?
-[laughs]
What kind of medication
are you on anyway?
Maybe I should have a dose.
[laughter]
Excuse me.
Henny: What, again?
She laughed so
hard she had to...
I hope you make it.
[laughter]
I'm going to have
my bedtime nightcap.
You want one?
I have to take my medicine.
And just where do
you think clean living
is going to get you at your age?
Do you ever feel like
you're drifting away?
What?
What are you talking about?
I don't want to give up.
I want to go on and on.
The medication is doing this.
I don't want to give up.
I want to go on and on.
I heard you the first time.
You're going to have
a nightcap with me.
You need to relax,
you need to rest.
And tomorrow we're going
to have something done
about your hair.
You look like Mother Time.
Henny...
You just keep going, don't you?
I'm running scared sweetie.
I always did and I always will.
What do you want, bourbon?
What's the matter?
Are you afraid of dying
with liquor on your breath?
[laughs]
[humming]
Henny, I don't want a drink!
[whistling]
Henny.
Oh, God.
No.
No, no, no, no, no.
Minister: I am the life
and the resurrection.
The light of world by whom
all believers shall not perish
but find everlasting life.
She never had a
sick day in her life.
She never saw the end coming.
That's the best way, Jan.
I think you should come home
and stay with us now, Mom.
I have to get on with my life.
Well then, we'll bring
someone in to stay with you.
No. I'll manage.
Take it from me, Grandma,
you do not argue with Mom
when she uses that tone.
[laughing]
All right, there we go.
Eric: Okay.
I'm going back
upstairs in two weeks.
-About the yard--
-I'll get somebody this week.
Okay. I'm gonna call that
home care agency.
Emily: I'll call
them in the morning.
-Eric: I'll get sheets.
-Richard: Okay.
Is that bed comfortable?
It is to me.
You were both conceived on it.
Well, I think we better
get the night stands.
This is strange.
I always wanted
a bed-sitting-room.
[lawnmower running]
[gasps]
[phone ringing]
-Hello.
-Robert: Hi Mom.
Oh Rob, yes dear.
-Rob: How you feeling?
-Oh fine, fine.
It's really good to be home.
Robert: What are you doing?
I'm hopping around,
doing all kinds of things.
Robert: Great, I thought
I'd come over tonight.
Oh that would be lovely.
And I'll make a London Broil?
-Robert: Terrific, when's good?
-Well anytime, dear.
Come any time.
-Robert: Okay, I gotta go now.
-Bye.
[knocking]
Just a minute!
Yes?
Look here, my mower
don't cut grass this thick.
Well, if you were
here last week
like you were supposed to...
I really need the grass cut.
Can you get another mower?
I doubt it.
I'll see.
Thank you.
[heavy breathing]
[phone ringing]
Coming, I'm coming.
[phone rings]
-Hello?
-Robert: Hi Mom, it's me.
-Oh Rob, yes.
-Robert: I can't make it.
Oh well, of
course I understand.
Robert: There's this
PTA meeting I forgot about.
Well, maybe sometime next week?
Robert: Yeah, we'll see.
-[Emily mumbling]
-Robert: Is something up?
You sound upset.
Oh, no, no,
nothing's the matter.
I was just, uh, napping.
Robert: Okay, you
look after yourself.
Yes, all right dear, bye.
-[sizzling]
-[screams]
[crying]
Oh boy, do I
wish you were here.
We're having some people
from Richard's department in.
I have to feed them all.
Mom, how's your new housekeeper?
Oh well, you know
I don't like to have
strange people in my house.
The Dean is
coming tonight, Mom.
Richard's all in knots.
We're hoping he'll
announce his promotion.
I'll cross my fingers for you.
-I shouldn't have called her.
-Yes you should, go on.
-Um.
-Is everything all right?
Oh, it couldn't be better.
I'll call you in a day or two.
Bye.
She's having a dinner party.
I shouldn't have bothered her.
Then call Robert.
Let's not talk about this.
I'm not going crying
to my children.
Don't do that.
At least let me
water the plants.
Oh my God.
-Em!
-[sighs]
She just didn't
sound like herself.
Honey, you just
worry too much.
You know what?
Let me help you.
-You think I'll ruin this?
-No.
I just thought
that if I help you
we could find a little time
for ourselves later on?
I'll tell you
what, you chop--
You chop those onions
over there and you're in.
Where are those onions?
-Onions?
-Go on.
♪ Should you have a
question about my direction
[phone ringing]
♪ I'm gonna answer
you right here and now
[phone rings]
"♪ I'll be your baby,
I'll be your best friend"
-Hello?
-Gladys: Janet?
This is Gladys.
Honey, I don't
mean to meddle, but
you've got to have
a talk with her.
She's hiding a lot
of things from you.
She's going downhill fast.
Robert hasn't
been there all week.
She never called a housekeeper.
She hasn't eaten and
the place is a wreck.
Richard: Send Rob over there.
He's no help, you know that.
Honey, we're expecting
twenty-five people for supper.
You can't go running off.
-You can't.
-Everything's ready.
Honey, you just talked to
your mother an hour ago.
-She said she was fine.
-I know.
I also told that something
really didn't sound right.
Okay.
Can't it wait till the morning?
Look, I'm all she
has to depend on.
You don't seem to
understand that.
I don't understand
the emergency.
Gladys said
that she hasn't even
washed her hair this week.
Now something is wrong.
If that means that you've
gotta dump a bottle
of peanut oil into a
fondue pot by yourself
I'm not going to feel
bad about that, okay?
So don't panic.
I will be back in time.
Okay.
[water running]
So why didn't you call
that home care agency?
Emily: You just don't
understand.
You're coming
home with me, Mom.
Emily: I am not helpless.
Well, if you let yourself go
much longer you're gonna be.
Now, up you go.
What have you had to eat today?
None of your business.
I want you to come home with
me until your hip is better.
You don't have any room.
Mother, it's a four
hour round trip.
I cannot check in
on you every day.
Let's pack a bag.
I'm staying here.
Everything I have is here.
Everything I love.
And you're not taking
me away from it.
Man: Come on. Come on.
[dog barking]
Hey!
What's wrong?
Well if you'd been to
see your mother lately
you would know.
-Rob: What?
-The place is a pigsty,
she isn't eating,
she can't pay her bills
and she can barely get around.
You're kidding.
No, we have to do something.
Jan, she's just down about Henny
and this hip thing.
She'll snap out of it.
She needs to be
looked after, Rob.
Well, all right, all right.
I'll go over after school
tomorrow afternoon.
Why don't you pack a
bag and go stay with her?
[laughing]
Come on, she'd
drive me crazy, Jan.
Well then you and I
are just going to have to
come up with some money
for a housekeeper.
I am a schoolteacher
for crying out loud.
I don't have any money.
Well what do you suggest?
She has income.
As soon as she's back on
her feet she'll be fine.
There's no reason
to panic about this.
This is my problem?
Is this what you're saying?
Well let me put it this way.
You went off to Northwestern
in your red Olds convertible.
You spent your summers
at your riding camp.
I went to State
and my summer enrichment
program was opening crates
at the old family drugstore.
I cannot believe you're still
throwing this stuff in my face.
-You're 45 years old.
-Rob: I'm sure, I'm sure.
All the same it is pretty clear
our father intended to
make it your problem.
He sure didn't give me the
means to do anything about it.
And let me tell you something.
We joke about those
Easter baskets
-but that's where it started.
-Oh right, oh right.
Don't forget my
acute appendicitis.
You must've been reeling
when that one happened.
Look. You and Richard have
means that I don't have.
You want Richard
to pay for this.
Yeah well if he hadn't
looked down his nose at me
from the moment he met me
I'd feel bad about that.
Brother dear, you
are taller than he is.
If you'd been standing
on your own two feet
he wouldn't have been able
to look down his nose at you.
Listen, Janet.
If I move in with her she'll
never let me move out.
Janet, you can't
expect that from me.
Jan! Janet!
[group chattering]
Mom, nice of you to stop by.
Those have to go in the
oven for ten minutes first.
And the crudités, you
didn't put those out?
Did you put the nuts out?
Anything?
-No, I did not.
-I will do this.
You go visit with
the company, okay?
Wait, wait, wait.
So how's it going?
How do you think it's going?
You didn't even chill
the dinner wine, Richard.
I don't believe you.
Eric, will you put that wine
in the freezer compartment?
Yeah, yeah, yeah sure.
Dad is really ticked.
And put the fondue
pots on the table.
Make sure there's
enough ice at the bar.
Eric: Okay.
Those dinner napkins.
Where in the hell are
the dinner napkins?
[Richard chuckles]
What are you grinning about?
The Dean wants to
make an announcement.
Oh Honey, that's great.
-How 'bout that?
-All right!
[laughing]
You need your head examined.
I'm not ready to lie
in state in the parlor.
Janet will have a fit.
I can't sleep down here.
How am I going to get better
if I can't sleep, hmm?
And this...
This is going in the junk heap.
Where it belongs.
Em...
I...
I had a letter from the
Riverview Retirement Center.
They have a room for me.
That's right.
Throw up your hands.
Well I'm dying on my
feet like Henny Dutton.
It's not a thing
we can choose, Emily.
You're missing a button.
Are we getting my
hair done or not?
Voiceover: "The night
is deep and oddly calm.
The Germans have
finally retreated.
How strange not to wonder
what lurks in the dark.
Not to wait for the inevitable scream of rocket fire.
I can sleep now and dream
of the life we will have."
-[cat hisses]
-[dog barks]
Radio: W ith temperatures now
in the mid 50s.
Tomorrow we can expect some
late afternoon thundershowers
with temperatures ranging
from 75 to 85 degrees.
[sighs]
[door creaking]
Who's there?
Ah! [screaming]
Shhh!
Where's the purse?
The chair.
Now, the rings.
[gasps of pain]
Shhh!
[police radio]
I appreciate your concern.
-She's all right.
-Has she seen the doctor yet?
Yes.
Did she get a look at the guy?
Well, she thinks it's the
man who came to cut her lawn.
Oh, God.
Where did you find this guy?
Well, he was just
a name in the paper.
Well the police want to know.
Yeah, yeah, well I'll
see if I can dig it up.
Rob, I'm going to take her
home with me for a while.
Yeah, okay, okay.
Mom.
Mom, I'm really sorry.
-These things happen.
-I know but...
Janet: Anybody want
some more coffee?
-Me. Please.
-Yeah, I'll have a cup.
Emily, it's pretty obvious
you can't stay here by yourself.
We'll talk about
this in the morning.
Sure Mom.
Good night now.
-Richard: Good night.
-Good night.
I'll be up in a little while.
Richard, if she leaves,
she'll be afraid
when she comes back.
We'll get her some
lights in the yard,
some decent locks and
some kind of an alarm.
-You can't be serious.
-I am serious.
You don't have anything
to say about it.
I think he does, Rob.
-Thank you.
-We'll get her another dog.
-Are you nuts?
-No, I'm not nuts.
I should've insisted she come
stay with us a month ago.
No, no, no. It was my fault.
It was my fault.
I should've been here.
I'll come back, I'll move here
for a week or two.
And then what?
Jan, if you take her away
from everything
she knows and loves
she'll give up.
She looks worse
now than when she did
when she came home
from the hospital.
If you two want to force her
out of here against her will
I don't want any part of it.
Just what the hell
were you a part of, Rob?
I don't have to
take that from you!
You're not part
of the solution.
Emily: Stop this!
[screaming]
Mom?
Mom...
Come on, I got you.
[panting] Darn it.
Janet, I don't
want any fighting.
No fighting, do you hear me?
You gotta let
us help you, Mom.
And I don't know how to do that
unless you come home with me.
All right.
It's not the end of the world.
It's just for a little while.
I can't fight you, Janet.
I'm too tired.
It's gonna be fun
having you around.
Such a battle, being alive.
Lie down at night,
close your eyes,
and add up your wins and losses,
get ready for
tomorrow's onslaught.
But when the years...
In spite of all your efforts,
when the years
are out in front...
Now what do you do?
You let me worry about that.
Mama.
So, we'll just move all the
things you use every day.
-Okay?
-Fine, but I want my books.
Yeah.
I'm sorry, Eric.
We only have one
downstairs bedroom.
Why can't she go to
live with Uncle Robert?
He lives alone,
he's got an extra bedroom.
This is something that your
mom feels that she has to do.
[sighs]
We've got to back her up.
Okay?
All right.
Okay Mom, you're all packed.
What are you doing?
Putting my mother's china
in Rob's storage locker
while I'm away.
Well if you're worried
about it we can take it.
No, no, it's no
problem, really.
Did you give him
Grandma's china?
He's just keeping it for me.
Oh mother, you
know good and well
if he gets in a
bind he'll sell it.
I don't know any such thing.
You don't know anything when it
comes to your golden boy.
Emily: And thanks
so much for coming.
Did I tell you I
sold my house, Em?
She didn't sell her house,
she gave it to the first buyer.
When are you leaving, Gladys?
Saturday.
Now listen, it isn't even
forty miles to Riverview
and when you get home
you call me
and I'll come down and
I'll stay a week or so.
I don't hug, Em.
You know that.
Write me, Gladys.
Oh! You'll be back in no time.
She looks awful.
I never thought she'd give up.
Not her.
We're never gonna
see her again.
Get in the car,
I'll take you home.
We're in my car, Gladys.
Now get a move on.
I have to get back
to the library.
[car horn]
Hey Grandma.
-Hi Miss Stanton.
-[kissing sound]
-Janet: Come on over.
-Richard: Hello Emily.
-Richard: How are you?
-Janet: Eric?
Will you and
Tommy get the bags?
Eric: Yeah.
-Emily: Don't fuss, don't fuss.
-[coughing]
Take it easy. Take it easy.
Here, you're losing
your purse there.
Thank you.
I've got you.
Hi.
This is a lot of stuff.
Is she moving in?
I don't know.
They gave her my room.
She can't make it upstairs.
Richard: I've gotcha.
You can't fall.
I hope I never get that old.
-Eric: Thank you.
-Man: Thank you.
Thanks.
Bye bye.
-This is good, this is better.
-Janet: Smooth.
-Flip it to manual.
-Oh you little stinker, ah!
Watch this you little rascal.
Hey, I'm a natural.
You're not gonna
have to worry about
pushing me around
when my time comes.
Don't even joke
about that, Mom.
I have to, Honey.
My mother's probably
going to spend
the rest of her life
in one of these.
Eric: Okay.
Now, it's just so
you can go to the park
on pretty days.
I'm not a cripple.
Janet: It's a long way
to the park.
Two blocks.
If I can't manage two blocks
what's the point in going?
Come on, Grandma.
Let's see what this baby
will do, huh?
I have things to do.
Why's she so crabby?
This is hard for her, Honey.
It's not exactly a
picnic for the rest of us.
[alarm beeping]
I didn't sleep last night.
Go back to sleep, Honey.
I'm just going to take Mom
out for about 15 minutes.
But I'm awake, Janet.
I'm awake and I'm awake.
Janet: Now, why don't
you walk for a minute?
No.
I can't.
Give me a break.
Sorry.
What are you doing?
I'm trying to
get some work done.
Did you pick up the laundry?
Oh, Hell.
No wonder I couldn't
find my green blouse.
Okay so crucify me, Janet.
You've taken care of the
laundry for the last 18 years.
I'm not used running all
these little errands.
Well you're gonna have
to iron yourself a shirt.
All right, I can
iron myself a shirt.
-Janet: Good.
-I know how to iron a shirt.
Morning.
I have a committee meeting
this afternoon, Eric.
I'd like you to come straight
home from school, okay?
I have to work on student
council campaign after school.
Honey, I need
you to take Mom out
for a few minutes
before it gets dark.
I can take myself
out on the porch.
Mother, when I ask
him to do something
I expect him to do it, okay?
Eric, don't wolf down
your food like that.
It's bad for the digestion.
For God's sake Emily.
The boy's 17 years old.
Whoa. Since when do we defend
him for eating like a horse?
Could I see you
for a minute in here?
Janet, when we decided
to bring your mom here
we said that we would
make as little change
in Eric's routine as possible.
I asked him to take
her out for five minutes.
Okay. What about us?
I wish you would understand.
If you would try--
Honey, we're all trying.
But it doesn't make sense.
It's not working.
I will cash in my retirement.
We can build another room
on the back of the house
with a bathroom, a big one.
You know she could have
her own sitting room.
Honey, what if your
mom has a heart attack
or she has a stroke,
or god forbid she falls down
and breaks her hip again.
Who's going to take care of her?
-We can't say what will happen.
-She'll need much more
than what you're giving her now.
-Where will you draw the line?
-That's not up to me.
Honey, you did not
make your mom old.
You can't fix it.
You have to accept it.
But that doesn't give me
the right to throw her away.
[sigh] Janet,
your mom's miserable.
She doesn't want Eric's room.
She doesn't want you waking up
in the morning to bathe her.
The poor woman has
enough to feel bad about
without forcing her
to impose on us.
I will not abandon my mother.
You really think that
if you sacrifice yourself
she'll lay a wreath of
laurel on your brow?
That's not true.
Richard: You want
to be her favorite.
This is your last chance
and you're afraid that if
you force her to face facts
she'll hold it against you.
Honey, is it really
worth all of this?
Be my favorite, hmm?
Hi, Mom.
How's everything?
-Good.
-Eric: That's good.
Need any help?
No, I can get it, thank you.
Mom, you know Tommy's folks?
They're nice people, right?
Yes, they're very nice.
Well, Tommy's brother is
away at college now
and they have an extra room
and his mother said
it would be cool
if I wanted to sort of
hang out in it for a while.
Move out?
Sort of, yeah. I mean
it's just up the street.
No.
Please.
I said no.
Emily: I told you the
swans wouldn't be out.
Janet: So the swans aren't out.
It's still pretty.
Emily: It's hot today.
Janet: Why don't you
take your sweater off?
Emily: All right.
Janet: Why don't we sit
and talk for a minute, okay?
Emily: Maybe I'll
hear from Gladys today.
I've written her twice.
Mom, I think it's
time we make some plans.
Plans?
Yeah, for you.
I'm way ahead of you, dear.
I invited Gladys to
come and live with me.
I'm sure she's just miserable
in that old age home.
Selling your father's car
and using the money
to paint the house.
I don't think that's
very realistic, Mom.
That's for me to decide.
You need more help
than Gladys can give you.
I'll be the judge
of what I need.
Mother, you are never
going home to live.
I know exactly
where this is leading
and the answer is no.
I am not living in
some dingy room in a...
death house
with some sweet sounding name.
I know that you're upset.
This is difficult but we
need to face some facts.
You're taking the rest
of my life away from me.
We're trying to help you.
Help me?
Right into the next world.
That's not true.
Then take me home.
And I don't mean your house
where it's perfectly clear
that I am not welcomed.
I'm sorry, Janet. I'm sorry.
I don't want to hurt you.
I still see what
you're trying to do
but oh my God, my God,
I want to go home.
I want the rest of my life.
Please.
Let me go home.
I just can't do that.
Forty years ago...
I could have children.
Twenty years ago I
could read all night
and get up and teach all day.
Five years ago I could drive
a car.
Last Easter I made
dinner as usual
and now...
look at me.
I'm...
You can't understand this.
And why should you?
It's like...
stars...
going out...
and I'm in the dark...
reaching.
My God, it's all unraveling.
Oh my God.
I can't stop.
Mom, I'm gonna be
right here with you.
I'm gonna be right here.
-Janet: Hi.
-Rob: Same to you.
You look good.
What's this Mom's telling
me about a nursing home?
Yeah well, I've looked at a few.
The ones I like
are so exorbitant.
I know, but a
nursing home, Janet...
That's pretty drastic.
I know but I can't
take care of her anymore.
She can't take care of herself.
When did she start
using the chair?
She doesn't need
it all the time.
-She looks so--
-She's okay.
Emily: Rob! Hello, Rob.
Hi Mom.
-Emily: Oh.
-Rob: Oh!
How are ya?
Is that jacket warm enough?
It's fine.
I say it's a little
chilly out here.
-I think I'll take Mom inside.
-Okay, I'll be right in.
All right, Good.
My God.
She's very excited
about your visit.
Thank you.
What is it?
She's so...
Janet: Old. I know.
It happened so suddenly.
Yeah.
I can't take care
of her anymore.
Yeah, I know, but a home?
Poor Mom.
It's the best thing.
Yeah.
I just take it all
for granted, you know?
Don't have any food at my place,
come over to Mom's.
A little short of cash,
Mom'll bail me out.
The laundry piles up,
she'll give me a hand.
I've never really
left home, have I?
Well, maybe it's
time to buy a washer.
Yeah, or marry one.
God, you're hopeless.
Hopeless.
Woman: We can put
her on the waiting list.
Well, the one place I like
is very expensive.
Would Medicaid pay part of it?
No, Medicaid covers
basic nursing home care
for people who have
very little resources.
Woman: You said your mother has
some money and some assets.
Yeah, but she's not rich.
What about health insurance?
Medicare.
Medicare isn't much help
if she ever needs a
long term hospital stay.
Well, what do you suggest?
See if her church sponsors
any type of elder care.
Most of them do.
If she were childless
or destitute
I'd have a lot more to offer.
Unfortunately, we live in a
society that leaves elder care
to the nearest living daughter.
I'll check with the church.
Thank you.
What are you doing?
Polishing silverware.
Mom.
I saw the most
wonderful place today.
It belongs to the church.
I really think it's the one.
It's just beautiful.
We can give them a lump sum
from the sale of your house
and they'll guarantee
all your expenses
for the rest of your life.
Is there a room
in the basement
where you sit and glue
scenes from nature
into conch shells that light up?
I'm going to take you
to see it on Saturday.
I have to teach at 1:00,
so if you need anything
I will be in my
office after 2:30.
[birds singing]
Janet: Impressive, isn't it?
Emily: You said
it was pleasant.
Janet: It's very pleasant.
Where's the dungeon?
We call this the sun room.
You can read, write letters,
or just rest if you want.
We have all kinds of
lectures and musical events.
A lot of our residents
play instruments.
Janet tells me you play
the piano, Mrs. Miller.
Oh, my husband was the
musician in the family.
Oh, Catherine, this is Emily.
Oh, I hear that
you're a bridge player.
Not for years now dear.
Catherine's writing
a book, on uh...
What's it on, Catherine?
Innate differences
between men and women.
All the art you see is
done by the residents.
We have a painting studio
and a woodworking room.
In fact, we put on quite
a crafts fair every fall.
The residents rooms are
on the second floor.
Well, I can't manage stairs.
Then let's take the elevator.
Well I have a million
things to do at home.
Would you rather
come back another time?
-Yes.
-No.
All our residents are here
because they choose to be.
I've never taken anyone
against his wishes.
Have you really
thought this over?
May we please
just see the rooms?
Is that all right
with you, Mrs. Miller?
Oh, all right.
[ringing]
-Ruth: Hello?
-Ruthie, it's me, Em.
Ruth: Emily.
It's good to hear your voice.
We've got a new librarian.
He wants everything on computer.
I told him this morning,
I said,
"You're not going to
computerize me, Buster."
I was thinking of
coming to visit you.
Oh, well.
Not just now, Em.
They want to put me away.
I thought maybe if I got out
of their hair for a while.
Ruth: I've got Gladys here.
Emily: I've written her
twice, she never answered.
Well, her daughter
has all those kids.
And they kicked her out
of that retirement place.
Emily: Kicked her out?
They found Alzheimers.
That place won't keep
people with Alzheimers.
Well, that settles it.
I'm going home and Gladys
is coming to live with me.
Ruth: Oh, no Em.
You don't understand.
She almost burned
the place down.
We're trying to find
something for her.
-I don't know--
-Who is it?
I have to watch
her every minute.
She's in and out.
I have to unplug my stove
when I leave for work.
Who is it?
It's Emily.
Emily!
Em?
Hello Gladys.
Oh, Em.
It's very bad.
Ruthie yells at me.
Are you coming home?
Gladys, tell me.
What happened?
Well I just couldn't
get used to it.
It was so different
and they had so many rules.
I left a pot on the stove.
Gladys: Twice.
They say I'm crazy.
You're coming to live with me
and we'll get someone
to come in part time.
Oh yes, Honey.
Yes I--
Gladys?
Don't talk to me
like I'm a damned dog!
What?
Oh.
Who is this?
Emily: Gladys, it's Emily.
Well, see what Henny says.
Em, she runs away.
I'm trying to get the
county to take her.
Don't tell her that.
Don't you tell her that!
What?
Gladys: Who...
Who are you talking to?
Go on into your room.
Ruth: Now just go!
I keep calling her daughter
but she won't come and get her.
I hate to put her
on the county, Em.
But it's all I can do to
keep going, you know?
Why use up the last bit of
strength you have to fight it?
I mean,
what did we think it
would be like at our age?
Sunsets?
You can't stop that.
What can we do, Ruthie?
Ruthie, what can we do?
Oh I don't know, I don't know.
Why don't you walk
a little bit, Mom?
It'll be good for ya.
No, not today.
You know, we are very lucky.
Some people have to wait years
to get into a place
like the McLinden Home.
I'm trying very hard
to see it that way.
Well, try harder.
Well, maybe I'll get lucky
and die before I have to go.
Janet?
I want to go back now.
You know how to
work that thing.
No I don't, I forgot.
Well, walk.
No. I can't.
I have done everything
I know how to do for you.
I have helped you in every
way I can possibly think of.
But you just sit there.
You sit in that chair
and you give up.
You've just given up.
Well I'm sorry.
-Do you love me?
-What?
-Janet, please.
-Answer me.
-Of course I love you.
Then why have you made
this so difficult for me?
I don't know--
Why have I spent
my whole adult life
trying to get you to notice me?
You stopped
needing me long ago.
No!
I will always need you.
Don't you get that?
Well, look what's ahead for me.
I am.
I'm looking straight ahead
and I see it.
Every time I look
at you I see it.
That's why every single
moment we have together
is so very precious to me.
Janet, at night when I
go to bed I close my eyes
and I try to let myself go.
I say to myself,
"It's okay, Emily.
It's okay, just
let yourself go."
And I go farther
and farther away
and it seems the
most natural thing.
But then in the morning
when I'm still here
I know I'm going to keep trying
to let myself go!
Fine.
Janet.
Janet, I'm afraid.
I'm afraid of what
is waiting for me
between now and dying!
Because underneath it
all I want to go on.
I, I, I...
I want to go on and on.
Well, then, let's go.
Let's go.
Well this is all
very fine inlaid wood.
Five hundred.
Two thousand.
It's gonna cost me a couple
hundred to get it refinished.
This is all
handcrafted, you know.
We're giving it away as it is.
-Yes.
-All right, 1,000.
Janet, your father brought
that home from an auction.
I always hated it.
Let them have it.
You advertised a freezer?
Yes, I did.
It's right in here.
It's yours.
I wish it were a ring, Em.
I love it.
I'll keep it forever.
Nothing lasts forever.
-Hi.
-Here, I'll do that.
Oh, it's okay,
I'm almost finished.
How is she?
Well, I think she's
doing fine, actually.
-How are you doing?
-Me? I'm fine.
I have a dustpan
around here just--
Janet.
Thank you for...
taking such good
care of our mother.
Rob, you're here.
Hi Mom.
Would you mind helping Richard
in the basement
for a little while?
I have to take Mom
to the cemetery.
Well, I'll take her.
No.
No, Janet can take me.
[birds singing]
Now then.
Where's Henny?
It's over here.
Over this way.
You won't come
here after I'm gone.
Of course I will.
No you won't.
And I don't want you to.
Oh, yes you do.
I know you think
I'm old and funny.
Well, you are old and funny.
Dearest child...
don't ever wonder if I love you.
I wouldn't be standing
here if it weren't for you.
Well, I wouldn't be standing
We taught you how to fly
and off you flew.
And I thank you for that, Mom.
That McLinden House.
Home.
I'm going to give it my best.
I'm still good for a
few hands of Bridge.
And I never had the time to
read the way I wanted to.
But what you said
about our time together,
I want that most of all.
Oh, Mom.
Your brother still needs you.
He just does.
-Stay in touch.
-I will, I will.
But listen.
And only because
it's on my mind.
You'll bury me in my blue satin
winter or summer.
I promise.
-And no lace.
-Promise.
Please be sure to show
them what to do with my hair.
We've been over
this twice already.
And in the summer,
I don't care if I'm in a coma,
you and Richard are
going to Europe.
God you're bossy.
There'll be plenty of money left
from the sale of the house.
We'll think about it, okay?
Oh, that Ruthie
and her damn plastic flowers!
Honestly.
I'm gonna take off, Ma.
I'll be up to see
you in a week or two.
I'll be expecting you.
But don't bring
your laundry, dear.
I'm gonna buy a
washer and a dryer
-with the proceeds of the house.
-Oh, good for you.
[laughing]
Rob, if you need
anything you call me, okay?
You do the same.
Ready?
Go ahead.
I'll be there in a minute.
Okay.
[door closes]
Oh, God.
Sweet heavenly days.
Richard: Emily?
-[door knocking]
-Janet: Mom!
Mom?
Emily?
Emily!
Emily? What are you doing?
It's all right Richard.
Just one minute.
It's time to go, Mom.
I know.
[sobbing]
I almost forgot
your father's letters.
[sighs]
I hid them up here
after the robbery.
This one...
This one in particular,
he wrote it somewhere
in France in a foxhole.
They thought that they
were surrounded by Germans
and that the jig was up.
Voiceover: "Dear Em,
my heart is with you now.
Our time together seems
like only a moment now.
A flicker in the wind.
But even here with
the creeping unknown
just over the hill..."
Lift up the knob to lock it.
I always meant to
have that fixed.
-Did you leave the light on?
-Yes.
Voiceover: "But even here
with the creeping unknown
just over the hill
I know that when two
hearts have joined
the bond becomes a lamp
that shines forever.
It shines now in
this terrible place
and no matter what happens
I believe that it will give you strength and comfort always.
There is only one
thing to do in life,
and that is to go on,
and go on bravely.
And if there is darkness
remember the fire that
shines for you in my heart.
Em, you are my
fire in the dark."
♪♪