♪ MUSIC
YOU'LL LOVE THIS CAR.
I KNEW YOU WOULD LOVE
THIS CAR.
AND YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU HAVEN'T EVEN
SEEN THE ENGINE YET.
LET'S POP THE HOOD ON THIS,
BABY.
YOU HAVE NOT SEEN ANYTHING--
SO TONY, YOU WANNA
TALK OPTIONS?
LET'S TALK SOME OPTIONS FOR
A MINUTE.
LOOK AT THIS, GOT A LUGGAGE
RACK, YOU GOT TINTED
WINDOWS, YOU GOT THE FOG
LIGHTS, POWER STEERING,
POWER BREAKS, WINDOWS,
DOORS, EVERYTHING.
LOADED UP, HUH?
OKAY.
ALRIGHT, THANKS A LOT
FOR COMING BY.
SORRY.
IS THAT THE CASSETTE?
A CASSETTE?
YOU WANT A CASSETTE?
YEAH, I GOT A LOT OF TAPES.
[KNOCKS]
I WANNA BUY A CAR!
ALL I NEED TO KNOW IS WHAT
IS IT GONNA TAKE TO SEE THAT
THIS CAR GETS DRIVEN OFF
THE LOT TONIGHT?
HUH, IT'S A BIG DECISION
ACTUALLY.
OF -- OF COURSE, IT'S A BIG
DECISION.
THAT'S WHY I'M HERE,
I'M GONNA HELP YOU
WITH THIS.
I'M TELLING YOU, IS THIS
A BEAUTY OR WHAT?
WE'RE -- WE'RE ALREADY
CLOSED. WE'RE [LAUGHS]
SORRY ABOUT
THAT BUT I -- I SAW THE --
I WANNA HEAR FROM YOU.
IS THIS THE CAR YOU LOVE?
LISTEN TO THIS.
WHAT WE HAVE GOT IS A
BEAUTIFUL FIRST-TIME
BUYER'S PLAN.
IT'S--
WHAT AM I SAYING?
WHAT AM I --
WE STOPPED THAT
PROMOTION LAST MONTH.
LAST MONTH?
YEAH.
UHM, WAIT A MINUTE.
WAIT, I GOT AN IDEA.
LOOK, MY FRIEND.
I -- I DON'T WANNA HAVE
ANY TROUBLE, ALRIGHT?
WE'RE -- WE'RE GETTING
READY TO CLOSE NOW AND
THIS --
MAYBE WE OUGHT TO GO
INSIDE AND FILL OUT
THE PAPERWORK.
FIRST, YOU GOT TO
PROMISE ME --
YOU GOT TO PROMISE ME YOU'RE
NOT GONNA TELL, NOT EVEN
YOUR FRIENDS, NOT EVEN YOUR
BEST FRIENDS OF WHAT I'M
GONNA OFFER YOU HERE,
ALRIGHT?
YEAH, I PROMISE.
ALRIGHT.
AND NOT EVEN YOUR RELATIVES,
TONY.
I'M SERIOUS.
I COULDN'T STAY IN BUSINESS
WITH WHAT I'M GONNA DO
FOR YOU.
LISTEN TO THIS, I'M --
TONY, WOULD YOU FORGIVE ME
FOR A SECOND?
I WANT YOU TO SIT BEHIND
THAT WHEEL.
THE KEYS ARE IN THERE,
TURN ON THAT STEREO, SEE HOW
IT SOUNDS TO YOU AND WOULD
YOU EXCUSE ME FOR JUST
A MINUTE?
SURE.
I'M GONNA BE RIGHT BACK.
OKAY?
♪ MUSIC
PUT IT IN THE BRIEFCASE.
ALRIGHT.
I HAVE A WIFE AND TWO KIDS.
[CRIES]
PLEASE, PLEASE.
IT'S MY LITTLE KID'S
BIRTHDAY TOMORROW.
SHUT UP!
HERE.
I'LL DO ANYTHING YOU SAY.
HERE, HERE.
[CRIES]
PLEASE DON'T HURT ME.
PLEASE, PLEASE
DON'T HURT ME.
HERE.
WHAT THE HELL?
OH, GOD!
[GUNSHOT]
[GRUNTS]
♪ MUSIC
MISTER, PLEASE!
PLEASE, PLEASE!
PLEASE DON'T HURT ME.
I -- I'VE GOT A WIFE AND TWO
KIDS, PLEASE.
[CRIES]
PLEASE DON'T HURT ME,
MISTER, PLEASE!
THIS AIN'T GONNA HURT
A BIT.
[CRIES]
[GUNSHOT]
♪ MUSIC
[CAR ENGINE STARTS]
[GUNSHOTS]
[CAR SCREECHES]
OH, DAMN!
HI, TONY.
HEY, TONY.
WHAT'S UP, MAN?
TONY, UH THE WIFE AND I
HAVE BEEN THINKING ABOUT
BUYING A CAR.
DO YOU KNOW ANYBODY?
SURE HE DOES.
TONY KNOWS THIS PLACE YOU
CAN GO GET CARS FOR NO MONEY
DOWN AND NO CREDIT CHECK.
OF COURSE, THEY AIN'T
GOT NO MORE CARS EITHER.
[LAUGHS]
VERY FUNNY.
SO LAST NIGHT I --
I HEARD THE
INSURANCE COMPANIES ARE
OFFERING A NEW RATE.
YEAH, YEAH, A BIG DISCOUNT
AS LONG AS YOU
DON'T KNOW TONY.
[LAUGHS]
[RADIO IN BACKGROUND]
I HEAR YOU'RE LOOKING FOR
A NEW CAR.
YOU KNOW, I DON'T THINK
THIS IS VERY FUNNY.
WHAT HAPPENED TO THE
SHOOTER?
HE GOT AWAY.
HE ESCAPED IN A CAR
THAT YOU WERE GONNA BUY?
WELL, YOU'RE RIGHT.
THAT ISN'T VERY FUNNY.
IT'S HUMILIATING.
WHAT IS IT?
IS IT BECAUSE I'M A ROOKIE?
IS THAT WHAT --
IS THAT WHY I CAN'T WIN
WITH YOU GUYS?
NO. BEING A ROOKIE HAS GOT
NOTHING TO DO WITH IT.
IF I'D BLOWN THESE GUYS
AWAY INSTEAD OF HANDLING
WITH MY FIST, THAT,
THAT WOULD HAVE MADE ME
A HERO, RIGHT?
NO, NOT A HERO.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO KILL
SOMEBODY TO GET THE
MESSAGE ACROSS.
NO, YOU DON'T.
BUT AT LEAST YOU'RE NEVER
MISUNDERSTOOD.
[RADIO]20 CRASH 12.
20 CRASH 12.
WE HAVE A REPORT OF A 415
IN PROGRESS.
GANG ACTIVITY IN THE
2000 BLOCK OF MAYFIELD
POSSIBLE WEAPON INVOLVED.
APPROACH WITH EXTREME CAUTION.
20 CRASH 12 ROGER.
SHOW US RESPONDENT, CODE 3.
YOU SHOT MY BABY SISTER
IN THE HEAD.
I SHOULD BLOW YOU
AWAY RIGHT NOW.
HEY, MAN.
I'M SORRY, I DIDN'T MEAN TO.
SHUT UP!
[GRUNTS]
♪ MUSIC
SAY GOODNIGHT, ASSHOLE!
[GUNSHOT]
ARE YOU ALRIGHT?
YEAH.
YEAH, I'M FINE THANKS.
FOR WHAT?
FOR THIS.
OH, YOU MEAN FOR SAVING
YOUR LIFE?
I COULD HAVE HANDLED
IT, MAN.
OH, SURE. I KNOW. I KNOW.
OH, HEY.
BY THE WAY, YOU MIGHT NEED
THIS SOMEDAY.
COME ON, SHITHEAD.
SHIT.
♪ MUSIC
[LAUGHS]
THIS IS A SERIOUS
CONVERSATION.
THAT'S RIGHT.
YOU TOOK YOUR SUIT OFF
A FEW TIMES, YOU CAN'T
[LAUGHS]
GET IN WITH THIS, YOU KNOW
WHAT I'M SAYING?
SHIT.
AT LEAST ONE.
[INDISTINCT]
[SIGHS]
NOW, BETTY'S LEAVING ME
FOR SOMEBODY ELSE.
REALLY?
YEAH.
OH, WHO'S THE LUCKY GUY.
[LAUGHS]
THAT WAS A VERY INSENSITIVE
THING FOR YOU TO SAY, MAN.
I'M IN PAIN HERE, YOU KNOW.
YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT.
WHO'S THE LUCKY GIRL?
[LAUGHS]
OH, YOU'RE REAL ASSHOLE,
FLANNIGAN.
OH, BOY, ARE YOU BRUTAL
WITH THOSE ONELINERS.
HUH.
HEY, I HEARD YOU TRIED TO
SCARE SOMEONE TO DEATH
TODAY WITH YOUR BARE HANDS.
LIGHTEN UP, FLANNIGAN.
WHY DON'T YOU HAVE ANOTHER
KEG OF SCOTCH?
YESTERDAY, YOU WERE A HERO.
TODAY, YOU COULD HAVE BEEN
DEAD MEAT IF YOUR PARTNER
HADN'T BEEN THERE.
WELL, THAT'S WHAT PARTNERS
ARE FOR, I THINK.
BACK EACH OTHER UP,
DO STUFF LIKE THAT.
YEAH, I'M GLAD YOU TWO
GUYS FOUND EACH OTHER
ANYWAY.
NOW YOU GOT A DESIGNATED
DRIVER.
[LAUGHS]
YOU KNOW, I'M NOT
EMBARRASSED FOR THE FACT THAT
I DON'T EVEN RECOGNIZE
MYSELF IN THE
MIRROR WHEN I LEAVE A BAR.
AND YOU SHOULDN'T BE.
HE'S RIGHT,
YOU ARE AN ASSHOLE.
THEY'RE BOTH VERY, VERY
SENSITIVE TODAY,
AREN'T THEY?
HEY, HAVE A SEAT.
JOIN US.
ARE YOU BOYS COPS?
DO WE LOOK LIKE COPS?
HE DOES.
YEAH.
WELL, THAT'S ABOUT IT FOR
ME GUYS.
SEE YOU TOMORROW.
WELL, I WAS JUST LEAVING
MYSELF.
MIND GIVING ME A RIDE HOME?
I --
NO, NO.
GO ON.
YOU GO AHEAD.
YOU DON'T WANT HER
WALKING HOME ALONE,
NOT IN THIS NEIGHBOURHOOD.
YEAH.
HE'S RIGHT.
ALRIGHT.
GOODNIGHT.
[LAUGHS]
WHEW!
YOU LIKE THAT?
DAMN RIGHT.
NO WONDER YOUR WIFE IS
LEAVING YOU.
WHY YOU SAY THAT?
THE CHICK IS A GUY.
[LAUGHS]
YOU'RE AWFUL QUIET THIS
MORNING.
YEAH, WELL --
SO HOW DID IT GO LAST
NIGHT?
IT WAS A STRANGE EVENING.
I'D RATHER NOT TALK ABOUT
IT IF YOU DON'T MIND.
GAIL! COFFEE, PLEASE.
YOU KNOW WHAT THE
CHOLESTEROL CONTENT
OF THAT IS?
YOU ADD THAT TO YOUR DRINKING
AND YOUR AGE THEN YOU --
WOULD YOU GIVE ME THE
KETCHUP, PLEASE?
IS SOMETHING WRONG?
I DON'T MEAN TO BE A PEST.
I HAD THE BEST INTEREST AT
HEART HERE.
I SAW A GUY IN THE NEWS THE
OTHER NIGHT.
HE WAS CELEBRATING HIS 100TH
BIRTHDAY.
HE SAID THE SECRET TO A LONG
LIFE IS TO HAVE 2 SHOTS OF
SCOTCH EVERYDAY, A GOOD
CIGAR EVERY AFTERNOON AND
LOTS AND LOTS OF
FRIED FOODS.
I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
SUIT YOURSELF.
YOU JUST MADE THAT UP,
DIDN'T YOU?
MAYBE I DID,
MAYBE I DIDN'T.
OKAY.
IF YOU MADE IT UP,
WHAT'S THE POINT?
THE POINT IS THIS,
IF YOU STOP PESTERING ME,
I'LL STOP LYING TO YOU.
GAIL, MORE COFFEE PLEASE.
♪ MUSIC
[GRUNTS]
[HEAVY BREATHING]
♪ MUSIC
SHIT.
[GUNSHOT]
COME ON.
COME ON!
COME ON, COME ON.
AGAINST THE CAR, ASSHOLE!
WHAT TOOK YOU SO LONG?
WATCH THIS GUY, WILL YOU?
PRETTY BIG MAN WITH A GUN
IN YOUR HANDS.
SHUT YOUR MOUTH.
IF YOU DIDN'T HAVE
THAT GUN --
YEAH?
YOU'D WHAT?
TONIGHT, YOUTH CENTER ON
MAIN STREET.
YOU'RE GONNA BE LOCKED
UP TONIGHT.
YEAH, DON'T BET ON IT.
I'M NOT A [INDISTINCT]
SHIT, IF YOU GOT THE BALLS.
YEAH?
YEAH, YEAH.
[DOOR CLOSES]
LISTEN.
WOULD YOU MIND IF I STOP AND
GET A LITTLE SOMETHING
TO EAT?
I GOT A LITTLE HUNGRY --
OH, SHUT UP.
DRIVE.
HUH?
JUST DRIVE.
YOU SURE?
♪ MUSIC
YOU WANNA
BUY SOME ROCKS?
WHAT?
DO YOU WANNA SCORE SOME
CRACK?
WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
LATOYA.
LATOYA, WHERE IS YOUR MOM
AND DAD?
I AIN'T GOT NO DAD.
[SIGH]
WHY DON'T YOU LET ME
TAKE YOU HOME?
CAN'T GO HOME IF I DON'T
SELL NO ROCK.
WELL, I'M NOT GONNA BUY
ANY SO WHY DON'T YOU GO ON
HOME.
I CAN'T.
WHY?
'CAUSE MOMMA SAID I CAN'T
COME HOME WITHOUT NO MONEY.
COME HERE.
[SIGHS]
MOMMA DON'T MEAN
NOTHING BY IT.
SHE'S SICK, YOU KNOW.
YEAH, I KNOW.
NO, TAKE THE MONEY AND
FORGET THE DRUGS.
BUT MOMMA KEEPS TRACK OF
STUFF.
ALRIGHT.
HM, THANKS MISTER.
YOU'RE GOING HOME, OKAY?
♪ MUSIC
[EXPLOSION]
YEAH, YOU GOT IT.
YOU'RE READY?
YEAH.
SO WHERE IS BRUCE LEE
TONIGHT?
HAVEN'T YOU HEARD?
HE'S DOING A HIGH NOON AT
THE BOY'S CLUB TONIGHT.
WELL, MAYBE HE'S OBSESSED
WITH HIS MANHOOD.
AFTER HIS SHE-MALE
LAST NIGHT.
IT'S NOT VERY NICE,
FLANNIGAN.
AH, THE WORLD AIN'T NICE.
BIG DEAL.
COP GETS SUCKERED BY TV,
HE DESERVES WHATEVER HAPPENS
TO HIM.
WELL, MAYBE THE KID NEEDS
SOME TIME TO ADJUST.
HE'S A LITTLE DIFFERENT,
THAT'S ALL.
[LAUGHS]
WELL, TIME HE GETS WITH THE
PROGRAM.
WHAT PROGRAM IS THAT?
DRUNKEN ASSHOLE PROGRAM?
AT LEAST I STILL GOT
MY WIFE.
YEAH, WHO SHOULD BE HOME
RIGHT ABOUT NOW SUCKING OFF
A VACUUM SALESMAN.
HOW YOU KNOW SHE'S GOT
AN APPOINTMENT WITH THE
SWEEPER MAN?
I DON'T --
I'M SURE IT'S PERFECTLY
INNOCENT
YOU ASSHOLE!
[LAUGHS]
WHAT WAS THAT ALL ABOUT?
MY SOON TO BE EX TOLD ME
LAST WEEK SHE HAS AN
APPOINTMENT TONIGHT WITH THE
SWEEPER SALESMAN WITH
FLANNIGAN'S WIFE.
NOT BAD.
[LAUGHS]
SO, TONY OUGHT TO BE WARMING
UP RIGHT ABOUT NOW, HUH?
YEAH, SO?
NOTHING.
JUST, YOU KNOW, HE'S GONNA
BE OUTNUMBERED AS ALL.
LOOK, HAPPY, I'M NOT
GOING, OKAY?
OKAY, OKAY.
WELL, YOU KNOW, I WAS JUST
SAYING.
YOU KNOW, HIM BEING YOUR
PARTNER AND ALL.
I SAID I'M NOT GOING AND
THAT'S FINAL.
OKAY, OKAY.
I'M OUT OF HERE.
♪ MUSIC
THANKS FOR COMING, MAN.
I WAS JUST ON MY WAY HOME.
BESIDE I TOLD YOU THE GUY
WOULDN'T SHOW UP, DIDN'T I?
♪ MUSIC
SO, YOU GOT A THOUSAND
COPS WITH GUNS WAITING
OUTSIDE?
JUST YOU AND ME, BUDDY.
AND ME.
WHAT'D YOU SAY?
I WAS SAYING THE LORD'S
PRAYER.
LET'S GET IT ON.
IN THE RING.
♪ MUSIC
[BELL RINGS]
[CROWD CHEERING]
♪ MUSIC
[GRUNTS]
[LAUGHS]
ALRIGHT, TONY BOY.
♪ MUSIC
ALL YOU GUYS, CHILL.
JOHNNY, CHILL.
DO WHAT I SAY.
♪ MUSIC
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
THANKS.
DON'T THANK ME, MAN.
YOU'RE MINE NEXT TIME.
ALRIGHT.
SAME TIME, SAME PLACE.
I'LL BE HERE.
I THOUGHT THAT WENT
PRETTY WELL.
♪ MUSIC
[LAUGHS]
THE REST OF THE WORLD
IS A LITTLE WACKY.
THANK YOU.
SURE.
YOU KNOW, IT'S FABULOUS,
REALLY.
THANK YOU.
DADDY TELLS ME YOU DON'T
APPROVE OF HIS EATING HABIT.
OH, HE DOESN'T EXACTLY EAT
FROM THE [INDISTINCT] MENU.
[INDISTINCT]
I UH, THINK THAT MAYBE --
HEY, DO YOU THINK MY
DAUGHTER HAS GOT NOTHING TO
DO TO SIT AROUND HERE ALL
DAY AND COOKING FOR ME?
CALM DOWN, DADDY.
HE'S NOT ATTACKING ME.
LOOK, I'M SORRY, OKAY?
BUT IT'S JUST THAT SOME
PEOPLE GET THE WRONG IDEA.
THEY THINK THAT JUST BECAUSE
SUSAN IS --
THE WORD IS BLIND.
OH, THE TRUTH IS THAT SHE
TAKES BETTER CARE OF
ME THAN I TAKE CARE OF
MYSELF.
[LAUGHS]
THAT'S NOT TOO HARD TO
BELIEVE.
SHE ALSO TEACHES MUSIC
5 DAYS A WEEK AT UCLA,
VOLUNTEERS 3 NIGHTS A WEEK
AT THE WEST SIDE BRAILLE
INSTITUTE, TAKES CARE OF
THE HOUSE, CLEANS MY
CLOTHES, TAKES CARE OF THE
GARDEN --
WHAT DO YOU DO?
SHHH!
HE DOES HIS BEST TO
TRY TO MAKE ME FEEL NEEDED.
I DO A HELL OF A JOB WITH
THAT, DON'T I, KIDDO?
YOU DO.
[LAUGHS]
ANYONE FOR DESSERT?
OH, NO.
OH, HEY TONY.
YOU GOT TO TASTE IT.
SUSAN MADE IT HERSELF.
I BOUGHT IT MYSELF.
♪ MUSIC
SHE IS QUITE A WOMAN.
HOW COME YOU DIDN'T
INTRODUCE HER TO ME BEFORE?
BECAUSE SHE IS QUITE A
WOMAN.
YOU MUST GET QUITE A VIEW
WITH THAT THING, HUH?
GARNET, MY WIFE, SHE
BOUGHT IT FOR ME WHEN WE
MOVED IN.
ON A CLEAR NIGHT WITH A
FULL MOON, MAN, YOU CAN
SEE FOREVER.
TAKE A LOOK.
OH, YEAH. THAT'S GREAT.
HEY, LOOK OUT! LOOK OUT!
I'M SORRY.
I FEEL SO CLUMSY SOMETIMES.
NO, NO, NO. IT'S MY FAULT.
THIS CHAIR, I PULLED IT.
NO, IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT.
YOU HAD NO WAY OF KNOWING.
I'LL GO CLEAN IT UP.
SUSAN, HONEY, IT'S OKAY.
I'M SORRY.
♪ MUSIC
UH, I'M REALLY SORRY.
LOOK, I TOLD YOU IT'S NOT
YOUR FAULT.
OH, OKAY. I JUST --
I JUST WANTED THINGS TO GO
RIGHT.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
I MEAN I WANTED TO --
I WANTED TO ASK YOU OUT.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO
ASK ME OUT.
NO.
I KNOW I DON'T HAVE TO DO
ANYTHING.
IT'S JUST -- SEE,
I HAVE THIS THING ABOUT
BEING SEEN IN PUBLIC WITH
A BEAUTIFUL WOMAN.
I DON'T THINK SO.
SO YOU'RE BUSY FRIDAY
NIGHT, RIGHT?
NO.
YOU ARE NOW.
[DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES]
SO I HEAR YOU'RE TAKING
MY DAUGHTER OUT.
YEAH, ON FRIDAY.
SHE DOESN'T NEED CHARITY.
YEAH, I KNOW THAT.
SHE'S A BEAUTIFUL GIRL --
YOU'RE DAMN RIGHT.
SHE IS AND SHE'S A LOT MORE
THAN THAT.
AND DON'T YOU EVER
FORGET IT.
I WON'T. GOODNIGHT.
27, 28 --
NOW, GO ALL
THE WAY DOWN.
29 AND 3-0!
YEAH, YEAH!
[LAUGHS]
ALRIGHT, GOOD!
I KNEW YOU CAN DO IT.
[LAUGHS]
SHIT.
[INDISTINCT]
PAY UP.
YEAH, YOU KNOW --
YOU KNOW, WE COULD TAKE
SOME MONEY OUT THE
SHERIFF'S DEPARTMENT WITH
THIS GUY.
NO. WE MAKE MONEY LATER.
PAY ME NOW.
I KNOW YOU, FLANNIGAN.
I KNOW YOU.
PAY ME NOW.
IT'S $10, RIGHT?
NO, 15.
15?
WHEN DID IT BECOME 15?
OH, WAIT!
I WAS TELLING YOU, LISTEN.
SO ANNIE HAD THE KID
CHALLENGES ME TO A
BOXING MATCH.
[LAUGHS]
CAN YOU BELIEVE THAT?
SO WHEN ARE YOU GONNA
FIGHT HIM?
OH, WHAT ARE YOU SERIOUS?
OH, YEAH. WHY NOT?
TONY FOUGHT A KID THE OTHER
NIGHT.
OH, SHIT!
THAT'S HOW THIS WHOLE THING
GOT STARTED.
YEAH, GREAT.
THANKS A LOT, TONY.
I DON'T THINK IT'S SUCH A
TERRIBLE IDEA.
COUPLE OF TOUGH GUYS ON EACH
SIDES, SQUARE OFF,
NOBODY GETS DEAD.
NAH, I DON'T KNOW.
SOME GIRL CHALLENGED ME
YESTERDAY.
OH, IT'S AN EPIDEMIC.
YOU SEE WHAT YOU STARTED
HERE, TONY?
I TOLD HER I'D MEET HER
TONIGHT.
I WOULDN'T MISS THIS FOR
THE WORLD.
[LAUGHS]
YOU'RE GONNA SHOW UP
TONIGHT, AREN'T YOU, ERNIE?
I DON'T KNOW, MAYBE.
YOU'RE NOT TELLING US YOU
FORGOT HOW TO BOX, ARE YOU?
HELL, NO!
HEY, I CAN STILL KICK SOME ASS.
COME ON, HEY, ERNIE.
ALRIGHT, ALRIGHT.
COME ON.
[INDISTINCT]
WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
ARE YOU ALRIGHT?
I'M ERNIE BLAKE.
[INDISTINCT]
I HEREBY TAKE YOU,
MADONNA, TO BE MY
LAWFUL WEDDED WIFE.
COME ON,
GET HIM OUT OF HERE.
COME ON, ERNIE.
COME ON, COME ON.
YOU KNOW, I'M NOT
NORMALLY ATTRACTED
TO FAT CHICKS
BUT I ALWAYS END UP
WITH THEM.
YEAH, ALRIGHT.
ALRIGHT, ALRIGHT.
OH, SHIT!
OH, MY DEAR.
[CROWD CHEERING]
WE'RE LOOKING PRETTY GOOD.
WE'RE LOOKING LIKE SHIT.
LOOK AROUND, JOHNNY.
WHAT DO YOU SEE?
I SEE A GYM FULL OF COPS AND
HOMIES, MAN.
WHAT I SEE IS A SERIOUS
DECREASE IN SALES.
LOT OF PEOPLE SITTING HERE,
YELLING AND SCREAMING,
NO BUY NOTHING, WHEN
THEY SHOULD BE BUYING.
I DON'T LIKE PEOPLE
GETTING IN MY POCKET.
YOU KNOW WHAT I'M SAYING?
I'LL SHOW YOU, MAN.
SHOW ME.
[CROWD CHEERING]
[GRUNTS]
BACK OFF!
[CROWD CHEERING]
[GRUNTS]
♪ MUSIC
[CROWD CHEERING]
[INDISTINCT]
HEY, TYRONE!
♪ MUSIC
WHAT'S GOING ON?
NOTHING, MAN.
I WAS JUST GOING HOME.
LIKED THE FIGHTS?
YEAH, THEY WERE OKAY.
WELL, I DON'T LIKE THEM.
AIN'T PLANNING ON
GOING BACK.
TAKE IT, MAN.
FRIENDS, RIGHT?
RIGHT.
GET ON HOME NOW.
THIS IS A DANGEROUS
NEIGHBOURHOOD UNLESS YOU
GOT THE RIGHT KIND OF
FRIENDS.
YOU KNOW WHAT I'M SAYING?
YEAH.
YOU BE CAREFUL WITH MY
DAUGHTER.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND?
YES, SIR. BRIAN.
FIRST DATE WITH MY DAUGHTER,
YOU CAN CALL ME SIR.
YES, SIR.
YOU BE CAREFUL, HONEY.
I WILL.
YOU SURE YOU WOULDN'T
WANT TO TAKE MY CAR?
NO, I LOVE MOTORCYCLES.
YEAH?
YEAH.
YOU EVER DRIVEN A UH --
IT'S A WONDER YOU CAN TALK
ALL WITH YOUR FOOT AND
YOUR MOUTH ALL THE TIME.
YEAH, I GET A LOT OF
PRACTICE.
SO WHERE ARE WE GOING?
WELL, I THOUGHT WE'D GO
TO THE COLLEGE AND TAKE
SOME CLASSICAL MUSIC.
I HEARD THEY'RE HAVING SOME
KIND OF CHAMBER MUSIC
TONIGHT.
IS THAT WHAT YOU USUALLY
DO ON A FIRST DATE?
TAKE A GIRL TO HEAR
CHAMBER MUSIC?
NO.
LOOK, DON'T TREAT ME LIKE
I HAVE THE PLAGUE.
EITHER TREAT ME LIKE A WOMAN
OR WE'LL JUST FORGET THE
WHOLE THING.
ALRIGHT.
OKAY.
SO I WANT YOU TO THINK OF
YOUR FAVORITE ROMANTIC
PLACE AND TAKE ME THERE.
[LAUGHS]
I DON'T THINK YOU'D
LIKE IT.
OH, YEAH.
OKAY.
NOW, HERE WE ARE.
HOLD ON A SEC.
GIVE ME YOUR HAND.
ALRIGHT.
[ENGINE STARTING]
♪ MUSIC
I REMEMBER A VIEW EXACTLY
LIKE THE ONE YOU DESCRIBED.
DAD TOOK MOM AND I TO
DINNER AT THE TOWERS.
IT WAS THE MOST BEAUTIFUL
SUNSET I EVER SAW.
IT WAS INCREDIBLE.
THAT WAS ON MY 16TH
BIRTHDAY, LESS THAN A YEAR
BEFORE THE ACCIDENT.
YOU KNOW,
YOU DON'T HAVE
TO TALK ABOUT THAT IF YOU
DON'T WANT TO.
NO, IT'S ALRIGHT.
I GOT OVER THE UNFAIRNESS
OF BEING BLIND REAL FAST.
AFTER ALL, MY MOTHER WAS
DEAD AND DAD --
IN A STRANGE WAY,
HE'S NEEDING ME SO BADLY
REALLY HELPED ME OUT.
FOR NEARLY 6 MONTHS AFTER
THE ACCIDENT, HE WOULD PUT
ME TO BED EVERY NIGHT AND
TRY TO ACT CHEERFUL.
AND THEN HE WOULD GO ON
HIS ROOM AND CRY HIMSELF
TO SLEEP.
I JUST FIGURED MY JOB WAS TO
HELP HIM STOP CRYING.
YOU'RE A VERY
BRAVE WOMAN.
STRONG, MAYBE.
BUT BRAVE, I DON'T KNOW.
WHAT OTHER CHOICE DID
I HAVE?
I WANTED TO LIVE AND I
WANTED MY DAD TO LIVE,
SO I DIDN'T REALLY HAVE ANY
OTHER CHOICE BUT TO BE
STRONG.
BUT YOU MAKE IT SOUND SO
SIMPLE.
LIFE IS SIMPLE.
PEOPLE JUST MAKE IT
COMPLICATED.
NO ONE'S EVER TOUCHED YOU
EXACTLY LIKE THAT BEFORE,
AND NO ONE WILL EVER AGAIN.
AND NO ONE'S EVER KISSED
YOU EXACTLY LIKE THAT
BEFORE, AND NO ONE --
♪ MUSIC
I DIDN'T LAY A HAND ON
HER, OKAY?
YEAH, I KNOW.
YOU DID WORSE THAN THAT.
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
SHE LIKES YOU.
SHE LIKES ME.
DON'T SOUND SO HAPPY
ABOUT IT, ALRIGHT?
WHY?
YOU KNOW, I LIKE HER TOO.
WELL, IT MEANS THAT
SHE'S PROBABLY GONNA WANNA
SEE YOU AGAIN.
AND WHAT'S WRONG WITH THAT?
I'M NOT SUCH A BAD GUY,
AM I?
YOU DON'T GET IT, DO YOU?
I MEAN, YOU JUST DON'T
FUCKING GET IT, DO YOU?
MY DAUGHTER DESERVES
MORE THAN "I'M NOT SUCH A
BAD GUY."
SO SHE DESERVES MORE THAN
A COP, RIGHT?
NO, NOT MORE.
JUST NOT A COP.
WHY? WHAT IS IT?
THE PAYS OR THE HOURS? WHAT?
NO, BECAUSE 10 YEARS FROM
NOW, SOME ASSHOLE BLOWS YOUR
BRAINS OUT AND I'M NOT AROUND.
WHO'S GONNA TAKE CARE OF
MY DAUGHTER, HUH?
TELL ME.
WHO'S GONNA TAKE CARE OF MY
DAUGHTER?
WHO?
YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE
TO GET YOURSELF AN AGENT KID.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING
ABOUT?
WHAT, YOU DON'T READ
THE PAPERS?
NO, WHY?
LA TRIBUNES BEEN COMING
DOWN ON THE FIGHTS.
SOMEONE TOLD THEM YOU
STARTED IT.
OH, SHIT.
YOU'RE AN INNER CITY
HERO, KID. GET USED TO IT.
CONGRATULATIONS.
YOU JUST BECAME A TARGET.
♪ MUSIC
HEY, WHAT DO YOU MAKE OF
THOSE TWO IN THE
MOTEL PARKING LOT?
I JUST DON'T WANT YOU TO
MISUNDERSTAND ME.
NO, I -- KNOW HOW YOU FEEL.
SUSAN'S --
SUSAN'S YOUR DAUGHTER.
YOU HAVEN'T GOT A CLUE AS
TO HOW I FEEL.
SUSAN IS A VERY SPECIAL
PERSON
AND I DON'T MEAN SPECIAL LIKE
HANDICAPPED.
WHEN HER MOTHER DIED, I FELT
LIKE THE WHOLE WORLD WAS
GONNA CAVE IN ON ME.
I KISSED HER GOODBYE ONE
MORNING AND A COUPLE OF
HOURS LATER, SHE'S LYING
UNDER A SEMI.
I NEVER GOT TO SAY --
I JUST NEVER GOT TO SAY A LOT
OF THINGS.
SUSAN AND I,
WE DEPEND ON EACH
OTHER A LOT.
AND EVERY ONCE IN A WHILE.
SOME GUY WILL COME ALONG.
AND WHY NOT?
I MEAN SHE'S A GREAT
LOOKING GIRL.
AND THEN THEY START THINKING
THAT JUST BECAUSE SHE'S BLIND,
THAT SHE OUGHT TO BE
HAPPY THAT SHE'S
GOING OUT WITH ANYBODY.
YOU SEE, SHE CAN'T
ALWAYS TELL THAT
THESE GUYS ARE BULLSHIT
ARTISTS AND ONCE IN A
WHILE SHE STARTS
LIKING ONE OF THEM.
AND I'M JUST REAL PROTECTIVE,
YOU KNOW,
JUST REAL PROTECTIVE.
NOBODY IS GONNA
MAKE MY BABY CRY.
I DON'T GIVE A DAMN HOW
PROTECTIVE I AM.
SHE DOESN'T HARM ANYBODY
AND I'LL BE DAMNED IF
ANYBODY IS GONNA HURT HER.
NOT ANYMORE.
YOU KNOW WHAT I'M SAYING?
BRIAN, I'M NOT LIKE THOSE
OTHER GUYS.
SO, WHAT DO YOU THINK IS
GOING ON WITH THOSE TWO?
LET'S GO FIND OUT.
YEAH, LET'S.
♪ MUSIC
GOOD EVENING, SIR.
SOMETHING WRONG,
OFFICER?
MAY I ASK WHAT YOU'RE
DOING HERE?
NOTHING.
ARE YOU WAITING
FOR SOMEONE?
NO, WE'RE JUST TALKING.
IT'S KIND OF A STRANGE
PLACE TO STOP AND CHAT,
HUH?
ARE YOU REGISTERED HERE?
NO.
WHAT? IS THERE SOME KIND
OF LAW AGAINST TALKING?
WHO'S THAT?
NOBODY.
WHERE IS SHE?
I DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU'RE
TALKING ABOUT.
WHERE IS SHE?
THIS IS POLICE BRUTALITY!
IT'S GONNA BE A LOT MORE
THAN THAT UNLESS YOU TELL ME
WHERE SHE IS.
NOW, WHERE IS SHE?
15! SHE'S IN ROOM 15!
KEYS. GIVE ME YOUR KEYS.
[GRUNTS]
YOUR WRIST.
GIVE ME YOUR WRIST.
♪ MUSIC
[KNOCKING]
POLICE! OPEN UP!
OPEN UP!
YES?
WHERE'S THE GIRL?
WHAT GIRL?
IT'S OVER, PAL.
WE JUST TALKED TO HER PARENTS.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU'RE
TALKING ABOUT, MAN.
LOOK, YOU CAN'T COME IN HERE.
YOU CAN'T DO THIS.
THIS IS ILLEGAL, MAN.
YOU JUST CAN'T DO THIS.
THIS ISN'T LEGAL, MAN!
SHUT UP!
ARE YOU ALRIGHT, HONEY?
YOU'RE NOT DADDY.
NO, I'M NOT.
BUT I WANT YOU TO KNOW THAT
EVERYTHING'S
GONNA BE ALRIGHT.
WOULD YOU LIKE ME TO CALL
YOU DADDY?
NO.
I WANT YOU TO GO IN THE
BATHROOM AND PUT YOUR
CLOTHES ON, OKAY?
OKAY.
♪ MUSIC
[SCREAMS]
[GLASSES BREAKING]
IT'S GONNA COST YOU.
IT WAS WORTH IT.
♪ MUSIC
I'M TELLING YOU, MAN.
GERARDO DOESN'T WANT YOU
HANGING WITH THAT COP!
I DON'T CARE WHAT GERARDO
THINKS --
YEAH, WE --
I STOPPED HANGING AROUND
THEM --
I'M TELLING YOU SOMETHING,
MAN.
SINCE WHEN YOU BECOME A --,
HEY, WHAT'S THE TROUBLE?
OUR LITTLE BROTHER DOESN'T
LIKE COPS.
IT RUNS IN THE FAMILY.
WHAT'S THIS ALL ABOUT?
THEY WERE THIS MORNING,
JUST STREETS AND BUILDINGS.
SOMETIMES, IT'S GUNS
AND KNIVES.
YEAH, WELL, IT USED TO BE
MORE THAN THAT.
PEOPLE ARE NEEDED TO BE
REMINDED OF WHAT THEY
ALREADY KNOW.
I GOT TO GO.
CAN I HAVE AN AUTOGRAPH?
YOU'RE PRETTY CYNICAL,
YOU KNOW THAT?
YEAH.
WELL, IT COMES WITH THE
TERRITORY.
AT LEAST WITH SOME THINGS,
ARE GETTING BETTER.
HUH, STILL THE SAME SHIT
GOING DOWN OUTSIDE.
YOU MEAN LESS
THAN LAST WEEK.
MAYBE.
HEY, TONY.
YEAH?
YOU AIN'T THE WORST COP
I EVER MET.
THANKS.
HEY, JIMMY.
YEAH?
GET A HAIRCUT, MAN.
[GRUNTS]
STEVEN, YOU OKAY?
YOU'RE ALRIGHT, MAN.
HEY, GUYS!
LET'S CLOSE UP, OKAY?
LET'S CLOSE SHOP.
IT'S GETTING LATE.
HEY, TONY!
COMPADRE!
GIVE IT UP, MAN.
YOU'RE LOOKING GOOD.
YOU GOT A MINUTE FOR AN
OLD FRIEND?
YEAH, SURE.
WELL, WE COME A LONG WAY
SINCE THE HOOD.
YEAH, IN SOME WAYS.
LOOK.
I KNOW WE LIVE ON
OPPOSITE SIDES OF THE STREET.
AT LEAST WE LEARN TO
RESPECT EACH OTHER.
I THINK WE NEED TO LEARN TO
FORGET EACH OTHER.
FORGET?
YOU SAVED MY LIFE ONCE, T.
I AIN'T GONNA NEVER
FORGET THAT.
IT'S NO BIG DEAL.
YEAH?
WELL, IT WAS A BIG DEAL FOR
ME. THE GUY HAD A GUN TO MY
HEAD AND WAS
GONNA BLOW IT OFF.
YOU KNOW,
YOU WOULD HAVE DONE
THE SAME THING FOR ME.
YOU KNOW, PEOPLE LIKE TO
THINK THEY DO THE RIGHT THING.
THE FACT IS, MAN, MOST
PEOPLE AIN'T GOT THE BALLS.
GERARDO, WHAT IS THIS?
THIS AIN'T NO WALK DOWN
MEMORY LANE.
THIS THING YOU GOT GOING
ON DOWN HERE.
THE FIGHTS.
YEAH,
THEY'RE PROBABLY MAKING
THIS SOME KIND OF
[INDISTINCT] DEAL.
I HAVEN'T REALLY THOUGHT
ABOUT MUCH.
WELL, I'D THINK ABOUT IT
IF I WERE YOU.
SOUNDS LIKE A THREAT.
NO.
I NEVER THREATEN A FRIEND.
WHILE WE'RE KEEPING THESE
KIDS OFF THE STREETS, THEY
CAN'T BE TOO GOOD FOR
BUSINESS, CAN IT?
OH, YOU KNOW,
SOME PEOPLE
MIGHT LOOK AT IT THAT WAY.
HOW DO YOU LOOK AT IT,
GERARDO?
I LOOK OUT FOR MY FRIENDS,
AS LONG AS I CAN.
HEY, MAN.
TAKE CARE OF YOURSELF, T.
YOU DO THE SAME.
♪ MUSIC
SO I HEAR THIS FRIEND OF
YOURS IS A TOUGH GUY.
HE'S THE ONLY GUY THAT
EVER BEAT ME.
NO KIDDING?
GERARDO AND I MET WHEN
WE'RE ABOUT 10 YEARS OLD.
[INDISTINCT] GUY RUNNING
A MARTIAL ARTS STUDENT
IN THE NEIGHBOURHOOD.
I FIGURED IT'S BETTER WHEN
WE'RE FIGHTING IN THE RING
INSTEAD OF CUTTING OUR
THROATS IN THE STREET.
MAKES SENSE.
BY THE TIME WE'RE 15,
WE WERE THE BEST.
PERIOD.
I LEARNED A LOT OF THINGS
FROM MY INSTRUCTOR.
THE MOST IMPORTANT THING I
LEARNED, DISCIPLINE.
YEAH.
WELL, YOU ARE THE MOST
DISCIPLINED SON OF A BITCH
I EVER MET.
THANKS.
I'M NOT SO SURE IT'S A
COMPLIMENT.
MEANING WHAT?
WELL, THE WAY I SEE IT,
YOU'RE NOT SO MUCH
DEDICATED TO CLEAN-LIVING
AS YOU ARE
ADDICTED TO DISCIPLINE.
WHAT'S THE DIFFERENCE?
YOU'RE LIKE A BORN-AGAIN
ALCOHOLIC SPURNING OFF THE
SAUCE.
YOU CAN'T STAND TO SEE OTHER
PEOPLE DRINK.
IT'S BECAUSE I KNOW WHAT IT
DOES TO THEM.
NO.
YOU KNOW WHAT
IT DOES TO YOU.
BULLSHIT.
I DON'T EVEN DRINK.
I NEVER HAVE.
I'LL BET SOMEBODY CLOSE
TO YOU HAS.
LOOK KID,
SOMETHING'S CHASING YOU.
AND UNTIL YOU LOOK AT IT
STRAIGHT IN THE FACE, YOU'LL
ALWAYS BE RUNNING.
SEE YOU TOMORROW.
♪ MUSIC
HEY. THANK YOU.
HEY!
[LAUGHS]
I REMEMBER YOU.
HERE.
HI.
HEY, NO NEED TO TALK TO
STRANGERS, YOU KNOW.
I'M SORRY, MA'AM.
I'M A COP.
NO NEED TO TELL ME THAT.
I'VE SEEN YOU FIGHT BEFORE.
PRETTY BAD FOR A WHITE BOY.
[LAUGHS]
THANKS.
SAY UH --
AREN'T YOU THE GUY THAT
THEY'S BEEN WRITING ABOUT
IN PAPERS?
THE GUY THAT'S DOING ALL
THIS
YEAH, I GUESS SO.
♪ MUSIC
THANKS.
BUT I STILL HOPE THE BROTHERS
WILL BEAT YOUR WHITE ASS.
♪ MUSIC
SO, UHM, HOW MANY OF YOU
HAVE EVER SERIOUSLY
CONSIDERED
BEING A POLICE OFFICER?
WELL, YOU KNOW --
YOU KNOW, BEING A LAW
ENFORCEMENT PROFESSIONAL
CAN BE VERY REWARDING.
HOW MUCH MONEY
CAN I MAKE?
[SIGHS]
UHM, STARTED AT ABOUT
$30,000 A YEAR.
SHIT.
I MADE MORE THAN THAT
SELLING CRACK LAST MONTH.
OH, YEAH?
YEAH.
MAYBE YOU SHOULD
COME WORK FOR ME.
[LAUGHS]
NOW, THEY'RE PAYING
TOO GOOD IN JAIL.
YOU GET TO BEAT
PEOPLE UP, MAN?
UH, SOMETIMES.
SOUNDS PRETTY COOL.
WELL, UH, YEAH, IT CAN BE.
OF COURSE, YOU GOT TO
WATCH OUT FOR THOSE
VIDEO CAMERAS THESE DAYS.
UHM, ANYWAY --
ANYWAY,
ANY OTHER QUESTIONS?
HOW COME COPS ARE SUCH
ASSHOLES?
WELL, I'M GLAD YOU ASKED
THAT QUESTION.
IT MAINLY IS BECAUSE WE GOT
TO DEAL WITH PUNKS LIKE YOU.
SO I'M A PUNK?
YEAH, YOU'RE A PUNK.
AND SO JUST 'CAUSE YOU'RE
A COP,
THAT MEANS YOU GET THE
SHOOT INNOCENT PEOPLE?
INNOCENT PEOPLE, HUH?
YOU KNOW WHAT INNOCENT IS?
INNOCENT IS A 3-YEAR OLD GIRL
THAT YOU GUYS SHOT THE OTHER
NIGHT IN A DRIVE-BY!
WE DIDN'T SHOOT
NOBODY, MAN!
OH, YEAH, NO?
YOU'RE A GANG MEMBER,
AREN'T YOU?!
YEAH!
WELL, THAT WAS A GANG
SHOOTING AND YOU'RE
PART OF ALL OF THAT!
YEAH, YOU'RE A COP,
AREN'T YOU?!
YEAH!
SO HOW COME YOU SHOT
MY HOMEBOY SMILEY
LAST YEAR?!
I DIDN'T SHOOT THAT BOY
SMILEY!
29 TIMES IN THE BACK!
29 TIMES?
YEAH, YOU DID IT!
WHAT WAS HE DOING, HUH?
HE WASN'T DOING NOTHING!
HE WAS GOING HOME!
OH, HE WASN'T DOING
NOTHING.
HE WAS GOING HOME!
YEAH,
WITH YOUR $30,000 OF
CRACK IN HIS POCKET!
HEY, MAN.
SMILEY DIDN'T SELL, MAN!
OH, SMILEY DIDN'T SELL.
NO, SMILEY DIDN'T --
YOU THINK JUST 'CAUSE WE
LIVING THIS NEIGHBOURHOOD
EVERYBODY SELLS?
YEAH, I THINK --
[LAUGHS]
PUBLIC SPEAKING WAS
NEVER FLANNIGAN'S STRONG
SUIT.
EVERYBODY DON'T SELL, HUH.
YEAH,
EVERYBODY DON'T SELL.
OH I SEE.
YOU COPS ALWAYS THINK
THAT.
OH, WE ALWAYS THINK THAT.
YEAH,
YOU COPS ALWAYS THINK THAT.
WELL, LOOK AT HOW YOU THINK.
LOOK HOW YOU SIT HERE,
"$30,000 LAST YEAR" LIKE
THAT'S SOMETHING SELLING
SHIT TO KIDS!
YOU SEE HOW YOU ACT?
HEY.
GIVE ME A HAND, WILL YOU?
YEAH.
HEY, I HEAR YOU'VE BEEN
TAKING SOME FLACK.
SOME PEOPLE DON'T LIKE
THE COMPANY I'VE BEEN
KEEPING WITH LATELY.
THE PLACE REALLY CHANGED
THOUGH, HUH?
YEAH, IT'S BECOMING A
NEIGHBOURHOOD AGAIN.
I MEAN, IT DOESN'T SOLVE
EVERYTHING BUT IT'S A START.
YEAH, I'M GLAD.
THINK. IT ALL HAPPENED
BECAUSE I CALLED YOU OUT.
NO.
IT HAPPENED BECAUSE SOME
PEOPLE TOOK ADVANTAGE OF A
CHANCE WHEN THEY GOT ONE.
HEY, JIMMY!
HEY, MAN.
I GOT TO GO.
TAKE CARE, ALRIGHT.
SEE YOU, BOY.
♪ MUSIC
[INDISTINCT]
HEY, DO YOU THINK I
SHOULD GIVE HER SOME
KIND OF -- I DON'T KNOW,
AN ADVANTAGE?
WHAT KIND OF AN
ADVANTAGE DO YOU SUGGEST?
NEVER MIND.
[INDISTINCT]
SURE DAD, THIS IS GOOD.
CAN I SEE YOU A MINUTE
OVER HERE?
YEAH, NO, NOT RIGHT NOW.
NO, COME ON.
LET ME BUY YOU A BEER,
ALRIGHT?
I DON'T WANT A BEER.
THANKS.
BRIAN, THEY'LL BE FINE.
COME ON, THEY'LL BE FINE.
REALLY?
HEY LOOK,
TONY COULD SCORE, RIGHT?
I COULD SCORE --
TONY?
TONY CAN WHAT?
YOU CAN WHAT?
BRIAN.
BRIAN,
JUST COME WITH US, OKAY?
I'LL BE RIGHT OVER HERE.
OKAY.
IF YOU WANNA COME
WITH US, DARLING?
YOU CAN COME WITH US.
NO, THAT'S ALRIGHT.
I'LL BE RIGHT OVER HERE.
I'LL BE BACK SHORTLY, ANYWAY.
OKAY.
I'LL BE BACK, SHORTLY.
I WANT TO HEAR YOUR
OPINION ON SOME BALLS
OVER HERE.
HI, HOW ARE YOU DOING?
I'M TONY.
I'M GLAD TO MEET YOU.
HE REALLY DOES LIKE YOU.
[LAUGHS]
YOUR DAD AND I DON'T EXACTLY
SEE EYE TO EYE ON
A LOT OF THINGS.
LIKE DATING ME?
THAT'S A BIG ONE.
HE IS REALLY PROTECTIVE.
BUT IT'S MORE THAN THAT,
NEXT YEAR I'LL BE 20 YEARS
AND WHEN HE DOESN'T
HAVE THE JOB
ANYMORE, WHAT'S LEFT?
I DON'T THINK YOUR DAD LIKES
THE IDEA OF YOU GETTING
TOGETHER WITH A COP.
ARE WE GETTING TOGETHER?
♪ MUSIC
IT KINDA FEELS THAT WAY,
DOESN'T IT?
ALL I KNOW IS IT FEELS
GOOD.
♪ MUSIC
SO WHAT'S THE HOLD UP?
THEY'RE GETTING NERVOUS?
I DON'T KNOW.
I HEAR THESE HOMEBOYS
BROUGHT IN SOME KIND
OF A RINGER.
A RINGER?
YEAH.
WELL, WE'RE
READY FOR THEM.
WHAT CAN THEY HAVE, HUH?
[CHEERING]
TONY!
TONY, MAN!
TONY.
LET'S DO IT!
THEY BROUGHT SOMEONE IN SO
YOU WOULDN'T BE BORED, OKAY?
I'M GONNA BEAT HIM UGLY.
HEY, TONY!
IT'S NOT OVER 'TIL THE FAT
LADY SINGS, RIGHT PAL?
THAT'S RIGHT.
YOU'RE DON'T FORGET WHO'S
GONNA BUY THE PIZZA?
YOU GOT IT.
MOVEMENT , TONY.
MOVEMENT.
♪ MUSIC
[CROWD CHEERING]
LOOKS LIKE YOUR OLD BUDDY
JUST TURNED THINGS UP A
NOTCH OR TWO.
[CROWD CHEERING]
HEY!
COME ON!
[CROWD CHEERING]
ALRIGHT, FINISH HIM UP!
COME ON, TONY.
[CROWD CHEERING]
COME ON!
COME ON, TONY!
[CROWD CHEERING]
YEAH!
BLOW HIM OFF!
AHH!
YEAH!
[CROWD CHEERING]
I THOUGHT YOU TOLD ME
THAT GUY COULD FIGHT?
HE USED TO FIGHT PRO, MAN.
YOU MADE ME LOOK LIKE A
FOOL.
♪ MUSIC
[CROWD CHEERING]
WAY TO GO!
[GUNSHOT]
JIMMY!
OH, GOD! [INDISTINCT]
HOW COME YOU CAN
NEVER FIND
A COP WHEN YOU NEED ONE?
[COUGHS]
DON'T TRY TO TALK, MAN.
IT DOESN'T MATTER, MAN.
I'VE SEEN GUYS TAKE IT
LIKE THIS BEFORE.
GET AN AMBULANCE!
I CAN'T MAKE IT, MAN.
DID JOHNNY DO THIS?
NO.
IT DOESN'T TAKE A GENIUS TO
FIGURE IT OUT.
[COUGHS]
GERARDO.
HE DIDN'T PULL THE TRIGGER
BUT HE BOUGHT THE GUNS.
[COUGHS]
SHHH, HANG IN THERE BUDDY.
YOU ARE GONNA
MAKE THIS, MAN.
THAT'S IT.
HURRY UP!
HOLD ON, MAN.
FIGHT IT.
HANG IN THERE.
COME ON, JIMMY.
JIMMY.
[SIGHS]
♪ MUSIC
[CAR SCREECHING]
[GUNSHOTS]
IT'S TOO BAD ABOUT THE KID.
HIS NAME WAS JIMMY.
WELL, IT COULD
HAVE BEEN YOU.
WORD ON THE STREET IS,
IT'S OVER.
WHAT'S ALL OVER?
THE PAPERS.
THEY'RE MAKING A SOUND LIKE
THE DEALERS ARE TAKING BACK
THE STREET.
THEY SAY YOU AIN'T
GONNA SHOW TONIGHT.
WHAT DOES IT GONNA DO WITH
ME ANYHOW?
WHETHER YOU LIKE IT OR NOT,
KID. PEOPLE THINK THE
FIGHTS WERE YOUR IDEA.
PROBLEM IS THE FIGHTS ARE
GETTING INTO
GERARDO'S POCKET.
WHAT DOES THE
NEIGHBOURHOOD
THINK ABOUT IT?
THEY'RE SCARED.
I MEAN, IF THE DEALERS
SCARED SOME COPS AWAY.
I HEARD THEY'RE GONNA KILL A
COP IF YOU SHOW UP TONIGHT.
SO WHAT DO YOU THINK HE'S
GONNA DO?
I DON'T GIVE A DAMN WHAT
HE DOES AS LONG AS HE
DOESN'T GET DEAD.
♪ MUSIC
YOU KNOW, YOU WERE RIGHT
ALL ALONG.
ABOUT WHAT?
MY LIFE IS JUST ONE GIANT
GOD DAMN MONUMENT TO
SELF CONTROL.
BUT YOU KNOW WHY?
WHY?
'CAUSE PEOPLE WHO DON'T
HAVE CONTROL ARE LOSERS.
MY MOTHER WAS A LOSER.
MY FATHER WAS A LOSER.
THEY DRINK THEMSELVES TO
FUCKING DEATH.
YOU KNOW, THEY SAY THAT
ALCOHOLISM IS HEREDITARY.
WELL, THEY SAY A LOT OF
THINGS.
YOU ARE NOT YOUR PARENTS.
YOU'RE GOD DAMN RIGHT
I'M NOT.
I HATED THEM. AND I CAN'T--
NO, NO, NO, I WON'T BE LIKE
THEM.
YOU KNOW, TONY.
SOMETIMES A PERSON PUSHES
AGAINST A THING SO HARD THAT
HE MAKES IT HAPPEN.
YOU THINK THAT'S GONNA
HAPPEN TO ME?
THIS HAS GOT NOTHING TO
DO WITH YOUR PARENTS.
YOU'RE RUNNING AWAY FROM
YOURSELF.
[SIGHS]
ARE YOU GONNA SHOW UP
TOMORROW NIGHT?
I NEVER RAN FROM A FIGHT.
EVER.
IT'S NOT GOOD FOR THE SOUL.
GETTING YOUR HEAD BLOWN
OFF IS NOT SO HOT FOR THE
BODY EITHER.
I AIN'T AFRAID OF GERARDO.
LOOK.
THERE ARE SUCH A THING AS A
HEALTHY FEAR.
IT'S KEPT ME ALIVE FOR YEARS.
THERE'S NO SHAME IN IT,
BELIEVE ME.
JIMMY TRUSTED ME.
A LOT OF THOSE
GUYS TRUSTED ME.
[LAUGHS]
HELL, EVEN SOME OF THEM
TRUSTED YOU.
SO WHAT?
SO WHAT?!
NONE OF THEM TRUSTED US
TWO WEEKS AGO!
WE'RE DOING SOMETHING
WORTHWHILE DOWN THERE.
WELL, LET ME TELL YOU
SOMETHING.
IT'S NOT YOUR JOB TO SAVE THE
WHOLE WORLD.
I'M NOT TRYING TO SAVE THE
WORLD.
I JUST WANNA SAVE THAT
LITTLE PIECE THAT I LIVE IN.
♪ MUSIC
BABY, YOU KNOW, YOU'RE
LOOKING REAL GOOD TONIGHT.
AND I LIKE THAT, IT'S GOOD.
[INDISTINCT]
YEAH --
THIS IS IT.
[PHONE RINGS]
LET ME GET THE PHONE.
YEAH, WHAT'S UP?
NO, MAN.
THAT WAS REAL SLOPPY.
NO, THIS GOT TO
BE REAL SMOOTH.
NO MISTAKES.
I UNDERSTAND HE'S DATING
SOME CHICK.
♪ MUSIC
[GUNSHOT]
SHIT!
♪ MUSIC
YOU'RE A FEISTY LITTLE
BITCH,
AREN'T YOU?
[SCREAMS]
[INDISTINCT]
[WHIMPERING]
WOULD YOU MIND IF I COME
IN TO SEE SUSAN?
IF SHE'S UP.
SOMETIMES SHE FALLS ASLEEP
ON THE COUCH.
YOU WAIT ON THE PORCH.
♪ MUSIC
WHAT'S WRONG?
THEY GOT MY DAUGHTER.
WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
YOUR FRIEND LEFT A NOTE.
WHOA, WHOA WHOA!
NO, YOU STAY HERE.
STAY BY THE PHONE
JUST IN CASE.
♪ MUSIC
I WANNA SEE GERARDO.
HE AIN'T IN.
YOU MEAN HE
AIN'T IN FOR ME?
EITHER WAY, HE AIN'T IN.
SO WHY DON'T YOU JUST RUN
ALONG --[SPITS] COP.
[SCREAMS]
♪ MUSIC
[GLASS BREAKS]
[SCREAMS]
GET OUT!
NEXT TIME, CALL AHEAD.
WHERE IS SHE?
WHERE'S WHO?
ANYBODY ELSE
TOUCHES ME,
EVEN TOUCHES ME,
HE'S DEAD!
DON'T PLAY TOUGH GUY
WITH ME, MAN!
I DON'T PLAY, T.
I KICKED YOUR ASS
10 YEARS AGO.
I CAN DO IT AGAIN.
WHERE'S SUSAN?
I DON'T KNOW.
BUT I HEARD THINGS.
WHAT'VE YOU HEARD?
I HEARD SHE'LL BE RELEASED
UNHARMED AFTER YOU DON'T
SHOW UP TONIGHT.
YOU REALLY THINK I DON'T
SHOW TONIGHT, YOU'RE GONNA
WIN THE STREETS BACK?
FOR A WHILE.
NOTHING LASTS FOREVER,
I KNOW THAT.
BUT I'M A BUSINESSMAN, T.
IT'S NOTHING PERSONAL,
IT'S BUSINESS.
I COULD MAKE YOU TELL ME.
THAT WOULD DEFINITELY BE
A MISTAKE, T.
♪ MUSIC
THAT'S THE SECOND TIME I
SAVED YOUR LIFE TONIGHT, T.
THAT MAKES US EVEN.
♪ MUSIC
DON'T EVEN THINK ABOUT IT.
WHERE IS SHE?
WHAT'D HE SAY?
WHAT'D HE SAY?!
HE SAID HE'S GONNA LET HER
GO IF I DON'T SHOW UP
TONIGHT.
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO?
I'D LIKE TO JUST --
HEY, LISTEN.
I DON'T GIVE A GOOD
GOD DAMN
WHAT YOU'D LIKE TO DO.
WE'RE TALKING ABOUT MY
DAUGHTER HERE.
♪ MUSIC
[DOOR SQUEAKS]
[BUSY TONE]
[PHONE RINGS]
HI, YOU'VE REACHED
555-8090.
NO ONE IS HERE TO TAKE YOUR
CALL BUT IF YOU'LL LEAVE A
MESSAGE,
WE'LL CALL YOU BACK.
WELL, WHAT DO YOU THINK?
IS THIS GUY GONNA LET HER GO
OR WHAT?
LOOK.
ALL I KNOW IS IF I DON'T SHOW
UP TONIGHT,
GERARDO TAKES THESE
STREET BACK. AND NO MATTTER
WHAT I DO AFTERWARDS, THIS
NEIGHBOURHOOD IS GONNA
KNOW HE BACKED ME DOWN.
WELL, I'M SORRY KID.
I KNOW HOW YOU FEEL, BUT --
NO. YOU DON'T KNOW
HOW I FEEL BUT DON'T WORRY,
SUSAN'S SAFETY IS A LOT MORE
IMPORTANT THAN MY PRIDE.
UH, I DON'T KNOW THE EXACT
ADDRESS BUT IT'S THE SECOND
EXIT, NORTH OF SANTA MONICA
ON THE 405 AND THEN --
[SCREAMS]
HELP!
[TAPE REWINDING]
DADDY, IT'S ME.
I DON'T KNOW THE EXACT
ADDRESS BUT IT'S THE SECOND
EXIT, NORTH OF SANTA MONICA
ON THE 405 AND THEN --
HELP!
HOW DOES SHE KNOW
WHERE SHE IS?
IT WAS A GAME WE PLAYED
WHEN SHE WAS A KID.
IF SHE KNEW EXACTLY WHERE
SHE WAS,
SHE FELT LESS HANDICAPPED.
SECOND EXIT, NORTH OF 405.
YEAH, MULHOLLAND
BIG DEAL. IT NARROWS IT DOWN
TO ABOUT A MILLION PEOPLE.
NO. DOWN TO ONE.
SHE'S AT GERARDO'S.
THAT WOULD BE THE LAST
PLACE I WOULD THINK
TO LOOK FOR HER.
♪ MUSIC
[INDISTINCT]
TOO BAD YOU CAN'T SEE
WHAT I GOT FOR YOU.
WHOA, WHOA WHOA.
YOU'RE GONNA GET
US ALL KILLED.
NOW, WHAT ARE YOU
GONNA DO, HUH?
[LAUGHS]
WHAT ARE YOU
GONNA DO NOW?
[LAUGHS]
WHAT THE HELL IS THAT?
[SCREAMS]
♪ MUSIC
[GRUNTS]
DADDY!
IT'S ALRIGHT, DOLL.
YOU'RE ALRIGHT.
IT'S ALRIGHT NOW.
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
DON'T WORRY.
EVERYTHING'S GONNA BE
ALRIGHT.
WE'RE GONNA GET OUT OF HERE,
OKAY?
OKAY.
[SCREAMS]
LET'S GO.
[DOOR CLOSES]
YOU UNDERSTAND I GOT TO
DO THIS.
I UNDERSTAND.
♪ MUSIC
[ENGINE STARTS]
GERARDO KILLED MY BROTHER.
I THOUGHT YOU COULD
USE SOME HELP.
THANKS.
♪ MUSIC
GERARDO!
[DOOR OPENS]
YOU SHOULD HAVE
WALKED, T.
TOO MANY PEOPLE
WALKED AWAY.
AT LEAST I GAVE YOU A
CHOICE, MAN.
NO, YOU DON'T GIVE CHOICES!
YOU GIVE ORDERS!
AND YOU'RE DONE GIVING
ORDERS IN THE STREETS!
I'M DONE TALKING.
♪ MUSIC
[CROWD CHEERING]
[SCREAMS]
GET UP! GET UP!
COME ON!
[CROWD CHEERING]
[GRUNTS]
[PEOPLE SHOUTING]
KILL HIM.
YEAH, MAN!
YOU GOT HIM!
COME ON, TONY!
[INDISTINCT]
[CROWD CHEERING]
[SCREAMS]
[GRUNTS]
HOLD ON, G!
COME ON!
COME ON, MAN!
[SCREAMS]
[HEAVY BREATHING]
THIS WASN'T EVEN YOUR FIGHT.
THESE ARE MY STREETS!
[HEAVY BREATHING]
THAT'S WHAT MADE IT
MY FIGHT.
[HEAVY BREATHING]
LOOK, [INDISTINCT], YOU
AIN'T GONNA MAKE
NO DIFFERENCE.
[HEAVY BREATHING]
IT DOES TO ME.
NOW, KID.
YOU LOOK LIKE SHIT.
[LAUGHS]
THANKS.
[HEAVY BREATHING]
THERE'S SOMEBODY
HERE FOR YOU.
HI.
♪ MUSIC