♪ Dream on, Cinderella
♪ Dream the day away
♪ Dreaming of a
handsome prince ♪
♪ To take your heart away
♪ Life was filled with joy
♪ But nothing seems
to stay the same ♪
♪ Spring gives way
and summer falls ♪
♪ And winter brings the rain
♪ Dream on, Cinderella
♪ Dream the day away
♪ Hoping that your
prince will come ♪
♪ And take your heart away
♪ Oh, dream on, Cinderella
♪ Dreaming of the day
♪ A handsome prince will come
♪ And take you faraway
♪ You're the most beautiful
girl in the land ♪
♪ But where is the prince
who will give you his hand? ♪
♪ And dance through the night
at the ballroom so grand ♪
♪ Make you the
queen of his heart ♪
♪ 'Til the clock
decrees you must part ♪
♪ Dream on, Cinderella
♪ Dream the day away
♪ Dreaming of a
handsome prince ♪
♪ To take your heart away
♪ Oh, dream on, Cinderella
♪ Dream the day away
♪ Hoping that your
prince will come ♪
♪ And take you faraway
♪ Oh, dream on, Cinderella
♪ Dreaming of the day
♪ Your handsome
prince will come ♪
♪ And take your heart away
♪ Oh, dream on, Cinderella
♪ Your dream is on the way
♪ Soon your handsome
prince will come ♪
♪ To take you faraway
- [Narrator] There once lived
a gentleman from a fine family
whose hard work made
him very, very rich.
His life was filled with beauty.
Not only was he blessed with
a loyal and loving wife,
but a most attractive daughter.
(calm music)
Sweet, kind, she was as
lovely inside as she was out.
Life, however, is not
always predictable
and darkness passed
across the man's future
and his wife took gravely ill.
A few weeks later,
she passed on.
Winter came and
covered everything in
a blanket of white.
(plops)
And when the sun
brought springtime,
the rich man had
found a second wife,
who brought along
her two daughters.
Like their mother, they had
nasty and wicked hearts.
This did not bode well for
the rich man's daughter.
Sometime later, the rich man
left on a long business trip.
- But you just came back.
- It can't be helped, I'm sorry.
Now what might I
bring back for you?
- Well, I--
- A beautiful dress,
my wonderful husband.
- And candy.
Lots of cherries covered
with thick, creamy chocolate.
- And pearls!
A long magnificent strand
to adorn my long and
magnificent neck.
- And you, my daughter?
- I need nothing, Father.
I wish only that
you return safely.
- I shall.
Until then, farewell!
- I miss you already, Father.
- What did you say?
- Nothing.
- Then stop wasting time
and go do your chores!
(stepsisters laughing)
- [Narrator] Blinded by
his love for his new wife,
the father didn't see what
was happening to his daughter.
The cruel stepsisters
immediately took
away her bedroom,
her fine clothes, and
made her do all the chores
around the house while
they had all the fun.
(laughing)
The father had no idea she
was sleeping on a straw mat
in front of the fireplace.
And although the
fire kept her warm,
the ashes and cinders
drifted across her,
making her look dusty and dirty.
The stepsisters made fun of
her and called her Cinderella.
(crying)
(lively music)
(sloshes)
- I miss you, Mother.
(mysterious music)
- Why, Cindy,
you've been crying.
- You're alive?
- Would I be talking
if I wasn't alive?
- No, but...
Who are you?
- I'm your fairy
godmother, of course.
- I didn't know I...
- Nonsense.
Everybody has a fairy godmother.
Well, almost everybody.
- You can fly!
- Oh, I can do all
sorts of things!
Watch.
(clatters)
- But I just hung those up!
- No problem.
(laughs)
- Oh, I wish you were
here all the time.
- I am, my sweet.
And I know everything
that's going on.
- Then you know about my
stepmother and stepsisters?
- Their deeds will
not go unpunished.
You have my word.
Now, no more tears, promise?
- I promise.
- Good.
Pleasant dreams, my child.
And fear no longer.
- Good night to you,
fairy godmother.
(kisses)
- Oh, too bad Cinderella
can't play with us.
- Somebody has to
do all the chores.
(laughing)
- Cinderella!
(gasps)
(shatters)
Now look what you've done.
- You frightened me.
- When you finish
cleaning up your mess,
the floors need to be
scrubbed, the curtains cleaned,
and the silver polished.
- But I just
polished the silver.
- Well, do it again!
I want to see my
face in every spoon.
What?
What's happening?
What is going on here?
(laughs)
- You cheated.
- I did not.
- Did too.
- Did not.
- You did!
Besides, it's my turn anyway!
- No, it's my turn.
- Move!
(tinkling music)
(bounces)
(crashes)
(laughs)
- [Narrator] Meanwhile, the
king's son had just come of age.
And the king and queen were
anxious for the handsome prince
to choose a wife from the
rank and nobility in the land.
- Do you think he likes her?
- Well, if I could
see, I could tell you.
(crashes)
- My father is the
Duke of Rockingham
and he is very, very wealthy.
(sighs)
My grandfather was
even wealthier.
- Wealth isn't important to me.
- Our collection of fine
art is the most exceptional
in the land.
Save yours, of course.
Huh?
- Quick, dear, he's coming.
- Well?
- Isn't she lovely?
- I will not marry
someone I don't love.
- But--
- I have an idea.
We will hold a grand ball
and invite all the eligible
young ladies we can find.
- Yes, a magnificent
ball, a feast!
Surely you'll be able to
find your princess then?
- I will agree
under one condition.
- Speak, my son.
- The choice is
mine and mine alone.
- Agreed.
The invitation shall
go out immediately!
(upbeat music)
(knocking)
(stepsisters laughing)
- I got it, I got it!
It's mine!
(grunts)
(laughs)
- It's here!
The invitation is here!
The king and queen request
the pleasure of your company
at the grand ball to be
held at the royal palace
three days hence.
- Oh, mother, that's wonderful!
But I need a new dress.
- Me too, me too, me too!
- Not to worry, my children.
You shall have
whatever you need.
(laughing)
- May I go to the ball?
- That's hardly
possible, Cinderella.
You certainly don't expect
me to buy three new dresses,
do you?
- Well, I just
thought it would be...
- Besides, you can't even dance.
Come, girls.
There's so much to do!
- I will not cry.
I will not cry.
- [Stepmother] Cinderella!
(owl hooting)
- [Narrator] The night
of the ball arrived
and the kind-hearted
Cinderella tried her utmost
to help her
stepsisters get ready.
♪ The time's approaching
♪ The carriages were called
♪ To take the young
ladies out to the ball ♪
(laughing)
♪ Oh, so pretty in satin
♪ So pretty in lace
♪ With ringlets of curls
around every face ♪
♪ It's the chance
of a lifetime ♪
♪ A chance to begin anew
♪ A chance to capture
the heart of the prince ♪
♪ And make your
dreams come true ♪
♪ The time is here
♪ The carriage is called
♪ The trumpeters herald
the start of the ball ♪
♪ The pretty young ladies
are ready to dance ♪
♪ But no one will give
Cinderella a chance ♪
♪ It's the chance
of a lifetime ♪
♪ A chance to begin anew
♪ A chance to capture
the heart of the prince ♪
♪ And make your
dreams come true ♪
♪ I missed my chance
of a lifetime ♪
♪ I missed my
chance for romance ♪
♪ All my dreams are
turned to dust ♪
♪ I never had a chance
- Everything ready?
- Oh, please can I go?
Won't you please reconsider?
- Well, she did
help us get dressed.
- Alright.
I've just emptied a bowl
of lentils into the ashes.
Pick them out of the fireplace
before our coach arrives
and you can go.
- Oh, thank you, thank you!
How will I ever do this in time?
- [Fairy Godmother]
Not to worry, Cindy.
We'll take care of it.
(swishes)
(chirping)
- Oh my goodness!
(drops)
- I don't suppose you've
finished, have you?
- I did what you asked.
- So you have.
(ominous music)
(drops)
Except for that one.
- But the rest are in the bowl.
- I said all, not all but one.
- Our coach is here.
- I will not cry.
I will not cry.
(crying)
- Come on, Cindy.
Stop it before
you drown us both.
- I know I promised
not to cry, but...
- Oh, it's alright.
I understand.
Why, even fairy godmothers
cry once in a while.
Follow me.
- Where are we going?
- You, my darling Cindy,
are going to the ball.
- To the ball?
But how?
- Now get me a pumpkin.
- A pumpkin?
- Yes.
Yes, you know, a
round orange thing.
A pumpkin.
- But how will a pumpkin
get me to the ball?
- Enough with all the questions.
Leave it to me.
In the meantime, get me
four mushrooms, six lizards,
and a rat.
- A what?
How strange this all is.
- You haven't seen anything yet.
Now go, go!
The fun's just beginning.
Birds of a feather,
come back together.
Scoop it clean, my
crested companions.
- I couldn't find any lizards.
- Well, look in
the watering can.
Now hurry!
- I found the lizards!
- Well done, Cindy.
Now place it here.
- What do you want to
do with these things?
- Don't worry.
Now stand back, my darling.
The fun has just begun!
(swishes)
- (gasps) Oh, I
can't believe it!
But how can I go to
such an elegant affair
in these wretched rags?
- Not to worry.
- It's beautiful!
But...
- Yes, I know, I know.
- Glass slippers?
How unusual.
- Not a bad touch, if
I do say so myself.
Come, it's time to go.
One last thing.
You must not remain at
the ball beyond midnight.
- Why not?
- If you stay a moment longer,
the charm will be broken
and everything will change
back to its old self.
- Before midnight, I promise.
(banging)
- What is it?
Well, (laughs) nobody's perfect.
(swishes)
Be gone, my Cindy.
And have the time of your life!
Remember what I told you!
Be home before the
clock strikes 12.
- I will, fairy
godmother, I will!
(lively music)
- I must say, dear, you've
really outdone yourself.
Everyone who is anyone is here.
- If this doesn't
get our son a wife,
I don't know what will.
We have the finest orchestra
all the way from Vienna,
the most important
chef from Paris,
and the most beautiful
young ladies in the land.
- Alright, girls, get
in there and get him.
You can do it, now go!
(crashes)
- Would you honor me with
a dance, your highness?
I understand you
have feet like wings.
- I beg your pardon?
- Dance with me!
I'm so much more graceful.
- You are not.
You dance like a stork.
- That's a lie!
- It is not.
- Is too.
- [Short Stepsister] Oh yeah?
Well, you're a dunce.
- [Tall Stepsister] Am not.
- [Short Stepsister] Are too.
- [Short Stepsister] Are too!
- What do you suppose happened?
- I've never seen anyone as--
Your face is like...
You're the most beautiful
young lady I've ever seen.
- I'm flattered.
Thank you.
- May I escort you inside?
- It would be my honor.
(gasps)
- [Announcer] Ladies
and gentlemen,
announcing the prince!
(applause)
- The prince?
- What a charming creature.
- Charming indeed.
- What grace.
- What elegance.
- What nerve.
And who is she anyway?
(upbeat music)
- That's the gaudiest
dress I've ever seen!
- And those shoes.
Who ever heard of
glass slippers?
- He'll soon tire
of her, you'll see.
- [Narrator] But the prince
did not tire of Cinderella.
He danced only with her for
the rest of the evening.
So entranced was
Cinderella with the prince
that she forgot all about her
fairy godmother's warning.
(clock chiming)
- (gasps) Oh no!
Forgive me, your
highness, but I must go.
- Wait!
I don't even know your name!
- Please, please let me
go before it's too late!
(gasps)
No!
(breathing heavily)
- Did you see a lady
come running out?
- She ran into the
maze, your highness.
But she looked more like
a peasant than a lady.
- [Prince] Hello?
- Oh no, no!
- Hello?
Come back!
(rips)
- [Narrator] Afraid
to get caught,
Cinderella left her
glass slipper behind
and fled into the night.
(tinkling music)
- How could I have
lost you so soon?
- I know he must love
me, but I do love him.
But how will he ever find me?
♪ Where has she
been all my life? ♪
♪ I'm drawn like a
moth to her flame ♪
♪ I'd make her my princess
♪ I'd make her my wife
♪ But I don't even
know her name ♪
♪ How can I find her?
♪ Where could she be?
♪ Without her I
won't be the same ♪
♪ Without her my heart
will never be free ♪
♪ But I don't even
know her name ♪
♪ He's the one I've
been waiting for ♪
♪ The handsome
prince of my dreams ♪
♪ I've never felt
this way before ♪
♪ Afloat in a sea of moonbeams
♪ Could this be love
the way that I feel? ♪
♪ Will I ever see him again?
♪ I have to know
if love is real ♪
♪ Without him my
world will end ♪
♪ Where have you
been all my life? ♪
♪ I've been waiting
for someone like you ♪
♪ Will you be my princess,
will you be my wife? ♪
♪ My darling, yes, I do
♪ Come back, come
back, I love you so ♪
♪ Save me, they're
tearing me away ♪
♪ Darling, tell me your
name before you go ♪
♪ I can't hear you
♪ Oh please, help me stay
♪ Where has love
been all my life? ♪
♪ Why is love
leaving this way? ♪
♪ Who will console me
and kiss away my tears ♪
♪ When love has gone away?
(sighs)
(slow music)
(crowd chattering)
- Hear ye, hear ye.
Let it hereby be known
that the royal prince
requests all single ladies,
regardless of rank or stature,
to try on this
unique glass slipper.
Furthermore, whomever
this slipper shall fit
will become the
bride of the prince
and be the princess of the land.
(crowd chattering)
- [Narrator] The prince
traveled over hills and valleys
in search of his true love.
(springing)
(squeaking)
But alas, no one was
found to fit the slipper.
The prince was growing
weary of his fruitless quest
as he turned up the road
to where Cinderella lived.
(horse neighs)
- (gasps) He's here!
The prince is coming.
- Cinderella, close that door
and come here this instant.
- My feet are freezing!
- And mine are boiling.
- Oh, stop complaining.
The idea is to get them
to fit into the slipper.
- But my foot will never
shrink enough to fit.
- And I don't think that
mine'll get any bigger.
- They better.
Cinderella!
Dispose of these buckets.
- May I try on the slipper too?
(laughs)
- Absolutely not.
You're much too
dirty to be seen.
As soon as you dispose
of these buckets,
go upstairs to the attic and
wait until I call you down.
- But I...
- Do as I say.
Now!
(knocking)
Good afternoon, your highness.
We've been expecting you.
Won't you please come inside?
(laughs)
- If only I could
try on that slipper,
the prince would know
I'm the one he loves.
Isn't there anything you can do?
- I'm thinking, I'm thinking.
- Oh, please, hurry!
The prince won't
be here forever.
- One thing you
must learn, my dear.
Never rush a fairy godmother!
(grunting)
- Push harder, dear.
- I'm trying!
- Stop, before the
slipper shatters!
Then I shall never
find my beloved.
(grunts)
- Sorry, Mother.
- Next?
- Oh, I just adore glass!
- Oh, no, no, I'm afraid
your foot is much too small.
- Perhaps if she tried again.
- Don't you have
any other daughters?
- No, I...
- I was told you
had three daughters.
- (laughs) Well, actually I do.
But Cinderella's
only my stepdaughter
and surely she
couldn't be the one.
(distant singing)
- That voice!
It's her!
♪ The handsome
prince of my dreams ♪
♪ I've never felt
this way before ♪
- Louder!
♪ Afloat in a sea of moonbeams
♪ Could this be love,
the way that I feel? ♪
- I have heard that
voice in my dreams
ever since we danced.
I'm sure it is her!
- With all due
respect, your highness,
it's only Cinderella.
- Bring her down here at once!
- [Stepmother] But
your highness...
- At once!
- Fetch her.
(laughs) Oh dear.
- I pray that I am right.
- You wish to see
me, your highness?
- No, please.
Be seated.
- A perfect fit, my lord.
- I knew it.
- She was lucky!
There must be some mistake.
A mere coincidence.
It can't be Cinderella.
- It is possible, my lord.
(dramatic music)
(thumps)
Hmm, what's this?
- The other slipper.
I lost only one the
night of the ball.
- We shall see.
- You are the one!
You shall be my bride.
- Oh.
(sniffling)
- No, sire, she
cannot be the one.
Why, look at those ragged
clothes, that dirty face!
- I did not fall in
love with a fancy dress.
Nor can a few simple
ashes conceal her beauty.
It is Cinderella I love.
- And I you, my prince.
- [Narrator] A few days later,
the prince and
Cinderella were married.
It was a grand and
glorious ceremony,
and Cinderella looked
more beautiful than ever,
while the prince was happier
than he ever
dreamed he would be.
Cinderella's father had
returned from his trip
to give away the bride,
but she never told him
how much she had suffered.
And when her
stepsisters apologized
for their thoughtlessness,
Cinderella,
with a goodness
that knew no bounds,
saw to it that they
married two handsome lords.
Cinderella and the prince
lived in comfort and happiness
for the rest of their lives.
And while Cinderella grew
to be a beautiful woman,
it was her good grace
that was far more precious
than her beauty,
and her forgiveness that
was a jewel beyond price.
As all who hear this story know,
only true kindness is worthy
of a fairy godmother's gift.
For without kindness,
we can do nothing.
But with it, anything and
everything is possible.
♪ Lovely as a flower blooming
♪ On the first of spring
♪ Roses blossom to her touch
♪ She makes the
song birds sing ♪
♪ Dream on, Cinderella
♪ Dream the day away
♪ Dreaming of a
handsome prince ♪
♪ To take your heart away
♪ Life was filled with joy
♪ But nothing seems
to stay the same ♪
♪ Spring gives way
and summer falls ♪
♪ And winter brings the rain
♪ Dream on, Cinderella
♪ Dream the day away
♪ Hoping that your
prince will come ♪
♪ And take your heart away
♪ Oh, dream on, Cinderella
♪ Dreaming of the day
♪ A handsome prince will come
♪ And take you faraway
♪ You're the most beautiful
girl in the land ♪
♪ But where is the prince
who will give you his hand? ♪
♪ And dance through the night
at the ballroom so grand ♪
♪ Make you the
queen of his heart ♪
♪ 'Til the clock
decrees you must part ♪
♪ Dream on, Cinderella
♪ Dream the day away
♪ Dreaming of a
handsome prince ♪
♪ To take your heart away
♪ Oh, dream on, Cinderella
♪ Dream the day away
♪ Hoping that your
prince will come ♪
♪ And take you faraway
♪ Oh, dream on, Cinderella
♪ Dreaming of the day
♪ Your handsome
prince will come ♪
♪ And take your heart away
♪ Oh, dream on, Cinderella
♪ Your dream is on the way
♪ Soon your handsome
prince will come ♪
♪ To take you faraway