(dramatic instrumental music)
- So the month of February
Canis Major is sitting in the south.
(instrumental piano music)
Sirius is prominent in the evening sky.
(instrumental piano music continues)
Perfect.
Sirius, the Dog Star,
his colors are magnificent.
As its light is broken up
in a multitude of ways,
as it makes it's way
through the atmosphere.
Perfect.
Sirius, perfect.
(thunder rumbles)
The shiniest, brightest star,
the Dog Star.
- I'm Sirius, the Dog Star.
- Dog Star,
the flaming snout of Orion,
8.6 million light-years away.
Orion was the most handsome
man who ever lived.
His two hunting dogs,
companions snappin' at his heels.
The Dog Star.
(thunder rumbles)
(Dad exhales loudly)
(gentle instrumental music)
- Dad?
- Just goes on forever and ever.
It never ends, it never ends.
- [Young Dogstar] It's infinite.
- [Marcus] It just goes on,
and on, and on.
- Goes on and on
forever and ever?
(gentle instrumental music continues)
(car engine rubles)
(rocks crunching)
(female speaks faintly)
(car door clatters)
(car doors thud shut)
(indistinct chattering)
(trunk clatters shut)
- Who's that?
- That's Dogstar.
- [Gabrielle] Oh, oh, so
it's Dogstar's birthday?
- Yeah.
- Hey, Dogstar!
Happy birthday!
- Come on.
(gentle instrumental music continues)
(chimes tinkle)
- Hello?
(gentle instrumental music continues)
(Dogstar clicks tongue)
(mellow instrumental music)
- Just goes on
forever and ever.
- It never ends.
Never ends.
(mellow instrumental music continues)
- Oh!
I didn't realize you were waiting.
- But it's true, I was waitin'.
I was in a state of readiness,
a state of anticipation.
(Gabrielle laughs)
I only wait for things I
think may be important.
- Oh-'kay.
(gentle instrumental music)
Hey.
You guys need any help?
- Would you get Dogstar for me?
- Oh, sure, sure.
- Okay.
(whispers indistinctly)
(both chuckle)
(dramatic instrumental music)
(door clatters)
(dramatic instrumental music continues)
(door thuds shut)
(Gabrielle scoffs)
- Hello?
(knocking on door)
(gentle instrumental music)
I'm really hungry.
(plate clatters)
- Hi.
- Oh, hi,
(Gabrielle speaks indistinctly)
- Would you take this for me?
- Hey, mom.
- Thank you.
Oh!
- What should I take?
- Just have a seat.
- Oh, I'll take that.
(Gabrielle speaks indistinctly)
Right here?
- Yeah, that's fine.
Perfect!
- [Arnold] Anything else, anything else?
- [Beth] No, my love.
(groaning)
(female laughs)
- Thanks.
(liquid sploshes)
(dramatic instrumental music)
- You're the one with the birthday?
- Sorry, what is your name?
- Happy birthday.
(Arnold chuckles)
I got you a present.
- This is Arnold, a hot new star in town.
- Hello, Arnold.
- Dogstar, I hear there's a comet coming.
Is it here yet?
- Hello, Gabrielle.
(dishes clang)
- So Dogstar,
happy birthday, mate.
Listen, I didn't have
to get you a present,
but, you know,
figured you're gettin'
a bit old for all that.
- No, you're just getting too cheap.
- So where's yours then?
Bring it on.
- After dinner, we always
get it after dinner.
- Why wait?
- Happy birthday.
(Arnold stammers)
- [Beth] All right,
does everyone have wine?
- Yeah.
- Thank you.
- Let us give thanks
for the provision of food,
and thanks for
the joyous company.
- Thank you all very much.
Thank you.
- Thanks.
- Thank you.
- Amen.
- Mom, is dad coming?
(Astro chuckles)
- He'll be along in just a minute, mate.
- [Beth] I think he's in India,
is he?
(Cassy scoffs)
- He's probably off finding
himself again or something.
- Are you eating properly?
- He likes to be a starving poet.
- Thank you.
- Poeta nascitur,
non fit, right, Arnie?
- If that's true, then there's no hope.
- There's only no hope
if you have to reform those who are evil.
In my opinion, reform is a waste of time.
We should simply lock 'em
up, and throw away the key.
- Are you saying, people
are just born one way,
a poet or a criminal, and
you can't change them?
- Yes dear, poeta nascitur, non fit.
We are what we are.
No point in trying to reform evil.
- Well, some people do bad
things 'cause they're desperate,
like hungry or something.
- [Astro] Yes, but I think
the point here really is,
why would they be desperate
in the first place?
- So you're saying only
bad people get desperate?
- [Cassy] Good point.
Come on then.
- No, not really a good point at all.
The point is, that we are born how we are.
Nature not nurture.
Nor more can a bricklayer
deny his true destiny
than can a poet.
- You know it reminds me of a story of
"The Turtle and Scorpion",
and the scorpion wants to
get across the river, right?
So he asked the turtle,
- Pass the bread.
- And he turtle says,
"Okay, but don't sting me",
and the scorpion says,
"I won't, 'cause I wanna
get across the river".
Anyway, they get to the middle,
and they're out in the middle,
- Pass the butter,
would you, sweetheart?
- [Gabrielle] and the
Scorpion stings the turtle,
and they both sink.
- Scorpions always sting.
- Yeah, and turtles are always stupid.
So you agree with me then, Gabrielle?
- No, I like turtles.
- Well, we can't help
contemplating our existence.
It's the only thing that
separates us from the rocks.
(Gabriel laughs)
- [Astro] Now, there's
a lot of crap out there.
People are looking for answers,
and producing nothing but junk.
- [Cassy] That's just your opinion.
- Have you got anything to add, brother?
(bowl clangs)
- Mom, you make the
most incredible dinner.
(Arnold laughs)
- Good.
- Yeah, really good, mom.
- Yes, yes, yes.
- Very good.
- The garden of science and of truth,
of these subjects, what
have you got to say?
- Don't be mean.
- Mean, what's mean?
He's a grown man, he has opinions.
- You're a bully!
- [Astro] I'm purely interested.
- No, Cassy, it's all right.
See, if people are constantly
wrestling with life,
and searching for answers,
then, of course, they're
gonna find some comfort
in philosophy, religion, in art.
- Oh, I find no comfort in it.
- I just think that accepting
that there is no one single
finite answer to anything
is the hardest thing for people to do.
- So in your book, it's
absurd to even conceive God?
- Absurd, Astro, my dear
brother, is your word.
Me, I just happen to
really love my dinner.
(all chuckling)
- Happy birthday, my dear Dogstar.
- Well, maybe I should
take this opportunity
to kiss you now?
- Do you ever rest?
- Astro?
- You know what they say,
the lovely Cassiopeia,
"Ars longa, vita brevis".
- Up your ass, too.
- Go on, give us a little kiss.
- Astro, she does not wanna kiss you.
- Are you suffering from lack of love?
Here, I'll kiss you.
(smooches)
- Listen, that reminds me,
I'm a little bit short of cash this week.
Have you got any I could borrow?
(gentle instrumental music)
(water splashes)
(object clangs)
(dishes clatter)
(gentle instrumental music continues)
(cups clang)
(water continues splashing)
(dishes clang and clatter)
(cabinet door thuds shut)
(water continues splashing)
- There, all done.
I actually enjoyed that.
(footsteps clomping)
- Gabrielle, Mark's waiting.
Do you wanna come with us to the studio?
We could rehearse, and you
could sing or something.
- Sure.
- Where's Beth?
- She went somewhere
with Arnold.
(Cassy scoffs)
- Just-
- I like her.
She's cool.
- I wish she'd act her age.
Come on.
(footsteps descending)
(gravel crunches)
- Dad?
(guitar strums upbeat tune)
(gravel crunches)
- It never ends.
Never ends.
(Dogstar exhales loudly)
(chair creaks)
(Dogstar sighs loudly)
- Oh, are you hungry?
Did I forget about you?
Would you like a red one or a green one?
(Dogstar sighs loudly)
Do you think she was a
little shooting star?
What?
Serious B?
You must be out of your mind.
Is your food out of date?
Are you tripping on me?
You little terror.
(Dogstar exhales loudly)
(Dogstar groans)
(gentle instrumental music)
(tinging)
- Dogstar!
(rock tings)
Dogstar!
Hi, Dogstar.
Dogstar, it's me Gabbi.
Hey.
Oops.
It's big.
(footsteps clomping)
Dogstar?
(Gabrielle thuds)
(footsteps clomping)
(Gabrielle sighs)
I brought you a present.
- Are you okay?
- Uh-huh.
(Dogstar imitates popping sound)
I'm tired.
(Dogstar groans)
- Very lovely.
(footsteps clomp)
Very lovely.
Un, deux, trois, quatre, cinq.
Gabrielle?
(gentle celestial music)
(gentle instrumental music)
Gabrielle?
(gentle instrumental music continues)
(car engine roars)
(radio stations play indistinctly)
(mellow instrumental music)
♪ An angel has come here as one ♪
♪ Still so close to where she's from ♪
♪ Beautiful child, her newborn eyes ♪
♪ Sleep sound, the day is done ♪
♪ Sleep my child, sweet to hold ♪
♪ The world is yours to unfold ♪
(car door clatters)
♪ Sleep my child ♪
(car door slams shut)
♪ Sweet to hold ♪
♪ The world is yours to unfold ♪
(car door slams shut)
(footsteps ascending)
♪ Mother and father will praise the Lord ♪
♪ Praise the Lord, praise the Lord ♪
♪ Praise the Lord ♪
- Hey.
- You look like shit.
- [Nicky] Well, you're not
lookin' too hot yourself.
What's up?
- I need to get a job.
(paper crinkles)
(objects clatter)
(phone thuds)
Shit.
It hasn't been paid, has it?
- Relax, it's a phone, you know?
Don't stress.
- I just want the phone to work.
You know, I need to get a job,
and I need to get out of this
shittin' nothing fucking work.
- Everything will work out,
you have to lighten up, you know?
Chill out.
- No, I don't...
Thanks, I don't wanna relax.
(Gabrielle moans)
- You know,
your problem is you're floating.
You're swimming
(both laughing)
upstream.
(Nicky giggles)
Where have you been, anyway?
- Somewhere.
(box clatters)
Hey, don't go.
- I'll be right here if you need me.
I'm not goin' away.
(Dogstar groans)
- She's still here.
♪ Twinkle twinkle little star ♪
♪ How I wonder what you are ♪
(gentle instrumental music)
- [Voice Of Gabrielle] Hi, Dogstar.
Hi, Dogstar!
- [Voice Of Astro] Well, maybe I should
take this opportunity
- She does not
- to kiss you now?
- [Voice Of Dogstar] want to kiss you.
- [Voice Of Gabrielle]
Dogstar, it's me, Gabbi.
Gabbi.
Hi, Dogstar.
- Mom, is dad coming?
- [Voice Of Gabrielle] Hi, Dogstar.
- [Voice Of Astro] Go on,
give us a little kiss.
- [Voice Of Dogstar] She
does not wanna kiss you.
(Dogstar's voice continues echoing)
(pounding on door)
(pounding on door continues)
(door clatters shut)
- There you are. It's a bit
late to be gettin' up, isn't it?
(Dogstar sighs)
- Mom's gone with Arnold to the show.
(Astro clicks teeth)
- Fuck!
I needed her here.
Listen, have got any money I could borrow?
- She'll be back later.
(Astro scoffs)
(fingers snapping)
- Looks like you had a rough night.
What have you been up to?
Hmm, well, listen,
maybe she left it out for me?
Hey, where's the show?
(door clatters shut)
(knocking on door)
- Go away.
(Gabrielle exhales loudly)
What's wrong with you?
- I'm orbiting, man.
(object clangs)
Everything is right.
(Nicky groans)
(Nicky exhales loudly)
I love you.
- I love you too, Nick.
- Are you happy?
(Gabrielle chuckles)
- Mm-mmm.
- What are you gonna do?
(Gabrielle exhales loudly)
I want you to be happy.
I'm happy.
- I'm glad for you.
- I wanna make you happy.
I wanna help you be happy.
(bag clatters)
You'd never hurt me.
- Everything's gonna be okay, right?
(objects in bag clatter)
I feel sick.
- Are you happy now?
(Gabrielle sighs loudly)
- Never felt happier.
- From that first big bang,
an eternal Titanic explosion,
stars rushing away from us, expanding,
like being flung out like
droplets of water off
a shaking dog's back.
(tinging)
(Dogstar breathes heavily)
(object clatters)
(Gabrielle thuds and groans)
- I feel happy here.
(Gabrielle sighs)
- I told you she'd be back, didn't I?
I knew you'd be back,
'cause you left something here.
You left it in my bed,
- Oh.
- in my bed.
- I need that.
- I drew it for you.
- Thank you.
Can I sleep here tonight?
(Dogstar clears throat)
- Before we go any further,
I think you and I should
get something straight
between us, all right?
What I wanna know is, are you in trouble?
- No.
- You're in trouble,
aren't you?
- No, I just wanna sleep.
- Oh.
Oh, it's all right then.
(Gabrielle groans)
You can stay.
- Thank you.
Dogstar?
You never go out, do you?
- No, never.
- It's okay.
You should always stay here.
I feel sorry for it.
- [Dogstar] Why?
- [Gabrielle] I'd hate to
be trapped in small space
going 'round and 'round like that.
- [Dogstar] Oh, it
doesn't remember its way
from one side to the other.
- [Gabrielle] It remembers how to swim.
- [Dogstar] He doesn't
have much choice, does he?
- The world beyond the
bowl must seem endless.
You think it wonders?
I dream about floating in big oceans
full of colorful fish and sea plants,
and when I wake up,
I can remember how beautiful it was,
but I can't quite see it
like it was in my dreams.
Oh, god.
I can't believe that...
I can't believe that I just showed up here
in the middle of the night,
and I slept in your bed,
and I've taken a shower,
and said all this really stupid stuff.
- Well, I don't get very many visitors.
- [Gabrielle] I mean, I hardly
even know you, and here I am.
- I know, here you are.
- I should go.
Should I?
- Do you wanna go?
- You want me to?
- Goldie and I might miss you if you go.
(Gabrielle sighs loudly)
(melancholic music)
- Here, put it back.
- Thanks.
- Like a shiny, bright new star.
- You are a star too.
What are you?
- Sirius.
- Sirius?
- Sirius, the Dog Star.
- The Dog Star.
- Show me.
Oh, I can't see anything.
You look.
- [Dogstar] Let's not fret.
(Dogstar mumbles)
- Okay.
- Like here?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- And just tell me when you see something.
(Dogstar mumbles)
(Gabrielle chuckles)
Maybe?
Hold still.
- It's a very bright star.
(gentle instrumental music)
(Gabrielle coughs)
(car engine roars)
(car door clatters)
(car door slams shut)
(Gabrielle breathes heavily)
(gears clatter)
(car engine whirs)
Nicky?
- Where have you been?
What time is it?
- Nicky, you gotta help me.
(Nicky moans)
- Sure, baby.
Sure.
- Nicky, don't go back to sleep.
(Nicky sighs loudly)
- We'll take care of you.
Do you have any money?
- [Astro] Einstein said, "Science
without religion is lame,
religion without science is blind".
- You're good at remembering
what other people say, aren't you?
- If it interests me, only then.
So how's your little show going?
Anyone actually turn
up for that, did they?
- Ah, he's doing amazing.
There are two galleries in Los Angeles
that's gonna show his work.
- Your mom's been very special to me.
- I'll bet.
Where did that girl go, by the way?
- I don't know.
- She's very quiet.
- Oh, I like that, though.
Quiet and calm on the surface,
a raging volcano underneath.
- You like to provoke people, don't you?
- Only by provoking people
can we reveal their true natures.
Anything to add, brother,
or is the construction of the zen garden
keeping you a bit occupied right now?
- Only your true nature is
revealed by provoking people.
- What?
What?
I can't even hear him.
- Only your true nature is
revealed by provoking people!
(utensil clangs)
- Don't you ever wanna get
to the bottom of things?
Disagree with inconsistencies?
Make small-minded people
see the small-mindness of their ways?
- Honey.
- Do you never
wanna get to-
- Typical type A personality.
You'll die young if you're not careful.
- Whom the gods love, die young.
- Ah, but you don't believe in God.
- It's a saying, Arnold.
It's just a saying.
- Where is he going?
- You know what?
That's about the smartest thing
that's ever come out of your mouth.
Where does he ever go?
- He's a funny one.
He's a funny one.
- Everything's so funny, funny, funny.
(food clangs)
(Arnold sighs)
- Please, now, there is
nothing wrong with him.
The world's just a little too
noisy for him, that's all.
- Well, whatever.
Listen, can I borrow a little bit of cash?
I'm just a bit short right now.
- In my bag.
- Thanks.
(smooches)
(upbeat mellow music)
(money rustles)
(door creaks)
♪ I'm going to town to see my baby ♪
♪ Got her a diamond ring for her to try ♪
- Yeah.
♪ And if that girl wanna take my hand ♪
- Yeah
♪ Forever this time ♪
♪ I'm gonna be her man ♪
- Bye.
♪ Mm mmm ♪
(phone clatters)
♪ When I got to her door,
she'd been drinking ♪
♪ And being a wife ain't
she was thinking about ♪
♪ By the morning ♪
♪ You'll be gone ♪
- Can I get you
anything to drink, ma'am?
Ma'am?
Can I get you anything to drink?
- Oh, sorry.
Yeah, a decaf.
- All right.
(upbeat mellow music continues)
♪ Lady, I'm not sure what else to do ♪
♪ Now that there ain't no
more me and you no more ♪
(tinging)
- Wow, there are colors too.
- Looking at that blue speck
is like seeing the
beginning of the universe,
a faint glimpse into
your past, ancient light.
- I always thought the universe
was just black and white.
- [Young Dogstar] What star is that?
- The same star-
- Great Orion Nebula
is fuzzy and huey green.
Antares, the Red Giant,
is actually pale orange.
Vega's white with a bluish cast.
And little Albireo, the
star at the beak of Cygnus,
the Swan, a binary star,
with a star partner.
- Star partners, how beautiful.
Together forever, orbiting
around, and 'round, and 'round.
Where'd they all come from?
Where's Dog Star?
- [Voice Of Marcus] The
shiniest brightest star.
- To the diagonal left of Orion.
- It's twinkling.
Here, you look.
(Gabrielle groans)
- Sirius, the Dog Star, has a star partner
orbiting with it.
- Perfect.
Sirius, perfect.
- A star partner?
- Sirius B.
- Are you cold?
- I need to lie down, sleep more.
(Gabrielle groans)
- Hmm, you don't look very well.
Where's your little star gone?
- I lost it.
- It's gone.
(knocking at door)
- [Astro] Is Gabrielle in there?
- What was that?
(knocking at door continues)
(Dogstar groans)
- Chaos.
(door clatters)
Why are you here?
- Me?
I'm just checking
everything's all right, okay?
- Everything's fine, all right?
It's beautiful.
Bellissimo, thank you for asking.
How 'bout you?
- Me?
All right, here it is.
I'm a bit strapped for cash.
What have you got?
Then I'll take that as a no.
- Can't Cassy help you?
- Cassy?
Hmm, maybe.
(tapping)
Maybe, maybe Gabrielle's got something.
- She's sleeping.
- Should we have a look?
All right, where's Beth?
- Beth, she's gone away.
She's away.
- Gone where?
- I don't know.
I don't ask any questions, all right?
I stay in my room.
- Beth's gone, no money, this,
this is fucking great, mate.
This is great.
- Well, what do you expect?
- For god's sake.
(door clatters)
(door thuds shut)
- I have to go.
I'm going.
- Maybe you should stay?
You don't look very well.
- I can't stay.
I need to go.
- [Voice Of Gabrielle] Star partner.
Sirius B.
- Perfect.
Sirius, perfect.
(car engine whirs)
(chair creaks)
- Goldie and I might miss you
if you go.
Where's your little star gone?
- [Voice Of Gabrielle] I lost it.
(money crinkles)
(statue clangs)
Dogstar, Dogstar.
(heavy breathing)
You never go out, do you?
(upbeat jazz music)
(car door slams shut)
(car engine whirs)
(motor revs)
(upbeat jazz music continues)
(gravel crunches)
(car door slams shut)
(upbeat jazz music continues)
(door slams shut)
(gravel crunches)
(car door slams shut)
(Dogstar laughs)
- You see?
Who's afraid of the big bad wolf?
(tinging)
(mellow music)
Gabrielle?
♪ There's a face in the moon ♪
♪ And he'll watch over me ♪
♪ Until the sun ♪
(door clatters)
♪ Rises up from the sea ♪
♪ The stars in the sky never lie ♪
♪ And they told me ♪
♪ I could wish for one dream ♪
♪ So when you see me in the night ♪
♪ Starin' up at the sky ♪
(gravel crunches)
♪ I'll be wishing you'll be mine ♪
(crickets chirping)
(gravel crunches)
(mellow music continues)
♪ Goin' down the lake ♪
♪ Goin' to the lake ♪
♪ Oh, it's a dirty, dirty, dirty car ♪
♪ So oh oh ♪
(knocking at door)
- Dogstar, honey?
Arnold and I have to go to
LA for a couple of days.
Will you be okay?
- Don't worry about me, mom.
I'll be okay.
(jewelry box clicks)
(Dogstar breathes heavily)
(knocking at door)
- Brother?
(Dogstar groans)
You in there?
- No!
- No?
- God, you get worse.
Look, I need your help, man.
(door clatters shut)
- Or I'll huff and
I'll, huff and I'll blow your house down!
- Look, I really need to borrow some cash.
- Mom stopped giving me
pocket money years ago.
- Oh, yeah?
Look, I wouldn't ask, you know that,
unless I really had to,
but, you know, mom's out,
and you're a good guy,
and everything like that,
and if I could just have
a little bit of cash,
or something like that?
Do you use this old thing anymore?
- Well, I don't look through it.
- [Arnold] It's been
here a while, isn't it?
Gatherin' dust, doing nothing.
- It was a gift from dad.
- Can I borrow it for a while?
There's a comet coming, you know?
- And what are you gonna
do, go looking for a comet?
- No, I'll be honest with you, brother.
I'm gonna take that and
get some money on it,
just until mom gets back.
Now, when she returns,
I'll have it back for ya.
I mean, let's be honest, you don't use it.
It probably doesn't work right anyway.
You won't miss it.
- Are you in trouble?
- Trouble?
Not me.
- Get your filthy hands off it.
(jewelry box clicks)
- Fascinating.
Is that for your new
girlfriend, by any chance?
- Right, it's for Gabrielle.
She lost the other one.
You can take the telescope.
- Be warned, brother,
women are dangerous.
- If you want to touch my
head, you've gotta pay for it.
(Arnold exhales loudly)
- Have you seen her recently?
(Dogstar sighs loudly)
- No, not in a while.
- [Arnold] Well, she
can't have been your type,
let's be honest.
- I feel sad.
I miss her.
- Well, sink or swim, brother.
Sink or swim.
(telescope clangs)
(telescope thuds)
(tapping)
(door slams shut)
- [Voice Of Dogstar] In the time it took
for the teardrop to roll off his cheek,
the spinning Earth carried
him half a mile to the East,
half a mile to the East.
The motion of the Earth about the sun
carried him back 40 miles westward.
And the turning pinwheel of the galaxy
carried him 300 miles in a great circle
about the galactic center.
And the drift of the solar system
among the stars of the Milky Way
bore him 20 miles towards the star Vega.
(dramatic instrumental music)
(rocks tinging)
(door thuds shut)
- Everything's gone.
Everything's gone.
42 million, 140, think, 2,241.
42,142,242.
42,142,243.
(both shivering)
42,142,246.
42,142,247.
Are you cold?
Jump!
42,247,148.
42 million, 247 thousand...
Come to me.
Come here!
(Dogstar shivers)
It's cold.
142 million, 247, yes.
- Where is it?
Where's the telescope, Dogstar?
- I gave it to Astro.
- Why?
- Because he needed it.
- What would he need it for?
- He wanted it.
- But there's a comet coming,
and I wanted to look at it with you,
and see the comet together.
- It's okay.
It's okay.
It's all still there.
(Gabrielle sniffles)
Why did you come?
- 'Cause I wanted to, more than anything.
(melancholic music)
(Gabrielle sniffles)
- I have something for you.
(melancholic music continues)
(Gabrielle sniffles)
(jewelry box creaks)
(gentle instrumental music)
- You went out?
(gentle instrumental music continues)
You went out?
You think there are people out there?
I mean, there must be if the
universe is infinite, right?
- Well, somewhere in the
center of the Milky Way,
near Sagittarius, is eaten matter.
- I can't see it.
- No, but if you listen
carefully, you can hear it.
It is constant and faint.
Radio waves, microwaves.
(Gabrielle laughs)
X-ray static.
The maelstrom even at
the center of Sagittarius
is a whirlpool of omni present
density feeding on stars.
It is a fierce monster, devouring light.
Imagine the weight of 100 million suns
condensed into one dark
seed chewing on suns,
and swallowing cosmic light.
- Yeah, people, you know,
they're like stars stuff too.
They are these big Red Giants.
You know, they're big, but
they're all hot gas inside,
and then you meet some,
and they're really hot and
bright, but they're small,
and they seem like they're gonna burn out
really fast and short,
and then others are just
like these lumps of rock,
and then there are the big
black holes devouring light.
Astro shouldn't have the telescope.
- Yeah, but he's my brother.
Are you lonely?
- When I'm with you I
feel like I've come home,
you know, close, like it's meant to be.
- Yeah, but you seem unhappy.
- Hmm, you know, some people
talk about eternal life,
but (chuckles) to me,
that seems like torture.
I mean, who'd wanna live forever?
(Gabrielle sniffles)
You promise I won't get
sucked into a black hole?
(Gabrielle laughs)
- Can I draw you some more?
- Mmm, I'm gonna lay down.
(paper rustles)
- Put your star in.
(jewelry box creaks)
(upbeat mellow music)
- Dogstar?
Dogstar?
♪ There's a face in the moon ♪
♪ And he'll watch over me ♪
- Dogstar, wake up!
♪ Until the sun ♪
- Wake up!
♪ Rises up from the sea ♪
Dogstar!
♪ The stars in the sky ♪
♪ Never rise ♪
- Wake up!
♪ And they told me I
could wish for a dream ♪
- What is wrong with you?
- It must've been something I ate.
- Should you not see a doctor?
- Maybe some water?
(Gabrielle shivers)
(cup clanks)
♪ The sun and the moon ♪
♪ And the deep blue sea ♪
(water sloshes)
♪ My darling, ♪
♪ Come and walk along with me ♪
(shower curtain rustles)
(water dripping)
♪ By my side growing older ♪
♪ In my arms I will hold her ♪
♪ Every night while we sleep ♪
♪ So when you see me in the night ♪
♪ Looking up at the sky ♪
♪ I'll be wishing that you'll be mine ♪
(gravel crunches)
(Gabrielle coughs)
(zipper zips)
(car door clatters)
(door alarm dings)
(Gabrielle coughs)
(car door slams shut)
(car engine whirs)
(gravel crunches)
- Nicky?
Nicky, she's not here.
No.
Look, I have waited, Nicky.
I...
Yes.
Yes, I know.
No, but she's not coming,
and I need her to come.
Nicky, you gotta help me.
Nicky?
Okay, I'll come home.
Bye.
(phone clatters)
- So Gabrielle?
You and Dogstar?
What'd you do to him?
Cast a spell on him?
(Gabrielle mumbles)
All right.
- Nothing.
- Nothin'?
How 'bout layin' some
of that nothin' on me?
Come on, what do you say?
Dogstar know about your
little secret, does he?
(mellow instrumental music)
(knocking at window)
- Gabrielle?
(knocking at window continues)
Gabrielle, what the hell
are you doin' out here?
Gabrielle?
What the hell are you doin' out here?
(car door clatters)
Babe, you look like hell.
Come on.
I'll take care of you.
- I'm lost, Nicky.
- I know, babe.
We're all lost.
Come on.
Come with Nicky.
- Who's seen the comet?
Have you, darling?
- Comet hot, comet cold, comet in the sky,
let the future be told.
But I can't find it!
I can't find it!
- Something seems definitely odd.
- He really misses his dad.
- Actually, it's girl trouble.
- How can that be?
- Gabrielle dumped him.
- What do you mean?
- Well, I don't know how much
she was here, but she was,
and now she's not.
Dogstar fell for it,
and now he's mourning.
- She seemed like such a sweet girl.
- No, she wasn't.
She's a slut.
- Cassiopeia.
- You shouldn't negate
a woman's sexual being.
- Most definitely not.
- But she is a slut.
- I thought she was your friend?
- Was.
- Hmm.
(dramatic instrumental music)
(intense dramatic music)
- [Gabrielle] What's this worth?
(intense dramatic music continues)
- [Beth] Cassy and Astro seem to feel
that you may be unhappy
because of Gabrielle.
- That's because I miss her.
- She's no good, honestly.
- No good for what, Astro?
- She's just no good for you.
- Dog, you can't trust her.
- Can't trust her, Cassy?
With what?
What have I got?
My reputation?
(Dogstar sobs)
My low self-esteem?
- [Cassy] We're just worried.
We're concerned.
- How dare you?
- She's no good.
I feel very strongly about this.
- You don't understand!
You know nothing!
- Now, that's not quite true.
I know a lot about that girl.
- Astro, do you know that I love her?
- Listen, mom's trying to say
something here, all right?
She's trying to talk some sense into you.
- Leave me alone, Astro.
(Astro scoffs)
- I worry about you.
- Dogstar?
(footsteps clomp)
- [Astro] Well, well, well.
- Go away, Astro!
You go away, Astro!
- [Astro] Ask her where
her lovely diamond is.
- You go away, Astro!
You go away!
Go away, Astro!
- You won't?
I will.
Tell him, Gabrielle.
- Leave her alone, Astro!
- Tell him what you did with it.
- Tell me about that
beautiful stone that he bought you.
- You leave her alone!
- Look at him.
My brother, who never leaves the house.
You know what?
Never leaves his fucking bedroom.,
went into town for you,
went on to town, and bought
that beautiful stone.
And what'd you do with it?
- Leave her alone!
- I think maybe we know.
What'd she do with it?
She sold it!
For what, what'd she sell it for?
Her smack.
- Leave her alone!
You didn't sell it.
- I did, but not-
- [Astro] Keep away from
her, mate. She's small time.
- She didn't sell it.
- She's small time.
- You didn't sell it.
You didn't sell it.
- Yeah, she sold it.
- No, she didn't sell it!
- No-
Nothing but trouble.
- I did, but he was
gonna take-
- She did.
See?
- He didn't get it.
- She's admitting it.
- Leave her alone.
- You didn't sell it.
- Look at you.
- You're nothing but trouble, hey?
You're nothing but trouble.
- You sold it.
- You're no good.
- Dogstar!
- You sold it.
- [Astro] Get out of here!
- Dogstar!
- I want you out.
- Yeah?
Feel pretty fucking bad, don't you?
(Gabrielle wails)
(Gabrielle yells)
Out the fucking house.
(car door slams shut)
(Gabrielle wails) Get out!
And you take your dirty habit with you!
(car engine whirs)
(gravel crunches)
(upbeat mellow music)
(door clatters)
- [Gabrielle] Nicky?
♪ A smile and a tear ♪
♪ Turn another year ♪
- Nicky?
♪ Searching for a home ♪
♪ As time marches onward ♪
♪ Waisted breath talking ♪
♪ Though no one cares to listen ♪
♪ These wings were built to fly ♪
♪ Spread my wings ♪
(Gabrielle sobs)
♪ And touch the sky ♪
♪ These wings were built to fly ♪
♪ Spread my wings and touch the sky ♪
♪ Life ain't easy ♪
- Dog Star?
♪ But it's perspective ♪
♪ Everything seems small
this high off the ground ♪
♪ You can see for miles
and miles in the distance ♪
(objects clattering)
♪ These wings were built to fly ♪
♪ Spread my wings and touch the sky ♪
♪ Take these wings and learn to fly ♪
- Dog Star?
♪ Take these wings ♪
- Where are you?
♪ And touch the sky ♪
(Gabrielle sniffs)
♪ Take these wings and touch the sky ♪
(bottle clatters)
- Dog Star?
(Gabrielle exhales loudly)
(Gabrielle coughs)
♪ These wings were built to fly ♪
♪ Spread my wings ♪
♪ And touch the sky ♪
- Can't see you.
♪ These wings were built to fly ♪
♪ Take these wings ♪
♪ Touch the sky ♪
- [Voice Of Gabrielle] And
you promise I won't get
sucked into a black hole?
- No, I haven't been
in his room for years.
Please come right away.
All right, goodbye.
(melancholic music)
- You see, inside are
tiny pieces of glass,
and they bring the light from
thousands of light-years
away into your bedroom,
straight into your eye,
and into your head.
The Egyptians saw wheat spread by Isis.
For the Eskimos, the fall of snow.
Bushmen saw campfire ashes.
(knocking at door)
And the Arabs, a river.
- Hey, Dogstar?
It's me, dad.
I'd like to talk to you.
(door clatters)
(door slams shut)
(Beth sighs)
Did you see the comet?
(Dogstar sniffs loudly)
- No.
- My god, what a beauty she was.
A golden trail of light.
I saw her makin' her way
through the night sky,
on a journey across the universe.
(Dogstar sniffs loudly)
(Dogstar exhales loudly)
Alone and bright,
what a sight, what a sight.
(Dogstar sniffs loudly)
(melancholic music)
- I can't find her.
I can't find her.
- We'll find her.
(Dogstar sniffs loudly)
We'll find her Dogstar.
We'll find her.
(melancholic music continues)
(Dogstar sobs and sniffs)
Hey.
(dishes clang)
- Thank you.
(smooches)
Baby.
(Beth groans)
- How are you, man?
- I was so worried.
- Now, Star Shine.
- Hmm?
- We're goin' out.
- You're going out?
Dogstar?
- Dad's taking me to see Gabrielle.
- Wait, you two are gonna find her?
How are you gonna help him?
Dividing rods, crystals?
No one knows this town better me.
If anyone should help him, I should.
- This is between me and dad.
- No, this is between you and me.
- Marcus?
- Dad promised me.
- Listen, no disrespect, but dad,
dad has trouble finding
his way around the kitchen.
- Astro.
- You know it's true.
Where is he gonna go?
Where is he gonna look?
- Astro.
- Dad?
- It's true!
- Tell him.
- Dogstar, this your journey now.
You should go with your brother.
- Dogstar, I've got one question.
Do you wanna find her, yes or no?
Yes or no?
We're off.
(glass clanks)
Listen, I need to borrow some money,
but it's just to borrow.
- Sure.
Here.
(Astro mumbles)
The keys.
- All right, thanks.
(footsteps ascending)
(car door clatters)
March, 1999, Agent Astro
enters porn shop with caution.
While prying an answer out
of the half-witted owner,
his brother, Dogstar, keeps a
vigilant eye over the street.
I have information.
- Just tell me what he said.
- Actually, bugger all,
but I know where we're gonna go next.
- Where?
- Nicky Peterson.
- I think she mentioned Nicky Peterson.
- Well, we find Nicky, we find Gabrielle.
- Well, how do we find her?
- Aren't you glad I'm here?
(Dogstar exhales loudly)
- Why do you want to help me?
- Because brother, you're my brother.
(car engine whirs)
Let's go.
- Let me show you something.
- What?
- Come on.
(mellow instrumental music)
(footsteps clomping)
(object thuds)
(Dogstar claps)
(knocking at door)
- You must be Nicky?
I'm looking for Gabrielle.
- Who are you?
- I'm Astro.
I'm here with my brother, Dogstar.
Dogstar?
- Ah, man, Dogstar.
Gabrielle, my lovely Gabrielle,
just wanted to be happy, you know?
She...
When something like this happens,
you either-
- Is she here?
- She's gone, man, you know?
- No, I don't know what you
mean. What on earth do you mean?
- She overdid it, choked, you know?
I found her.
She didn't know what she was doing.
She was so sick.
- Never ever tell him how you found her.
- I knew I shouldn't have
left her there, you know?
- [Astro] When did you find her?
- It was like last week.
It was on a Sunday.
No, Monday.
Yeah, it was Monday.
- [Astro] This isn't right, Dog.
This isn't right.
- No, it's her car.
It's her car!
- Oh, well, he's gotta come in,
'cause she had something
she wanted to give him,
but I just didn't get to it yet.
- Sorry.
- Where's Gabrielle?
Where's Gabrielle?
- She said she felt like
she always knew you.
She pawned her diamond for the telescope,
and she wanted to bring it to you.
- Where is she?
- She's gone.
- When is she coming back?
- No, she's gone away forever.
- Where's she gone?
(Astro sighs loudly)
- To make a new start.
I don't know.
- She was in my arms,
and I let her go.
- I'm sorry.
(Dogstar sniffs loudly)
- It's all just...
It's all just absurd!
It's all absurd!
Oh, that's your word, Astro.
Well, now I know what you mean.
Now I know what you mean.
(somber instrumental music)
(toy clanks a whirs)
(somber instrumental music continues)
Did this belong to Gabrielle?
(object clatters)
(crickets chirping)
- Should we go get him?
- Let him go.
(somber instrumental music)
(gentle instrumental music)
(upbeat mellow music)
♪ A smile and a tear ♪
♪ Turn another year ♪
♪ Searching for a home ♪
♪ As time marches onward ♪
♪ Wasted breath talking ♪
♪ Though no one cares to listen ♪
♪ These wings were built to fly ♪
♪ Spread my wings and touch the sky ♪
♪ Life ain't easy ♪
♪ But it's all perspective ♪
♪ Everything seems small
this high off the ground ♪
♪ You can see for miles
and miles in the distance ♪
♪ These wings were built to fly ♪
♪ Spread my wings and touch the sky ♪
♪ Take these wings and learn to fly ♪
♪ Take these wings, touch the sky ♪
♪ Take these wings and touch the sky ♪