(bright music)
(whistles)
(country music)
(dramatic music)
(growls)
(rumbles)
(exciting music)
(horse whinnies)
(plucks violin)
- So, tuning your violin again, Papa.
Just in case ask me to play
at the cheese festival today, Mama.
- (laughs) You'll play Papa, whether they ask you to or not.
(laughs)
- That cheesecake smells fantastic, Mama.
You'll win the blue ribbon for sure.
- Not if there's a piece missing I won't.
- Oh, that's not right.
(gurgles)
How will I ever get ready,
was supposed to be watching the baby?
- He was, now where has that boy disappeared to this time?
- He quietly approached the savage beast
then prepared to make his move.
The Lonesome Ranger spied the wildcat up ahead.
There's the wildcat now.
(growls)
Yeehaw!
I'll tame you yet, you ornery critter!
(growls)
(screams)
(shouts)
- Do hurry Chula, my arm is getting tired.
m almost there boss, just a little lower.
(whines)
(shouts)
- [Homeowner] Ah, a spider!
(growls)
(moans)
- Well, what have we here?
- Uh-oh.
- I was looking forward to a roast chicken dinner
for a Mouseling canape instead.
(gulps)
(moans)
come back here you rodent.
That was a close one.
- Forgive me Fievel, I didn't recognize you.
Now come out and we'll shake hands
and make up like gentlemen.
- Chula quick, our lunch is right under your feet.
(moans)
- Gotcha!
(laughs evilly)
(coughs)
The traffic in this town is intolerable.
Now, where were we!
(shouts)
- Whoa!
- Come back I say.
(action music)
(laughs)
- Who did that?
- [Sidekicks] Yeah, who did that?
(clatters)
- Howdy, partner.
(moans)
- Fievel, where have you been?
(pants)
- Hmm, most intriguing, now I see where I can locate lunch
at my convenience.
This is (shouts)
- I thought I told you to stay out of our alley, Wall?
- Yeah. - That's right.
- Now, you've gone and interrupted my meal.
And I hate when that happens.
- Yeah, he hates when that happens.
- Shut up, Slim.
- Yeah, shut up, right chief.
- Why, Sweet William, and his delightful alley cat friends.
I was just looking for you gentlemen.
- It seems that we have a problem in common,
namely, proper nourishment and how to obtain it
with the least amount of effort.
It just so happens I have a plan.
- Sorry I'm late, buckaroo.
But I was busy roping me a wildcat.
But instead you were out daydreaming again.
- But Papa, I was just,
- Someday Fievel, your imagination is going
to get you into serious trouble.
- Yes, Papa.
- Come on everybody, the wagon is here
to take us to the cheese festival.
(playful music)
- G'day mates.
(sniffs)
Smells like a mighty tasty cheesecake
- And how is the Smythe family today, Glynis?
- As we used to say in Australia Mr M,
- G'day Fievel, how's about we ride the wheel?
- Oh boy, can I Papa, can I?
- I suppose so Fievel, as long as you keep an eye on Yasha.
-Oh.
(laughs)
Gosh, I forgot my Lonesome Ran er Lariat.
I gotta go back and get it.
- [Driver] Giddy up.
(horse neighs)
Don't worry Yasha, I'll catch up.
(moans)
Got it, whoa!
(clangs)
Help, I'm trapped!
- Fievel, bye bye.
(dramatic music)
- Help, I'm trapped in here.
can anybody hear me
- Gentlemen I assure you, your money will be well spent.
My mouse tasting tour of Green River
will be remembered as one of the splendid moments,
in culinary history .
- What are you trying to say, Wall?
- I mean, we'll be eating mice til we drop.
- Then what are we waiting for?
- Ah, after you, gentlemen.
- Gentlemen, thanks boss.
- [Wall] Not you, bug face.
- What did I do, what did I do?
- Is anybody out there?
Please help me.
Papa help, I'm in here, hey, what's going on,
- Fievel, buddy, where is everyone?
On vacation, or what?
The town’s deserted, the humans are gone.
- The whole town went to the cheese festival
at Harvest Meadow.
And I missed the wagon.
- You mean you’re home alone?
- Don't you see, Tiger, I was supposed to look after Yasha.
And now I've let Papa down, again.
- Hey, no problem, let's go find 'em, come on, Fief.
(laughs)
Which way to Harvest Meadow?
- You know what they say, when the mice are away
the cats will play.
town to ourselves,
hey, lets play a game of cat and mouse.
(laughs)
- One one thousand, two one thousand.
- Okay okay, where can I hide?
It's got to be a place he'll never think of looking.
Oh, ha ha, that's it, he'll never find me there, (laughs)
(moans)
I take that back, bad, bad idea.
I'm stuck.
- [Sweet William] All right, what you doing down there?
- Wow, Fievel, that's amazing,
you sound just like Sweet William.
Hey, hi, I mean howdy fellas.
- All right pal, we came here to eat some mice,
what did you do with 'em?
- Mice, there's no mice around here, Mouseless.
(shouts)
oh no, they've got tiger
(bright music)
- Yasha, where's your brother?
(gurgles)
Fievel, where are you?
- Jack here says he saw Fievel run back into the house
- Oh, that means we left him back in Green River.
And the wagon won't be returning until dusk!
- Fievel.
- Ah, don't you fret, we'll find another way to get back.
- It's not fair, Papa, while we worry about Fievel,
he's probably out playing with that silly Tiger.
- No, no, oh no, please, you're killing me, ah stop.
please, (laughs) i can't, wooho
oh please, oh please, oh tell him to stop
- All right you mouse in a yellow bellied cat suit.
I'm a give you one more chance,
where are the mice?
I already told ya, they're not here.
They all left town for a picnic.
- Oh, so the mice are all gone huh?
If you’ve crossed me Catterwall,
they'll find bits of your fur scatted
from here to Boot Hill.
(laughs)
- Oh, tut, tut, tut, gentlemen.
This is becoming tiresome,
this pathetic excuse for a feline
is obviously prevaricating.
that's right
And he's lying too.
- There are mice here and I can prove it.
what would the lonesome ranger do?
what would the Lonesome Ranger do?
(chomps) (dramatic music)
A good cowboy always has his lasso handy.
(growls)
(moans)
(barks)
Uh-oh.
Whoa!
- Oof, oh.
Gentlemen, I rest my case, I said there were mice
in Green River and here is my proof.
- Oh, that's not proof, that's Fievel.
- No, that’s supper.
(laughs) (cheers)
(laughs evilly)
- Give up you bushwhackers,
my men have this place surrounded.
(laughs evilly)
- Indeed.
Then why not just open the door and invite them in.
(growls) (gasps)
(barks)
(shouts)
(yells)
(groans)
(plops)
- [Wall] Get off, get off me.
(squeaks)
(yells)
- Fievel, you saved the day, what a guy!
- Yeah, but if I know Catterwall, those cats'll tear
So we leave town too, right?
- Wrong, the Lonesome Ranger doesn’t run
for trouble, partner
It's time to take a stand.
- You sure this thing is seaworthy, Cyrus?
- I'd bet a wallaby' widget on it.
With a canoe like this we could hunt crocs in the outback.
- Pappy, bye bye.
(dramatic music)
- Well, where was I before we were so rudely interrupted.
(snaps) Ah es.
- I'm tired of your puss footing Catterwall.
All this running around has made me powerful hungry.
We spread out, (mumbles)
oh yeah, yeah, so we can surround 'em.
- [Minions] Great idea chief.
- All right.
Let's get 'em.
(laughs)
- No Chula,
(yawns)
run along and terrify some mice if you must,
even ingest one or three but I must catch a brief cat nap.
over my dead body, wall
You took our money and now you’re gonna earn it or else.
- On second thought, I do love the thrill of the chase.
(shouts)
(tense music)
- Okay, tiger, lower away
Make your move, pole cat.
Let's go, I'm talking to you fur head.
(laughs)
- That’s two down and let me see, three take away four
is seven, no, no, no, wait, wait, what am I doing?
maths is my worst subject
(dramatic music)
- Go in and flesh him out, Wall, and then I'll put him
out of our misery.
(yells)
- I loathe this running around as much as you do, Fievel.
Hmm, I assure you if you give up
I'll make it quick and painless.
- I'm not finished with you yet, hombre.
- That is that last straw!
(bangs)
I'll have that nap now!
(plops)
- You good for nothing tin horn,
guess I'll have to handle this one myself.
When I get my hands on you mice,
I'm gonna, (groans)
Hey, cat.
You want a mouse to munch.
keep it up tiger
- How bout picking on one your own size!
- Yeah, well, you’re one big rodent.
- I knew you was yella.
- With a mouse your size I'll be snacking for a week.
- Tiger, we've got a problem.
- We've got a problem, you double dealing,
oh, Fievel, run for it.
(dramatic music)
- Why you!
(yells)
(grunts)
- I've got you now, cheese eater.
(laughs evilly)
yeah, now I getcha, (laughs evilly) yeah.
(shouts)
(poofs)
(laughs)
(sneezes)
(playful music)
(moans)
(splashes)
- [Wall] You oaf!
Go away, go back to your.
(shouts)
(yowls)
(meows)
(squeals)
(spits)
- That's mud in your eye, partner.
- You forgot about me, little furball.
Now it’s dinner time.
(groans)
- Hey Fievel, come here quick.
- Doesn't anybody knock anymore?
- Papa.
(laughs)
Fievel, you worried your mother sick, what happened to you?
- I thought I had time to go back inside
and get my Lonesome Ranger lariat,
but I'm sorry I let you down, Papa.
- Well, the important thing is that you’re okay.
We were afraid the cats would get you.
- The cats?
Let me tell you pilgrim, they came outta nowhere,
five of 'em, it was a brutal battle
but when the smoke cleared he town was saved.
(claps)
And me and my trusty sidekick
were the only two left standing.
(laughs)
- Oh Fievel, such a tall tale,
what am I ever going to do with you?
(country music)