MAN: Somebody bet.
Will you, please?
JOHNNY: Come on, all bets.
It's up to you.
MAN: I bet.
I bet.
Blue, blue, blue.
MAN: Come on.
MAN: Oh.
JOHNNY: Are you staying
looking at three queens?
NINO: What the hell
you hollaring about?
JOHNNY: Oh, come on.
How does the man stay in?
You know what?
Forget about it.
[interposing voices]
MAN: You are a moax.
You are a moax.
MAN: I'm playing with my money.
MAN: You know, I'm disgusted
with the two of yous.
I'll talk to yous later.
Not for nothing, you know?
MAN: You're good, kid.
You're real good.
But as long as I'm around,
you'll always be second best.
MAN: [inaudible], see?
Yeah, Moses.
Where's your Jesus now?
MAN: What is that supposed
to mean, [inaudible]?
MAN: What?
MAN: What is that?
What am I, [inaudible]
of the year.
MAN: If you cook the steak too
long, defeats us on purpose.
Looks like a piece of charcoal.
MAN: Oh, bring it over.
MAN: I don't know.
I don't know.
MAN: Bada-boom, bada-bing.
Bada-boom, bada-bing.
MAN: First they come after
you, then they come after me.
MAN: I don't know.
I don't frigging know.
[music playing]
[doorbell ringing]
-Hey, you son of a bitch.
You're dead.
[shouting]
-No.
No.
Not here.
They don't know me.
-Come on, Dory and Steve.
Cut it out.
You're scary the kids.
It's not funny.
[laughter]
-[inaudible].
Thank you.
-Can we sit them
at the kids' table?
-Definitely.
-I'm sorry.
-You're not sorry.
-Oh, you know me too well.
-Now, listen.
You almost broke your neck.
I hate it when you guys
do that macho crap.
-That was not macho crap.
That was performance art.
JOHNNY: Yeah, it was the
living theater revisited.
-Did you bring my spatula?
-Yes, I did.
And the cheese grater
just like you asked.
-Good.
-Hi, honey.
-Oh my god, Samantha
in the kitchen.
Call the paramedics.
I'm about to have a stroke.
-I'm cooking corn.
-Quit picking on my wife.
I love you, sweetheart.
Hey, Hannah, come in here.
-What?
-Listen, I know you
guys said no presents.
But na, ah, ah, we
could not resist.
So because we love
you so much, happy
anniversary from Sam and I.
-What?
-What is it?
-Oh, Dory.
Dodger-Met tickets.
Oh, you guys, this is
going to be-- hey, kids.
Look what Uncle Dory brought?
-Now, see, I thought that
no gifts meant no gifts.
-Look what Uncle Dorian gave us.
Box seats to the
Dodger-Met game.
You can bring Janie, too.
-Cool.
-Wow.
Out of site.
-Thanks, Uncle Dorian.
-Thanks.
-Far out.
-Whoa, far out.
You're welcome.
Oh, far out.
Out of site?
They sound like little hippies.
-Yeah.
Well, they've been watching
"Mod Squad" reruns back to back.
-And speaking of mediocre
TV, look who's here.
-Oh my gosh.
-Oh, sire.
Your excellency.
Maurice, I'm honored.
I was sure I would
get a call saying
you were in Aspen
skiing with Tom Cruise.
-Honestly, I wouldn't
miss this for the world.
This is Catrice.
She's in my new pilot.
-Catrice.
-Hi.
-You wanted to meet
actors, they're all here.
Every gumba hit man,
Jew lawyer, Irish mug
you have ever seen on TV.
This is an elephant graveyard
of faces you cannot name.
-Wow, thanks for the
stereotyping, Maurice.
Glad you don't fit into
any pigeonhole yourself.
You still driving
a black Beamer?
-Touche, you son of a bitch.
-Oh, and speaking
of stereotypes,
you know Steve, and
Armand, and Dorian?
-Sure.
-Hey.
-Dorian.
I saw that bit you did
in the Pacino film.
-Oh, yeah?
-Saw the rough cut.
Very nice.
-Oh, thank you.
Oh, thank you.
Thanks very much.
-Oh, that was you ?
-Yeah, that was me.
CATRICE: You were excellent.
-Thank you.
I'm Dorian.
CATRICE: Dorian.
-Look.
Is that flirting?
-I've seen you somewhere
recently, haven't I?
-Theater?
-I mean, is he
flirting right now
or is he just being cordial?
-Yeah.
-I'd say he's just
sucking up to a producer
by any means necessary.
-You know, Sam, I really can't
tell because being married
to Steve has sandpapered
the flirt right out of me.
-So where's your father?
-Oh, yeah, my dad.
Oh, yeah.
Hey, Pop?
Pop, look who's here,
Maurice Melnick.
-Who?
-Maurice Melnick, the producer.
Remember, he used
you on his TV show?
You played the old
man on a stoop.
-Soup?
I didn't order any soup.
JOHNNY: Like you said,
he's one of a kind.
Help yourselves.
-Dorian.
Catrice.
-Did you hear that?
He saw me in a rough cut.
I got to call my agent.
-What are you talking about?
You had two lines in that movie.
-It was a pivotal scene.
The plot turned on it.
-Oh, the plotted turned
on, "I'm sorry Mr. Lee.
I can't give you
that information."
-How do you know that?
-I was up for the
same part, remember?
-Oh, that's right.
I forgot.
You would have been good.
-Look at him.
I've auditioned
for him five times.
Twice I had callbacks.
He looked at me like he
didn't even remember me.
-What's that?
What's that thing you're doing?
That's an Italian thing,
biting your knuckles.
Jews don't bite their knuckles.
Jews slap their foreheads.
-Well, thank you
for the tip, Dorian.
But I am allowed to
do Italian things, OK?
-I'm trying to help you.
-I'm married to an Italian.
-Hey, hey, at least
you read for him.
He looked at me
like I was a valet.
I'm surprised he didn't
throw me his keys.
-Oh, screw him.
Screw him.
Everything he touches
is schlock anyway.
-Yeah. we don't do schlock.
-That's right.
-Do you believe
that Maurice came?
This is incredible.
This means I got a real
shot at that Paramount part.
They still haven't
made a choice.
-John.
Johnny, take it easy.
You know he came for the food.
He's the cheapest guy in town.
-Yeah.
You know they say that he
stole an entire wheel of brie
from Spielberg's house?
-He's the one who
stole Spielberg's brie?
-Absolutely, it's him.
-Come on.
All I know, he's here
and I can't be bad.
We're talking about
a featured part
here with some real dimension.
-Really?
What is it this time?
Cab driver or plumber?
What, you going to stretch
and go for the hit man, huh?
-Come on, Armand.
I'm serious.
It's a lawyer.
All right, a corrupt lawyer.
But this character
has got some depth,
complexities, intelligence.
Oh, Armand.
Maybe this is my lucky day.
Oh, look who's here.
Theresa.
-Johnny.
Hello, my baby.
-Look at you, sweetheart.
Oh, the party's complete.
You look great.
It's like the old
days [inaudible].
-Hey, it's Theresa.
-Hey, Armand.
Your ex is here.
She came to LA for
the palimony suit.
-Hello.
JOHNNY: This is great,
Theresa shows up.
-You didn't even give me a call.
-No, I was going to.
I was going to, but I'm
just here for a couple days.
-You look great.
Hey, come on over.
I'll cook you a meal.
Some fettuccine alfredo?
-Oh, come on.
Don't tempt me.
-Oh, you can get away.
-Hey, Theresa.
-Hi.
-Give me my boyfriend back.
You had your chance with
him a long time ago.
-Yolanda, how have you been?
-I'm great.
-Hello.
-Oh my god.
-Hi, pal.
[interposing voices]
-Everybody.
[applause]
-I'm going to finally
have a real moment.
20 years of acting, I'm
going to have a real moment.
-Thank you, everybody.
Thank you very much.
We're just thrilled
you could be here
with us on this special day.
And remember, in
lieu of gifts, we're
asking you to make a donation
to the Los Ninos Mission.
-It wasn't my idea.
[laughter]
-As you know, they
do great work with
the disadvantaged children.
And, oh, I just want
to say, thank you.
We love you all.
-Aw.
[applause]
-What can I say?
I mean, if it weren't
for Hannah here,
I wouldn't be with great family
and friends giving away gifts
to strange children who will one
day grow up and try to rob me.
The truth is, I'm the
luckiest guy on Earth.
[applause]
-Well, I don't know why
political correctness
has crept into casting.
You can't even say like,
I want a fat guy anymore.
It's got to be like,
I want a large person.
Big human being.
You know, big, expansive.
But you just can't say, I need a
fat guy who's 6 foot 10, right?
-Oh, I hope we're
like Hannah and Johnny
on our 15th anniversary.
Don't you?
-Sure, babe.
-Make love to me tonight.
Will you, honey?
-What's the matter, baby.
You seem so sad.
-I'm not sad.
Just make love to me tonight.
Will you?
-This is what I'm talking about.
We have these opportunities.
Every once in a while,
you got to crack them.
Speak to him.
-I know.
I know.
I should be more assertive.
-And I said, no, no, no, no, no.
It's not the Woody Allen film.
So anyway, then he died.
-You should.
I talked to him when
he came in, so just go.
-I can't.
You go first.
-What?
What's the matter?
-Because I can't.
I feel bloated.
I ate chocolate.
-Honey, will you
listen to yourself?
Listen to us.
We're acting ridiculous.
Let's just go.
We're like normal people.
-Let me hold your arm.
-Can you tell my
shirt is ripped?
-No, just hold your arm down.
I'll hold it.
-Would you like a cup
of coffee, Maurice?
-Pretty please?
-You got it.
-This is like two coupling.
Let me-- let me just--
-We are a-- Maurice,
um-- really thought, um,
"Breakneck" was, uh,
just a terrific--
really terrific film.
-Thank you.
-Yeah, it was really terrific.
It was really terrific.
-Thank you very much.
STEVE: What is
with the whinnying?
CATRICE: Oh, gosh.
What, you want to
pack a bag and go?
-Hey.
What's in the bag?
-Oh, your wife said why
not take something home
when there's all this Parmesan.
-Sure.
Enjoy.
So, uh, I guess we'll
be in touch soon, huh?
I mean, there's been no
word on that Paramount part.
-Paramount part?
-Oh, come on.
You know, the lawyer
on your feature.
-I'm going to kill
that casting agent.
-What?
-Nobody called you?
-No.
-They were supposed to
call you a week ago.
We went another way.
-Oh, I didn't know.
-I feel like a complete putz.
-Ah, what's the difference, huh?
It's just another part.
Who cares?
Give me back my cheese
though, you prick?
-Oh, I'm so sorry.
-So who'd they go with?
-Oh, what difference
does it make?
Somebody else.
-I know.
I'm just curious.
Who?
-Rudy Ptak.
-Oh, Rudy?
Good.
Uh, he's good-- good actor.
-Think so?
-Good choice, yeah.
-Oh, good.
I'm glad to hear you say that.
-Yeah.
-Takes a load off my mind.
All right, see ya.
-See ya, Maurice.
[engine starting]
-Rudy Ptak?
Rudy Ptak.
We're the same guy.
He's me.
They're using me, except
I'm not getting paid.
How the hell could this
be happening, Hannah?
I was right in the
pocket with this role.
I had it.
-Honey, you're going
to have to calm down.
You'll make yourself sick.
-No.
No, I had this
feeling this time.
Like for once I was
going to slip through.
Do a character with some
layers, with something
more than a
fourth-grade education.
Instead, it's the same old shit.
Second chooch from the left.
-Now, come on.
Quit putting yourself down.
You are a success.
CATRICE: Oh, Christ.
Hannah, please.
-You work more than those guys.
-Not the glass is half full bit.
Not this time, please.
[sigh]
Who am I kidding?
The De Niros, the
Pacinos, the Hoffmans.
The [inaudible].
I'm just one of the ottomans
hanging on a branch.
[sigh]
Screw them.
I'm not going to
let them get to me.
I'm not.
You're my little angel.
[inaudible]
-What happened, Daddy?
You lose another part?
-No, no.
It's all right, honey.
Go back to sleep, OK?
Daddy loves you.
Oh, god.
I'm starved.
And that prick took our
Parmesan, too. $12 a pound.
-Well, I said he could take it.
-Why?
-Because it's not good for
you, but you can have some
of that soy cheese I
got at [inaudible].
-Soy cheese?
[phone ringing]
That's not cheese.
That's spackle.
You cover your walls with it.
-Hello?
Hi.
How's it going?
Uh, yeah.
Hang on.
Just a second.
Johnny?
-Oh, no.
-It's Theresa.
-Oh.
-I don't know.
Hey.
Hi, Theresa.
-Hi, Johnny.
Uh, party was great.
Thanks.
But listen.
There's something
I couldn't bring up
with all those
people in the room.
But first, you
gotta promise me--
and I mean, no bullshit, Johnny,
that you won't tell a soul.
This is the most hush-hush
thing I've ever worked on, OK?
My ass is on the line with this.
-Theresa, I can keep a secret.
What?
-Oh, yeah?
You're like a
one-man wire service.
You compete with
CNN for God's sake.
Now, promise me.
-Yeah.
All right.
What is it?
-Cross your heart
and hope to die.
-OK, cross my heart.
-And hope to die.
For God's sake, now what is it?
-Scorsese is doing "Capone."
He's in from New York.
He's seeing a few people.
It's all very QT.
And he asked me to help me out.
Now, he saw you on "NYPD Blue"
and he wants you to come in.
He liked you.
-He did?
THERESA (ON PHONE): Yeah.
He wants you to read.
-For what?
-For Capone, dummy.
They want an unknown.
De Niro can't do it
because he already
did Capone in "The
Untouchables."
It's wide open.
But look, don't
breathe a word, OK?
Or else every punk
actor in Hollywood
who thinks he's the next Pacino
or De Niro, which is most
of your friends, will be all
over us like flies on shit.
And Marty doesn't
want that, capisce?
And especially don't
tell Armand, OK?
Because the last thing in the
world I need is to offend him.
Now, listen.
If anyone asks
you who's casting,
say your agent got a
call from the producer.
-Yeah, OK.
Theresa, I don't want to say.
-Well, get prepared.
Now, they're going to call you
into Warner Brothers on Friday,
and they're going to give
you something to read then.
-OK.
OK.
I got to ask you, is
Rudy Ptak up for it?
THERESA (ON PHONE): Rudy Ptak
is on a series until April.
Listen, Johnny, I
want you to work.
I want you to go
deep, all right?
-OK.
THERESA (ON PHONE): OK?
None of that TV gumba schtick.
I mean, this is-- this
is Scorsese, all right?
Scorsese.
OK?
I mean, go-- go, go
against your bigness.
OK?
I know you can do it.
I saw you in "American Buffalo."
I know you've got the range.
I mean, you worked with
Stella for god sake.
OK?
So don't embarrass
me, all right?
JOHNNY (ON PHONE): All right.
Of course not.
No.
No, no, I won't let you down.
I'll go deep, deep.
-All right, go deep.
Go deep, John.
Deep is the word.
Deep.
JOHNNY (ON PHONE): You
don't know how deep.
-All right, Johnny.
All right.
Please.
Now, work, work, work.
-Thanks, Theresa.
-[sigh].
-Hey, what's up?
Johnny?
Honey, what's wrong?
-Oh.
Oh.
-Honey, what is it?
What's wrong?
Is it your heart?
Just try to relax.
Can you breathe?
Just try to-- take-- what?
Should I call 911?
What?
Are you all right?
Please, just-- just
try to take a breath.
Honey, what?
What is it?
Tell me by a hand signal.
What?
-Thank you.
Thank you.
You bring me luck.
Thank you!
Thank you, Universe!
-[gasp].
-Oh, god.
Oh, god.
Honey.
Are you all right?
-Oh.
-What was it?
Was it the "Grapes of
Wrath" dream again?
-Yes.
-Oh, no.
On the truck?
-Maurice was there.
He was chasing everybody.
He was going to
foreclose on the farm.
I just-- I still
couldn't talk to him.
-Oh, god.
Oh, honey.
Honey.
It's going to be all right.
Come on.
-Oh, honey, I--
-Come on.
It's going to be OK.
It's OK.
It's over.
It's all right.
Ow.
My hair.
-I'm sorry.
-It's all right.
It's OK.
It's going to be all right.
Yeah, it's all right.
JOHNNY: Friday.
I got to have this thing
prepared by Friday.
-Oh, honey, you
have enough time.
JOHNNY: Yeah.
I have enough time if
I'm doing "Baywatch."
But for Scorsese?
-OK.
Come on, girls.
Let's go.
-Come on.
And Theresa said go deep.
She made a point of it, go deep.
Did she mean that
I have no depth,
or did she mean find the
depth of the character?
-Honey, what are
you talking about?
You'll be fine, just treat
it like any other audition.
-Come on, mom.
This could put Dad on the map.
He'll finally stopped
being pigeonholed
as a small-time hit
man or slob cab driver.
-Thank you.
Nice thing to say to
your dad, Gabriella.
-What?
It's not the way I feel.
It's just the way
this business works.
Right, Dad?
-Right.
Right.
Let's go.
Come on.
Listen.
While we're at it, not a word
of any of this to your friends.
They'll tell their fathers.
And before you
know it, there will
be a damn stampede
for this part.
All right?
-Don't worry, Dad.
I never talk business
with my friends.
-Sounds like Pacino
in "The Godfather."
All right.
GIRL: Hi, Janey.
JANEY: Hi.
-Hey.
-Bye, Mom.
Bye, Dad.
-Great party, you guys.
I'm hungover and suicidal,
but I really had a good time.
-And they say she
can't do comedy.
-I love you, Johnny.
OK.
Does everyone have their lunch?
Their homework?
Their virtual reality pets?
-All right.
-Let's go.
-Bye Janey.
You know something?
Gabriella's right.
This is not like
any other audition.
I got to hit this one
out of the park, hun.
-OK.
So instead of going to
the track with Dorian
or the golf course
with Steve, why
don't you really
prepare on this one?
Hm?
-This is the LA library?
I feel like I'm in Vegas.
I'd like a room adjoining
the casino, please.
-Mm.
-Johnny.
-Dorian?
-Hey.
Johnny boy.
How are you?
What the hell are you
doing in the library?
-What are you
doing in a library?
-Babette, I'd like you
meet a dear friend of mine.
This is, uh, Johnny
DiMartino, a wonderful actor.
-Babette.
-Babette's one of my students.
I'm introducing her
to Stanislavski.
-Terrific guy.
-Johnny studied
with Stella, too.
-Really?
Wow.
Oh, that must have
been incredible.
-Oh, yeah.
The quest to unravel
the mystery of subtext
has become the metaphysical--
-Johnny's a riot, isn't he?
Do you want to hang on a second?
I'm just going to
walk Babette out.
It's all right, honey.
I got to talk to this guy.
-So, uh, you'll call me?
-Yeah.
Yeah.
No, I'll call you.
I'll stop by the restaurant.
All right?
I will.
I promise.
I said I promise.
I'll see you.
-Bye.
Johnny.
-Jesus, Dorian.
You're unbelievable.
-Can you not say
anything, please?
Especially not to Hannah.
You know how women are.
They tell each other everything.
-Oh, come on.
What do you take me for?
It's not my business.
-Johnny, I can't help myself.
She saw me in "The Crime Story."
She starts asking
me about acting.
She's all over me.
She wants to get together.
That's why I came here.
I didn't think I'd run
into anybody at a library.
What the hell are you
doing here anyway?
-An errand for Hannah.
She needs them for a class.
-Johnny, I'm cursed.
Women love me.
-My heart's breaking for you.
-No, it's the truth.
And the worst part of it
is I love them right back.
Did you look at her?
-Yeah, young enough
to be your daughter.
-Exactly.
Is that a curse or not?
This is what wrecked
my first marriage.
Johnny, I thought
it was Samantha.
I thought, all right,
I'm going to settle down.
But I swear to god, on our
wedding-- Johnny, I swear.
This babe was with my
cousin from Buffalo.
She came onto me.
I could have got laid
at my own wedding.
Johnny, I can't change.
And now my marriage
is coming apart.
Samantha, I love her.
I don't want to hurt her.
-Jesus, Dorian.
I had no idea things
were this bad.
You're really out
of control here.
You better go see a
shrink or something.
-I did.
I did.
I saw a shrink six months ago.
A woman.
-Yeah?
-She starts asking
me all about myself.
One thing led to another.
-No?
-No, no, no.
We just went-- we just
went out to dinner.
She took me to a
nice place, too.
Johnny, I'm freaking miserable.
-But where do you get
the energy for all this?
-I don't know.
I'm an actor.
I got a lot of down time.
I go to the gym.
Of course, I meet
women there, too.
-Oh, Christ.
You're insatiable.
What gym is this?
-Oh, god.
You know, it's funny.
I'm glad I ran into you.
I've been wanting to get this
off my chest for so long.
It makes me see, you
know, I got to stop this.
Oh my god, what a day.
You being here, too.
That is weird, huh?
Oh.
What's Hannah got you
bringing in to class?
-No, no, no.
-Come on.
"Capone?"
What's-- "Mr. Capone."
What's Hannah doing with that?
She teaches 19th Century poetry.
-Beats the hell out of me.
-You son of a bitch.
-What?
-That stuff's for you, isn't it?
-Sort of.
-So?
So, why the big subterfuge?
Come on, Johnny.
I just got through spilling
my guts out to you.
Talk to me.
We'll share secrets.
-OK.
OK.
But you got to promise not
to breathe a word of this
to anyone.
Not a soul.
-My lips are sealed.
-Cross your heart
and hope to die.
-Jesus.
-Say it.
-Scorsese!
Jesus.
He's going to add a whole
new dimension to Capone.
Physically, you're
perfect for it.
-Why do you say that?
You don't think I'm
emotionally right for it?
-No.
You're going to be great.
I'm saying, Theresa was
right to bring you in.
Let me tell you something, this
is a feather in her cap, too.
-Yeah.
But you can't mention
anything about her involvement
with this.
Especially to Armand.
You know, the two of
them were together once.
-Don't even sweat it.
It does not go beyond us.
-Oh.
-Hi, honey.
What happened?
Your audition was canceled.
I didn't know
where to reach you.
-I know.
I found out, uh,
when I got there.
Have you seen the, uh--
-So where have you been?
-I was at the--
I was at the gym.
Hey.
-Well, I called Jenny
and Steve and they
didn't know where
you were, so I was--
-I'm sorry, honey.
I know.
-All right.
-I know.
I'm sorry.
Hey, Barbara, it's Dorian.
Can you-- Dorian.
Get me Harry.
Well, just cut into
his bullshit meeting.
This is an emergency.
Honey, could-- the-- the,
uh, sound is-- Harry, listen.
I want you to call Theresa
Reynolds at the Argyle.
She's doing a special casting
session with Scorsese.
He' is doing Al
Capone and he wants
an unknown to play Capone.
No, I am telling you
it's happening, Harry.
I got it from Johnny DiMartino.
But it's all very hush-hush.
You cannot tell anybody
how you heard about this.
You can't.
Now, Harry.
I-- I am not street enough?
Street my ass.
I'm an actor and
I'm Italian, too.
What?
So what if my family
came from Florence?
They had murderers in
Florence, too, Harry.
Listen.
I am right for this part.
I am calling in the
chips on this one.
Now, you call that
bulimic bitch, Theresa.
See if you can't get her
head out of the toilet
long enough for her to
schedule me an appointment.
Thank you.
-Are you still there, Harry?
Yes.
No.
That's my, uh-- it's
not water running.
I'm-- I'm in my car.
I'm moving through
Laurel Canyon.
Dammit.
How did you hear about this?
Your daughter's dating a
guy in the mail room at CAA?
The place to meet future moguls?
Great.
You haven't told
anyone, have you?
Uh-huh.
Yeah.
Hey.
I know you helped me
out with the "Barney
the Dinosaur Special," Harry.
I haven't forgotten.
Now, what do you want?
Dorian.
I know he's a lovely
actor, but I mean-- no, I
didn't know his
father was Sicilian.
-Harry, you are beautiful.
You are beautiful.
Thank you.
Hey, you didn't tell anybody
how you heard about this, right?
Great.
3:30 on Friday.
Harry, I love you.
I love you.
You are the greatest.
Yes.
I'm in.
-Well, that's just great.
And what are you going to
tell Johnny if he finds out?
-He's not going to find out.
We're going in at
different times.
-And what if you get the part?
-Well, then I'll tell
him my agent got me up
for it, which is
the truth almost.
-You know what?
I think it stinks.
-What?
-Johnny and Hannah
are like family.
She's one of my closest friends.
-Honey, Johnny is
like a brother to me.
But this part doesn't
have his name on it.
And this is a chance
to meet Scorsese.
Scorsese.
-(MOCKINGLY) Scorsese.
-Hey, honey.
-Hey.
Hi.
-Honey, would you give
me that Phillips head?
The pointy yellow one.
-Oh.
-How was the library?
-OK, I guess.
I got books.
-Good.
What'd you have for lunch?
-I didn't eat.
I wasn't hungry.
What?
Come on, what?
-You got to promise
not to tell, Hannah.
You got to cross your
heart and hope to die.
-Please, what is it?
-I ran into Dorian
at the library.
-Yeah?
-He was with some
gorgeous young bimbo.
And believe me, they
weren't there to read.
-Oh, no.
-And that's not all.
He's been doing
this kind of thing
ever since they were married.
He sounded like a one-man
deflowering expedition.
-Oh my god.
Poor Samantha.
-I know.
I know.
It's a mess, but
you can't tell her.
It's their marriage,
for them to work out.
-I feel terrible.
What am I supposed to
say when I see them?
-Nothing.
We care about both
of them, right?
We stay out of it.
Even those he's being
a major asshole.
-I just don't believe it.
-I know.
I know.
It's amazing.
On the one day in
maybe a decade that I
decide to go into a library.
Then I started
thinking, maybe he's
been put there for
my work on Capone.
You know, get into his evil
soul, the lies, the betrayal.
You know, maybe it's an omen.
You know, work him a little.
-Wait-- wait a minute.
You're going to substitute
Dorian for Capone?
I mean, he's from Connecticut.
His dad's an orthodontist.
-I know.
I know.
That's my point.
I'm trying to find
Capone and I could
end up doing an
Italian Seinfeld.
I'm losing my mind on this.
And who the hell has
got time to read?
No, no, no.
For this, I need a
jolt int he guts.
A direct connection
to my Sicilian roots.
Please, Hannah.
I need a guy who kills,
not a guy who naps.
No, No.
For this, I need to
talk to a real mob guy.
-Honey, you don't know
any real mob guys.
-I know.
All these years playing hit men
and I've been phoning it in.
But you know, then it struck me.
Maybe I do know somebody and
he's right under my nose.
-Who?
-Armand, that's who.
-Ha.
Armand?
-Of course.
Come on, all that money.
His mysterious family back
East no one's ever seen.
Plus, what's he known for?
-I don't know, his
salad dressing?
-No.
No, Scott Goldstein.
His agent, remember?
Scott never set him up for that
terrorist role in "Die Hard 2."
Armand flipped, punched
him out, broke his jaw.
-So?
-So he did the one thing
every actor's dreamed of doing
but never had the balls to do.
It was legendary.
It was the only time Armand
ever got mentioned in "Variety."
On top of that, he's brilliant.
-Theresa specifically said do
not mention this to Armand.
-No, no.
She doesn't want him to
know that she's involved,
that's all.
I'll tell him the producer
has called me in directly.
I have to talk to Armand.
I have to.
-Well, no.
You got to go easy
on those capers
because you don't
want them to overwhelm
the taste of the salmon.
Yeah.
You got to go easy
on the cream, too.
[dog barking]
-Hey, Java.
Take it easy.
It's all right, boy.
It's Uncle Johnny.
That a boy.
You little Nazi prick.
-What?
It's not boned?
You got to bone it.
You don't want bones
in the cream sauce.
Hey, John.
Johnny's here.
All right, Steve.
-Hey, I heard you.
Two grown men sharing recipes.
You banging him, too?
Personally, he's not my type.
I prefer guys with talent.
-Capone?
Incredible.
And Scorsese?
Wow.
That's a tremendous opportunity.
Jeez, so, uh, what's
the problem, huh?
-Well, you know,
I'm pretty sure I
got the big vicious thing down.
You know, the cocky asshole.
The flashy,
over-the-top dresser.
The ladies' man.
-Oh, really?
I think ladies' man would
stump you completely.
-Come on, Armand.
Please.
Come on.
It's the other stuff.
The deep, quiet thing.
Those swirling
Sicilian currents.
That's what I need.
-Swirling Sicilian currents?
-Yeah.
You know, like Pacino
had in "The Godfather."
Like Marlon has.
You have it, too, Armand.
-I do?
-Oh, yeah.
Something you carry with you.
It's an intangible.
-Well, thanks, Johnny.
But you got it, too.
Anybody has.
-Nah.
I went to Catholic school.
I was an altar boy.
I never looked
death in the face.
-What makes you think I did?
-I don't know, a feeling.
Armand, I-- I need
something real.
I need something as
ancient and as Italian
as-- as this clove
of garlic here.
-All right.
All right.
Hey.
Hey, we'll start right there.
-What?
-You slice the garlic, you
help me make a sauce, huh?
What could be deeper than that?
Here.
-You serious?
-Yeah.
Come on, smell this.
That's the power of
your tradition, right?
Come on, slice it up.
Got to connect with
the swirls, right?
Connect with these swirls.
-Ah.
Ooh, I cut myself.
-Hey, well, there you go.
Hey, real blood, huh?
Now we're talking.
-Oh.
What the hell?
Am I out of my mind?
I'm talking to a demented
Wolfgang Puck here.
-Hey, Johnny.
Can you get me in to read?
-What?
-Well, you say I
got Sicilian swirls.
There's got to be
other parts, right?
Other Sicilian swirlers, right?
-Ah, what a business.
All right, Armand.
I mean, if I get in the
door, I'll see what I can do.
Now, come on, Armand.
I need your help.
-All right, I'll tell
you what I think.
The guys with real balls,
they never show it.
The scariest guy I ever met,
he looked like the grocer
down the street.
He blended in like
your average Joe.
But if you ever looked into
his eyes, he didn't blink.
It was like looking in
to the eyes of a shark.
They-- they were dead eyes.
-Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's good.
-Quiet and calm, dead eyes.
-Right.
Right.
Dead eyes.
-Right.
All right, let's give it a shot.
That's it.
Feel it.
Good.
Yeah.
You know, your hair is
perfect for this, Johnny.
You're going to have to lose
about 50 pounds, though.
So is Rudy Ptak up for the role?
-You had to mention
his friggin name?
-Hey, come on.
Use your anger.
That's it.
You're doing it.
[dog barking]
[dog crying]
-My life is like some weird
cosmic test, you know?
I haven't worked in
a year and a half.
You know, if God has
given me all this talent,
why doesn't he give
me a way to use it?
It's a curse.
It's a punishment.
-A punishment?
For what?
-I don't want to do this, OK?
-No, look.
I think-- why don't you try to
go up for this Capone thing?
-Because it's a
secret thing, OK?
And I-- I wouldn't cross Johnny.
-You're an actor just
like everyone else.
Why shouldn't you go up for it?
-Because I wouldn't do
a thing like that, OK?
End of story.
[car honking]
-Jo.
You forget I needed the car?
That audition's in 20 minutes.
-No.
I didn't forget.
-You didn't?
So what-- what happened?
-Nothing.
I'm sorry.
-Jo?
-Good luck.
-Jo, don't do this to me, OK?
What's happening?
Will you tell me what's
going on, please?
-OK.
I had to go to the bank.
We bounced another check.
-Oh, no.
Who was it this time?
We bounced a check on my mother?
-Johnny DiMartino
for the Casper's
famous low-fat hot dog spot.
This is my father.
He comes with me.
-Oh, right.
You're on the list.
-Hey, you're late.
What the hell happened?
-We got hung up.
-OK.
I'm going to need you
right here, right in tight.
And when I say
action, then you go.
I love the sweatshirt.
It's a nice touch.
-Thank you.
-OK.
And action.
-Why are you breathing so hard?
What's the matter with you?
I just dropped two-thirds of
my fat and half my calories.
-Two-thirds of your fat
and half your calories?
That's wonderful, sir.
-Um, Tony, right?
JOHNNY: Johnny.
-OK.
The idea of doing
it like Scarface
is interesting, sort of.
But this is an
upstairs/downstairs thing.
The bun is the
schlepper who's been
carrying the hot
dog like forever.
-Aha.
-So you're-- yeah.
So you're more of a
swelled head poshon, dig?
Think John Goodman in pink
tights, but not too shitcky.
We want a little Larry Sanders
reality thing to it, too.
You dig?
-Not too shitcky.
STEVE: What are you doing?
-Hm?
-What are you doing?
-What?
-That thing with your eyes.
What are you doing?
Stop it, Johnny.
You're blowing this job for me.
I need it.
Snap out of it.
-Oh, uh, sorry.
Stevie.
Hey, Trent.
Trent, look.
I'm sorry.
I was trying something.
It didn't work.
Uh, Larry Sanders
via the Flintstones
but not too shticky.
It's a beautiful concept, Trent.
-Let's do it.
-Very Spielbergian.
-Thanks.
Uh, Johnny, listen.
Uh, the original
idea was to go with
an emaciated anorexic pickle.
You know, Kate Moss and
vinegar kind of thing.
But pickles also come
aged and wrinkled.
And some of the clients have
worked with your father before
and thought that he might
be right for the spot.
-[snoring].
-Oh, god.
-My father's a garbage man
in New York for 40 years.
He comes out to Hollywood.
He's got a bigger
career than me.
-Yeah.
Well, at least one of us
is getting a damn callback.
I hate your guts, Nino.
-What?
No.
I had a salami sandwich before.
-Salami?
-Star material, no?
-Yeah.
Well, the fruit doesn't
fall far from the tree.
-All right.
All right, pops.
Sit down.
Come on, let's go.
I got to get to practice.
I got a lot of
things to do today.
-So what was that thing that,
uh, you were doing before?
-What thing?
-That-- that weird
thing with your eyes.
-Oh, why?
You like it?
-I like it?
Do I like it for what?
-Hey, kids.
We're here.
Hi.
-Hi, Daddy.
Hi, Daddy.
-Daddy.
-Hi, there.
Hey, sweetie.
-Can I be up first?
-Yeah.
Yeah.
Go-- uh, give me a second.
-OK.
-Hey, Anthony.
Twice around the bases
on the double, all right?
-You know, I spoke
with Dorian earlier.
And, uh, he asked me
if I had talked to you.
And I told him I hadn't.
And he dropped it, like
it wasn't important.
Which made me think right
away something was up.
-Really?
-Yeah, really.
And now you start in with
this weird eye thing.
You want to tell me what
the hell's going on or not?
-Nothing.
Nothing's going on.
-15 years of acting
class, you're
still the worst
liar on the planet.
I'm hurt, man.
Really.
I am really hurt.
And after you nearly blew
that audition for me, too.
-Hey.
All right.
Hold it.
Jesus.
You're like Carl Sagan
looking for a speck of dust
in another solar system.
All right, look.
Look.
If I tell you,
you got to promise
not to say a single
word of this to anyone.
Not--
-Hey.
Hey.
Who you talking to?
It's me.
It's Steve.
-You got to promise not to
get into the actor envy thing.
Not on this one, please?
-Oh, god.
This one's really going
to kill me, isn't it?
Unbelievable.
And Capone has never
been done right.
Never.
Well, sure.
Sure.
Leave it-- leave it to Scorsese.
I mean, look what
he did with LaMotta.
-Exactly.
-Oh, man.
I-- I am stoked.
I'm inspired.
You know why?
-Why?
-Because if this can happen for
you, then anything is possible.
Peaks and valleys.
Life is peaks and valleys.
That's what my
shrink always said.
And he was right.
I-- I just happened to have
been in a valley for a while.
That's all.
-More like the Great
Canyon I'd say.
-Yeah.
Well, tell me about it.
Anyway, the universe
is smiling on you.
It's time for gratitude.
-You're right.
You're right.
-Now, look.
If there's anything I can do,
you need any kind of help,
you call me.
I'm there for you.
You're going to have
to fight your tendency
to go over the top.
-Over the top?
I don't have a tendency
to go over the top.
-No.
I just-- I mean, your bigness.
-Oh.
Oh.
-You know, your
larger-than-life persona.
-Oh, yeah.
But that works
for the character.
I just have to
keep it reined in?
-Yes.
Exactly.
Rein it in.
Let it simmer.
You let it percolate.
And then, boom.
You let it explode.
-Exactly.
Blow the fuckers right
out of the water.
-That's right.
Hold on a second.
Is Ptak up for it?
-No.
No, no.
The door's wide open.
I just have to walk right in.
All right.
Come on.
All right, sweetheart.
You remember.
Watch the bat.
Hit the ball.
-I don't know.
I just, um-- I just had
to stop by, you see?
And, uh, it's just you-- you
know, you're like family.
I mean, my real family.
And, um--
-Hey, it's OK.
-It's just--
-You can tell me.
What is it?
-It's just-- oh, Hannah.
Dorian is going after
that Capone part,
after he promised Johnny
he wouldn't do anything.
-Oh, no.
-Please don't tell Johnny.
Please.
Because if you do, it
will end their friendship.
Our friendship.
But I want you to
know I was against it.
Oh, I'm so confused.
I swear I feel more loyalty
to you than I do to him.
I'm all alone in
this marriage, Han.
I asked him if he was having an
affair straight out like that
and he said, no.
You know, it's just
all the career stress.
All the craziness.
-Yeah.
-Oh, god.
And I took my diaphragm
out last month.
-What?
What?
You--
-I threw it away.
-You threw away your diaphragm?
-I want to have a family, Han.
Acting isn't my calling.
I just get cast
as bimbos, anyway.
-I know that.
But listen to me,
having a baby is
not going to solve
your problems.
-I know.
But-- you know, we only made
love eight times last month.
We're married three years.
Don't you think it's
a little soon to be
making love only
eight times a month?
-I should be so lucky.
-Oh, I'm serious, Han.
-Wait a minute.
Does Dorian know that you
threw out your diaphragm?
-No.
-No?
I want to be a mom, Han.
-I know.
-I want a baby.
It's the only thing I
feel really sure about.
Everything else is so mixed up.
-But Steve, you're Jewish.
-Yeah.
And the pope is Catholic.
-You don't expect him to
be bar mitvahed do you?
-Look, Jo.
All I know is that they
are looking for an unknown.
An unknown.
Who in this town is
more unknown than me?
-No one.
-Oh, ha, ha, ha.
Look, this is Scorsese, OK?
It's not some schlepper.
He needs me.
We are cut from the same stuff.
-There's just one
problem, Steve.
You're not Italian.
So what does that have
to do with anything?
What are you, a bigot?
JOANNE: [gasp].
-Besides, you're Italian.
Don't I get carry-over credit?
I could do this part, Jo.
Look at me.
I'm perfect.
I am perfect.
Besides, I'll tell
you something else.
I am tougher than Johnny and all
those other guys put together.
You know, they're just getting
by with their phony street
bullshit, strutting around
here like middle-aged Fonzies.
These guys have
made careers feeding
stereotypes to idiot producers.
But meanwhile, I
am the real thing.
A street guy who clawed
his way up from nothing.
I know what it's like to have
somebody beat the crap out
of me and look me right in the
face and say, hey, Jew boy.
Hey, Jew boy.
-I'm sorry, but I'm not
making the connection!
-The connection is the rage.
The bottomless, unending fury.
That is who Capone is.
That's who I am.
I feel this part, Jo.
It's my time.
-And what about Johnny?
He's your best friend.
Hannah is my best friend.
They're godparents
to our daughter.
-They don't have
to know anything.
-And what if Jupiter
collides with Mars
and you actually get this part?
-Then I say mavel
tov, bravo, and let
the chips fall where they may.
-It's a deal with the devil.
-Well, sometimes when
opportunity knocks,
you got to grab it, baby.
Maybe it's fate.
I mean, look at Brando.
You know, if he didn't
have that trick knee,
he would have ended
up in World War II.
We never would
have heard of him.
That one little quirk,
that one little deformity
that made all the difference.
-Wait.
Am I hearing you correctly?
Are you now comparing
yourself to Brando?
-Yes.
Yes, I am, dammit.
I don't care.
-Oh my--
-Jo, look.
Listen to me.
I am desperate.
OK?
I have to make something happen.
It's either that or
we go back to Newark
and work in my uncle's
carpet-cleaning business.
-Newark?
-Yes, Newark, Jo.
Carpet cleaning in Newark, Jo.
Newark.
-OK, we deal with the devil.
But how are you going
to get in there?
-Maybe it's finally time
to call my cousin Max.
-The proctologist?
-No, Jo.
The proctologist to the stars.
He knows every asshole in town.
MAX: So I take it you
were pleased with the film
even though the
reviews were scathing?
-Yeah.
-Frankly, I thought you had
a few second act problems.
But hey, we can't be nominated
for Academy Award every year,
can we?
No.
Right.
All right.
Todd, hang on.
You might feel a
little discomfort here.
-Whoa.
Woo.
-Yeah.
Aren't you glad I didn't say
it was going to hurt, huh?
All right, we're
almost done here.
I promise.
Oh, uh, Todd, you're tight with
Marty Scorsese, aren't you?
TODD: [grunting].
-Was that a yes or a no?
Sorry.
-Han.
What are you doing here?
-Pour me a scotch, will you?
-A scotch?
-Mm-hmm.
-Han, what's up?
-You're not going
to believe this.
But look, it's just got
to stay between us, OK?
JOANNE: Well, sure.
-I found out that Dorian
has been screwing around
on Samantha throughout
the entire marriage.
-No.
-Yes.
Johnny caught him red-handed
with a beautiful young actress.
And Dorian begs him not to say
anything to me because he's
afraid I'm going to say
something to Samantha, right?
Then, Samantha comes over
to the house all upset
because she's afraid
Dorian is having an affair.
And I don't say anything.
-Jesus.
-Then, she tells me that Dorian
is going up for this Al Capone
part that Johnny
is being brought
in on by Martin Scorsese.
I mean, Dorian is going
in behind Johnny's back.
Can you believe it?
And please, don't
say anything to Steve
because it will just
complicate things more, OK?
Is this nuts or what?
And Johnny, well, he
won't stop eating.
He had another shortness of
breath episode the other night.
I thought he was
having a heart attack.
I mean, I had to
practically twist his arm
to get him to agree
to have a checkup.
He's making me crazy.
JOHNNY: What is this place?
They have real doctors here?
HANNAH: Yes, they do.
-What are we doing?
A field trip to the
Cloisters over here, or what?
I feel like a day player
in Ghandi over here.
I'm waiting for Ben
Kingsley to show up.
Come one.
What are you serious
or what over here?
Look at this.
We got Elsa, the she-wolf of
the SS leading us through.
-Johnny.
-I don't know
whether to genuflect
or take a urine analysis.
-Let's go.
-All right.
-Sorry.
-Where's the holy water fount?
-It was my pleasure, Johnny.
You certainly are a big spirit.
-Yeah. before you're
through with me,
I'm going to be a
much smaller one, huh?
-Yeah, but in weight only.
-Come on, doc.
You're an Italian.
How do you resist
the Parmesan cheese?
-Moderation is the key, Johnny.
Moderation.
-Will moderation get
me to look like you?
-No.
You know, I realize
who you remind me of.
One of my patients.
A wonderful actor.
I saw him a couple of days ago.
Rudy Ptak.
Do you know him?
-Rudy Ptak is in LA?
[phone ringing]
-Hello?
-Hi, Theresa.
It's Johnny.
-Oh, hi, Johnny.
-Look, I got to ask you, is
Rudy Ptak up for this part?
-What, Ptak?
No.
I already told you, he's booked.
-But he's here in LA and
his show shoots in New York.
-So, maybe he came to
LA to pick up his mail?
Johnny, you're obsessing.
Stop.
-I'm sorry, Theresa.
I'm going a little nuts here.
I won't let you down.
I'll go deep.
-OK?
-Armand's on two.
-[sigh].
Listen, honey.
I'm sorry I can't make it.
In fact, I'm booked on a flight
to go back to New York today.
-That's too bad.
You know, you ought to give me
a warning next time you come in.
I really wanted to see you.
Yolanda, too.
-All right, I promise.
-All right.
Give your son my love, OK?
-OK, sweetie.
Bye.
[sigh]
Actors.
-I just need to get
street a little.
Rough up, you know?
-What's the part?
-Just a mob guy, you know?
But I want to give it
some bite, you know?
-It's Capone, isn't it?
Johnny told me
about it yesterday.
-Oh, shit.
Armand, please, you cannot say
anything to him, all right?
He'll kind of go crazy.
What-- what am I supposed to do?
My agent called me.
Am I supposed to say no?
-What is it about me everybody
tells me their secrets?
-Because you can keep a secret.
Look, Armand.
Since we're being completely
honest, the reason I came here
was because I thought you might
have an inside track on this.
-What the hell
you talking about?
-Well, you never talk
about your past, you know?
And so I started thinking
that maybe your family was--
-What about my family?
-Well, the-- they
were, you know?
-What?
-Connected.
-Connected?
Where do you get this from?
-Why-- I don't know.
I just assumed.
I mean, nobody's ever met them.
-My family owns two
car dealerships,
which are totally legit.
-I'm sorry, Armand.
It's just that you don't
work much and-- I mean,
you don't have a job job.
And you just-- you
have a lot of money.
-Dorian, I made a
few good investments.
Is there a law against that?
-No, no.
Absolutely not.
No.
I apologize.
I'm out of line.
Look, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
-This is unbelievable.
I punch out my agent.
You think I'd murdered somebody.
If I'd actually
murdered him, I'd
probably have my own
talk show by now.
Or at least a movie of the week.
Oh, god.
It's unbelievable.
And they call you some
cushy middle-class poofta
whose mother squeezed him
orange juice every morning.
-Exactly.
See, you know.
Armand, please.
You got to help me.
I would be indebted to you.
-All right.
Jeez.
What are you going to do?
So what do you want from me?
-Anything.
If you were directing me,
what-- what would you tell me?
ARMAND: Dorian, you
got to understand.
In Capone's world,
it wasn't enough just
to be brutally tough.
You had to promote
the idea, too.
Capone was a strutter.
He was a mug.
I mean this wasn't
because he was stupid.
It's because he knew
how to hold the power.
They didn't have elections,
so everybody he met
was a potential threat.
The strut and the mug let
them know who was boss.
-Oh, this is good.
This is good.
Do you mind if I
just-- it helps me.
No, this good.
No, but I understand what
you're talking about.
It was a PR thing.
A hype.
ARMAND: No, it was not a hype.
-No, no hype.
Definitely not.
No.
-I mean, he-- you know,
he could back it up.
Remember, he was the general.
-Right.
Right.
Like a loose cannon
Patton or a Napoleon.
This guy was Shakespearean.
He was Dostoevsky.
-Take it easy.
What are you going to tell me,
he was a great humanitarian?
Remember, he was one level
above-- above a reptile.
Don't forget that.
-Right.
Right.
That's even better.
A strutting reptile.
Oh, what an image.
ARMAND: Yeah, go with that.
Come on.
Take it-- take it
back a little bit.
You know, in general.
Put the arms to the side.
Think it first.
It's an attitude.
It's an attitude first, and
then it's something physical.
Reptile.
Cold-blooded.
-Right.
ARMAND: You're in control.
Reptile.
Dangerous.
Everybody knows he's boss.
He doesn't have to prove it.
-Yeah.
-All right, Dorian.
That's good.
All you got to do is sell that.
-All right.
[dog barking]
[dog crying]
-Yeah.
-Honey?
Maybe you should call Theresa.
She's friends with Scorsese.
Maybe she can help you
with this audition.
-She's on a plane
back to New York.
-Well, the plane's going
to land eventually.
-[sigh].
Why you getting on me?
Why you pushing this?
-Because you're sitting in the
dark in the middle of the day,
Armand.
You're such a wonderful man.
You're good at so
many different things.
You paint.
You draw.
You build things, you know?
Maybe it's time
for you to start--
-I'm an actor.
That is my work.
-Fine.
-Oh, Yolanda.
I'm sorry.
Please, wait.
Please.
It's just that-- I--
I'm bugged by this.
-I know what you're
bugged by, believe me.
Now, let me ask you this.
Has it ever occurred to
you once that maybe you
have some
responsibility in this?
Maybe you are just not
willing to do what it takes.
You're incredible.
Would it kill you to
schmooze once in a while?
Use a contact.
For god sakes, you already
slept with Theresa.
Shouldn't that
count for something?
-Come on.
-Oh, great.
I'm getting laughs now.
Maybe I should be an actor.
We can both sit in the dark.
Would you like that?
You know, maybe we can
do a sitcom together--
"Dim Sum Meets the Ravioli."
Tune in next week,
see what happen.
-Yolanda, please.
BABETTE (ON PHONE): Hello?
-Hey.
Babette, baby.
How are you?
You free?
BABETTE (ON PHONE):
Yeah, but I'm a mess.
-Well, I don't
care what you look
like, I'm coming right over.
BABETTE (ON PHONE):
Oh, all right, baby.
-OK.
BABETTE (ON PHONE): Bye.
JOHNNY (ON PHONE): Hi,
it's Johnny and Hannah's.
You know what to do.
[beep]
-Hey, Johnny.
It's me.
Listen, I got a
last-minute looping
session doing that
Pacino picture.
I don't even think
I can make it today.
I feel terrible.
I'll call you later.
-How come they have no OTV.
In Los Angeles?
A city like this needs OTV.
-Pop, will you stop it?
I'm trying to work here.
-You're working too much.
Let it be fresh.
-Let it be fresh?
You're turning
into Lee Strasberg
right before my eyes here.
Dorian.
-You talking to me?
Me?
I'm the only one here.
[car honking]
Son of a bitch.
She is so damn devious.
-You, too, with this?
You know, I am insulted.
I am offended.
Not to mention shocked.
-Armand, I feel
like an asshole, OK?
I had no idea that
Johnny was over here.
And Dorian!
That snake.
That two-timing son
of a-- oh my god.
What am I saying?
-Steve.
Steve.
Why are you doing this?
Aren't you godfather
to Johnny's kids,
or he's godfather to yours?
-Both.
-Well?
-I, I had to do it.
I had to.
I'm dying here, man.
I'm dying.
-Tell me about it.
I haven't worked since
the Bicentennial.
-Yeah, but you've got
someone to fall back on.
-There you go again.
A guy has a little bit of
money and right away you
think he's got it from
Murder, Incorporated.
-Well, where did
you get your money?
-Steve, it is none
of your business.
-You think Capone ever
had a fruit salad?
How is it?
-It's good.
JOHNNY: Ah, maybe I
should have a bite.
Why not?
What could it be?
What, 800, 900 calories?
A couple of hundred
grams of fat.
-Hey, Johnny.
Sorry I'm late.
-Where the hell were you?
-I got hung up.
I tried to call you.
-Were you with
that Babette again?
God, I've been having
fantasies about her.
Look at me, I'm feeling
guilty about your affair.
-Will you, please,
Johnny, keep it down?
-You hurt your wife,
I splatter your brains
all over that fancy
Persian rug of yours.
-Johnny, I told you,
I'm sick about that.
-Got ya.
-What?
-Armand gave this to me.
I told you, the guy's brilliant.
-Armand gave you that?
Unbelievable.
-And like we suspected,
I think he's connected.
-No.
No, he owns two car dealerships.
-Yeah, and the Corelone family
was in the olive oil business.
-Son of a bitch, you're right.
-Well, why should
you panic, Steve?
A Jewish guy who looks like
a rabbi going up for Capone.
-Hey, Armand, I
can do this role.
I just-- I need a boost.
An image.
Something.
-All right.
All right.
Now, no offense, but
you're most comfortable
as the dull neurotic.
And you almost made a living
playing guys like that.
-Yeah, the key word is "almost."
-Yeah, right.
But dullness is a
form of aggression.
Your job is to get to the
real aggression underneath.
That's where you're going
to find the real colors.
The reds, the purples,
the shocking greens.
Think of it is as-- as opera.
That's where these guys live.
It's Pagliacci,
Traviata, [inaudible].
All right?
Now, can you go there?
-Yes.
How?
-What do you think?
Come here, Steve.
Come here.
Huh?
-It's incredible.
Thank you, man.
-Hey.
No problem.
-This has got to
stay between us, OK?
-Sure.
And I will be indebted to
you for the rest of my life.
-Hey, come on.
Hey.
Come on.
Hey, what did I
tell you about that?
Huh?
-He threw in fresh basil.
-Oh, he cooked for you
when he gave you the eyes?
-Yeah.
Yeah.
Enough with the food,
let's do some improvs here.
-All right.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
We'll put it on its feet.
That always helps.
-Mm, that's a good idea.
Pop, we're going to walk.
Stay here, all right?
-All right, so what am I?
-My henchman, of course.
-Oh, that's good.
That's good.
Good.
-Oh, I like that.
That bounce, that thing.
I got to use that.
It's nice.
Hey, you're a good
actor, you prick.
Remind me not to kill you.
-Yeah, sure, boss.
Whatever you say.
-[inaudible].
Oh.
Oh, Rocco.
Want to take care of this?
-You gentlemen
care to step aside?
-Maybe sometime this decade.
-Come on.
-Don't go too small.
All right?
I think your big
comic impulses might
be good for the character.
-I don't get it.
You think I should make
him like more ha-ha funny?
-No.
No.
Not ha-ha funny, but like,
you know, weird funny.
-Weird funny?
-Don't complicate it.
Just stop.
Stop, stop.
Hey, contain it.
JOHNNY: Contain it?
-Listen, Johnny.
I got to go.
-Go?
No, no, no.
No, you can't.
Not now.
-Didn't I tell you?
-No.
-I got the last-minute looping
session on the Pacino thing.
-You just got here.
-Oh my god.
-What?
-Don't turn around.
Those guys are following us.
JOHNNY: Oh, Christ.
Oh, let's go.
Come on.
Maybe I came on
too strong before.
-You?
I gave my best Ray Liotta
in "Angel Dust" look.
That's the kind of thing
you get killed for.
-Come on, let's get my
father and get out of here.
DORIAN: Johnny, I wish
I knew how to fight.
I don't know how
to fight, Johnny.
I never did.
Oh, God.
Is this-- this is it.
It's the end.
Murdered at Venice Beach.
It's like a bad
movie of the week.
God is punishing me.
What are we going to do, Johnny?
-Shit.
What are we, mice or men?
-What are you saying?
-What do you-- what do
you fucking guys want?
You looking for trouble?
-Whoa.
Whoa, now.
We don't want any trouble.
Look.
My name is Joey, and these are
my friends, Paulie and Ralphie.
-How you doing?
-I'm doing good.
-Good.
-Now if you don't
mind, I just want
to talk to you for a minute.
In private.
-He's with me.
-You want to be alone?
All right.
-OK.
OK, now this may seem
a little off the wall,
but, uh, I'm in
from Buffalo and I'm
doing some research
on, uh-- La Familia.
You know, people of that ilk?
Now, please, just stop me
right now if I'm out of line.
-No, no, no, continue.
-Great.
Anyway, when I saw you
guys, I said, Jesus,
this could be the real thing.
So I'm just going to come right
out and ask you, am I right?
-Are you right?
Is he right?
-I don't know.
-Anything's possible.
So what's this research for--
a magazine, newspaper article?
what?
-Actually, no.
You see, I'm auditioning
for this part tomorrow.
Do you know the director
Martin Scorsese?
-This damn Theresa.
What the hell, is every mug from
here to Miami up for this part?
-You-- you know Theresa?
-Oh.
-It's all right, Johnny.
It's all right.
Buffalo.
Got an agent out here?
JOEY: They got an
office out here.
-Would you-- what's
the matter with you?
-What?
-I'm helping you.
[phone ringing]
THERESA (ON PHONE):
Hi, it's Theresa.
You've reached Broadway Casting.
You know the drill.
[beep]
JOHNNY: Come to Papa.
-You are unbelievable, Johnny.
-Garbage.
Garbage.
-It looks like a curse.
-Come on, when it comes
to poker, I'm Sinatra
and you're Sonny Bono.
-Yeah?
Well, when it comes
to acting, I'm De Niro
and you are Desi Arnaz.
-Please.
It's more like I'm Pacino
and you're Pat Sajak.
-No.
It's more like you're
Costello and he is Abbott.
And can we please pay cards?
I'm down $80.
-Oh.
Hey, yeah, speaking of
Italians, I was at Spago today.
Scorsese was having lunch.
Yeah, calamari in
a marinara sauce.
Wonder what he's doing in town.
MAN: Hm.
Come on, give me an ace.
Ah, damn.
-[inaudible].
-Not for nothing,
but you know, I
think Scorsese is
the best there is.
-Yeah, but he should
stick with what he knows.
Nobody does street
guys like him.
-Hey, did you fuck my wife?
-That's a sick question.
You're a sick fuck.
I'm not going to answer that.
-Did you fuck my wife?
-I'm not going to answer that.
MAN: Did you fuck my wife?
DORIAN: I'm not
going to answer it.
I'm not going to answer that.
-Did you fuck my wife?
-I'm not going to answer that.
-Stevie, what are
they talking about?
-It's a movie, Mom.
It's just imitations.
-I don't know, I
heard some things.
-What things you heard?
-I hear some things.
-What things?
-I heard some things.
-I hear some things.
-What things?
-Some things I heard.
-You both are over
the top in your manner
than everything else.
Because I am, without
a doubt, the finest
Italian American actor
of my generation.
-Danny Aiello.
-You got it right, Estelle.
-Well, goodbye, Susan.
And I hope I never
see you again.
-Tony Curtis.
[laughter]
-You're a very funny man.
-Funny how?
-A very funny man.
-What, like a clown?
-No.
You're a very funny man.
-What, like I'm here
for your amusement?
-No, you're a very funny man.
-What, like ha-ha funny?
-No, you're funny
like this funny.
-I don't know, but I mean, it's
amazing what one role can do.
I mean, before
"Raging Bull," Pesci.
What, he was nothing.
Now he's a big star.
MAN: Did you fuck my wife?
You fuck my wife?
DORIAN: No, did
you fuck my wife?
BOTH: Did you fuck my wife?
Did you fuck my wife?
Are you talking to me?
I don't know.
-[inaudible].
And then Steve.
And then, you know?
And Dorian, too.
It's a total farce.
Total farce.
And I do not want to
leap into that insanity.
-Then why are you helping them?
-Oh, I don't know.
They're my friends.
-Ah.
-Yo, am I scary?
-Hm?
-Am I a threat?
No, they all think I'm
connected, like some mob guy.
-Are you connected, Armand?
-What is this?
You, too?
-Well, you are oftly secretive.
I mean, I've never
even met your family.
-Well, I-- you know, I
hardly see them myself.
-Is it because I'm Chinese?
-I love that you're Chinese.
I told you, my
marriage ended when
I became an actor and my
family sided with my wife.
End of story.
-I got a phone
call this morning.
-Mm-hmm.
-I got a job.
-Hey, great.
YOLANDA: In Seattle.
-Seattle?
-Yeah.
I have to tell them by
tomorrow if I want it.
ARMAND: Tomorrow?
YOLANDA: It's a really
good graphic arts firm.
I'm sorry to spring this on
you like this, but I-- yeah,
I have to make a decision.
-I guess you do.
-So, if you, uh, want me to
stay, I'd like that very much.
But I'm going to need more.
-See, I'm thinking the mug,
but I start with a walk.
And then I make it a strut.
And then I add a little bounce.
But then-- this is
key-- I bring it down.
I bring it down.
And down.
Then all of a sudden--
boom, I'm letting
the whole world know--
don't fuck with me.
-It's working.
-It is, isn't it?
I know.
I can-- I can feel it.
God.
Oh, Sam.
I just-- I love-- I love acting.
What?
-You are so good and so pretty.
You're even prettier than me.
-Do you really think so?
-Yeah.
-I love you.
I love you.
-All right, get in the
kitchen and make me a snack!
-No, now you're whining.
Don't complain in the scream.
Threaten me with it.
God knows you have enough
anger to start World War III.
-What the hell is that
supposed to mean, Jo?
-Oh, that's it.
The scumbag prick in person.
-Yeah, but that's just mean.
-Exactly.
-I just-- I need something else.
You know, it needs-- it needs.
I got to have the right
prop or something.
I know what I need.
Silk boxer shorts.
De Niro wore them in
"The Untouchables."
-You don't have
silk boxer shorts.
-Get me a pair of
your babydolls.
-Steve.
-Your babydolls, Jo.
-They're not going to fit you.
-Jo, just do it.
Don't make a face.
Help me.
All right?
I'm asking for help.
-Why don't you just try acting.
Acting.
-I am acting.
-What a concept.
-Acting consists of a
lot of things, honey.
-Do you want the pink
ones or the red ones?
-Try the red ones, Daddy.
They're more masculine.
-Honey.
-All right.
Marching back to bed.
Marching down the hallway.
Turning off the light.
Under the covers.
-Ugh.
-I love you.
Bye.
[door closing]
-Yeah.
This feels like something.
This is good.
This is good, honey.
What do you think?
Huh?
-Steve.
-What do you think?
It's not Steve.
It's Al.
Al.
And if you're nice to me,
later I'll show you my scars.
Muah.
-Oh.
-Yeah.
Yeah, baby.
This is a start of something.
Yeah.
What do you think?
This will work.
Oh, god.
-Janey's bird pot.
-I, I got carried away.
-What happened?
-Nothing, honey.
-Mommy, what's wrong?
-We got-- it was an accident.
-Oh, Steve.
Oh.
-An acting accident.
-Oh, god.
-Sweetheart, I'm sorry.
-You know, it's times
like this that you really
have to admit to yourself
that you have a dream.
That maybe you're just
like every other fool
who came to this town.
-You're not l everybody else.
-What do you dream about, Daddy?
-Hey, girls.
What are you doing up?
-I'm thirsty.
-Oh, come here.
Poor baby.
-I can't see any stars, Daddy.
There's too much smog.
-No, no, no, look.
Look, look.
See over there in the West?
Venus.
That's Venus, see?
See that big thing there
that looks like a star?
That's Venus.
-Cool.
You'll be great tomorrow, Dad.
Don't worry.
HANNAH: And no more rehearsing.
Take the morning off.
-Guys, nine holes on me.
I insist.
A little gift to show
how much I love you.
ARMAND: Thanks, Johnny.
That's very big of you.
-Johnny.
-What?
-Your audition is
this afternoon.
Do you think this
is the best idea?
-Yeah.
Yeah.
That's this afternoon,
but this morning I
want to relax and play
some golf with my friends.
Screw it.
Look who I'm talking to, the
three extras from "The Piano."
Will you guys tattoo some
smiles on those faces?
STEVE: Absolutely.
Nice.
DORIAN: Very nice.
ARMAND: Must be your lucky day.
STEVE: No, you go.
You go second.
I don't like going second.
DORIAN: You always go second.
STEVE: And I always hate it.
Will you please just go today?
DORIAN: Why are you
telling me this now.
You've always gone second.
Go second.
STEVE: General, I'm
just tired of you
telling me what to
do all the time, OK?
DORIAN: OK.
I won't tell you.
Just go second.
-Johnny?
Johnny, where you going?
DORIAN: Johnny.
-Johnny, what are you doing?
-Rudy Ptak.
You son of a bitch.
-Johnny.
How the hell are you doing?
Jeez, I look in your face.
It's like-- like
looking in a mirror.
We're incredibly handsome.
-Yeah.
Yeah.
We look like a
couple of bouncers
at a teamsters convention.
-Ha-ha.
This is my agent
here, Sean Nusbalm.
-Yeah, hi.
-So, uh-- hey, congratulations.
I heard you got a TV
series in New York.
-Yeah.
Yeah.
Well, you know, just
a little bit of luck.
-Yeah.
So what are you doing out here?
-I'm auditioning.
It's just some thing, you know?
-Yeah, I know.
It's Capone, isn't it?
-It's not your business what
roles I go up for, John.
-Not my business?
Every time I turn around,
you're in my face.
What do you got,
somebody telling
you what I'm going up for, huh?
Are you clocking me?
-What's he nuts or something?
What's he doing here?
-Oh, no, no.
That's it.
No.
He's got somebody
tipping him off.
That's it, right?
-Johnny.
-Right?
Really.
Who is it, a friend?
This guy?
-Maybe he's, uh-- maybe he's
just a better actor than you.
-Oh, hey.
-Oh, really?
Oh, look, the suit talks.
What are you drinking here, pal?
Some actor's blood?
-You're way off-base here.
Now, back off before
something happens.
Back off.
-Ooh, tough guy, huh?
Oh, good anger, Rudy.
The trouble is I'm not scared.
You're not going deep enough.
-Yeah.
You're going to tell
me about deeper.
Mr. Over-the-Top himself?
-Over the top?
-Hey.
-Hey. hey.
-Hey, Johnny.
-Johnny.
[interposing voices]
-No biting.
-Hey, hey, hey.
-Calm down.
-Stop it.
Look at what you're--
[interposing voices]
RUDY: I think he bit my ear.
-Jesus.
God, Rudy.
I, I lost it.
I don't know what got into me.
Rudy, I'm--
RUDY: You're a maniac.
-Hey.
-It's all right.
-You know how many roles-- you
took just as many roles from me
as I took from you.
-I did?
-Yes, you did.
The cabby in "Baywatch."
And-- and there was
that-- the stalker
in the Lizzy Wagner movie.
No, maybe it was a gynecologist.
The point is, everywhere I
look, I see your face, too.
JOHNNY: Rudy.
All right, Rudy.
I'm sorry, Rudy.
I don't know what it is.
It's just this part, man.
It's got me crazy.
-All right, all
right, all right.
-All right?
-I know.
-All right.
-I heard there's only
a few of us up for it,
but the new word I hear is
that the list is growing.
-Yeah.
Your pals are on the list, too.
-Oh my god.
-I have no idea what
he's talking about.
SEAN: What do you mean?
I saw your names myself.
Both of you have
appointments this afternoon.
-Johnny.
My agent got me up for it.
I swear to god I was
going to tell you.
-Johnny.
Johnny, I--
DORIAN: I'm sorry.
-I have always wanted
to meet Scorsese.
This was a golden
opportunity for me.
I-- I'm very sorry.
Hey.
Johnny.
What the hell?
-Johnny.
[interposing voices]
-Somebody call a doctor.
-He's turning blue!
-Doctor!
-Hey, do something.
-I'm out of the service area!
-Where do you hit him?
-Where the heart is?
DORIAN: Call a doctor.
[phone ringing]
-Hello.
Hi.
What?
-I don't care what it
took to set it up, Harry.
Cancel the damn addition.
No, you're not hearing me.
Do it.
-I should go to hell
for all eternity.
I almost wish I
believed in that stuff.
-Oh, it's OK.
I'll go for both of us.
Hannah, I should have told you.
I'm--
-Will you stop,
both of you, please?
You're not responsible for this.
He is.
And I am.
All those years of cream
sauces and Caesar salads.
And cheesecake and cannolis.
And Thai dumplings.
-Oh, Han.
Don't do this to yourself.
-Oh my god.
I'm starving.
-Hi, honey.
-The audition.
What time is it?
-Johnny, please.
Sit back down.
You're not going anywhere.
You're sick.
STEVE: That's his voice.
I hear his voice.
-Jesus, Hannah.
What happened?
What?
-Just take it easy.
STEVE: I got to talk to him.
Johnny.
Thank god you're all right.
I'm so sorry.
I didn't want to
hurt you, buddy.
-Johnny, thank god.
I wanted to die myself
after what I did.
-What is this?
Am I dying?
-No, no.
-Jeez, Hannah.
What's happening?
What's going on?
-It's OK.
Now, listen to me.
They took a lot of tests.
They're still not quite sure.
They think you had
a mild heart attack.
-Oh, [speaking italian].
-It could have been a lot worse.
You are still here.
That's all that matters.
-Oh, Hannah.
It happened.
It finally happened.
-Honey, it's going to be OK.
I know it.
I do.
-The kids, do they know?
-No.
They're still at school.
-And Pop?
-Went to the track.
He's not home yet.
-Oh, Jesus.
-Johnny, we canceled
the audition.
We don't want to go to
any auditions without you.
-Buddy, I got bit
by the envy monster.
It consumed me.
-You too?
You should have just
told me, that's all.
You're my best friends.
My family.
What's happening to us?
And for what?
For fame?
Fortune?
Are we willing to throw
away everything for it?
Maybe that's just the
way it's supposed to be.
Nothing more.
But in the end, my kids will
remember me as the hit man
on "NYPD Blue."
-Oh, sweetheart.
-No.
-Johnny.
-No, Johnny.
-No.
Johnny, no, no, no.
Johnny.
-You're just tired.
You'll be fine.
-Oh.
-Excuse me.
We've had quite a
day, haven't we?
-[inaudible].
-You'll have to excuse us now.
-Well, that's it.
I'm quitting acting.
I'm getting the hell out.
-What about me?
I actually tried to
sabotage his performance.
I'm out of control.
My whole life is a sham.
-Your whole life?
What are you talking about?
-Oh, nothing, honey.
I'm just nuts.
-Look, I, uh-- I know we got
a lot of stuff to talk about.
But this happened and--
-No, that's OK.
Listen, I've made a decision.
I've decided to take
the job in Seattle.
It will be a good change.
And you and I will have time
apart to think things through.
-Wait a second.
When did you decide this?
Don't I have anything
to say about this?
-Of course.
Say anything you want.
-Um--
HANNAH: No!
What are you--
JOHNNY: Get these things off me.
HANNAH: You cannot do that.
Stop.
-It was gas.
Gas.
From the burrito I
ate this morning.
It mimicked a heart attack.
Where are my clothes?
-Will you just listen--
-No, there's time.
There's time. no.
Gas.
Thank you.
And you're all forgiven,
you bunch of shits.
Now, where's [inaudible]?
I need my clothes.
-Johnny.
HANNAH: Stop it.
Stop running.
-Oh, food.
Thank you.
-Give me that.
-Life is precious.
Hang in there, pal.
-Honey.
You're coming off a sedative.
You're not yourself.
-I've never been more myself.
Don't you see, sweetheart,
how beautiful everything is.
The universe wants
me at this audition.
-Great.
He's going holy on us.
-It's a miracle.
- --perfect Capone.
Harry, Harry, it's Dorian.
Listen.
Dorian.
Look, did you cancel
the audition, Harry?
Good, because I'm
going in after all.
-You snake.
After everything
we've been through,
you're still going
in on that audition?
-Fucking A I'm going in.
It was-- it was an accident.
It was a false alarm.
He forgave us, didn't he?
You should go back in, too.
You son of a bitch, you
didn't cancel, did you?
-I couldn't cancel it.
-What the--
-My cousin got me the audition.
-What the hell was going
to be the criteria?
A coma, you go in?
A death, you cancel?
What?
I'll kill you.
You broke my cellphone.
JOHNNY: Look at this day.
What a beautiful day.
Where's that car?
I love that car.
-Listen to me, if we are
going to do this, I'm driving.
-Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I love you.
-Johnny, listen.
Did you mean what you said?
You forgive us?
-Stevie, my tortured friend.
I wish you could love yourself
the way others love you.
The world would be your oyster.
And Dorian, my deceiving,
guilt-ridden pal,
cherish this moment.
Give her babies.
-All right, Johnny.
OK.
And Armand, you.
You have more character
in your pinkie
than most men have
in their entire mind.
You knew it all, didn't you?
Dorian and Steve going for
the part, Theresa running
the audition, and still
you remained loyal?
-You're my hero, Armand.
-Break a leg, Johnny.
-All right.
-Knock them dead.
-Thank you.
Thank you.
-Bye.
-Good luck, buddy.
-All right.
-Why did Johnny say you were
deceiving and guilt-ridden?
-Armand, what is it?
-My Theresa handled
the audition.
-Hey, Tommy.
You help me and I help you.
Two neighborhood guys make
good, gumba and a mick.
But now you want to
get elected again,
put some distance between us.
Hey, I understand.
I know the game.
But this, calling
me names in public,
saying bad things
about my people
when we get you in office.
Hey, I know it's an act, huh?
Put on a little show.
What the hell?
I'm the bad guy.
You're the good guy.
Put a little
distance between us.
But you show me respect.
If you don't, I'll kill
your whole fucking family.
Blow their brains all
over the sidewalk.
I'll start with that pretty,
little wife of yours.
Hey, I know, pal.
I'm just protecting my own.
So now we understand each other.
You play your part, I play mine.
And we'll all be out
there with bells on.
I promise.
I'll see ya after the election.
Oh, and give my regards
to Evelyn and the kids.
-Good, Johnny.
Great.
Very good.
Very, very good.
Thank you.
-Thank you.
Thank you very much, sir.
THERESA: Thank you, Johnny.
-That was pretty good, you know?
-Mm-hmm.
-Hey, I-- I know it's an act.
We all got to put on a show.
What the hell?
You're the god guy
and I'm the bad guy.
And you want to put some
distance between us.
But you show me some respect.
If you don't, I'll kill
your whole fucking family.
I'll blow their brains
out all over the sidewalk.
I'll start with that pretty,
little wife of yours.
Pal, I am just
looking after my own.
OK?
So now we understand each other.
You do your part, I'll do mine.
And we'll be there
with bells on.
Promise.
I'll talk to you
after the election.
Regards to Evelyn and the kids.
-Good.
It's really good, Steve.
Thanks.
It's really-- it's good.
Very good.
That was good.
THERESA: Mm-hmm.
-Thank you, Steve.
THERESA: Yeah, thank you, Steve.
-What the hell?
I'm the bad guy and
you're the good guy.
Sure, put some
distance between us.
But show me respect.
If you don't, I'll kill
your whole fucking family.
I will blow their brains
out all over the sidewalk.
And I will start with
that pretty wife of yours.
Hey, I know, pal.
I'm just protecting my own, too.
OK, so now we
understand each other.
You play your part, I play mine.
And we will both be out
there with bells on, promise.
I will talk to you
after the election.
Give my regards to
Evelyn and the kids.
-Good, Dorian.
Very good.
THERESA: Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
-Excellent.
Excellent.
-Thank you.
Thank you.
You-- you want to
go another way?
We could try a little,
uh, something--
-No, no, no.
That was-- that was fine.
It was great.
-OK.
Thank you.
I-- I'm a big-- thanks.
-Yeah.
-Thank you.
-Uh, other way.
-Thanks.
Um, do you validate for parking?
-Um, I don't know.
Do we validate or what?
THERESA: I don't know.
-Ask the kid.
There's a kid outside, ask him.
-All right.
I'll ask.
-Did you feel good about
that note I gave you?
-It was so right on.
-It was?
-Yeah.
Because--
-That felt good.
You did well, huh?
-Yeah.
You?
It was OK.
-Wild, huh?
-Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
-How you guys doing?
-Hey, Rudy.
What do you say?
Rudy, my wife, Hannah.
Rudy Ptak.
-How you doing?
-So how'd it go?
-It was, uh, good.
I-- I think.
You?
-Uh.
-Are you-- are you
feeling all right?
-Yeah.
You?
No business like show business.
Take care of yourself, Johnny.
See you around.
JOHNNY: You too, Rudy.
-Dorian.
-Babette.
-Hi, babe.
-Hey.
What-- what are you doing here?
-I'm reading for Scorsese.
My agent got me in.
-That's great.
That's great.
Babette, this is my,
um, wife, Samantha.
Sam, this is Babette from the
Victory Boulevard Playhouse.
We did the Mamet
Showcase together.
-Really?
Um, what play?
-"Death Trap."
-"American Buffalo."
-"Glengarry."
-"Streamers."
Well, bye.
-What?
Honey, she's an old friend.
We work together.
She-- she's an actress.
She's overly demonstrative.
ARMAND: Where's Therese?
ASSISTANT: What are you doing?
Who are you?
ARMAND: Don't worry about it.
It's not your concern.
Now, where is she?
-No, you don't have
an appointment.
-Armand?
ASSISTANT: She
can't be disturbed.
She's in a session.
-Yeah, she's going
to be disturbed.
-Armand?
ASSISTANT: Wait a minute.
Listen.
-Armand.
ASSISTANT: I told you,
you can't go in there.
I'm sorry, this
maniac just barged in.
I didn't--
-Armand.
-What are you doing?
ASSISTANT: I told him
he couldn't come in.
-Everybody, back off.
-Oh my god.
-Everybody just back off.
Back away.
MAN: What's going on here?
-Come on.
Come on, we got a
private audition.
-How would you like a
private ass-kicking?
-Whoa.
Hey.
-Armand.
-Hey, I'm auditioning here.
-Your audition is over, friend.
Sit down.
JOHNNY: Armand,
what are you doing?
-Don't call me that.
That's not my name anymore.
I am finished with all that.
Everybody, sit down.
You do not want
to make that call.
WOMAN: Sit down.
Do what he says, please.
-OK, OK.
Whatever your name is,
what's in the suitcase, pal?
-None of your business, pal.
Everybody just sit down.
Hey.
What did I just tell you,
sit down and stay put.
All of yous.
Look at you, think you're
so smart with your slick,
show biz lives, spitting
out one lie after another.
Give me that chair.
You have any idea
what it's like to be
typecast your whole life, huh?
To have people
smile in your face,
but behind your back whisper,
oh, watch out for him?
You know who his family is?
Or what it's like to
be a kid and elicit
fear from grown people?
A kid does not
want to be feared.
He wants to be loved.
But fear is what
you grow up with.
It's the air you breathe.
And soon, you
cultivate that fear.
You learn to look someone in the
eyes and just make them shake.
It's pathetic.
Those whispers still hurt.
Smiles and whispers.
You know it splits
you right in half.
You walk around with--
with stitches going
down right the
center of your body.
But then you discover
that there are people
in this world who have
it every which way.
Yeah, they play all the roles.
And they are loved for it
because they are our magicians.
They are our sorcerers.
And then you start
to think, hey,
I could do that because
I understand both sides.
I am both sides.
So destiny takes a little
turn, it breaks the chain,
and then you leave
your family and you
venture out into
this big, new world.
Now, this is a
very special world.
It's got big dreams in it, hm?
You had those dreams, right?
You almost tasted the
glory that awaits you.
But it's never the right day.
It's never the right moment.
And it's never the right part.
And then you realize that
it's a punishment for all
the bad things you did
in your other life.
We lived together.
I was godfather to your son.
-Armand, I didn't
want to hurt you.
-Well, this is a lie.
You are all liars.
And I-- yeah, I am
a fool because I
am a traitor to my family.
But I have learned
my lesson very well.
This son is going to return
to his family with pride
and ferocity and a gesture
that will make my father proud.
Hey, you.
Will you sit down?
I relish this moment
because in this moment
I reclaim my father's respect
and I make myself whole again
in the eyes of
god and the devil.
And Dad, [speaking italian].
May this fuse us in
our ancestral glory.
Yeah, Dad.
Let's show them what
they fear the most.
[screaming]
-Oh, god.
-Huh?
-I'm available.
All you got to do is
call my agent, 555-1635.
-You mean you're not that guy?
-No, I'm not that guy.
And, uh, my father's
a Toyota dealer.
-Oh.
-It's the truth.
Nobody believes me.
-OK.
-Crazy actors.
You're going to hear from
my lawyer, you little prick.
-Jesus Christ, you need therapy.
-Honey.
-I want a divorce.
-Jesus, are you
out of your mind?
Have you lost it completely?
-No, I just want to know
why you didn't call me in.
-What?
-Theresa, why did
you pass me over?
You're one of my oldest
friends in the world.
Just say it, will you?
Just once.
Right to my face.
Why didn't you call me in?
-Because you weren't
right for the part.
OK, let's hear it for
Yolanda and Armand.
May you share joy and happiness
for the rest of your lives.
[applause]
-Salud.
-Well, uh, I got to say being
here with, uh, my lovely,
uh-- my lovely,
ooh-- my lovely wife.
And all of you makes me feel
like for the first time maybe
in my whole life I am
right where I ought to be.
[applause]
-And, um, to all of our
great friends, some of whom
invested in this
very restaurant,
that my husband-- oh my god, I
can't believe I'm saying that.
My own personal husband
is the proud owner of.
Thank you, guys.
[applause]
-Dad.
Can I call you dad?
-I'd love you to call me dad.
-At last we meet the
mysterious family.
-We're so happy he
married a Spanish Asian.
-What is that jacket?
Salmon?
-It looks like a
maitre d from the Copa.
Here, give me a $20 quick.
We'll get a table.
-I'm the father of the groom.
-No.
-That's funny.
A lot of people do that.
But you know what I thought
when I saw you, I said, Camry.
That's what I said to myself.
Call me.
I'll give you a good
deal on a Camry.
Talk to me personally, not to
that bastard brother of mine.
Ah, here you go.
Frank Minetti.
-Thank you, Frank.
-Bye.
-I still think he's connected.
-Will you stop with that?
You're going to give
Johnny gas again.
-Very funny.
That audition ended
Armand's acting career
and nearly cost me my
life, right, Therese?
-Oh, come on, Johnny.
Don't remind me.
OK?
ARMAND: Oh, Therese.
The one casting person who
genuinely loves actors.
-Yeah.
Well, she's dated about
a thousand of them.
-Yeah.
And every one of them
would have been more right
for Capone than you or Dorian.
-Ooh.
God, I love you.
-You should.
At least now you have a career.
-Yeah.
What were those roles?
It was the, uh-- the shady
lawyer that got disemboweled
and the shady lawyer
that got impaled.
-And the compassionate
doctor who's head exploded.
Hey, they pay me.
I work.
Right, honey?
Muah.
-Muah.
Can you believe this?
He's blowing me kisses.
I can't decide what's
weirder, the new, wild Steve
or the old, depressed one.
-Hey.
How are you, honey?
-Good.
It's so good to see you.
-Doing OK?
-Hi.
Congratulations.
I'm sorry [inaudible].
-You all right?
-Can you believe that, Johnny?
She's carrying my kid.
She still won't talk to me.
WOMAN: So Johnny?
-Yeah.
-Who'd they finally
cast as Capone?
-Uh, we don't like
to discuss that.
WOMAN: No, come on.
Who'd they cast?
-Keanu Reeves.
-Keanu Reeves?
-That's right, the studio
wanted to go another way.
-No, the studio wanted a name.
JOHNNY: Yeah, I know.
Scorsese thought they
were nuts, so Keanu's in.
Scorsese's out.
-Wait, wait, wait, what?
The kid from the bus, he's
going to play Al Capone?
-I like Keanu Reeves.
-Go meet somebody.
Keanu Reeves?
-Can you believe this
[inaudible], Mr. M?
Capone, the elementary
school years.
-Who understands show business?
-(SINGING) Still searching
out my destination.
I just got back from all--
-Steve. -(SINGING) --from
all around the world.
-You OK?
-Yeah, I'm fine.
I got it all.
Except for maybe a good
cannoli every now and then, eh?
I love that tofu.
-Hey, Johnny.
-Hey, [inaudible].
-Hey, Hannah.
How are you?
You look great.
-Hey, uh, [inaudible].
Did you hear?
The Palm is doing Mussolini.
You're perfect.
Check it out.
-What are you doing?
-Hm?
No, no.
Nothing.
-Sorry.
-Honey, what are you doing?
You all right?
-Yeah.
-What else?
-Mr. Mussolini.
-Mr. Call me Benito.
-Oh, please.
[music playing]