Now I want you and your sister to slow down, okay? Becasue one of you is going to get hurt.
Do you remember yesterday?
They sure grow up fast, don't they?
Too fast.
Oh Jerry, no!
Hello. Can you point out Robby Brown for me, please?
Robby Brown?
The Unborn II
SOLD
So Joey, what do you think of our new home?
Here it is.
Look. Joey, I found it.
Where should I put this?
Y
SOLD
Sorry about that
I got used to this
place being empty.
It's okay. Summers getting kinda hot anyways.
Artie! Who are you talking to?
New neighbor Marj. The Clarks finally sold their place.
How much did you pay for it?
-US $ 450,000 and you?
$500,000
I told you they wouldn't get $600,000 for it.
Oh! We would be right over.
So exciting! New neighbors.
Hello there, hello...!
I am Marjorie Phillips,Marge...
-This is Arthur. -Artie.
Catherine Moore.
Catherine! Nice to meet you and welcome to the neighborhood.
You are going to love this neighborhood. It's really a wonderful place
Except for the couple across the street She's a little funny...
She might ask you over on Saturday night, for you know what..
Artie stop talking. "Help her with the crates."
That's ok! I'll manage.
I need the exercise.
He's really very strong.
He picks me up every saturday night every once in a while, if you know what I mean..
Catherine, are you married?
Of course she's married! Look at all the things in the truck! Baby bottle, stroller...
No, I'm not
Do you smell smoke Ms. Moore?
I smell smoke.
It's that daughter of yours. Sally Anne.
You better not be smoking again!
Did you manage to see what coloured jacket it was?
It was dark. Dark..? Yeah!
This is Lieutenant Briggs. He'd like to ask you a few questions.
First, what is CSAT?
California Scholastic Aptitude Test.
They give those tests to 7 year olds?
His QI was estimated at 180.
And I say estimated, because we don't have the ability to test any higher.
It says here that he was expelled from school. Why?
He was always fighting.
That time he pushed a little girl off a swing.Her arm is broken.
Detective, check out the girl's parents.
Why did let a violent kid back into your school?
Lieutenant, the boy was in 5 foster homes in 4 years.
I felt sorry for him.
I understand.
I think that's about it.
What if the killer comes back?
What if she hurts the other children?
I have two kids of my own, Mrs Wagner.
We will do everything we can to make sure that doesn't happen.
-Alright
-Thank you.
Catherine!
Your neighbors are here!
Yuuhuu, Hello Dear!
We thought you would be so busymoving in with the baby...
I made this for you.
Oh Arthur, look what she has done with the place.
This is so much nicer than the Clarks, you just couldn't imagine!
Oh look! I don't....
They had plastic plants all over the place.
It's really nice to have live things. Look!
Look what she's done. What's this?
Oh! Are you a typist dear?
No. I write children's books.
Do you make a living doing it?
Sometimes. Currently
the market is not very good.
I'm a writer too you know!
O
You wouldn't want to read that Catherine
Oh by the way, this is
for the baby.
Thank you, I'm sure he's going to love that.
Can I give it to him?
I'm afraid he's napping
Oh please, Can I just pick him up? I just love babies.
I just got him now..
-How old is Joey?
-6 months.
This is very complicated stuff for a 6 month old.
That was Joey's fathers when he was a boy.
Okay...
I know where this piece is goes.
- I'll go get a bandage.
-No! I got to get home.
He hates the sight of blood.
Especially his own.
Come on, Arthur. Careful.. You are dripping it on the carpet!
Excuse me!
Are you Catherine Moore, the writer?
Marge told me, when she brought over my casserole.
Oh, you got one too?
Of course. I have the right credentials.
I am John Edson.
I guess you already know who I am.
Who might this be?
This is Joey. He's asleep.
If I stop moving he'll wake up.
Excuse me.
I'll see you around.
Have you tried the casserole yet?
I'm afraid to.
Don't be, I hate to admit it but I ate mine all in one sitting.
Boy or girl?
-Boy. and yours?
I've got a boy too. "This is Patrick.
He is 12 months old.
Joey is 6 months.
Let's meet Joey.
He's very special.
Don't you pay any attention to her.
Oh! You better not tell my parents.
Why should I? "It's not going to stop you from smoking." Can I have one?
Thanks! It's been a while.
So, do you mind if I hangout back here for a little while?
-Oh, no... I'm leaving
-Oh, you're working?
I got to meet a publisher.
So, bet you already have a babysitter for the kid, no?
No, I don't know any.
Would you mind staying with him?
He's asleep. You don't have to play with him or anything.
Babysitting 101, never work the kid when he's asleep, right?
You know your parents are right about the cigarettes.
They just don't want you to die of lung cancer.
No they would rather, I die of boredom.
THE BOY ON THE OUTSIDE
Dr. Forrest,
I'm sorry miss, visiting hours are over.
Can I just have a minute to see my nephew?
This is my first chance to see him.
I'm sorry, you'll have to come back in the morning.
Hey! you can't come in here.
She's got a gun!
Drop your guns!.
Now!
Don't stop!
Jesus fucking christ!
Lieutenant Briggs.
Same shell casing we found at the playground.
Checkout those security monitors and see if it picked up anything.
I want to see her face.
Would you turn down that noise, please?
Mother!
So, what was the baby like?
How am I supposed to know?
Well you were baby sitting.
Like I said, he
was asleep.
The whole time?
-I don't know.
So then he wasn't asleep.
Well, I did hear something.
Sally Anne! If that baby was awake, you should have been playing with him ...
Becasue you are the babysitter and that is what babysitters do.
Mom, I couldn't. Ok?
-Why not?
Sally Anne, you are not telling me something?
The door was locked. "What door?"
The door to the baby's room.
Artie!
Live with Channel 4
We are here live from Kennedy medical center,
At approx. 9 PM, an
and killed newborn
Joey, where are you?
Joey, come on out!
L1 here, go ahead.
We have that BMW, she ditched it in Woodland Hills
L1 copy. I'm enroute
Excuse me sir. Is this a Lexus?
-"I'll take the keys please."
Move back. Back.
Hey it's my car! Jesus
Guess what Joey? They are going to publish mommys book!
So to celebrate, let's give this a try. Ok?
I think you're going to like it.
Look Joey I know it's hard for you. It's hard for me too!
I know. Mommy is sorry.
Lieutenant Briggs.
A guy about half a mile from here, reported a stolen Lexus.
He said he got a good look at the lady who took it.
So she's mobile again.
Mommy knows.
Well, when you are through with this...
We shall loosen you, Ok?
Maybe tomorrow.
Catherine Moore?
We are from the child welfare agency
We would like to ask a few questions.
What kind of questions?
I'm sorry to say,
but there has been a report of possible misconduct ...
Involving you and your child.
Who called you? "It was anonymous Mrs Moore."
I can assure you that
there has been no misconduct.
Can we see the child?
Excuse me! "Do you folks have a warrant?"
Because you can't go in there unless
she invites you.
or you have a warrant.
Would you please leave?
We'll get the
warrant, Mrs. Moore
Or is it ... miss?
You know, they can't just barge intopeople's houses like that.
I do not understand. "I would never do anything to hurt Joey.
Does somebody have an in for you?
It's yours.
If you need anything, Just give a holler.
Thank you.
Oh God!
Come on!
Oh my baby!
I'm never going to let them take you away from me.
We leave tomorrow. Ok?
Are you still hungry?
"Can I help you?" I need to rent a trailer. "
Didn't you just return one of these? "Yes, couple of days ago."
Well you should have held on to it.
The weekly rate saves you tons of money.
"Can I help you mam?"
-No, thanks.
I'm just waiting for my sister.
Oh! Bad leg huh?
-Yard work! "Maybe you should get a gardener for that."
You take care now.
Joey!
You scared the hell out of me!
My mother didn't see you, did she?
No, I parked around the block.
I thought she gave you direct orders not to come over.
She did.
She thinks Ms. Moore is abusing her kid or something.
It she?
"No, Catherine wouldn't do that."
-How do you know that?
I just do..
You know you better watch it, something you almost sound like you have a heart.
-What wrong?
-The baby is crying.
Get out of the way!
Jesus Christ! You stupid bitch! You think I could stop this thing at an angle? I can't
Move!
*abuses angrily*
-So open it! "It's locked."
Joey?
Jesus! The kids a fucking freak!
It's a baby.
Come here, sweetheart.
Look at you!
You see? He just needs to be loved!
Joey killed them!
What are you talking about?
-He'll kill anyone who gets in his way.
-Where is he?
What have you done with my baby?
Your baby is a killer.
Do you remember what Joey did to your husband Catherine?
Or has he blocked that out?
They are able to do that you know?
He is controlling your thoughts.
That's why you can't see what he really is!
-He's using you. "He's a baby!"
He's not going to stop.
It only gets worse.
Everything is going to be alright.
She was babysitting.
Her name is Linda Holt.
18 months ago she gave birth to a premature baby.
The baby was a conceived in vitro
and was born deformed.
Her doctor was namedMyrellin.
I was a patient ofMyrellin.
As were the mothers
of the other victims.
Did she threaten you?
It's Joey that she's after.
I'm Sorry, I can't even think straight.
What about Joey?
Did the suspect mention Joey?
She didn't make any sense.She said...
that Joey was using me.
We think that she has a vendetta against normal healthy babies.
-And the teenagers? "Just the wrong place at the wrong time."
Did you see Mrs Holt take Joey?
Please help me get him back. "He is all I have."
Do you have a
photograph of the baby?
A photograph could just help us find him.
You don't have a photo of your own child?
There is something you need to understand about Joey
He is not a normal, healthy baby.
He's handicapped?
Ms Moore, I want you to rest assured that we will do everything we can
to get Joey back, Ok?
Right now why don't you try to get some rest?
We'll be back first thing in the morning to get a formal statement.
Can I help you?
I'm a personal friend of Ms. Moore. "I was wondering if I could talk to her for a minute?."
Yeah. Go ahead
-Thank you.
Catherine, are you ok?
Don't worry.
They will find him.
Do you think so?
I am so scared.
I'm Sorry.
It's ok
You wait right here.
Thank you.
Do you have any kids?
Yeah, I have one. Wonderful little boy.
I'm hoping he can come live with me sometime soon.
The custody balance must be tough, huh.
-Feeling better?
-Yes thank you.
Listen, I'm going to get going and get out of the way.
Let you have a little time...
If you need anything...anything at all
A BLT, a bowl of chicken soup...
a cup of sugar...
Just give me a call, okay?
Promise?
Thank you.
I was so worried!
Where were you?
You were hiding?
That ought to take care of things.
- She wanted a warrant...
'She's got one!'.
What do we have here?
Looks like sleeping beauty.
Ms. Moore?
-Sedatives. "Mother of the year".
She probably left the baby in the house all night!
"Let's go see what we find, shall we?." "We've seen it all."
- Why don't we split up? "You take the front room and the kitchen is mine."
Jesus! This house stinks. "She is feeding it meat."
Alright we need to find this kid
and we need to get him out of here now.
Let's try upstairs.
No safety gate.
"Surprised?"
-No I am not.
-Did you hear that? "It sounds like it's coming from downstairs."
In the closet.
"He's probably been hiding in the closet all night long." "Poor thing.
"Must be scared to death" "Wouldn't you be?"
-Can you see him?
-I don't see a thing.
Come here, come on. It's okay.
Don't be afraid .
-Come here sweetheart.
-Hello baby, come here.
Don't be afraid of the light.
"Come to Papa". "Come here, come.
It's alright.
It's time, Catherine.
Thank God. Help me.
It's there!
Quiet! Quiet!
Did you see something? What did you see?
The baby.
Lets go.
I'll take him some place safe.
You don't understand.
No place will be safe with him in it.
Now move.
How many morehave to die Cathrine?
You did try the formula!
I did too.
My baby girl screamed so much ...
my neighbors thoughtI was torturing her.
The only reason Joey hasn't killed you, is because he needs you.
He needs your breast milk to survive.
That's all he needs you for. "How can you say that?"
I've been there.
If you say something, I will kill you. "I don't want to, but I will."
Now go ahead, answer the door.
-Who is it? "Lieutenant Briggs".
Yes, Lieutenant?
Good Morning. We've come to get your statement.
Don't you remember?
We said we'd come back.
Yes! But I've said all I have to say.
Your statement may just provide us with some leads.
Leads that could help us find Joey.
Not now. I have to rest now.
We'll come back later, but today. I'd appreciate that lieutenant.
Good work Catherine.
I loved my little girl Katherine.
She was my little miracle.
I couldn't wait to have a baby
and hold her
and walk her through the park.
Just like all the other mothers.
But I could never be like all the other mothers.
Because my baby...
wasn't like all the other babies.
What? What was her name?
Grace.
What happened to her?
The first victim was a neighborhood child
...
who came up to play with her.
He drowned in the pool. "I thought it was an accident."
My husband was next.
I managed to escape.
He has to be stopped Catherine.
Call him.
Louder!
"Joey! Where are you?"
-Here.
Look at mommy!
There is your momma!
Who you are?
He is your special boy.
Yes he is.
It's it?
"You pretended to be my friend."
-I'm your friend.
What do you think those child welfare workers wanted to do?
What do you think Linda was going to do?
I protected you.
I watched over you! Over Joey!
Joey! Come on! Come to mommy!
Joey and I have a surprise for you.
Don't we?
Who's your papa! Yeah! Drink...!
Do you know what pisses me off?
Difference.
The world is literally falling apart, and people give a fuck about is...
cars, looks, how much money do they have ...
because they are all so materialistic.
Dr, Myrellin..
Care about the air..
about the water...about the soil...
care about the whole planet.
care about the fact that so many
indifferent people are born in that planet.
I worked withDr. Myrellin for 10 years.
Do you think I was going to let decades worth of dreams slip away?
What does all this have to do with Joey?
-Think! Catherine! Think!
People of average intelligence are not going to make the difference.
These children will make the difference.
Not some vicious morality binding them
These children are our only hope.
You must be proud Catherine.You should smile
because you are a part of it all.
Just too sad, but we don't need you anymore.
We do appreciate what you've done up until now
Just think of this...
as one of those sacrifices
that a mother makes for her child.
Give me back my baby.
Did you see how fast they turn on you?
That's why I am never getting married!
And I don't want you to get married.
Be good.
survival of the fittest time!
Come on, Catherine!
Don't make things difficult.
Good girl!
Are you in there?
Nice trick Joey!
Honey! Please let mommy inside. If you open the door ...
I'll take you to Toyland.
You can buy some new pieces pieces for your set.
I think you'll like them, alot!
Do you want mom to read a story?
That's a good boy!
Maybe it's not too late Joey!
Maybe mommy can help you change.
"Mommy knows you are afraid."
So that's how you lash out.
If you come out right now ...
We can work on this together.
Get back here!
God Damn it!
I know you are up here.
Joey get over here. Now!
Joey did you just say...
I'm going to get you.
Enough!
People People! Can you please stay back!
Hang on! Just a second!
Where is the baby?- Your baby is gone Mrs Moore.
Are you sure?