(SIREN WAILING)
FRANK: All right, fellows, now listen up. This is it.
Now, Wayne, I want you to look for a side door before you go in.
We may just get lucky.
All right, Ricky, you gotta be ready to move, boy.
I may have to come to you before I really want to.
Hojo, now Ricky will be there to cover you.
I'm expecting they'll be all over me like a cheap overcoat.
One of you guys should be open.
All right, we all know what it took to get here.
We know we're the best.
Now, we've gotta prove it.
Let's go.
(ALL EXCLAIM)
All right! Set!
Six, hold it! Two, three, four...
(ALL YELLING)
Good!
All right! Way to go, Frank!
Gotta run! Run, run! Whoo!
All right, come on! Yeah, yeah, yeah!
(SIGHS)
Yeah, yeah, yeah! Go for it!
(WHOOPING)
(WHISTLE BLOWING)
(ALL WHOOPING)
Hell of a good play. Thanks.
Did you throw it?
Hey, Pete, we need somebody to sell hot dogs
when we play the feds.
Hey, did you see that, Joe? Huh?
Did you see them big bastards? We foxed 'em.
(LAUGHING) I gotta tell you something.
You still got the moves out there, old man.
I've got the moves. I just don't have the legs anymore.
Yeah, you'd better check that bum knee out.
Listen, I'm gonna set up a med-psych exam for you sometime next week.
All right, set it up. I'll take it.
One more thing. You'd better give up... Yeah?
...this boy's game before it kills you.
One more game, Joe. Just one more against the feds.
Then I'll pack it in for this year.
Linda says, "Quit the booze."
You say, "Quit football." What's left?
Work? Yeah.
So, how's it going?
This one we been working on looks a lot bigger
than we thought it was.
Just about ready to pop, too, I think.
Well, let me know if I can help. Anything special you need?
Yeah, maybe you could keep the DEA off my back.
Give me some room to maneuver. Just for little while.
All right. God damn it, go for it. Okay.
MAN ON TV: Concern is raised by a study of how many U.S. soldiers have...
(SNORING)
The Surgeon General says battered women are...
Tough game, huh, Dad?
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, I'm getting too old to play football, sport.
You're not as old as Joe Montana.
(LAUGHING) That's true.
You were snoring, Dad. Real loud.
Have you ever known Daddy to do anything quietly?
Are you gonna stay in there all day?
Oh, I'd like to.
Oh.
There's some coffee there. I thought you could use some road tar.
Thank you. Pleasure.
All right, what do we got, guys?
All our ducks in a row, taken from the catbird seat.
Wayne, you are amazing. How'd you get these?
Nikon, F-three, 700 millimeter lens at two 285 feet.
All right, refresh my memory. Who is this guy anyway?
Anthony Reece. Six arrests. No convictions.
I remember Mr. Reece now.
Sure, he's gotta be guilty of something, this guy.
Now this tip came from Fast Eddie, right?
Frank, we been waiting on this a long time.
Eddie finally supplied the last piece of the puzzle.
He's usually pretty reliable.
All right, let's go visit Mr. Reece.
MAN: Fire up!
Look out! Freak.
Think you own the place?
This is Daly. Get me Torres.
DISPATCHER: Okay, Frank. Stand by.
Keep your eyes open.
Yes, Mr. Reece.
FRANK: Wayne.
Yeah.
Can you see what the hell's going on in there?
WAYNE: Checking it out.
Hello, Frank? Don't have a good point of view from here.
But this truck's unloading dope, I'm sure of it.
JOE: Frank? Yeah. Joe?
Joe, now is the time. We need back-up, fast.
What is it, Frank? Where are you?
The one I was telling you about.
We're downtown at the Alamo Meat Packing Company.
You can't jump on me like this.
I told you to keep me posted.
I'm keeping you informed. I just told you.
All right, I'll get the DEA on it as quick as I can.
Joe, Joe, Joe, listen to me. We've got to go.
We've gotta go right now.
They have got to be informed... Fuck the feds.
Just send me some black and whites. My hands are tied.
That's bullshit. I'll get back to you.
Joe?
Shit!
(SIGHS)
All right, listen up. Torres wants us to wait for the DEA.
Everybody just sit tight.
(MEN CHATTERING)
GUARD: Hey, what the hell is this? Come on.
Come on, get your wrinkled ass out of there.
Boy, is she ugly. Hey, what are you doing here, huh?
Getting a suntan, motherfucker.
(GRUNTING)
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
Hey, Frank, these guys are packing up.
What the hell?
Fuck the back-up. Let's go.
(GRUNTS)
Freeze, assholes!
Meat inspectors! Don't even fart.
(GRUNTING)
(GUN FIRING)
Halt!
Hi, girls.
(GRUNTING)
Oh, fuck this!
Let's move.
No!
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
(SIREN WAILING)
(CHATTERING)
Officer Daly, can you tell us what happened here tonight?
Yeah, it was the fucking weenie roast that got out of hand.
We had 'em, Joe. God damn it, we had 'em.
Had who, Frank?
You don't know and we don't know.
Oh, and why don't we know, huh?
We're waiting for fucking hours for the goddamn Feds
and their dog and pony show.
To hell with this DEA coordination bullshit.
I want to be left alone next time.
You were alone. You went in without a back-up, without a warrant,
without probable cause, no nothing.
I told you to run this thing by me first, now, didn't I?
I did run it by you. Oh, come on!
We couldn't wait any longer!
Listen, sir, sir, we tracked this thing from ground zero on up.
From the dope dealers, the collection guys, the crack houses.
Every time... Tell me something, Gross.
Was it worth a four-alarm fire?
This place went up like a goddamn H bomb.
Exactly! Why? Why did it come up like an H bomb?
No, no, why? JOE: Hey, guys.
It was probably a crack factory for Christ.
Look, it could be a major distribution center here.
Do you hear yourself?
Maybe? Maybe? What maybe?
Two suspects DOA? That's not a maybe.
That's a goddamn naked certain.
Listen to me. Look, we got a line on a real character named Reece.
R-E-E-C-E.
You know, up until a few years ago,
this guy was strictly small potatoes. A nickel bag hustler.
Now all of a sudden he's playing in the big leagues.
He is involved in this place up to his eyeballs.
Can you place this Reece on the site?
Evidence, Frank. What evidence do you have?
Look, we're not sure exactly how he fits in,
but take a look around. Does this look like small time?
An entire meat packing plant used as cover?
We're talking major drug money here.
Whoa! We're talking about what?
Drugs, money. Ashes!
Lab guys sifting these!
That's what we're talking about. Come on.
A gram of nothing couldn't survive here. Aw, fuck this!
Frank, listen.
Why don't you just lay off for a couple of days?
Come on, man, relax. Take it easy.
I think you need some rest.
I don't need no rest.
I need to nail this slime ball Reece.
I need some evidence, that's what I need.
Look, Frank, your medical report came back.
They say you're borderline.
But I'd say you're slipping over the edge. I mean it.
(SCOFFS)
Well, that's where we live.
We're cops, Joe. Remember?
(HELICOPTER WHIRRING)
Listen, you've done an outstanding job.
They wanted me to convey that to you personally.
NORRINGER: Well, everything is on schedule. The money's at hand.
We're ready to make the exchange.
Good, 'cause the overseas account's already been opened.
We're fully committed now.
All we need is the money.
It'll be wired within three days.
Fine. We'll get the contracts to you immediately.
(CHATTERING)
(INAUDIBLE)
Excuse me.
Well, listen, it was nice to talk to you.
You'll have to excuse me, all right?
What's this all about, fellas?
You can see I'm kind of busy out there now.
Oh, good to see you.
Christ, that's $22 million just gone?
Thanks very much for your support.
Thanks for coming. We appreciate it.
Don't you realize I've got to wire $18 million to an overseas...
Hello, Mary, how are you? It's nice to see you again.
MARY: Hi, good to see you. George.
Both of you, go on.
WAYNE: Well, Frank, there's no drugs.
This fragment's paper.
WOMAN: Paper money. Federal Reserve notes.
It's gotta be in the multi-millions.
Correct threads, ink, everything.
It had to be dirty.
It's a laundry. We put their laundry out of business.
God, I hope we stung them real good.
(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
(DANCE MUSIC PLAYING)
(CHUCKLING) That's the Mexican hat dance, darling.
What else are you supposed to do to this stupid music?
Maybe we should just sit it out until they do the twist or something.
Right, good idea.
Frank, you just can't dance sober.
Well, we can remedy that easily enough.
You want some garlic bread? Yeah.
Why are you asking... Hey, feed them well because
there's not going to be enough for everybody.
You should be getting your own...
Oh, my God, they got the whole tribe... You made it!
Yeah, hi. We couldn't find a sitter.
No excuses, Harriet.
I want them here. I want them to see who I do what I do with.
My Dad says you're ballsy.
(CHUCKLES)
Well, he's right. I am. So is he. I know.
Nice thing to teach him, Wayne.
A man's greatest asset.
What? All right, all right, Harriet, you're right.
Jimmy, come here. What?
Listen to your mother. Develop your brain.
(CHUCKLING) Jimmy is a smart kid, Harriet.
I wouldn't worry. Yeah, and he's ballsy, too.
She hasn't even started drinking the punch yet.
FRANK: Uh-uh, uh-uh. Look at this.
How's it going there, little mama, huh?
I'm just fine now, Frank.
The worst is over. Oh, that's what you think.
Hey! Hey! Whoa!
Hey, here comes twinkle toes now.
Hi, Rose. Hi, Linda.
How are you, Ricky?
Harriet, do you know Rose? No. Rose, hi.
This is Rose. Hi. How are you?
Anita, this is Rose, Ricky's friend. Hi.
Oh, Rose, Ricky is so great with kids.
My kids just love him. She's gonna make him watch 'em.
HARRIET: Well, say hello to my son. He's right over there.
Okay, hey, you wanna meet some kids?
Yeah, I guess.
(WOMEN LAUGHING)
FRANK: Dirty dog. WAYNE: Stay away from my daughter.
Hey, Frank, check out Torres over there with the brass.
(CHATTERING)
Time to go kiss the ring?
As long as that's the only thing I'll have to kiss.
(CHUCKLES)
More ice here, lime here.
Hello, Joe. Commander, how you doing?
Daly.
Mmm.
I bet Commander Orsini is not going to ask me to dance tonight, hmm?
BARTENDER: Drink, sir? I don't want anything.
Listen, Frank,
if you have a minute tomorrow, why don't you drop by the house?
I'd like to talk to you.
All right. What's up?
Manana. I don't want to talk business tonight, Frank.
Joe.
Come on, Joe. We go back a long way, you and me.
All right? Don't bullshit me.
Now, tell me what's going on.
All right.
You and your unit have been suspended.
Jesus Christ.
Temporary inactive, pending a hearing.
I'm really sorry. It's beyond my control. You're really sorry.
God damn it. Remember now, I warned you, didn't I?
They're gonna suspend us now?
Now, they're gonna suspend us? Just please.
We're a half a step behind Reece, this... Will you listen to me?
Look at it this way. It's a couple of days off.
Oh. No!
(SCOFFS) I'll look out for you. You can count on me.
This unit was formed because the job wasn't getting done, Joe.
Now, we are doing the goddamn job.
We are this close.
(DANCE MUSIC PLAYING)
RICKY: You know what it is?
It's just all PR bullshit because of the shoot-out, Frank.
That's all it is. Fuck 'em.
I'm sorry, ladies.
ANITA: No. I'd say "fuck" was just about right.
Well, guys, there is a bright side.
We can all finish digging the septic tank
down at the playground just like you promised.
Thanks a lot, Linda. Hey.
They suspend us and now you're gonna throw us in the shithouse!
(LAUGHING) Come on. Don't let it get to you.
Why don't we make a holiday out of this thing?
Yeah, shit, they gotta pay us anyway.
God damn it, we're the best.
I mean, why do they keep fucking with us?
Well, I don't know about the rest of you guys,
but me and Ricky are going swimming.
(ALL SHOUTING)
It's too cold.
(ALL CHATTERING)
I'm freezing my ass off!
Shit.
Never thought I'd be able to utilize all that
valuable army training that I got.
Digging latrines ain't dignified for a man of my education.
Hey, hey, hey, come on. Come on, you guys.
We're doing it for the kids, remember?
So they can do their little number without choking half to death.
I wonder what that asshole Reece is up to.
I'm not allowed to give a shit.
I'm suspended.
This temporary inactive duty sucks.
How did you make out, Eddie?
I got it all squared away for you, sir.
Hey, what's that dirt bag Fast Eddie doing here?
Hojo,
the trail will be cold if we wait until we're reinstated.
(LAUGHING)
All right!
Our friend Fast Eddie's gonna do his duty as a good citizen.
He's lined up this hooker named Haley.
She's gonna spend a weekend with Mr. Reece on his boat.
Well, where is this boat?
Hey, you guys aren't serious?
It's either that or dig out this tank for the rest of our fucking lives.
So, where is this boat?
FRANK: God damn it, where the hell is she?
He said she'd be here for lunch? She is lunch.
Shit, just when we find a hooker Reece likes, she stiffs him.
Shit. I'm gonna give Eddie a call.
(CLICKS)
I'm all out of film.
Got the exposure at five-six. Don't change it.
Just press that button.
(INAUDIBLE)
HOJO: Shit.
(CAMERA SNAPPING)
Christ. Out of film.
Well, maybe he's on the way. There's no answer there.
Some guy just made a hand-off to Reece.
Did you get his picture? Dude.
There she is. There she is.
HOJO: That's Haley? FRANK: That's her.
Outstanding toilet.
What did you say? Huh?
Never mind.
"Sorry I'm late, shit for brains.
"When's the coke coming in?"
RICKY: "Oh, don't worry about that, sweet meat.
"I was a little tied up myself."
(LAUGHING)
"I brought the baby oil and the rubber sheet.
"Who do you work for?"
"Well, I hope you brought some of those heavy duty chains, sweetheart."
"No." "Yes."
(LAUGHING) "You're into chains, too?" "Yes."
"Bless those computer matchmakers.
"Who the fuck is your boss?"
"You like my car, honey?"
"Oh, my God, what is that bulge in your pants?"
"Well, baby, that is the boss.
"And he's looking forward to rocking your little box all weekend."
"You old smoothie."
(LAUGHING)
(CAMERA SNAPPING)
Good luck, sweetheart. It's up to you now.
(PHONE BEEPING)
(POP MUSIC PLAYING ON CAR RADIO)
Yeah. I've just met Travers.
He gave me the contracts.
NORRINGER: Good. Are they in order?
Well, he assured me they were official.
Stamped and signed. I'll get them to you by special messenger.
That's excellent, Reece.
By the way, your stock's just gone up again.
Now, we've gotta make up lost ground.
There isn't much time, but we can do it.
You bet. Bye-bye.
(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
Man, this place stinks.
Listen, fellows, we gotta finish digging that hole.
We promised the Friends of the Park.
This park has no friends.
I almost forgot.
Gentlemen, our lottery ticket came through.
How much? One hundred split four ways.
All right! Yeah!
How about that?
ALL: LAPD! LAPD!
LAPD! LAPD!
LAPD!
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
Come on, Ricky!
Oh!
(PEOPLE CHEERING)
Come on, LAPD!
Come on! Kill him!
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
Oh, fuck it.
Hey, pal, watch your language.
The wives and the kids.
ALL: LAPD! LAPD! LAPD!
Frank. What?
You know who that quarterback is?
No.
That's the guy who met Reece at the restaurant.
(INAUDIBLE)
Are you sure? Dead on, positive.
Shit. All right.
Let's find out what these federal faggots are made out of.
Red Dog return right.
Hojo,
why don't you see that Flash Gordon there gets the keys to the city.
Ready? Break. Yeah!
(GROANS)
(GRUNTS)
(CROWD CHEERING)
(GRUNTING)
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
(CHEERING)
You out of your fucking mind?
Let's watch the language, pal. The wives and kids.
You son of a... Break it up now. Come on. Get out of here.
Nice block, homes.
Aw! Hey!
Hey, Braden.
I see you got a ringer playing quarterback.
Yeah. Yeah, he's new. Spotted him, huh?
Yeah, I spotted him, you son of a bitch.
Who is he? His name's Travers.
Some kind of undercover agent out of D.C.
Heavy connections.
Rumor has it, he started for West Point when he was there.
WAYNE: Hey, Frank.
Yeah, I'm coming.
(PHONE RINGING)
Hello. FAST EDDIE: Lieutenant Frank.
Mmm-hmm.
It's one of your mouth breathers.
(SIGHS)
Yeah. Lieutenant Frank, Fast Eddie here.
Yeah, Eddie, what?
Yeah, sorry for the wake-up call, Chief,
but we got a serious situation on our hands here.
Eddie, Eddie, give me a break, will you?
I have a very low shit tolerance right now.
I just watched David Letterman.
Look, this guy Reece turned out to be a psychopath, Lieutenant.
Haley got pretty beat up.
She's with me now at the Deville Motel on Ingraham.
She got the names, if you got the cash.
All right?
Wait a minute, Eddie. Wait. What names? Eddie?
I gotta go.
Oh, Frank.
(SIGHING) Why doesn't filth ever sleep?
FRANK: That's a nasty thing to say.
Besides, we're not supposed to think of them as filth anymore.
Personally, I think of them as children.
Disadvantaged children, who've been lied to.
Sure you do.
Yeah. Listen, I got to borrow some of the Christmas money.
Bye.
(KNOCKING) Eddie, honey, hurry up.
When we get you back to the country,
you are going to get so new...
You'll heal up like a flower.
FAST EDDIE: Okay, Eddie. Get ready. Cold water, shock treatment.
(IN SINGSONG VOICE) Okay, cold water, wake me up.
Slap me in the face.
Oh! It's too fucking cold.
(SCREAMS)
Eddie?
RICKY: We got worse hours on suspension than we had on duty.
Wayne, see if you can find out what room he's in.
FRANK: Hojo, Hojo, wait! Hojo, wait!
Wayne, cover him.
(TICKING)
(GRUNTS)
(SOFTLY) Hojo.
Hojo!
Hey! FRANK: Hey!
You all right?
Where's Hojo, Frank?
I'm sorry.
What do you mean?
I'm...
I'm really sorry.
Oh, Frank.
(CRYING)
I don't want him to be dead.
I don't want him to be dead, Frank.
I don't want him to be...
(SOBBING)
It's out of my hands, Frank.
There's gonna be an Internal Affairs hearing.
Three people killed, including a cop on suspension.
(GUN FIRING)
Do you know how close we are here, Joe?
Do you even give a damn?
I give a damn.
They killed Eddie and the girl because we're right on their ass.
They could have been killed by anyone, Frank.
No. No, she had a name for me.
I'll tell you something else.
There's a federal agent involved.
How the hell do you know this?
I know. I know.
Pieces of a puzzle, Joe. Pieces of a puzzle.
They're all coming together.
All I need is two weeks. One week even.
Look, it's out of my hands. It's not my decision anymore.
You're getting blamed for Hojo's death.
You missed one.
I don't kill cops.
(INAUDIBLE)
ORSINI: Before the formal hearing begins, Lieutenant Daly,
let me fill you in on the procedure.
You have been charged with violating your inactive status
resulting in the fatality of Officer Howard Jones.
The med-psych report notes
obsessive, stress-related behavior.
Now departmental regulations state...
Let me make it easy on you, Commander.
Frank, you'll have a chance to respond at the proper time.
I resign.
We might as well save ourselves a lot of bullshit here.
I quit.
It's really what you want, isn't it?
They're burying us in their shit out there.
And when you finally get rid of all the cops like me
who's gonna stop them?
You?
TRAVERS: The policeman has resigned.
And they've disbanded his unit,
so your position is safe.
Good. That's good.
By the way, I've been ordered back to Washington.
So, I'll say goodbye.
Well, thank you.
We appreciate everything you've done for us.
Thanks again.
That was Travers on the phone.
He took care of that little problem we were having.
CALVERT: Now, where are we on the money?
There's been a little trouble with one of our sources of finance.
You see, there was a fire...
Norringer, I don't wanna know anything
about your sources or your problems.
You know that.
I trust you to work these things out.
Look, it just means a short delay before I can wire the money
into the overseas account. Well, how long?
A week. Ten days.
That's too late.
Our friends are in an emergency situation, for God's sake.
We need all the money within 48 hours.
The exchange must go ahead as planned.
And all cash.
That's very dangerous.
That's the way it has to be.
Yo, boss.
So, what's it feel like being a civilian?
Boring.
(CHUCKLING) All right.
Everything's back to normal. Frank's drinking again.
Come on. Let's all get loaded.
So, where did they stick you guys?
I'm back where I started.
The Crash Unit.
Gang Intelligence?
That's a contradiction in terms if I've ever heard one.
What about you, Wayne?
They shoved me back to Technical Development Wing.
An office pogue again, huh?
Well, I bet Harriet's a lot happier about that.
Look, Frank, I just want you to know
I told 'em how I felt about
the bullshit they put you through.
Oh, yeah? Like they give a shit, right?
Fuck 'em.
Take their money, do your time,
play with your kids, retire to Arizona.
No.
I quit this morning.
What about your pension?
You got a family. You got a spotless record.
Well, I quit with a spotless record.
Looks good on a resume.
Frank, you know me. I always follow good orders,
good or bad, but this was bullshit.
Fuck their pension.
(CHUCKLING) All I got to do is tell Harriet.
Shit!
Well, I ain't quitting.
FRANK: Ricky, relax. Nobody's asking you to quit.
Hey, listen, I want Hojo's killer just like you guys want him, all right?
But what do I...
I can't do nothing about it cleaning swimming pools
or some bullshit like that.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
Haven't you been able to figure this shit out yet?
What do you think? The department is gonna go after Hojo's killer?
Wayne, don't give me this paranoid bullshit. What do you think?
This is not paranoia.
They wanted us off the case, well, they got us off the case.
What the hell do you think that FBI guy was doing at Frank's hearing?
Look, man, we're on our own on this one.
Frank,
I know you got a raw deal, got screwed.
But I...
I can't quit the force, man.
You know what it means to me. I can't do it.
What am I supposed to do?
Go back to the barrio and hang out with the homeboys?
Homeboy, my ass.
Ricky, the only spic thing about you is your name.
If you could find your old man, I bet he'd turn out to be Irish.
You son of a bitch! Hey! Hey! Hey!
What the fuck is the matter with you? Get over there!
Knock it off, Wayne! You sit down and you shut the fuck up.
Ricky, you keep your badge. You earned it.
This is my problem anyway.
Frank, you ain't street legal no more.
You can't do this on your own.
No, Wayne's right about that, Ricky.
We can only do this on our own.
Okay. Here's what we do.
I stay on the force and help you from the inside.
No, that's a bad idea, Ricky. It's bad for both of us.
We gotta break off all contact with the department.
Look, any kind of a leak would be fatal for us.
Besides, what happens to you if they ask you about us?
You'd have to perjure yourself.
But, no, you need informants to keep you posted.
Look, don't worry about it. We'll find him.
Just don't go telling the cops on us.
Wayne.
You know, sometimes you can be a real asshole.
Sorry.
Go on home. It's okay.
Frank, listen, I...
Look, it's okay. I understand. You're right.
I'll call you later. Okay?
Go on.
You shouldn't have called his old lady a spic.
I didn't call his old lady a spic.
I called his old man a mick.
(CHUCKLES)
I can't believe he's keeping the job.
Well, you see, that's exactly the point, Wayne.
To you, it's a job. To him, it's his whole life.
Fuck it. I quit, too.
How the hell did you get that door open?
(CHUCKLING) Been stuck for 10 years, for Christ's sake.
Well...
We better get drunk before we change our minds.
Hot dogs are ready, guys.
The burgers are gonna have to wait.
Who fixed the garage door? I did.
We're gonna need weapons.
We're going to need equipment.
We're gonna need money.
(CHUCKLES)
What?
What's up? Nothing's up, man.
(RAP MUSIC PLAYING ON CAR RADIO)
How is this shit, man?
Man, the shit's good. Come on, cold snap.
Got it all here.
And close that door behind you.
Holy shit!
Oh, shit!
Sanitation department!
Where's the garbage?
Keep that money down, God damn it.
What's it look like, anyway?
Come on, Wayne, what does it add up to?
Wait, wait. I lost count.
Roughly $29,000.
(WHOOPS) Christ.
Man, if we did this every day, you know where we'd be?
Yeah, we'd be dead. Soon, and don't you forget it.
All right, Skip, I can get us everything we need.
It can't be traceable. Remember that, Wayne.
Where you gonna go?
Remember the fence we busted about three years ago? Big Harry?
Wow! He's out.
Is he back in business?
Yeah, he is, and his prices are insane.
(LAUGHING)
Well, you always think you know everything that's going on.
What do you think you know now?
I know you turned in your badge,
which means you shouldn't be packing that.
Nah. It's just habit.
Bullshit.
You resigned, Frank.
You're no longer a cop.
You're gonna go out and break the law now?
After 24 years, turn into a vigilante,
and solve everything on your own?
You're right.
Everything you say is true.
It's not fair.
(SIGHING) I'm not being fair.
Maybe I shouldn't even be doing it,
but I can't stop now.
You understand?
(SIGHS)
Linda?
I'm asking you to go along with me on this.
Please.
Damn you.
Be careful.
(DOOR CLOSES)
I couldn't make it in there even with a tie.
You couldn't make it in there with a diamond tiara.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
Tell Rose I said hello. Later.
Hope that's a collect call.
Where's Gross?
He's over there watching Reece's Porsche.
What are you watching?
I'm watching him watch the Porsche.
You both might as well pack it in for the night.
I'll put Mr. Reece to bed.
Oh, he's not going to bed. He's all dressed up.
Hey, Frank, you finally made it. Yeah.
Come on, let's go. He's moving.
(CAR ENGINE SPUTTERING)
Come on, come on. Come on, let's go.
Man, I just gave her a lube job last week.
Don't do that. You're gonna flood it.
All right, forget it. We'll take my piece of shit.
Shit, I forgot the phone.
Got it! Let's go.
What the hell is he doing?
I hate guys who walk in L.A.
They ought to be arrested.
They usually are.
Wait a minute. Where'd he go?
Where'd he go? Son of a bitch.
RICKY: In that cab. Right here. Right here.
Come on, Frank, we're gonna lose him!
All right, all right. Hold on.
Frank, take it easy, man. Take it easy.
We ain't even street legal. All right, all right.
Shit, I'm getting soaked.
Hey, never mind that, Wayne, cover up the telephone.
That thing's worth more than this truck.
Look at this, for Christ's sake.
You can't get a cab in L.A.,
now we got two of them exactly the same.
God damn it! Shit!
All right, which one is it?
Come on! Try the one on the left. The one on the left.
I'm feeling lucky.
You better be right.
(DEMONSTRATORS CHANTING)
FRANK: There he is.
Rodriguez, you're one lucky bastard.
Hey, who you calling lucky?
All right, fellows, we're the action news team in business again.
Film at 11:00.
I'll be Sam Donaldson.
MAN: Please have press passes visible. Thank you.
How you doing? Nice to see you again.
Excuse me, I need to see some passes.
No, that's all right. He's with me.
Well, that's okay. I still need to see passes.
Well, we got passes. Show him the passes.
Hold on. I got it. He probably left them in the truck again.
I got it. I got it. I got it.
Check your pockets.
Here we go. Here. Ah! See.
Yeah. Yeah. Here we go.
Okay, thank you. All right?
Thank you. Nice to see you again.
Don't even ask.
Yeah, I am Kathleen Karr of Channel Three News.
We must have just misplaced our passes.
Uh-huh, well, I'm sorry, but I still need to see them.
I understand that. We had our passes about three minutes ago.
NORRINGER: If I might remind you, ladies and gentlemen,
it wasn't so long ago
that out of sheer political desperation
a disorganized, undisciplined...
FRANK: I don't see him ...under-equipped...
Ah, he must have shitty seats. ...sometimes starving
handful of guerrillas...
Oh, there he is. Right over there. Behind the column.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
...of the most powerful nation in the world.
What the hell is he doing here anyway? What is this, some...
Excuse me, can I borrow that for a second?
To the astonishment of the world,
"Central American Relief Fund"?
The freedom fighters prevailed.
And the United States of America was born.
With that bloody birth, the torch of freedom was lit for all nations.
And it is our sacred duty to help the freedom fighters
of Central and South America
in every way we can.
Including, if necessary, by force of arms.
(AUDIENCE APPLAUDING)
At the present time, the freedom fighters can defend themselves
if they have the weapons to do so.
We have those weapons, ladies and gentlemen.
And we must supply them
to our friends freely and now.
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
(INAUDIBLE)
(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
WAYNE: Reece! Where'd Reece go?
Shit.
Back here. Follow me.
(HELICOPTER WHIRRING)
Come on!
Zoom in real tight.
The light sucks. I got it opened all the way.
I don't know if I can get it.
FRANK: Just get their goddamn faces.
Shit. What?
Ran out. Oh, for Christ's sake.
All right, let's get out of here.
What about Reece?
The hell with Reece. We can pick him up anytime we need him.
I wanna see what we got in here. Come on.
I had a whole new career going before I ran out.
Hope we got it, Frank.
Look at this. Look at this.
Watch this.
Freeze.
Norringer. R.I.?
No, no, J. Very clear.
All right. R.J. Norringer.
Big shot? I don't know. We'll check him out.
Fast forward to the roof.
Now look at that. That's my favorite shot.
Pretty shaky.
Well, no, if I had the time and a tripod,
I could've done it. No, Wayne, if you'd had a microphone
we'd know what the hell they were saying. Shit!
You ran out of tape.
Well, we don't need a microphone.
We could have used more tape.
We don't need a microphone.
It's a raid!
The Garrity gang. Shoot to kill.
Well, Frank, we all heard about Hojo.
Are you gonna get the bastard who did it?
We're trying to. Is Tommy around?
Been in his room for days.
Want me to tell him you're here?
No, Myrna, we'll kick the door in.
And no Black Velvet, either.
He pees in the hall.
(KNOCK AT DOOR)
Ain't nobody getting in this door without a warrant.
FRANK: Tommy Grogan?
We got a warrant that says you're out of Black Velvet.
Hey, Frankie, boy. Come on in.
Come on in. How are you? How you doing, Wayne?
Hey, Tom. How you doing, Ricky, boy?
FRANK: Yeah, we checked. We didn't have any tails.
Hey, good thing you brought this, man.
I was just about ready to knock over a 7-Eleven.
(ALL CHUCKLING)
Let me close this door. There's a stink in here.
What the hell is all that shit about?
Tommy, we got a tape we want you to look at.
(CHUCKLING) I hope it's a porno.
Hey, Frank, did I tell you about a guy
who took a service revolver, put it to his head
and was gonna blow his brains out.
And his wife walks in and sees this and starts laughing.
He says, "What the hell are you laughing at?
"You're next."
(ALL LAUGHING)
An Irish cop, right?
Yeah, most likely.
Listen, Tommy, we need your help.
We're trying to find Hojo's killers.
Hey, Frank, I'm sorry about that.
Yeah. I liked that big boy cop.
I ought to come out of fucking retirement.
That's what I should do. All right, you're out of retirement.
Do me a favor.
Put some voices in the mouths of these assholes, huh?
Hey, run that by me by me again there, huh?
Wait a minute. Let me get these Ben Franklins on.
Don't worry about the stuff on the dais, okay?
It's the two guys on the roof.
"The ship's at sea." Missed it.
Run it back again. One more time.
Run it back.
"The ship's at sea, Mr. Norringer.
"We should be docking at San Pedro tomorrow night."
"It's essential that the turnaround be fast.
"The money must leave with that shipment,
"or the whole deal is jeopardized."
"Don't worry, it will be leaving Pier..."
Son of a bitch, I missed the goddamn pier.
Pier, pier, pier.
It's, um...
You know, it's a "T" sound, a "T" sound.
Twelve? Two, twelve, some multiple of.
That's great. Tommy, that's great.
That's swell, thanks a lot. I'll be a son of a bitch.
Shit on a stoop. Who the fuck is that guy Norringer?
Did I blow it on a big one here?
No, no. Look, Tommy, we're still digging. You were a big help.
We appreciate it.
Did they kill Hojo?
It looks that way, Tommy.
Hey, where you going? Where you going?
You guys keep me in good spirits.
(CHUCKLING) As a matter of fact, we owe you a case of spirits, Tommy.
Thanks for everything.
I'm holding you to it, Frank. Okay.
Tommy, don't drink all that tonight.
Don't worry about it. Hey, put your safety belt on driving there, huh?
Ah, that's it there.
FRANK: Get this. Norringer is a graduate
of the United States Naval Academy.
He's an ex-rear admiral, believe it or not.
The printout tells quite a story.
He was on the staff of the Office of Naval Intelligence.
And he worked for the NSC as a specialist in the Mideast.
Resigned three years ago to enter the private sector.
Entered the private sector to make a fucking fortune.
Yep.
This guy's no lightweight.
Shit.
FRANK: Now part of this shipyard just happens to be leased
to R.J. Norringer and Associates.
What do we got so far?
Norringer's gotta be the man.
Say he's using this shipyard to import drugs, right?
The coke, the heroin comes in,
the money goes out. Right.
Sometime in the next 24 hours
there may be a shipment or two.
Right. So...
So, what do we do next?
What's this?
Jesus Christ.
What's wrong with this picture?
Jesus.
WAYNE: Army? National Guard, maybe?
Holy shit.
(CAMERA SNAPPING)
I'd sure like to get a look inside that warehouse.
First we gotta get inside this yard.
Let me think about it for a minute.
Wait a minute, Frank.
Look, I don't want you to take this the wrong way, okay?
But we're not on the force anymore.
Yeah. So?
So, we're volunteers just like you, Frank.
So, what does that mean? Nothing, I mean,
we'd follow you anywhere. That's not the point...
What he's trying to say is that together, right?
The three of us should decide what we're going to do.
Together. Right.
You mean like we should have like a committee.
No, a democracy.
So, we take a vote. Yeah.
Sure, of course. Why not? All right,
you guys propose something and then we'll vote on it.
All right. So, go ahead. Propose something.
Me? Yeah.
Why not you? Go ahead.
All right, I propose that you draw the plan of attack
so that we can follow it.
Yeah, I second it.
We'll make it unanimous. It's so ordered.
Are we finished with this bullshit now?
Yeah. Good. Let's get out of here.
You think it's an excuse for an old fuck like me
to get you up here for more Black Velvet?
But I'm worried for Frank and the boys.
JOE: So am I, Tommy.
What was on the tape?
Two guys talking about bringing in some shipment.
One was a big shot.
Norsinger or Noringer.
Norringer? That's him. You know him?
Oh, yeah, yeah.
I think I've heard of him.
We'll check him out, Tommy.
Thanks a lot.
And don't worry about our buddies.
You and I, we'll keep them out of trouble, right?
Hey, Captain, how about a little touch before you go?
No, not now. I'm on duty.
Hey, thanks for coming by.
Take care of yourself now.
Thank you.
(SIGHS)
(GRUNTS)
WAYNE: Geez, all those containers have false tops.
I don't believe what I'm seeing.
RICKY: Man, there's enough coke in there to build a ski slope.
Oh, can you say, "Motherfucker"?
So, think we should call for back-up or what?
All top-of-the-line shit, too.
Top of the State Department's restricted list.
The drugs come in, the weapons go out.
Norringer gets rich in the middle.
Look at that.
Hey. We got Norringer right by the balls.
Yeah, there are bigger balls involved in this than Norringer's.
You don't pick up weapons like these at the local Kmart.
MAN: Hey, what are you guys doing?
Shit! Duck!
(GUN FIRING)
God damn it, hang on.
Hey, watch it!
Come on! Go!
Move!
All right, how do I get out of this place?
Go up there and turn right at the end of the building.
Shit. Trouble, trouble!
Stand on it. Hold on.
(GUNS FIRING)
Which way? Which way?
We gotta get to Humboldt Street. Where's the van?
It's on Humboldt Street. Take a left up here.
FRANK: Okay, turn here.
We're looking for a dead-end street.
All right, Humboldt Street. This is it.
All right, there's the van. It's on the other side of the bridge.
Rodriguez, wait a minute. We're not gonna make it.
We're not gonna make it.
We'll make it. Stop! Stop!
(BRAKES SCREECHING)
Oh, my God!
FRANK: Jesus. We got their laundry money.
It was going to Panama.
Well, now it's staying here.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah, it's gonna pay my fucking mortgage.
Come on. We gotta get the hell out of here.
Wayne, get the van.
Let's pack it up.
Christ, it's all hundreds.
It's all used hundreds.
We don't have to turn this in. This is untraceable, right?
Who would we turn it in to?
We're the only good guys.
That's right, Frank. Who we gonna turn it in to?
It's ours. It's ours.
Come on. Let's go.
(POP MUSIC PLAYING ON CAR RADIO)
RICKY: Just get on the freeway, man.
And ride, mama, ride. Look at this, man.
We got millions of dollars. We got millions...
We can break their asses with this one.
We can wipe 'em out.
Okay, now it's all agreed. We're keeping this.
We don't give it back.
We'll cut in Anita, too, all right?
Absolutely we cut Anita in. Yes.
Listen to this asshole. We've got more money than he's got.
(ALL LAUGHING) Whoo! Yes!
Frank, where are we going?
Just keep driving until we figure out
what the hell we're gonna do with it.
We're keeping it, Frank.
For every poor, honest, flatfoot son of a bitch.
For Hojo.
I could get one of those motor sailors I've been dreaming about.
Oh, Jesus. I could get two of them.
Shit. What? What's the matter?
Highway Patrol.
Oh, a code 86.
All right, take it easy.
Kill the fucker. We ain't stopping for nothing.
Kill him. What do I do, Frank?
Take it easy. Relax.
That was too close.
From cops to cop killers.
Jesus Christ. Listen to us.
Look, look, let's get a case of beer and figure this shit out.
Yeah, that's just what we need.
Some sober thinking.
I thought you were gonna get a case.
I only had three bucks and he couldn't change 100.
Why didn't you give him the 100?
A hundred bucks for a case of beer?
Where's mine?
(CHUCKLES)
He's got it.
All right, gentlemen,
now that we're a democracy,
what do we do next?
Well, we ain't gonna get loaded on two beers,
so why don't we just go hide this shit?
Wait a minute.
Where we gonna hide it?
I know just the place.
FRANK: Five point one.
WAYNE: All right, man, what do you got?
RICKY: Five and a half and six.
That's five, six, 17 plus five is...
FRANK: So, well, what is it? What is it?
Uh...
Twenty-two and a half million, give or take a couple hundred thousand.
(CHUCKLES) Okay.
But it's definitely real, right? This is real money.
It's real. It's definitely real.
Yeah!
Come on. Let's put it away.
Twenty two and a half million dollars and we're sitting in a shithouse.
Who wants to take the point?
What?
You're our leader, Frank.
Kill the light and fuck you guys.
WAYNE: Oh, I'm gonna be sick.
You're gonna be sick?
I'm standing in this crap up to my hips,
and you're gonna be sick, right? Tie that off.
Oh.
Geez, I think I'm gonna be sick.
For Christ's sake, get me the other bag!
Let's get the hell out of here!
God damn... Here, Frank.
You didn't put rocks in this one, you dumb son of a bitch.
Oh, shit. Here, get it down there.
Jesus.
FRANK: So, we just sit tight and wait.
Scope the situation out.
Maybe they don't even know it was us.
One thing's for sure, we don't spend a dollar of that money.
Jesus. Fuck!
It's Tommy Grogan.
They know it's us.
(CLICKING)
(GASPS)
(BABY CRYING)
Mommy, what is it?
Justin, get out of here. Go stay with the baby.
(BABY WAILING)
It's all right, darling. Mommy's here.
Justin, would you go run down the street and get some help?
LINDA: All right, dear. I've got you, honey. Be careful. Be careful.
With your sister.
(BANGING)
Go away!
(BRAKES SCREECHING)
Justin!
What happened? Mommy, Mommy. They're after Mommy.
Wayne, take care of them.
(PANTING)
(DOOR RATTLING)
(SCREAMS)
Oh, Frank. Oh, Frank.
(SHUSHING) Oh, God.
It's all right. It's all right now. Oh, thank God.
The kids, the kids! The kids are fine. The kids are all right.
They're outside. Yeah. Is she okay?
(CRYING) Wayne, it's okay.
Mommy.
Go home and pack up Anita and the kids, get Rose.
Take whatever you'll need.
We've got to find a safe place.
(CHATTERING)
FRANK: Bring the kids in first.
LINDA: Justin, come on. Grab the pack if you can.
(BANGING AT DOOR)
Let's get the kids settled. I'll get the gear out of the cars.
All right.
Come on. Let's look over here.
HARRIET: Twenty-two million? LINDA: No wonder they're trying to kill us.
So, you told them.
Yeah, they told us.
So? I think we should keep it.
(SCOFFS) You're goddamn right, we should keep it.
Well, I say we head for the border.
I mean, with $22 million,
we could buy our own country.
What are you saying?
Hey, this is the money that killed Howard.
Anita, Hojo wouldn't care.
He would, too. He was a good cop, Ricky.
Look, whatever we decide,
it's gonna have to be unanimous.
Now, if we vote to turn it in...
Wait, wait, Frank, I mean, give it back to who? Norringer?
Can't we turn it in to the Feds?
No. Norringer is the Feds.
So, you're saying the money's untraceable,
and the authorities don't even know it exists.
Right. The bad guys know.
We would know.
We would spend the rest of our lives in hiding.
I don't wanna spend my life like a common criminal.
Well, you won't be common, dear.
WAYNE: Anita, please, for Christ's sake, would you lighten up?
I mean, this is the only chance any one of us will ever have to be rich.
Think about it. This is your pension.
I think we should do it.
Yeah. I say we do it.
Look, it's been a long, tough day.
(SIGHS)
Why don't we sleep on it?
Baby, you awake? Mmm-hmm.
What are you thinking about?
I'm thinking about Anita.
Yeah, me, too.
The money.
That money killed Tommy.
And Hojo.
We should all piss on that money.
MAN ON TV: A well-armed patrol has attacked the small town of Las Citas,
near the Guatemalan border...
Sandanistan government forces have held out against the
freedom fighters for several hours... MYRNA: Hello there.
But fierce fighting still persists in the area and casualties are...
I'm out.
Anything you can remember about this guy is important.
Garrity.
So, they killed Tommy.
Why would any bastard want to kill him?
I don't know, Garrity. I was just asking Myrna here.
What can you tell me about this guy that Tommy left with?
Some guy I never saw before.
Tommy was pretty drunk. Yeah.
Shitfaced he was.
Captain Torres bought him a bottle.
Wait a minute. Torres was here?
Yeah. Just before he left with the guy.
Frank?
Joe Torres.
Torres.
Did you kill Tommy?
You didn't kill Tommy, did you, Joe?
As good as, Frank.
I let someone else do it.
(SIGHS)
How much money did they pay you to kill Tommy Grogan?
Enough, Frank. Oh, I took money, all right.
Why not?
What difference does it make?
Who cares anymore? The war is over, Frank. We lost.
Oh, I see. We lie down and we just pretend we're dead, is that it?
We just bend over for these scumbags.
Is that it? Don't you get it?
Why don't you read the newspapers, Frank?
They're running the goddamn world now.
Hell, they may even do some good.
What the fuck are you talking about?
You know that when Castro took over Cuba,
they killed my father and his two brothers.
One was a priest.
I watched it.
You didn't know that, did you, Frank?
Know how I watched it?
It was on television, man.
Those Communists have got to be stopped, no matter what.
Oh, no matter what? Yes!
No matter what, huh? No matter how.
Fuck the law, is that it, Joe?
Kill a pimp, kill a hooker, kill a cop.
For Christ's sake, what difference does it make?
And if you can make a couple of bucks on the side, well, why not?
Who gives a shit anyway? Right?
It's all for a good cause.
Well, let me ask you something, Joe.
What makes you think you're any goddamn better than Castro? Huh?
Why don't you give the money back?
I promise you
that I'll call them off your family.
I can't do shit for you, but I'll do my best.
Norringer can have that money. He can have it tonight.
Oh, he's not gonna come. Norringer comes.
He comes, or no deal. No money.
Now you look at me, Joe. You know me very well.
I got nothing to lose.
I will burn that goddamn money.
Where?
Canyon Park. Midnight.
Yeah, we're building a playground for the kids. You remember the kids, Joe?
The kids you and your crack-peddling friends have helped to fuck up.
I'll try to get him there, Frank.
Midnight. Frank...
I'm really sorry.
(SCOFFS) Fuck you.
(SIGHS)
Why the hell should we give that money back anyway, Frank?
We put our asses on the line every day for the department,
and the department pays us dick.
That's right, and in the end,
the pension they hand us ain't worth shit.
It'd keep my family on popcorn if I ever got clipped.
Wait a minute, what am I talking about? I don't have a pension.
God damn it, why do I keep sounding like a cop?
Because you are a cop.
For years, I've been listening to you guys
talk about those assholes out there.
Those lowlifes, those scumbags.
Well, if we take this money, this lousy drug money,
we're no better than they are.
Well?
Are we gonna vote or anything?
I guess not.
Okay.
Well, if this is the right thing to do, how come I feel so shitty?
JOE: They're off the force. They're no further threat to you.
Look, why don't you let me handle it?
Daly's my friend. I can deal with him, the son of a bitch.
I mean, he knows he fucked up when he took the money.
I want all the money back
or you're dead in the water.
I don't care about them.
You have to be there, or it's a no go.
Midnight.
Sounds like a trap.
It could be.
Jesus Christ.
How does it look?
What did you say? I said, how does it look?
Ricky, how does he look?
(CHUCKLING)
What is this, trick or treat?
No. Seriously. You know the old vests I had,
I took them, I rigged these up.
One for each of us.
Total body armor by Gross.
(CHUCKLING) No. Forget it, man. I ain't wearing this shit.
No, hear me out, man.
It's gonna be Kevlar from the top of our heads to our toes.
Takes a licking, but keeps on ticking.
Frank?
Try it on.
(CHUCKLING) Come here. I want to show you this.
I thought instead of the walkie-talkies, we'd use this.
FRANK: Yeah? You know, this way, we'll be able to
keep our hands free for other purposes. Good thinking, Wayne.
RICKY: Gross, you're something else, man.
Yeah, well it's about time you admitted it.
WAYNE: Good luck.
Wayne? Are you ready?
No, but let's do it anyway.
Ricky?
You bet your ass I'm ready, Frank.
Listen, fellows...
Thanks.
Good luck.
Take care of yourselves.
Good luck, Frank.
Here we go.
Okay, Frank, where's the money?
Where's Norringer?
Come on, Frank, what's the point?
You people don't get shit from me until I see the man.
Look, Frank...
Okay, asshole, you'll meet the man.
Check him out.
He's clean.
REECE: We're clear.
(HELICOPTER WHIRRING)
Well, well... Last of the rebels.
Where's the money?
You tried to hurt my family.
I don't give a shit about you, your family,
or your whole sordid little world.
You're interfering in interests you don't understand, mister.
If you were a patriot... Oh, don't give me that patriot shit!
Every time you assholes fuck around with the Constitution,
you call it patriotism.
As far as I'm concerned, you're just another
lowlife, drug-peddling piece of trash.
But you just made a fatal fucking mistake.
Rodriguez, that's the signal.
(GRUNTS) Hold on, hold on, hold on. Can't clear the rotors.
Get a shot, man. You gotta get a shot.
We gotta go. Let's go.
Can't clear the rotors. Hold on, Wayne.
Tell me where the money is!
Shithouse.
What?
The cesspool.
Check it out, Reece.
Danny! Bobby!
(GRUNTING)
Come on, give me a knife.
(GAGGING) God.
(CHUCKLES)
Got it!
Kill him.
Move, Frank!
(GRUNTING)
(GASPS) Joe!
(GUN FIRING)
Frank!
REECE: Cover me! Cover me!
(GRUNTS)
Fuck you!
Reece, come on!
Yeah! Hurry up!
(GRUNTS)
Reece! Come on...
(GROANS)
Motherfuckers!
(GROANING)
Fuck!
Fuck.
(POLICE SIREN WAILING)
Move it, the cops are here!
Take it up. Take it up!
I can't see.
Braden, where the fuck did you come...
Stepped in the shit again, huh, Frank?
How the hell did you... Linda called us in.
We made it. Go!
The rotor. Shoot for the rotor.
Good shot! Good shot, God damn it!
Watch it, you're too low!
We've been hit.
We're gonna hit it!
(SCREAMING)
(SIRENS WAILING)
(CHATTERING)
For Christ's sake, Frank.
You should have kept it.
God damn it.
(MARCHING BAND PLAYING)
(PEOPLE APPLAUDING)
MAN ON TV: In Washington today, White House aide Lauren Calvert
made a statement on the R.J. Norringer arms scandal.
I want to make it perfectly clear that this administration
has never been involved, nor does it condone in any way
the illicit arms shipments.
While we sympathize with their cause,
we must condemn all those
who would violate the laws of the United States. All right, that's it.
That's good.
Personally, I am committed to continuing my efforts
on behalf of the freedom fighters in Central America,
and to keep raising money legally, from every possible source.
The flow of arms will never stop, so long as they are needed.
Giving unconditional support is, in my opinion,
the most fundamentally American thing we can do
to keep alive the spirit of freedom and truth.