Hi.
I'm Rushion McDonald.
My next guest represents the
new millennial entrepreneur,
spirit, determination,
and drive.
He's faced a number
of challenges,
had some huge setbacks, but
that has not stopped him
from being successful today.
Please welcome to "Money Making
Conversation" Chad Tomlinson.
Thank you so much for having me.
It's an honor to be here.
Well, I'm glad you
made time to do my show.
Oh, of course.
I love your show.
I really love the
episode with Nick Cannon.
There's a lot of
insight in there, man.
I really appreciate...
That lets me know
you watch my show.
That makes me happy.
Let's get started here.
Education.
Education played a major role in
your career branding early on.
Your educational
background was where?
Wake Forest for undergrad and
Duke University for graduate.
Why?
Well, I have a degree
in business analytics,
and I wanted to compete
with the best in the country
in order to be the
best in the country.
Now the reason I ask why,
because of the fact that I know
I'm a pushy dad.
I'm a successful dad.
I have a daughter, single child.
And so what influenced you
to go to those schools?
Well, I'm I'm a
single child, as well.
And I will tell you that my
parents had a huge influence
on me going, as well.
My dad is crazy successful.
And I think that's all I've
ever wanted from my life.
And I'm doing something very
similar to what he's doing.
I'm an operations consultant.
After I graduated
from Duke University,
he aligned it to where I could
get with one of the biggest
firms in Charlotte.
Chad, let me tell you
what my major concern is.
It's your lack of
job experience.
Experience?
I completed my
master's, and it took me
the last six years of my life!
And then I came here to intern
for you for an entire year!
I was never even late,
sir, so with all due
respect, where am I supposed
to find this experience,
if not from here?
With all due respect,
internship isn't always enough.
Now, listen... what?
I didn't get the job.
And did you tell your dad?
Not immediately,
but ironically enough,
as soon as I got home
from the internship,
he was standing in the driveway.
He had this look in his
eye like he knew already,
so I was more so
bracing for the speech.
But, I mean, he didn't know.
He didn't know.
So how'd it go?
You know, just...
You know, let's
talk about it inside.
Come on.
OK.
Surprise!
What is all this?
It's just a little party
to celebrate you finally
making your way in the world.
Congratulations, baby.
After all of the hard work
that this young man has put in,
congratulations are
finally in order.
- Congratulations.
Congratulations.
I'm proud of you, son.
That's my boy.
And at the point
where everybody was calling me
a winner, I really
felt like a loser
inside because I
hadn't gotten the job.
I felt like I was the
littlest person there.
Chad.
Have you been looking into
an investment portfolio?
You know it's never too
early to get started.
No, not really.
What about real estate?
I don't think I'm
ready to buy a house yet.
But when you're ready,
look over at Eastover.
They've been up and
coming for some time now.
OK.
All right.
Thank you.
As long as you delay the truth,
certain things step in
the way of the truth.
I learned that lesson, as well.
Chad!
I heard you got a fat
signing bonus, buddy.
Congratulations on the job, man.
Thank you, Will. Thank you.
I don't even know who I am
or what I'm going
to do at that point.
Chad, young brother.
Hey.
Have you ever seen
Aspen in the winter?
No.
It's a beautiful place.
Matter of fact, I
need to introduce
you to my nephew, Brett.
You're going to be working
one floor under him.
Matter of fact, his wife
and him do a couples
retreat every year there.
Bring your lady friend.
I will bring my lady friend.
Thank you.
Man, everybody
in the room had a job but me.
Failure is scary.
Is that what drove
you to Atlanta?
That's exactly what
drove me to Atlanta.
I felt like I was lost,
and like most millennials,
I have social media.
I was inspired from a post from
my old roommate at Wake Forest,
and I decided I was
going to try something
different since
clearly this life
didn't have anything for me.
Let me ask you this.
OK.
So that friend
invited you to Atlanta.
That's how we got here.
My friend painted a picture
for me that I could not refuse.
Yo.
Jacob, it's Chad.
Chad?
Freshman year, college?
Oh!
Yo, what up, boy?
Yo, what are you up to, man?
It's been a minute.
I've been good, man.
Just school and stuff.
School?
Wait, still?
Man, what, you become
a doctor or something?
No, operations consultant.
Yeah, I have no
idea what that means.
Yeah, a lot of people don't.
Anyway, I saw on Instagram
that you're in Atlanta.
How's that been going for you?
Oh, yeah, man.
I hooked up with
this indie film crew.
Yo, business is
booming down here, man.
Yo, we worked with
some dope people.
Man, we party every night.
All right, yo, we going
to some cool places, man.
It's been dope.
That sounds awesome.
So what's up, man?
Like, you looking for
a change of scenery?
I think so.
Dude, get down here!
Hey, yo, you know a
smart dude like you,
you would kill it man, for real.
So what's up, man?
You looking for
something in particular?
I don't know yet.
Yo, yo, Chad!
Hey.
I hate to drop a bomb on
you, but I'm in Atlanta.
Yo, that's what's up.
Man, you just missed me.
What?
Yeah, me and the
crew are going down
to Miami to shoot on location.
We on the way there now.
Yeah, cool, cool, man.
That's... that's good.
No problem. Awesome.
Oh, damn.
I didn't... I didn't...
I thought you were talking
about doing your own thing.
I mean, you know, you
know, I travel a lot, bro.
No, it's no problem at all.
Trust me, it's totally fine.
It's cool.
Hey, but you're welcome to
come down to Miami and meet us,
man.
It's only like a 10 hour drive.
It's going to be lit.
Yeah.
I would let you
stay in my bed, man,
but you know I got roommates.
Yo, but if it's cool with
them, it's cool with me.
I'll shoot you to
address, the Copper Coin.
Go by and see what's up.
Good luck.
Yeah, cool.
I'll think about it,
and I'll let you know.
All right, I'm going
to talk to you later.
Fuck my life, man.
Damn it.
Hey!
Man, roll down your window, man!
I need some help, man.
Yo, you got to give
me something, man.
You got to give you something.
I know you got it, man.
Help me out, man.
I don't have any cash on me.
OK, I got some food.
You want some food?
I don't want no food!
I need help, man!
Wow.
Can I just say the word wow?
Wow, dreaming about the
homeless people that I am.
It was so weird.
I can't even put that
into words, like,
the whole experience,
sleeping in the back of a car
when I just drove
3 and 1/2 hours...
And running.
I go back to the
fact, you're running.
I was running really fast.
Maybe if you told a
little truth back then...
Yeah.
Found a table, huh?
Yeah, I guess so.
Is this your section?
This is my section now.
Can I get you something?
$2 for all tap beers tonight.
Here's a menu, unless you
already know what you want.
Yeah.
Do you know Lola?
Yeah, I know her.
Do you think I could
talk to her for a minute?
Sure.
I've been shook
down, shook down by love,
shook me down
taught me a thing or two,
that's when I
learned there are few
things that a man should do.
I'm.
Lola
Hey, I'm Chad.
I'm a friend of Jacob's.
We went to school together.
He's never mentioned you.
I mean, it was a while
back, freshman year.
Didn't Jacob drop out
after freshman year?
Yeah, he did.
We were roommates.
Well, he's my roommate now.
Right, so he said I could
talk to you while he's in Miami.
I'm in Atlanta, possibly stay
in his room until he gets back.
Oh, whoa, whoa.
I don't know.
See, I have my little sister
living with me, as well,
and I don't really know you.
Oh, no, no, no, I'm
really good with kids.
That's the problem.
That's my little sister.
So no offense, I don't really
think it's a good idea.
I'm sorry.
Oh, no.
I totally understand. It's fine.
It's cool.
No big deal.
Are you OK?
Yeah.
I'm going to be fine.
I got to figure some things
out, so I'm going to go.
I really wish I
could help you more.
I'm sorry, but I'm sure
it'll all work out.
Nice to meet you, Lola.
Hey!
Are you serious?
What?
Come on, man!
I...
Did you forget something?
Yes, I did.
Thank you so much.
It's going to be
that kind of night.
Appreciate you.
Yeah, hello?
I got a boot on my car, and this
is the number to call, right?
75... dude, there's
no signs to indicate
that I can't park here.
There are no other
cars with boots.
Are... how long?
OK.
I need your ID.
$75 is a lot.
Is there really
nothing we can do?
No.
Jesus Christ.
Hey, can you just
cut him some slack?
No.
You got any cash on you?
No, I don't.
Will 40 do?
All right.
Yo, you really don't have...
Listen, there's an ATM inside.
You could just
pay me back later.
Thank you.
Hey, I actually have a
friend that has a little bit
of establishment down off
the farmer's market, always
looking for a few extra hands.
You could make a
few extra bucks.
I could tell him about you.
Yeah, yeah, thank you.
You're welcome.
What's your number?
Hello?
Oh!
May I speak to the
manager, please?
I'm the owner.
Nice to meet you.
Would you guys be running the
seven-day free trial still?
Sure.
Do you have, like,
lockers and showers?
Absolutely.
Let me show you around.
Oh, cool, man.
Thank you.
I need to know everything, who
and the what and the where.
I need everything.
Trust me.
I hear what you saying,
but act like it's
new what you're telling me.
I'm Curious George.
I hop in the Porsche.
It's 500 horse.
I'm ready for war.
I'm coming for throats.
They turn into ghosts I
need to know everything.
Oh, perfect timing.
We're about to unload.
Cool, man.
Well, look, I have
two free hands,
so what do you need me to grab?
Oh, you ready to work.
Let's see.
Come on.
What am I getting
myself into here?
Kombucha
Kombucha?
Major health benefits.
It's an acquired taste, but
people around here love it.
What's up, man?
What's going on, man?
Looks good.
So what you thinking?
Let's take a shot.
All right, yeah.
Oh, my... there go my baby momma.
Look at my dumpling right here.
This Miss Mary right here.
- Hi, Miss Mary.
- How you doing?
This is Chad.
Nice to meet you.
All right, let's taste.
Thank you so much my brother.
Hey, I say let's take
it to the ..
- Ready?
- Yeah.
All right.
Cheers.
It's an acquired taste.
Yeah.
None of them cold,
they just got lucky but
never adapted, so I'm 10
to one if it's coming to blows.
My enemies cutting it close.
I let them think that they
got me, but what do you know?
I had them beat
before we ever spoke.
I'm ready for smoke.
I need to know everything,
who and the what
and the where I need everything.
What's up?
Hey, Eric.
- How are you?
- Good.
How are you doing?
Good.
Good to see you.
All right, yeah,
all right, let's go.
Pop the trunk.
I'm sorry?
Yeah.
Cool.
Come on, man.
I'm trying.
There you go.
So I guess Airbnb is
running a special on car beds.
You didn't strike me as a type
that would sleep in his car.
Yeah, well, I didn't really have
a plan or money or anything.
Well, sleep at my place.
Really?
Yeah.
And it's Thursday, so
there's no farmer's market.
Let's roll up to the
auto parts store.
OK, you want to just
drop your car off at the...
Nope.
I'm going to fix it myself.
It's the alternator.
You fix cars too?
I watch YouTube.
Hang on a second.
Hello?
This is Chad.
Chad, Hey. Mr. Burke.
Got a minute?
Sure, what can
I do for you, sir?
It's about your interview.
I respect your boldness,
and I've given it
some careful thought, and
after talking to you dad,
I'm going to offer
you the position.
That will include a
$10,000 signing bonus
and three weeks paid vacation.
Hello, Chad?
Yes, sir.
I'm here.
Did you hear what I just said?
Yes, sir.
I heard you.
OK, well, it sounds like
you need a little time
to think about it.
Why don't you discuss
it with your parents
and then get back to me?
But I need to hear from
you by next Tuesday.
OK, I will.
Thank you.
I'll be in touch.
Let's go.
Let's head out.
Miss you, too.
Thanks for not fussing
at me like before.
I just don't know.
Not yet.
I just need some time to
figure some things out.
I didn't run away.
What you looking for, man?
I don't know.
I'll let you know
when I find it.
Grab your stuff.
Follow me.
Come on in.
This is my place.
Put your stuff over there.
Come check this out.
So my boy is a drummer
and he's on tour
right now, so you can crash
in there until he gets back.
I'm sure he won't mind.
- All right, man.
- There you go.
- Thanks.
- All right.
Wake up.
What do you got going on today?
All right, you coming with me.
I got to be out of
here in 20 minutes.
Wake up.
OK.
All right, come on, let's go.
All right, man.
All right.
Man, I told you to get up.
Jamin, my man.
Yo.
What's up, man? What?
Come on, man.
What up?
I ain't hacking nothing
for you today, bro.
Just tell
me you upgraded that Rambo.
Of course I did.
I always do what I say I'm
going to do, unlike some people.
See, I knew it.
Yeah.
Every time I come in,
it's the same stuff, man.
Are you going to do this for me?
You still owe me for that ..
And the wireless mouse
went missing last week.
No.
I do not owe you for
that wireless mouse.
Every time I come in here,
you say the same thing
about that mouse.
Aww, you're rude.
I'm Jamin.
Your friend is rude.
It's all good, man.
My name is Chad.
I really like the spot.
Oh.
I've never seen a computer
repair place look so...
Um... elegant.
Thank you.
You can take a look around, man.
Get comfortable.
You might be here a minute.
Oh, OK.
Unless... are you here to
help him move the boxes?
No, I'm just looking around.
He's here to help
me move the boxes.
- Come on, my brother.
- What?
You didn't know it,
but now you know it.
Wow.
So how long do you think
you're going to be out here?
I mean, I haven't
really figured it out yet.
Yeah?
So what you thinking?
Right now?
I'm thinking about how good
this barbecue's about to be.
Well, I'm thinking...
What you got up for tonight?
I don't know, man.
Let me check my schedule.
It's good.
Man, look, Jam's dude this
having an art show tonight.
We should pull up.
Let's do it.
All right.
This is amazing.
I appreciate it.
How long you been doing this?
Man, I came out
the womb painting.
Now the real talk.
My mother bought me a sketch pad
to keep me quiet during church,
and it was a wrap since then.
I can tell you been
doing this for a while.
You do this full time?
Nah, not yet.
I'm an investment banker
on a regular 9:00 to 5:00.
But soon, though.
It's coming.
I appreciate it, man.
Really good, man.
Appreciate the support.
Of course.
Let me show you this
over here, though.
Check got this 2Pac.
[MUSIC - IKAI & CYRUS FEAT.
Space man, hell yeah.
ATL, check it, ATL, check it.
I make moon like Black boys.
I'm on the black nonstop, boy.
Jesus.
Shit!
You see me behind you?
No, I didn't see you at all.
Are you blind?
No, I'm not blind.
Then what the fuck is
wrong with you, then?
You know what?
We're just going
to call the police
and get this insurance
thing rolling.
OK, I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Shit.
Ugh.
Just bought this damn car.
OK, uh...
What the fuck?
There's gotta be...
Uh, hey, so my insurance lapsed
two days ago, but I mean, we...
Nigger, please, with your
no insurance having ass.
Unless you're going to pay for
this damage out of your pocket,
I ain't trying to hear it.
No, we can go to
the place right now
and get it taken care of.
I promise.
I can just pay for it...
If we pull out of here
and you try and dip on me,
I will be right on your ass.
I don't know what "dip" is.
As in NASCAR, nigger.
I will be on you.
Don't fuck up because
I will catch you.
OK.
And then we gonna use
the police for real.
No need. I promise.
Just follow me, and
everything will be all right.
I promise. I'm sorry.
It better be.
OK, I'm sorry.
With your no driving ass.
Hey.
All right, man.
Man?
Yo, here are your.
And now you know it's cheaper
if you pay cash, right?
I don't... I don't
think I have cash, man.
I kept imagining
myself in those people's lives.
Um, here.
Yeah, that's fine.
Just put on this credit card.
All right, we'll be right
back with your receipt.
What's up, man?
How you doing?
What's up, Erik?
You know, I'm all right.
Everything is good.
Everything is great.
I'm just trying to
edit this shit down,
and it's driving me crazy.
Yeah.
How you really doing?
I'm good.
I swear I'm good.
All right, what is it?
Dude, I just backed
into somebody's car.
And then I find out that
my insurance lapsed,
so I had to pay to
get that reinstated.
But since here at the car
without any insurance,
I had to pay out of pocket
to get the lady's car fixed.
Pay out of pocket?
You just told me
you had no money.
Where'd you get money
to pay out of pocket?
I'm still broke, OK?
I put it on a credit card.
Credit card?
Yes.
Man, look, it it'll
all work itself out.
It always does.
No, I don't think you get it.
It's not going to work
itself out like that.
It's my dad's credit card.
Ooh, must be nice.
Dad's credit card.
I wish I had a
dad's credit card.
Hell, all the times I need
somebody's credit card
to put my stuff down on, man.
Look, I had a job
for us tomorrow.
Can't do it because
the truck broke down.
So hell, I guess we can't do it.
No, no.
Do you know anybody
with a truck?
I'm just going
to let it go, bro.
I mean...
My dad does not play.
I need to pay this back, please.
I got one dude that I can call,
maybe, because he's a hustler.
So I don't know.
Shit.
Please... please call
the hustler, please.
Hey, what's up, man?
This is E. Listen, man, I got
a job to do in the morning,
but my truck broke down, so
I was just wondering if you
got a truck I can borrow.
Yeah.
Well, I kind of need it tonight.
Oh, you do?
Oh, man.
All right, yo, I'm going
come by with my homie,
and we'll pick it up
tonight, all right?
Thank you. There you go.
I get shit done.
If you ever question me again.
Thank you.
Hustler, yeah.
You know what?
Shake my hand one more time.
Of course, man.
Yeah.
Give me your other hand.
Give me your hand.
That's different?
What are you doing?
OK.
What's up with this?
I don't... I don't
know what's happening.
Nigger, them is white collar
hands, not a knot on them.
Nigger, the job we got
to do in the morning
calls for blue collar hands.
You ain't shit.
I don't care what we need.
I will do it.
Dude, I need the money.
Please.
I have to pay this back.
Man, go check with Lola.
She might need something
down there at the restaurant.
She might need some help,
so go check with her.
What?
Is she, like, the
manager or something,
what are we talking about?
Lola owns the restaurant.
Somewhere on the scene,
you got a little
longer, so it seems.
I burned out, so to speak.
Now come a little closer.
A feel a little light in
the track.
Hey, is that your truck?
No, not really.
I can move it if you need me to.
That's OK.
Come here.
OK?
Excuse me.
Is there a problem, officer?
I don't know.
Is there?
Well, I was just
asking because you
asked about the truck.
Don't ask me no questions.
Let me see your IDs.
Why do you need to see our...
I said, let me see your ID.
Hurry up.
Sit on the ground.
Lock your legs in front of
you, and put your hands under...
You didn't even need...
I said, sit on the ground.
Lock your legs in front of you.
And put your hands on your head.
Shit.
This is motherfucking
bullshit, and you know it.
Come on, man. It's cool.
Shut up.
OK, the jail cell ..
Did your parents know then?
I called home.
That was the first time
I had spoken to my father
since I "ran away"
from the house.
But yeah, that moment
was pivotal for me
because I'll be the first
to admit that, if I'm
being completely honest, I...
I hear about it.
I grew up in Charlotte,
North Carolina,
but I wasn't on the
side of the fence
where it was common to see it.
I have to call somebody.
Oh, my God.
Why do you keep whining, man?
It is not that bad.
The truck was stolen.
Did you steal a truck?
No, I didn't steal a truck.
Well, I didn't
steal a truck either,
so it's going to
all get worked out.
No, it's not going
to just get worked out.
What are you going to do?
Snitch and tell them when
you got the truck from?
Give me a stolen truck
and don't tell me about it?
Hell, yeah, I'm gonna
snitch on that nigger.
We are in jail.
My dad is going to kill me.
One, you're a grown man.
Two, why do you
keep thinking you
have to tell your
father everything.
And you ain't in jail.
Man, we in jail.
So chill.
At least it's just
me and you in here.
We can eat, make phone calls.
We can chill.
I don't... I don't know, man.
I just got to call my
dad, and everything
will be taken care of.
Back to this shit.
Why do you feel like you
got to call your dad?
So he can bail us out of here.
Officer.
Officer!
Ooh.
Hey, dad.
So you're going to
call me from jail
and start off with, hey, dad.
Sorry, it really is
a huge misunderstanding.
And what the hell does
it have to do with me?
I'm your son.
Oh, no, no.
You are not my son, see?
Because my son would be working
at his job, the one that we
just celebrated.
See, now, the man I'm talking
to you on the phone right now.
This man has lost his mind.
This man that I'm
talking to is stupid.
You're just
going to leave me here?
Leave you where?
I don't know where you are.
And apparently, from
the sounds of it
you don't know where
you are either.
Good Lord.
So?
How did that go?
Did I just hear you correctly?
Chad's in jail?
Did you just hang up on my son?
Yes, and now if you
would stop letting
them drink off your titty, maybe
he wouldn't be in this mess.
If he is grown enough
to up and leave,
then he is grown
enough to handle
his own affairs out there.
You and I both know that he
is not grown enough to handle
what happens out there.
And why is that?
Because my son's father is
a despotic narcissist who's
too busy with his head
up his own fucking
ass to realize that he
hasn't allowed his son
a chance to be his own man.
So this is my fault.
No, no.
It's never your fault.
You never wrong.
You're such a humble being.
That's why I married you.
You're just... you're
so fucking perfect.
Fix this!
Have you been smoking?
No.
You liar.
I smell it all over you.
Ooh.
My father hates me.
Your father don't hate you.
He's leaving me in here.
And he probably should.
And this is just a bump in the
road, and you need to relax.
We're in jail.
And so what?
What are the facts?
You didn't steal
a truck, did you?
As a matter of fact, you
put money in your pocket,
and you did it all by yourself.
It had nothing to do
with your damn father.
If I was listening to my father,
I bet I wouldn't be
in here with you.
Hey, you.
You made bail.
Must be nice.
Hey!
I already told you.
Knock that shit off!
Switching my lanes.
Living too fast.
For living, as long we prison.
So many crash.
When I feel like...
What did I tell you?
Get in here.
Sit down.
It was
like looking in the mirror.
You know?
Hmm?
I just didn't want
my life to end up like that.
I'm Black and I'm Black
and I'm Blacker than Wesley.
My flow is amazing.
You flow.
I'm feeling established.
Hello?
Chad, what's good, player?
You tell me.
It is what it is.
What will be will be.
Are you back from Miami?
Yes, sir.
Great.
Um, do you think you
could pick me up?
Take me to my car?
I just got let out of jail.
What?
Yeah.
Hop in, boy.
Hello?
Hello.
Grab your stuff, and
let's get out of here.
What about Erik?
Lola called over there.
He had a warrant.
He's going to be there a minute.
Damn, I hate leaving him there.
Yeah.
I'm sure he's not
happy about it either.
I know Erik.
He's got abandonment issues.
Dad hates me, and now
Erik's going to hate me.
Hey, grab your stuff; get to
my place; and figure out there.
Go.
Go, go.
Damn.
What smell like ass in here?
Hey, mom, I was actually
going to call you after I
finished showering and shaving.
How are you?
Now is not the time to
stall talking to me, OK?
What is going on?
What do... what are
you doing in jail?
Mom, I promise, it's...
It's taken care of.
Everything was good.
It's a big mix-up.
No, it's not fine, Chad.
It's not fine.
I got a call in the
middle of the night
from Atlanta telling
me that you're in jail,
and I got a credit
card bill for $2,200.
What is going on?
You know what?
You better fix this.
OK.
Um... I didn't get the job, mom.
So what?
You got another job
offer in Atlanta?
I actually saw a friend of
mine's page on Instagram and...
On Instagram?
Chad.
Look, I just...
I just needed a
change, you know?
I had to take...
What?
To run away to Atlanta?
No, not run away to Atlanta.
Yes, and why Atlanta?
I don't know.
And it wasn't just Atlanta.
It was somewhere, you know?
I... but everything is good.
Like, I started working here and
I have this friend now, right?
And we've started to go to the
farmer's market and move things
and...
No, wait a minute.
What friend, Chad?
And moving... you
just got to Atlanta.
Where are you moving?
Not moving to Atlanta?
Like, moving furniture.
OK.
Look, it's a lot, right?
It's a lot.
And just... if you
give me some time,
I can explain it in person.
Yes, come home.
Yeah.
Huh?
Yeah, I can be there tomorrow.
Tomorrow.
Yeah, that works.
Look, that's a long
drive home, Chad.
It should be plenty of
time for you to come up
with a story that makes sense.
Yes, ma'am.
I just don't get what is wrong.
What... what's going on?
This is not you.
We gave you everything,
Chad, everything.
What is wrong?
I just don't... I
don't understand.
Just, please... just let
me just explain it tomorrow,
please?
I love you.
Hey.
Thanks for coming.
Thanks for the invite.
I really am sorry.
About what?
It's my fault. I
introduced you to Erik.
This is not your
fault. It's fine.
Erik's cool and all, but
he's all over the place.
Sometimes he hangs
with shady people.
Still, this isn't
your fault. I mean,
you were just trying to help.
You could have just
sent me on my way.
That's my problem.
I'm always trying
to help people.
I need to learn that I can't.
Still, I'm grateful
that you decided
to help me out in this case.
Listen, you're more than
welcome to stay at our place
for a bit, if you want.
It's the least I can do.
I really am sorry.
Thank you.
Still, that's nothing
compared to what's going
to happen when I leave, so...
Stay here then.
Order what you want.
Don't worry about it.
It's on me.
- I don't know.
I just got to hurry
up and go home.
My parents are pissed
off, and they're worried.
You want me to
ride down with you?
My schedule's pretty open.
Thank you.
But no, I wouldn't even
throw you in the deep end.
Well, just so you know,
I'm a pretty strong swimmer.
Look at you you, always
trying to help somebody.
Oh, my God, I need help.
Yeah, you need to go
to Helpers Anonymous.
So what brought you to Atlanta?
I don't know.
I guess I was just
looking for something.
And you think you're
going to find it here?
Not specifically Atlanta,
but I did need a change.
But why?
I'm not sure.
After I graduated from
this really prestigious
private school my
parents sent me to,
they sent me off
to this college.
And I really wanted to go
to school out of state.
But since I wasn't
paying for it,
beggars can't be choosers,
as my dad always says.
I went straight into my
master's and aced everything,
landed this really big
internship, and really didn't...
It really didn't lead to
anything, and now I'm here.
OK, what was the problem?
I think it's time for me to
start making my own decisions.
I get that, but what
do you want out of life?
I want to be successful.
Define "successful."
Oh.
Well, I have my master's
in business analytics,
so I'd imagine I'd go
get a job in my field
and work really hard to
where my family doesn't
want anything financially.
And that's it?
That's what you
define as successful?
What about you?
What about your life?
You have to be more specific.
Well, that would be my life.
Your job?
That's your life?
What do you define a success?
Happiness, freedom.
I like that.
So how can someone have that
if their bills aren't paid?
You were taught to go
to school, get a degree,
get a good job, making money.
So we're successful, right?
Right.
OK, then you're good.
What are you passionate about?
That's what drives me.
I used to take care of
myself and my little sister,
but I came up with a plan
that addressed my passion.
It wasn't always just
about paying the bills.
So how did you end up with
the responsibility of Vanessa?
She seems like she
could be a handful.
Long story short, she is.
But when it comes to family,
you do what you got to do.
Yeah, well, I
know all about that.
That BMW you drive out
there is pretty nice.
Did you pay for that
with your intern salary?
No.
Was it a gift from mommy?
No, it belongs to my father.
Oh, so he's pretty successful.
Yes, very.
So why not take his
blueprint for success?
I have, my entire life.
Obviously something went wrong.
Let me ask you this.
What would you do every day
for free because you loved it?
Figure that out, and
you'll feel right as rain.
That's right.
Where is mom at?
Oh, I'm good, son.
Thanks for asking.
I mean, I have been dealing
with some things around here,
but I think I'm OK.
I'm sorry.
Uh...
Yeah, she's upstairs.
Do you know what
I do for a living?
Yes, dad.
I know what you do for a living.
So what do I do?
You're an equity broker.
And what does that mean?
It means sometimes you
trade for a currency
and sometimes you day trade.
But I know you like
foreign currency
better, stocks and bonds.
And your clients trust
you, so they invest big.
Yeah, that's right.
My clients invest
big because of trust.
That's a trust that's
been built over time.
That trust has a
value on it that only
a fool would throw away.
You look like a fool right now.
I tell my clients you got to
spend money to make money.
I've spent a lot
of money on you,
and I am not seeing the
return that I expected.
Well, I'm sorry
to disappoint, dad.
Let me ask you...
Do you know what
I do for a living?
No, I don't.
Why don't you tell me?
That's the problem.
I can't tell you
because I don't know.
I haven't had a chance
to figure it out yet
because you have made every
decision for me my entire life.
Oh, please.
You told me what school
I'm supposed to go to.
You told me what car
I'm supposed to drive,
where I'm supposed to live in
the future, how much money I'm
supposed to have, and even what
girl I'm supposed to settle
down with, and you
never once considered
that maybe I wanted a
hand in the decisions
being made in my life, dad.
Never.
We both know there's been
nothing wrong with my choices.
That is not what we are
discussing here today.
What we are discussing
are your choices,
and we both know that there
have been some problems there,
jailbird.
Good morning.
- Good morning.
- Nice to see you.
Good to see you, too.
Whoa.
Chad.
Mr. Burke, how are you, sir?
Fantastic. How are you?
I'm great.
Listen, you have
earned this position.
You shined here as an
intern, and I expect nothing
less than you as an employee.
Let's put that
degree to work, huh?
Thank you for the
opportunity, seriously.
Listen, after what your
father's done for me,
it's the least I could do.
Yeah, right, of course.
Listen, I will see you tomorrow.
Yes.
Talk to you later.
"Mom and dad,
thank you both all of your love"
and your sacrifice.
I feel as if the only
way for me to honor
that is by going off and
actually living a life of love
and sacrifice on my own.
So I'm taking a train
back to Atlanta today,
and I'm writing the
address of where I will be
"at the bottom of this letter."
"You
support is more than welcome."
But it's not necessary anymore.
You taught me well.
Thank you.
"I love you both."
"Chad."
So
Yeah, I believe so.
Would you be down to assist
me on a few I got?
Yeah, of course.
It sounds like fun.
Cool.
Well, I had to let
my last assistant go.
She was getting a
little too attached.
Oh, nobody ain't attached
to your trifling ass.
Look, you had your chance.
Suspect.
Please.
You know how I get down.
You know.
I do not.
Wait, where are you going?
Bathroom, damn.
Number one or number two?
Shh.
You good?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Just getting my legs
back underneath.
You know.
What did you have in mind?
I don't know.
I might check back
in with Ted Jinks.
You should talk to Lola about
you have a Copper Coin, man.
Waiting tables?
You'd be great at it.
I don't know.
You gotta about
that comfort zone.
I did.
Look at me.
Like, I'm bowling.
Yeah.
But you're still going to be
my assistant, though, right?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, yeah.
I got you.
Hi.
Lola, um, I really
need some work.
Do you have any openings
at the restaurant
where I can come in and...
I'm serious.
Can we both agree?
You know nothing
about waiting tables.
So what is it exactly
you have in mind?
I don't know.
I would do anything, Lola.
How about this?
You take my yoga class.
I'll think about it.
Hello, everyone.
Hello.
My name is Lola.
I want to welcome you
all today's class.
How many of you are new to yoga?
Well, today's class
is a beginner's class.
So feel free to take as
many breaks as possible.
And please do remember one
thing above all things,
to always breathe.
Ooh, Chad, you do yoga, too.
Amazing.
I love a limber man.
You're late.
Sorry.
Excuse me, ladies.
Do you all need anything else?
All right, well, if you
do, my name is Chad.
Do not hesitate to stop me
if you see me because I'm
here for you, all right?
Thank you.
Hi.
Hey.
I'm coming to say, good night.
- We're good.
Thank you so much.
- You're welcome.
Good night.
Good night, Ty.
Make any money?
Yeah, I did OK.
I'm proud of you.
I didn't think
you had it in you.
What?
All the work?
Most millennials I know
love to talk about the work.
I really haven't met too many
that actually do the work.
My daddy ain't
raise no punk, so...
Apparently not.
I know you're
figuring things out,
but I've been watching you,
and you're working really hard.
I'm happy I gave you a shot.
Hey, so...
We're friends, Chad.
I'm OK with that.
And I feel like
there's a, but, coming.
There isn't a, but.
There's an, and.
And we're friends, and I don't
mix business with pleasure.
But there could be pleasure
if there was no business.
I did not say that.
So what are you saying?
I'm saying, good job, homie.
So I'm the homie then?
Yeah.
OK.
After saying, good job, the
guys are saying something else.
Good job, isn't good enough?
Yeah.
Thanks.
You're welcome.
So this is the part
where I start calling
you, sister, or, cousin?
Or boss.
All right, so we
have the sandwich here.
We have the burger here.
And the salad in the middle.
If you guys need anything else,
my name's Chad, all right?
Excuse me.
You guys OK?
If you need anything,
name is Chad.
Please call, me all right?
Thank you.
Are you good?
OK.
Sir, can I get
you anything else.
No, I'm good.
You know Lola?
Yeah.
Is she here?
Not yet.
I was supposed to be
meeting her, but I'm early.
Oh, OK.
When she gets in,
I'll let her know.
- Thanks, man.
- No problem.
Are you Damien?
Yes, Lola.
Yup, and you're early.
I like that.
Follow me to my office.
I did a "Time" magazine
article on millennials.
There are three
types of millennials.
They're the ones that
are lazy, entitled,
self-obsessed narcissists.
And then there is
the ones who are
open-minded, liberal
self-expressive,
upbeat, and overly passionate.
It kind of sounds
like my daughter.
OK.
And the third kind
are the ones who know how
to turn their followers
and their likes into money.
It's all about the cash.
Which one are you?
You want a taste?
Nah, we good.
We good.
I... wow.
Oh, my God,.
This is so beautiful.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's crazy to
see all that greatness
come from this little thing.
All right,.
Have you ever noticed
that you're the only one
that laugh at your jokes?
Man, it's because I'm the only
person educated enough to grasp
my comedic genius.
Bow.
I have a master's degree.
What is that supposed to mean?
Well... are you implying
that you're more or less
educated than, say, me, because
I ain't a master's degree but...
Lola, do you have
a master's degree?
- Sure don't.
- No, I wasn't...
Shh.
I wasn't...
At, da, da.
Shh, der, da, der.
You know I wasn't
trying to say nothing.
Mmm, just remember that.
Yo, she done yet?
No.
You know I
didn't mean what I said up...
You're just do.
Don't sweat it.
Some things you just
lie by just doing.
Other things you might
need a master's, bro.
Leave him.
Alone.
Chad, do you want to snack?
I got a banana, bag of nubs.
Don't nobody want your
plant and seeds, OK?
We need actual food, please.
Nourishment, please?
You know what?
Actually, food does sound good.
What do you guys have in mind?
Something good.
Something cheap.
Sounds good to me.
Hey, you got a minute?
JAMIN Yeah, Chad, come on.
I got a proposal for you.
Yeah?
Shoot.
Hire me as your
operations consultant.
This place has so much potential
to tap into a massive
audience that I don't
think you can reach without me.
Right.
Chad, what do you
know about tech?
I know as much as the next
man walking down the street.
So why would I hire you
as my operational consultant
if you don't know
anything about tech, Chad?
Because I don't have
to know about tech.
I'm not the tech genius.
Right.
You are.
That's your job.
But that's not enough.
You got to create an experience.
You don't want a
bunch of techies.
You want customers, right?
Chad, I'm still
waiting for a proposal.
The proposal is trusting
me with your business
for the next 30 days.
If I can increase your
traffic and your profit margin
by at least 20%, you'll
hire me for one year
here as your
operations consultant.
It sounds fairly reasonable.
Uh-huh.
Mmm-hmm.
So how much am I out
of pocket for 30 days?
Nothing.
Everything is already here.
Let's put some visuals up, man!
Let's make things pop.
This whole generation is visual.
You've got to give him
something to look at.
Example, right?
The average person
would not understand,
let alone buy, a
cooler-base computer.
Right.
However, I would rather hire
somebody who knows how to fix
my phone and my computer,
that knows how to build that,
than deal with some snooty
geek at a corporate store.
Man, every single time someone
walks in here, that 3D printer
should be printing something.
I don't know.
I don't care.
Phone cases, computer parts.
It really doesn't matter.
And when people see that,
they tell the next person,
and then they tell
the next person,
and they tell the next
person, and so on and so on.
And that creates the
most powerful form
of marketing, word of mouth.
And that's just the start.
All right.
Let's see what you got.
We got a deal?
Got you.
Thank you so much.
How you feeling, champ?
Right as rain.
I think I'm ready.
Ready for what?
To propose.
Propose what?
Nah, it's a joke.
I'm ready to make
a proposal to you.
Don't play.
I'm not.
I just signed Jamin, tech
genius to a one-year consulting
contract.
What?
Oh, my God.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
I want to do the same thing
for you at Copper Coin.
What?
Copper Coin is killing it.
OK.
It is.
If you say so.
What did you have in mind?
You have to highlight
what's best about us.
And what is that?
Great music, great coffee.
Every time I've been
there, it feels like home.
But sometimes that
can pose a problem.
I mean, the
comfortable environment
can come off lazy to the
clients that we serve.
We have great
service at Copper Coin.
I didn't say you did.
I'm... but when's the last
time you revised the menus?
What's wrong with the menu?
I didn't say there
was anything wrong,
but a couple of vegan
options wouldn't hurt, right?
Vegan?
Uh-huh, you have to
stay ahead of the wave.
Having it is better
than not having it.
It's just good business.
Well, if that's what they
want, then I shall provide.
I tell you what.
Let's pop in there.
Let's talk to some
of your customers
and see what they want.
But I know it's a good idea.
Hey, yo.
So this is the nigger that
you going around with?
Let me take this.
You get the fuck out
of my restaurant,
or you get dragged the fuck out.
I seriously doubt that
shit going to happen.
Why are you even here?
I told you we should've
got a restraining
order on this punk ass bitch.
You a scrub.
Do something I dare you.
I already called the police.
So you want to run up, nigger?
Run up.
Yo, it's OK.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry about that, bro.
It's OK.
You know we're not
going to let anything
happen to you out here, bro.
Strong, man.
Yeah, let's go home.
Yeah.
The night's just
getting started, love.
You ready to go home, Chad?
Yeah, I think so.
Thanks for having
my back over there.
You're one of us now.
All right.
Uh, hello Can
somebody get the door?
Damn.
Hey.
Um, this is where you said
you would be if we needed you.
Yeah.
Going to let me in?
Oh, yeah, of course,
please, please.
Come in.
This is it.
Mrs.?
Hey.
You remember me?
Jacob!
No.
High school?
Me and Chad were roommates
freshman year in college.
You look different.
Yeah, a lot of things have
changed since high school.
Chad?
Is this why you moved from home?
Oh, no, ma'am.
No, ma'am.
No, not at all.
Is this where you're sleeping?
Yeah, this is my spot.
Hi, who's is?
This is my mother.
Hi, I'm Vanessa.
Hi, Vanessa.
I'm Lola.
Hi, Lola.
Chad, can we talk?
Yes.
Yes, we can talk.
Oh, sorry.
Sorry.
Vanessa, come.
Your father is very upset.
Yeah.
What is wrong, Chad?
What's wrong?
What do you... just tell me
what do you need, and I'll
make sure that you get it.
I just want to figure
things out by myself.
But we need you at home.
And what about Paris?
She's beside herself.
OK, well I'll have to call her.
You have to do more than that.
That's all I can do right now.
Chad, I'm sick.
In three weeks, I have to
have a surgery to remove
a mass from my breast.
What?
No, what are you talking about?
Look, I've already
seen the specialist,
and they've assured me that,
after these treatments,
that I will probably be OK.
Probably.
Mom, what does... what
does, probably, mean?
Chad, I have cancer.
But I have to have this
surgery in three weeks,
and then there are some
post-operative things
that I have to do.
But they said, after I do
this, that I will be fine.
Your dad and I... we have some
of the best doctors on this,
and they've assured me
that I will be fine.
So I know what I need to do,
and I'm not telling you this
to try to get you to come home.
It's just that I want you to
figure things out for yourself.
I do.
And I drove all the way out
here to see you in person.
I'm sorry I just showed up.
But I wanted to say this in
person and not over the phone.
For a little while.
Mom, why didn't you tell me?
Chad, it just...
Just... it's so much going on.
There's so much happening.
You knew when I was home?
Yeah, we did, but we were still
waiting for the full diagnosis,
so there was nothing to say.
Mom, you should have told me.
No, we felt it was
more important to get
you back on track first.
Don't you think I should have
been a part of that decision?
No, I didn't.
I didn't.
No.
Yeah, bro.
Your mom is sick.
Jacob.
My bad.
Look, I'm going
to be there for you.
Just give me time to just
tie up some things here,
and I promise you I'm going to
be there for you ..
OK.
Well, I'm going to head back
to Charlotte before your dad
does something drastic.
Um, it's nice to meet everyone.
Bye, Mrs. Sterling.
Nice to meet you.
Jacob, it's good
to see you again.
Yes, ma'am.
You take care.
Um, mom, thank you for coming.
I love you.
Mmm.
OK, baby.
I'm way proud of you.
I feel like you
deserve a reward.
For what?
For taking a road
less traveled, Chad.
I'm proud of you.
You should be proud of yourself.
Thank you.
You remember that guy,
Damien, that came to my spot
a while back with the suit?
Yeah, I remember Damien.
Well, he represents
a restaurant group here
in Atlanta, and they've
had their eye on Copper
Coin for some time now.
They bought us out.
I brought up some of your ideas
in the meeting, might have set
us over the top.
This is good?
Yes.
Oh, wow, great, cool.
They cut me a nice check.
My restaurant is
under their umbrella.
They like my style.
I can get that.
Guess who else gets broken off?
What's broke?
A check.
Oh, who?
You.
Me?
Yes, you.
I want to hire you
next year to be Copper
Coin's business consultant.
I mean, you can still
wait tables if you want.
It's up to you.
Thank you.
I love you.
You're amazing.
Thank you.
I love you.
You're amazing.
Thank you.
I'm going to be right back.
I need this.
Thank you so much.
I'm sorry.
I'll be right back.
Excuse me.
Yeah, wait.
Thanks.
Hey, is that for mom?
Yeah.
Do you mind if I take it
up to her when you're done?
Nah, go ahead.
Here, mom.
Thank you.
How are you?
I'm good.
I'm OK.
I'd be better if
dad didn't hate me.
You just need to talk to him.
He doesn't hate you.
You're the only
person he listens to.
Can you talk to him, please?
Directness works
with your father.
Clarity... that works with you.
OK.
You know, what happened
was necessary for me
to be the man you want me to be.
You know that, right?
So say you.
Answer me this.
Did you do everything your
father told you to do?
What's game plan?
Hmm?
Do we have one?
Yeah, we do.
I just signed Mr Burke
as my third client,
so I'm in business.
All right, so what
do you need from me?
Nothing.
What do you want?
When you look
at him and he looks at you...
Before we close... your father...
If he had to ask you what you
wanted, what you wanted, Chad,
what would be your answer?
This whole run, this whole run.
And my plan, what I want is
to make sure that I make them
proud every single day, make
sure that they get to reap
the benefits of all
of my hard work,
their hard work raising me.
And... and most
importantly, I want
to make sure I can steer this
ship that is my life without...
Without making the same mistakes
that I've always made before.
I commend you for that honest
answer, and that's why I wanted
to bring you on the show,
is that "Money Making"
"Conversation" allows CEOs,
industry decision-makers,
celebrities, and athletes
to tell their story.
Yeah.
Thank you.
It's crazy to even
be in that category
or in the alumni
of amazing people
that have graced this seat.
So thank you so much...
- Thank you.
- for having me.
Appreciate you.
Keep being successful,
and keep winning.
Thank you.
[MUSIC - BARROWS AND
SUN, "ONE - ALTERNATIVE -"