[ Ducks quacking ]
[ Faucet squeaks ]
[ Water runs ]
Mom, you still here?
Yeah.
You need something?
Can you listen for the door
and just watch the kids for a
sec?
Just for a second.
[ Knock on door ]
Hi! Come on in.
Good morning.
Sylvie will be right with
you.
Sylvie!
Here, look, look, look, look.
Look.
We are going to have [gasps]
A magical, magical day,
Princess Annabelle.
[ Giggles ]
[ Chuckles ]
Let's go see what we got over
here, okay?
Bye, honey.
Say bye, Annabelle!
Daddy loves you.
Both: Bye.
Want to go in the fire truck?
No, I want to go here.
Oh, okay.
That's a good spot for you.
[ Toy whirs ]
[ Indistinct conversation ]
Hey, mom, do you happen to
have anything I could take
before you go to work?
I'm not sure I do.
'Cause I've got these kids
till 5:00 today, so...
Let me see.
Thanks.
What are we cleaning?
I'm cleaning the mess.
There's a mess on the floor?
Yeah.
Oh, my goodness.
My ... my Princess right
here made a crumbled mess.
Hey, oh, thanks, but
i-i-i actually ... I need two to
have any effect on me anymore.
Don't you think your back
would feel better if you
walked around a bit, did your
physical therapy?
Yeah, I will, once the pain
dies down.
You have a boo-boo?
[ Chuckles ]
[ Sighs ]
Okay. Okay. Fine.
[ Mumbling ]
Tickle, tickle, tickle!
Oh, that helps!
Thank you very much.
Bye!
I'm a tickle Princess
monster.
You're a tickle Princess
monster?
[ Laughs ]
[ Telephone rings ]
Coming, coming, coming.
Mail boxes & thangs.
Fay speaking.
What are you doing?
I'm watching
"America’s next top model."
I'm working.
I haven't seen you in so
long.
Aren't you supposed to be
watching those kids?
They love this show.
They pretend they're on photo
shoots and pretend to be
dieting.
It's so ...
[ Clatter, child crying ]
[ Receiver clicks ]
[ Dial tone ]
[ Sighs ]
[ Telephone beeps ]
Hi.
Can I get a book of stamps with
cars on 'em, if you got 'em?
Uh, two Boston creams, and...
Nipple Pierce.
Ugh.
Sure thing.
[ Piercing gun clicks ]
[ Grunts ]
♪ The sun is beatin' down ♪
♪ talks to his friends in the
pumpkin fields ♪
♪ has laugh lines and great
ideas ♪
♪ if only he could get out of
here ♪
[ Indistinct conversations ]
Can I help you find
something?
Uh, yeah, I-I think.
Um, I'm looking ... s-something
for my plants.
I'm not sure this is even the
right place to get it.
Well, try me.
Uh, powdered plankton?
Right this way.
Yeah, it's great ... especially
sprinkled on a mushroom quinoa
casserole, or even a grilled
cheese, ma'am.
People eat it?
Well, fish and people, yep.
[ Sighs ]
I give it to my tropical plants.
Oh, cool.
I never thought of that.
It makes total sense, though.
I read that if you, um,
give it to them, it replenishes
their nutrients, you know, that
they lack in the colder
climates.
Hold on one second.
This is my secret to good health
all year 'round.
Seaweed?
I eat this at least once a
day.
I haven't been sick with
anything ... I mean anything ...
Since I was 9 years old.
You sound pretty ridiculously
healthy.
[ Chuckles ]
Oh, I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to come off like
that.
No, I ...
I just ... I get really
passionate about eating right
and living right, and, um,
have you been in here before?
I shop at key foods.
It's down the street.
It's a little pricey in here.
That's true, it is,
unless you join the co-op.
Then you get a discount.
Oh, well, that's ... that's
good to know.
[ Chuckles ]
Or if you're friends with
someone that works here.
I'm sorry ... I didn't mean that
you should be my friend.
[ Laughing ]
But not that we couldn't be.
I ... I was just trying to
explain how discounts work
around here.
I guess it's all about who
you know if you want cheap
plankton.
[ Chuckles ]
I'm not really meant for
retail.
Oh.
You can probably tell.
Uh, no, I-I will take that bag
of seaweed.
Please.
It was quite a sales pitch.
Thanks.
[ Sighs ]
Sylvie?
Mom? That you?
Who else would it be?
Wow.
I know Wednesdays are your
long days, so I went to the
store and made you a feast.
It looks amazing ... like a
fancy restaurant or something.
You didn't have to do all this.
Who else is gonna treat you
like you deserve?
What happened to this place?
To my room?
Did you go in my room?
Where did you get these?
Jerry lent me some.
Jerry?
What do you mean, "lent"?
Can't give it back ... it's all
gone now.
I mean I borrowed some
of your money and bought it
from him.
You went through my things.
[ Sighs ]
Sylvie.
You have got to stop lying and
pull yourself together.
I cannot do it all for you,
sweetheart.
[ Sobbing ] You hate me.
Of course I don't hate you.
I love you.
And that little accident set you
back, is all, hmm?
Yeah. Yeah.
[ Sniffles ]
Stuff was different before the
accident.
That's right.
I was dating around more.
Mm-hmm.
And you almost had your g.E.D.,
huh?
[ Sniffles ]
Yeah, but my granddad never
trusted me, and now you don't,
either.
[ Sighs ]
Of course I do, and they did.
I...
I should never have gotten in
the car that night.
It wasn't your fault, mom.
You must have just hit a patch
of ice and hit that tree.
[ Sighs ]
I had to go see Jerry because
you have all my medicine.
I hate that you're in pain
all of the time.
I don't know why the doctors say
that you're healed, when clearly
you're not.
It's...
[ Sighs ]
Sylvie. Hey.
Hi, doctor.
Hi.
So, what seems to be the problem
today?
It's her sciatica.
It's my...
Which is it?
Well, her whole back, really.
Okay. So, uh...
Your dislocated disk is still...
[ Sighs ]
...giving you some trouble,
huh?
All right.
[ Sighs ]
I can't thank you enough,
doctor.
No problem.
Uh, this is for physical
therapy.
She's in severe pain.
When we discussed our
pain-management policy here, you
agreed to help your daughter
comply.
Well, I know that, and I
did.
I do.
I'm her mother. I ...
It's been several months.
Physical therapy and an
appointment with the
pain-management clinic in
Cornwall.
A-And ... and what are they
gonna do for her?
Cortisone and steroid shots.
God, what an asshole.
[ Sighs ]
Excuse me, Sylvie?
I'm sorry, but my mom and I
have done everything right.
You're the one who's not doing
your job right.
You don't even care if I'm in
pain.
Oh, my god.
I'm gonna grab my office
manager.
I'll be right back.
What are you thinking?
I'm sorry.
I'm ... I'm panicky.
I blurt things out when I panic.
Shh.
[ Sighs ]
Hi, there, Ms. Worth.
Ms. Worth.
Hi.
Hey.
Uh, Dr. Kinski will continue
to offer you emergency care for
the next 30 days, but I’m
afraid you're gonna have to find
a new doctor.
Y-You're dropping me?
Well, by not following
Dr. Kinski's recommendations,
you now have a non-therapeutic
relationship, so he feels it
best you find another physician.
My daughter needs the
doctor's care.
That is his job.
What do you want us to do, just
live in pain?
I'm very sorry to hear about
your difficulties.
Fuck me!
[ Door opens ]
Hey, there.
Long time, no see.
Small world.
Small main street.
[ Chuckles ]
Do you mind if I hang this on
your bulletin board?
As long as you're not
advertising anything illegal.
No, it's just, uh, I’m
looking for a room to rent.
And I also need a p.O. Box, and,
uh, I want to mail these
containers of water.
All right. Um...
You ... you really do
piercings here?
Mm-hmm.
Did you have to go to
piercing class or something for
that?
[ Laughs ]
Just had to demonstrate basic
hygiene.
Remind me not to come here
for the "thangs," just the
"mail box" part.
[ Laughs ]
Here is a key for your p.O. Box,
if you just sign there.
And, uh...
Why are you mailing water?
Well, I'm studying the river
and local water sources.
You know, I-I-I take samples and
I send them to a lab at my old
college.
You determine the life of the
river, and you determine the ...
The health of the land, and
all the life living in and
around it.
Th-th-that is just great.
Thanks.
Let me just line this with,
uh...plastic and double up on
the packing tape.
Oh, I can do that.
[ Tape unwinds ]
I'm gonna make a great big
pile that you can't make.
[ Laughs ]
[ Dog barks ]
I can make a big...
[ Indistinct conversation ]
I've asked you not to kick my
door.
You're making scuff marks.
I have a doorbell. See?
Here's 10 bucks.
Give me a Percocet.
I got to charge you more than
than 10 bucks, and I don't do
singles.
They're very high in demand
right now.
$10 is all I have.
Just give me what I asked for.
You need to charge more for
your babysitting, Sylvie.
[ Scoffs ]
I have an injury, and I need
something for the pain ... now.
[ Country music plays ]
Hey.
Hi.
Uh, I thought I'd get my produce
here instead of key food.
Right on.
Did you find a place yet?
In the last hour?
Uh, no.
[ Chuckles ]
Well, I-I remembered, after
you left, uh, I've got a room
to rent.
Well, me and my daughter, that
is.
Um...and, you know, you two
could have so much in common.
Well, she loves to cook, and,
well, you love food.
And she loves to go outside.
She loves the outdoors.
So isn't that funny?
We happen to have a spare room
to rent, also.
[ Chuckles ]
Uh...
Okay.
Great.
We live in a house by, uh,
the creek.
Oh, I love it over there.
I hike the trails by there all
the time.
Yeah?
Well, isn't that something?
What? Isn't what something?
[ Sighs ]
[ Knock on door ]
Hi.
Come on in.
Make yourself at home.
Okay.
[ Both chuckle ]
Ahh.
[ Grunts ]
[ Chuckles ]
Aren't you ever gonna
introduce me, mom?
I mean, I'm standing right here.
Oh, I'm so sorry. Hi.
It's Sylvie.
Becket Strom. Thank you.
For what?
I-I don't know.
For just inviting me in,
showing me the room to rent.
Oh.
Oh, yeah.
Come. Come, come, come, come.
[ Chuckles ]
Wow.
You've got quite a green thumb.
[ Chuckles ]
I know.
It's a little freaky at first,
but you get used to it after a
while.
No, I love it.
Can I get you something to
drink?
Oh, just a glass of water,
please ... with a slice of lemon,
if you have it.
Thank you.
I'll put a slice of lemon in
your coke, Sylvie, seeing as you
like lemon so much, too.
So...where are you from?
I haven't seen you around.
Uh, I'm from up near
saugerties, via new paltz.
Oh, world traveler.
Compared to us, you are.
Your family still in saugerties?
Yeah.
They're kind of hard to keep in
touch with, though, because they
don't believe in phones.
[ Chuckles ]
No phones? Ugh.
We keep in touch all the time.
No, my parents and I keep in
touch more spiritually than
literally.
I am trying to do my part to
really focus on ... on doing
something for the world around
me.
Is there anything else you
wanted to know about me?
Do you have any conditions,
like allergies, or injuries we
should know about?
No.
Well, I'm lactose intolerant.
Sylvie is so sensitive about
other people's concerns.
[ Laughs nervously ]
Well, I'm the healthiest
person I know, so...
Mm.
[ Chuckles ]
Do you have anything you want
to ask us?
Before you ask, um,
fay and I are more like
best-friend roommates than
mother and daughter.
Uh, she had me when she was
young.
You'd be the only man of the
house.
Good to know.
[ Drums fingers ]
The sound of the creek is so
soothing.
You know, I catch Sylvie
looking out at those treetops
all the time, just like that.
This was my grandparents'
house, and their parents were
born here, too, and before
that, it had to be just apes.
Oh. [ Laughs ]
No one in our family has left
this town, ever.
You know, this creek feeds
right into the Hudson.
Mm.
Becket studies water.
Oh, I remember doing that in
school ... watching it turn from
liquid to ice, or liquid to
steam.
I-I think he studies more
what's in it, right, Becket?
I don't think the state is
doing its job protecting the
Hudson, and I think the aquifers
are being poisoned.
See, the hydrological cycle
continues, whether or not our
water is potable after g.E.
Dredges up pcbs or Halliburton
Fracks.
I want to get the e.P.A.
Involved ... let them know that
not enough is being done.
I want to rally this community.
You know, this is our river.
My grandparents used to fish
this river, swim in it, drink
it.
Now it's just ... it's a source
of harm.
[ Sighs ]
We want to help.
We want to help in any way we
can.
Really?
We're with you, all the way.
[ Chuckles ]
Can I see the ... the room
that's for rent?
[ Laughs ] Oh.
Oh, of course.
Right this way.
[ Laughs ]
Uh-huh. Uh-huh.
Yeah, nice walls.
Mm-hmm.
Wow.
Lots of dirt.
I-If  my plant supplies bother
you, I can just move them.
Not at all.
You got fish oil and crab meal.
Yeah, I'm gonna be snacking at
night.
[ Laughs ]
Do you, uh, need to go pick up
the rest of your things?
N... t-this is pretty much it.
Oh. One more thing.
I run a daycare here during the
week.
Right now, I just have two kids,
but they really sound like more,
like five or six kids.
Is that a problem?
Uh, I forgot to mention it.
I-I guess it's sort of important
to know.
[ Chuckles ]
Oh, no.
I'm out and about when the sun
rises.
I don't like to miss a drop of
daylight.
Great.
That's that, then.
[ Chuckles ]
[ Train horn blows ]
We're out.
Oh, oh, my god.
Shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh.
Oh, oh, no. Oh.
No, no, no, I need ... I need
you to keep it together.
[ Sighs ]
Shh.
I know we'll get some more, all
right?
It's okay.
Yeah.
[ Smooches ]
And we'll figure it out, okay?
Yeah.
[ Telephone rings ]
[ Coughing ]
Hello, there.
Hi, doctor.
I don't know if you remember my
daughter, Sylvie.
Uh...
She drove me in today,
'cause, uh, well, I can't drive
with this pain.
Sure.
I-I haven't seen her since she
was a lot younger.
Mm.
But I remember.
[ Chuckles ]
What are you up to these days,
huh?
I'm ... I’m, um ...
I'm in a lot of pain.
Oh. Uh...
Who am I seeing here, today?
Me. Y-You're seeing me.
I, uh, wrenched my shoulder out
at work.
[ Sighs ] Okay.
Uh, post office, right?
Well, mail boxes & thangs,
actually.
Mm-hmm.
I, uh, was lifting a box I
never should have, and, um, the
pain is j... oh, oh.
Ooh.
Oh. It's killing me.
[ Sighs ]
You know, I can't sleep, i-i
can't lift, I can't drive, I ...
Oh, can't drive ... that's no
good, huh?
Mm, yeah.
I'm going to write you a
prescription to, uh, see the
orthopedist.
And another one to help you with
the pain.
[ Sighs ]
In the meantime, obviously,
no lifting, no skydiving, no
rock climbing, either.
[ Laughs ]
Of course.
Oh. Um...
What's ... something the
matter?
Well, I was hoping for
something a little more
stronger than Tylenol 3.
[ Sighs ]
I'll prescribe an additional
Vicodin regimen for you to use
when the pain is at its worst.
But if we're talking that much
pain, I want you to go straight
to the orthopedist.
Oh, yes, I will.
And I want to see you back
here in three weeks, along with
a report from the specialist.
Oh. Yes. Uh...
All right?
O-O-Of course. Yes.
Thank you so much, doctor.
Okay.
Thank you.
[ Clears throat ]
You know, before the pills
run out, maybe we could go up to
Canada ... get some of the
codeine syrup they sell over the
counter.
We could get a bunch of that
until we figure something else
out.
It helps me ease the pain
sometimes.
You are not supposed to bring
that stuff over the border.
It's illegal here without a
prescription.
[ Scoffs ]
It wouldn't be you doing it.
It would be me.
You just have to come along
'cause I have a little record.
Yeah, for driving drunk
underage into Canada.
You don't want me to be in
pain and lose the kids.
There are so many scams online.
You got to go in person.
You've already done enough
illegal stuff, giving me your
prescription pills.
You'd totally go to jail if I
told on you.
You would never do that
because you'd never see me
again.
We'd be separated.
I'd be in jail.
Of course not.
We don't buy water.
I only drink bottled water
now, ever since Becket told us
the regular water is ... is not
good for you.
Well, I don't think that's
what he said, exactly.
Well, I'm not taking any
chances.
I'm gonna say I ate earlier,
do a little garden work,
so you two can spend time
together, hmm?
What if he doesn't want to
eat with me?
Mnh, of course he will.
Who wouldn't, hmm?
You two are perfect together.
[ Smooches ]
[ Chuckles ]
Okay. Close your eyes.
Okay.
Where's fay?
Picking up dog shit in the
yard, raking, that kind of
thing.
She already ate.
You have a dog?
No, other people's dogs'
shit.
[ Sniffs ]
Oh, it smells so good.
It's my secret specialty.
Open your mouth.
[ Both laugh ]
Mmm.
Mmm. Mmm. Delicious.
Oh. Forgot the drinks.
I love this stuff.
Thank you.
What's in this dish?
Well, I'll tell you some
things, but not all.
I don't give it all away on the
first date.
[ Laughs ]
Uh, you don't have to tell
me anything you don't want to.
I'm just ...
Jalapeños, cherry tomatoes,
pork loin, heavy cream, smoked
Gouda, two sticks of butter.
[ Groans ]
What's wrong?
Sorry. It was my stomach.
I'm, um...Lactose intolerant.
Yeah, I know.
That means no milk, right?
[ Strained ] No dairy.
No cheese, cream, butter.
Oh. Bummer.
What happened?
I totally spaced the whole
lactose-allergy thing.
Oh, Jesus. How awful.
Are you okay in there?
[ Strained ] Fine. Sorry.
Don't want to be rude, uh...
Just so much dairy at dinner,
in the pork.
I'm so embarrassed.
Oh, we're roomies.
No need to be embarrassed.
[ Floor creaking ]
[ Snoring ]
[ Snoring continues ]
Whose water?
All: Our water.
We don't want your pcbs.
It really means a lot to me
you guys came out today.
We wouldn't miss it.
We'll come out every time.
Sylvie used to do this all the
time.
[ Giggles ]
Yeah?
Mm-hmm.
Right on.
[ Giggles ]
I try not to get too
disappointed when the turnout's
low.
Well, you're doing something.
That's what matters.
Yeah ... we're nobody, but we
have a voice.
[ Chuckles ]
Whose water?
Our water.
Oh, Sylvie. Sylvie. Sylvie.
Hold your signs up.
Put your arms around each other.
I'm not really doing this for
show.
Of course not.
Thinking about water just
makes me thirsty.
Are you thirsty?
Hmm?
Hey, do you want to sign our,
uh, petition against fracking
and dredging?
Why would I want to stop
fucking and drugging?
You know, maybe it would be
better if you picked one thing
the next time you protest.
You're so right.
Thanks, fay.
Mom, I'm not feeling so good.
She okay?
Oh, yeah. She'll be fine.
She, uh ... just that time of
the month, you know?
Sorry.
[ Dog barks ]
Fay.
[ Knocks on door ]
Shh, shh, shh, shh.
Shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh,
shh.
What?
It hurts, mom.
No. You just had one.
You need to pace yourself.
Give it or I'll scream.
If you scream, Becket will
want to leave, hmm?
I need to go to sleep.
[ Blender whirs ]
[ Blender stops ]
Fay, I ... I have to talk to
you.
I found this in the garbage.
You found garbage in the
garbage?
No, compost.
All of this is compostable.
Fay, you, of all people, who
turn houseplants into
superspecies, have to compost.
I usually just throw that
stuff away.
[ Chuckles ]
But i-it just takes a little
time.
You want to keep it moist, but
not too moist.
Uh, you stir it once a day.
You want a good mix of
carbonaceous and nitrogenous
ingredients.
There's nothing to it.
I know you're just being
helpful.
Of course we should have a
compost.
I've always thought that.
I just never thought our
garbage was good enough ...
I mean, the right kind of
garbage.
Actually, gum doesn't
decompose.
It really serves no good purpose
on earth.
Fresh breath?
Well, there is that, I
suppose.
But, really, parsley and fennel
are better for bad breath.
Boo.
[ Chuckles ]
So, fay is too shy to ask,
but she wants to know if you
could remove this really big
rock from our yard so she could
finally plant a garden outside.
It's too heavy for us.
I have a-a bad back, and she's
not very athletic or
coordinated.
Of course.
No, I'd love to.
I ... yeah, I'll go take a look.
Okay.
Th-that rock's never been
moved in the history of this
house.
It's not meant to be moved.
I-I-It can't be.
And I don't have a garden
because I don't have time to
take care of one.
The ... the houseplants are fine.
No weeding.
We're gonna take care of that
rock for you once and for all.
Plus, Becket and I need some
quality time together.
Right now?
That rock isn't going anywhere.
It's not worth the trouble ...
Really.
Kind of like that rock.
Hey, what if you two went to the
movies instead, huh?
My treat?
[ Grunts ]
[ Panting ] I'm doing this.
I want you to be happy, fay.
Maybe I can get in here a
little bit, break that up for
you.
[ Kettle whistles ]
Oh!
Aah, fuck!
Aah!
Blazes, what happened?
[ Gasps ]
[ Groaning ] I think my hand
is broken.
I-I must have just lost my
grip or my ... my aim, or
something.
I-I was just trying to help.
We got to get him to the
hospital right away.
Are you in much pain?
Yes.
Oh. Go get an ice pack.
[ Panting ]
I've got to get him to the
doctor.
Do you want me to come along?
No!
Come on, Becket.
Up you get. That's it.
[ Straining ] Let me help.
There you go. Okay. Okay.
[ Sighs ]
Mm-hmm.
How's your hand?
Hurts. [ Chuckles ]
Ugh, god, what a stupid mistake.
I've never broken anything in my
life.
Well, let's get you to the
doctor, hmm?
Uh, this is embarrassing, but
I-I don't have health insurance.
I don't do doctors.
My doctor's group takes
walk-ins, and they take people
without insurance on a sliding
scale.
Okay.
[ Chuckles ]
Aah.
Take it.
Ooh.
[ Groans ]
[ Sighs ]
[ Chuckles ]
So sorry to be so much trouble.
I'm so very sorry.
It's all my fault.
No. It's no one's fault.
Humankind's been battling
nature and losing since the dawn
of time.
[ Chuckles ]
The rock won.
[ Sighs ]
[ Door closes ]
Oh.
[ Whimpers ]
Um, ow.
[ Sighs ]
Everything okay?
I survived the doctor.
[ Chuckles ]
Well, let's get to that
pharmacy before it closes...
And bring you home to get some
rest, huh?
[ Engine turns over ]
Sylvie? Hello?
Sylvie?
[ Sighs ]
Um...here we go.
Oh.
Right?
Thank you.
Thanks.
What is she up to? Sylvie?
Oh.
Sylvie?
Found her.
Oh, Sylvie.
Fuck.
Sylvie. Sylvie.
Get up.
Get up!
Oh.
[ Smooches ]
Oh. What did you take, huh?
Sylvie.
Oh, god. Oh, my god.
Get your undies up.
That's it. That's it.
Oh, oh! Shit! Aah!
[ Grunting ]
Okay. Okay. All right.
Oh, god.
Oh.
Okay.
Okay, we can handle this.
All right, sweetie. Come on.
What did Jerry give you, honey?
Huh? What did he give you?
If he did this to you, I’m
gonna kill him.
Everything okay?
Uh, just a minute!
Uh...
Oh, god.
[ Sighs ]
What's happening in there?
E-Everything is...
Not all right.
It's Sylvie.
She's, uh, epileptic, and she,
uh, had a fit and hit her head,
uh, while she was on the toilet.
And she would be so humiliated
if she knew you knew.
But I-I can't lift her on my
own.
Could you?
Oh, Jesus.
Oh, my god.
You ...
Uh, okay. Okay. Um, uh...
I'll lift her up. You call 911.
No, no need to call a
doctor.
They're always so useless, you
know?
Always suspecting the worst.
[ Groaning ]
Um, no, we'll just get her
up, and ... come on.
Come on, baby.
Okay. Okay. Okay.
Oh. Okay.
All right.
Now we just walk her around a
bit till she comes to.
What?
Yeah. Yeah.
It happens all the time with
epileptics.
It does?
Oh, yeah.
[ Both panting ]
Okay.
Come on, sweetie.
Come on.
That's my girl.
Thank you so much, Becket.
J-Just ... wait ... just pick her
up, down the stairs.
Can you help?
O-Okay. I got it. Okay.
I've got it.
Okay. Oh, oh. My back.
[ Both grunting ]
Okay. I've got it. Got her.
Okay.
Okay. We got her.
Just get her walking, now,
Becket.
We've got to get her walking.
Come on, girl. Come on.
Sylvie?
Come on. Wake up.
Sylvie.
Come on, baby.
Snap out of it, girl. Come on.
[ Both grunting ]
Oh.
Oh, oh.
Aah.
Okay. Okay. Okay. I got it.
All right, let's just put her
here.
Put her down here. Right here.
Okay. Okay. Okay.
Watch your hand.
Down. I'm gonna put her down.
Aah. Aah. Aah.
Ohh, oh. Oh.
Come on. Snap out of it.
Come on, Sylvie. Come on.
Becket, slap her.
Slap her as hard as you can.
No, I'm not comfortable d...
Just do it.
Oh!
That's it. That's great.
Sylvie?
Good job.
[ Groaning ]
[ Faucet squeaks ]
[ Water runs ]
Sylvie?
Come on.
Aah! Fuck!
That's the way.
Aah.
Why did you do that?
It's okay. It's okay.
Shit.
[ Whimpers ]
[ Panting ]
This happen a lot?
Well, this is pretty bad.
Not usually this bad, no.
[ Groans ]
She's really very upbeat.
Ugh, some shit Jerry gave me.
Is she gonna be okay?
It didn't help my back.
Yeah, yeah, she's gonna be
fine.
We're just gonna get her up,
and, uh, get her to bed.
[ Grunts ]
Let her sleep it off, huh?
Should we put something
between her teeth, you know, in
her mouth?
That's a great idea.
This never would have
happened if I had my real
medicine.
I know.
You know, she hit her head
pretty hard on that tub.
You think I could grab a few
of your pain pills for when she
wakes up?
Oh, absolutely.
Yeah, I've always been pretty
squirrelly about taking
medicine.
Fay, is that you?
Yes, sweetie, that's me.
Oh, god.
You smell like skunk.
I don't smell like skunk.
It's the compost, honey.
[ Retches ]
[ Coughs ]
Ugh.
O-Okay, sweetie. All right.
You want a towel?
[ Groans ]
It smells so good.
You shouldn't be cooking,
though.
No, I love to do it.
You don't deserve all these
distractions.
Being with you's not a
distraction.
I enjoy it.
You're such a strong woman.
D-Do I smell like skunk, or
anything?
[ Laughing ] No.
[ Sniffs ]
No, you smell great.
You ... you smell like your
plants.
Maybe a little bit like barf.
[ Laughs ]
Do I smell like rubbing
alcohol, or [sniffs] plaster?
I-I worry about body odor
sometimes.
[ Sniffs ]
I'm not sure. Let me see.
[ Chuckles ]
[ Moans ]
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Mm.
I should do something about
my beard.
No, no. I'm ... I'm sorry.
I'm sure you meant to kiss
Sylvie.
She made you the cake.
She's younger.
My aim is terrible, but I’m
pretty sure I meant to kiss you.
N-No, you must just be
confused because of your...
Hand hurting so much
and everything.
[ Telephone rings ]
[ Sighs ]
Hello?
Ms. Worth?
Who's calling?
Is this fay?
Yes.
This is Dr. Marquez, and I
would like you to make an
appointment to come see me as
soon as possible.
Oh. Yes, i-I'll do that.
Uh, thank you for calling.
[ Telephone beeps ]
[ Receiver clicks ]
Solicitor.
[ Gasps ]
Oh, you are such a nice guy.
[ Sighs ]
I think I'd better go to bed
now.
O-Okay. Sure. Yeah. Um...
Yeah. No, I understand.
Me, too. Um...
I have a little work I should
do.
Thank you.
Good night.
That's all?
For now.
I want to mail these.
No shit.
Excuse me?
What the fuck did you just say
to me?
If you ever go near my
daughter again, I will kill you.
Are you threatening me?
Yes.
That's what I thought.
You got to keep your daughter
away from me.
She's the one begging me for my
shit.
I help her out.
You should be thanking me.
With a dull knife.
What?
Do not go near Sylvie!
Yo, how long's the wait for a
Pierce?
Hey, man, how's it goin'?
Ooh, what's up?
Good to see you, man.
I'll be right with you.
Here's a doughnut while you
wait.
Sweet.
Anything flammable or
breakable?
Nope.
Anything that could explode
under pressure or is otherwise
hazardous?
Nope.
[ Sighs ]
They're all about five grams.
Hmm.
That makes it easy.
I-i-I'm so sorry.
Oh, fuck.
And listen, the next one ...
It's on us.
Ugh.
Like I'm ever fucking coming
back here.
[ Door opens, closes ]
The d.E.C. Got my samples ...
My research.
[ Sighs ]
They found it troubling and
important that fluorinated
compounds used in fracking
chemical solutions turned up in
the Hudson river watershed.
Oh.
They want to meet with me to
discuss more.
[ Gasps ]
No one's ever answered me
before.
[ Gasps ]
Oh!
I took your advice, and I
focused on one thing ... fracking
chemicals in the Hudson.
This is it!
I'm so happy for you.
Oh, for us ... for all of us.
I'm so glad I met you...
[ Sighs ]
...and Sylvie.
Having someone to share this
with.
Aw.
Hey, come outside with me.
No, I can't. I ...
No, no, no one's here.
We'll put one of those "back in
a half-hour" signs on the door.
[ Laughs ]
When was the last time you
walked down here?
Oh, a few weeks ... months
ago, I guess.
Uh, th-there was music over
there, I think.
You know, the truth is...I
haven't been down to the water
in ages.
[ Sighs ] Mmm.
[ Groans, sighs ]
What would we be without all
this?
Right?
Huh?
Even the heavens come from
this river.
[ Chuckles ]
Everything's connected.
One person poisons the river,
everyone suffers, for
generations.
Nothing is more important than
this water.
No?
That must make things pretty
easy for you.
Thought there was a bathroom.
[ Chuckles ]
You know, Sylvie's got a lot of
great qualities, once you get
closer to her.
Yeah, I'm sure she does.
You're her mother.
[ Chuckles ]
She's got a great sense of
humor.
She's so good with kids and
pets.
[ Chuckles ]
Brave as she can be about her
health problems.
She has your beautiful eyes.
A little ... a little bit of you
around the ... around the mouth.
I, uh...
With you...She ... she...
...has some self-esteem
problems, but you wouldn't know
it.
She's...
There's nothing you wouldn't
do for her...To make her
happy...'cause you are an
incredible mother.
Oh, I failed her in the
beginning, and I've got to make
it right.
Ohh.
W-We don't deserve you.
I ... I ... I don't ... don't
deserve you.
You deserve better.
Because I'm such a catch?
No.
Because you're so hopeful.
[ Both moaning ]
I don't want this to be awkward
for Sylvie, or ... I don't want
her to get upset, o-o-or
confused, so let's just keep
this to ourselves for now.
Hmm?
Sure.
Yeah, I understand. I think.
[ Chuckles ]
You know, if she just thinks
you're attracted to her, even
though that may never be so,
um...
Sylvie won't know.
Don't worry.
She's gonna be so excited
about how well your hard work is
paying off.
Will you let me take you out
to dinner tomorrow night, to
celebrate ... just the two of us?
On a date?
You mean, out somewhere?
[ Laughs ]
Yes.
No, it's been a long time for
me, too.
[ Sighs ]
I think I was in college the
first time ... last time I was on
a proper date.
Proper date?
Sure.
I mean, yes.
I'd love to.
Oh, no.
What are you doing with my
stuff?
Oh, hi, there.
What stuff?
D... what stuff?
Are you serious? Wh...
Excuse me.
Oh, oh, I'm sorry.
That makes sense now.
I just ... I've been a little bit
out of it since the seizure.
I just ... I thought that those
might have been granddad's
old things.
Did you get Becket's medicine
I left you?
We need money.
No, we do not.
We're fine right now.
[ Sobs ]
What ... what are you
thinking?
We don't need all of this.
We need pots and pans.
We don't need this thing.
Well, nobody's gonna buy
that, silly.
Somebody might.
You all right, Becket?
[ Sighs ]
I'm really sorry I sold your
backpack, Becket.
I want to replace it.
I'm gonna sell some of my blood
to get you one.
You don't have to do that.
I-It's just a bag.
It's not a big deal.
Sylvie, that's not a good
idea.
Well, I have to do something
for you, or I'll feel so bad.
Fay and I are gonna take you to
Canada.
I have it all planned out.
It's gonna be a blast.
That is very sweet of you,
honey, but I don't think
that's a very good idea, either.
It used to be your favorite
thing to do, mom.
I think it's a great idea.
I do.
I've never been.
I've always been looking for a
reason to go.
It's supposed to be beautiful.
Maybe some other time.
I don't even know if grandma's
car would make it there, at this
point.
Come on, mom.
Becket wants to go.
Why are you so against going?
No reason.
Be fun.
I-I ... why not?
It might be fun.
[ Telephone rings ]
Should I grab that?
N-No.
U-Unless ... are you expecting
a call?
No.
I'll get it.
[ Telephone beeps ]
Hello?
Fay worth, please.
Speaking.
This is Dr. Marquez calling
again.
You never made a follow-up
appointment with me.
And I have some concerns I need
to address with you in person.
I see.
Uh, I'll drop by soon.
Thank you so much.
[ Telephone beeps ]
Hello?
Yes.
Yes?
Uh, h-hello. Yes, this is him.
[ Squealing ]
Oh, my.
[ Sighs ]
I called you in because I'm very
concerned about you and your
daughter.
And that's very nice of you.
How old-fashioned.
[ Chuckles ]
I feel that there could be
prescription-drug abuse going
on.
I never received a report from
your orthopedist.
I never saw you again after your
shoulder injury.
And I know Dr. Kinski and a lot
of the pharmacists in town.
M-M-My shoulder's feeling
much better now, and I...
Been very busy.
I just figured I would save on
the co-pays.
[ Chuckles ]
Fay.
I've been your doctor for a
while.
I wanted to tell you that you're
not alone, that there are
treatments for your daughter.
She doesn't want treatments.
She ... she doesn't need
treatment.
She's feeling much better now.
What she needed was for a doctor
to show some concern, take some
responsibility, figure out
w-w-what had happened after her
injury ... why she was in so much
pain.
How about that?
She is an addict.
She is in pain.
Maybe, but she is an addict.
And the kind of pain that
accompanies is intractable.
She may not want treatment.
She may not know what she wants.
And this isn't a life for you,
either.
My life?
My life is just fine, thank you.
If this happens again, I will
have to report you.
This is a small medical
community, and we are all under
scrutiny here.
I ha... what are you doing
here?
I have a doorbell, you know.
It's right here.
Works and everything.
May I come in?
You need something to help
you sleep, get horny, what?
I'd like to come in.
Now is not a good time.
Just let me in.
Kids, this is one of daddy's
neighbors who needs to borrow a
cup of sugar.
[ Scoffs ]
It's my weekend with the
kids, so don't fuck this up for
me.
Well, I'm sorry.
I just assumed you weren't
related to anyone.
I came over to ask you to move.
Move at least one county away
from my home as soon as
possible.
Are you high?
I have one of the packages
you tried to send from my store
locked away.
And I have you on surveillance
tape bringing in the packages
and mailing them.
You are a dealer.
And I'm gonna have you put away
if you don't move out.
That's tampering.
Yeah.
Fuck.
Isn't that tampering with
official shit?
[ Telephone ringing ]
[ Telephone beeps ]
Hello?
Hey, I'm sorry to call so
late, but you'll never guess
where I am.
Where?
The city.
In New York City?
No. Albany.
They wanted me to come up right
away.
Oh, wow.
So I meet with the guys from
the d.E.C., and they thank me
for my work.
They corroborated my findings
with their own.
They fired the local watershed
officials.
And they said they want me to
stay up another day or so to
discuss more.
Well, that's great.
I ... I knew you would do what
you wanted to do.
What we wanted, right?
That's right.
You know, I was a fool to
think this was gonna change.
Business as usual.
It's not gonna go any further
than the regional d.E.C.
It's just a blip.
You know, I made a blip.
I wanted to make a wave.
What you did matters.
You're just beginning.
I see you making waves.
You're...a doer untethered.
You, uh ... you should do what
you're doing.
You should stay.
Well, I'm ... I'm gonna be
back for the Canada trip.
I-I took a couple days off work.
Don't feel like you have to
come back for that trip.
Really. Just forget about us.
No, I'm coming back.
We're going to Canada together.
Sure.
[ Sniffles ]
Congratulations, Becket.
Why are you being so weird?
Mm, i-I'm not.
Hey, um...
How's ... how's your circulation?
H-Have you noticed anything
since, uh ... since we had
intercourse?
What?
No.
Should I?
Well, all, you know, kinds of
endorphins get released that,
uh, gives you renewed energy.
It's ... I mean, it's good for
a-all your body functions,
really.
Did you have sex with me
instead of jogging or something?
No.
[ Laughs ]
Of course not. No.
That's not what I meant.
No, I think ... I think you're
beautiful.
Like I said [sniffles] you ...
You should just do your work.
You've got your whole life ahead
of you.
What ... what is this all
about?
Nothing.
I-I'm just tired, and...Good
luck.
[ Telephone beeps ]
[ Dial tone ]
You look like a beautiful young
woman.
Thanks.
You look good, too, mom.
You know, uh...
I am quite sure Becket is
not going to make it.
He, uh, has so much going on.
We'd go anyway, right?
[ Door closes ]
Hello?
[ Chuckles ]
I'm home.
We missed you!
Oh, oh.
[ Chuckles ]
Me, too.
Wait right there.
I have something for you.
W-W-Where are you going?
Be right back.
[ Gasps ]
I know it's not as nice as
the one you had, but I thought
you might like it.
I do.
I love it.
[ Chuckles ]
Where did you get the money
for that?
Is there something in here?
[ Chuckles ]
Once a mom, always a mom.
I got, uh, a really big
thank-you tip from the mom of my
new baby.
That's great.
Big bonus.
You deserve it.
When did this happen?
A few days ago, you said?
Yep.
Yeah, I, um ... I packed us some
snacks for our trip to Canada.
Nice.
Thanks, Sylvie.
Yeah, I kept it light, since
you're injured and all.
Just some nuts and berries and
things I thought you might like.
So nice of you, Sylv.
I-i-i-i just love the color
and everything about it.
Well, I have some good news,
too.
I picked up my car from friends
upstate, so we can take that to
Canada.
That is so perfect.
[ Fruition's "bent" plays ]
♪ Well, I'll probably sleep
in late again and not wake up
till way, way, way past noon ♪
♪ and I'll probably fall in love
again, and in the evening I'll
be howlin' at the moon ♪
♪ well, but problems, they will
follow you, so don't you stop
and think ♪
♪ just get those wheels a-movin'
till that engine starts to
stink ♪
♪ 'cause they can't catch you
if you're movin' ♪
♪ they can't find you if you're
gone ♪
♪ well, I might be bent, but I
ain't broken ♪
♪ and I might feel weak ♪
♪ but my heart is strong ♪
♪ well, they can't catch you, if
you're movin' ♪
♪ they can't find you if you're
gone ♪
♪ well, I might be bent, but I
ain't broken ♪
♪ and I might feel weak ♪
♪ but my heart is strong ♪
God, isn't it nice just to
get away from work for a little
while, take a break, go away?
Always.
I'm sorry.
I-I don't know why Sylvie wanted
to come here instead of some
place a little more Canadian.
I think she thinks this is the
kind of place you would like.
Well, I'm having a good time.
I mean, I'm dying to let all
these guys free, but I’m
enjoying the whole trip.
I missed you.
Well, it's getting late.
We should probably head home.
It's a long trek.
All right.
All righty.
Oh, I just need to stop at
the drugstore and get some
tampons and candy bars before we
go.
They're like 500 times cheaper
here in Canada.
Let's do it.
[ Rain falling ]
Oh, god.
Ugh.
Fay, you coming?
D-Did you lose something?
Oh. Uh...
All right.
Be right back.
I feel like your driver.
You want to come up here?
Sylvie rides better in the
front.
I can't stop thinking about
us.
You know, she gets pretty
carsick, so...
Let's move in together.
We already live together.
I don't want to rent a room
from you.
I want to share a room with you.
I-I don't know.
I ... what about Sylvie?
I can't do this.
I ... pretending there's nothing
between us.
I'm gon... I'm gonna have to move
out.
That's okay.
I-I understand.
All your work and everything.
I've never loved a person
more than I've loved trees
before.
I'm old.
I ... I'm a fuck-up.
I am not forgivable.
You're not a fuck-up.
You're incredible.
What's there to forgive?
Do you love me?
I think you better go back up
front.
Yes.
Sorry that took so long.
Ah, god. I love Canada.
Everything is so much cheaper.
That's excellent.
All right, I got everyone
presents.
Maple-leaf hats.
[ Chuckles ]
There's one for you.
And coffee crisp candy bars.
Let's listen to the radio.
[ Radio clicks ]
[ Heavy metal music plays ]
What do you think ... should
we turn it?
No. This is perfect.
It is?
[ Radio tuning ]
Hi.
All three of you U.S.
Citizens?
Uh, yes, sir.
Passports, please.
What's the relationship of
everybody in the car?
Uh, I'm the roommate of these
two, who are, uh, mother and
daughter.
What was the nature of your
trip into Canada today?
Just a day trip.
Sightseeing.
Shopping.
Did lots of shopping.
Everything's so fucking cheap up
here.
We shop here all the time.
Mom.
What kind of shopping?
I don't know.
What did you buy in Canada?
Just tampons and candy bars.
And medicine.
The good kind.
That's it.
Pull in over into spot number
one.
Unlock all the doors on the
vehicle.
Leave your bags and belongings
in your vehicle.
Mom, what the fuck did you
do?
What are you doing?
What's happening here?
All three of you, sit down.
[ Clears throat ]
Whose is this?
Uh, that's his.
Mine.
Whose is this?
Hers.
Describe your relationships
for me once again.
This is my daughter.
And this is Becket, our new...
Roommate.
Uh, no relation.
My daughter asked him to go to
Canada with us.
What's going on here?
Officer, my daughter bought
those drugs.
[ Scoffs ]
He had nothing to do with
this.
He had no knowledge of anything.
What?
That's a lie.
She's lying.
They're both lying.
The drugs were in his bag,
right?
Wait, what was ... what was in
my bag?
I'm sor... what's ... what's
happening?
I'll decide who's lying here.
But for right now, none of you
is going anywhere.
I can explain.
You're too good for us.
I'm so ashamed.
I hate you!
I can't believe you would do
this to me!
We had a plan!
It was your idea to use Becket,
not mine!
You need me!
I don't need you!
Can you please tell me what's
going on, fay?
They're gonna lock me up,
mom!
I'm in pain!
How am I gonna get my medicine?
[ Crying ]
[ Birds chirping ]
Can I please just have just
a minute of your time?
Please?
Against my newfound better
judgment, go ahead.
I'm sorry.
I am so sorry.
I never meant for all this to
happen.
Is any part of you real?
Were you using me the whole
time?
Am I a complete fool?
No. No, no, no.
You are not a fool.
I thought you could help Sylvie.
I was the fool.
You made me want to be a part of
the world again.
I just ... I wanted to
apologize...
And to see you again.
Hey.
What you did at the border was
brave.
I don't think I could have done
it.
I'm not even brave enough to
call my family.
You know, I just selfishly don't
stay in touch with them because
i-i-i want to pretend to be
who I want to be and not some
guy who...Is just average and...
Relates better to...Nature than
he does to human beings.
I just thought you must be
really hard-up to want to live
with us ... either that or you're
just not so lucky with the
ladies on account of your...
Naturalness.
I smell?
Oh, like low tide.
It won't smell so good, you
guys, but it's gonna make you
healthier and happier.
[ Woman speaking indistinctly on
P.A. ]
[ Sighs ]
I'm sorry, but your daughter
doesn't want any visitors.
I am not a visitor.
I made her.
This process isn't easy for
anyone ... not the patient, not
the family.
I just need to know if she
hates me.
Does she hate me?
[ Sighs ]
[ Astra via's "push/pull"
plays ]
♪ I can't see outside ♪
♪ my window ♪
♪ when I look right ♪
♪ into other people's lives ♪
♪ I look for the old familiar,
and, yes, I see it there, too ♪
♪ as I put my head to pillow,
I review the day's events ♪
♪ some are forever
forgotten ♪
♪ if you ask, I'll tell you
the rest ♪
♪ I'm the cable, you're the
track, and I feel every little
snap ♪
♪ are you pushing, are you
pulling, or are you pushing
back? ♪
♪ Who's gonna take the fall this
time? ♪
♪ Who's gonna poke themselves on
the mind? ♪
♪ I look into those people's
windows, but I pretend they
can't see me ♪
♪ watch the kids run 'round
the table ♪
♪ see them flipping through
their TV ♪
♪ I'm the cable, you're the
track, and I'm still picking up
the slack ♪
♪ are you pushing, are you
pulling, or are you pushing
back? ♪
♪ Are you pushing, are you
pulling, or are you pushing
back? ♪
♪ Are you pushing back? ♪