Next, we have the greatest
karate competition
in the State of California.
The competitors
are Bruce Lee from Seattle,
and the three-times champion
Hoffman,
a ninth Dan holder.
Ah, first time in the competition,
and you won't be winning.
Sorry.
No.
My goal is to win.
But that's too hard for you.
It's no fun if it's not hard.
Begin.
Good!
Bruce, come on!
Continue on.
Keep on. Keep on.
Hoffman, get up!
Ladies and gentlemen,
the champion in this competition
is Mr. Bruce Lee!
There he is!
Mr. Lee, is this your first time
in this kind of competition?
Oh, sir.
- Thanks.
Never participated before.
Tell us, then,
how did you beat
the third consecutive champion
who holds a ninth Dan position,
Mr. Hoffman?
Do you think it's luck?
Nothing to do with luck.
Right here. It's a strength.
One more question.
What level are you in karate?
Don't want to disappoint you,
but that wasn't karate
I used back there just now.
What you saw me do back there
to that Hoffman was kung fu.
Kung fu? What is kung fu?
It's Chinese kung fu.
Maybe you can't find it
in your dictionary,
but, today, I, Bruce Lee,
will add it to your dictionary.
Here he is, Bruce Lee.
Hey, Bruce, congratulations.
- Bruce.
Linda.
Tell me you didn't get hurt.
Oh, no. Not even a single scratch.
Great.
He must be the man
you've been telling me about.
Linda, let me introduce you
to Master James.
He's my first kung fu master.
Much like a father to me.
Bruce has often
mentioned you to me.
You should give him
more good ideas in the future.
You should take some credit
for Bruce's success today.
Thank you. But only if he can afford
to pay me a decent salary.
I've already decided
that I'll pay you with my whole life.
James, let's begin.
Okay.
I love kung fu so very much.
I've been searching
for a Chinese kung fu school
to study, and I've finally found one.
It's great.
Okay. This way, please.
Hi. May I have your name?
- Hello. Jim.
Good.
- Thank you.
Yeah. You can go in.
That Bruce Lee...
he must be out of his mind.
For so many years,
we Chinese set up
the kung fu schools in the US.
We abide by the rule
"never teach the outsiders."
Many years have passed,
and no one dared break this rule.
But this Bruce Lee
went and recruited students
using his title of karate champion.
In his school, most of the students
are either Caucasian or black
and Filipino and Japanese.
That's exactly why I'll help Master Wang,
whom we respect,
and stop Bruce Lee
in the name of Chinese kung fu.
Otherwise, our longstanding rule
of never teaching outsiders
will be destroyed by him.
The only way to stop him
is to win by fighting.
What?
What are you saying?
You know Bruce Lee?
Not only do I know him,
he and I have unfinished business.
Tø be honest,
the only reason I came here
was for Bruce Lee.
Look, Yellow.
He's beaten the karate
champion of California.
He must be extremely good.
You better be very confident
to beat him.
Don't worry, Master.
I've been working very hard in Taiwan
with only one thing in mind...
me kicking his ass.
He only uses Yong Chun Quan,
and all my techniques
are ready to beat his moves.
Now I'm worried.
He's afraid to face me.
What happens when you win?
I will follow the tradition.
Make him announce it.
Bruce Lee tells everyone
he lost to Wing Chun style.
The school will shut down.
Shifu, what are you thinking?
Nothing.
I want to remind you, on this matter,
you can't do it on your own.
If you pick a fight with him,
let me arrange it for you.
We'll do it aboveboard.
Good.
Two.
Good. Three.
Good. Let's do it together.
One, two, three!
Good. One, two, three!
This way, sir.
It's my honor to see you here, Mr. Lee.
It's my honor, Master Wang.
Please, Bruce.
Thanks for coming.
- Thank you.
Bruce, I feel so happy
that you knocked out Hoffman.
You made our Chinese
proud of ourselves.
Have a seat.
We are so proud of you.
A brilliant young man.
Bruce, I was invited to come here
to help our friends
and manage the business
of the Chinese Kung Fu Association.
I'd like for you to verify
the contents in these letters are true.
The main thing is, your school in Seattle
is a Chinese kung fu school,
which is very important.
Absolutely. It is indeed true.
However, I must say,
the students you have
are not all Chinese.
You're saying the international
students enrolled?
Yes. I've heard you've indeed
accepted many of them.
Tø be honest,
in my kung fu school,
80% of the students
are foreigners.
This is going to be a problem.
Listen to me, Bruce, many Chinese
have opened kung fu schools
to teach in America,
but none of them has done like you.
For a long time,
everyone here has been following
this unofficial rule
of teaching only Chinese students.
I invited you here for a talk today.
I hope you can correct your mistake
by expelling all the outsiders
to avoid complaints from others.
Master, these rules
don't help us develop Chinese kung fu.
If we want our kung fu to move forward,
we have to abandon these old rules.
Mr. Bruce Lee,
haven't you ever thought
about the consequences
of teaching students from other countries?
Isn't karate from Japan?
The Japanese brought it to America
and made it available to all.
You can see karate clubs everywhere.
There are national, even international
karate competitions in America.
If the Japanese had never done this,
would karate even
be popular in America?
All right, Mr. Lee. I get it.
Mr. Lee, I was trying to be nice,
but let's forget that.
Master Wang, it looks like we're...
having a Hongmen Banquet today.
Well, then, on behalf of the association,
I advise you to obey all the rules
and behave yourself.
Higher. Higher.
Your hands, higher. Higher.
Master, look.
Hello, sir. You must be sent
by Master Wang.
Yes.
On behalf of Chinese
Kung Fu Association,
here is an invitation of challenge.
A challenge?
Yes.
Now, what if I accept
the challenge I've been given?
And what if I don't? Then what?
If you accept,
there will be a winner or loser.
If you are the loser,
you will have to accept
all requirements from the association.
You have to do whatever they say.
You have two choices
from which to pick.
Either stop teaching the outsiders,
or shut down your kung fu school.
Okay, I'll accept your challenge.
Bruce Lee!
Yellow Skin. Is that you?
You didn't expect me?
It's unexpected indeed.
Bruce Lee,
doesn't matter you've defeated
Americans or Japanese.
But today, you will lose to me.
You are just a ghost.
Right. I am a ghost.
Wherever you go,
I will never leave you.
In fact, I think we came up
with a winner years ago.
Tøday, we are just going to fight,
have a competition
in front of everyone.
This way,
let everyone watch,
let them see how you will fall
right in front of me,
and that's that.
You're done.
So, then, let's fight!
Stop!
That's it!
- I'm not done yet.
I haven't lost yet.
- I said stop!
I did win, didn't I?
From now, I can teach whomever I like
and do whatever I want
with my kung fu school.
This is great.
- It's great.
Let's go.
Oh, Bruce!
Bruce!
Careful. Careful.
Bruce...
I can't fall.
I must stand up.
What did the doctor say?
We're still waiting for the result.
I will tell you as soon as we get it.
Jesse, let's go ask the doctor what's up.
All right.
- Okay. Let's go.
Linda?
Yeah?
Do I look very ugly?
No.
What did the doctor say?
He said you would be fine.
Linda?
- Yes?
Don't lie to me. Tell me the truth.
Just from their look,
I could see my injury
must be severe.
Bruce, please don't think so much.
You'll recover and be fine.
Fortunately, we still have our baby.
Bruce, don't talk so much.
Control your emotions.
He will be fine.
If our little son Brandon
saw his father like this,
I think our little Brandon
would feel very sad.
He won't be sad, Bruce.
Proud.
Doctor, please don't comfort me.
I need to know his real condition.
Please sit down, Mrs. Lee.
I don't want to waste your time.
Your husband's injury
is much worse.
Tell me if he's paralyzed forever.
Your husband's backbone
is severely injured.
I would even say shifted.
- What?
I don't care about the backbone.
I need the final result.
He will never stand up, will he?
Well, we can hardly find
any fat in his whole body,
only incredible muscles.
If he's mentally strong,
he may live in a wheelchair.
Wheelchair?
Spend his life in a wheelchair?
Like I said, Linda,
I can't even say if he can stand up,
not to mention continuing his karate
which I'm sure his body won't allow.
No. It's Chinese kung fu.
Okay. Chinese kung fu.
Is he ever gonna be able to walk?
Only if there's a miracle.
What is it, Linda?
Did the doctor tell you
when I can get rid of this
stupid, horrible equipment?
The American top doctor praised
your muscle a great deal.
And what else did they say?
The doctor said there's hardly any fat
in your body to be found.
He can't believe how strong you are.
Yes, you're injured,
but with your body's condition
and strong willpower,
it just might be a miracle.
A miracle?
Linda, don't beat around the bush.
Please tell me the truth.
You better tell me the truth now!
Bruce...
Tell me!
Bruce, listen to me.
Linda, I can handle it.
Just tell me the truth.
You should.
You should tell me the truth...
that I'll never stand up.
Right?
Bruce...
You tell me now.
Bruce, I... I...
Is it true or not?
Don't you ever,
ever come see me again.
Get out!
You get out of here!
The next couple is Bruce Lee
and Kim Jaman.
Please give them a big round of applause.
He was great.
- Notice he really mastered the steps.
The champion of the Hong Kong
Cha-Cha Competition
is the couple of Bruce Lee
and Kim Jaman.
Bruce Lee, you felt good today,
didn't you?
So what? You want to fight?
Right. I'll make
an Asian man kiss my ass.
Don't be rude.
Get him!
Come on. Let's go.
Let's get a couple of pies tonight.
You dirty Asian.
Blair, you just wait.
James.
Why'd you get up so early?
You have to go back to the U.S. Soon.
I just want to learn more moves from you
while you're in Hong Kong.
So what do you think
about that, James?
Okay. Go practice standing method.
All right.
You have to practice every morning.
Don't even miss one day.
I know that,
but I want to learn
something more practical.
You're too anxious. Relax.
Anxiety is a big mistake
when practicing kung fu.
I am anxious.
Bruce, if you really want to
master this technique for yourself,
it's not one or two days
or not even one or two years.
Besides, to have
a real perception of kung fu,
you need to have
a superb perseverance.
If you don't have that,
then you'll have nothing
when you get old.
Do you understand me?
Take it.
What's up?
What, are you waiting
for revenge or something?
Or are you waiting for my fists?
But I should warn you,
these are well-trained fists.
I've come to teach you a lesson today.
A lesson.
Then let's find a place.
Right here.
- Oh, really?
If you kick my ass,
I'll fix my bike myself.
Got it?
Are you out of your mind?
Okay. It looks like you need
another lesson from me.
Come on.
I'll let teachers and students see
how a whitey like you falls in front of me.
Get him! Come on!
- Get him!
Honey!
Bruce!
Do you see that? I'll beat him
down on the dirty ground
and let you guys step over him.
Come on!
Bruce...
There goes your children's future.
You embarrass this family!
- No. Stop. Stop. Bruce...
Bruce, just apologize
to your father. Hurry up.
Dad, why don't you listen
before you punish me?
No...
- There's no need.
I've known everything.
I told you not to fight, for God's sake,
and I swear to God,
I'll punish you if you do.
You heard me.
But I didn't promise you
I wouldn't fight today.
You bastard!
- Stop! Please stop!
Just run away, Bruce, please. Just stop it.
- All you know is fight.
Stop it! Enough! Please just go!
- Come here!
All you know is fight!
- Stop!
Stop, please!
- You're spoiled!
Dad, what's with you?
- Enough!
You can't hit Mom.
You can't ever do that to her.
It's okay, Bruce honey. It's fine.
Even if you beat me to death,
I won't run away,
even if I really want to.
You feel like it?
You dare talk back to me
after making such trouble?
Stop it!
- Bruce!
Stop beating him.
- I'm telling you...
I am telling you...
- Help us. Stop beating him.
- Okay. Dad,
- Please.
I swear to you I won't fight again.
But how can I fight back
if someone insults me?
I mean, look, son,
today you were at the school
where you picked a fight
with your own classmate Blair.
But he insulted me yesterday
on Udang Street.
Do you understand
what that feels like?
He also broke my sister's bike.
He did it on purpose,
and I didn't even pick the fight.
The bike is broken.
Dad can fix it.
Can you make no more trouble?
You must've offended him,
you see?
I didn't!
I didn't do anything wrong.
He's jealous 'cause I'm
the champion of cha-cha.
He's British,
and I'm Chinese!
I don't deserve to win the title?
Son, I'm sorry.
We are all Chinese.
We are a nation of etiquette.
Can you not learn to hold back
or be tolerant?
Dad, he called me a dirty Asian, Dad!
The son of a dirty Asian!
Why are you fighting
with your clothes?
What's with you?
What do you want?
Hey, Bruce, we better go.
Better to fight with a pro.
You are the one I want to fight.
You want to fight?
Hey, come on.
Stop there.
What was that?
Kung fu.
Go and learn some kung fu.
Kung fu?
Hoi-chuen, I'd like to tell you
that it seems like your son Bruce
has made up his mind
to learn kung fu.
Is that right?
Hoi-chuen, when you didn't
allow him to learn kung fu,
I totally agreed.
Indeed, it's hard
for kung fu artists to live.
Why bother to learn?
But I had a chat with him tonight.
And your son Bruce, you know,
the only thing
he thinks about day and night
is learning kung fu.
I'm afraid this time,
neither you nor I can sway him.
You know, the saying goes,
a father knows his son.
Let me ask you.
Do you really know him?
He's my son.
How can I not know him?
That's bull crap!
Tø be frank, Bruce is smart.
When he dedicates himself to something,
he does it completely.
When he studies it,
he learns it faster than anyone else.
That's right. For example, cha-cha.
Do you know why
he wanted to learn cha-cha?
Hoi-chuen, you don't get it.
I'll tell you why and what.
Because all those
foreign classmates
were looking down on him,
so he wanted to prove
that he could do it, too.
Yes, but my Bruce...
he never committed
to one thing whatsoever.
You see, he won
the champion of cha-cha.
Right?
- Exactly.
But now he doesn't want to continue.
This is what
you don't understand about him.
I think from now on,
we should get
a real kung fu master.
Someone to train him.
James,
if Bruce really wants
to learn kung fu,
then you'll be the best for him.
Why bother to get a master?
Tø tell you the truth, Hoi-chuen,
if Bruce is really up for kung fu,
then I can't teach him.
I'm not among the top masters
in Hong Kong.
I'd like to introduce him right away
to the head of Yong Chun
Boxing Academy, Master Ye.
It's 1:30 a.m. Already.
What the hell's going on here?
It's way too late for this.
What's wrong with him?
Let's go.
Hey, who are...
Hey, who are you?
What do you want?
- What the hell?
Hello, Master Wang.
What do you want?
I would like to practice
with Yellow Skin.
Come practice with him.
Yeah! Nice!
- That was great!
Good job!
- You got him!
Very good! Yes!
Dad.
Bruce, get your clothes and come.
I'll take you to see someone.
Come on. Follow me.
Dad, please.
Follow me. Quickly.
Faster.
Stay with me. Quickly.
Dad, what is this all about?
Bruce, you didn't give up.
Good for you.
Master Ye, I brought my son to you.
Based on your instruction,
I let him run over here
from Kingburg Park.
And my son... he made it.
Well, that's good.
Not so many people
can run such a distance in one go.
He's passed the first test
for acceptance?
All right. Come on back.
Yong Chun Quan,
created by Master Wu Mei
from Fujian.
The key thing is
it's simple and practical.
They're practicing an entree routine
called "small idea."
All right.
You guys spread out.
Small combat. Three groups.
Yong Chun Quan
requires coordination
of hands and feet,
including three-side fist...
...breakthrough fist.
The steps include clam step,
tripod step, chasing step,
and also one leg standing.
And another thing is,
what you see is striking fists.
That means you launch attack
while defending.
What he's doing is chasing step,
which requires speed and ferocity.
This is grab and strike,
used when you are close.
Yong Chun Quan is integrated
with Nanquan and close-fighting fists.
It stresses actual combat.
Shun Leung, come.
Show Bruce the inch punch.
Over here.
Get a board.
Inch punch means one burst
at all the strength to beat
his rival within an inch.
Within an inch?
That's right.
Other kung fu boxings...
the strength's from waist and arms,
while Yong Chun Quan...
the strength's from
the stroke of your whole body.
Therefore, you can strike a deadly blow
within an inch.
Come show him.
Take it.
Morning, Master.
So, did you actually
run here just now?
Yes. Based on your instructions.
10 kilometers a day...
5 coming here and 5 back home.
Good. You must keep it going.
Master, what are you
gonna teach me today?
You see the corner of the wall?
Go there and practice horse squatting.
Horse squatting?
Master, I want to learn actual combat.
Horse squatting I can do at home.
Shut up.
Go horse squatting now.
Yes, Master.
Morning, Master.
- Morning.
Master, do you mind if I practice
with my brothers today?
I've been horse squatting
for a week now.
Shun Leung, go work
on strengthening his wrists.
Let's go.
Let's go, Bruce.
Bruce, can you lift it up?
Yeah. Of course I can.
Like this?
No, not like that.
Grab it from one end
and lift evenly
while horse squatting.
Let me do it.
You see? I can lift it evenly.
Can you hold it still for an hour?
Brother, can I please skip practice
on this useless nonsense?
It's ridiculous.
I don't want to spend
my vacation this way.
You'll achieve nothing
without basic practice.
Just do what Master asks you to do.
Master, Bruce is still practicing.
Bruce, it's almost done.
Take a break now.
- Leave me alone.
It seems you think
I didn't keep my words,
didn't you?
But do you know why
I keep asking you to squat?
I guess you still don't
understand the essence of kung fu.
Essence?
What were you thinking
while horse squatting?
What could I think?
I was thinking
why you changed your mind.
What else?
Whatever you ask me, I'll do it.
Don't worry, Master.
I'll keep horse squatting
well till you say so.
Yes, Bruce,
you've wasted time so far.
Lots of time.
Why? I don't understand.
Do you know why you have to squat?
Master James told me
that horse squatting is practice.
Can't learn kung fu
without practicing.
So I'm practicing.
I thought you'd teach me the real thing
sooner or later.
If you want me to lift the pole forever,
I'll just do it.
So Master James
has taught you the importance
of horse squatting.
However, you didn't get
the core of it, you see?
Horse squatting is a basic skill
for all kung fu artists to master first.
Horse squatting is not only
for strengthening your legs,
but more importantly,
it is to strengthen your mind.
The key of kung fu training
is to train your mind.
Train your mind
is to strengthen your mind and spirit.
What, squatting can train your mind?
That's right, Bruce. You're too anxious.
What's vital to kung fu training
is to make both your body and mind
as calm as still water.
A calm mind can reach
a thousand miles away.
A thousand miles away.
While you're horse squatting,
you're like a tree.
Just imagine yourself
as a big tree reaching the sky.
No matter how tall it is,
it stands on its root, you know?
So your entire body and mind
should take root
into the earth under your feet.
The deeper your root gets,
the better your kung fu is.
Kung fu training means
to build yourself up
from the inside out.
That eventually integrates
with all creatures on earth.
If you can reach this level,
your entire body and mind
will then turn into water...
from a big tree to water
which can infiltrate to everything on earth.
At that time,
you will reach an even higher level
of kung fu training.
Only when you integrate yourself
into water consciously,
or unconsciously,
can your body and mind integrate
into the earth beneath you.
Only by then can you get the true spirit
of kung fu.
Master is back.
Master.
- Master.
Keep practicing.
Did you ask him
to lift two poles together?
No. He did it himself.
I've been out so long.
Has he been doing it?
Absolutely.
It's been the whole day.
Good boy.
He has the makings of a kung fu artist.
Originally, he didn't like
this kind of boring stuff.
But he did it against your will.
What a character.
Mind your posture.
Looks good.
Master.
Bruce,
from now on,
you may practice
with your elder brother
and see how that feels.
Really? That's awesome!
Go. Practice over there. Just go.
Thanks, Master.
Slow down. Don't drag me.
- Hurry up.
Why did you take me here
in the early morning?
Do you want to get beaten again?
- Hey, you go in there.
Think of a way to get Yellow Skin out.
Aw, Bruce,
I can't help you this time.
You've just recovered.
You can't do anything...
but get beaten up all day.
You go in now.
Okay. I know.
Go in!
- Okay, I'll go.
What should I tell him, huh?
Just tell him his rival is here.
What did you say?
Whose rival is he?
- Of course it's yours.
It's mine?
I might like to learn
a few tricks from you.
It seems I didn't kick you
hard enough last time.
Tøday would you like me
to break your ribs
or your legs first?
What if I broke your ribs
or your legs?
What, then?
Then I'll say you're great.
Come on.
Hey, Bruce, why do you
ask for trouble?
Leave me alone.
Just kick.
Kick, you idiot.
Shun Leung, begin.
Right away.
Yes, Master.
Jun Lee, you'll be defending.
Come here.
Master.
Bruce.
Well, you two go get ready.
Make sure to go beyond that.
Get it? Ready? Begin.
Bruce, when fighting
with Yong Chun Quan,
don't stick to the rules and tricks.
Fight whatever you feel like.
Billy, go on.
Good job.
Way to go.
Brother, are you okay?
No. You've used inch punch.
I did it involuntarily.
Wow. You did it in such a short time.
Really awesome.
- You got it.
Good job.
Bruce, although you just fought
with the inch punch,
your level of skill wasn't good enough.
Little did your brother expect
you could learn do it
in such a short time.
He underestimates you.
That made you a very lucky guy.
But, Bruce,
you can't always count
on luck to save you all the time.
Yes. I didn't expect it, either.
I think Bruce's punches
are quite powerful now.
Bruce, to learn a certain boxing,
action is the foundation.
Your brother has taught you about it.
But you want to make it perfect.
You have to put
your whole heart into it,
and it takes a long time to master it.
Get the board. Give her a try.
Try this.
Okay.
Get more strength.
You see, you've got the essentials
of the inch punch.
But to smash the board
with one punch
is not training you can do in one day.
What you're learning
now, Bruce, see,
is real kung fu.
The rules of action, hands and steps
will be of less importance.
If keeping practicing, everyone can get it.
Tø simply put, get power from feet
and punch out from the heart,
attack whenever you can,
and defend each inch of land.
Again, simply put,
you get power from feet,
punch out from the heart,
and simply attack when you can,
and defend each inch of land!
Get power from your feet
and punch out from the heart,
attack whenever you can,
and defend each inch of land.
It's like a kid holding a concave mirror
to emblaze paper with collected sunlight.
The theory is that the concave mirror
converges sunlight to one final point, no?
Which emblazes things.
I got it, Master.
Also, utilize the power
of your opponent.
- You mean
utilizing the rival's power
to get back and attack him
quickly enough to save our energy.
You'll understand it more
when thinking about it.
I believe in your perception.
The core of real kung fu
is that while attacking,
you should focus all your power
on one point and attack in a second.
While defending,
eliminate the rival's attack
and turn your defense mode to offense
with the suddenness of a thunderbolt!
You have to reach the unity
of offense and defense,
the harmony of yin and yang.
This is the level you should achieve
when fighting with Yong Chun Quan.
In other words,
your attack includes defense,
and within your defense,
hides offense.
The speed and skill
of the transition between the two
is what kung fu artists
need to master.
Prepare.
Bruce, I always admired you as a man,
and you're a hero in my heart,
but now... you're different,
and I thought...
you have a side of weakness
and cowardice.
But we can't do anything about it.
You're Bruce Lee.
Find a way to make it work.
You see?
You won't be beaten by anyone.
You will bounce back.
We can do this, Bruce.
Tøgether we can overcome anything.
Will you let me help you, Bruce?
We'll do this together.
Bruce, I love you.
No matter when the miracle's
coming, okay,
I promise to stay by your side.
But you must stay strong, Bruce,
and we'll face the problem together.
I trust you, Bruce.
Okay?
Linda,
I understand what you mean.
Let American doctors'
diagnosis go to hell.
I refuse to let it happen to me.
Trust me.
- I know.
I swear I'll make the miracle happen.
I won't let anybody down like this.
I won't.
I believe in you, sweetheart.
I believe in you.
James,
Kimura,
I'm sorry.
What are you guys doing here?
Master Wang.
What in the hell
are you guys doing here, huh?
Haven't you put Bruce's life
in enough danger?
What else do you want anyway?
But, please. Master James,
we mean no harm.
We heard Bruce's injury is quite severe.
We're extremely worried.
We are here to see him.
Mr. Lee, how are you feeling?
Good or bad?
You can tell with your own eyes.
Yes, yes.
The things that happened
were totally unexpected.
What Yellow Skin has done to you
is surely unforgivable.
He's already been dismissed.
You guys can feel at ease.
Happy Yellow Skin left?
Master Wang, what you did
is very smart.
Mr. Lee, you misunderstand.
I truly feel terrible
for such an accident.
These past couple of days,
my colleagues and I
have been thinking.
We are all Chinese
who live in a foreign country.
Why can we not
negotiate it peacefully
rather than end up like this?
We are responsible.
Therefore,
I have discussed it
with all of the Chinese
kung fu colleagues in California,
and we are here
on behalf of the association
to apologize to Mr. Lee.
Master Wang,
all of you,
I, Bruce Lee,
don't deserve this.
All of you, please rise.
Just for what Master Wang has said,
we are all Chinese.
I forgive you.
I won't blame you.
Bruce is right. You can stand now.
Master Wang, please rise.
Linda, go help him up.
Mr. Wang, please, stand up.
James, Kimura,
please help Master Wang up.
Master Wang, we Chinese
have a very low social status
in foreign countries.
They call us "Asian sick men"
or "yellow dogs with pigtails."
How dare they treat us like this?
'Cause we don't bond together.
Rather, we fight amongst ourselves.
If we stop fighting each other
and never create chaos within us,
I will be grateful,
even if I never stand up again.
Please, Master Wang.
Please stand up.
Bruce Lee,
you are a true master.
One, two,
three...
Bruce...
Bruce, love, you're done.
You don't have to do any more.
I can do it.
Your determination's
three times stronger than others'
No problem.
Go ahead.
Bruce, be careful.
How is it? Can you keep going?
Is that okay?
How are you feeling?
Look. You're doing it.
Good job.
Are you feeling okay? Does that hurt?
- You know what?
Does that hurt?
Does it hurt?
So the physical therapy works.
- Bruce, you're doing great.
I think your legs are recovering.
What are you doing?
Just a little more. Drink it.
Just drink it. Drink it all.
All of it.
I'm so useless. I got your clothes dirty.
Doesn't matter, Mr. Lee.
You know what?
If your positive energy
travels to the injured area,
it'll beat negative energy.
First, you must keep
taking herbal medicine.
Meanwhile, the doctors suggest
you start with acupuncture treatment.
This will connect your meridian
and boost the blood
circulation in your body.
The key of Chinese acupuncture...
- Oh, I see.
...isn't just healing whatever
goes wrong in the body.
Instead, it cures...
by way of conditioning
the relationship
between body and mind, you see?
You're starting to finally get it.
Overall concepts.
Yes?
Actually, kung fu also requires
the overall concept.
For example,
when attacking and defending,
it's important
to coordinate the whole body
so you can better
play the role of Yong Chun Quan.
You're so crazy about kung fu
that everything has to relate to it.
I remembered a competition.
What about it?
I realized that Chinese wushu
has a drawback in actual combat.
For example, both Hong Quan
you taught me,
and Master Ye's Yong Chun Quan
have some disadvantages
in real-world fighting.
Yeah, I hear what you're saying.
I think the traditional kung fu styles,
its movements and patterns
are all outdated,
and with no innovation.
I want to...
I want to empty the glass.
This way, I can fill it up again.
This is what I'm thinking.
Empty the glass...
and then refill it.
You're... You're talking about
enlightenment.
These days,
since I'm not able
to move around much at all,
I have time to think
about those problems
and the kung fu theories.
I just spend time
emptying my own glass.
You know what I mean, Dad?
I believe I will fill it with what I need.
Learning kung fu
will influence our thought and lifestyle.
The training you get from
certain masters or a school,
you still won't get developed fully
even though you may reach
to its highest level.
If you follow the traditional model,
all you learn is the old routines.
In kung fu training,
we don't want to be limited
by any school or tradition.
The core of kung fu
is freedom.
Daddy's here.
Come on, son. Let Daddy hold you.
Come on, son. Let me hold you.
- We won't let you.
Son, give Daddy a smile.
We can show Daddy your trick.
We'll show it to you.
- Come on, son.
Right. Okay. Here we go.
Right there.
- Son, come over here.
Oh, Daddy.
Come here, son. Come.
Here we go.
- Come. Come.
Hey, be careful.
You scared Daddy.
Bruce... Bruce, you're standing.
Linda, it's Brandon
that made me stand up.
Oh, sweetheart.
Give me the baby.
Okay. I'm so excited.
Oh, it's wonderful. I'm so proud.
Yes, it is very good. Let's take a walk.
I stood up because of Brandon.
I never expected this.
- You can walk.
Yes, I can walk.
Hey, Bruce, did you read
today's newspaper?
Don't you know what the article
"The Miracle Return of Bruce Lee"
means to us?
The enrolling students
are beyond capacity.
Bruce, did you hear what he said?
Usually, Kimura is such a slow coach.
He jumped on the news today
and came to tell you right away.
You know, I knew this day would come.
Master, Bruce Lee
dares to show his kung fu
at our arena.
Is Bruce Lee gonna perform?
Yes. I just came from the committee.
The clerk told me.
The opportunity's here.
I'll be known in Seattle.
I'll win and make this arrogant brat
unable to stand up before everyone.
So you mean to say
we'll challenge him?
Whether it's a challenge or not,
you just wait and see
the good show I put on.
Hey, now!
You are going to know the hero of Seattle.
My man. That's who.
In front of you, you, you, you and you,
5,000 years of history
will be displayed.
That's right. Come on. Follow me.
You're really awesome.
How did you beat me just now?
What I use is Chinese kung fu.
Great. Great, man.
Who are you? Give your name.
I'm Yamamoto.
I have waited so long,
and now you've showed up.
It's a good opportunity.
Bruce Lee, you can fight in any style.
I've heard that you're arrogant.
You said you didn't have
an equal in Seattle, didn't you?
Didn't you?
That's right. I said this.
Well,
I really want you to see
how I'll teach you a lesson,
you arrogant China boy.
Okay. Come on.
Brat, you're quite flexible.
Come on. Again.
Bruce Lee, now you've got an idea
what Japanese karate is like.
In Seattle, there is no place for you.
None for you!
Bruce! Bruce, calm down!
Kimura, these days, a demon
has been bothering me a lot lately.
This demon... is he Yamamoto?
Yes.
Yamamoto's a well-known karate master
in Japan and America.
He pays great attention to his training.
He's opened karate clubs
in many places in the U.S.,
but mostly he's keen on teaching
rather than competing.
I don't really get it.
Why is he able to build
such a solid foundation?
Probably it has something
to do with the iron man.
Iron man? What do you mean?
I've just heard of it.
But I've never seen it myself.
His students told me
that he fights every day
with a big iron man twice his size.
I've never heard of this kind of thing.
Well, I'd like to meet
this Yamamoto again.
Well, if it isn't Bruce Lee.
Am I not welcome?
I didn't teach you
a good lesson last time.
Aren't you asking for trouble?
Bruce Lee, you are such a nuisance.
I don't intend
on spying on your training.
I've just come to deliver
my challenge invitation.
You don't have the eligibility.
I have.
Get lost.
Bring it on.
Bruce?
Where's Bruce?
- Where could he be?
Could he be at school training?
No. I just came back
from there. He wasn't there.
Oh, God.
I bet he went to visit Yamamoto.
We should go.
Don't come back!
Let's go.
- Are you okay?
Bruce, you're not sleepy?
I can't sleep.
If I don't go compete
with various masters,
how would I know the core
of their exquisite skills?
Kimora, I want to set up my own style.
Your own style?
That's right. My own style.
Well, that's not easy.
When I was little,
I learned from Master James
Tang Lang Quan, Shaolin Quan,
Hong Quan, Chang Quan,
and many other styles.
Later on, I learned from Master Ye
his Yong Chun Quan.
And after that, I felt Yong Chun Quan
was the most powerful one
in the world.
Later on, I joined
on the Western boxing team
and found there was something
useful as well.
Now I realize some secret tricks
in Japanese karate.
Oh, right.
More and more,
I feel that each style
has its own advantage
and disadvantage
which can be studied and utilized.
Now, I haven't known
enough boxing styles,
but I believe that through
my studying and research
of the various boxing styles,
I can improve Yong Chun Quan
and make it a more practical one.
Improve Yong Chun Quan?
Right.
Bruce, why don't we sit down
with Professor Klein
and discuss it further,
creating a new way for kung fu together?
- You got it.
Good.
UNIVERSITY OF WASHING TON
Professor Klein,
I know that I have to learn
a lot of knowledge about martial arts.
I need to understand the essences
of various schools...
analyzing, comparing,
and doing research.
And for achieving my goal,
I have no better way
but to compete
with those masters from each school.
That way, I can discover
which school is practical and which is not.
You know what, Bruce Lee?
Rodin once said,
"It's not a lack of beauty in life
but the eyes to discover."
In your case, it means
it's not a lack of master of martial arts
but the eyes to discover.
You may have to compete
with yourself after all.
Compete with myself?
- Yes.
One's biggest rival is none but himself.
I guess you've chosen a philosophy major,
which is the best way to find out
how to compete with yourself.
And what's more,
my understanding of martial arts
is that it isn't just
for building up your body,
nor competing with your rival.
The biggest benefit
for studying martial arts
is probably a way
of an appreciation of cultures.
Young man, you should make
the best use of your time
to study and figure out how to create
your own theory for martial arts.
I believe that you have such potential.
Our jujitsu is the most
powerful skill of combat.
No other combat styles can defeat us.
Come over.
Aim it. Come on.
Make him unbalanced at first.
And then it'll be easier.
This is called defending with one blow.
Yong Chun Quan has its strong points
and its limitations, too.
Are you still thinking
about Willy Jay's jujitsu?
We should learn anything
useful to us.
Well, let's send him
a challenge invitation.
I have a challenge invitation that says
Bruce Lee wants to compete with me.
Bruce Lee wants to compete
with you now?
I bet he doesn't want to lose his ribs.
James, I don't understand all this.
Bruce Lee is such a small
and slim guy at only 140 pounds.
I mean, I won't waste more time on this.
Where will it take place?
In a public venue.
You're competing in a public venue?
I've never heard of such a thing.
Yeah, he's crazy.
I think he's too arrogant.
Completely arrogant.
Only a maniac would take
his own life lightly.
Don't you think?
- James, what do you want to talk about?
Well, it's about the match.
There's gonna be
a supervisor there officiating.
Who?
Inosando.
That guy.
He's a professor at a sports college.
Right. Right.
You know what? He's famous for
the "King of Filipino Stick."
Really? It sounds great.
Mr. Willy Jay.
- Hello, Mr. Lee.
After you.
Come.
Tøday, the master
of Bruce Lee Kung Fu Club,
Mr. Bruce Lee,
will challenge Mr. Willy Jay,
the master of Willy Ja Jujitsu Club.
As the host of this game today,
I'd like to invite Professor Inosando
from the Sport Academy
to be our supervisor.
The rule of the game is
as long as one party makes the other
unable to stand up again,
he declares victory.
Both parties get ready.
Is that clear?
Professor Inosando.
Are you ready?
Now begin.
Yeah!
Go on. Go on with it.
This is Bruce Lee's fight.
Your jujitsu is really powerful.
Thank you, Mr. Lee.
You didn't make a fool of me
in front of everybody.
I knew you showed me some mercy,
allowing me to have the upper hand.
I knew it, Mr. Lee.
And even if you went all the way,
maybe I couldn't keep my feet.
And also, you dominated me
when falling to the ground.
If you'd used the eyeball trick,
I'd have been blinded already.
I think I understand what you want
isn't for winning or losing
but to get to know me,
or I'll say to improve your skills
by learning from my jiujitsu.
Is that right?
Correct. You've got it.
Now, I try to compete
with various masters.
My goal isn't for winning
but to improve my kung fu
to a higher level.
So I hope you can help me,
Master Willy Jay.
I appreciate it.
It's my honor to teach you
my jujitsu, Mr. Lee.
Thank you.
Thank you so much, Master Jay.
Class is dismissed.
Bruce! Bruce, the professor is here.
Professor Inosando.
We've met before.
Yes.
I just want to know,
when you were competing
with Willy Jay,
why did you hold back?
I don't want to just beat Willy Jay
and lose the chance to learn
and study jujitsu together with him.
Would you please
give me a chance like that?
You're too humble.
I've heard you're a great martial artist
with high achievements.
I haven't had a chance to learn from you.
- Flattering.
Okay, well, watch out.
You're indeed fast.
Let's see who's faster.
Thanks for the opportunity.
I admit defeat.
You're too modest.
Professor Ino,
I feel that Filipino boxing
is quite flexible,
with rapid speed
and the various changes,
but it is not powerful enough.
Yong Chun Quan's key
is simple and direct.
It requires you to launch attack
while defending yourself.
This is the crucial characteristic of it.
But there are weaknesses
in its footwork.
It's quite useful at a closer distance,
but it doesn't work well
between the middle to long range.
Kimura, I'd like to promote
our kung fu club
in a really big way in the community.
I still truly believe in the importance
of exchanging ideas
with different schools.
But how?
Breaking into their schools?
Well, come.
It's not a good idea
to challenge them at their door.
I suppose it'll be better
to ask for them to challenge us here
rather than we go to their door.
What are you dreaming again?
When you compete
with others in our club,
if you happen to lose
before our students,
it would be a shame.
My goal is to set up
a new style of boxing.
I don't care about winning or losing.
It's worth it even if I lose.
All right? Like this.
Write it down.
No matter, whenever,
wherever, and whoever
wants to challenge me,
I'm going to accept it.
Looks like Bruce Lee
is going to challenge...
the Americans.
Bruce Lee is challenging
the whole field of martial arts in America.
Bruce Lee has put up a sign
at the gate of his club,
saying anyone at any time at any place
wants to challenge him,
he's ready to accept.
Bruce is too damn arrogant.
He's out of his mind.
He had some nerve to come
and challenge me in my home.
So he came up with such an idea?
I'll smash his kung fu club.
Did you hear me?
What are you doing here?
Hello, Mr. Yamamoto.
I'm glad you're here to instruct me.
I'm only here
to see your kind of boxing.
I've been wanting
to learn from you, Master.
Thank you for paying me a visit.
I'm so thrilled to see you.
I'm warning you right now,
there is no place
for you in America, Bruce Lee.
You can't be so arrogant.
Whether I'm arrogant or not,
we'll find out after the match.
If you lose the game today,
you have to be my coach,
and I'll teach you Yong Chun Quan
and some other things.
You teach me?
Only if you beat me
will I accept any of your requests.
Come on.
- Good. Come on.
Master, my apologies.
Mr. Yamamoto.
You've made your promise,
and I really hope you can keep it, okay?
I'll visit you in a couple of days
to see how you're feeling.
Jesse, please put up the sign again.
- Sure.
Here's $20.
I'll bring the ice bucket back
a little later.
Come on, guys.
Let's get ready for class.
Tell us about your matches.
- Yeah.
Bruce Lee.
Have some ice.
- Okay.
I've met a real master.
You don't have to do that.
I just wanted to cool you down.
If you can beat me,
I'll cool down immediately.
Do you have any idea
how this will finish?
Of course. Only one of us
will walk outta here.
If that is the case,
why do you want to act
like a fool right now?
If I don't accept your challenge,
I'll be the idiot.
Bruce, forget it.
Tell them to leave.
Kimura, please take them out.
Let's go. Everyone. All of you.
You're a one-armed martial artist.
Your kung fu is really good.
Why don't you compete?
It's pretentious and makes me sick.
Cool guy.
I'm giving you a little lesson.
No one should ever be that arrogant.
Hey.
Bruce!
Bruce, did he hurt you?
He's smarter than me.
Master, can you beat him?
Bruce, what did he say to you?
Yong Chun Quan
has many advantages
as well as disadvantages.
I want to integrate the hand techniques
and footwork of jujitsu
into Yong Chun Quan.
I will also combine the footwork
of Western boxing with it.
After this improvement,
Yong Chun Quan will absorb the essence
of many other boxing techniques
and will eliminate the complicated
and unpractical stuff.
A new boxing style. Good paper.
Professor Klein,
do you see any problems with it?
I'm really pleased
to see the progress you've made.
Remember, I told you not long ago,
you should defeat yourself.
The biggest enemy is... yourself.
So now I see you have
revised your view on it.
But, still, there are a lot
of unanswered questions.
Please, have a seat.
Go ahead. Sit down.
Professor Klein,
I've been troubled by them for a while.
Oh, Bruce Lee, you are now quite clear
about the innovation of your new style.
You've used the power
your rival attacked you
to counterattack him.
As for the boxing,
it is your way of attacking.
As for styles,
there are too many variations, correct?
Bruce Lee, you must realize that the new
style that must be established...
Whoa. Hold on.
On the basis of Chinese philosophy,
will keep developing.
The new style created
is based on Chinese kung fu,
Both the Confucianism and Daoism
have influenced Chinese kung fu
tremendously.
The Confucianism
values harmony and moderation,
while the Daoism
focuses on dialectics and perception.
So, you can learn a lot
from other schools
and transplant them onto
the tree of Chinese kung fu.
I think you should aim the core of kung fu
and simplify them.
I get it. But, Professor...
It's important for you to always simplify
everything you do, Bruce.
Simplify? So what should I do
to simplify the theories?
Now, what I'd like to know is,
what is the simplest issue
of the kung fu theories?
Please tell me.
It should be offense and defense.
How very smart.
Please take a look
at this dialectic picture.
It consists of persuasive colors.
This is a simple way
to make it easy and clear.
Professor Klein, so keep it simple then?
Right. You've got to study
to keep it simple,
and then you have more freedom.
I must free myself and be relaxed,
simplifying everything,
eliminating the unnecessary,
freeing myself from the shackles
of complication.
Right you are. You said that perfect.
But when you relax yourself,
you free yourself
and control your own life.
Whoever can control the initiative
of the transformation...
he will find himself definitely.
Thank you, Professor.
Kung fu is a special skill,
an exquisite form of art,
but not a simple physical exercise.
It is a kind of art that must combine
wisdom and techniques together.
The principle of kung fu
is to utilize your body and mind effectively.
Yin Yang Tai Chi stands as
the highest of achieved states,
which indicates the essence
of everything in the universe.
As for kung fu theory,
Yin Yang Tai Chi simplifies
the complicated kung fu
theory into two words:
"Defense" and "offense."
In order to reach
the highest state of kung fu,
you must eliminate
all the extraneous elements
to reach and maintain the essence
of fighting within the shortest time.
In fact, it's a kind of
one-two punch, if you will,
that is very practical in combat
rather than those elaborate slick moves.
Meaning, it turns the intangible
into something tangible.
Jeet Kune Do doesn't have
any fixed set form
which, in turn, is the best form.
It doesn't belong to any schools,
so it's free to use anything from them
without any limitation and forms.
It's good at using all skills and techniques
which serve their own purpose.
Instinctive defense
with well-established offense
is the most straightforward definition
of Jeet Kune Do.
How many students do you have now?
No more than 200,
with four different training sessions.
This is the evening class.
They're doing their drills right now.
Bruce, let's talk about
the American fighting competition.
I think you should take
some time to recover better.
Don't rush.
- No. I feel fine now.
Professor, come on.
Help me analyze. How can I win
the U.S. Championship?
Bruce, okay.
I'll give you my opinion then.
Actually, this time,
only three of the fighters
will be competitive:
Rolex, you, and Piao Zhengyi.
And Rolex looks the best here.
And, Master Lee, you can only win
if you have an exchange,
you see, with Master Piao.
All right. I may go
see him right away then.
Hey, what's up?
I want to see your master,
Piao Zhengyi.
My master can't see anyone.
Whether he likes it or not,
I must see him now.
Master.
Master Piao, sorry to interrupt you.
I heard that you have competed
in the U.S. Karate competition,
and you're honored as a genius
of Tae Kwon Do.
But as far as I know,
you're still not able to rival Rolex.
If you want to defeat Rolex at all,
I think you and I should try
to have an exchange.
Who are you?
Bruce Lee.
Correct. You heard right. Bruce Lee.
What qualifications do you have
to walk into my dojo?
Now, you're looking down upon me,
which I understand.
You are the famous genius
of Tae Kwon Do.
But I, Bruce Lee... I'm nobody here.
Let me tell you, if you compete with me,
I will take you down on the ground
within three rounds.
I promise you that.
Stop.
Ready? Continue.
Bruce Lee wins.
Now, in the final round
of the Karate Competition begins.
Let's welcome Mr. Bruce Lee
from Oakland
with a big round of applause.
Now, presenting the champion
of the last National Karate Competition,
Mr. Rolex.
Please give him a round of applause.
Begin.
Yes!
One, two, three.
Game's over.
I am Chinese!
Mr. Rolex, will you please tell us
about your feelings about this match?
Please tell us.
It's really hurt my whole career.
I don't understand
how Bruce Lee could strike me.
What's more, when I hit on his fist,
my fist turn powerless all of a sudden.
But I believe he hasn't
tried hard on his three kicks.
- That was amazing.
He has amazing power.
- Thank you very much.
He should be the winner.
Thank you.
An amazing scene just took place here
at the National Karate Competition.
We have never seen anything like it.
A young man from China
has completely rewritten the way we fight.
Journalists cannot figure out...
Okay, that's all for today.
You may leave now, everyone.
It's good. It's absolutely amazing.
It looks like you have some regrets.
What are you thinking?
What a pity. I...
I should've gone to watch him
fight in the stadium.
We should go visit this
Chinese guy Bruce Lee maybe.
He's a Chinese hero, in fact.
We should go visit him.
Well, Mr. Harrison, I've got an idea.
Hollywood needs this kind of action hero.
George,
I have to say you are
a brilliant businessman.
Yeah? I hope so.
Bruce Lee. Well, well, well.
Hey, hello, Mr. Lee.
- Hi. Hello.
We're here to congratulate you.
We've been waiting for you for a while.
- What...
Come on. You've never heard of him before?
You're kidding me, right?
He's with Robert.
Big Hollywood producer of stars.
Very important man.
Let's go and talk to him.
James?
Sure you should go. Go see him.
Okay. I'll go.
It can't be bad that someone
from Hollywood asked to meet Bruce.
Let's go wait for the good news.
Let me introduce you.
This is George from Hollywood.
Hello, Mr. Lee.
I've been watching you for a long time.
What can I do for you
this afternoon?
Well, but, of course,
with your specific permission,
I'd like to make a movie
of your great performance.
Why?
I saw you win the championship on TV.
I admire your
kung fu skills very much.
Your movements were so fast
in the game,
I'd like to record it for other players.
But my real purpose,
to be honest with you,
is to work together
in some other field someday.
You mean, shooting movies?
Yes. Kung fu movies.
You have a chance
to showcase your work in Hollywood.
What better way to showcase
your kung fu performance?
Well, this is not a bad idea.
You persuaded me.
Ah, that's great, Mr. Lee.
Wouldn't you say we have a deal
between us, don't you think?
All right. I'll listen to you.
That's great.
We should have a drink
to celebrate, don't you think?
Sounds good.
- Let's go.
That's great.
Mr. Kato's appearance
definitely gives us a fresh impression.
Mr. Kato, you're a great warrior
nobody can match.
Don't you understand?
Wearing the mask will only
boost your charm as a warrior
and show a kind of mysterious style.
You may choose whatever you like
from all these masks
we prepared for you here.
George, so you're still planning
on using a mask to cover my face?
Listen, it's not about your face.
Warriors have been known
to often wear masks.
After putting on the mask,
you will show a special characteristic.
And so I hope you will wear the mask.
It's really up to you.
Maybe you'll be amazed
and even like it.
Mr. Lee,
the masks I've created for you
are to enhance your mysterious style.
Okay. I know.
You look great.
George, how do I look?
How do you like it?
Well, then, this time,
I don't want to argue with you
because I like this film
and this character.
But there's one thing you must
listen to me on, George.
Right now.
- What?
I want to use kung fu.
- Wait, wait, wait.
You must Jeet Kune Do.
Use Jeet Kune Do.
- All right.
Right. Great, then. That's it.
- Thank you.
Okay, sounds good.
All right, everybody.
Let's welcome back Bruce Lee.
We're all ready to go.
Welcome.
Come on now, people.
Come on now. Hurry.
Action!
I'll ask you the last time.
Where is the recipe of the Green Hornet?
- Okay, okay.
I'll never tell you.
So you're not gonna tell us,
is that right?
No, no, no.
Let's kill him another way.
Okay, cut!
Hey, Director, why did you stop?
Why not keep going naturally?
What the hell's going on here?
I just got started
on the whole routine with these guys.
Bruce, that was perfect.
That's exactly what I wanted.
It was just great.
You were being irresponsible.
How come I haven't even hit them,
and they've all fallen down?
- Bruce, man...
Stand up. Stand up.
Hey, Director Huang.
Yeah, he's Bruce Lee.
You know, champion
of the Cha-cha Competition
of Hong Kong High School.
You know. Yes, that's him.
He's also the champion of the Hong Kong
High School Boxing Competition.
He played in several movies
when he was a kid.
The one in the film
Xi Lu Xiang. That's right.
You have to keep Bruce Lee here.
With him, we'll have hope yet.
Hi!
How are you, Linda?
- Hello, Miss Shen. You came so fast.
Well, you know, I didn't waste a minute.
After I hung up the phone with Bruce,
I just rushed right over here.
Well, Bruce is waiting for you.
Oh, okay. Great.
- All right. Come on in.
Thanks.
Nice place.
Bruce.
Hi, Minzhi. Come in. Have a seat.
- Hello, Bruce.
I've gone through the contract.
Everything looks good so far.
Basically, I'll agree to it.
However, one more thing, though.
I'd really like
to read the script first, if I could.
I have brought it with me.
Here.
Good.
If everything is okay with it,
I can sign it right away.
Bruce, to be honest,
I just talked to Mr. Xu on the phone.
He actually mentioned to me
even to postpone for another six months.
He will work with you on this movie.
The Big Boss.
What kind of story is it?
Tell me more about it.
- Well,
The Big Boss screenplay
is actually based on a true story.
The main character, Zheng Chao-an...
he's from mainland China.
During the end of the 19th
and early 20th century,
he was the leader
for Chinese in Thailand.
Due to his resistance
of the local triad,
for many Chinese laborers,
he became their hero.
Those overseas Chinese
called him "the Big Boss."
There's a wonderful statue
of him in Bangkok.
Have you seen it?
Good.
Someone like me who lives abroad
understands well how difficult it is
for us Chinese to survive here.
I can fully understand
the main character's feelings.
I'm exactly like him.
Therefore, no one else
could play it better than me.
I like this kind of story.
I'm willing to sign your contract.
Scene 96. Shot 12. Action!
Play. Play.
- Good! Get him!
Quiet. Quiet.
What?
Good! Good move!
Good. Continue.
Good!
Bruce!
Action.
You know, my opinion,
this script is too unbelievable.
What?
Because I can hardly put it down.
I've read it three times in one sitting.
Even at midnight, I woke up my wife
and told her that this...
this is the best script I've ever read
since I started producing films.
Boss, you scared me.
I thought you didn't like it.
I didn't like it? If I didn't like it,
I'd be the biggest idiot
in the Hong Kong film industry.
Good. Let's get started.
You can count on me.
I'll try my best.
Ready. Scene 22. Shot 16. Take one.
Action!
Cut!
It was great! Wonderful!
Right. Wow. Wow.
Thank you, George.
Thanks so much.
Darling.
- Bruce, you're fantastic.
Everyone, great job. Fabulous.
Director, like us?
- You were great, Bruce.
Let's...
Let's take a break.
Bruce! Bruce!
Bruce! Somebody get
a doctor or something.
I reviewed all these reports.
The problem is...
Sorry. Doctor?
Mr. Lee, what's the problem?
I'm sorry, Doctor.
I've been in the hospital for a week.
I've just been wondering how come
there is still no diagnosis yet?
Mr. Lee, we're studying
your reports right now.
We're looking very closely at them.
Have you come to a conclusion?
The other reports
won't come in till tomorrow.
We have to wait for all of them
before we can reach any conclusion.
What's your projection?
Mr. Lee, you're 32, right?
What do you mean?
We can hardly believe
that there isn't any fat in your body.
Your body is just like
a large piece of steel.
Doctor, whatever it is,
you should know.
You can tell me frankly.
I'll know when I see all the results.
This isn't guesswork.
Well, I think when Bruce goes back
to the States for the movie premiere,
it shouldn't be a problem.
Okay. Okay.
Bye-bye.
Come in.
Hey, Bruce.
Mr. Xu.
Bruce, aren't you supposed
to be at the hospital?
Why did you come here?
I'm not sick. Why should I have to stay
in the hospital any longer?
Are you really all right?
- I'm fine. Look at me.
Nothing's wrong.
- That's great, Bruce.
Let me tell you, George just called,
and he said the Hollywood gurus
loved Enter the Dragon after the screening.
You made it again.
- Yeah.
This is exactly
what we expected, right?
This time, it's even better, you see?
The Hollywood side
has just decided to have
the premiere in August, in L.A.
They invited you to go back
for the premiere.
I think this is your good chance
to rise as an international superstar,
which is a big deal.
And... therefore,
I've accepted for you.
Well, Mr. Xu, this is my plan
for shooting Game of Death.
I want you to take a look first.
Tell me what you think.
What I mean is,
you should take a few months off.
We'll wait until after.
And...
- No, no, no, no, no.
Let's shoot right away.
Feeling strong enough?
Are you, Bruce?
If there is no problem, I'd really like
to start working on it
in three days, if that's okay.
Are you sure?
You're in good shape?
Mr. Xu, for this film, I'd like to invite
several world-class martial artists
and celebrities to join me.
For example, Inosando,
the " Nunchakus
King of the Philippines."
He's an amazing martial artist.
Their participation will surely make
our film more fun to watch.
Okay.
Bruce, you handle the creative.
I'm always here for you.
But you don't look very well.
Please go take some rest.
Mr. Xu, I got a lot to do
before shooting Game of Death.
I gotta go get some work done.
Thank you.
Game of Death?
Well, what kind of title is this?
Why? What's the problem?
Well, based on Chinese tradition,
it's not very lucky.
Can we change to another...
- No, we can't.
Just go with it.
Good. Push hard.
Do you know why
we need to practice kung fu?
Tø beat others?
- Not really.
Do you know the way of kung fu?
- No.
But of course.
Well, the question is too deep for you.
But we martial artists
have a simple goal.
That is to challenge
our entire body to its limit.
Do you know what that is?
Don't know?
Can you kick that leaf?
Take a look.
You can't, right?
Then you wait for a few years.
You will make it by then.
Son, watch.
Daddy will show you a kick.
All right. Good.
Daddy's kicking!
- Oh, God!
He's kicking!
He's kicking! Kicking!
Baby, did he scare you?
- It's okay, darling.
Don't cry, Shannon. Let's go, Brandon.
- It's okay.
Come on.
- Hurry. Dinner's ready.
Dinner's ready.
- Do you know what I cooked for you?
Foshan pig. It's delicious.
Bruce, what's wrong?
We have started Game of Death.
You know, once we start shooting,
we can't stop even for a day.
From now on, every day I go to the set,
you mark it on the calendar for me.
When you make it till next month,
The Game of Death will be wrapped.
Okay.
Stop. When I was hitting you,
I didn't get it,
so you have to keep punching.
Keep doing what you were doing.
You must attack just like this.
Let's do it again.
Bruce Lee, I will watch you fall this time.
Who is it?
- I want to speak to Bruce Lee.
Hello? Who is it?
It's me.
Bruce Lee,
you may forget everybody,
but you'll never forget me.
Yellow Skin.
Our business is not done yet.
What the hell do you want?
You know what I want.
Yellow Skin, listen up.
We don't have any
unfinished business anymore.
Your Master Wang had apologized to me.
No!
Back then, I made a big mistake.
Tø make it up to you,
I'd like to challenge you again.
I'll defeat you fairly and openly.
Otherwise,
the rest of my life will be meaningless.
But I don't want to compete with you.
You're afraid.
I'm not afraid of you.
I no longer want to prove myself
through competing.
What I'm doing is to promote
the way of martial arts.
I don't give a damn about
your way of martial arts.
My goal is to defeat you.
Listen up, Bruce Lee.
This is it.
I am now formally challenging you.
I told that I won't challenge anyone,
nor take a challenge anymore.
No! Bruce Lee,
you have to accept my challenge!
I'll never give up if I don't defeat you!
Bruce Lee, you will not ignore me! No!
And?
- 14, 15, 16...
Bruce? Darling?
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
Come.
Hey, I've fixed some snacks for you.
Your mom taught me
how to make dim sum.
And I know how much you love dim sum.
Come. Sit down.
You need to take a break.
Just rest.
Sweetie, I don't want
to eat anything right now.
I just want to lie on your lap
quietly for a while.
My mind has just
been racing recently.
I just got so much stuff going on
that I just can't relax, you know?
These days... These days,
you seem to have changed
into another person,
and I think Professor Ino was right.
I think that you're exhausted
to the point
where you just need to lay and rest.
Like you are now.
Quietly, not thinking of anything.
Bruce, I'll call the hospital tomorrow
to set up an appointment
for your checkup.
And if there's still no diagnosis,
I'll take you to the States
for an even better checkup.
No, damn it!
What are you saying?
You want me to stop the film?
So many people on the crew
depend on me,
and the boss has thrown
so much money into this,
but you want me
to moan in the hospital,
having exams,
even a vacation in the States?
How the hell could I do that?
Darling.
Please don't call the hospital again.
I don't have any disease.
If I did,
it'd be nothing but a headache
caused by exhaustion, right here.
Bruce, your expectation
is way too high.
You need to calm down.
Let me.
Hello?
Bruce Lee, either you accept my challenge,
or you admit you lose in public!
Listen, you insane, crazy devil,
Bruce does not accept your challenge.
This is something between us men.
Nothing to do with you.
I'm warning you, now leave us alone.
Bruce, what are you doing?
Linda, I cannot allow him
to be so arrogant,
especially right now.
I have to keep all my dignity.
Do you understand
what this means to me?
Bruce...
Hold on.
Okay, I'll accept your challenge.
Please tell me the date and place.
Listen carefully.
In just three days,
I'll invite all the masters
of Honk Kong martial arts,
and they will see
how the great Bruce Lee...
loses under my fists!
All right, Yellow Skin.
You'll regret this.
Let me tell you,
you don't know me at all,
nor do you understand me.
You didn't disappoint me.
I'm telling you,
I've never been defeated by anyone,
much less some loser like you.
Well, let's meet at the arena.
By then, don't forget to bring
a stretcher for yourself!
Crazy nut job.
Bruce Lee!
We finally meet again.
Long time no see.
You still look the same.
You're still so arrogant.
It seems that you got better in kung fu,
but I'm not so sure
if you got better ethically.
I failed to defeat you in the States.
I've regretted it for many years.
But today,
we'll finally decide who the winner is.
Wait.
Before we start,
I have a little suggestion.
We'll compete one round first.
After the first round,
if you can't defeat me,
we'll stop the competition.
You shut up.
If you're able,
let your kung fu speak!
You've already lost.
You're doomed to lose this competition.
You're too eager...
too eager
to defeat me.
You shut up!
If I were afraid of death,
I wouldn't have come.
I'm ready now.
Let's stop right here.
It's not a bad thing
to stop at the right time.
How do you like that?
For speed, I'm faster.
For kicking,
I'm tougher than you.
I've said it long before,
kung fu takes more practicing,
less yapping.
Don't instruct me
like a master in front of me!
Quit your nonsense.
Just sign it!
You dare not?
I will.
Tøday, you're doomed to die!
Why don't you say stop?
Stop, stop, stop!
Stop! Bruce Lee, you win.
Yellow Skin, didn't you ask me
about my boxing?
Well, now I'm telling you.
It's a Chinese martial art
called...
Jeet Kune Do.
Bruce.
Bruce, you can soar now.
The 32 years of Bruce Lee's life
is a journey filled
with extraordinary vitality.
Bruce Lee has opened
two brand-new fields for us.
He has contributed to the world
his amazing kung fu
and his unforgettable films.
He helped the world discover
authentic Chinese kung fu,
and Chinese kung fu
has also dazzled the world
through Bruce Lee's achievement.
Chinese kung fu movies
have opened a new and fresh chapter
because of Bruce Lee.
We believe, deep in our hearts,
that the spirit
is the core of a human being.
The day of death is also the moment
of coming back to life,
as the spirit never dies.
May God bless Bruce Lee
and accept his soul.
Amen.
Don't wake him.
Subtitled By J.R. Media Services, Inc.
Burbank, CA