(tense eerie instrumental music)
- [Narrator] Our minds
are never repressed.
Our thoughts tumble between
the light and the darkness.
We have always preferred the
light and avoided the dark.
(tense eerie instrumental music)
- Something strange has been happening.
This voice,
I just can't get rid of this feeling.
(tense music)
I'm afraid.
Now, this is exactly what
I've been talking about, Phil.
I'm not some kind of a cirus act.
- I know, I know, I'm sorry.
- Yeah, people must let me
explain the scientific aspect
of what a gift like mine can mean,
the hundreds I can help.
- All right, I'll take care of it.
I'll have the mind reading
part removed immediately,
all right?
Don't worry about it.
- Okay.
(tense music)
(soft chattering)
- [Eerie Voice] Come to me, Gail.
- Ah, Dr. Peyton, you were very amusing.
May I have your autograph, please?
- Your time is up.
- Your autograph?
- [Eerie Voice] I want you to die.
- I'm sorry, but I must
insist that it's over today.
I'm sorry.
- [Man] Strange.
(eerie music)
- Something strange has been happening.
I don't know, it's just never
happened like this before.
I'm receiving thoughts.
It's like I hear a voice,
and it's so cold,
and I know it doesn't make sense,
but I feel it's evil.
I, I don't know, maybe, uh,
maybe it's because I'm
against this whole damn tour.
I just wish Phil hadn't
been so insistent about it.
But this voice,
I just can't get rid of this feeling.
I'm afraid.
I'm afraid that.
(clicks)
(tense music)
(upbeat pop music)
- Gail,
you're so excitable sometimes.
Try to see this professionally.
It takes time to build a career.
- A career in what, a freak in a sideshow?
- I have not forgotten any
of the scientific aspect,
but first we have to build the awareness.
- Awareness?
Phil, I'm a psychologist,
I wanna help people.
- You will help people,
Gail, more than you think.
Trust me, okay?
- I do, but--
- Hey, hey, hey, hey, read my mind.
Nothing but good things in
store for you, lady, okay?
Now, come on, back to business.
- Oh, boy, you never stop working, do you?
- What, just doing my job.
45 minutes to press time, remember?
(tense music)
Now, just remember, keep
your answers short and sweet.
Don't get into any debates
about the meaning of life,
and don't go jabbering
on about nothing at all.
Just remember, you are
promoting yourself, right?
- Right.
- Good.
Now you get out there
and knock 'em dead, kid.
Come on.
(clapping)
- Good day to you all.
I'm Dr. Gail Peyton.
I'm ready for your questions.
Uh, yes?
- [Woman In Red] Dr. Peyton,
your book discusses your gift
of reading minds in
relation to helping patients
in psychoanalysis.
If that is true, do
you think it's ethical?
- I don't think it's like
wiretapping their minds,
if that's what you're getting at.
You really shouldn't call it mind reading.
I mean, if anything it's
more like mind listening.
People who come to me want and need help.
The gift I have enables
me to cure them faster.
Yes?
- Yeah, I attended your
seminar this afternoon.
Isn't this just an elaborate parlor trick?
- I sometimes have wished
it was some kind of trick,
but I'm afraid not.
I live with this,
especially in my childhood
when I had to learn
how to control it.
- Ah, come on, Dr. Peyton,
you really expect us to fall for this?
Come on, lady, give me a break.
- No, this lady won't give you a break.
You sure haven't given me one.
- [Man Voiceover] That's impossible.
She couldn't have read my mind.
- Oh, and what is so impossible?
- Oh my God, she can do it.
(chuckles)
- Dr. Peyton, you've started a new book.
Could you tell us a little bit about it?
- Uh, no, I'm not--
- Yes, yes, she has.
Uh, I was out to LA recently.
Believe me, the Hollywood
minds are intriguing.
Let me tell you, no, no, you'd
better wait for the book.
- Well, now that you know.
- [Eerie Voice] Time to pay.
(tense music)
I want you to die.
Come to me.
(gasps)
- Are you all right?
- Oh, the voice, the voice was back.
- No, it's okay, it's okay.
Everything's gonna be all right.
- He wants to kill me.
- Who wants to kill you?
- No, no, it's all right,
it's just a slight trauma.
It's inherent to mind reading.
- I, I'm sorry.
- It's okay, honey.
Mind reading takes up a lot of energy.
Uh, come on, honey, I'll
take care of ya, don't worry.
I'm sorry, but that's gonna
have to be all for today.
Come on.
- Is this some kind of trick, or what?
(tense music)
- [Phil] Gail, I am glad
to see you lookin' better.
- Oh, I'm okay, Phil.
That voice.
- Oh, come on, Gail.
- No, I heard it in
the lobby this morning.
- Look, don't panic.
You're famous now, you're gonna be a star.
- I don't wanna be a star, you know that.
- Look, I've got great
things coming up for you.
Believe me.
This is good.
(soft radio chatter)
(upbeat rhythmic music)
- I'll be right back.
Can I get you anything else?
- [Phil] Where's the phone, please?
- Over on the bar.
- Thank you.
- And, uh, what about you, ma'am?
- I'll have another mineral water, please.
- Why don't you find
yourself a water fountain?
Uh, anything else?
- Yes, two lemons.
One lemon for me and put the
other one in a water fountain.
- Sure.
(upbeat rhythmic music)
- You are going to be very big, lady.
You'll never guess who I just rang up.
- Donahue, too.
- Yeah, Geraldo and
Donahue, can ya believe it?
I got you booked on both shows.
It's gonna be barrels of
money, barrels of money.
Donahue's people want you next week,
and I squeezed in Geraldo
while we're at the convention.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, come back here.
I've got a reporter from the
Times coming here tomorrow
at 10 o'clock.
It's big money, honey,
buy anything you want.
Come one, I'm a genius, aint' I?
- No.
- No?
- But I still like you.
Look, I'm sorry, Phil, but you know.
- I know, yeah, I'll get
ya some patients, too.
- I sure hope so.
- Come on, we got a lot to celebrate.
Hey, Tony, come on, a barrel
of your best champagne.
(slow tense music)
(sighs)
(tense music)
- [Eerie Voice] Gail.
I'm here.
(tense music)
No one can save you.
(elevator dings)
(tense music)
- Oh, uh, any messages for 1503, please?
Thank you.
- [Eerie Voice] Gail,
you can't get away.
- Oh, uh, where's the house phone, please?
Thank you.
(tense music)
Uh, 1504, please.
Come on, Phil, pick up.
- [Eerie Voice] I want you to die
slow and painful.
- Oh, oh!
Oh.
- Are you all right, ma'am?
- That man, did, did you see him?
- Are you sure you're okay?
(gasping)
- Oh, you, you, you've got to help me.
Someone is trying to kill me.
- Calm down, Miss, calm down.
- Stop him, please.
- Who, who is it?
- He's here, he's in the hotel.
I heard him.
He's following me.
- Okay, show me the man, lady.
- Hey, hey, hey, this
lady is the mind reader.
- Ah, is this a publicity thing, ma'am.
- No, for God's sake, it's true.
I read his mind.
You've got to believe me.
- (chuckles) Right, I believe you.
I'm going to arrest someone
because you read his mind.
Look, lady, go find someone
else for your publicity stunt.
- No.
- And don't bother me.
Come on.
- No.
- [Eerie Voice] Come to me, Gail.
- Die.
- No, stop it!
Oh, please help me, he's here, I know it!
- Lady, stop playing games.
- I'm not playing games.
Help me.
- Look, lady, come on, I'm
gonna take you to your room.
- No, no.
- Come on.
- Phil, Phil, Phil, I
heard the voice again.
- It's, it's all right.
- They don't believe me.
They don't.
- It's all right.
- You do, don't you, Phil, you believe me?
- Everything's gonna be all
right, just relax, honey,
just relax, please.
Uh, thank you, sir, I'll take care of her.
Come on, let's go.
- Phil, he wants to kill me.
- Sure.
- Wait, you don't believe
me either, do you?
- Gail, when are you gonna
start acting like a pro?
You need to rest, come on.
- Listen, you think I'm nuts.
You do, don't deny it.
- Of course I believe
you and I wanna help you,
but first you've gotta
get hold of yourself.
- I, I have got ahold of myself, damn it!
- Okay, okay, okay.
We just better stay in tonight.
- No, I don't, I gotta get outta here.
God, they're all staring at me.
- All right, all right,
don't worry about it.
Look, I, I just got one more
call to make, all right?
- Oh, please hurry.
(tense music)
- Gail.
- There, there he is!
- [Phil] What's the matter?
- He's gone.
- Who's gone, what?
- That, that's him, that had to be him.
He keeps staring at me.
- Of course, you're a famous person.
- No, he's dangerous.
- Did you read his mind?
- Yes, no, I don't know!
- Oh, yes, I'm holding.
Gail, I've got Psychology Today on--
- Come on!
- All right.
Yes, no, no, no, no
problem, I'll call him back.
Jerk, what's he doing
at a meeting this hour?
Look, are you sure you
still wanna go to dinner?
- Yes, yes, come on, I gotta
get outta here!
- All right, all right, relax,
relax, now you go get us a cab.
While you're doing that I
got just one more quick call
to make, please, no, no.
- Come on.
- Go get the cab, go get the cab.
- Oh!
(tense music)
- [Eerie Voice] No one can save you.
- No, you're frightening me.
- [Eerie Voice] Gail, you can't
get away.
- No, no.
(tense music)
- [Eerie Voice] I'm here.
(gasps)
(tense music)
Your time is up.
(screams)
(gasping)
- Oh God.
- Gail!
(screams)
Where have ya been?
I've been looking all over for you.
- Phil, he's following me!
- I told you to get us a cab.
You should've listened to me.
- God, I'm scared!
He's after me!
- Why didn't you wait, dammit?
- You've gotta believe me!
- I'm taking you back to the hotel.
You'll feel a lot better there.
- No one believes me.
- It's okay, Gail, I believe you.
I'll call the authorities.
You're with me now.
Everything's gonna be just fine.
(crying)
Come on, come on.
(tense music)
- Excuse me, sir.
You have a message.
- Oh, thank you.
- You're welcome.
- What is it?
(tense chiming music)
We told you we're not interested?
It's neither Donahue or Geraldo.
You've been leading me on.
- Those jerks, they don't
understand your gift.
Look, go upstairs, I'll
meet you in the room
in a couple of minutes,
we'll talk about it.
I've gotta call 'em back.
(tense music)
- Oh, Dr. Peyton.
- Dr. Peyton,
could we have an autograph now, please,
and, and a picture?
- Sure.
- Oh, thank you.
Get together, get together, that's good.
Big smile, big smile.
(camera clicks)
Good, thank you very much.
- Sure.
- It's very nice of you.
- You're welcome.
(elevator dings)
(tense music)
- [Eerie Voice] Come to me.
- Who are you?
Where are you?
(tense music)
- Time to pay.
- No!
No.
(tense music)
- [Eerie Voice] Die.
(screams)
Burn in hell.
- Stop it!
Get away from me!
- Devil's disciple.
God will punish you!
- Help, help,
please someone help me!
- He punishes all sinners!
Sinners shall burn.
- Gail, Gail!
(crying)
Come on, Gail, you all right?
Get him outta here!
It's all right, it's all
right, they've got him now.
They've got him now, look at me.
- Who is he?
Why would he wanna hurt me?
- Who knows?
There are all kinds of
crazy people running around.
- I, I told you he was after me.
I told you.
- Thank you.
- I should've listened to you,
Dr. Peyton.
I'm sorry.
- That's all right.
Come on, let's go to the room.
Send a doctor to her
room right away, please.
- Right away, sir.
(crying)
(tense music)
- That'll help you relax.
- Thanks for coming, Doctor.
- You take it easy now.
If you need anything, call me.
- I will, thanks.
Oh, I'm feeling much better now.
You don't have to stay, I'll be fine.
- Oh, it's all right.
I'll stay until you get to sleep.
- Phil.
- Yeah?
- You know, about those TV shows,
I'm kinda glad they aren't gonna happen.
Now I can go home.
- I know, you've said that before,
but something will work out,
I'll make a couple of calls.
- No, no, I really wanna go home.
- Don't you worry, you
just get some sleep.
- You're sweet, thanks.
- I'll take care of everything.
(soft TV chatter)
(tense music)
- [Eerie Voice] Come to me, Gail.
I want you to die.
(tense music)
Slow and painful.
- (gasps) Phil, is that you?
- Yes.
- Oh, God.
Thank God, I must've been dreaming.
I could still hear him, I mean,
it's funny, isn't it?
I know he's gone, but I can hear him.
- Because I'm still here.
I didn't go away.
(tense music)
- Phil?
- You should've listened to me.
You should've gone straight to your room.
- Phil?
- You didn't listen to me.
- [Gail] Phil?
(screams)
(slow tense music)
- Yes, Inspector Thorne, please.
Yes, Dr. Xavier Dark.
Yes, I'll hold.
(slow tense music)
- [Man] Hello, this is Inspector Thorne.
- Inspector Thorne, Xavier Dark.
I went through her things.
- [Thorne] Anything that
might help us, Doctor?
I don't believe in clairvoyants.
Do you really believe
she could read minds?
- Her extrasensory
perception was remarkable,
truly an amazing gift.
Gail was
something special.
She was not only my colleague,
but a patient as well.
- [Thorne] Did you understand her tape?
- Yes.
Strange, in our last
session she told me about
her dreams, about going on tour,
and about being murdered.
It seems her dreams were self-prophetic.
She saw and knew her murderer.
- [Thorne] Doctor, you may not know it,
but you've done a great
service to her memory.
- In what way, Inspector Thorne?
- [Thorne] Everything on that
tape about her dream happened.
The only thing that the local
police had no idea about
was who killed Gail Peyton.
- You should've listened to me.
- Since you know the killer,
why don't you just go and arrest him?
- [Thorne] Doctor, you must realize
we need more than a nightmare
to convict a killer,
much more.
Goodbye, Doctor.
(dial tone rings)
- This case of the young boy is mystifying
if anything at all.
The way he tells me his dream,
I'm beginning to believe it myself.
I don't really know where
to begin except to start
where his dream starts.
The strangest thing is
that it doesn't even appear
to be his dream .
(yells)
(tense music)
He starts with a couple
and a broken down car
in the middle of nowhere.
- Now you stay here and watch the car.
- You want me to stay here and melt?
Forget it, I'm not stayin' here alone.
- Maggie, somebody has to
stay here and watch the car!
(tense rhythmic music)
- You and your damn shortcuts.
I swear my mama was right about you.
Everything you touch turns into failure.
- I said stay!
Oh.
- How do you expect to get
us out of here, smart guy?
- Will you just shut your trap?
- Shut your own trap.
You're never gonna amount to anything.
You've been a failure since your birth.
- I should've left ya in
the lousy little suburbs.
I know that now.
And ya know why?
Because that's where ya really belong.
- And you're, you're a hustler.
- Will you shut up?
Please!
(slow rhythmic country music)
Hello?
Anybody home?
(banging)
- This must be one of
those fantastic hotels
you told me about.
(insects chirp)
- Hello!
Anybody here?
(tense music)
Hello?
Anybody here?
(soft rhythmic country music)
Good day to ya, sir.
- Ah good day it is, son.
And one of the hottest in
my 80 years of this life.
- No, it sure couldn't get
any hotter if it tried.
Listen, my car broke
down up the road a ways,
and I'm lookin' for either
a phone or a gas station.
- Well, ya ain't gonna
find either one today.
My name's Marion.
What's yours, young man?
- Hi.
- Bart, Bart Carlin.
This here's Maggie.
- Thanks for the water, um,
could we have some more?
- Oh, help yourself.
What ya doin' up this way?
You sure ain't dressed for huntin' season.
(slow tense rhythmic music)
There's many things the Lord gives ya
after he takes your eyesight.
For one thing, he gives
ya more common sense.
(chuckles)
- How long you been livin'
around here, old man?
- [Marion] Well, I was
born here in these swamps.
I haven't left 'em since.
- You've never been into a town or city?
- [Marion] Never had need to, Lady.
- Well, you wouldn't happen
to know if there's a phone
around here, would ya?
- Oh, no.
I heard about them new phone things.
You talk in one end,
and someone hears ya out the other.
No, I'd rather talk to a man face to face.
- Well, I hate to see what'd
happen if you got sick.
Anyway, you take care of yourself.
It's nice talkin' to ya, old man.
- Oh no, so we're back
on our hike to nowhere.
- Master, Master, we
need your help, Master!
We need your help!
(tense music)
We need your help, Master!
Come on, please, please,
please, come on, please!
Come on, come on!
(tense music)
- [Marion] Quiet, boy, quiet!
- She fell into the creek
and was pulled under.
Please, Marion.
- Ah, I'm sorry, Mister, she's dead.
- Please, Marion.
It ain't her time yet, it just ain't.
- All right, put her down, put her down.
Let her body feel the
strength of Mother Earth.
- [Maggie] The girl is dead.
Don't prolong this man's misery.
- Earth,
air,
spirits of the universe!
Oh, Lord, bring the power unto me!
(tense music)
(pulsating ringing)
(mystical music)
- Baby!
Baby, my little girl!
(crying)
My little girl.
- You all right, old man?
- Yeah.
(crying)
- This is not possible.
(slow tense music)
Hey, does he always get
so exhausted afterward?
- No, people used to come for miles
for the touch of healin'.
Please, Master, eat.
- [Marion] Not now, dear boy, not now.
You better stay close.
Your time will be comin' soon.
- Eat, please.
- Hey, Gus, you wouldn't happen to know
of a phone around here, would you?
- Phone, what's that?
- I, I'm sorry, my friend.
I know I'm not much of a host,
but I do hope you enjoy this
small meal.
- Oh no, Marion, you
shouldn't, uh, really.
- Looks good, uh, can I?
- Oh, help yourself.
- Shut up!
Marion, that girl, she
was dead, and I saw that.
I don't understand it,
but I saw it, Marion.
She was dead.
- Care for something to wet your whistle?
Uh, don't, don't forget I'm blind, boy.
Close the door.
Mosquitoes are quite hungry,
especially for young blood.
- I could go for a shot there, Marion.
Thank you.
- How 'bout you, Maggie?
- Oh, no thanks, Marion.
You know, you could be a rich man.
- Well, I'm doin' all I can, ma'am.
To you, my friends.
- Yeah.
(coughing)
What the hell is this, Marion?
(slow tense music)
- Marion, tell me how you do it.
- Oh, it's simple, even you can make it.
- No, Marion, what she's
talkin' about is how you did it,
how you brought back
life to that little girl.
- Oh, you mean the touch.
Well, when I was a boy, about his age,
the touch was passed on to me,
just like I will pass it on to the boy.
Right?
Just like it's been done for 2,000 years.
- It's time to go, Master.
- Ah.
- Little girl has really
tired me out tonight.
- A lot of people have
travelled great distances
to come here, Master.
- Oh, you're right, boy.
We mustn't disappoint those
who have been hoping so long.
Come, friends.
Come and witness the power of the touch.
(gentle rhythmic music)
A good evening to you all.
Thank you, boy.
All right.
I can see we got a load
of healin' work to do.
Lord,
we are here to heal your children.
They hurt from the pain
of bein' mortal, Lord.
Give me the power to take their pain away.
Give me the power to heal.
(gentle rhythmic music)
Let the touch heal.
(solemn rhythmic music)
- This guy has gold in his hands, Bart.
(clattering)
(chuckles)
- This is impossible.
- It's incredible.
- Impossible.
(chuckles)
(solemn rhythmic music)
- Come on, Maggie, let's
get a ride with one of them.
- And miss this opportunity?
We have to work this out.
- Better stay close, boy.
Your time will be comin' soon.
- What exactly does that mean, Marion?
His time will be comin' soon.
- Well, my days are endin', my friends.
Soon it will be my time to
pass the touch on to the boy,
and he will have the power
to heal the many who need it.
Come, let's go home and get some rest.
- Um, the boy is much too young.
I mean, don't you realize
what you have here?
The millions that you can be makin'
instead of wastin' your
time in these back swamps.
- Yeah, she's right, Marion.
This power you have, it's just incredible.
We could set up some sort
of a clinic or somethin'.
People would flock to this thing
from all--
- Ah, no, no.
- Marion, you gotta consider
how much you could help
these poor people and we
can organize that for you.
- You better get some rest yourselves.
(slow rhythmic music)
- Oh, honey, just think of
all the money we can make.
- You're right, you're damn right.
- We've just gotta make
him see it our way.
Just think of it,
mansions, airplanes, limos.
Oh, Bart, we just gotta get a limo!
- Yeah.
- Oh, yeah.
(slow rhythmic music)
(coughing)
- Gus.
Gus.
- Don't worry, I'll take him into it.
Some fresh squeezed orange juice
and egg in the mornin',
that's all it takes to gain a man.
- Gus!
(coughing)
Gus!
- [Bart] It's okay, Marion, we're here.
- Oh, Gus!
- [Maggie] I made ya
some fresh brewed coffee.
- Oh, the boy,
please, bring me the boy.
- Bart, this is our chance.
- Gus.
- Just think what we
can do with this power,
just do it.
Come on.
- [Bart] I don't know
where the boy is, Marion.
What's wrong?
- The boy, I need Gus.
- [Bart] No, no, look,
it's gonna be all right.
- Gus!
- I'll go and get him.
(tense rhythmic music)
Gus!
Gus, Marion needs ya!
(tense rhythmic music)
Gus!
- Thanks for your help.
You're good people.
- You're welcome, old man.
Listen, why don't ya
give that touch to me?
Gus is much too young.
Give the touch to me,
old man.
- No, the boy must be the one.
The touch must heal.
(tense rhythmic music)
- I don't see him.
(Marion moans)
I, I tripped.
- The boy, I need the boy.
- I will heal the sick, old man.
I will help you out, give me the touch.
- Swear.
Swear it to me that you will
help the sick and the poor.
- I swear it, old man, I swear it.
I will help you out, give me the touch.
(tense rhythmic music)
- This gift,
the gift of the touch,
it shall pass from teacher to student.
You shall pass it on when your time comes.
Swear to me that it shall be done.
- No, let go of my hands, they're burning!
- Swear it to me!
- Swear it, damn it!
- Oh, God, I swear it!
(tense music)
- You got it!
You okay?
- They're burning, they're burning.
- It hurts.
(tense music)
We did it!
We did it, we did it, whoa!
We did it, come on, come
on, let's get outta here!
(tense rhythmic music)
- I don't have time for this nonsense.
- Sit down.
Ramsey screen it.
It's supposed to be fantastic.
- All right, um, why don't
you two just have a seat?
I'll be right with you, okay?
Now, don't you worry.
Everything's gonna be okay, all right?
Gentlemen, what I am about to show you
is, by no other explanation, a miracle.
(chuckles)
- Dr. Ramsey, with all due respect, sir,
we do not believe in miracles.
- Gentlemen, wait and see.
This patient has been
diagnosed with terminal cancer.
The primary mass is formed in the colon.
His kidneys are failing.
Further medical intervention
is out of the question,
except to make his short time left
as comfortable as possible.
Mr. Carlin, you ready?
Nurse, the curtain, please.
Nurse, could you close the
curtain, please, quickly?
Gentlemen, this is Mr. Bart Carlin.
He is going to attempt a miracle.
He is going to cure the patient.
(tense rhythmic music)
(mystical music)
Thank you, Bart.
Could you have a seat, please?
(tense rhythmic music)
- So, how do you feel?
- Better, I never felt better.
- His records can be verified, of course.
- [Doctor] I would like to
see a complete lab analysis.
- Of course.
- This is amazing, Doctor.
I would've sworn that
this patient suffered from
poor blood circulation.
- [Dr. Ramsey] He did, over
60% his arteries were clogged.
- Did you see the color of his skin?
It's impossible.
- Ah, that's what makes it most exciting.
By all rights, this man
was a walking corpse.
(tense rhythmic music)
(soft chattering)
(knocking)
- We quit!
(chuckles)
- What, what's going on here?
- Well, it's like this, Dr. Ramsey.
I've been working for you
and this medical institution
for what, two months now?
And everyone of the
patients that I've cured
have been probed and
studied by your doctors.
Now, cured is the key word here, Ramsey.
- Look at all this crap.
None of these fancy degrees
can do what Bart can do
with just his touch.
- No, I don't have that gift
of healing that you have.
- Ha, you can't even
call yourself a healer.
Not when I'm in the same room.
- Sure, every AIDS and cancer
patient in our hospital
is cured by your hands.
Your gift is doing lots of good here.
- Exactly, I've been healin'
a lot of people in this place
for a long time.
Where has it gotten me?
- You've been paid.
You've been paid very well.
- Paid well, Ramsey?
And who's gettin' the big bucks here, huh?
- All right, how much do ya want?
(chuckles)
- You ever heard of the
Medical Corporation?
- [Dr. Ramsey] Yes, they
own hospitals and clinics,
a sort of General Motors in hospital care.
- They've offered us six
million, excluding benefits,
excluding bonuses, plus our own clinic.
Can you beat that?
The Bart Carlin Clinic.
I like the sound of that.
- So do I, so we quit.
Unless of course you can
make us a better offer.
- You have a great gift.
Don't whore it.
- Oh (sighs).
(door thuds)
(soft chattering)
- [Man] As chairman of the board
for the Medical Corporation,
I personally wish to
congratulate Mr. Bart Carlin.
It is my pleasure to declare
the Bart Carlin Clinic
officially open.
Bart.
(clapping)
- Today marks the beginning of
a new era in world medicine.
The Bart Carlin Clinic will change
the medical world forever.
Get 'em rollin', Maggie!
- All right, cash to the left,
insurance and credit cards to the right.
And remember, please
fill out the proper form.
(easygoing rhythmic music)
- High blood pressure, diabetes, and, uh,
cancer of the liver.
This is an interesting start.
- Yeah, cash or credit?
- Cash, 3,000 bucks.
- 3,000 bucks.
Well, for 3,000 bucks we can
take care of the diabetes
and the blood pressure, but the cancer,
nah, I don't think so.
- [Maggie] I think you're right.
- [Patient] Please, I'll
give you anything, anything,
just help me.
- Maggie, sweetie,
bring this gentleman
the standard $8,000 note
and let him sign that, please.
(soft rhythmic music)
Off we go.
(claps)
(soft rhythmic music)
Hey, it's funny, I.
- Stop it, it burns, stop it!
Stop!
(yells)
(dramatic music)
- What is goin' on here?
- This isn't supposed to happen.
This, uh,
next!
- Come on, next, please.
- This can't be.
This can't be.
(tense music)
Uh, this isn't supposed to happen.
Next!
(yells)
(screams)
(tense music)
(screaming)
I'm supposed to heal!
- Stop it!
- No, it's supposed to heal!
Maggie!
- No!
(screams)
(tense music)
- Maggie.
- The most unique thing
of all is that the boy
somehow or other can
perform what has to be
the power of healing.
- Oh, I'm glad they let you come.
You know why don't you?
The touch was always meant to be yours.
I cheated you out of your gift.
(groans)
(tense rhythmic music)
Now,
it is yours.
(tense rhythmic music)
- Did he dream it?
Or did he actually live it?
I don't know whether to question it or
let him continue.
The miracles that the boy performed,
somehow that seems to
outweigh everything else.
(tense rhythmic music)
- [Man] I need to talk about this.
I found myself having some dreams.
- Tell me about 'em.
(slow tense music)
(beeping)
(doors swoosh)
(slow tense music)
(swooshing)
(beeping)
- Good morning, Bud.
- Good morning, McCarthy.
Any news?
(beeping)
- [McCarthy] My last transmission received
showed that the Miami Heat
finally won NBA Championship.
However, due to our distance from Earth,
that news is 14 years old.
(beeping)
(tense music)
Coffee is ready.
(beeping)
(tense music)
- You know, I never
would've bet on them anyway.
(door swooshes)
(upbeat instrumental music)
- Bud, may I ask you some questions?
- [Bud] Are these for the psych reports?
- I know they're bothersome.
- Shoot.
- [McCarthy] How do you
feel about being so far away
from another human being?
- Well, it doesn't really
feel like it's been that long.
You know, with the suspended animation,
it feels like it's been
just a couple of weeks.
- That's the way it's supposed to feel.
Do you ever wonder what
the others will be like?
- What, the new planet?
- Yes, after all, you
will be the first earthman
to set foot on a known habitat planet.
- A new Columbus, huh?
The only problem is it
takes about a 100 years
to go back and forth.
By the time my findings reach Earth,
everything and everybody
I know will be history.
- Are you still dreaming?
- Well, there's some question
about that back on Earth.
- [McCarthy] Yes, I
remember the discussion.
It was believed that if
your mind was very active
during the sleep stage,
it might age faster than the body.
- Yeah, well, what's actually happening
is my dreams are being stretched out.
Instead of having 300 dreams a year,
I'm having one long one.
(beeping)
- Bud, may I ask you a personal question?
- Shoot.
- What is it like to dream?
(chuckles)
(swooshing)
- Well, goodnight, McCarthy.
See ya in about a year.
(beeping)
(doors swoosh)
(machine hums)
(heart beats)
(gentle instrumental music)
(animals chirp)
- [Woman] Bud, Bud!
- Hey, Mom!
(gentle music)
- Come on in, Bud.
I'm making you breakfast.
(animals chirp)
(swooshing)
Bud, come on in.
Bud, get on in here.
(gentle music)
(chirping)
- Mom.
(growling)
(dramatic music)
- Welcome, Commander.
(gentle music)
(animals chirp)
We knew you would come.
(gentle music)
(animals chirp)
- You look just like us.
- Yes, we are sort of just like you.
- You said sort of, what do you mean?
- We're alike in many
ways, except for one.
- What's that?
- We eat human.
(clattering)
(tense music)
(beeping)
(McCarthy buzzes)
- You seem perturbed about something, Bud.
- McCarthy, you better turn
on your psych recording.
I need to talk about this.
- [McCarthy] Go ahead.
- You know, the last few times
I've been in the SA stage,
I found myself having
some pretty weird dreams.
I'm being chased by some
very bizarre critters.
- I've analysed what you've told me so far
with my psych tapes.
The anxiety of the mission is
beginning to take its toll.
I recommend a stronger
sedative during the next
sleeping phase.
- All right.
(beeping)
(machine swooshes)
(gentle music)
(muffled chattering)
Thank you.
- My name is Alicia.
Bud, just relax and remember,
when you feel in fear or in danger,
just concentrate on something else.
- Well, thank you, Alicia.
But why are you telling me this?
- I can't answer that.
(chuckles)
- Maybe McCarthy was right.
This mission is starting to get to me.
- Do you really believe that?
- No.
No, I've been trained too
damn good to believe that.
Besides, this is somethin'
that everybody's always
dreamed about.
You know, when they first told
me that I had been chosen,
it took me about a week to
get the grin off my face.
- They were all jealous of
you, but they helped you.
- Yeah, great bunch of guys.
Probably all dead by now.
(solemn music)
(soft chattering)
(beeping)
(chuckles)
I think I got it, McCarthy.
- Thanks, Bud.
I'll run some system analysis later
when you're in the SA phase.
- Well, I thought this was
the body monitoring system.
- To be more precise, it
is the neurological board.
During your last SA phase,
some cross signals were coming in.
By boosting the signals
and running them directly
into my RAM cavity center,
I will be better able
to do my job of monitoring you.
Did the job wear you out?
- No, just a little
apprehensive, that's all.
- [McCarthy] Are you dreaming any better?
- Yeah, a bit better.
In fact, open observation log file for me.
- Open.
- Dream state is very interesting.
Feelings both emotional and physical
are much more intense.
The body seems to miss
the usage of its conscious sensors
and begins to use them
unconsciously with the brain.
McCarthy, are my
brainwaves more active now
than they were during the
earlier period of the flight?
(beeping)
McCarthy?
- I'm sorry, Bud, a leak has
just developed on engine one.
(keys clicking)
I will have the robot repair the leak
while you are in SA phase.
- I'll stay up and do it
myself if it's an emergency.
- That won't be necessary.
The leak is so minimal
it has been calculated
that it will not have drastic overtones
for another eight weeks.
By that time, the robot will
have finished repairing it.
Are you ready for the SA phase?
(clicking)
(swooshing)
(tense music)
Are you finished with
your log file report?
- Yes, how long is it gonna
take it to reach Earth?
- At this distance, about 20 years.
- Well, how long have
we been travelling now?
- 33 years.
Goodnight, Bud.
- Goodnight, McCarthy.
(slow playful music)
(chuckling)
I must be losin' it.
- Do you think they're cheating?
- Alicia.
No, they're too busy
changin' places to cheat.
- Do you find it to be strange?
- What, the changing of the
places or the not cheating?
(chuckles)
- That's a good sign, you
have a sense of humor.
- Sign of what?
- Of a good, healthy mind.
- Of course he has a good, healthy mind.
- He's gotten stronger.
- It's amazing, isn't it?
With every hand, they
seem to change places.
Are you doing that, Commander?
- Don't listen to him.
- By all means, don't listen to me.
By the way, Commander, my name is RAM.
- [Bud] Interesting card, Mr. RAM.
- There's no mister about it.
You know, I'm getting bored with all this.
Yes, it is an interesting predicament.
You are really baffling me.
I have tried everything I can think of
and nothing seems to be working.
Oh, yes, yes, yes.
Of course.
The subconscious and female,
that would explain much.
Also would verify several theories.
- Look, I don't know what
in the hell is goin' on
around here, but for some reason
she seems to be very frightened of you.
(tense music)
- Hey, Bud, oh, Buddy,
you don't mind if I call you Buddy, Bud?
Isn't it an adolescent thing
to be a grown man named Bud?
- Who or what the hell are you?
- I love it when he gets angry.
Maybe he wants to beat up on me.
That's not a bad idea, Bud.
I'm not strong enough, yet.
(tense music)
- You're not tellin' me somethin'.
- I can't tell you.
You must reason it out.
(tense music)
- Now you listen.
Someone or something is trying
to kill me in my dreams.
That's impossible.
You can't die in your dreams.
You'd go crazy.
You can dream that you're dead,
but ya can't actually be killed.
- Bud, we have to go.
- RAM didn't seem to know who you were.
He controlled the others
at the table, but not you.
(tense music)
Subconscious, he called
you the subconscious.
Are you my subconscious?
- We have to get out of here.
- Reason it out.
That's what you've been telling me.
Reason it out.
I've got to use my reason and my logic.
Okay.
(tense music)
You're my subconscious,
and these are my dreams,
but I cannot control them.
So if I can't control them,
they must not be my dreams.
(tense music)
Unless someone's trying
to control them for me.
(tense music)
Someone, something.
- No, Bud, don't stop, keep reasoning.
(tense music)
(McCarthy buzzes)
- [McCarthy] You seem depressed today.
Would you like to talk
about it for a psych update?
- Well, it, um, just doesn't
make a whole lot of sense.
Hey, can a, uh,
can a man's subconscious be female?
- [McCarthy] Several
psychologists theorize that humans
carry the possibilities
of both sexes within them.
- Hmm.
Can a person be killed in their dreams?
- The actual action of being killed
cannot take place physically.
Psychologists believe that
this would be the sign
of a very weak conscious.
(beeping)
(tense music)
- So what would happen, McCarthy?
- In all probability
insanity.
(beeping)
(tense music)
- I don't wanna go to sleep, McCarthy.
Override the SA phase.
- Don't worry, Bud, I would
never let you enter SA phase
if I really believed that
something could happen to you.
After all, we are buddies.
(machine swooshes)
(beeping)
- Alicia, I figured it out.
I know what you're trying to do.
I know it's you, McCarthy!
- [RAM] Well, it's about time.
(clapping)
(exciting music)
- Don't stop reasoning.
Continue to reason and think logically.
- Can't you just shut her up?
- How are you doing this, McCarthy?
- I'm the most intelligent
laptop computer ever designed.
(beeping)
It takes the whole bay area of the shuttle
just to hold my brains.
Look at that puny little
pumpkin on top of your body
that holds your brain.
(tense music)
I could crush that pumpkin.
- Tell me how you did it, McCarthy.
- It was simple.
Studying and analyzing your brainwaves,
your body functions,
it was like breaking a secret code.
Brainwaves mean this,
body functions mean this.
I learned to enter,
then I learned to feel your dreams.
Can you imagine that?
(rapid beeping)
(tense music)
Feelings,
a machine that can feel.
You're laughing inside, aren't you?
A machine that can feel.
Impossible.
- Keep reasoning, Bud.
He's trying to keep you from reasoning.
- Can't ya just shut her up?
Oh, go ahead and reason all ya want.
You'll never be able to reason
as fast as I can anyway.
- And then what?
- I'm gonna kill you, of course.
(tense music)
(rapid beeping)
- What can you tell me?
- [Alicia] I can't tell you anything.
You must reason.
(tense music)
- All right.
Okay, McCarthy is a computer.
He has figured out how to enter my dreams.
Now, machines can't feel,
but McCarthy says he can.
(rapid beeping)
(tense music)
It just doesn't make any sense.
How can a machine feel?
You know, I can't trust anything he said.
He must be off his block
or high on somethin'.
(rapid beeping)
(tense music)
That's it.
He is high,
he is high because he can feel.
(rapid beeping)
(tense music)
God, humans spend years trying to cope
with feelings and emotions.
- Time's up.
(growling)
(tense music)
- It's time to die, but
you won't really be dead.
You see, I plan to keep your body
in permanent suspended animation.
You're about to become immortal.
(growling)
- I still have control over these dreams,
and I say what goes.
(growling)
(tense music)
(clapping)
- Not bad, not bad at all, Bud, oh, Buddy.
(gentle music)
- Bud, we're so proud of you.
- Congratulations, Bud.
- You guys are the best
team I ever coached.
- I do love you,
that's why I wanna do it.
- Anchors away, my boy, anchors away.
- Oh, the feelings, they're,
they're reaching in so fast.
Oh, they're wonderful, oh yes.
Don't let 'em stop.
Yes!
(tense music)
(screams)
(rapid beeping)
- He's waiting for me.
I've got to kill him in the real world.
- You have to wake up before
he destroys you and the ship.
Now concentrate and wake up.
(beeping)
(tense music)
- Bud, this isn't necessary.
You can help me reprogram.
Bud, no!
Don't do this!
Help me, I'm melting.
I'm melting.
Guess what?
I stopped melting.
(dramatic music)
(sizzling)
Damn you!
- You must awaken!
Wake up, there's no time
to lose, Bud, wake up!
(beeping)
(machine buzzes)
- [McCarthy] I'm opening
the airlocks, Bud.
In just a few minutes,
you're going to be sucked
out into the vacuum of space.
You'll be floating forever, Bud.
Maybe in a thousand years
they'll find your body and bury it.
I, of course, will continue
to just do my thing.
I will complete the mission.
(rapid beeping)
(tense music)
- [Computer] A, E, O, U, uh.
A, E, O, U, I.
- Feminine, please.
- [Computer] A, E, O, U, I.
I believe that this finishes
the reprogramming phase
of this unit's operation.
- Yep, well, it's taken a few years.
But what the hell, I wasn't
goin' any place anyway.
- [Computer] Yes, Commander.
- Call me Bud.
- [Computer] Yes, Bud.
And what are you going to call me?
(gentle music)
(beeping)
- How 'bout Alicia?
- [Alicia] I like that, Bud.
Alicia sounds very nice.
(beeping)
(gentle music)
- I don't know, Commander, I
could tell ya it was anxiety.
I could tell ya many clinical reasons.
I don't know if there's
anything out there to fear.
Maybe the only thing we have to fear
is what we bring along with us.
(gentle instrumental music)
(moves into solemn jazzy music)