(Multicom Jingle)
(dramatic music)
(window squeaking)
(razor scratching)
(nail file grinding)
(zipper buzzing)
(upbeat music)
(crowd talking)
- [Woman] You could do it,
get your client to come out.
- [Man] I'll make room.
- So, all is forgiven, Coco?
- Of course, how could I not?
- We really mustn't fight that way.
- Let's promise that we don't.
And seal it with a dip.
(Ruth giggling)
- When a Coe scores with
them all, amazing isn't it?
- Oh, Coco, it's been ages
since I felt so alive.
Who are all these people?
I wanna meet everyone
that's important to you.
- Oh, there's only you, only you.
Come on, I'll introduce you
to the big boss Mr. Brody.
Now he only appears to
be crude and cunning.
Deep down he is a lamb.
Wonderful party, Mr. Brody.
- Introduce us to your date, Kevin.
- Harvey, this is Ruth, my mother.
- Do you think I was too much tonight?
- No.
- Oh I was, I know.
But I know what this world is like.
You have to stand out from
it just to be noticed.
Most of those people didn't
like me, but they won't forget
me or you, and it's you I
don't want them to forget.
- Oh, don't worry
mother, I won't let them.
- We're a good team, aren't we?
- Hey, of course we are.
Listen, mother bear, in a year,
maybe less, we'll be in L.A..
I talked to John about the disco idea
and he is falling over to get it started.
All I need is a few more
selling months like this one.
Did I tell you 5,500 in commissions?
I listed three properties just yesterday.
Two of them, cash only deals.
No one's gonna out volume me, no one.
(chuckling)
- Oh Ret.
Ret, darling, it's a brand
new day, Tara is saved.
Oh, my goodness.
(humming)
(Ruth giggling)
Going somewhere?
- Ah, did you two have fun?
- [Ruth] It's Jennifer, isn't it?
- Jennifer, mother,
Jennifer's in Las Vegas.
I have a date.
- At this hour?
- It was fine, Gordo.
I met Kay Lauren there.
I didn't know she was into real estate.
Her husband works for you, right?
- She has to sell real estate.
Her husband doesn't make enough money
in the newspaper business.
God, it's stifling in here.
- Yes, he did work for me.
He transferred to the morning paper.
- [Newsman] Reject the proposed orders.
Another rape attempt was reported
in Hamblen Park earlier today.
The woman managed to escape,
but was unable to describe her assailant.
- I can't bear it.
It's unconscionable that in
today's society the tragedy
of rape continues to
proliferate unchecked.
Why must women suffer
this terrible violation?
- Oh, the woman apparently got away, Ruth.
- Others haven't been so lucky.
Oh, I know you'd never publish
a word about rape and sully
the Christian image of Spokane,
but some madman is on the
loose out there and every
woman in South Hill knows it.
- I'm sure the police are--
- Just drop it!
Let's just drop it.
Go on.
Go on to your secret date.
When will I ever be free of the Coe men?
But be here for breakfast.
I'm making your favorite.
(car engine rumbling)
(light dramatic music)
- Jay.
Don't let them fold over,
take them right to the car.
- Remember when we found that lost dog
and kept it in your
basement for three weeks
before your mother
knew, when we were nine?
I wonder why I'm thinking of that now.
- Kevin, you're home.
What a nice surprise.
Nice to see you too, Jay.
- Hi, mother, your hair looks nice.
- Thank you, I didn't
go to the hair dresser.
Did I spoil something?
- No, Jay was helping me take
some stuff to the cleaners.
- You actually think I
don't know what's going on?
You've been running over there for months.
Has that tart finally
convinced you to move in?
- I better get going.
- And you, you helped
bring her back to Spokane
and get them back together.
- It's what Kevin wants, Mrs. Coe.
- Kevin has no idea what he wants.
Now, would you please leave my home.
- Gladly.
- How can you do that to him?
Jay is my best friend.
- How can I do that?
You're pathetic.
Don't you even know what you've done.
- I'm trying to live my life.
- Then go live it, but
not with that bitch.
An occasional whore woulda
been a far better choice.
- Jennifer's in Las Vegas I just--
- Don't you dare lie to me.
I've seen you with her.
- You followed me?
- Yes, I followed you.
$400 suits, you can't afford
them, you don't have the money.
Your father gives it to you.
I know.
I know everything.
Now get the hell out of my
house and remember if you go
running back to that
tramp you are not my son.
(door slamming)
- [Dispatch] Criminal mischief at 883.
(muffled radio talking)
(Lois crying)
- Get this off me, these are dirty.
I can't have dirty clothes,
get them off of me.
- Okay, we'll do that.
Lois, I'm sorry to have
to put you through this,
but I need you to tell me everything
you can remember, every detail.
(Lois crying)
- Please just hold me.
- Flashlight over here.
- Hold me.
(muffled police radio)
- Before he ran off he patted
her on her bare buttocks
and said be more careful next time,
like he was giving her friendly advice.
I know I don't have good
visual id's, Lieutenant Donner,
but I do know the M.O.'s are similar,
I think there's a pattern here,
like maybe a serial rapist.
- Liz--
- And I don't wanna have
to tell her mother and dad
that manpower shortages are slowing down
the investigation of
their daughter's rape.
(knocking on door)
- [Matt] You wanted to see me?
- Uh yeah, this um,
this rape thing, it's a,
I agree with Liz here,
it's getting out of control
and I want you to help her out, Matt.
Liz, this is Matt Forbes.
He's kicked enough butt in
his day to satisfy even you,
and I was there in '79,
the one time he smiled.
- [Man] Lieutenant Adam, can
I talk to you for a second?
- [Ruth] I'm so glad you
could come to dinner, Kevin.
- You call the office 12 times a day,
then you start in on Jay,
you don't give people
much of a choice, do you?
- Yes, I well understand the
hardship of having to eat
a home cooked meal with
parents who love you.
- Don't start mother--
- I even baked your favorite pie.
- It's very tasty--
- I've been thinking,
it would be nice to have your boss,
Mr. Brody and his wife to dinner soon.
It would be good for your business.
- It is my business, mother,
- He really
- Why don't you let me--
- Shouldn't have you wasting
your time in residential properties.
The real money is in
commercial real estate.
I'm not even sure his
company's big enough for you.
- Have I told you all about Ginny?
- Ginny, who's Ginny?
- Ginny Perham.
The Perhams.
One of the oldest families in Spokane.
I'm sure you've heard of them.
I think you'd like her.
Maybe I'll invite her over for dinner.
I mean, no sense in getting involved
in another relationship
without your blessing, right?
- [Marie] Ut oh, he's back.
Mr. Wonderful.
- Well, he's nice.
- Who's his South Hill?
And what's he after a laundry manager for?
As if I didn't know.
- I was hoping you'd be on duty.
This laundry has a certain
attraction for pretty women.
- [Ginny] Hi, Kevin.
- Hi.
Hi, Marie.
- Hi, Kevin.
Goodbye, Kevin.
Call me later, Gin, okay?
- It's good to see you, Ginny.
Okay, I confess, there are
laundromats closer to my house.
How's school?
- It's hectic.
Exams are coming up.
- I really admire you.
Not a lot of people who would work
full time and go to school.
You're really something.
Oh, I've embarrassed you, I'm sorry.
But I meant it.
Well, my laundry is calling.
(romantic music)
There is one question you
haven't asked me, Ginny.
- [Ginny] Well, actually there are lots.
- The laundry; nightgowns, the lingerie.
You have noticed, right?
They're Jennifer's, my ex-wife's.
She's an alcoholic.
We got divorced about a year ago,
she tried to make it on
her own but she couldn't.
I felt so sorry for her, I took her back.
But no one can help her and I was foolish
to think that I could.
(Ginny giggling)
- Yeah.
(Kevin chuckling)
- Well, my real name is Fred.
Fredrick Harlen Coe, I chose Kevin.
- Virginia K. Perham,
it's nice to meet you.
Very nice.
And thank you for a
marvelous lunch, Mr. Coe.
- Ah.
- What?
- Oh nothing, really, I just
fell while I was jogging,
it's nothing really.
- Oh, let me see.
- No.
What a klutz, falling
while I'm jogging, huh?
Where were we?
I hope to see you soon.
- Me, too.
(Kevin whistling)
- [Tom] Kevin, you got a moment?
- [Kevin] For you sir, always.
- But not for selling houses?
- [Kevin] Pardon?
- You've been here almost a year
and you've done is run up office expenses.
Not a single sale or
single closing, nothing.
- I understand, Tom, this is a business,
you have to run it like a business.
But the thing is, I have finally
cleared away every distraction.
I'm ready to go full-steam
ahead into real estate.
So, I even got a new car.
Why?
For clients.
It's the only reason.
- It's not just for lack of sales.
You don't show up for floor time,
you don't answer your messages,
your mother calls constantly demanding
to know where you are.
I can't--
- She won't take her medication, Tom.
I have pleaded with her.
Look, I'll call her psychiatrist
and I'll get her back into treatment,
and I'll tell you what.
I will forgo commissions
on my next five sales.
Fair enough?
- I'm afraid I've gotta let you go.
- Why?
What did I ever do to you?
- [Tom] Pardon?
Kevin, this isn't personal.
- Oh, please.
Obviously this is some kind of vendetta.
Afraid I'm gonna take your
job from you, is that it?
- Kevin, this business just isn't for you.
Your mind isn't on it,
but I'm sure you'll find something else.
- Fine, it's cool.
You know, you're doing me a favor.
You ever heard of
commercial real estate, Tom?
That's what I'm into and I
was gonna bring it to you,
but you blew it.
Who knows, maybe I can
give you a job some day.
(car engine rumbling)
- [Tom] I need your lockbox keys.
(muffled talking)
- [Receptionist] Can I help you?
- How dare you harass our family.
First you vindictively fire son
and then you hound us
for some ridiculous key.
- It is a lockbox key, Mrs. Coe.
If he doesn't return it we'll lose
our multiple listing rights in Spokane,
to say nothing of a $1,000
fine, I need it back.
- Do you have any idea
who you're speaking to?
We are the Coe's.
My husband is the managing editor
of the Courier, we are Spokane.
You're nothing but a parasite, Mr. Brody,
trying to suck a little pocket
change from the wealthy.
It won't work, and as
for your precious key,
you'll find it at the door
when Hell freezes over.
(keys jingling)
(car engine rumbling)
(tires screeching)
He's an utter fool, a cipher.
We needn't concern ourself
with the Brody's of the world.
- I couldn't agree more.
Listen, I'll have another job by tomorrow.
I'm not the least bit worried.
I hope you're not.
I got to think of that
commercial property,
you were dead right.
It's a gold mine, it's just sitting there,
it's waiting for me.
I have so much I can do
with it, I can, I can...
- The problem dear, is
you have no character.
It's something I have finally faced,
and we must do something about it now.
Your car, you can't go to Gordon anymore
if you're unable to make the payments.
We will feed you, nothing
more, not another dime.
From this day forward,
you will pay your own
way in the real world.
I will not have my own son
be an embarrassment to the Coe name.
(light dramatic music)
Breakfast is at 7:00, dinner at 6:00.
I don't care where you live,
I don't even care about the
sluts you choose for company,
but you will pay your own way,
you will live up to your name,
and you will become a man.
Now, go have your little
tantrum if you must.
I'll see you at dinner.
We're having lamb, your favorite.
- You rotten bitch!
(upbeat music)
(muffled talking)
- [Man] That's hot.
- It's a beautiful day
here in Constad Park.
Why don't you sneak out of your offices,
come on down and say
hi on your lunch break.
(audience cheering)
Get a little sunshine in your life.
Now how about some digestive music.
This is Sunshine Shelly
on KQNT broadcasting to
you live and in color.
We're live and colorfully
from downtown Spokane,
the all American city.
(audience cheering)
- I read it.
- His sorted sexual desires
fit a pattern of other South Hill rapes.
Now, if the damn newspaper can
see a pattern, why can't you?
- Don't push me, Trent,
this articles gonna cause
panic, the last thing we need.
- 41 women have been raped,
there are probably more.
Bureau's still don't exchange information
and we need an official centralized--
- We have never faced
anything like this in Spokane,
the mechanism isn't there.
The mentality isn't there.
The captain told me the best way for women
to handle rape was just
lay back and enjoy it.
- He said that?
- He said that.
I'm doing what I can, Liz.
And in the meantime, try decoys.
Use male officers, you hear me?
Dressed as women.
Catch the bastard in the act.
(light dramatic music)
(paper crinkling)
(keyboard clicking)
- Excellent recommendation.
I've heard of this group.
They write a few letters
they wrote to the papers.
Real pro-Spokane organization.
Jay seems to think pretty
highly of you, too.
I think you'll fit right
in at Vista Reality.
Welcome aboard.
- I can't believe you're here Coe.
The old team together again.
- I'm here.
I'm on my way Willy Jay, life
has never been better, never.
No more foolin' around.
- [Jay] Well I'm glad
to hear you say that,
because we're not granted
the same latitude you had at Brody.
We either perform or we're outa here.
- I may even get married,
what do you think about that?
- Ginny?
It's gotten that serious?
- Damn right, Jaybo, in fact,
I may go give her the good news right now.
- Now?
We've got an open house at Newman's Lake.
- I'll meet you there.
Our first sale together.
- [Jay] You'll never make it on time.
- Speedy car.
- Ooh, you smell good.
(car tires squeaking)
What?
(hushes)
- Listen.
- What is it?
- It's Jennifer's car.
- You told me she wasn't here.
- I also told you she was
crazy, now stay there.
Don't make a scene.
- Hi, honey.
- Hey.
- [Jennifer] I got off early.
It looks like you had
someone over for dinner.
I see you left all the dishes for me.
- [Kevin] Jay came by.
- [Jennifer] How does he rate at dinner?
- [Kevin] You look great.
- Oh thanks, thanks.
You know, did you leave any--
(crashing)
What was that?
Somebody's here.
Who the hell are you?
Is this your latest, Kevin?
Huh?
Don't just stand there, get
the hell out of my house.
- Wait, wait, hey.
Come on, come on, calm down.
Now, I can explain this.
This is, Ginny, where are you going?
- Get her out of my house--
- Now look what you've done.
- He ripped up my shirt and he
was kinda like on all fours.
He used, I can't say the words he said.
Real dirty.
- [Liz] Um, did he have an orgasm?
- Excuse me?
- I asked her if he'd had an
orgasm, but she wasn't sure.
She doesn't even know what an orgasm is.
She is only 14 years old
and her life is ruined,
and somebody's gotta stop this guy.
(dog barking)
- Ginny.
Ginny.
Please, just hear me out.
I didn't know Jennifer was coming over.
She still thinks she lives there.
I don't love her, Ginny.
I just wanna be with you.
I love you, Ginny.
- You made me feel terrible last night.
You lied to me, Kevin.
- Never, I would never lie to you.
- Well, I don't wanna see you again.
- You don't mean that.
You don't mean that.
You wouldn't throw us away.
I know what you feel.
You just look me in the eye
and you tell me that you don't love me.
You just tell me and I'll go.
Do you love me, Ginny?
- Yes.
I do.
God, Kevin, I love you.
- And we play among
the huge oaks that line
the driveway up to the main
house and in the spring,
oh Virginia, I can smell them to this day.
The magnolias in full bloom,
nothing is sweeter on Earth.
It was a crime the way
the Yankees ravaged us.
Thank the lord we were able
to recover from what they did.
- Mother, I don't think Ginny
wants to hear about the old south.
- Why son, it's for you.
Every girl wants to hear
all about her man's family.
Don't you love me enough to
let me share my memories?
Just look me in the eye and tell me
that you don't, and I'll stop.
(light dramatic music)
I'm waiting, son.
- Of course I love you, don't be silly.
I just didn't want you
to rehash the civil war.
- Are you from Spokane, Ginny?
- [Ginny] I was born here,
but I traveled a lot.
My father was in the Air Force,
but I wouldn't live any place else.
- She's studying art,
writing and philosophy.
I'm trying to get her into real estate,
she is a natural for it.
- Well, I admire anyone who can
pull herself up by her bootstraps.
- Oh, well you don't have
to feel sorry for me,
I had a wonderful childhood.
- Would you like some more pie?
- Oh, I couldn't, but it was delicious.
- It's son's favorite.
Oh, just look at you two.
Such a handsome couple.
Honestly, I was worried.
Kevin hasn't always brought home
the most suitable women, Ginny.
I'm proud of him though.
Fine new job, and you're so lovely.
Can I say that without
horribly embarrassing you both.
(Ruth giggling)
(Kevin chuckling)
- You never told me
she was from the south.
- Well, she isn't, not really.
She likes to pretend.
Gone With The Wind is her Bible.
It's harmless, though.
She loved you.
She told me.
Did you like her?
- Well, yes, I mean
she's such a character.
Your father seems like
a real nice man, too.
- Listen, Ginny, I've been thinking.
You shouldn't be in that house
alone and now that Jennifer
has moved out, why don't
you move in with me?
- You mean live together?
- Yeah, yeah, why not?
- Oh, I'd like that, Kevin.
- [Cashier] Price check
register number six,
code MI5 please.
- [Woman] He tried to tell me no.
Yeah, I meant to try it.
- He's back.
- [Cashier] Okay, here we go.
Did you bring your coupons?
Yeah?
- Yeah.
- [Cashier] You finally remembered.
- I want him this time.
- [Cashier] Okay, let
me count 'em up here.
- Let's go.
- All right.
- Hey.
Hey.
- Yeah?
What are you, what?
- You didn't pay for this.
- Oh, I completely forgot.
I'm sorry, I was thinking
about something else.
- Come on, we'll have to go inside.
- [Kevin] What for?
- For shoplifting.
- Shoplifting?
I told you, I forgot to pay.
- [Man] You've been seen twice before.
- Of course you've seen me,
I'm a regular customer here.
Now look, how much do I
owe you, I'd never steal.
- Come on, let's go upstairs.
- Forget it.
- Hey.
- You run, I'll break your legs.
- Are you nuts?
Do you know who you're messing with.
I will sue you blind.
- Yeah, what's your name?
- Go to hell.
(door slamming)
- When did this happen?
- Huh?
Oh, about three weeks ago.
The manager tried to frame me.
I simply forgot to pay.
The thing is though, if
I'm convicted, I'm dead.
I mean, who's gonna trust their
investments to a shoplifter?
- Well, nobody in their right mind
will find you guilty, just tell the judge.
- No, don't be naive.
Now these two guys, they'll
lie their heads off.
- Well maybe you should hire a lawyer.
- A lawyer?
Ha, I can defend myself
better than any lawyer.
I think what I need is a witness.
I'd like you to testify for me?
- You mean, like a character witness?
- No, something like you were
waiting out in the car for me
and I came out and I remembered
that I had forgotten to pay,
and then I started back and
these guys they grabbed me.
Like that, how does that sound?
- Terrible.
That's perjury, I can't do that.
- Ginny, oh you don't
think I'm guilty, do you?
- Well no, it was all just a mistake.
Just tell the judge.
- I need you to back me up.
I don't think there's any other
way that I'm gonna beat it.
Just back me up, okay?
- Forget it.
I won't do it, Kevin.
- I can't believe it.
That stupid judge didn't
buy a word of your story.
Did he think you would lie?
A person of your background?
How can he be that stupid?
- Kevin, I did lie.
He just saw right through it.
- It was some kind of
pay off, I'm sure of it.
I was framed.
I'm morally opposed to all crime.
I would never steal.
Never.
(muffled talking)
- Kevin, please just drop it.
You only got three days
of community service,
you should be happy.
- Why are you turning on me like this?
We're living together, this is your home.
- My home?
Jennifer's stuff is all over this house
and I pay half the rent, remember?
And Kevin, you just have so many secrets.
Don't you trust me?
(Kevin chuckling)
Where are you going?
Kevin what are you doing down there?
- [Kevin] Don't come down here.
- How can you just walk
away from me like that?
Kevin?
- [Kevin] You know what I think?
I think you're too selfish and immature
for a real relationship,
that's what I think.
You can't even control yourself,
don't try to control me.
What is it, sex?
Is that what you're after?
- [Ginny] Oh, if I was
looking for sex Kevin,
I wouldn't be with you.
I'm sorry, I didn't mean that.
Don't go out.
Where are you going?
- I need to be alone.
- [Ginny] Well, I don't
wanna be let alone anymore.
I want you here.
- Get off my back!
(door slamming)
- You can't treat me like this, Kevin.
I won't be here when you get back.
- Who cares.
I mean, who the hell cares?
(car engine rumbling)
(tires screeching)
- [Shelly] That wraps
it up for another night.
Gotta go home and feed my parakeet.
This is Sunshine Shelly saying good night,
until another sunny day.
(dramatic music)
(leaves rustling)
(heavy breathing)
(Shelly screaming)
- She was out there an hour, naked.
It's 34 degrees.
She won't let me touch her.
(Shelly coughing)
- Okay.
It's gonna be okay.
I promise you, you're gonna be okay.
(Shelly gasping)
He still hasn't given
us a special rape squad.
- [Matt] Give him time, Liz.
- We don't have time.
Listen, I've been
thinking about something.
Why don't we do it ourselves?
Get volunteers, off duty
cops, work on our own time.
What do you think?
- [Matt] Well, it's a good idea.
- It's a great idea.
I'll start to make some calls.
- To your first sale.
(glasses clinking)
- To the first of many.
Vista Reality has a much broader listing
than Brody, including commercial property.
Thank you very much.
I have a great plan.
- [Ruth] Or just plan
to make a lot of money.
You're the only insurance policy I've got.
- Have no fear, mother dear,
and thank you for lunch.
Champagne is great.
- You're a good boy, aren't you?
- The best you've got.
- Well, maybe not that good.
You didn't have $8.08 that day?
Oh, I'm not angry.
I'm just surprised by how
really stupid you are.
And to get it erased from your record,
well it'll be a little
messy, but I'll do it.
I'll do it.
Now, why don't you have lunch alone.
Now, don't be upset.
I'm very proud of your
new job and I like Ginny.
I think she'll be very good for you.
You know what the truth is, Kevin?
I could dump you and never see you again
and it wouldn't bother me a bit.
(muffled talking)
(phone ringing)
- [Liz] Shelly.
- Have you got anything?
Anything at all?
- No, not yet.
- I slept in my closet for the first week.
I'd come home, I'd take
out a butcher knife
and check in every square
inch of my apartment.
- Are you going back on the air, Shelly?
- Oh, I don't if I--
- I miss you, you know.
- I don't know.
Yeah, I guess so.
What else am I gonna do?
Hide from him forever?
David and I are getting a divorce.
- Oh, no, Shelly why?
I thought he was okay?
(Shelly crying)
- I wanted to talk about it.
You know, I needed to talk
about it to get everything out,
but I guess...
- [Man] Here it is, captain.
- I guess the marriage
just couldn't handle it.
(Shelly bawling)
(sprinkler ticking)
(knocking)
- Ginny, what a nice surprise.
I'm afraid Kevin isn't home.
- [Ginny] I know.
- Oh, well, do come in.
Have you had lunch?
- Kevin and I had a fight
and I was just hoping
that you'd be able to
help me to understand it.
- Why even bother?
He doesn't deserve you, Ginny,
none of the Coe men are any damn good.
They can't provide.
I couldn't believe he forced
you to pay half the rent.
- He didn't force me, I offered.
- Now, you don't have to
defend him, I know what he is.
- You know, I'm not so
sure you do, Mrs. Coe.
- I'm his mother, dear.
Don't pretend you know
what makes him tick.
- I better go, I shouldn't have come.
- Hi.
Hi.
What a nice surprise.
My two favorite girls.
- You're pathetic.
How dare you take money from a woman.
You call yourself a man?
Are you completely spineless?
- What are you talking about?
I've never borrowed anything from her.
- I am so sick of your lies.
Are you using her money to pay your bills?
- I pay all my bills and I'll
pay you back every penny.
- [Ginny] Kevin, let's go.
- How dare you embarrass me like this.
I wish you'd never been.
- Oh, go ahead, say it mother.
I've heard it before.
Don't be bashful just 'cause Ginny's here.
- My God, you are rotten.
- Kevin, let's just get out of here.
- All those promises he made,
to take care of me, lies, all lies.
You were gonna make so
proud, you make me sick.
I'm grateful you're merely my son
and I never had to have you in my bed.
(door slamming)
(woman screaming)
(fist thudding)
- [Man] I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
- [Man] More bags over here.
- How's the woman?
- He almost broke her neck.
He's getting more and more violent.
If we don't stop him soon
he's gonna kill somebody.
- I got your rape squad, officially.
And I've ordered them to do a complete
statistical study of
the rapes immediately.
I'm sorry it took so long.
- Thanks Lieutenant.
- Hey, Liz.
I think we made his car.
The custodian described
a silver gray Chevy
that was parked over there
about 6:30 with a warm motor,
gone by 7:15, the time fits.
- [Liz] Did he get a license number?
- He can't have everything,
but he did remember that it was in state,
with a clear yellow cover over it
to make it look personalized.
What kind of a jerk would want it
to look like he had a
personalized license?
(car door slamming)
(dog barking)
- Kevin?
- [Kevin] Yeah?
- Where have you been all night?
I was worried about you.
- You shouldn't have bothered.
- [Ginny] Open the door.
(knocking on the door)
I said open the door.
(banging on door)
- What?
- Can I come in?
Open the door.
Kevin!
Kevin, open the door!
- [Kevin] Stop spying on me,
I'm trying to wash up in here.
- Kevin, open the door.
(Kevin groaning)
Kevin!
- What?
- [Ginny] What happened?
- I was jogging, a dog jumped me.
- [Ginny] No dog would
mark you up like that.
Did you get in a fight or something?
It looks like fingernail scratches.
- What, I was trying to get
away and I fell in the bushes.
Now don't mother me, I'm fine.
I have to get ready for work now, okay?
(door slamming)
- You know, your mother
was terrible last night.
She's called four or five times since.
I'm sorry about the
things she said to you.
- Don't be, I'm used to it.
- I found something out about you.
- Yeah, what?
- [Ginny] I mean, in some
ways you're a lot like her.
- Of course I'm like her,
that's the big thing that you found out?
- But you don't have to be.
I mean, she just has
such a strong influence,
it's the way that she wants you to be.
Oh, I don't know.
- No, you don't know.
So why don't you just stay out of it.
- No, I'm in it.
I love you, Kevin.
That's what I'm saying.
I don't think she does.
- Your mother killed herself.
That's how much she loved you.
- My mother was ill for a long time.
She just couldn't take the pain anymore.
She didn't do it to hurt me.
- I know Ruth, she gets nuts sometimes.
She'll get over it.
- Oh, I'm sure, but will you, you're so--
- What?
What?
You think I'm crazy, right?
Isn't that what this is all about?
- No.
I just think that she's harmed you.
- Why do you care?
- That's the whole damn point.
I do care, but you lie to me.
You keep secrets, you go places,
you don't tell me where you're going.
You don't trust me.
Kevin, I love you.
You don't believe that.
You believe whatever it is
that your mother tells you.
I don't.
I see someone to love.
Someone trying to love me.
Aren't you?
(phone ringing)
Don't answer it, Kevin.
- Hello?
- [Ruth] Hello, darling.
- Hello, mother.
- [Ruth] You all right, Coco?
You sound strange.
- I'm late for work, what is it?
- [Ruth] Don't you have just a minute?
Look, I'm sorry.
We really mustn't fight anymore.
Your barging in the house like that,
I'm afraid I lost my temper
and Ginny certainly didn't help things.
- [Kevin] Just leave her out of it.
- [Ruth] And then Gordon and
I had a fight and I just,
I just wanted to hear
your voice, that's all.
I'm glad you're there.
I love you.
- I have to go, goodbye.
- Kevin.
(thudding)
- [Man] Unlock cell
four when we get there.
- Hey.
Try to imagine it, the DMV moved quickly.
Here's a list of every silver
Chevy owner in Spokane.
- It must our lucky day,
here's the FBI profile.
Wanna hear it?
- Uh, okay, I guess so.
Yes!
- A power rapist seems
to have a special hatred
for medium sized dark haired women.
Where is it?
Oh, yeah.
May come from a well to do family.
The rapist is an underachiever
who indicates that
he's totally dominated by
someone, possibly a parent.
He's emotionally undeveloped.
And, listen to this.
Now, he's motivated by rage, not lust,
and his main intent is
to degrade the victim.
They said that subconsciously
he probably wants
to degrade the person who dominates him.
- And the hand down the throat?
- Trying to shut her up.
- [Liz] Her?
Yeah, her.
Well, whoever she is, she is
good looking with dark hair.
- This is just too weird.
Listen to this description.
He had a modulated sort of loving voice
when he called me beautiful.
I mean, what kinda creep is this guy?
- Your problem is you
believe everything you read.
- What the hell have the police
been doing all this time?
There're vigilante gangs out there
following bus lines with shotguns.
I swear, if I had my old M-16
I'd be out there with 'em.
- So part of your Christian ethic?
Sounds terrific.
- [Jay] Hey, what's wrong?
Kevin, are you okay?
- Of course I'm okay.
- Are you sure, because lately
you've seemed a little uptight and weird.
- Don't call me weird, Jay.
- All right, a little moody then?
- You're my friend.
I know that, so I'm gonna
tell you what's wrong, okay?
Life is too short for
everything I wanna do.
I wish I had more time.
- What's the matter?
Did I do something to turn you off?
- I can't.
I can't.
Nothing's happening.
- It's okay.
- Its not okay, it's humiliating.
- Well, we can just lie in each
others arms and fall asleep.
Being together is just
the same as making love.
- I'm sorry.
I can't do anything right.
I try to show you how much I
love you, and look what I do.
My mother's right, I'm an idiot.
- Kevin.
- You don't do anything that she does.
You're not anything like she is.
You don't belittle me like
she does, you don't punish me.
When I, when I was a kid.
- Kevin.
You know, you can tell me, I love you.
- When I was a kid, and I
would put my feet on the sofa,
she would make me sit
absolutely still for an hour,
and that damn dog of hers
could jump on everything.
He was more important to her than I was.
She wanted to abort me, she told me.
She was right, it would've been better
if I had never been born.
- Don't say that, sweetheart.
Come here.
Forget about her, forget about everything.
- I wish I could.
She was right about one thing.
- What?
- That you were the right girl for me.
You are.
I don't, I don't deserve a
girl as good as you, Ginny.
- It's okay.
We don't have to stay in
Spokane, we can move to L.A..
Oh, don't cry, baby.
Please don't cry.
It's gonna be all right.
(muffled talking)
- Morning.
- I think we found our guy.
Out of all the Chevrolet
owners, one lives right here.
- Right in the middle of South Hill.
From a well to do family.
So, what's wrong?
- Car is registered to Gordon Coe,
managing editor of the Courier.
- You gotta be kidding me.
- Not him, his son.
- Frederick Harlen Coe.
- No.
- [Matt] You ever see this guy?
- Yes.
That's him.
I mean, his hair is different,
but, but that's him.
- [Matt] You're absolutely certain?
- Well, I'd like to see
him and hear him talk,
but, but, yes I'm almost positive.
- We can't pull him in
on a 13 year old photo,
we need a recent one.
- Didn't you say he sells real estate?
- Yeah, but so what?
- Don't you need to buy a house?
- Judy?
- Yes.
- Hi.
- I'm Kevin Coe.
- Oh, nice to meet you.
- Hi.
- My husband and I love this neighborhood.
Now, isn't there a school
up on the next block?
- I don't know.
- Oh, because I was driving by this one,
I thought it to be a school
with a yard or something
that I didn't know if it
was like a junior high.
- Hello Ginny.
Here, let me help you with those.
Don't you just loathe shopping?
- How did you get in here?
- [Ruth] I know where he hides the key.
Honestly, when I see how
he lives I'm appalled.
There's no furniture in there.
Where do your guests sit?
- Mrs. Coe, I really don't appreciate you
coming in to my house like this.
- Now, now, it's not
your house yet, Ginny.
I'm sure Gordon's still paying for it,
and take that sour look off your face,
I'm not gonna steal anything.
Including Kevin, he's all yours.
You're the best thing
that ever happened to him.
I wish you luck.
- It's me.
I checked out the rents
in L.A., guess what,
they're not as bad as we thought.
- What rents?
What is this?
Are you going somewhere?
I demand to know.
Kevin, is this another one
of your skulking deceptions?
- Relax, mother.
You spoiled the whole surprise.
The deal in L.A., the disco, it's set.
We are going to L.A..
Ginny and me and the.
Gordo, he can visit on the holidays.
- Oh, I don't believe
any of this of course.
- Doesn't matter whether
you believe it or not
because it's true.
Ginny didn't even know
till this very moment.
- Los Angeles Coco?
- Not Los Angeles.
Malibu.
Bev Hills.
- Oh.
(Kevin chuckling)
- Okay, okay, we'll be
practical, Brentwood.
A nice house, we'll rent before we buy.
A warm climate.
Us in the dirty dancing
capital of the world,
with a disco, and the best
of all, not in Spokane.
(Ruth giggling)
- Oh, yes.
- [Doctor] Take 25 milliliters.
- [Woman] Dr. Granville,
please call the operator, Dr. Granville.
Dr. Burrows, call 125 West.
- Hey Liz, it's Matt.
Jeanie Maise.
No, she can't talk, he used
an oven mitt this time.
Nearly tore her throat out.
Yeah, they think she'll make it.
They hope.
- You be on the D.A.'s desk
8:00 a.m. for a warrant.
I will get ahold of Irene
Pool, show her these photos.
Tomorrows the last day of freedom
for this filthy son of a bitch.
(knocking on door)
- Are you Ginny Perham?
- [Ginny] Yes.
- I'm detective Liz Trent,
we have a search warrant.
May we come in?
- [Ginny] This is my boyfriend's house,
he's not here right now.
- We know where he is.
I wanna talk to you.
- [Officer] Bob you take the kitchen.
- [Officer] You got it.
- [Officer] You go back in the
hallway, I'll check this way.
- [Officer] Yes, sir.
- [Officer] This like
the one we looking for?
- Shall we sit down?
- Check those closets.
Look for any garden suites.
- Sure.
- Ginny, Kevin is wanted
for first degree rape.
We think he's the South Hill rapist.
Several women have identified him.
I'm very sorry for your sake.
- Kevin?
Well how?
I would know.
I mean, I would've known.
- Now Ginny, we need your help
to find some of these things.
- Oh, my God.
Oh, my God, Kevin.
- [Officer] What's the
color on that parka?
- I don't understand.
These things were here a few days ago.
- [Officer] Liz.
- Are these his?
- Yes.
He was washing them like
last week and asked him why,
but he wouldn't tell me.
Is it important?
- Ginny, you must've seen some things
without really knowing
what you were seeing.
Would you be willing to testify?
- No.
I couldn't do that.
- I've seen this house.
Pictured it in my mind.
The the way great things are conquered,
from women to wealth.
But this house is rare.
It's located a Big Sur, 1,000
feet above the Pacific Ocean.
Made from rough hewn timbers
scavenged from ship wrecks.
Glass on glass.
- Frederick Harlen Coe.
- I'm Kevin Coe, can I help you?
- You're under arrest for
the rape of Irene Pool.
- What?
- There must be some mistake.
I don't even know this women.
Are you guys confused?
- No, we're not.
You're the one we want.
Cuff him.
You have the right
- Is this some kinda joke?
- To remain silent.
- What the hell is this?
- If you give up the right
to remain silent,
- Is this a joke?
- Anything you say can and
will be used against you.
- You can't take him.
- In a court of law.
- He hasn't done anything.
- You have the right to speak
with an attorney and to have the attorney
present during questioning.
- Kevin, this is ridiculous.
- If you so desire and cannot
- Want me to call Gordon?
- Afford one, an attorney
will be appointed for you without charge,
before questioning.
- This is a joke, right?
- Get him outa here.
- Do you understand each
- Don't sweat it buddy.
- of these rights as I
have explained them to you?
- [Jay] We'll get you out.
(light dramatic music)
- [Liz] Number four, read please.
- Don't look at my face.
Do as I say or I'll kill ya.
- It's him.
I'm positive.
His voice.
I'll never forget that.
Never.
- Thank you, Miss Pool, very much.
(muffled talking)
Hi, Shelly.
How you doin'?
- Well, I met some nice
rape victims in the hall.
It's a large group.
Shall we get on with it?
It's nothing.
It was so dark, I never got a good look.
I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
I was glad to hear you
back on the air again.
- Well, thanks for helping me get back.
I wish that I had seen him.
I should have fought harder.
But I was so scared.
- The way we look at it,
Shelly, if you make it through
a rape alive, you did the right thing.
- You'd have to see the
guys face in broad daylight
and they'd have to be
able to recognize him
in the lineup cold, and even then
you only get 2% convictions.
- But six women have identified him.
- Only six out of all those who came in.
It's bad numbers for the good guys.
He almost always attacked from behind
and a night, he was very clever.
I wonder how many didn't report.
Never told anyone.
Or they left town, they're
too scared, too ashamed.
I wonder what those numbers are?
- [Man] Hey Walco.
- I wanna win too, Liz,
for the brave ones as well as the timid.
(dramatic music)
- Son.
Son.
I want you to look me in the eye.
Kevin, I want you to look me in the eye
and tell me you did not
rape all those women.
Can you do that?
Just look me in the eye and tell me
and I can get you out of here.
- I didn't do it.
I didn't rape those women.
I'm innocent.
- I know.
I know, darling, I've
known it from the start.
They were just out to
smear us, that's all.
In a minute, Gordon.
Don't you worry, Coco.
I'll get you out.
You'll be free soon.
(dramatic music)
I love you.
- I hope you know I'm innocent.
- I know.
It just, it doesn't fit.
Kevin, I hope you know that
I'll do everything I can.
(dramatic music)
Mr. Coe.
- [Gordon] Jay.
- I think we need to step
into your office for a moment, sir.
(muffled talking)
- But what does she think?
- Yeah, put that.
- [Man] I believe you have
been good service before.
- Mr. Coe, Kevin's guilty and you have
to convince him to plea bargain.
- Jay, I've seen the evidence.
He's innocent.
- He asked me to dispose of some evidence.
I had it in my hands,
Mr. Coe, in my hands.
I got rid of that stuff,
but when I saw it,
I knew that he did it.
All the funny little episodes
and all the unexplained things.
He did it, Mr. Coe.
He's the rapist.
- I understand how you
might think that, Jay,
but I've seen enough of the
evidence to think he's innocent.
- Mr. Coe, will you please wake up.
Kevin has been lying and trying to charm
his way out of everything his entire life,
but this time it won't work, sir.
He's guilty.
- He lied to you constantly.
You don't owe him a damn thing.
He preys on honest people like you.
You have to testify, Ginny.
- But who would believe me?
I lied for him in court once already.
- So?
Now you have a chance to tell the truth.
Do you really think he loved you?
The way you love him?
(knocking on door)
I'll get it.
What the hell are you doing here?
- [Kevin] Hi Marie, I'm out on bail.
- [Marie] It's illegal for you to be here.
- [Kevin] No, my dad's in
the car, I'm in his custody.
Is Ginny here?
- I'm here.
- Gordo bailed me out.
Can you believe that?
He sold the Cadillac.
Marie, can we have a
little privacy, thank you.
- It's all right, Marie, really.
- I'll be in the kitchen,
call me if you need me.
- Why are you here?
- I had to see you.
You didn't come to the
jail, I was going nuts.
- How could you do it?
How could you make love to me
and be out raping other women.
- You don't really think that I--
- Oh, stop it.
Stop lying to me, to
everyone, to yourself.
Women have identified you.
Don't mock me by lying to me anymore.
- Ginny, I'm not.
I swear it.
I have never raped anyone.
I was even afraid of hurting
you when we made love.
Now how could I rape somebody?
- You have hurt me so much, Kevin.
I loved you.
- And I love you, I adore you.
- Oh, get your hands off of me.
You don't love anything.
There's nothing inside of you.
Everything was lies, everything.
You are so pathetic you make me sick.
- You sound like my mother.
- I'm sorry.
- Ginny, I need your help.
Jay refused to help me.
Ruth is too obvious.
I need you, Ginny.
I need you to testify for me.
You're the only one who
knows what I'm like.
You have to tell them what I'm
really like, Ginny, please.
Please.
- [Man] Hey, Jack, get down here.
They're here.
(reporters talking over each other)
- [Man] How about a statement for a--
- [Man] Please.
- [Woman] Has he been naughty?
- [Man] Mr. And Mrs. Coe.
- [Man] A statement for the press, please.
- [Woman] Mrs. Coe, was Kevin guilty?
- Would you please give us room?
(muffled talking)
- He shoved his hand a
little further down my throat
so I really couldn't scream.
He was wearing gloves.
- [Lawyer] Can you describe these gloves?
- They were dark leather.
I can't be sure of the exact color.
- And how do you know they were leather?
- I tasted them.
- Oh, what a case.
- How terrible.
- Sue Ann, is the man who raped you
inside this courtroom now?
- Yes.
That man over there.
- [Lawyer] Let the record
state that the witness
has identified the defendant
Frederick Harlen Coe.
- Sue Ann, in the police lineup,
how did you identify
the man who raped you.
- It was the voice mostly.
- According to this
report you told officers
that you never saw the man's face.
Is that correct?
- Yes.
- I have nothing further.
- I just don't think rape is any big deal.
I've known a lot of women who were raped,
didn't bother them.
Picked themselves up,
dusted themselves off.
Very good friend of my
mine was raped twice,
didn't let it ruin her life.
- Well, I think the courts take
a different view of it, Ruth.
- Oh, I saw that Irene Pool by the way,
that jogger that Kevin illegibly raped.
No one's gonna believe her.
Older women don't get
raped for heaven's sake.
(knocking on door)
- Surprised?
- Actually, yeah.
I've been following the trial.
- Me too, I'm suing them all.
The prosecutor, the city, Spokane P.D..
We can work on the lawsuits together
Willy Jay, we'll be rich.
Rolling in it.
- Sure.
- I was trying to catch
the South Hill rapist.
Now once they realize
that they'll understand
why I was out there where he was.
Ruth knew about it.
Honestly, Jay, it would really cinch it
for me if you would testify.
- To what?
- That we were both out there
trying to catch the creep.
You'd pose as a women,
I'd follow you in the car,
and we'd wait for the rapist to attack.
Like that.
- Kevin, my credibility
as a witness was destroyed
when you asked me to get
rid of that stuff for you.
What if they ask me about it in court?
- I'm being railroaded, Jay.
The cops talked all
those women into lying.
Now, how am I supposed to
fight a frame like that?
They would never doubt a
solid Christian like you.
- Kevin, listen to me.
If you want to get off, plead insanity.
Try to get into one of those
sexual psychopath programs.
You'll be out in a year or two.
- I would never lie about my sanity.
Never.
You know what the problem is?
You think I'm guilty, Jay.
Don't you?
Come on, say it to your old buddy.
Come on, say it!
- I think you are guilty, Kevin.
- Miss Perham, can you tell
me what this is a picture of?
- It's a photo I took last summer
of Mr. Coe in his gray sweatsuit.
- And what has happened to the sweatsuit?
- It turned up missing the
day Mr. Coe was arrested.
- And did Mr. Coe where anything else
when he went out jogging?
- Yes, a pair of heavy
black leather gloves.
- Describe them for the
court if you will please.
- Well, they became
more and more beaten up
and I noticed a few tears.
The last time I saw them they
were all scarred and torn.
At the end, the fingers were coming off.
- Miss Perham, would you
describe for this jury,
what Mr. Coe would do preparatory
to having intercourse with you?
- Objection, I don't think the sex life
at home as anything to do with this.
- Subject irrelevancy.
You may precede.
- [Lawyer] Miss Perham, would
you describe for the jury,
exactly what Mr. Coe would do preparatory
to having intercourse with you?
- He...
He would of, most often, the nod.
He would.
- His M.O. as a rapist was
the same as in the bedroom.
I think we've got him, Matt.
- [Matt] He got himself.
- Okay, bye.
- Ruth.
- [Woman] Okay, great,
I need to get the file.
- Didn't you tell Kevin that he was
the best thing that ever happened to you?
That he was lifting you up
into a new social strata.
- I don't remember using those words.
- [Karen] Isn't it true, Ginny,
that you wanted to marry Kevin Coe?
- Yes.
- And don't you now feel
like a woman scorned?
- No.
- Nothing further.
Defense calls Ruth Coe.
(muffled talking)
- Kevin tried very hard
to catch the rapist.
He felt it was his duty.
The citizen review splash on rape
in the bus routes inspired
us to keep on trying.
So instead of son jogging and
me following him in the car,
we followed the buses to see
if a man got off when a lady did.
We were hoping to identify
a potential rapist.
- [Karen] How many times did
you follow buses with Kevin?
- [Ruth] Oh, um, 10, 12, maybe more.
I wish we'd been more successful.
- [Karen] How would you characterize
your sons relationship with Miss Perham.
- Well, I know he felt the compassion
for her that we all felt.
- Objection, unresponsive.
- Just describe the relationship
between Kevin and Ginny.
- Yes, well, I felt--
- Objection, witness is
stating her feelings.
- Sustained.
Mrs. Coe, please answer
the question directly.
- Oh, thank you, Your Honor.
It was like Henry Higgins
and Eliza Doolittle in My Fair Lady.
He gave her a sense of style,
improved her posture, how she dressed.
He accomplished an amazing transformation.
- Mrs. Coe, you've testified
that your son was with you
at the times of the rapes he's accused of.
- [Ruth] Yes, he was.
- Do you remember that on April 14th,
you told investigators that Kevin
was with you while you went
to visit a hairdresser?
- Yes.
- [Lawyer] And do you
also remember that when
the investigator checked it out,
he found that Kevin was with you
for only the last 15
minutes of your visits?
- [Karen] Objection.
- I'll withdrawal the question.
Mrs. Coe, haven't you
covered for Kevin before?
- If you mean would I lie--
- [Lawyer] I'm asking
whether you have ever said
your son was with you
at a time he was not.
Yes or no.
- No.
I have never lied for my son.
I don't have to cover for him.
He has nothing to hide.
- I can't believe he's gonna testify.
- Rumor has it his
lawyers couldn't stop him.
He's an ego wonder.
- [Karen] Please tell the
court your name and address.
- [Kevin] Frederick Harlen Coe.
I live at 1418 South Tyler, Spokane 99206.
- [Karen] Kevin, are you
the South Hill rapist?
- [Kevin] No.
- Kevin, each time you ate
dinner with your parents,
why did you tell Ginny you went jogging?
- There are great many
things I didn't tell Ginny.
She's an inquisitive person, jealous,
and constantly insinuating
that I was with other women.
So I would be vague.
I didn't think it was any of her business.
- And were you just as vague when
she asked you about
washing the oven mitts?
- I've never seen oven mitts in my house.
Maybe the police planted them?
- And the police planted
the story with Miss Perham?
- I didn't say that.
But I would say that at least
90% of her testimony is false.
- Is this the way you've
always known Ginny to be?
- Ginny's a sucker for anybody
who's good at persuasion.
The police may have manipulated her.
- Mr. Coe, have you ever
been convicted of a crime?
- Objection, prejudicial and irrelevant.
- [Lawyer] It is not only
relevant Your Honor, but--
- [Judge] Approach the bench.
(muffled whispering)
- [Lawyer] Well his line of questioning
to consider the relevancy, all right?
- Overruled, restate the question.
- Have you ever been
convicted of a crime, Mr. Coe.
- Of a misdemeanor, yes.
- [Lawyer] What was it?
- Third degree theft.
- And what did you steal?
- I didn't steal anything.
- [Lawyer] My mistake, what
were you convicted of stealing.
- A steak.
- [Lawyer] And after your conviction,
did you write Judge Murphy,
who presided over that trial a letter?
- Objection, the letter is irrelevant.
- [Lawyer] I will establish
relevance if council will allow.
- Overruled.
Continue.
- Did you write Judge Murphy a letter?
- Well, yes.
- Mr. Coe, let me read to you from
your own letter to Judge Murphy.
I quote, Miss Ginny Perham,
a very classy young lady,
with the upmost integrity was devastated
that the judge would call her a liar.
- She was devastated.
- So, you think that Miss
Perham is a lady of the upmost
integrity until she testifies against you?
- Well.
No.
Well, I mean, yes.
- [Lawyer] Your witness.
- [Woman] I think the biggest
surprise was to find out--
- [Man] It isn't fair, it isn't fair.
- [Woman] Mrs. Coe, do you think
they'll find your son guilty?
- [Man] Just a second, one shot
here, miss, please, please.
(reporters talking over each other)
- [Man] Can I get a shot?
- [Man] Was it smart to
have your son testify?
- [Bailiff] All rise, please.
- [Man] All right.
- Be seated.
Madam Foreman, your verdict.
Madam Foreman, you may read the verdict.
- We, the jury, find the
defendant Frederick Harlen Coe
on count number one, not guilty.
(audience groaning)
- [Judge] Order, order.
Order in the court!
- [Woman] I'm shocked.
- [Judge] Continue.
- On count number two, guilty.
On count number three, guilty.
On count number four, not guilty.
On count number five, guilty.
On count number six, guilty.
- The court is signing an order,
jailing the defendant
Frederick Harlen Coe.
This court is adjourned.
- [Man] Well, I guess he's gonna have to.
(muffled talking)
(phone ringing)
- Detective Trent.
You've gotta be kidding me.
She did what?
I, yes, I think we can handle that.
- [Ruth] Terry?
- Yeah, get in.
- [Ruth] How do I know you're not police?
- Do I look like a cop?
How do I know you're not a cop?
You want a job done?
- Actually, there're two
I would like taken out.
One is a judge.
A vicious cold man, a
vicious, vicious man.
The prosecutor, he's the other one.
I have their names and
addresses right here.
How much cash are we talking about?
- 500 up front, against 4,000.
Is that a problem?
- No, well, yes.
I have the down payment now.
The rest won't be easy,
but I'll get it because it's worth it.
- We are talking about
the same thing here?
You want these people--
Gone.
- Dead.
- Dead, right.
Well, if I had my druthers I'd like to see
the prosecutor as an addlepated
vegetable so his family
has to take care of him
for the rest of his life.
Diapers and everything.
So, dead is great, but I
think he should suffer.
- You wanna be there?
- Oh, I would, but I don't
want it to lead back to me.
Oh, marvelous.
Marvelous.
I'm glad I met you.
I love this car, by the way.
You keep it up beautifully--
- [Officer] Mrs. Coe, would
you step out of the car please.
You're under arrest for solicitation
to commit first degree murder.
- I, I don't suppose I
have a letter from son?
He's so loyal.
He writes me often.
I have a fine baby boy.
Well, he's not really a baby anymore,
but he'll always be my baby.
Do you have children?
No, I asked you that before.
Everyone should have children,
it's life's grandest experience.
To watch them grow to come
good and fine and strong.
Someone to look after you in your old age.
He was framed of course.
It's unconscionable.
All political, all of
it, to get my family,
to bring down the Coe's.
And to what end?
I'll never understand it.
You know what Kevin and I share?
It's much more than mother and son.
It's closer, deeper.
I know what he's feeling right now,
and he knows what I feel, always.
Nothing can ever come between us, nothing.
No one can be closer
than a mother and a son.
(dramatic music)
(light dramatic music)
(Multicom Jingle)