♪ The roof, the roof ♪
♪ The roof is on fire ♪
♪ We don’t need no water ♪
♪ Let the motherfucker burn ♪
♪ Burn, motherfucker ♪
♪ Burn ♪
[siren]
♪ Everybody, here we go ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh ♪
Come on, party people.
Throw your hands in the air.
♪ Ooh-ooh ♪
Come on, party people.
Wave ’em
like you don’t care.
♪ Ooh-ooh ♪
Come on, party people.
Everybody say "Ho."
♪ Ooh-ooh ♪
Come on, party people.
Everybody, here we go.
♪ Ooh-ooh ♪
Come on, party people.
Throw your hands in the air.
♪ Ooh-ooh ♪
Come on, party people.
Wave ’em like you don’t care.
♪ Ooh-ooh ♪
Come on, party people.
Everybody say "Ho."
♪ Ooh-ooh ♪
Come on, party people.
Everybody, here we go.
♪ Ooh-ooh ♪
Come on, party people.
Throw your hands in the air.
♪ Ooh-ooh ♪
Come on, party people.
Wave ’em like you don’t care.
♪ Ooh-ooh... ♪
So what are you
gonna do now?
I’m working.
So stop working.
April.
I love it when
you call me that.
Everyone calls you that.
It’s your name.
Where’s Claire?
She’s in the alley
with Jeff.
Again?
Yes.
Claire,
get off the car.
No!
Claire, get off--
Claire,
the drama is over.
[screams]
The drama’s over!
No!
I was fucking
happy today, you know?
I was fucking happy!
My team made
the semi-finals.
We made it to
the semi-finals today!
Can’t you let me
have my moment, huh?
No. No fucking glory
for Jeff, Claire, huh?
No glory for Jeff!
Sit down!
Good-bye.
[starts engine]
[tires screech]
I’m sorry, Jenn.
Nobody likes me, Jenn.
Ravi, come back.
Ravi, wait.
Wait. Jenn, I gotta
tell you something.
Jason--
Wait. Let me just
tell you something.
I just gotta tell you
something really quick.
Jason, I’m supposed to be
babysitting Ravi.
Now, what the fuck?
Please just listen to me.
I know he’s in there.
Just-- Please.
He’s fine. He’s fine.
Did you forget
your I.D. again?
No. No.
Can you spit it out?
I need to go inside.
Jenn...
Jenn, I’m--
Jenn, I’m in love with you.
I--I’ve been in love
with you since the first
day that I met you.
May-- Maybe since
the exact microsecond
that I was fucking born
and-- and into the future
and-- and--
and that, you know,
and that maybe--
that maybe infinity.
But-- But...
I don’t know
what else to say.
Can I go inside now?
It’s very sweet.
Thank you.
Oh, my God.
Mitchell, I’m-- I’m
at this place in my life
where everything
inside me is exploding.
I have to get away,
and Italy just feels right.
Now, it’s not gonna be
forever, honey.
It’ll just be till
I can feel some
independence, some culture.
Mitchell, I love you,
but I have to do
something for myself,
for Suzanne.
What?
No.
No, hon.
[laughs]
Well, Mitchell...
Okay. I’m gonna put this
to you a better way, then.
I’m breaking up with you.
[gags]
Oh, Neal, let’s escape
the madness.
I told you I’m working.
I don’t get off
for another hour.
I hate you.
Why do you say that?
I need you to take me
back to your apartment.
Come on.
You’re gonna get me fired.
So?
Uhh!
God, that hit the spot.
But, April,
I didn’t finish.
That’s all right.
We’ll get to you
next time.
Will you lock the door
on your way out?
April, this is my house.
Oh, right.
April.
Mm-hmm?
April, I think
we need to talk.
[sighs]
You know, about
what we talked about?
Oh. Yeah.
Yeah?
So what do you think?
Hmm?
Huh?
What?
April!
What, Neal?
What?
You want to talk?
Why do you like
aggravating me?
I’m content.
I feel good.
Whatever.
[Claire]
What do I do?
Where do I go?
I don’t know!
Move on!
Fuck you! I love you!
Hey!
Come here!
I’m scared!
[crying]
I need you!
I can’t be alone!
Claire, we’re leaving.
Come say good-bye.
Claire, you father
and I are leaving.
Hello!
Hello.
You are my father.
We are on.
Okay.
So, Clair,
listen, uh,
there’s emergency money
in the top dresser drawer,
but I gave Mike enough
to last him while I’m gone.
Don’t blow it all
at once, sport.
You didn’t give me
enough for two weeks.
You’re right. I gave you
enough for five.
Claire--
Are you feeling okay?
You don’t look so hot?
Dad, who’s gonna
pay Rosario?
Mike...
be good.
Be...
good.
There, that’s taken care of.
All right.
Where was I?
Phone numbers.
On the fridge.
Please,
use them in case of
an emergency only, all right?
Bye, Dad.
Bye.
Hi, Jason.
You going on a trip?
Yes, we are.
Give us a hug.
Jason! Son!
Make it official.
How’s your mom?
Great.
That’s too bad.
Hi.
You must buy.
Bro, I’m just browsing.
Break seal,
you pay.
What are you reading?
Bikini.
Ah, yes.
Spike Lee.
What a character.
What’s the name of
that magazine again?
Oh.
Anything else?
Hmm? No.
Do you mind
standing over there?
Yes?
Your hair.
I know. It’s red,
and I have really fair skin.
Look, I was up all night,
so could you not pick up
on me right now?
No, no, I’m not trying
to pick up on you. I’m just--
I’m just intrigued.
You’re not from L.A.,
are you?
Well, that’s
a very long story.
I don’t think I can
disclose that kind of
information quite yet.
Thank you.
Uh, hot dogs.
Can I buy you
a hot dog?
You’re intrigued, huh?
Yes.
Yeah, well, when
he does his laundry,
he’ll be looking
for that sock.
So tell me
about this new guy.
Um, his name is Chad.
I met him at
a magazine stand.
End of story.
Chad? That’s his name?
Yeah.
[sighs]
Honey, Chads
are the worst.
Okay. Here we go.
No, no. I’m just saying
that Chads are bad news.
I believe in
the exceptions of this world
and all that bullshit,
but I’ve been dumped
and dogged by too many Chads
to not say anything.
Let’s get cocktails.
Good. Let’s go.
I don’t get it. Okay, what?
You do what?  You do what?
[sighs]
You wrap your fingers
around the base of the sac,
and you lick all around.
You know what you get.
[laughs]
Whatever!
It gets them off,
and that’s all
you need to know.
Next.
Jenn, seriously.
You mean to say that
in 22 years of innocence,
you haven’t
learned this?
This is the basics!
Okay, wait.
Do you do this
while or before
you’re sucking on him?
Oh, good. Now, there’s
an intelligent question.
Now we can get somewhere.
Okay. And the answer
to that is...anyone?
Anyone?
I don’t know.
April?
I’ll say either
for 200, Pat.
Beautiful.
If you’ve already
started sucking him off,
and you want to go back
and do the sac thing,
you never break
the rhythm.
You always transition
your hand
into stroking
your partner
before you head
for his balls.
And also, Suzanne.
What?
Don’t be afraid
to experiment.
Like what?
Like using the teeth.
People think
teeth are bad.
That’s not
necessarily so.
Teeth are your friends.
Teeth are danger,
which
equals excitement.
It’s nothing like it.
Let me see your teeth.
See, that’s a mouthful
of potential right there.
Just try it.
They get this glazed
look in their eyes.
It drives them crazy.
And then they say to you,
they say,
"April. God, where’d you
learn how to do this, baby?"
And you say,
"Jenn taught me."
[gargles]
[Suzanne]
You’re vile.
Eww, Jenn.
[Bartender]
Ladies and gentlemen,
I have an announcement
to make.
[all]
Last call for alcohol!
Earl, what are you
doing later tonight?
[Earl]
Hey, baby.
[telephone rings]
[ring]
Hello?
Hi.
Who is this?
Chad, from the magazine stand.
Who do you think it is?
So how you doing?
Fine. How are you?
Good, good.
And you?
I just told you
I was fine.
I know. I realized that,
and I was hoping maybe
you wouldn’t notice, so--
Claire, hey, guess what.
I just finished
my first sculpture.
You sculpt?
Nope. I’ve only done
one sculpture.
Oh.
So I’m talking you out.
Really? Where?
Well, I’ll pick you up
and we’ll just...go.
Whatever.
Okay, so I’ll see you
tomorrow night.
Okay. Um, do you wanna
know where I live?
This right here is
the labia majora.
This is the labia
minora on the inside.
This is
the access canal.
[squeals, giggles]
What’s wrong with her?
I don’t know.
[Claire screams]
And this is the marrow
of personal achievement--
the clitoris,
otherwise known
as the clit.
[laughs]
♪ That summer feeling ♪
[coughs]
♪ When there’s things to do
not because you got to ♪
♪ When you run for love
not because you ought to ♪
♪ When you trust your friends
with no reason nada ♪
♪ The joy I’ve named
shall not be tamed ♪
♪ And that summer feeling ♪
♪ Is gonna haunt you
one day in your life ♪
♪ Well, when your friends
are in town ♪
♪ And they’ve got
time for you ♪
♪ When you and them
are hanging around ♪
♪ And they don’t
ignore you... ♪
April, I--
Don’t ask!
♪ If that’s not appealing,
it’s that summer feeling ♪
♪ That summer feeling ♪
♪ Is gonna haunt you
one day in your life ♪
April.
What, Neal?
Will I see you tonight?
I’m really tired.
I didn’t get enough sleep.
’Could you not ask me
that right now, please?
I’m so sorry.
You’re okay to drive?
I don’t know.
[car door closes]
I’m obviously picking her
up from some one-night stand.
I’m supposed to act
like nothing unusual
is going on?
Like I’m picking her up
from work or something?
This is wrong, Claire.
I’m dating a hooker.
She’s
an honorary hooker.
April is evil.
She’s not evil.
She’s-- She’s confused.
I know she longs for
stability in her life.
Neal, Neal, Neal--
I’m gonna tell you this once
and forever hold my peace.
April is a selfish,
man-hating, man-eating
reptile.
That’s not true.
It is true,
but...I love her.
Because you can’t have her.
That’s not entirely true.
Okay, then why are
you in love with her?
Because I’m in love
with her.
She’s wild. She’s...
I love her voice.
I love her-- her eyes.
She’s...intellectually
stimulating.
What?
I’m just making sure
you’re listening.
I’m listening.
Why can’t someone
say those things about me?
I-- I would say those
things about you.
You don’t count.
Do you know one time
I got crabs from
thrift-shop clothing?
Are you sure
it was a thrift shop?
Yes!
[clears throat]
Hey, have you talked
to Neal at all?
I told him you’re evil.
What?
[laughs]
Claire,
that’s really good.
I-- I keep my distance,
yes, but I’m not evil.
What did you say?
You’re breaking
his heart, April.
No, he’s breaking
his own heart.
He has to realize
I’m not always gonna
be there for him.
Yeah, but when
you need him,
he’s there.
What a second.
Whose side are you on this?
I just like having fun.
Is that such a crime?
I don’t know what’s
wrong with people.
I gotta be
completely honest
with you.
I’m completely
attracted to you.
No holds barred--
Humor me. Tell me
what you think.
Just be
completely honest,
be completely candid.
Tell me what you
think about me?
Honestly?
Yeah.
I think you’re
disgusting.
What do you think
of this dress?
Um, no.
I think you should
show your body off
a little more.
Like one of these
would be nice
on you, Claire.
You’d see my crotch.
You wear underwear.
I plan to.
Are you gonna buy those?
No.
I’m that close to
bursting out in tears.
So do you think
this guy’s really worth
buying a new dress?
I don’t know.
I’ll find out.
Okay, so are we
gonna leave,
or are we gonna move in,
or what’s going on?
Are you on
amphetamines?
’Cause you’re really
annoying, Jason,
in that special
buzzy way, you know?
That’s completely original.
Great.
[laughs]
So where is he
gonna take you?
Do you know?
I’ll find out tonight.
I hope it’s
someplace nice.
[sighs]
Is this where you
take all the girls?
No, you’re the first.
My clothes weren’t dry,
and I didn’t want to be late.
Well, as long
as I’m your first.
Yes, the first and only.
So where to now,
the supermarket?
Ha ha! I like that,
but, uh, no.
The restaurant will do.
Hi.
You’re not offended,
are you?
I haven’t had time
to think about it.
I like you, Claire.
Claire, I like you.
Look, all I’m saying
is you shouldn’t be
working for me, Jenny.
You’re too fucking smart.
God, I don’t know what
I’d do without you.
You saved my life.
You know, I was
thinking last night.
You wanna know
what I thought?
Yes, Ravi.
That you are
a hell of a lot more
talented than I am.
I mean, I should know.
It’s fucking me,
isn’t it?
Wow.
Hola.
Oma?
You know, I’ve been
watching you all night.
Really?
How’s that feel?
Uh, pardon me.
Is this guy bothering
you at all?
Who the fuck are you?
Who the--
I’m your worst fucking
nightmare, dick breath.
Why don’t you
go back to your fucking
drink over there?
She’s my fucking
girlfriend, all right?
Since you put it
that way.
Uhh!
Oh, come on.
Peace, guys.
Hey, fuck you, lumberjack!
You know, I’m not--
I’m not offended.
How you--
What?
How you kissed me.
I thought about it,
and I’m not offended.
Oh. Oh, good.
I mean, it’s not like
you shoved your tongue
down my throat.
Yeah. Yeah, right. I mean,
sexual tension, you know?
You gotta deal with it.
You get rid of it or it grows
into this thing, you know?
I know. Maybe that’s
why I never date.
I get paranoid
and uncomfortable,
and it’s like you
barely know the person
you’re sitting
right across from,
and you’re like--
Can I smell your hair?
Yeah.
[laughs]
I want your hair
to cover me
with maps of new places.
So that everywhere I go
will be as beautiful
as your hair.
Richard Brautigan.
Oh, shit! You know him?
Yeah, very well.
What is that one poem?
That one-- I love this poem.
Um, it’s never having
had it so gently--
I’ve never had it done
so gently before.
Yeah, right, right.
The sweet juices
of your mouth
are liked castles
baked in honey.
I’ve never had it done
so gently before.
You put a circle of
castles around my penis,
and you swill them--
Like sunlight
on the wings of birds.
Wow.
What a coincidence.
Are you a Sagittarius?
No.
Me, neither.
You want to come in
for a minute?
I can’t. I want to,
but I can’t.
I gotta be in Nevada
at 6 a.m. tomorrow--
Or today, actually.
Are you doing
some gambling?
[laughs]
No, actually. I’m doing
a K-Mart commercial.
You do K-Mart commercials?
This is my first one.
Well, okay. I guess
this is good-bye, then.
Hey, I’ll call you
the day after tomorrow--
Or I guess tomorrow--
I’ll call you
when I get back.
Friday.
Jesus,
you are brilliant.
I could have just
said Friday.
Okay.
Good-bye, Chad.
[groans]
Hi. Thank you so much,
Suzanne, for getting me.
Oh, my God!
What happened to your forehead?
[coughs]
What?
You have, like, a--
Look!
Oh, man.
I guess the bedpost
must have hit it.
It’s really that obvious?
No.
No, no, no. No.
Oh, man.
It wasn’t
that hard, Claire.
I shouldn’t
have a bruise.
I’ve never had this happen
before in my life.
Maybe you bruise easily.
Are you taking
enough iron?
I don’t know.
I have to try that.
Where’s Chad? Isn’t he
supposed to meet you here?
Claire?
Chad.
Oh, God, I’m so glad
you’re still here.
Oh, my God,
This is destiny.
My car runs out of gas.
Okay, so my gas gauge
is all messed up,
and I’m, like,
telepathically zoning
to you to stay here.
Well, I’m just glad
you showed.
I’m so glad you’re
still here.
This is-- Your hair.
We’ve met, haven’t we?
Hmm?
You have?
I think so.
Uh...right.
Oh, Ben’s roommate
over on 4th, right?
4th, yes.
Yes.
Wow.
Small world.
Where were you
last night?
What happened
to your head?
Excuse me a second.
Hi.
You look beautiful.
Neal--
Neal, okay.
Okay?
What?
This whole
commitment thing
is not gonna
work right now.
Commitment?
I didn’t know that
you’d even taken it
that far.
I just don’t understand
why you’re such
an inconsiderate flake.
I’m not inconsiderate!
Oh, yeah?
Yeah!
I have a lot on
my mind right now.
On top of the fact that this
serious relationship thing,
it totally
cramps my style.
Fine. We need to talk.
I just wanna iron this
situation out once
and for all now.
Let me ask you
a question.
Do you want to spend
your nights and days
riddled with guilt
because you’re suffocating me?
You’re totally limiting
my social life.
I’m suffocating you?
That’s nice.
Is it over?
Why don’t you just
tell me if it’s over?
No, it’s not over.
That’s not
what I’m saying.
I’m just saying
go back to work.
Call me later.
When should I call you?
You’re never home.
You don’t call me
back anymore.
Sweetie, can you make this
any more difficult?
I’m sorry.
I’ll call you.
When should I call you?
I love you.
I love you, too.
I really do.
It’s just...
It’s not that, you know,
shaving your legs daily
kind of love,
that "I’d quit smoking
for you" kind of love.
That Everlasting
Gobstopper kind of love.
[applause]
Yeah.
Well, what is it?
I don’t know.
Just call me later.
"The sea is me,
you are my son,
"a cure to thee,
a heaven to be.
"Would you like
a dose of eternity?
"I’m smitten sweet
will give it to thee
in tomorrow’s
conversation."
What is that,
"Blemich?"
You can’t read?
It’s blemish.
What the fuck
is the "C" for?
"Ch" is for "shhh,"
all right?
French version,
i.e. chagrin, chic,
chapeau, Chevrolet.
Chapeau?
These are my roommates.
Hey, uh, guys,
this is Claire.
Hi.
I challenge.
I challenge you.
So challenge me.
It’s a word.
Thank you. Right?
Am I right?
It’s a word.
I’m counting it.
Look up shithead.
C-H-I-T-H-E-A-D.
[laughs]
Ha ha ha!
[Man]
You shut up.
[Second man]
You gotta mellow out.
[Men]
We spend more time
with you pouting
than we do playing.
♪♪ [Man singing opera
on stereo]
Claire.
Yeah?
I don’t want to
fuck you tonight.
Oh, no, no,
I wasn’t--
No, no, wait.
Let me finish.
I don’t want to
fuck you tonight.
I mean, if that’s
all you want,
I can take you home
or something.
Well, no,
I have my car here--
Wait, wait, wait.
Just let me finish.
Oh, shit.
That’s the best part.
[volume increases]
Claire?
At the risk of
sounding cliché,
I want to make love
to you tonight.
No fucking.
I wanna make love.
Okay.
Hey, come on.
No, I’m serious.
It’s not funny.
Ow!
You know what?
You might be the last
serious man on earth.
I have taken you
for granted.
So, wait. Does this mean that
you’re gonna go out with me?
Um, no, that’s negative.
Wait, wait, wait.
Look, I mean, you like music.
I love music.
You’re smart,
and I’m sexy and smart.
You’re 29. I’m 22.
It’s perfect.
You like to give
good blowjobs,
and I fucking
love good blowjobs.
All right! Okay.
I will go out with you.
Are you serious?
You look happy.
Is that a new shirt?
Yeah.
[laughs]
Where are you going?
Out on a date with Jenn.
Nah.
Yeah.
Really?
Well-- Wow.
You look so nice.
Okay. Okay.
Okay.
Have fun.
♪ Yes, he is ♪
♪ What a man, what a man ♪
♪ What a man, what a mighty,
mighty good man ♪
♪ Do it again ♪
♪ Ah, ah, mighty, mighty
good man, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Let me put it
on your mind ♪
♪ ’Cause he thrills me
and he kills me ♪
♪ ’Cause he’s
the loving kind ♪
♪ Another ounce
of his love ♪
♪ And I think
I’m gonna slip ♪
♪ Lose my grip... ♪
Hi.
What’s up?
[laughs]
I’m early, right? I know.
I’m early. I’m early.
You look nice?
Yeah, I know.
Sexy as a son of a bitch.
I’m excited.
Let me get my coat.
Yeah, okay.
I’ll just wait here.
What’s up, Ravi?
What are you doing, man?
I’m hungry.
All right.
Is he-- Is he coming?
He’s not going
with us, right?
Yeah, he is.
But, uh, I have reservations
for only two people.
Well, guess what.
We’ll get one for three.
Uh...
[Jenn]
Come on, motherfucker.
[both laugh]
Did you make all this?
No, it’s take-out.
Do you like it?
I’m starving.
I didn’t realize
how hungry I was
till I started eating.
[giggles]
[clunk]
Oh, shit!
Sorry.
Is everything okay?
You seem kinda nervous.
I’m fine.
Am I being too aggressive?
No, I like it.
You’re a good kisser.
I like you, Chad.
I like you, too.
I just...
I don’t want to keep
making the same mistake.
You know,
I meet somebody,
and I like him,
and I feel like
I scare him away.
Or, I don’t know,
after a couple weeks,
they turn out
to be assholes.
Either way, I get
my heart broken.
Then I lock myself
in my room
and do the whole
"If only I could be
a lesbian" routine.
It’s pathetic.
Do you think
I’m an asshole?
No, I just wanna
do things right.
You know, I wanna
take it slow.
So you don’t
end up a lesbian.
[laughs]
No, so after
a couple weeks,
we won’t
hate each other.
Okay, well, we’ll
take things slow.
Let’s make a deal.
I promise
to never hate you
if you promise to
never hate me.
Okay, it’s a deal.
Hey!
Hi.
You running away?
Well, I have to
go home sometime.
Why?
I have to take a dump,
okay?
I thought we were
passed that stage.
I love you.
I’ll call you.
[telephone rings]
[ring]
I got it!
Hello?
Oh.
Hi.
Where are you?
No, no, it’s fine.
I’ll come get you.
Okay.
♪ You’re such
a beautiful freak ♪
♪ I wish there were
more just like you ♪
♪ You’re not like
all of the others ♪
♪ And that is why
I love you ♪
♪ Beautiful freak ♪
♪ That is why
I love you ♪
♪ Beautiful freak ♪
[Claire]
April--
Don’t ask.
♪ Some people think
you have a problem ♪
♪ That is why
I love you ♪
♪ Beautiful freak ♪
♪ Beautiful freak... ♪
Are you all right
to drive?
Yeah, I’m fine.
Thanks.
[car engine starts]
Claire!
Claire, wait a second.
I have something
I have to tell you,
and I’m just gonna
get it over with.
Okay.
But could you
not be mad?
I won’t get mad.
You promise?
I promise.
Actually, you might
think it’s funny
because it happened
such a long time ago.
[laughs]
♪♪ [opera playing]
[sighs]
Look, am I just
wasting my time,
or are we gonna fuck?
Why didn’t you tell me?
I just did.
No, I just--
I just wish you would
have told me earlier.
What, at the club?
"Hey, Hi!
Didn’t we fuck?
Oh, I’m so happy
to see you again!"
No...
Look, can we just
forget it?
This is just kinda
weird for me.
Okay.
So does that mean
that everything’s fine?
Honestly, no.
All right, Claire.
Why don’t you go bask
in your bitter existence?
And if I may,
it’s usually the girl
who had the guy first
who complains.
You didn’t have him.
I didn’t want him.
Jenn-- Jenn,
haven’t you noticed
that I’m a little
upset with you?
No. Why?
Why? I knew
you would say why.
Why?
’Cause we had a date.
We had a real
fucking date.
And you know,
Ravi’s there.
And plus-- plus,
I had to pay for it.
Okay. I know. I know,
and I feel bad, okay?
But, you know, Ravi had
a really bad nightmare
the night before,
and he needed me,
so I brought him,
and I didn’t think
you’d mind.
You know what?
It’s not even about--
This song’s for
my first wife Damica
who I was married to
for seven years.
Seven years.
Can you believe that?
Oh, fuck.
Wait, Jenn.
Jenn, wait, wait, wait.
Let me just ask you
one thing.
What do you want
from me?
Why didn’t you
respect me, Jenn?
Jenn, why didn’t
you respect me?
1, 2, 3, 4!
♪ I’m afraid
to fully love you ♪
♪ You might hurt me ♪
No, Jenn,
this is for you!
Can I get-- Can I get
another drink?
Just a minute!
Sorry.
Sorry. I just wanted
another drink.
Chad, I wanted to talk
to you about something.
What?
Just this completely
coincidental,
irrelevant thing.
What?
[humming]
Hi, Jason.
Hi!
Chad.
Hey! Jason.
Good to meet you.
Jason’s my brother.
Oh!
Chad! Let’s get
to know each other!
All right.
Claire tells me
you’re an actor.
Yeah, I’d like
to think so.
You’d like to think so?
That’s cute.
Thanks.
I think that acting
is, like...
one of the most intriguing
professions, you know?
Yeah, I guess,
I guess.
It’s a great way
to channel out
artistic energy
if nothing else.
Really?
Yeah. No, it is.
That and through
my music.
Oh, you’re
a musician, too?
A vocalist, in
the band Bruc Lee.
Your band’s name
is Bruce Lee?
No, Bruc Lee.
Bru--
Oh, Jesus fucking
Christ, man!
[Claire]
Jason, get out.
All right.
Hey, Jason. Come on and
check out my new BB gun.
Hey! All right!
Let’s go shoot stuff!
Hey, Chad?
All right!
Hey, you drink
whiskey?
[both laugh]
Look, I’m sorry.
He was rude.
Was he?
Oh, maybe not.
Do you--
What do you wanna do later?
Um--
[clears throat]
Are you, um...
I’m kinda tired.
I think I’m gonna
go home and sleep.
Really?
Okay.
I’m sorry.
No, don’t be sorry.
No, um--
[clears throat]
Okay. Yeah, I have
stuff to do tomorrow, too.
Um...
Okay,
I’ll call you later.
Yeah.
Okay.
Personally, I think
I should have specified
what "later" meant.
I mean, I thought
later last night.
What time is it?
Mike, go see
what time it is.
Please, Claire, no--
Mike!
He already said
he loves you.
What’s there
to worry about?
Yeah, but the
"I love you" thing.
You never trust a guy
who throws the term
"I love you" around loosely.
Guys like that
lack passion in their lives,
and they’re not thinking
about the girl they say it to,
and what it makes
her think.
It’s 1:32.
It’s 1:32, Claire!
Hey, little man, go get us
some fire, matches.
Ándale.
It’s so weird.
He’s not calling.
He’s not gonna call.
What do I do?
What do I know?
You just feel it out,
and you go up to the guy,
and he can either deal,
or he can’t.
There’s a problem?
Okay.
Then you say, "Hey, Chad,
what crawled up your ass?
"Will it be coming out
in the near future?
"No? Okay, then.
See ya.
"I’m a smart, sexy hard-ass
who will now be moving on
to someone better."
Enough said.
Fire.
Where’s my gin?
Mike, go get
some more gin.
God, Claire!
Mike, you’re fired.
[pager beeps]
You’re always pageable.
Where are you going?
I’ll be right back.
Claire.
Hi.
Hi. Uh, I can’t come
out to play right now.
I got this
important audition
I’m preparing for.
Oh, no, no, no. I was
just in the neighborhood,
so I thought
I’d stop by.
It was just--
It was kinda weird
the last time
we saw each other.
When, last night?
It wasn’t weird last night.
Okay, well, maybe
it wasn’t weird,
but you haven’t called,
so I thought
something was wrong.
Claire, I just woke up
an hour ago, okay?
Well, maybe we could
do something tonight.
Um...
yeah.
Yeah. Uh, actually,
I’m gonna stay in tonight.
I got this throat thing.
Are you sick?
No.
Well...
I’m sorry. Look,
I just wanna feel good
for my audition
tomorrow.
Well, maybe we could
do something tomorrow night.
Yeah. Okay.
Okay, so I’ll call you
tomorrow night.
All right.
Thursday night.
I could have just said
Bye.
Fuck!
Neal.
Hey, Claire,
how’s it going?
Fine. How are you?
I’m good.
What are you
doing here?
I’m grocery shopping.
In the feminine
hygiene section?
Yeah, well,
you know how it is.
My mom asked me to pick up
some, um, some Monostat 7.
Nah, she--
She didn’t tell me
to pick it up.
She doesn’t have
a yeast infection.
I mean, if she does,
she probably wouldn’t--
No.
Hey, have-- have you
spoken to April?
Yeah.
Yeah?
I haven’t spoken to her.
If you talk to her
later or something,
can you tell her
that I, um...
that I say hello
and I love you and--
Neal, I’m gonna
give you some advice.
Advice is nice sometimes.
You can take it
or leave it.
But April is
fucking with you.
She’s stringing
you along.
I think you should save
yourself some dignity
and move on
with your life.
Is that it?
Yeah.
Thank you.
It’s not that I don’t
think it could
lead somewhere.
It’s just I decided
that it’s best
if it doesn’t.
Yeah?
The commitment issue’s
been exhausted, you know?
I wanna make
a clean break
and breathe
a little.
Oh, completely.
Yeah, I completely
understand, Neal.
I can see where
you’re coming from.
Good.
I mean,
you understand--
Oh, yeah, totally.
So do you want
to figure out how to...
get your stuff
out of my apartment?
Let me just
ask you something.
Why the sudden shift
in attitude? I’m curious.
Hmm?
Huh?
When you guys
first broke up,
did he cheat on you?
No, no. It was only
for, like two days,
and he came running back
with flowers.
Plus, Mitchell’s
not one of those guys
that can get laid
just like that.
I think he give
most girls the creeps.
I love flowers.
Mmm.
Claire, darling.
So what’s with you
advising Neal to
break up with me?
He broke up with you?
Yes, he did.
Wow. Good for him.
Good for him?
Why are you all of
a sudden interested
in my love life?
First, I’d be careful
in calling it a love life.
Second, Neal is my friend.
I thought I’d crack the door,
let a little light in.
I’d do the same
for you, April.
[laughs]
Really?
Ooh, this is good,
Claire.
Let me just
absorb this.
You’re wrong for Neal.
He deserves better, something
a little more dignified.
You know, you’re right,
actually,
’cause I thought
you and Neal would make
such a good couple.
No. No, no.
I would never fuck
my best friend’s boyfriend.
Hmm. I would.
Hey, can I interject here
for a second?
Yeah, sure, Jason.
Go ahead, interject.
We’re dying to hear you.
Just by rare chance
if you might find yourself in
the same room as a dictionary,
why don’t you look up
the word devotion?
And, uh, you know,
while you’re at it,
you can even check out
some of the synonyms,
like, uh, faithfulness,
or loyalty, or fidelity, or--
monogamy’s a good one.
Wow. This coming
from someone
who’s never even had
a real girlfriend?
No, no! Oh, God, no!
Coming from someone who’s
never been a real girlfriend.
Oh, Jason, you sure
you’re only 5’5".
You know what?
Merely because I’m
one of the two guys
in our graduating class that
you did not go to bed with,
that doesn’t mean
I haven’t been around, April.
I’ve been around.
I’ve been approached.
I’ve been stopped.
I’ve been sought after
by-- by women
who-- who make you look
like what you look like.
6’2" and--
[laughs]
Good for you.
You’ve been around.
Good.
What’s the point?
Hey, you know what?
Let me ask you something.
How does it feel to have
the biggest pussy known
to mankind, huh?
You’re really trying
my patience, Jason.
That’s really funny.
Yeah, well, you’re
looking a little spent there.
Listen,
you little faggot.
You want me to
drag you out by your
puny little cock
and take away what
manhood you have left?
’Cause I’ll do it!
What are you gonna do?
Are you gonna blow me to death?
Oh!
Ugh!
Are you okay, Jas?
No.
Here.
Ow! Ow! Ow!
I hate her!
She’s so bitter,
and she’s so
contemptuous.
She’s just like
a---
What did I do to
make her do that to me?
She’s a...
[laughs]
Oh, God. I’m drunk.
I’m deformed.
No, you’re not deformed.
It’s good. It’s sexy.
It’s a black eye.
Really?
Really sexy.
[mumbles]
Uhh!
Oh, fuck!
[vomits]
Ugh!
What’s the point?
Who cares?
The guy’s a joke.
Oh, but he’s so sweet.
You’re crying.
Sorry.
No, don’t apologize
about that.
Claire, risk it all.
Just fucking jump in.
That’s what I did
with Jenn.
You pledged your
eternal love to her,
and she completely
blew you off.
Yeah, but see--
No. No, that doesn’t matter.
Because you know why?
You know why?
Because it was worth
looking like an asshole.
I mean, what if she
felt the same way,
and she was just
too shy with me?
Jenn too shy?
Yeah.
Okay, right.
No, I guess
she wasn’t too shy.
Okay, so now
I’m really depressed.
[both laugh]
Hey, uh...
do the model poem.
You want me
to do that?
Do the--
Do the model number.
I’ve got spirit,
I’ve got zest,
I do commercials for
Tampex and Crest.
I’m beautiful
and slender with
silicone breasts.
My measurement checkups
always pass the test.
You see me
in magazines.
You watch me on TV.
Don’t you freaks
wish you were me?
I make bush-loads
of money.
No talent, no brains,
while poets and artists
go slowly insane.
I’m the American Dream.
Every man wants me.
I share myself
with the world
It’s ecstasy.
Shopping, the gym.
My fiancée’s parents
are coming for dinner.
Tanning salons,
bikini waxes,
endless appointments,
diet-pill stashes.
Don’t you wish
you were me?
[sighs]
That’s the fourth time
you’ve spelled penis today.
Now he’s gotta go get
someone to touch it.
You got some serious
issues, yeah.
Hey, guys.
Greetings, Claire.
What’s up?
Not much.
We’re really
entering a new realm
of Scrabble, though.
We’re going on
our fifth straight hour.
Where’s Chad?
Queef?
Dude,
that is so slang.
Proper word.
Challenge.
Wait, before you guys
get too deep into this,
where’s Chad?
Upstairs.
Uh, listen, Charlene or--
Wait, what is it?
Claire.
Yeah, is queef
not a word?
’Cause you’d look
like you’d know.
Uh, no comment.
You’re wrong.
You are so wrong.
It’s so far from
being in the
Scrabble dictionary!
So you’re saying
it’s slang. All right.
In order for something
to be slang,
it had to be slang
before something.
[talking continues]
♪♪ [opera playing]
[passionate moaning]
[Man]
You’re fucking crazy!
If it’s not in
the dictionary,
then it’s not a word!
Aah!
[passionate moaning]
It’s good
to see you again.
♪ I don’t even care
if you don’t love me ♪
♪ And I don’t even care ♪
♪ If you don’t want me ♪
♪ Can’t we just
spend the night together ♪
♪ So I have something
to think about tomorrow? ♪
[crying]
Hi, Claire.
How’s it going, Chad?
Uh, good.
And you?
Where’s the whore?
What?
Why don’t you
put down the BB gun?
It’s not a BB gun,
it’s real.
Claire,
let’s go downstairs.
I’ll
make us some tea.
We can talk
about this, all right?
You ripped my--
my heart out
and swallow it whole,
and be so bold
as to offer me tea?
Well, it all depends
on what you have.
Let me guess.
Lemon Zinger?
No.
No?
Fucker!
Aah!
God damn it!
Fucker! How about
Good Earth?
Yeah, yeah. I think
we have Good Earth, okay?
Just put the gun down,
we can talk.
Cinnamon or regular?
[cocks gun]
I don’t know.
You don’t know?
He doesn’t know.
[shot]
Oh!
God!
BBs do hurt actually!
Hey, Chad, want me to
call 911? [laughs]
Fuck you!
Did I misunderstand you
when you said "I love you?"
No.
Will you say it now?
I guess I deserves this.
Claire, it doesn’t
always click.
Claire, you should
really come inside.
Ow!
[knock on door]
[knock]
What?
[Mike]
Claire, it’s Suzanne.
I’m not home.
Take a message.
She’s not on the phone,
she’s here.
[Suzanne]
Claire, I’m coming in.
God! Stop!
Jerks!
All right, crazy Claire,
what happened now?
Nothing.
It’s official.
Well, come on.
I’ll kick his ass later.
Let’s get you out of
the house for a while.
Suzanne, please.
Please, please, please
leave me alone.
Claire, please, please,
please lighten up.
No, come on.
No, no, no, no, no.
Come on. We’re getting
your ass out of the house.
What the hell’s
taking so long?
What the hell
is that?
Oh, my God!
Hey, sugar!
Nice, Claire.
That’s a good look.
Let’s get cocktails.
The point I’m trying
to make, Jason,
is that you are a realist,
whereas I am an idealist.
That’s exactly
how we’re different.
That’s how we differ.
You’re drunk,
and I’m not.
Okay. Let me-- Okay?
Mm-hmm.
You think,
therefore you are.
I think,
therefore I is--I am.
I am.
No difference.
There’s no difference
in what you just said.
Do you see what I mean?
Okay. Okay. Yeah.
Okay?
Okay.
This about this.
Okay. Sure.
[Waitress]
You guys all right?
I would like
another drink.
Jason?
No, thank you.
I’m fine.
Um, could you pour that
a little strong?
Thank you. Where was I?
Okay, she opens
he beloved journal.
[laughs]
Wouldn’t you know?
It’s Chad and Claire.
How you doing,
Chad and Claire?
I hate him.
He’s a bad boy.
[laughs]
Won’t be needing this.
You’re lighting it
on fire right now.
It’s on fire.
It’s embarrassing.
Put that out.
Mitchell, hi!
April. April.
April.
Yes, Claire?
Come here.
I gotta talk.
This is my friend Stephen.
Stephen, can you give me
one moment with April,
please? One moment?
She’s really rude.
One moment.
What?
I have something
extremely important
to tell you.
That’s fine. Because I have
something extremely
important to tell you.
Okay, listen, listen.
I-- I fucked up, okay?
I did.
I’m a bad person.
You are good.
I didn’t mean to say
those things to Neal.
And it’s my fault.
So fucking-A!
I just don’t see how
you can piss someone
like that away.
Why don’t you have
another drink, Claire?
It’s on the way.
Um, I’m gonna throw up
right now,
and I’ll see you
in a minute.
Chad fucked
another girl.
What?
That’s terrible.
[high-pitched voice]
Hi, April!
Shut up, Jason.
[gargles]
[spits]
Claire, are you okay?
I’m good.
I’m really...
really fucking good.
Are you sure?
April, has anyone
ever loved you?
I mean, not your
blowjobs or your facades,
but I mean really
loved you?
Like unconditional,
all the way.
Like-- Like...
in a soulful way?
I don’t know.
’Cause I haven’t
had that.
[sniffles]
Is that all right?
[crying]
I mean, is now the time
for me to grow hard
and not ever care,
not ever want it?
No. No, Claire.
Maybe you did have it,
and you just didn’t see it.
Oh.
I thought what I had with
the Chad guy was real.
I mean, I thought
we both really had
jumped in together.
But really I was just
swimming in my own piss,
and he’s on
the diving board
fucking some other girl.
Okay, Claire, listen.
Listen to me, okay?
Just--You have to pull
yourself together, okay?
This isn’t--
This isn’t you at all.
There’s plenty of guys
out there
that would
love to be with you.
He doesn’t know
what he’s missing, all right?
Listen, just keep
your cool, Claire.
It’s the best revenge.
I know.
I know you know,
’cause you know
everything.
Happy Halloween,
everybody.
I’d like to have
your attention.
I’d like to remind you
that this is
a bon voyage party
for our dear Suzanne
who is off to Italy,
where the real men are.
Are we even invited?
Claire’s party.
Get that space!
Hey, hey, hey!
I’m parking here, man.
Hey, man.
Hey!
Ease up!
Are you all right, man?
Yeah, he’s fine.
I’m parking here.
This is
my sister’s house.
my sister’s party.
I’m parking here.
Cool.
[laughs]
Hey!
[all laugh]
Oh!
Trick or treat, man!
You wanna get it on?
That’s good.
All right?
Yeah.
All right.
Take the spot.
Hey, come on.
Happy Halloween.
All right.
Hey, hey!
Don’t go changing,
all right?
Good one!
♪ You got me now, but there’s
only one exception ♪
♪ Not quite
part of the crowd ♪
♪ I try so hard not to laugh
in the right places ♪
♪ But he thinks
it’s just not funny ♪
♪ Get the feeling
that he’s... ♪
Marry me, will you?
Marry you?
Yeah. It’s fucking destiny,
you know that.
It was meant to be.
We were meant to be.
Marry you?
I don’t even like you.
Do you know
where Clair is?
No, I don’t know
where she is.
Neal!
Oh! Hi!
Hi!
How are you? I’m sorry,
I didn’t wear a costume.
That’s okay.
This is Karri.
Hi, Karri.
[Karri]
Hi!
You wore a costume!
Of course!
I’m very festive.
Oh, I’ll bet!
Come on. Let’s go
get a drink.
Come on.
So what’s with Tinker Bell?
Are you trying
to make me jealous now?
No, that’s my date.
It’s a bona fide
date, April.
That’s a hood ornament,
that’s not a date.
I’m not trying
to make you jealous.
Yeah, well,
it’s the thought that counts.
Hi.
[clears throat]
Claire, it was me.
I slept with Chad.
I just thought
you should know about it.
I’m meant to assume
this is recently,
as in the night
before last?
Yeah, I don’t--
Enough. Enough.
But may I commend you
on sinking to such
an astounding depth,
or would that be
pushing the issue?
Claire, would you
just let me--
April, get out!
Neal was all I had--
Just leave! Please!
You made him
break up with me!
Leave!
I’m trying to tell you
that I’m sorry
because you’re
my best friend!
[Chad]
Hello?
I’m trying to  apologize!
Chad. Hi.
Oh, good.
Call Chad.
It’s Claire. Guess who
I’m here with. April.
We’re discussing
old boyfriends.
Just one question
for you.
Did you fuck her,
or did you make love to her?
That’s good, Claire.
What?
[Chad]
Look, I’m sorry.
I really have to go.
Oh, you got a date?
April.
You all right?
Neal...
just so you know,
I am sorry.
About what?
Everything.
This whole past year,
our relationship...
I don’t think you can
call what we had
a relationship, April.
I’m not as ungrateful
as I act, you know.
I mean, do you think
I don’t see who you are?
I mean, do you know that
I think you’re a beautiful,
special,
compassionate person?
[crying]
That’s what I think of you.
And I never intended
to hurt you, you know?
I don’t feel that you deserve
to be hurt that way.
I just don’t
understand myself.
I better go inside.
[car door closes]
April.
Thank you.
Can I call you tomorrow?
I’d be very happy
if you call me tomorrow.
I’ll call you tomorrow.
Good night.
Okay.
Aah!
Chad!
Fucker!
[Claire]
His name is Chad.
I met him at
a magazine stand.
[April]
Honey, Chads are the worst.
[Jason]
Look, I don’t trust actors.
Especially ones
named Chad.
[Chad]
My name’s Chad.
[Claire]
Where’s Chad?
[Suzanne]
Chad fucked another girl.
[April]
Honey, Chads are the worst.
♪ We don’t need no water ♪
♪ Let the motherfucker burn ♪
♪ Burn, motherfucker ♪
♪ Burn ♪
[siren]
Good morning.
Morning.
Is everything okay?
I’m fine.
Could you stop
walking, please?
Is there a problem,
Officer?
Would you step to
the front of the car, please?
The front of the car,
please?
Are you drunk?
No.
Ma’am, it seems
to me like you’ve had
a little too much
to drink.
My name’s not ma’am.
It’s Claire.
All right, Claire.
What are you doing
out here this early?
I just-- You know,
I just came back from
a Halloween party.
Uh-huh.
Can I go home now?
Where do you live?
Around.
Get in the car.
I’m giving you a ride.
No, no.
Actually, you know what?
I made it this far.
It’s not that far. I’m okay.
Claire, I just
came back from an
arson investigation.
There could be a lunatic
on the streets.
It’s not safe.
Wow. Arson.
Yeah.
In the neighborhood.
Burned a house down.
Um, all right. Let’s go.
No, you can sit
in the front.
The back seat’s
for the bad guys.
Okay.
Uh, Claire?
Yeah?
Your, uh, hair.
I know. It’s red.
♪ It’s magic, it’s magic ♪
♪ The way we got together ♪
♪ There’s magic,
around us in the air ♪
♪ It’s magic,
it’s magic ♪
[Officer]
How’d you get so dirty?
[Claire]
Um, it was
a good party.
♪ There must be
a higher power somewhere ♪
♪ I know that magic is
an easy word to abuse ♪
♪ But I’ve tried
other words ♪
♪ And what words
can I use? ♪
♪ And I knew it
from that first kiss ♪
♪ So stingy
and so spare ♪
♪ That there must be
a higher power somewhere ♪
♪ It’s magic, it’s magic ♪
♪ The way we got together ♪
♪ It’s magic,
it’s justice ♪
♪ It’s grace ♪
♪ It’s magic, it’s magic ♪
♪ No, no, not random ♪
♪ And there must be
a higher power somewhere ♪
♪ It’s magic, it’s magic ♪
♪ The way we got together ♪
♪ It’s magic,
it’s freedom ♪
♪ It’s fair ♪
♪ It’s magic,
it’s magic ♪
♪ No, not at random ♪
♪ And there must be
a higher power somewhere ♪
♪ Everywhere I go ♪
♪ I’m looking for you ♪
♪ What can you do?
What can you do for me? ♪
♪ What can I do?
What can I do for you? ♪
♪ Every time ♪
♪ I lose my reflection ♪
♪ You know all about me ♪
♪ You know,
but that’s me ♪
♪ You made your choice
and you took her voice ♪
♪ She silenced you ♪