Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
[wind howling]
[phone beeps]
[keyboard pinging]
[suspenseful music]
[Becca screams]
[Joyce] Oh, God. What was that?
- [Sam] Becca.
- [Joyce] Sam?
[Sam] Call the cops.
[Becca cries]
- [Becca cries]
- [Sam] It's okay.
It's okay.
[glass shatters]
[Becca cries]
[siren]
[Sam] It's okay.
It's okay.
[police radio chatter]
[officer] Has your daughter
ever mentioned
anyone following her before?
Maybe some threatening calls
or text messages?
[Sam] Hey, Rebecca?
Has anybody been bothering you?
Rebecca?
Becca?
Has anybody been bothering you
at school?
Has anything happened
strange online?
No. Nothing.
- [Becca] Goodnight, dad.
- [Sam] Goodnight.
Sleep well.
Becca, what were
you doing up, anyway?
[Becca] I was just getting
a glass of water.
[phone vibrates]
Who's that?
It's nothing,
it's just Layne calling me.
He's calling you
at four in the morning?
[Becca] I don't know, Dad.
Probably to see if I'm okay.
How'd he know something's wrong?
[Joyce] Sam, let's just let...
- [Sam] I...
- [Becca] Dad!
I'm just gonna tell him
not to call so late.
Can I have it back?
If he calls back, tell him
you'll see him tomorrow.
Go to bed.
- [Becca] Goodnight, Dad.
- [Sam] Goodnight.
What, Joyce?
Well done, Sam.
After everything
she's been through,
you still have to do
that to her?
Why would he be calling so late?
She's probably tryna sneak out.
Why didn't you tell the police
about your car getting
broken into last...
Because it probably didn't have
anything to do with this.
It's probably just some
neighborhood junkies
breaking into cars,
or this Layne kid
for all we know.
Ah, so that's
what you're becoming?
Stereotypical
boyfriend hating dad.
I'll start liking her boyfriends
when she stops dating losers.
This Layne kid just rubs me
the wrong way.
And why would an 18 year old
wanna date a 16 year old,
- is beyond me.
- Okay, you know what?
I cannot have
this conversation tonight.
When you come to bed, will you
please leave the lights on?
I gotta be at work
in a few hours, anyway.
I'll get dressed
and get out of here.
You're going into work?
Call it off. They'll get it.
I've got an important
presentation this morning.
Look, I'll just make it
a half day.
Okay?
[Joyce] Okay.
- Goodnight.
I love you.
So, is that it, Sam?
Look, I get it.
I understand.
And I enjoyed whatever this was.
A fling.
A mistake, whatever.
[Sam] I knew what I was doing.
And it wasn't a mistake.
It's just over.
[suspenseful music]
[Mel] So, do you wanna talk
about what happened last night?
[Becca] No. To be honest,
I'd rather not.
[Mel] Yeah. I get it.
I'm sorry, but you gotta
clean your car.
It stinks so bad.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
What happened
after the cops got there?
- Did they catch the guy?
- No.
They told my dad
they'd let us know
if there were
any other break-ins.
They just sat outside all night.
Why? Are they gonna sit
outside tonight too?
I don't know. Maybe?
Maybe I could
come over after school.
I don't think
that's gonna be a good idea.
[school bell rings]
Come on. I'm freezing!
[Mel indistinct]
[background chatter]
Morning, Sam.
[Sam] Morning.
[suspenseful music]
[knocking]
- [Chris] Hey, bud. What's up?
- [Sam] Hey.
Morning, Chris.
Sorry. I didn't mean
to startle you.
[Sam]
No, that's okay. I'm just...
still a little jumpy
from this morning.
Yeah. Joyce called me
on the drive this morning,
and filled me in.
You guys gonna be okay?
[Sam]
Yeah, I think we'll be good.
You know, the police
are doing their thing.
They're just searching
for a lead.
How's Becca?
She's shaken up,
but she's tough.
You know,
I think she'll be okay.
She's a tough cookie, that one.
A true badass,
just like her mom.
Well, you just
make sure to take care
of my sister
and my niece, there.
You got it, chief.
[Chris] One more thing.
This weekend.
It's Aaron's baptism on Sunday.
You guys still...?
Yeah. Of course, Chris.
Okay.
Well, you let me know
if you need anything,
and I'll be seeing you
in the meeting.
Alright.
I will see you in there.
[phone rings]
Hey.
[Joyce] Hey, hon.
You talked to Chris yet
this morning?
[Sam] Yeah. Actually,
he was just in here.
Okay. I didn't want
to give him an answer
until after I had talked
to you about it.
What did you tell him?
I said we'd be there.
You sure?
- Cause we don't have to go.
- [Sam] Joyce, look.
It's your brother's
kid, alright?
We'll make it work.
You promise you're okay with it?
[Sam] Yeah. I mean,
the only thing we have left
is the mess in the kitchen.
Actually, I got most of it
cleaned up already.
- [Sam] Really?
- Yeah.
A little too slow
to the draw there, slick.
[Joyce laughs]
You can make it up to me
if you pick up dinner
on the way home, okay?
Love you.
[school bell rings]
[Mel coughs]
[Mel] Becca, I'm sorry,
but your car stinks so bad.
[Mel coughs]
[Becca] God. It smells like
something's dead.
[Mel] It's worse than it was
this morning.
[Becca] Look to see if there's
anything on the floor.
[Mel] Okay. No.
No, I don't see anything.
There's nothing down here
that can smell like that.
- That smells like death.
- [Rebeca] God.
What the hell is that?
[Mel coughs]
I can't do this.
Can you pull over?
[Becca] Okay. Okay, fine.
Just give me a second.
[both gag]
[Becca] Oh, God.
[phone ringing]
Hey, Bec. What's up?
[Becca] Mom?
Bec?
[Becca vomits]
[Joyce] What's going on?
Just tell me what happened.
[phone rings]
Did you tell anyone?
- Why would I do that?
- Did you?
Believe it or not,
it's not worth
screwing my life up
either, okay?
I got pictures of us
sent to me this morning.
What?
Someone emailed me
pictures of us
in your apartment this morning.
Did they say or want anything?
No.
You don't think
that she would hire
a private investigator, do you?
No. I don't think
that's what this is.
Look, I just wanna
forget about this.
I just made a mistake.
[phone beeps]
What?
Look, I have to go.
Alright? Just be cautious.
I think you're the one
that needs to be cautious, Sam.
[Sam] Jesus, Bec. Are you okay?
When would they have put
it in there?
Last night
or maybe today at school?
Has Layne been messing with you?
Okay, Dad.
Yeah, he broke in too,
and tried to kill me.
Why the fuck would he put
a deer in my car?
Hey, watch your mouth!
[Joyce] Hey, both of you,
stop it!
You're making a scene in
the middle of a police station.
Honey, why don't you go
check on Melanie?
I just saw her
walk in the lounge
with her mom and dad, okay?
Okay.
- Becca, I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
[Sam] Hey, who's that?
She's a detective.
She talked to us
when we first got here.
She wants to talk to you, too.
Me? Why?
Mr. Hodges?
I'm Detective Savannah Simpson.
May I speak with you
in my office?
[Sam] Yeah.
[Savannah] Have a seat.
[Sam] So, did you need
another report
on what happened last night?
I wanted to ask,
in your opinion,
if you think that your daughter
might have a stalker?
Rebecca?
Or an ex-boyfriend
that ever was a problem?
You think Rebecca has a stalker?
Or maybe you?
In my opinion, this person
went through a lot of trouble
to break in,
only to steal nothing,
and to secretly open
Rebecca's car
and leave a dead animal inside.
No notes. No threats.
Which is why I wanted to ask you
if you think
you might have any enemies,
or someone who might be
upset with you.
Well, I did get
an email this morning.
An email?
Yeah. Someone talking about
my house in a suspicious way.
Really?
Did it say anything else?
Can you send me this email?
No. I deleted it.
You deleted it?
Yep.
Any reason why?
Well, it just freaked me out
a little bit,
and just wanted to forget
about it.
Okay. Well, maybe we can
log into your email
and you can archive it
from there.
[Sam] No, you can't.
No?
I cleared the trash bin.
And there's a lot of sensitive
work material, so...
Was that wrong of me?
No. No, it's okay.
Just gonna make my job
a little harder.
Yeah, sorry about that.
Well, if you do get another one,
can you please send it to me?
May be our only shot
at catching this guy.
[Sam] Thank you.
[soft thud]
[creaking]
[knocking on door]
Becca?
[knocking on door] Rebecca?
- [Becca mumbles]
- [Sam] Hey, open up real quick.
[Becca grunts]
[Becca yawns]
What, Dad?
Is someone in here with you?
What?
[soft thud]
What was that?
Go to our room.
Shouldn't you call the cops?
No, not yet.
I'm gonna go check it out.
Tell your mother
what's going on.
Go, go, go.
Why the hell wouldn't we
call the police?
[Joyce] Sam, what is it?
Hang on a minute!
Damn.
What the hell is this?
You miserable little cocksucker.
- [paper rustles]
- [grunting]
- Rebecca?
- Dad?
- Sam, what is going on?
- Was someone in your room?
- What?
- Was Layne in your room?
[Joyce]
Sam, what happened outside?
Someone broke in my car.
It's probably just kids.
Is there anything else?
[door opening]
Lock the door.
Call the police.
Tell them what's going on.
[Becca] Mom?
It's okay. It's okay.
I have a gun, you piece of shit!
[Sam]
Oh, you think that's funny?
No gun, huh?
Fuck you! [grunting]
Fucking...
[grunting]
[door clicks]
[door shuts]
So this is what it's come to?
He knows we don't have guns
in the house.
And he knows how to get
in and out the house
before the cops get here.
Why don't we just move?
Because this is
my fucking house!
And I'm not gonna get run out
by some fucking sewer rat.
Somebody jealous
of something that I have!
What we have.
This? This is our house.
Our life.
- Joyce.
- Don't you ever raise
your voice to me
like that again.
Now, I am well aware you
have mentally checked out
these last few months.
So let me be very clear to you
that this marriage
takes two people
and our daughter
has two parents.
At least for this Christmas.
Joyce.
Hey, Joyce?
[knocking]
Joyce?
What?
[gasps]
[sighs]
[grunts]
[gasps]
[knocking on door]
Who is it?
Mr. Hodges,
it's Detective Savannah Simpson.
Your wife said it would be okay
to come by and speak with you.
Hang on. Give me a second.
[rattling]
[decanter clanks]
May I come in?
[Sam] Yeah, sure.
Guess you want some water,
whiskey, anything?
No, it's okay. On duty.
I used to always take
the option of not working.
Well, to be honest,
I spend a good chunk
of my day in the office.
It's the only way I can unwind
on my day off,
given the situation.
I understand that, Mr. Hodges.
No, please call me Sam.
Okay.
So, we have the stories
from the reports
the officers took last night.
But I wanted to talk more
about what we were discussing
at the station.
Sure. Go ahead.
Well, before it was a theory.
Now I think it's almost certain
whoever's doing this knows you,
or all of you.
I wanted to know
if you thought any more about
any enemies that you might have.
Or any older men
that might've been an issue
to Rebecca in the past?
Well, there is this boy that
goes to my daughter's school.
I think they're dating.
Layne Lewis, right?
She mentioned him.
What'd she say about him?
Usual stuff high school girls
say about boys they like.
Yeah. Anyway, that's him.
Is there any specific reason why
you get a bad feeling about him?
[door opens]
[Becca] Mom, I don't need it.
[Joyce] ...for Christmas?
Hey, Savannah.
Mom says I need to wear
a warmer coat.
[Sam] Yes, you do.
This is Layne.
Hey, Layne.
Why don't you wait here
while she gets her coat?
Hey, Mr. Hodges.
Would you like
some coffee, Savannah?
Oh, no, I'm...
- just about to leave.
- [Joyce] Oh, okay.
So if we could...
discuss further about
what you mentioned.
You need specifics?
It would help.
[Becca] I'm ready.
There's some Christmas cookies
in the kitchen if you want.
Do not let me forget to pick up
something for the baptism, okay?
[Sam] You got it.
I'm so sorry we have to go.
But my week is free
if you have any questions later.
[Savannah]
Yeah. It's okay, life happens.
Thank you so much
for what you're doing.
Bye, hon.
So you mentioned Layne Lewis
because you
actually suspect him, right?
I'm sorry?
This isn't you just not liking
your only daughter's
boyfriend, right?
You actually believe that
it could be him?
Okay. I'll look further into it.
In the meantime,
we'll have a scout
who will spy
on the sub division.
Just in case.
Twelve gauge, huh?
Yeah, you can't be too careful.
You ever shot a firearm before?
Is that required to own one?
No. Not at all.
Well, I'll look further
into what we discussed.
I'll be in touch.
[door closes]
[Layne] Does your dad, like...
not like me?
I know. I'm so sorry.
Why?
It's not you.
He's just been acting...
What?
I don't know.
He's just been acting
weird lately.
It's been like that
for a few months now.
I've never seen
my parents fight this much.
[Layne] Why are they fighting?
[Becca] I mean, I tried
listening in on their arguments,
but they always wait
until I fall asleep.
I don't know.
I think it's to do with his job.
Does your dad ever get, like...
mean?
- Or...?
- [Becca laughs] No.
The most he's ever done
was just yell a couple times.
But I just think
he's shutting off.
- Emotionally?
- No, just as a dad.
[phone vibrates]
What is it?
[Julia] Why did you call off
at work today?
- Is everything okay?
- Yeah, everything's fine.
Look, I told you. We're not
talking outside of work.
- But I thought...
- Hey, Chris is calling me.
I gotta go.
Look, don't call me again.
Hey, Chris. What's going on?
[Chris] Hey, brother.
You guys doing
anything for dinner tonight?
No. No plans yet.
[geese honking]
[Terri] So I'm arguing
with the cashier,
telling her there is no reason
my card should not be working.
And on the fifth try,
still convinced
that she's the idiot
with the broken card reader,
I finally look down,
and I see that
Chris has been putting in
the wrong pin
over and over!
[Terri laughs]
Woman, you're so fucking
stupid sometimes.
Now, had you given me
the credit card
instead of the debit card,
we wouldn't have even had
this whole going off on a tirade
on some 18 year old cashier.
"Can I see your manager?"
She's always so spicy, this one.
[Joyce laughs]
Speaking of going off
on a tirade,
did you hear what happened
today at the office?
No.
[Chris] You know that...
what's her name,
the new paralegal, Julia Hilt?
I've seen her around.
Well, she was caught...
texting in one of the most
important meetings.
Oh, are you kids not allowed
cellphones in the office?
Well, we had a really important
client today at the office.
And her face,
right into the glass.
I don't know. Social media.
Doing something, whatever.
So, privately, Mike comes up
to her, with respect,
excuses themselves
into the hallway.
Tries to explain the situation.
Of course, she's not having it.
He's getting closer,
trying to calm her down.
As soon as he barely even
touches her, she screams.
"Get your fucking
hands off me, Mike!
"Get your fucking hands off me!"
The guy's red
in the face embarrassed.
She's freaking crazy.
Is this normal? I mean,
normal behavior for her?
No, she's just some new
paralegal in the office.
She's a total wackjob.
Have you talked
to her before, then?
No. No, I just...
I've heard of her around
the office, you know?
Coffee talk.
[Joyce] You're a gossiper, then?
- Guilty!
- [Terri laughs]
[cellphone rings]
[Chris]
You gotta try one of these.
It's Bec.
Hi, hon.
What do you mean
you're still at home?
What happened
to your plans with Mel?
Well, I wish
you had called us sooner.
You know we don't want you
home right now.
Yes.
Becca, yes.
We trust you.
You know exactly why...
Alright.
Yeah, we're gonna
head back right now.
Love you.
Is everything okay?
Yeah. Just...
Becca's plans with her
friends got canceled today
so she's been home alone,
and I don't like that.
Okay. Yeah.
Well, you guys...
No, no. We'll see you guys
at the baptism.
Okay. Well, are you two sure
you're okay to drive?
Yeah. I've only had one,
but she's...
[Terri laughs]
[Christmas music]
Why don't you fuck me anymore?
What?
We used to do it all the time.
Even in the car.
Remember how I used to
suck your dick
when you'd drive us home
from the movies?
Come on.
Come on. Take your pants off.
- Come on.
- Stop.
- Honey!
- Stop it.
I miss when you'd jump
in the shower with me.
The way you'd slap my ass.
How many wives are begging
their husbands for that?
I'm okay.
Thank you.
[thudding]
- [Sam] What was that?
- Becca?
It sounded like it was out back.
[Joyce]
Should we call the police?
[Sam] No. Get in the car, call
Becca and make sure she's okay.
[Joyce]
No. I'm gonna go check on Becca.
Get in the car. Call Rebecca.
It's probably just her shutting
a window or something.
[Joyce] Becca?
Becca?
[Sam] Come on, you bastard.
[Joyce gasps]
Mom?
Is everything okay?
You scared the shit out of me.
[Sam grunts]
You okay?
Yeah, everything's fine.
Did something happen?
- [Sam grunting]
- No.
No, it's fine, okay?
[Sam panting]
[gasps]
[grunts]
Okay. Let's see
who you are, huh?
You son of a bitch. I knew it.
- Hey.
Becca didn't hear anything.
- What happened to you?
- Oh...
Chasing a raccoon off
the back porch, and...
- I slipped.
- [Joyce laughs]
And also, I remembered
I left my phone at the bar.
So I gotta go get it.
I can call Chris.
Maybe he's still there.
No, no, no. Don't.
They have a kid at home
and they gotta get back.
I'll just be a little bit.
- Okay.
- You gonna be okay?
Yeah. No, we'll be fine.
- Okay, honey.
- Okay.
Love you.
[suspenseful music]
[Chris] Hey brother,
I'll see you this weekend.
Alright. We'll see you there.
[email jingle]
["Trumpeting Ecstasy"
by Full of Hell playing]
[Sam vomits]
Oh, shit.
[gasps]
[cell phone vibrates]
Hello?
[woman] Hello. I'm trying
to reach a Sam Hodges.
Is this him?
- Who is this?
- This is Officer Lang
at Lake [unclear] P.D.
Detective Simpson
is having me call
to ask you to come in
and answer some questions.
What, now?
Yes, sir. She's going
to need you right now.
[suspenseful music]
[officer] Savannah,
Sam Hodges is here for you.
Thank you. Have a seat.
Alright, so what's this about?
First off, how are Joyce
and Rebecca doing?
They're doing pretty good,
but it's been a stressful week.
One that won't end, will it?
I guess not.
So, about the young man
we were discussing.
- Layne?
- Yeah. Did you look into him?
The only problem with that, Sam,
his mother reported him
missing this morning.
Becca didn't mention anything
about that.
Have you seen her yet today?
Not since she left for school.
Cause we called her
after we heard this.
And his mother seems to believe
that he went to go
see her last night.
No. He doesn't come by
the house at night.
Yeah, I assumed as much.
That's what Rebecca said,
but I don't know.
She already seemed...
upset and stressed.
I'm sorry?
Well, after we talked
to Rebecca,
we talked to one
of his closest friends,
and he also said
Layne was supposed to go
to your house last night.
And apparently
he didn't show up.
Much to your disapproval,
I'm sure.
The hell does that mean?
I don't know,
just the way you described him
the last time we communicated.
Didn't seem like you had
the highest opinion of him.
Yeah, I don't think
I can talk about this
until I speak to my lawyer.
Why?
You're not being detained
or brought in as a suspect.
Yeah, but you did ask me
to come in.
To verify that he hadn't stopped
at your house last night.
No, he did not come by my house,
and even if he did,
I wouldn't let him in.
Are you sure about that, Sam?
Are we done here?
I have to get back to my family.
We're wrapping presents tonight.
Yeah, you can go. You're free.
I'd bundle up, Mr. Hodges.
It's coming down out there.
[phone rings]
Hey, baby.
[man] Good afternoon, Sam.
Hello?
How are things over there
at the police station?
Any interesting developments?
What are you doing in my house,
and where's Joyce?
She's just enjoying
a warm bath right now.
Don't worry.
I won't have a peak.
You don't mind if I poured
myself a glass of whiskey
while I'm here, right?
Look, I don't know
what the fuck you want,
but you got about 15 seconds
to get out of my house.
Or what, Sam?
All I have to do is leave
this envelope right here with me
in front of the bathroom door
on my way out.
A few snapshots.
One's from last night,
and a few more spicy favorites
I haven't shown you yet.
Get out of my house!
That temper's going to get
the best of you one day, Sam.
I want you to clear
your schedule for this evening
and take a rain check
on wrapping those presents.
We're helping Rebecca
pick out an outfit
for tomorrow's baptism,
because you and I are going
to meet up for a date.
And why the hell would
I do that?
Maybe I'd just like to sort
some things out.
Sanctuary Club on Bennett. Nine.
- Look, I'm not...
- You know, it sound like
Joyce might be finishing up
her little soak right now.
Are we going to be meeting,
or am I leaving
this envelope here?
I'll be there.
I'll find you, Sam.
Fuck!
Fuck! Fuck!
God!
- Everything okay over there?
- What do you want?
Oh, sorry.
My car...
And, you know...
arguing with my wife.
That guy looks like
he's ready to pop.
You know what's funny?
That's the guy
from Simpson's
home invasion case.
Who, the homeowner?
Yeah, him. She's having me look
into a few things on that guy.
Is he a suspect?
Get the feeling she's starting
to think that way at least.
Well, I can't imagine why.
That guy looks like
he's about one bad day away
from stepping into traffic.
[chuckles]
You know, out of curiosity,
I've been looking at statistics
of stalker and break-in cases
to see how often someone from
the home or family is involved.
How's that going for you?
Not good.
Pretty useless rabbit hole,
to be honest.
Check this out.
D.O.J. numbers show
there's almost
270,000 home invasions a year.
And there's over
1.3 million victims
that annually report having
a stalker. Jesus Christ.
Do you know what the statistics
don't tell you, Castillo?
What's that?
How many of those people
deserved it.
[laughter]
There's that element.
[Castillo] You're right.
[Becca sighs]
He still hasn't texted
you back yet?
No. His phone just goes
to voicemail now.
Derek say anything?
No, he said the same thing.
He said Layne hasn't gotten
ahold of him.
I mean, he snuck out
my window last night
when my parents got home.
Maybe his phone's just dead.
- Mel?
- What?
Do you wonder if your parents
are capable of killing someone?
What?
You ever think your parents
are just so damn boring
that they pretend
that everything's okay
when it's actually not?
I don't know.
Probably not my parents.
If anything,
they're probably just guilty
of being into some weird,
kinky shit.
[Mel laughs]
But what? Like, you think
your mom's
a serial killer or something?
["Starlight Dancer"
by Scary Black playing]
- [Sam] How much?
- Five bones.
Just you,
or you waiting on someone?
Just me.
Keep the change if you just say
you never saw me.
I'll take it to my grave, bud.
You here for the band?
Just meeting someone.
Your funeral, pal.
[background chatter]
[bartender]
Hey, what you drinking?
- Just give me water.
- Sure.
Actually,
Crown on the rocks, please.
[bartender] Sure.
Sam?
You stand out like a sore thumb.
What's this?
Why the hell are you here?
Are you here for me?
I need to talk to you.
- I gotta get out of here.
- What?
I need to talk to you. Outside.
Jesus. It's fucking freezing
out here, Sam.
- What do you want?
- Are you involved in this?
- Don't yell at me.
- Are you a part of this?
A part of what, Sam?
The stalker that
keeps messing with me.
Told me to come here tonight
and meet him.
Why would you do that?
Because I need to try
to end this.
So why don't you just
call the cops?
Because I can't.
Well, if you're not going to,
maybe I have to.
Hey, no. Don't call the cops.
I need to try to end this
on their terms.
- I can't lose my family.
- You give a shit about them?
You know what?
Now it's my turn
to tell you this.
Leave me the fuck alone,
and don't follow me!
- I'm not following...
- [door slams]
["Digital Vampire Redux"
by Love Under Will playing]
Hey.
Hey!
[both grunting]
[gasping]
[stalker screams]
You come around me
and my family again,
I'm gonna end your fucking life!
[music ends]
[soft organ music]
Thank you, Deborah,
for that lovely rendition.
Y'all, wasn't that beautiful?
Now, before we continue
with our Christmas service,
on the Eve of little
Baby Jesus' birthday,
I wanna remind you
that one of our own
is about to have
her little boy baptized,
to join us in union
with the Holy Spirit.
Now, I wanna remind you
what that means,
that word baptism,
to us Christian folk.
Why?
Why do we, as parents,
have our little ones baptized?
Why do we lay their tiny
heads in the water,
and sometimes scare them,
while we anoint them
with the holy water?
We baptize
because our souls are thirsty.
So we give it a drink
of that water.
That water, being what it is,
that we desire from the Lord,
and what the Lord will promise
to give us in return.
- [man 1] He's right.
- [man 2] That's right, minister.
- [baby cries]
- Matthew 28:19.
Jesus says,
"Go and make disciples
of all of your nations.
Baptize them
in the name of the Father,
the Son and the Holy Ghost."
You see?
It washes
the spiritually dead and blind,
and protects us from
the enemies of God.
[baby cries]
We get it done to us
when we're little boys
and girls,
because it isn't a contract.
It doesn't need consent
from both parties.
That's not what
baptism is, y'all.
It is simply
God's promise to us.
But it's not magic.
Is it magic, y'all?
[all] No.
[minister]
Because we have the freedom
to deny that promise, that love.
We are given the opportunity
to turn away.
Like a marriage that's broken.
One where there is no love.
There is no salvation
where there is no faith.
But where there is baptism,
and where there is faith,
there is promise of salvation.
- Amen.
- [all] Amen.
Amen indeed, y'all.
[sighs]
But there is a current member
of our family
who's suffering, everyone.
So before we welcome in another,
let us take a moment
to heal one of our own.
Little Miss Margaret has
recently been released
from the hospital,
after she was burned
in her home's kitchen
while preparing supper.
Now, as she has confessed,
and as she told all of us
a few months back,
Margaret stepped outside
of her marriage.
She committed adultery.
But we forgive her.
Oh, we forgive her
and we love her,
because she repented
and she asked for forgiveness,
and the Lord in return
forgives her and loves her.
So when we pray
for little Margaret's
painful healing
of her body to begin,
we are also gonna pray
for her soul.
'Cause I don't believe this was
just an accident, Margaret.
I truly do not.
I don't think this was just
a matter of some grease
catching fire.
I think the Lord sensed that...
even though you had repented,
you were thinking of going down
that path of sin again.
Am I wrong, Margaret?
Shh. I know. I know.
And the Lord knew it.
And I truly think...
that he placed
the demon Wrath in you,
and he caused that fire.
And he caused that pain
to remind you of the fire
and pain that awaits you
should you ever
turn against Him again.
Because no matter how painful
flames upon the flesh may feel,
it's the flames that
await our soul,
should we turn on Him,
that we must fear!
So we're not just praying
for her body to heal.
We're gonna cast
a demon Wrath out.
I mean it.
Do you hear me in there, demon?
You're no longer welcome here.
You leave this God-fearing woman
and you take that sin with you!
You take that sin
back to hell with you!
And you take any adulterer
in this room
and you take them back
to those lakes of fire!
Go on. You take those sinners
and you leave!
Go on! Get!
Leave.
Leave. Leave.
- Leave.
- [parishioners] Leave!
- [all] Leave.
- Leave.
- Leave!
Leave!
And Our Lord has delivered
our sister back to us all.
She is here to stay.
Now, let us welcome our sister
back to us, shall we?
[applause]
I'll see you
next week, Minister.
See you then, brother.
- Thank you.
- You play one hell
of an electric guitar
probably, right?
Seriously, Terri's been trying
to bring me into the fold,
and full disclosure,
I gotta tell you
I've been looking forward
to the whole
snakes and serpents kind of,
fire and brimstone thing.
I'd love to introduce you
to my sister and my niece.
Well, she's actually a
foster sister,
so you can take it easy on her.
Certainly, we're always thrilled
to watch our little family grow.
Hey, guys.
I'd like to introduce you to...
- Father...
- Minister.
[Chris] Minister Fairfield.
So you guys wanna go
grab breakfast?
- Yeah. Sounds good to me.
- Tammy's up the street.
Steak and eggs
special on Sundays.
- [Terri] Chris?
- Yeah, babe?
Merry Christmas, Sam.
[suspenseful music]
- Who grabbed my shoulder?
- What?
Did you see
who grabbed my shoulder?
No, it's probably someone
just saying bye.
Hey, kid. I got
a really stupid question.
Did you break that hand,
or did you lose any fingers?
What I'm trying to ask you,
is your hand broken?
Do you have all your fingers,
is what I'm tryna ask.
- It's just broken.
- Oh.
Okay. Well, can I see it?
Your hand. Let me see your hand.
Merry Christmas.
Did you grab my shoulder
over there?
- No.
- Do we have a problem?
No, there's no problem.
I'm just trying to see
your kid's fingers.
Excuse me?
[Sam] I just wanna see
if he has all his fingers.
Yeah, he's got
all his fingers, man.
Just let me see...!
Are you a psychopath?
Listen, I...
No, shut up
for a goddamn second, Sam!
I'm sure you know at this point
you just elevated yourself
to chief suspect, Sam.
Me calling in favors?
Because I'm looking for the guy
that's been stalking us.
He attacked me last night,
and in the fight,
he lost two fingers
and then he ran off.
- What? Where?
- It was after work last night.
And then in there,
someone grabbed my shoulder
and said my name.
And he was missing fingers.
You're either not keeping us
in the loop,
or you're being really
fucking creative.
Now, which one
is more suspicious?
Look, it was last night,
and I was gonna come in
after church today.
Did you get a good look at him?
No, nothing.
Well, good news for you,
the boy's father sounds like
he's not gonna press charges.
I advise you
consider doing the same.
Just chalk it up
to holiday stress.
No more secrets.
Have a good Christmas, Sam.
What a beautiful ceremony.
Becca.
No, I think we'll definitely
remember that one.
Enough. I get it.
[Becca] Do you, Dad?
Do you know what it was like
for Mom and I
to have to stand there
and watch you run around
like a serial killer?
Do I look like
a serial killer to you?
What we doing?
Can we just go home?
Stay here.
Or what?
Or your crazy fucking dad
is gonna chop you up
in a thousand pieces.
Stay here.
Joyce, I'm sorry.
They were at the house again,
weren't they?
So you walking into a door
and smashing your eye,
that was all just bullshit?
Why'd you lie about it?
- Because I was afraid...
- Who has reason
to be messing with us?
Do you owe someone money?
You think this is my fault now?
What I think
is that when you went back
to the bar
to get your cell phone,
you were gone
an awful long time.
[upbeat music]
[chiming softly]
What happened
this last year, Sam?
I keep going over it in my head.
The days and the months, and...
I just can't figure out where...
whatever this is,
where it started.
I still love you.
I promise I do.
But I know
something has been going on.
And it started before
all of this craziness.
I have my suspicions.
But I hated myself
for feeling them.
I mean, how could I think
that about you?
It's what I tell myself...
alone at night,
wondering where you are.
I think...
what I was most afraid of,
though, was if...
I was right and I confronted you
and I made you stop doing
whatever it was you were doing.
And I would lose you completely.
[Joyce cries]
So I just swallowed my pride
and I looked the other way,
and I convinced myself
this is just
something that
marriages go through.
Something we would go through.
You would realize
you were making a mistake,
and we would just move past it.
You see, Sam...
I love you so much...
that I removed myself
from the picture.
And I just hope that
I'm worth coming back to
when you're finished.
[Joyce sobs]
But I can't do it.
I can't do it anymore.
I can't sit in the dark.
I can't.
It's torture,
and it has got to stop.
So...
is there someone else?
[Sam] There was.
There was someone else.
You're not crazy.
[Joyce cries]
[Joyce sobs]
[upbeat music]
[door slams]
- [Sam] I'm sorry!
- [Joyce cries]
- [Joyce] Who is it?
- What does it matter?
- [Joyce yells]
- [glass smashes]
Who is it?
It's a girl at work.
Her name is Julia.
The crazy one?
[Joyce cries]
You know what
the worst part of it is?
You thought I was so dumb,
you didn't even try
not to be obvious.
She's too stupid.
She'll never figure it out.
You think that fucking
little of me.
[Sam] Look, it's over.
I ended it.
Look at me.
- It's you.
- [Joyce cries]
- I love you.
You expect me to believe that?
[Becca screams]
[Sam] Hey!
[repeated thuds]
[glass smashes]
[glass crunches]
[Joyce screams]
[Becca and Joyce yelling]
[man] I want you to hear
what daddy has done.
[both grunting]
[Joyce gasping]
Becca!
[both grunting]
[thud]
[man] Look at me!
[Joyce] No.
[man] I'll always be able to
find a way back in.
- [thud]
- [man yells]
[all yelling]
[Joyce] Becca!
- [man snarls]
- [Becca screams]
[Becca screaming]
[Joyce] Becca! Becca!
Stop, please!
[man] Where you going, Rebecca?
I still want you to hear this.
- [thud]
- [Joyce yells]
[gun reloading]
Now I have a gun.
[gunshot]
- [Joyce] Sam!
- [Becca] Dad, dad!
- [Becca cries]
- [Joyce] Oh, Becca. Becca!
[Becca and Joyce cry]
[Joyce] Are you okay?
Let me see.
[tense music]
Oh, quit being a baby.
Do me a favor.
Let me check your eyesight.
Look straight ahead at me. Okay.
You didn't lose any
consciousness when he hit you?
- No.
- Okay.
Alright.
I think everybody's fine.
If you guys...
Who are you?
And why are you here?
- Okay? Thank you.
- Thank you.
Wait.
Before you leave, do any
of you guys recognize him?
[camera clicks]
No.
[Sam] What's his name?
[officer] There's not a wallet.
There's no identification.
Nothing on him.
Why, Sam? You recognize him?
No.
No, I don't know who he is.
Alright, well,
we're gonna John Doe this guy.
We'll get his prints.
Blood at the lab.
I'm sure he's in the system.
Yeah, you guys can go.
We'll get out of here
pretty quick
once we get all
the photos we need.
And you guys can hire someone
to get this cleaned up.
I know it's a shitty way
to spend the holidays.
Look, Sam,
I wanted to apologize.
You gotta admit,
you didn't make it easy on us.
You know, all of this
and poking around.
See if we can figure out
the fuck this guy is.
Maybe he had something to do
with Layne Lewis.
You've got some tough girls.
Yeah, they are.
So, what are you guys gonna do?
Stay at a hotel?
No, I think we're just gonna
drive ourselves to the hospital
and stay at the in-laws'.
Try and save Christmas.
Sounds good.
It's gonna be a pretty wide
investigation for a few days.
Look, I'll try
to give you guys some time.
- Contact you after New Year's.
- Thank you.
Do you remember
the Christmas we spent
at the hotel when I was eight?
When we moved?
Yeah.
The reservation got screwed up
at the nice place with the pool.
So Dad had to get us a new place
at the motel down the street.
I thought that was
the worst Christmas ever.
I don't know.
I remember you guys told me
that we wouldn't get
any presents that year,
because Santa wouldn't be able
- to find us.
- Right.
But when I woke up,
you guys had set
all the presents out.
Then we opened them
on the twin beds
before going downstairs
to eat pancakes and waffles.
Nuts and chocolate chip.
Yeah.
Then we watched Christmas movies
all day in our PJs.
[Joyce sighs]
You know...
When I think about Christmas,
that's the year
I actually think of.
Let's hope that's the Christmas
you always think of, sweetie.
[Becca cries]
Yeah.
[inaudible]
You look like shit.
Aww, thank you.
I want a fresh start this year.
Can we do that?
I'd like that.
I just wish your mom
let your dad keep
booze around here, you know?
I'm so sick of having eggnog.
Where's my scotch? [chuckles]
I doubt
if anything's open, though.
It's still early.
That liquor store on Union?
It's still open.
Well, I think you should go
get us something.
What if your mom catches us?
Then we'll have to do what we
did when we were teenagers
and we'll just have to hide it.
- Okay.
- [both laugh]
- One more thing.
- Name it.
Swing by Charlie's
and get us some pizza.
Their kitchen's open
tonight 'til 2.
Okay.
Alright, darling.
I shall return.
Love you.
[Christmas music]
[Sam] I ordered a pizza
about 15 minutes ago.
[man] Yeah, I was hoping you
wouldn't get here so quickly.
Burned that one. They're making
a new one for you.
It'll just be a second, man.
Just grab a seat.
Maybe grab a drink.
It'll be right out.
[Sam] Yeah, let me get a whiskey
- and a glass of ice, please.
- [man] Sure.
[chuckles]
Can I help you?
No, it's nothing. I'm just...
relieved to see you putting
that ice on your face,
instead of ruining a perfect
glass of whiskey with it.
- That's all.
- [Sam laughs]
Hey, I'm sorry.
What are you drinking?
[Devon sighs]
What am I drinking?
Whatever this place's
cheapest scotch is.
Hey, bartender.
Get him another scotch.
You didn't have to do that.
Top shelf.
I appreciate it.
You look like
you could use another round,
and you didn't say
"no thank you."
Well, my mom always said
to not let my pride
get in the way
of a kind gesture.
Pleasure to meet you.
Sam.
Devon.
You try giving the cat
a bath or something?
Come again?
Oh. [Sam laughs]
Oh. It's been a hell of a week.
Well, I hope it's getting
better for you.
Things are looking up
after tonight.
Some good news come
with those cuts, then?
Yeah. They represent a fresh
start, you could say.
And that's definitely something
I can give
my family for Christmas.
Well, they say simple gifts
usually resonate
the most with family.
Well, if you have a wife.
[Devon laughs]
I'm not quite ready
for that road yet.
Keeping things simple
for the holidays, right?
I suppose that's a more
cheerful way to look at it.
Maybe if I was ready
to settle down,
I'd appreciate an easy life,
but I have no...
Marriage shouldn't be
in your cards
if that's
what you're hoping for.
Really?
Any advice for it, then?
Yeah.
Find somebody that
you love more than
your friends, your hobbies,
your top shelf scotch.
[Devon laughs]
You gotta be willing to give up
everything for that person.
Well, that's what you did?
I married someone I loved
just as much
as all those things.
When you first meet someone,
they come into your life,
and you don't think
about what it's like
you coming into theirs.
But eventually,
you're gonna have to choose.
You're gonna have
to choose between...
the life that you had,
and your life with them.
And you'll see
other people do it,
and you tell yourself
that's not me.
That's not gonna be us.
Then you'll feel selfish
for living both lives.
But here's the truth.
Finding someone
you're not gonna resent
for forcing you
to make that choice.
Merry Christmas.
[Sam laughs]
[glasses clink]
So, is there a woman
in your life that knows
you're at a bar at Christmas
getting marital advice?
[Devon laughs] That's funny.
No, no, no. Not me.
Nope. Nope, nope, nope.
You see, my sense of romance has
always been a bit stinted.
I had this one friend
when I was younger.
He met this girl
when we were kids.
You know,
he fell in love with her.
And all he could do is
talk about her.
You'd swear
he'd never seen the stars
before seeing her eyes,
you know?
She thought the world of him.
But years
after they were married,
before they ever had
a chance to have kids,
he got killed in a wreck.
No goodbyes, no farewells.
He just never came home
from work one night.
She always kept his name.
Never remarried.
Even after years and years.
She always kept his name
and always wears his ring.
She'll always be his,
no matter what.
You see, that right there,
that's my idea of a romance,
of devotion.
[Devon laughs]
Now good luck telling that
warm hearted story to someone
and then not
scare them off, right?
Fuck.
Is it always so bleak in here?
Just during the holidays.
It's actually a good place
to bring somebody
if you just
wanna have a good time.
Oh, yeah? Friends or wives?
Something in between.
You know, that choice
you mentioned earlier
when you did have to choose,
would you ever
settle on a compromise,
or did you choose something
more convenient?
To be honest,
I didn't choose either.
I took the easy way out.
Did it help?
Made me feel worse.
And I knew
it wouldn't fix things to stop
or go back,
so I just kept going.
They say hindsight's
always 20/20, right?
So going back was never
an option?
[Sam] Not for me.
It hasn't been.
That's because you're running
from something.
I don't run.
Don't lie to yourself like that.
You've been running
for a long time.
Afraid your responsibilities
have anchored you down.
Afraid something one day
might catch up.
[tense music]
How's Rebecca handling
everything?
She's scared.
She's still scared.
And your wife?
She's strong.
- How'd you know I'd be here?
- [Devon laughs]
You're predictable, Sam.
You follow the same routine.
You listen to the same
radio stations.
You take the same way to work
at the same time every morning.
Now, I was here
the night you came
with your brother-
and sister-in-law.
I've sat in here and watched you
drink until close several times
right over there.
Creature of habit.
What if I make a scene?
[Devon laughs]
That would be stupid of you.
There's clearly a plan in place,
Sam, and you know that.
Let me ask you a question, Sam.
Why didn't you come clean
with the first piece
of leverage anyone had on you?
Before you killed someone
to protect it?
Like I said,
a creature of habit.
Tell me what to do next.
You come with me quietly
in my car right now.
Then we drive back
to your house.
The police are already
gonna be there,
and so are your daughter
and wife.
Oh, no, no, no. Don't worry.
Her parents weren't hurt.
You know, we'll just...
We'll just drive over there
and, shit, you can tell them
everything, Sam.
You can tell them
fucking everything.
how we broke into your house,
stalked Rebecca,
and you can even tell them
how we're the ones
who killed her boyfriend
when it's all over.
What do you think about that?
What do you get
in return for that?
[Devon laughs]
Come on.
[Devon] ♪ Deck the halls
With boughs of holly ♪
♪ Fa la la la la la la la la ♪
♪ Tis the season to be jolly ♪
♪ Fa la la la la ♪
Why are we doing this?
You're just gonna kill me
when we get there anyway.
[Devon] I can 100% assure you,
if you do everything I say,
it won't happen.
You went
to Oakridge University, yeah?
- [Devon shouts] Yeah?
- Yeah.
Yeah.
You knew Molly Adwaller,
didn't you?
That's what this is about?
[Savannah] Just lower the gun.
Hey, you got us here.
Lower the gun.
I need you to lower the gun.
Hey, hey! Who's this guy?
What's his name?
Let's see your hands.
- Hands up!
- Show me your hands!
Woah, woah, woah, woah!
Freeze, or I'll blow
your fucking brains out.
Okay! Easy, easy, easy.
I want you all to put
your fucking guns down now!
Want us to lower the guns?
- Put them down!
- Okay, okay.
Put the guns down.
Look at me.
Just you and me here.
You're the one
who brought us here.
What are your demands?
For you to shut the fuck up
and listen!
Okay, okay!
Okay, we're listening.
Listening to what?
[Devon] I want y'all to listen
to Mr. Hodges here.
He's got a story I'd like
for him to tell all of you.
Right, Sam?
- There was a girl...
- So they can hear you!
Name was Molly.
She was at OU.
It was a party.
I was so drunk.
Tell the fucking story.
[Joyce] Sam!
She kept wanting to leave,
but I don't know why,
I followed her
to the bathroom and...
my friends held the door shut.
I didn't wanna scare her.
I just wanted to make her
feel bad
for making me look like a creep
in front of everybody
for just asking her out
on a fucking date!
I don't remember what she said
that pissed me off,
- but I hit her.
- Louder!
I beat her up!
I beat her up
until she was unconscious.
- Then I fucked her.
- Raped her.
- I raped her! I raped her!
- Say it!
And she took it to the school.
But all my friends said
I wasn't at the party.
And my family lawyer
charged her with perjury
and defamation of character.
Then she left.
And we forgot.
[Devon] She didn't forget.
She didn't forget.
She never forgot about you, Sam.
Every man that fucked her,
she remembered.
She fought a terrible fight.
Dragging three sons from
different men along the way.
Her parents had rejected
their Catholic daughter
fallen from grace!
Her friends, she...
[Devon cries]
There were no friends.
Only empty pill bottles and us.
Three young boys. Starving.
Regretting we couldn't
feed our mother!
One of her suicide attempts
eventually was successful.
And she left three parentless
children to the state.
Three!
But we knew one man
better than the father
we never met,
and that was you, Sam.
[Devon laughs]
You see,
she always told us about you.
And we promised ourselves
one day we would find you.
You know what
she never told us though, Sam?
[Sam grunts]
Our oldest brother, Corey,
the one you shot last night...
[Devon laughs]
...she never did tell us
who his dad was.
Officers...
my brother and I are very sorry.
[gun shots]
[Joyce cries]
[somber music]
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull