[♪♪♪]
[GASPS]
[DOG BARKING]
[DOG BARKING, GROWLING]
Come on.
I think I've had enough
of this city for one day.
I'll ask you again,
Mr. Capello...
or do you prefer DeAndria,
or Nicky the Knife?
I lose track
with all your aliases.
I object, Your Honor.
I think by now
defense counsel is familiar
with the witness' name.
I expect closing arguments
today, Mr. Stein,
so please skip the theatrics
you've so adroitly managed to
slip in during this entire trial
and ask your question.
Mr. Capello, you have admitted
that you have killed
on occasion.
On Ringerman's orders.
[GALLERY MURMURING]
You've also told us you've lied
for Mr. Ringerman in the past.
Hey, I'm a stand-up guy.
I work for somebody,
I work for 'em,
no matter what it takes.
Yet you're here today
trying to put Mr. Ringerman
in jail
for a crime he did not commit.
He committed it. I saw it.
I was there.
You admit you lie?
Why should the jury assume
that you're not lying to them?
Because I ain't.
Don't insult the court,
Mr. Capello.
Did you or did you not
make a deal with the DA's office
in return for your testimony?
UNDERWOOD:
Objection.
That has no bearing.
If you're working
for the DA now
like you did for Mr. Ringerman,
would you lie for the DA?
Objection!
Would you lie
to stay out of jail
like in the past?
I object!
Sustained.
Counsels, approach the bench.
[GALLERY MURMURING]
He got us good.
We still have our last witness.
[♪♪♪]
Closing arguments
immediately after recess.
UNDERWOOD:
I have one more
rebuttal witness.
STEIN:
I know nothing
of any other witness. I object.
UNDERWOOD:
This witness was afraid.
She feared for her life
and would not come forward
until today.
Mr. Stein knows
who this witness is by name,
and he knows
what she will do to his case
if he keeps
her from testifying.
JUDGE:
If you feel
this witness's testimony
will have that much effect
on the case, bring her forth.
The court calls
Madilyn Dougherty to the stand.
[REPORTERS CLAMORING]
[CAMERA SHUTTERS CLICKING]
I don't know, Dan.
Something's wrong with her.
BAILIFF:
Do you solemnly affirm to tell
the truth, the whole truth
and nothing but the truth?
MADILYN: I do.
UNDERWOOD:
Miss Dougherty...
will you please
tell the court
exactly what you told
my assistant early this morning?
I...
Take your time, Miss Dougherty.
No one is going to hurt you.
Just speak the truth.
Please tell the court your
connection to Mr. Ringerman.
I...
don't have one.
You don't have-- Miss Dougherty,
don't you work for the Argent
Corporation as a bookkeeper?
And didn't you, while working
with the company ledgers,
come across evidence that proves
that Mr. Ringerman not only is
a secret owner of the company
but that the company itself
is nothing more
than a money laundering front
for Mr. Ringerman?
I know nothing
about any of that,
and I have no proof.
[GALLERY MURMURING]
Miss Dougherty,
you told my assistant something
very different this morning.
I was mistaken.
How could you be mistaken?
You came forward voluntarily.
I was confused. I was mistaken.
I don't know anything
about Mr. Ringerman.
Your Honor, this witness is
obviously terrified.
I object.
There is no evidence to
support counsel's statement.
I have to agree with Mr. Stein.
Does the witness realize
the seriousness
of perjuring her admission
to the DA's office this morning?
[♪♪♪]
I don't know anything...
Anything about
Mr. Ringerman's business.
REPORTER:
Here they come.
Mr. Ringerman, can you give me
anything for the evening news?
We were confident
in the legal system all along
and in the jury.
Can I have a comment?
Mr. Ringerman has no comment
to make at this time.
Thank you very much.
No further comment, thank you.
[REPORTERS CLAMORING]
I don't know what to say.
Whatever there was to say,
it should've been said in here.
I understand if you press
charges against me.
I think we're done
pressing charges
in any matters
regarding Thomas Ringerman.
We had our shot.
Justice wasn't on our side.
[♪♪♪]
[TELEPHONE RINGING]
Hello?
MAN:
You follow directions well.
Very well.
All right, now let him go.
I did exactly what you wanted.
Now let my brother go.
Just continue
to do as you're told,
and you'll get
what you want.
That's the way it works.
I did what you wanted.
You said--
I said do as you're told!
You're not done doing that.
Get a pen and piece of paper.
Write this down,
because if you forget,
you'll have no way of reaching
your brother ever again.
Along the pier
near 10th Street,
walk past the warehouse
with the old Cavanaugh
Maritime and Salvage sign.
Hope to see you there,
but probably not as much
as your brother does.
And be careful.
It's not a neighborhood
for a pretty lady
to be wandering around in
at night.
[LINE CLICKS, THEN DIAL TONE]
[♪♪♪]
Remember telling ghost stories
as a kid?
Remember turning
all the lights off
and huddling together
with a flashlight
and trying to dream up
the worst nightmares possible?
Well, I bet you've never
dreamt up anything like me.
We're gonna have a scary time.
Me, you...
and your sister.
[WHISTLES]
[LAUGHING]
I love this crap.
SONNY:
Good to see you laughin'
again, Tommy.
It's been a while.
That judge took care of you.
He didn't give that DA an inch.
It wouldn't have been
the same last year
if Cain had been on the bench.
I don't get nervous about
little girls with big mouths.
I don't get nervous
about dead men.
If I had to worry
about dead men,
I'd have 10 times
as many worries as I have now.
Some guys think, you know,
he's still around.
I mean, you must've heard.
Toomey says it was Judge Cain
who nailed him and
Patty Boxcars last month.
[CHUCKLES]
Toomey's doing his time
at the state laughing academy.
You don't think
he was serious, do you?
He didn't wanna do hard time,
so he came up with that
"Cain still being alive" garbage
to help him
cop a plea for soft walls.
He'll be out in a few years
with pottery he made for us all.
He never said Cain
was still alive.
Enough!
She's here.
[CHUCKLING]
[♪♪♪]
[THUNDER CRASHES]
[RINGERMAN LAUGHING]
Madilyn, we were just talking
about coming back from the dead,
and you and your brother
can give us a firsthand report
whether or not that's possible.
Just let Patrick go.
Please.
Please just let him go.
He won't--
He can't do anything to you.
You're so right.
No one can do anything to me.
Not your brother, not you,
not the police...
not even ghosts.
[LAUGHING]
[THUNDER CRASHES]
What the hell?!
Boo!
See a ghost?
No, I-- Heh-heh.
Hey, I just, uh-- Makin' sure
she didn't bring anybody.
She didn't bring anybody.
Did you, Madilyn?
No.
[THUNDER CRASHING]
She knows better than that.
What about m-my brother?
Go kill him.
Make him scream loud enough
for her to hear.
No! No, no!
[MADILYN SCREAMING]
[RINGERMAN LAUGHING]
Hey, did you guys give him
a new wardrobe to be buried in?
[♪♪♪]
What the hell is this?.
[GROANING]
Jilly?
[BEEPING]
Tommy? Tommy, you there?
Shut up! Keep quiet.
[MUFFLED GASPING]
Your brother is safe.
Whoever the hell you are,
there better be
more than one of you!
What the hell
do you think you're doing?
MAN:
I accuse Thomas Ringerman,
head of the largest drug-
smuggling racket in the city,
personally responsible
for hundreds of thousands of
ruined lives, children's deaths,
all caused by the poison
you import and sell.
You, Thomas Ringerman,
I find guilty!
And I find you dead!
MAN:
I accuse Ramon "Sonny" Santiago.
I charge you with extortion,
drug smuggling, kidnapping,
attempted murder and murder.
And you, too, I find guilty.
What the--?
[THUNDER CRASHES]
[GRUNTS]
[ELECTRICITY CRACKLING]
What did you do to him?
Okay, man. Okay, what is this?
What are you doing?
Who are you?
MAN:
I'm your judge and jury.
And if necessary,
I'm your executioner.
You're crazy!
[MAN LAUGHING]
[TRIGGER CLICKING]
[YELPS]
[WHIRRING]
What the hell are you?
You're a robot.
You're a damned robot!
No, Ringerman.
I'm a ghost story.
[SCREAMING]
I confess to the charges of
kidnapping Patrick Dougherty.
Kidnapping him
with the intent
of forcing Madilyn Dougherty
to change her testimony.
Her testimony
would've sunk me.
And I knew,
to save her brother's life,
she would do anything...
even lie in open court.
Right there, "to save his life."
That's it.
He admits he was planning
to kill him.
You're going to have to go over
this again and again and again,
here and in court.
You have no idea who it was
who gave you this videotape,
who it was that saved you?
I mean, mystery men who
materialize from the night sky
don't cut it for a jury,
and this testimony could
get thrown out, except...
Except what?
Except when I contacted Stein,
Ringerman's attorney,
this morning,
he'd already spoken
with his client.
Ringerman wants to try
to make a deal.
He's not even trying to say he
was coerced into a confession?
No, he's not.
Which makes no sense.
It makes no damn sense at all.
Unless he's afraid.
More afraid than going to jail.
Afraid of what, though?
Of who?
Of ghosts.
Ghosts?
[♪♪♪]
[CHIMING SOFTLY]
[BEEPING]
[TV BROADCASTS OVERLAPPING]
RAE:
From what I hear
of Tommy Ringerman,
he won't give up
till he sees you dead.
He already has.
You spook me too
when you get this way, judge.
A word of friendly advice.
You're gettin' off on this
Dark Avenger gig way too much.
Computers, electronics,
even some makeup.
I didn't know your expertise
spilled over
into psychoanalysis.
Just, uh, stuff I pick up
from the prison shrink
and the freako movies
I used to see as a kid.
All them deformed guys start
to go bonkers after a while.
It's strain from having
to hide in the dark so long.
The only strain I might feel
is having to put up
with this thrift-shop equipment
you send me out there with.
Hey, hey, hey,
thrift shop, my tuchus.
I use the same components you
find in anything made by Sony.
Well, when I want to take on
the criminal element with a VCR,
I'll call.
Oh, wait, what'd you do,
downfield block
an express train?
Hey, one of Ringerman's
associates
tried to take off my arm
with a pipe.
How much longer you think you
can get away with this, judge?
I mean, sooner or later,
someone's gonna figure you out.
No one will figure me out.
Not unless somebody tells 'em.
Don't run that rap on me.
I'd be doin' hard time
on the dark side of Pluto
if not for you. I just...
Speakin' of which,
I gotta get back
to my nice, safe cell tonight
or I'm gonna get in deep guano
and blow the work furlough
you got me.
You should've left.
Nah, I just wanted
to finish up some work
on this new tear-gas pellet.
I think I found a way we can
load it under the laser.
What would you say
if I could put you
into all the police
interrogation rooms at Central?
They cabled up the building
and all the cameras
are centrally linked.
And you say
you're not into all this?
Oh, don't get me wrong,
you know.
I'm not into throwin' on
strange get-ups
and scarin' the crap
out of bad guys with a whisper,
but you and me, we're like...
Courageous Cat
and Minute Mouse.
Why, Rae, be careful.
Your emotions are showing.
I don't care any farther
than being concerned
with who gets all this
if you don't come back one day.
I mean, I built all this stuff.
I feel, you know, owner-like.
Except for however many of those
hats you got layin' around,
which I would not be
caught dead in.
Scratch that.
But I don't know what happens
once you walk out
your secret panel there.
Now, like this Ringerman.
He can be a real bad dude.
So can I.
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
[SCREAMING]
REPORTER [ON TV]:
The Grim Reaper
has struck again.
Police say the Reaper
claimed his fourth victim
earlier this evening in
the exclusive Oakhurst District
of the city.
Like the other Reaper victims,
Janis Elwick was in her early
20s, attractive and alone.
[BROADCAST CONTINUES
INDISTINCTLY]
Is that like
a King Kong laser or what?
Anyway, here are the blueprints
to Central Division downtown.
I think if we mount
a microwave dish
on a building
above the west side,
we can pull in
from the main terminal.
Yes, no, maybe?
Until now,
there has been no indication
by the police
that there have been
any suspects in the case.
Indeed, that there
have been any leads at all.
But tonight Captain Strauss
has implied otherwise.
Oy vey.Heh.
You can't wait for that one
to be on trial, can you?
On the warpath again.
We put one to bed,
and already you're lookin'
to be back on the case.
I might be back on the case.
You're gonna be back in jail.
[ENGINE POWERING UP]
Turbines to speed,
batteries to power,
bat thrusters ready.
[CHUCKLES]
When we do this,
I can't resist, heh.
See, Rae, talk to your shrink.
There's a little Lone Ranger
in all of us.
[♪♪♪]
We spoke earlier today
with Captain David Strauss
and Commissioner
Peter Kinghorn.
KINGHORN:
The entire police department
was caught off guard
by this turnaround
in the Thomas Ringerman case,
but as long as truth prevails
and matters reach
their proper end,
then justice has been served.
The department is here
to see that happens.
REPORTER:
What about the Grim Reaper?
Is it true you have a suspect?
I'll address that
later today, all right?
REPORTER:
There's a rumor
that you have a confession.
Like I said, there'll be
a formal explanation
from Captain Strauss
later today.
Now, thank you very much.
No more questions.
REPORTER: But, commissioner--
Just once I'm dyin' to see you
catch a couple of minutes
of Wheel of Fortune
or Pink Panther
or something truly frivolous,
like a guy in a black hat
would watch.
I mean, you have seen
Casablanca,haven't you?
Everyone's seen
Casablanca,right?
[♪♪♪]
You know, not that
I'm crazy about this gig,
but, uh, we never
have any company picnics,
office Christmas parties,
no softball league.
You think we take our jobs
too seriously?
I never get
an end-of-the-year bonus.
Well, we haven't been together
for a year yet.
Oh, well, let's chalk that up
to a subtle reminder, then.
You wanna come in?
Meet the gang?
As a matter of fact,
you know some of 'em.
You put 'em here. Bunch of 'em
would probably love
to make you
a personalized license plate.
Send my regards for me.
Mention how close we are,
you and I.
You're gonna check up
on this Grim Reaper?
That means goin' to Kinghorn's.
Why don't you let me do that?
If Kinghorn finds out you're not
at the bottom of the river,
he'll be more dangerous for you
than any 10 gals in here...
not to mention your daughter.
[♪♪♪]
I'll go to Kinghorn.
[DOG BARKING IN DISTANCE]
[BARKING]
I'm home, Ma.
[CHILDREN CHEERING]
GIRLS [IN UNISON]:
Birthday girl first.
You first, Amanda.
I'll get it.
[♪♪♪]
There's someone in there.
There's someone watching me.
You're just saying that
because you missed it,
but since it's your birthday,
you can have another chance.
No, there really was
someone in there.
Well, then let's go see.
No, I think
we should call my mom.
I'll get it.
[ROARS]
[GIRLS SCREAM]
[GIGGLES]
You're such a dork, Amanda.
Now watch how it's done.
You watching, Amanda?
She's over there.
Amanda? Honey, are you okay?
I was worried.
Libby and Tracy said you thought
someone was in the bushes.
He was there, Mommy.
He gave me these.
Who, Amanda?
Who gave you these?
A man in the bushes?
Who was he?
I don't know.
I didn't see him.
Didn't you say Daddy gave me
white roses on my birthday?
Didn't you say he gave me one
for each year?
Yes. Yes, baby, I did.
Yes.
You ever found out what the hell
happened with Ringerman?
Well, he refuses
to speak to anyone
except his lawyer
and the district attorney.
[CHUCKLES]
He's gonna deal, Pete.
Why?
It makes no sense.
I mean, why the hell
is he gonna do that?
He was off.
Good God in heaven,
he was walking.
We gave him every chance, even
getting him with Judge Reasoner.
Does he know the kind of
maneuvering that took?
Well, he doesn't seem to care.
He just wants to make his deal
and do his time.
Wait, what are you doing?
That's a $10,000 piece
of pre-Columbian pottery.
Well, whoever sold you this
should be on
the 10 most wanted.
What about us?
Hmm?
What has Ringerman
going to say about us?
Nothin'.
He won't say anything.
There's no connection,
and we did the right thing.
He'll remember that.
Now, what happened Friday night,
the confession, I don't know
if we'll ever know.
And I don't care.
I heard talk of Cain.
Cain's dead.
Did his name ever come up
in connection with Ringerman?
Maybe.
Yeah.
Maybe or yes? Which?
Yes, I think so.
I-- I don't know.
That's all so vague.
What are you worried
about a dead man?
'Cause this wasn't
the first time his name came up.
What if he left
something behind?
What if he wrote
something down?
He didn't
have anything towrite down.
Cain was the damn toughest judge
walkin' the earth.
You think he would've settled
for a couple of threats
when he could've had us standin'
before him in his own court?
Eventually he would've
turned up somethin',
but he never had anything,
anything concrete,
while he was alive.
There'll never be anything
now that he's dead.
He is dead?
He is dead.
And no matter
what anybody dreams up
or whispers in the streets,
he's staying dead.
All this talk, though,
it's just so crazy,
about the phantom judge
with the face from hell.
Yeah.
What?
The guy I had with me
that night, he must've talked.
You never told me
you were there.
I never told you anything.
You never wanted to know.
Like how we used acid...
so everyone would think
that it was a vendetta
and not just
a random homicide.
[SIGHS]
Oh, my God.
You don't have
the stomach for it, huh?
Well, I don't have the stomach
to send a man to his death,
a man like Cain,
unless I'm there to do it.
[♪♪♪]
[BEEPS]
MacReady?
MacReady, I'm looking at an
open roof door in stairwell 2.
MACREADY:
We'll check it out
pronto, Mr. Kinghorn.
You do that, MacReady.
Then decide what you're gonna
say in your resignation
if I have to do your job
for you gain.
Relax, Pete.
Hmm?
Whatever else
we have to worry about,
whatever or whoever
is gonna take us to task,
it's not gonna be
a man named Cain.
Magruder, you still on 7?
MAGRUDER:
In elevator 4,
just comin' down.
You told me to look in on
Mr. Applegate's office next.
Right. What about you, Harv?
HARV: Okay here.
Everything checks out.
This is Gunderson.
I'm just coming
out of the men's room on 12.
The roof door in stairwell 2,
Gunderson.
Looks like it's open.
Check it out.
The door is open.
No sign of it being forced.
Didn't we have this elevator
serviced this morning?
Maybe Morrissey didn't lock it
up before he went to lunch.
MACREADY:
Heh, I'll worry about
Morrissey. You look around.
Ten-four.
[♪♪♪]
Nah, nobody up here
but me and some pigeons.
KINGHORN:
What about the Reaper?
The public is
screaming for blood
over these Grim Reaper murders,
and it's not going to be mine.
STRAUSS:
What are you saying?
It's gonna be mine?
KINGHORN:
I just don't wanna wind up
on the news
in another Ringerman fiasco.
Do you have any kind of leads?
Can you make up any?
STRAUSS:
I could, but we don't have to.
I've got a suspect.
KINGHORN:
You do? Why wasn't I informed?
STRAUSS:
It just happened
early this morning
and I didn't wanna call
in case you'd told Bonnie
you were with me.
The guy's an outpatient
at a psychiatric hospital
over in Highland Park.
We got tipped to the guy by
the director of the institute.
KINGHORN:
Jeez, a doctor rolling over on
his own patient. Some ethics.
STRAUSS:
Yeah, you just can't trust
anybody, can you, commissioner?
Unlike two such above-reproach
members of society like us.
KINGHORN:
Find your conscience
on your own dollar.
You get those charges filed.
I'm going to be
standing by tomorrow
to make the announcement
about the arrest.
This city is going to see
their government is effective,
that we can get a lunatic
like this off the streets.
Do you think he's guilty?
STRAUSS:
Does it matter?
KINGHORN:
Get me an arrest.
STRAUSS:
Don't worry.
No one's gonna take away
your commissioner's hat.
That's why we had
to eliminate Cain, isn't it?
[CAIN SCREAMING]
[♪♪♪]
Well, what's happening
to me now?
Why do I remember things
that I feel are dreams
but I know are not?
I have some things here
I want you to look at, Walter.
Photographs.
They're police photographs.
Police?
I just want you
to look at them.
Tell me how they make you feel,
what they remind you of,
if anything.
They're not very pleasant.
What?
What's happening to me?
What are these?
What are they to you?
My dreams.
They're all my dreams...
that aren't dreams.
[SWITCH CLICKS]
I'm convinced.
I'm not.
Well, this is
a change of heart.
I'm not saying
I don't believe it's possible.
I'm just saying
I'm not convinced.
I'm not sure what I am.
I mean...
I'm not even sure
why I did this.
This is a breach of every ethic
I can think of.
Doctor-patient confidentiality--
There is no doctor-patient
confidentiality
when the doctor's made aware
a crime has been committed.
All I have is a sick man
who has dreams.
They're not dreams, doctor.
Dreams aren't real.
See, this man has
described to you
every murder that's taken place.
You don't even keep
this type locked up.
He gets to roam around,
slips away when he wants
and comes back in
for his evening medication.
That's pretty good.
This type
is just a man suffering
from circumscribed amnesia
brought on by severe trauma.
Until a couple of days ago,
he wasn't even staying here,
Captain Strauss.
He was being treated
as an outpatient,
just coming in for his therapy
with Dr. Russell.
She just admitted him
the other night when--
Yeah, when he came in
with blood on him. Yes. Yeah.
It's too bad you run such
an efficient hospital here.
I would've liked
to have analyzed that blood
before your staff
had washed it off Mr. Donovan.
Does he remember the blood,
doctor?
Or can he conveniently
forget that too
with his, uh-- What is it?
What kind of amnesia?
Circumscribed amnesia.
Partial amnesia that allows you
to remember things
from the past,
but it's like dropping
a wall at a certain point
and not being able to remember
from that moment to the present,
like carving out one
particular piece of your life.
Yeah, like something traumatic
and so bad that you
don't want to remember it.
Don't play psychiatrist
with me, captain.
And you don't play cop.
[DONOVAN SIGHS]
I... I have some others
for you to look at.
I don't need to see them.
I know they're disturbing,
but you should
really see these others.
I don't need to see them.
[♪♪♪]
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
They're the other two,
aren't they?
Yeah, the girl with the red hair
and the seashells.
She was wearing earrings
with little seashells.
And, uh...
then there's the blond girl...
in the yellow top.
Yeah, a yellow top.
Find a straitjacket with
his initials on it, doctor.
He's goin' to court.
No one...
No one can know that I...
I allowed you
to see this session. I...
Sure, doctor. Don't worry.
No one will ever know.
[SOBS]
TREMAYNE:
Donovan may not be able
to stand trial.
He may not be well enough.
That's a determination
to be made by members
of the medical profession.
I'm just gonna charge him
and let the system take over.
Then what's bothering you,
Captain Strauss?
You look troubled. Haunted.
Now, that's a bad choice
of words, doctor.
Let me ask you...
is there any reason
why I'm suddenly having
the same dream
over and over again?
It's a dream I used to have
a long time ago, ahem,
and I'm suddenly--
Suddenly it's cropping up again.
Well, it could mean
many things.
It could mean
you can't hide from it anymore.
Hide from what?
Whatever it is
about this nightmare
that you want to forget.
I didn't say it was a nightmare.
A couple of officers will be
here for Donovan in the morning.
Good night, captain. Sleep well.
Tanya, how's Mr. Donovan doing?
I've just come
to discuss that with you, Colin.
Your secretary said
you were with the police.
They were here
about Walter, weren't they?
Yes.
We were supposed
to discuss this.
Perhaps you should have a talk
with Murch or Tucker?
Perhaps they felt
it was their civic obligation
to contact the authorities.
They came to me, despite
your recommendation not to.
I was only reminding them
who Walter's doctor is, Colin.
I hope you haven't
forgotten that, either.
Or that I'm also your sister.
Oh, I haven't forgotten.
And I hope you haven't forgotten
who the director
of this institute is.
[♪♪♪]
[DONOVAN SIGHS]
Oh, seashells...
Blond,
yellow top.
Her eyes...
[GASPS]
[PANTING]
[CAIN SCREAMING]
[TAKING SHUDDERING BREATHS]
STRAUSS:
Where'd you get that stuff?
WES:
The forensics lab.
STRAUSS:
Do I have to ask you if anybody
knows what you needed it for?
WES:
No, I was in there
when Levine was doing
the Fishbein autopsy.
When he went to the can,
I filched it.
[SIGHS]
Amazing how this stuff
won't do a thing to glass,
but, man, what it'll do
to metal, not to mention skin.
[CAIN SCREAMING]
[SIGHS]
[TELEPHONE RINGING]
Yeah?
WES [ON PHONE]: Captain.
Sorry about the hour,
but I thought you'd wanna know.
That bastard struck again.
The Reaper.
Where?
When?
We've got the time figured
as about an hour ago, but...
But there's more.
I called Dr. Tremayne
in the institute,
right from the murder scene.
Tremayne went to see
his patient and, big surprise,
our amnesia victim
had slipped out
and was just comin' in
covered in blood,
and it wasn't his own.
All right. Good work, Wes.
That's real good work.
I'll be right down.
I thought you'd wanna know
right away.
Sorry to wake you.
That's okay.
I've been sleeping too much
lately anyway.
First District Court
is now in session,
The People v. Walter Donovan.
Mr. Donovan, do you realize
what is taking place today?
Yes. Yes, sir.
This is not a trial.
This is a hearing
to determine
whether or not
you should be tried
regarding the deaths
of the six women
with which
you've been charged.
Your Honor, as you can see,
my client has been voluntarily
under psychiatric care
for the past two months.
Since having
a serious automobile accident,
he has been experiencing
a temporary memory lapse.
In light
of this medical situation,
I would hope
the court would understand
he cannot hope to receive
the proper medical expertise
in a prison hospital.
Very well.
Give me a moment, please.
I don't want you here. I don't
want you to listen to this.
I'll be okay, Walter.
I'll be okay.
Susie-- How's Susie?
Where does she think I am?
Has she seen anything?
She just thinks
you're in the hospital,
that her Daddy is sick.
I don't let her watch the news,
and I kept her out of school
this week.
You can't keep her home from
school the rest of her life.
She won't have to worry about
that. You'll be home soon.
Mr. Underwood,
what is your feeling
regarding Mr. Donovan's
medical history?
Your Honor, I appreciate
what defense counsel is saying,
but we are talking about charges
of multiple homicide
in the first degree.
The defendant cannot be
released on bail.
I appreciate that,
Mr. Underwood,
and under other circumstances,
I would agree with you.
But I do not want
the defendant's health,
mental or otherwise,
unduly at risk.
Mr. Newton,
do you have a suggestion?
Dr. Tremayne's institute, where
my client currently resides,
does have a security wing
where I believe Mr. Donovan
could be incarcerated
and still be available
for proper treatment.
Very well, but I would
hold one person responsible
for Mr. Donovan's care.
Perhaps his doctor of record?
I've discussed that
with Dr. Tremayne,
and we both agreed
that he should be that person.
JUDGE:
Are you comfortable with those
arrangements, Mr. Donovan?
Mr. Donovan, are you all right?
Am I all right?
I woke up with blood
all over me, judge.
That's enough, Walter.
I don't know if I'm all right.
Nobody knows if I'm all right.
You don't need to say anything.
I just need to know, because
I remember killing them.
I remember killing them, judge.
I remember killing them!
I remember killing them.
There's no doubt this guy's
the Grim Reaper, judge,
so let's boogie
onto somethin' else.
Somethin' we can
really sink our teeth into.
CAIN:
Did you pull up that file
I asked you for?
You know, I'm not doing
your taxes
or running a daily planner here.
You know, you got me accessing
the police central mainframe.
It takes
a bit of genius and time.
If I'm not careful, they'll
lock on and trace us back.
They trace hackers all the time.
Now, that wouldn't do,
would it?
To have a knock
on the old silo here,
a couple
of the old team in blue,
their eyes lightin' up
in surprise.
"Hey, judge, what
ya been up to this past year,
besides terrorizing the ungodly
and running around the subways?"
I want everything
not released to the public
on the Grim Reaper murders.
We ever get caught, certain
people are just gonna kill you,
but I'm gonna have to take
my summers in Tibet.
Read it and weep.
CAIN:
Get ready to saddle up, partner.
We're ridin' into town tonight.
What? I don't see anything.
Nothin' I haven't read
or seen on the tube.
Exactly. There's only one way
Donovan could have
information about the murders
that aren't on the file.
Yeah, he's the murderer.
Or the murderer
gave them to him,
maybe without
Donovan's knowledge.
That's supposing
Donovan isn't the Reaper.
Why should we suppose that?
Because on the night
the Hillman girl was murdered,
Donovan had an alibi that
satisfies me a thousand percent.
Oh, I know this
is gonna be good.
I was with him
in his room all night.
[♪♪♪]
Why?
Why is Dr. Tremayne on my case?
Why not you?
Why-- Why aren't you
my doctor any longer?
TANYA:
I don't know why Dr. Tremayne
was put in charge of your case.
[GASPS]
Oh, my God!
Who are you?
What are you doing in my house?
I'm here to talk to you
about Walter Donovan.
[SCOFFS]
I don't understand.
I don't know
how you got in this house
or-or how you got these tapes.
From your office.
Please don't do that.
I know it's a panic button
that signals a security system,
but please don't press it.
Not until you've heard
what I have to say.
I believe that together
we can convince the court
of Donovan's innocence.
How do you know of any of this?
Who are you?
God, what are you?
You told the DA that even
though Donovan had knowledge
of the Grim Reaper murders,
facts that only
the murderer could know,
you were not convinced
of his guilt.
How do you know
what I said to the DA?
Did you break into their office
in the middle of the night too?
I know things.
Such as someone else told the
police of Donovan's confessions.
Someone else who had access
to his medical files and tapes,
someone else who could alter the
medication prescribed by you.
The medication?
No, no one can do that.
No one can change anything that
I've prescribed except maybe--
Dr. Tremayne?
Dr. Tremayne is one of the
finest doctors in this country.
I don't believe he would betray
a patient like that.
He's the one
that fed Donovan to the police,
maybe to cover up
for somebody else.
Check the institute.
Find out if Tremayne changed
Donovan's medication.
This is preposterous.
Some lunatic
in a black coat and a hat
comes riding in like Zorro,
and I'm supposed to do
what you ask?
Surely doctors of psychiatry
are not supposed to use words
like "lunatic."
In instances like this,
they do.
Why?
[SCOFFS]
Why should I listen to you?
Because you're
the member of a profession
that deals
in learning the truth.
I can show you the truth.
All right.
I'll go to the office.
But I can't--
[♪♪♪]
Damn! Oh, I don't know,
Kemosabe.
There's a lot of
microwave activity out here.
A lot of satellite dishes
from that broadcasting station
we passed comin' up
South Street.
I'm gettin' jammed
out the wazoo.
Keep at it.
I want everything
in the institute's computer
on Walter Donovan's treatments.
I'll phone if I get work.
Wait a minute.
You really believe
this Donovan is getting
more than Thorazine treatments?
I slipped into his room
as soon as he was brought
there that night.
I stayed until 4 a.m.
The police file you pulled said
that Cindy Hillman
was murdered at 3 a.m.
So however Walter Donovan
got soaked in blood...
Blood, mind you, that matched
that of the Hillman girl.
...it happened after the fact
by somebody else
that was at the murder scene.
It's too bad there's already
a Wizard of Oz, judge,
or your next career'd be a lock.
If I'm not home by midnight,
call the president.
No problem.
His number's in the auto dialer.
He said he'd come back.
He said--
Come on, Walter.
Down the hatch.
Do what she says, Mr. D.
We're all buddies here.
And I know it's not you two,
but there's one orderly
that's decided
he can leave things laying about
without putting them away.
Scully told me this morning.
I don't know who it is,
unless it's
that new guy, Deacon.
Well, have a talk with him.
I'll have a talk with him.
You behave, or I'll have
to have a talk with you.
You did as I said.
You've been avoiding
taking your drugs. Good.
I didn't think
you were coming back. I...
I started to think there
was no one to be coming back.
I thought this was
part of what's wrong with me.
I can't speak to your amnesia,
but part of what's wrong
with you is these.
You know, in the past few years,
they've made interesting
discoveries in the relationship
between blood chemistry
and mental disorders.
You've been receiving
a dangerous dosage
of a complex
chemical compound which can,
in a normal human being,
temporarily duplicate
all of the mental
and physical sensory symptoms
of a violent schizophrenic.
My God. They've been
making me into a monster?
No, they just made it
appear that way.
You haven't killed anyone,
at least not to my knowledge.
But I see them.
I see the women
screaming and dying.
I see them.
Someone is making you see them.
Is someone making me see the
blood from one of the victims?
How does it get there
if I didn't--?
Not how.
The question is who.
Who is putting it there?
And the answer is the Reaper,
the true Reaper.
You have no idea
how much I want to believe you.
How much I needto believe you.
My little girl.
She's only 5.
That's all I think about.
Even my wife, I mean,
it kills me not to be with her,
but my baby needs me.
Who'll take care of her?
Who'll watch out for her?
I missed the father/daughter
dance last night.
All the daddies
with their little girls...
and I couldn't
be there for her.
I missed it.
You haven't told anyone
about my visit the other night,
have you? Anyone?
No. No.
Not that I know of.
How do you get in here?
As Houdini once postulated,
certain places are made
not to be broken into.
That's why he always insisted
on being locked inside a safe.
These rooms were designed
not to be broken out of.
They're easy to get into
from the corridor.
But then how do you get out?
Sleight of hand.
What do I do?
Just what you've been doing.
You wait to hear from me
and you avoid taking
that medication as best you can.
We're going to need
hard evidence
and someone on your side.
You're on my side.
Someone real on your side,
someone who can
stand up for you in court.
[BEEPING]
[LATCH CLICKS]
It's all in the touch.
Wait.
Why?
Why do you do this?
Why do you do this
the way you do it?
Because they make me.
[♪♪♪]
Yes, Tina. Tanya.
No, I came to the office.
Do you have that information
I called you about?
He did? When?
[SIGHS]
No. No, no, no, he--
He did clear it with me.
I just... Thank you.
Tremayne did change
the medication.
[SIGHS]
I didn't even...
I didn't even hear you at all.
I didn't know
when I'd see you again...
or if I even would.
I, uh...
[SCOFFS]
This whole thing is--
Crazy?
[SCOFFS]
Psychiatrists don't use
words like that.
Look, what do I do?
How do I handle this?
I have to call the police.
First, you need something
definitive to take to them.
When you have it,
go to District Attorney
Dan Underwood.
He'll know what to do,
and you can trust him.
What an odd thing to say.
Do you work with him?
Does he know you?
No one knows me.
You don't seem like a man
who has to hide.
Why do you?
Bring Tremayne here.
Why?
What are you gonna do to him?
Talk to him.
DONOVAN [ON RECORDING]:
I can see the blood.
The blood on the clothing,
the blood on the...
I can't hear her scream.
No, I can't hear her screaming,
but I know she does.
I...
I don't know why I can't see
her face clearly enough.
I...
I-- I never see their faces.
I must block them out.
It's like I can see them. I...
Long, pretty, yellow hair.
Earrings with...
little seashells.
[SCREAMS]
Pretty girls.
Such pretty girls, but I...
[SCREAMING]
I can't see their faces.
Colin!
It's like...
I can see
what's happening in...
In quick images, like I'm
walking through an old movie.
Colin.
Colin! Damn it!
Col--
I need to go out.
No! No, not tonight.
Not with Donovan locked up
in the security wing.
Then they'll know
he can't have been the Reaper.
I have to.
Dear God, you fight me
every step of the way.
Colin, how can I help you
hide what you are
if you won't let me?
I don't think
I can do this anymore.
You're getting worse.
No.
No, I can be good.
I can.
[SIGHS]
Help me.
Help me and I can stop.
[SIGHS]
Tanya...
Tanya, you always took
care of it all.
I just thought if I could...
give the police something,
someone...
Then Walter gets locked up.
And two weeks later
when another girl is dead
and they know
they have the wrong man,
where will they look?
[♪♪♪]
I can stop.
I can.
Like you did the last time?
Or the time before that?
Or the time before that?!
I am the institute.
Without me,
there is no institute.
Without me...
there is nothing.
Nothing for you.
I'll help you, Colin.
I promised you.
I'll help you...
but you must listen to me.
You must do as I say.
You can't hide any more
of these recordings from me.
They all have to be erased.
All.
Let me speak to Murch.
Murch, Dr. Russell.
There's someone in my office.
[GROANS SOFTLY]
Damn.
Donovan.
Walter.
Walter, come on.
Walter!
Walt, come on, I've gotta
get you out of here. Walter!
[♪♪♪]
[GRUNTS]
Everything's gonna be
okay now, Colin.
Everything's gonna be okay.
Fifteen cc's.
Fifteen?
Oh!
We're gonna find out
exactly who this is.
Put it back on him.
Ugh!
[♪♪♪]
[GROANS]
[BREATHING RAPIDLY]
CAIN:
From the grave, Strauss.
I'll get you...
you and Kinghorn.
From grave...
Strauss.
Strauss...
Shouldn't be more than another
hour. Keep her up if you can.
I've got someone here who wants
to sleep over with her tonight.
I think it's the one she wanted.
No matter. If she doesn't
want it, it can sleep with me.
Heh, no.
No, no, it's nothing.
It's just a business meeting.
Yeah, yeah,
it has to do with Kinghorn.
Karen, it's nothing
to worry about.
I'll be home before you know it.
Make sure
Amanda waits up for me.
Love you.
[BEEPS]
[GASPING]
You're mad, Strauss.
You and Kinghorn.
You think you can scare me off?
No, judge, I surely don't.
But that's what Kinghorn
wanted to try.
We figured the most
important things in your life
are your wife
and baby girl.
Now, Kinghorn figured
we'd take one from you, yeah?
We'd kill one,
maybe you'd stay in line
so you didn't lose the other.
It's not a bad plan,
but this is simpler.
I'll get you, Strauss.
You and that bastard
masquerading
as a police commissioner.
I'll get you--
From the grave.
If that's what it takes.
You'll get swallowed,
even if for my murder.
Anyway, that would be me
getting you even from the grave.
Now, you talk nasty
like that to me, judge,
and I may go visit
your wife and kid tonight,
even while you're taking
your first harp lesson.
I may go see them
and arrange a family reunion.
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[SCREAMING]
Come on, we gotta stop him.
WES:
We don't need
to stop him anymore.
[♪♪♪]
[GASPING]
Take it easy, man.
We'll get you home.
[CAIN GROANING SOFTLY]
Judge!
God, Judge, it's you!
Oh...
Oh.
Oh! Oh, God.
Judge, oh...
[GROANS, THEN CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
From the grave, Strauss.
[MAN SPEAKING IN CHINESE]
Oh, please, Grandpa,
can give me a chance, huh?
[SPEAKS IN CHINESE]
[IN ENGLISH]
Grandfather is right.
Why did you bring him here?
Why not to the police?
CAIN:
No, no...
N-n-no...
No...
That's why.
He doesn't want the police.
He's in shock.
He doesn't know
what he wants or needs.
I cannot do for him here
what he requires.
You must take him
to the clinic.
As far as I know,
the police did this.
I was meeting him because he
had me diggin' up files on--
It's better you don't know.
This appears to be
some kind of carbolic acid.
There's probably been
nerve damage.
He's going to lose the hand.
Whatever it takes,
you have to do it, Lee.
I owe this guy.
He's the judge.
He's the reason
I'm not in there
with the hard-timers
and scuzzbuckets.
He's the one
who gave me the chance.
I'm asking you, as my brother,
you have to do
what it takes, Lee.
I'll do whatever you need.
If he dies?
[SCOFFS]
Well, if he dies,
I'm in deep anyway.
Who'll believe
a convict out on furlough
with a dead judge on her hands?
Lee, the guy trusted me.
A judge trusted a convict
to dig up files on the police.
I turn him in, he could be a lot
worse than what you see here.
Rae, with what exists
in medicine today,
you have no idea
how much I could help him
if he goes to a trauma center.
We keep him here, even
with everything I could do...
Look, when this man realizes
what he will be...
he may hate us.
No...
No police.
He may hate himself.
He'll be alive, won't he?
[SHEARS CUTTING]
No... N-n-no police.
No-- Strauss...
S-s-s-strauss...
Captain,
glad I was able to find you.
You're not going to believe
what I have to tell you.
What?
[♪♪♪]
Tremayne...
Tremayne.
Colin.
COLIN: You'd better come now.
I gotta go.
You better hang up.
You'd better come here and
hear what else he has to say.
CAIN:
No...
No. No, not Donovan.
Tremayne.
Tremayne is the Reaper.
Tremayne killed them.
[♪♪♪]
[KEYBOARD CLACKING]
[TIRES SCREECH]
Did you locate
Commissioner Kinghorn yet?
WES:
No, captain. I left word
at his home and his office.
Keep trying. Call both
girlfriends if you have to,
but find him.
Take care of the other matter
and get here.
Already made the stop
and I'm on my way.
And I left word
for the commissioner
you have something
he'll really wanna hear.
No, it's not something
he wants to hear.
It's not something
he wants to hear at all.
What am I doin'?
No one can see in.
Captain Strauss. I'm supposed
to meet Dr. Tremayne in OR 1.
I'll show you the way.
Just tell me. I'll find it.
Captain Strauss,
I'm Dr. Russell.
Dr. Tremayne asked me
to meet you.
All right, let's go.
I'm expecting someone.
Just send him up.
[GEARS WHIR]
[♪♪♪]
[GRUNTS]
Hey, where are you going?
Oh, uh, did Captain Strauss
come this way?
Yeah, he said you'd be along.
Oh, he did?
He told me to send you on down.
Up the corridor to the left.
Operating Room One.
Nothin' like a little
police cooperation, right?
[GROANS]
[YELLING]
Look, I wanna
see Tremayne now, okay?
He'll be right with us.
He said to meet him in OR 1.
Is that where Cain is?
[YELLING]
[ELECTRICITY CRACKLING]
[GROANING]
Tremayne?
Dr. Tremayne?
Colin?
Cain?
[GASPS]
It's me, Cain.
The one you want, isn't it?
Come on, let's end
this nightmare, Cain.
You've been haunting me
for almost a year now. Come on.
[SOBBING]
I tried for you, Colin.
I tried.
I'm tired
of ghosts and goblins, Cain.
I'm tired of dead men, Cain.
Aren't you tired of being one?
[MUFFLED SCREAMING]
Remember that family reunion
I promised you?
[AMANDA WHIMPERING]
Well, today's the day.
Don't you wanna say hi
to your daughter
and goodbye once more, huh?
Talk to your daddy.
Tell your daddy to come out.
Come on. Come on.
Go on. He told you
to call your dad.
My-- My daddy's dead.
Well, how right you are.
Your last chance to look, Cain!
[AMANDA WHIMPERING]
[♪♪♪]
Stop fighting, you little--
All right, take it easy.
Now you just watch the door.
This is an operating room.
An emergency generator
should kick on.
[WHIRRING]
[WHIMPERING]
Now, keep that kid still.
[♪♪♪]
[MUFFLED GROANING]
Wes?
CAIN:
I told you
I'd come back for you, Strauss,
from the grave, if necessary.
[GUNSHOT]
Face me. Face me, damn you!
You want me, you got me. Why
don't you stand up and face me?
You wanted me?[GASPS]
You've got me.
[GASPS]
[♪♪♪]
[HISSING]
Watch her die, Cain!
Cain!
[SCREAMING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Oh!
AMANDA: No, no.
Are you okay? You okay?
No, no, no.
Oh, no, I'm a friend.
[SOBBING]
Oh, I knew your father.
Oh! Oh...
Are you okay?
Now that that monster's
gone away.
Let's go home.
[♪♪♪]
[INAUDIBLE DIALOGUE]
Anything I say...
Anything I try
to say will sound inane.
I know that you can
never understand
what you've done for me.
Just this morning...
I mean, just this morning
I thought my life
as I knew it was over.
Looking across at my home,
knowing Susie and Lisa
are waiting for me,
that I'm gonna
walk through that door
like I have
so many other times...
I feel reborn.
When I truly lost all hope,
you've given me
a second chance at life.
What can I do
to thank you for that?
Use it.
How will I find you again?
How do I contact you?
What if I need you?
You won't need me, Walter.
You won't need me.
And if you do,
I'll be listening.
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
Thanks.
Someone's waiting for you.
Daddy! Daddy's home!
[♪♪♪]
There is still
much to be unraveled
in this truly bizarre
turn of events
connected with
the Grim Reaper murders,
but it is suspected that the
man who kidnapped Amanda Cain,
daughter of
the late Judge Paul Cain,
was indeed a city police
officer named Kevin Wesley.
Wesley died tonight
in the fire
at the Broadmoor Institute,
along with Captain Strauss,
Dr. Colin Tremayne
and Dr. Tanya Russell.
There are
unsubstantiated rumors
that Dr. Tremayne
is going to be named
in connection
with the Reaper murders
along with his sister,
Dr. Tanya Russell,
who also worked
at the institute.
It is believed
they conspired together
to have one of their patients,
Walter Donovan,
convicted of the heinous
Reaper crime.
I-- I have no idea
what happened or why.
I-- I was out for the evening
and someone came
to the babysitter
and identified themselves
as a police officer
and took my daughter, and...
Oh!
Why Amanda Cain was taken
from her home tonight
is a complete mystery.
Why did that man say
I was gonna meet Daddy?
For a minute he made me think
Daddy wasalive.
I can't explain why people do
such cruel things, honey.
They're sick people.
They need help.
And sometimes innocent people
get hurt by their illness.
But you don't
have anything to worry about.
I'm here, and I love you.
Will you stay with me
for a while? I'm afraid.
Afraid of the monster.
Oh, sure, baby.
I'm just gonna make sure
the door's locked, okay?
I'll be right back.
But what if
the monster comes back?
Oh, honey, mmm! He won't.
I'll be one minute.
Here, while I'm gone,
you hold this.
You don't have
anything to worry about.
What do I always tell you?
Daddy watches over us.
And Daddy will protect you
from the monster, okay?
Mmm.
You'll protect me
from the monster, Daddy.
You'll protect me.
[♪♪♪]