[interface buzzing]
[interface humming]
[light booms]
- [lights buzzing]
- [thunder crackling]
[electronic music]
[dramatic music]
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
[gentle music]
[sighs]
[interface humming]
[roaring]
[dramatic music]
[growling]
[roaring]
[growling and roaring]
[roars]
[man] Verifying behavioral
functionality.
[raptor growls, sniffs]
[screeches]
[chirping, growling]
[chain jingling]
[music continues]
[raptors hissing, screeching]
[raptor chirps]
[raptors screeching, chirping]
[door whirs]
[raptor growls]
[raptor screeches]
[raptors screeching, snarling]
- [man grunting]
- [chain jingling]
[man screams]
[man grunting]
- [raptor screeches]
- [man grunts]
[raptors screeching]
[raptors chirping]
- [man grunts]
- [chain thuds]
- [chain rattling]
- [man grunting]
[raptor screeches]
[man grunts]
- [man screaming]
- [raptor chirps]
[raptor chirps]
- [man grunting]
- [raptor screeches]
- [chain rattling]
- [man grunting]
[raptor chirps]
- [raptor chirps]
- [man grunts]
- [man screams]
- [raptor screeches]
[raptor chirping]
[raptor screeches]
[chain rattling]
- [raptor screeches]
- [man grunts]
[raptor screeches]
[man grunting]
- [man screams]
- [raptor screeches]
- [chain rattling]
- [chain thuds]
[man groaning]
[flesh squelching]
[alarm buzzes]
- [hologram buzzes]
- [raptor snarls]
[raptors screeching]
[intense music]
[alarm buzzes]
[holograms buzzing]
[raptor growls]
[raptors screeching]
[raptor screeching]
[rifle fires]
[intense music]
[raptors screeching]
- [man grunts]
- [raptor screeches]
[rifle fires]
[raptors screeching]
[rifle firing]
- [raptor screeches]
- [rifle fires]
[rifle firing]
[man]
Alpha testing complete.
The total immersion VR game,
"Dinosaur World,"
is almost ready for release.
Five million will be awarded
to the participants
of the upcoming closed beta,
the ultimate test of
program effectiveness.
20 players will be
selected at random
to compete in our pioneering
gaming experience.
Survive the game and
share in the grand prize.
Everyone is welcome to enter
"Dinosaur World."
[lively music]
[cellphone buzzing]
[missiles firing]
- [descending tone plays]
- [Eric sighs]
Have you figured out how to pay
your tuition next semester?
[Eric sighs]
We've tried about everything,
but it's hopeless.
Just can't afford it.
So that's that. Game over.
See you around.
[cellphone buzzes]
Go ahead.
[notification chimes]
No way.
[upbeat rock music]
- [crowd cheering]
- [cameras snapping]
[notification chimes]
Down. Go down.
[video game music playing]
Right. Move right.
[cellphone ringing, buzzing]
[Lily laughs]
- [both] Yes!
- [Lily] Let's get a drink.
[Lily sighs]
- Can I get water?
- Water.
- Soda.
[cellphone ringing, buzzing]
It's Peter.
See what he says.
[cellphone chimes]
Peter! What do I owe
the pleasure of your call?
I hear you and Lily are going to
be beta testing Russell's new game.
You have your own gaming
company to worry about.
- What's it to you?
- [Peter chuckles]
Let's just say
a little bird told me.
[Lily over phone] It was easy.
I hacked into their system and
left a little subroutine.
It's a recursive operation
that submits our names
with a callback frequency of
every five seconds.
- [Lily chuckles]
- Wow, color me impressed.
It was nothing.
Ass kissing aside, Peter,
what do you want?
We never hear from you
unless you want something.
Through my own means,
I'll be in the game with you.
Yeah, good luck with that.
We'll need more than luck.
I want to win.
We can figure this game
out in the process
and produce a copy of it.
How about we partner up?
I have a plan that will guarantee
we win the five million.
We'll split it
three ways equally.
Think about it. Not bad, right?
Well, five million split
two ways is even better. Hm?
[Lily chuckles]
Would you two rather work with
me or against me? [chuckles]
You might end up with
nothing at all.
He's got a point.
Dinosaurs are gonna
be hard enough.
I'd rather not have
to worry about
this sneaky asshole
stabbing us in the back.
[Peter over phone] So?
Can I count on your cooperation?
Mm. Okay.
We're in.
But we gotta share
the prize equally.
Cool. You're on.
[cellphone chimes]
[cellphone clicking]
[gentle music]
[cellphone buzzing]
- [woman over phone] Hey.
- Hey.
Is he asleep yet?
He just passed out
waiting for your call.
But we should let him
sleep for now.
When you tried calling earlier,
I was working. Sorry.
He's probably upset with me.
[woman]
Don't let it get to you.
He'll understand.
Mm.
Hey, know what?
[woman] Mm-hm?
[Alex over phone] You know how
much he likes to play the games
made by Mental Abyss? Well,
they're releasing a new one.
I signed up as
a volunteer tester.
And you won't believe
what happened.
Me, they've selected me
to take part.
I really wanted to tell him
today, but I was swamped.
And I just got back.
[woman] It's okay.
I'll tell him in the morning.
You know, he's gonna go crazy.
I better get going.
Tomorrow's another long day.
Love you.
Love you too.
[Alex sighs]
[upbeat music]
- Hi.
- Hm?
You were picked for
the beta too?
- Mm-hm.
- [Eason chuckles]
Their games are great.
I've played every single one.
Wow, cool.
[Eason]
Oh, what do you think that is?
I'm gonna go check it out.
- [Eric chuckles]
- [Eason] Oh, I recognize this.
- [chuckles] It's the...
- Oh!
- Sorry about that.
- It's okay.
Excuse me.
Um, I'm...
Whoa.
[chuckles]
[Eric] Uh, hi, Peter.
The name's Eric. I know you.
Yeah? Well, I don't know you.
- [Eason] Sorry.
- Beat it.
My friend must be mixed up.
[hologram buzzes]
- [Tyrannosaurus rex roaring]
- [testers gasping]
- [Eason chuckles]
- [upbeat music]
What do you think? Our AR tech
is pretty realistic, huh?
[testers laughing]
Hello, players. Welcome.
- You made it.
- [testers applauding]
[Eason chuckles]
[Russell] This game is like nothing
you've ever experienced before.
There are two things
to remember.
First, when you enter the game,
there will be
backpacks scattered
throughout the starting field.
Each one will carry a variety of
equipment to aid you.
The second is that
there are no rules.
Players still alive
after four hours
share the grand prize
pot of five million.
And if you're the last one
standing, you take it all.
Now get ready. Start-up can be
a bit disorienting.
Welcome to "Dinosaur World."
Let the game begin.
[interface whooshes]
[group screaming]
[pterodactyls screeching]
- [man] Run!
- [pterodactyls screeching]
[dramatic music]
Leave the bags. We'll come back.
- [pterodactyls screeching]
- [group shouting]
You won't last long if
you stay here.
[pterodactyls screeching]
[man screaming]
- [body thuds]
- [man screaming]
- [notification chimes]
- [interface buzzing]
[ominous music]
[Eason panting]
They look so real.
- [Eason chuckles]
- This game is tougher than I expected.
You could've left me
to die back there.
- Thank me later. We still got 12 hours in here.
- [tree creaking]
[Tyrannosaurus rex growling]
[Eric screaming]
- [man groans]
- [Tyrannosaurus rex grunts]
[man screaming]
[Tyrannosaurus rex chomps]
[Eric yelping]
[Tyrannosaurus rex grunting]
- Stay back.
- [growls]
- [Eason groans]
- [woman whimpering]
- [Tyrannosaurus rex growls]
- Come on! There's a cave here!
[woman screaming]
- [Tyrannosaurus rex snarling]
- [Eric] Run!
Yeah, let's go, let's go!
- Get in here!
- [Tyrannosaurus rex roars]
[Eric panting]
[Tyrannosaurus rex snarls]
[both sighing]
[Tyrannosaurus rex snarling]
Shh.
[Tyrannosaurus rex growls,
snarling]
[saliva dripping]
[Tyrannosaurus rex snarls]
[whispering] One.
[whispering]
No, no, no, no, no.
- [Tyrannosaurus rex snarls]
- No, no, no.
- Yes.
- [mouthing words]
- No, no. Don't, don't.
- [Eric screams]
- [Tyrannosaurus rex growling]
- [Eason screams]
[both panting]
[Tyrannosaurus rex snarls]
[Tyrannosaurus rex roars]
- [Eric screaming]
- [Eason whimpering]
[Tyrannosaurus rex growling]
[Tyrannosaurus rex roars]
[Tyrannosaurus rex snarls]
[Eason laughs]
[ominous music]
[woman panting]
[raptor snarls]
[raptor screeches]
[gentle music]
I think we're good.
Looks like it.
[both sighing]
Thanks.
I know it's not real,
but it sure feels real.
Heart's beating like crazy.
[chuckles]
I've never been so scared
before.
We've been hounded nonstop
since we got here.
[Eric sighs]
[Eason sniffs]
You smell something?
Did you fart?
Huh? It's you.
Huh?
You're covered in dinosaur spit.
[Eric chuckles]
[saliva squishes]
- [Eric chuckles]
- [Eason sniffs, groans]
[Eric laughing]
I suppose they meant it when
they said it was real, huh?
- That?
- [both laughing]
[Eason groans]
[Eric sighs]
If this part feels real,
then what would being
eaten feel like?
[footsteps rustling]
- [crickets chirping]
- [woman panting]
[sighing]
[footsteps rustling]
[ominous music]
- [raptor hisses]
- [footsteps rustling]
[gasps]
- [gasps]
[raptor snarling]
[raptor hisses]
[raptor chirps]
- [raptor snarls]
- [woman screams]
[raptor screeches, chomps]
[woman screaming]
[raptor growling]
[raptor screeches]
- [raptor growls]
- Whoa.
[raptor hisses]
[raptor calling]
We should head back now and
see if there are any bags left.
[raptor calls]
[tense music]
Lily, grab that one.
With a little cover,
this place should be
safe for a while.
If we're lucky, the T-rex scared
away the other players
and, hopefully, the smaller
dinosaurs as well.
[Eason] If we're lucky?
That's not exactly a reassuring sentiment.
I can't guarantee anything.
We know next to nothing
about the game.
That said, if it's like
the others I've played,
hiding won't work for long.
Sooner or later,
it's fight or flight.
[chuckles]
- What d'you think?
- Huh?
It's good.
- Let's rest.
- Oh, yeah.
- Huh?
- My name is Eason, by the way.
Oh. Eric.
Nice to meet you.
I think we should team up
if we want to win.
I can really use that
prize money.
Yeah, sounds good.
Hope we make it.
Did you have a look
in your bag yet?
Not yet.
Hm.
- I got a rope, looks like.
- [Eason chuckles]
Rope against dinosaurs?
What good is this?
Whoa!
- [knife rasps]
- Got this knife too.
Mm.
Seriously, talk about
ineffective.
- Not against players.
- Huh?
[Eason chuckles]
[laughs]
Hey! Medicine.
I may live through
this after all.
When I fell during the chase,
I got scratched up.
Hey, help me with this?
It'll probably sting a bit.
[Eason chuckles]
I'm tough. I survived a Tyrannosaurus rex.
I can take anything...
- [Eason screams]
- Really, tough guy?
[both chuckling]
- [Eason groans]
- Don't be so loud, dude.
- Just a bit more.
- [Eason chuckles]
- All right, calm down, dude.
- [Eason groans]
- Nearly there. Almost done.
- [Eason whimpers]
[Eric chuckles]
The man survived at T-rex,
defeated by salve.
[Tyrannosaurus rex roars]
Let's get back inside.
We need to keep
a low profile for now.
[group panting]
[Peter] Think we're good here.
Yeah.
I hope there's something
awesome in here.
- [Lily chuckles]
- Hey, how about this?
Hm?
- [tense music]
- What do you think this is?
[device beeping, hums]
Whoa. Cool, man.
It's a smaller version
of the game map.
Hey, what are the dots for?
I think the green dots show
our current position.
Red dots are likely
the dinosaurs.
There's no way we can
lose with this.
[Lily laughs]
Not really. It doesn't display
the other players.
Antivenom?
[scoffs] What's this for?
Toxic dinosaur?
Ha!
- This.
- [baton crackles]
This is what I'm talking about.
- Nice. That could be fun.
- [baton crackling]
We've got to go, quick.
- [device beeps]
- [Jeremy] Okay.
[Eric] So here's my plan.
We just stay here hidden.
[Eason] Yeah, sure beats
running for our lives.
- We'll win this for sure.
- [Eric] Shh. Someone's here.
[Vivian scoffs] Amateurs.
- [Vivian grunts]
- [Eason] Hey!
The hell?!
Why'd she do that?
- 'Cause she's mean.
- What you did...
It's a mess.
Hey!
Was this your master plan,
to hide behind some sticks?
Yeah, he was almost eaten
in the first few minutes.
What? Wasn't only me.
Look, she's hurt,
and no use to us.
We should take her out.
She hasn't done anything to us.
She needs help.
I get that, but it'd be
one less person
we need to worry about.
If we don't work together,
I don't think anybody's
gonna win this game.
I won't do it.
- [Vivian] What are you doing?
- I'm gonna help you.
Hold on. She might just
be faking it.
No, I don't think so.
- [Eric sighs]
- Don't you dare.
It's okay.
Trust me.
[gentle music]
[winces]
I'm going to need your medicine.
- But we might need it.
- Hurry.
Okay. Before I begin,
could you pull your shirt down?
Ju... ju... just a little so I can
see the wound.
If you try to take advantage
of me, you're dead.
I won't, I promise.
[light jingling]
It feels so real.
Trust me, I know.
So how did someone so tough
get hurt so bad?
I was careless.
It didn't take long for people
to turn on each other.
I'm Vivian.
I'm Eric.
His name's Eason.
[chuckles]
Okay.
All done.
Thank you.
No problem.
Hey, is this a dating app
or a game?
[upbeat music]
Whatever, dude.
[chuckles]
[crickets chirping]
[suspenseful music]
Hey!
- [Alex grunts]
- [man groaning]
[man grunts]
- [both grunting]
- [man groans]
[man grunts]
- [hand slaps]
- [man groaning]
Better give that back.
I'm sorry! Sorry.
[man grunts]
Okay.
[man grunting]
[ax whooshing]
- [Alex grunts]
- [man groans]
- [Alex] Watch out!
- [crocodile roars]
- [man groaning]
- [water splashing]
[crocodile roars]
[man yelping]
[music continues]
[raptor snarling]
[raptor screeches]
[Eric whispers]
Looks like a raptor.
[sighs]
[raptor snarling]
[raptor screeches]
Where's she going?
I knew it was a mistake
to trust her.
She just left us here.
[raptor snarling]
Oh. Oh, oh.
[raptor hisses]
[raptor snarls]
[Eric whimpers]
[raptor screeches]
- [Eric whimpers]
- [Vivian screams]
- [Eason gasps]
- Whoa!
What are you guys doing?
Don't just sit there! Run!
I knew we could trust her.
[Eason grunts]
[Vivian panting]
- [Eason] Wait, hold on a sec.
- [Eric] What are you doing?
- [raptor snarls]
- [both whimpering]
[thrilling music]
[man grunting]
Help!
Help.
Help me.
Help!
[man grunting]
Over there. He needs help.
Grab on!
[all grunting]
[rocks clattering]
[man screams]
[body thuds]
- Oh, sorry.
- I'm sorry, man.
[man chuckles]
[both grunting]
What's happening?
Wait, wait. We're friendly.
- Don't worry, fellas.
- [Eason] We're friendly.
This will be quick.
- [Eason screams]
- [man grunts]
[tense music]
- [Eric screams]
- [man groans]
- Sorry.
- [Eric whimpers]
You guys are so dead.
- [man screams]
- [straps ripping]
- [man chuckles]
- [pterodactyl screeching]
[man groaning]
- [bones cracking]
- Whoa!
- [pterodactyl screeching]
- [raptor calls]
[pterodactyl screeching]
[both whimpering]
[raptor snarling]
Oh, yeah.
Another player is dead.
- [Lily chuckles]
- Let me see.
Pterodactyl got him.
[Lily chuckles]
That building is too big for there
not to be something useful in it.
Let's go.
[pterodactyls screeching]
[door rumbling]
- Hey, hey!
- [banging]
- [Eric] Open the door!
- [Eason] Open up!
I open this door for you,
and we all die!
- Asshole.
- [Eason] Come on.
[raptor calling]
Hey! Hey!
Why didn't you let us in?!
It's everyone for themselves,
you know that!
[window crashing]
- [all gasping]
- [raptor growls]
[door rumbling]
[raptor snarls, screeches]
[intense music]
[raptor snarling]
[man panting]
[raptor snarls, screeches]
[Eric yelps]
[raptor growling]
[raptor screeches]
[raptor snarling]
- All right, let's go!
- [raptors growling]
[man screaming]
[raptor chomps]
[pterodactyls screeching]
[raptor calls]
[raptor screeches]
This is way more stressful
than I expected.
- [raptor calls]
- We're trapped.
Any idea how to get
out of this one?
[Eric panting]
[raptor screeches]
- Hey.
- [Eric] Huh?
What are you here for?
[Eric sighs]
I attend a local university.
- [Eason] Uh-huh.
- Masters in paleontology.
It was going pretty well,
but a year ago,
my mother became very ill.
The medical bills
are adding up.
On top of the tuition,
we just can't afford it.
Might have to drop out
and take care of her.
[sighs] I see. So this
competition is your best shot.
It is.
The prize money could
go a long way
in paying for her procedures
and giving me a chance
to stay here.
[raptor snarls, screeches]
- [Eric] And you?
- Me?
[sighs] My life isn't
what you'd call fulfilling.
Wanted some fun.
I'm a math teacher,
and I hate math.
- Math?
- Yeah. [chuckles]
That sounds awful.
- Right?
- [Eric laughs]
[raptor screeches]
I tried my best for my students,
but it just wasn't enough.
They still don't like me.
This test is being
streamed online,
so let's win the prize
to show them...
that they have a cool teacher.
[chuckles]
[Eason] Deal.
[raptor screeches]
[raptor calls]
[both laughing]
- [Eason groaning]
- [Eric yelps]
- [pterodactyl screeching]
- [Eason groaning]
[intense music]
[Eric] Eason!
[Eason screaming]
- [glass shatters]
- [pterodactyl screeching]
No key.
- What about the machine gun?
- Help me out.
- Uh-huh.
- [machine gun rattling]
[sighs] It's not moving.
[sighs]
You guys know how to
hot wire a car?
Do I look like I know how to?
This isn't a movie.
[raptor growls]
[Eric whimpering]
[tense music]
[raptor screeches]
Oh, yeah. That's right.
The knife.
[raptor screeches]
- [knife rasps]
- [Eric grunts]
[dramatic music]
[Eric yelps]
- [raptor growls]
- [knife thuds]
[upbeat music]
[sighs]
[bag thuds]
[ominous music]
[raptor snarling]
[raptor screeches]
- [rifle fires]
- [raptor chirps]
- [Lily gasps]
I think that was a gunshot.
Let's go.
[raptor snarls]
[raptor screeches]
Come on, you son of a bitch!
[raptor snarls]
- [raptor growls]
- [rifle fires]
[man grunts]
[water splashes]
Someone has a gun,
and I want it.
They're not just gonna
give it to you.
I know that, idiot.
Unlike you two, I have a plan.
I asked you to join me because
you're supposed to be the best,
so less talk, more show.
[Peter scoffs]
I think he's alone.
- [baton crackling]
- Wait, he's still armed.
Hey, I got this.
[Lily sighs]
[Lily panting]
Don't shoot!
I'm unarmed.
- [upbeat music]
- [man grunts]
Slowly.
- Are you alone?
- Yes.
I was with another player,
but a raptor killed him,
and I ran this way as
fast as I could.
Have you killed anything
with that big gun?
[man chuckles]
Yeah, I just got three raptors.
[Lily chuckles]
[man chuckles]
It's so big.
- [man chuckles]
- You're so strong.
[chuckles] It's nothing.
[both chuckling]
- [baton crackling]
- [man groaning]
Woopsie! [chuckles]
Hey, I think he was
shocked to see me.
- [Jeremy chuckles]
- Yeah. [chuckles]
Tie him up.
[man groaning]
Let's go, big boy.
- [Jeremy grunts]
- [man groaning]
[dramatic music]
[Eddie grunting]
- [raptor snarls]
- Help!
[raptor screeches]
[Eddie grunting]
- [raptor growling]
- [buckle clicking]
- [Eddie grunting]
- [raptor screeches]
[raptor hisses]
[raptor snarls]
[Eddie groans]
Help me!
[Alex] Hey!
- [knife rasps]
- [raptor hisses]
[raptor snarls]
- [raptor growls]
- [knife rasps]
- [raptor whimpers]
[chuckles]
[gasps]
Come on.
I can't trust you.
Why? I could've walked away
and let that raptor eat you.
[chuckles]
Hm?
[scoffs] Okay, fine.
Bye.
[ominous music]
- [Jeremy grunting]
- [man groaning]
Seriously?
- Come on, guys!
- [Jeremy] Bye.
You can't leave me
here like this.
- Hey!
- Hm?
Look, I don't even want the gun.
You can have it.
Just please let me go!
Sorry, can't do that.
Oh, by the way,
I've seen bigger. Hm.
Help!
- [man in distance] Somebody help!
- Wait. Did you hear something?
- No.
- [man in distance] Help!
You heard it that time.
Yeah, I did.
- [man] Hey, help me!
- That way!
[man] Anyone!
Hey, someone's coming.
[ominous music]
[man groaning]
[screams]
[groaning]
Hey. Hey, over here.
Could you guys help me? Please.
- [woman] What do you think?
- [sighs] I don't know.
How did you manage to
get yourself in this position?
I was tricked by three assholes.
They took my rifle.
Would you guys just get me outta here
so I can go kill them?
- He's pissed.
- [panting]
Might come in useful.
Yeah. All right.
Just hold on.
- [rifle fires]
- [man groans]
- [woman groans]
- [rifle fires]
- [man groans]
[chuckles]
Like shooting fish in a barrel.
- [Lily chuckles]
- Now we're playing.
I like it.
[man over PA]
10 players remaining.
New equipment has been
delivered to the starting area.
Everyone will be
headed that way.
Well, then, let's go back.
[rifle clicks]
[man groaning]
- What the hell?
- [headset clatters]
[ominous music]
- [dart gun fires]
- [Eddie gasps]
- Poison.
Come on, that was so close.
Wait, did you seriously
catch that dart?
- Wait right here.
- Hm.
[gun clicking]
Hey, hey, man, I'm sorry!
Hold on!
It's just a game, dude!
[man panting]
Hey! Stop!
Keep away.
You crazy?!
Why'd you shoot it at a kid for?
What's your problem, man?
You are, you spineless coward.
Picking on those who are
too weak to fight back.
- [dart gun fires]
- [dart thuds]
Seriously?
[chuckles]
How about a taste of
your own medicine?
- [dart clangs]
- [man yelps]
Whoa.
- All right.
- [gun thuds]
Come on, man.
- [kick thuds]
- [man groans]
- [hand chops]
[neck cracks]
You take away consequences,
and people show their
true colors.
- [Alex chuckles]
- Where is he?
I killed him.
[gentle music]
I had no choice.
You saved my life.
Yeah, of course.
That's the second time
I saved you.
Let's not make it a habit, okay?
- Thank you.
- You're very welcome.
Now do you trust me?
Okay.
Let's get the new supplies.
Come on.
Don't fall behind.
- [notification chimes]
- [interface buzzing]
That way.
Give me it.
How come no one has
shown up yet?
I don't like waiting.
We don't know how many
players are left.
Don't worry, whoever's
still alive will show up.
[Alex] Hey, why did you sign up
for this anyway?
[Eddie] Hm? Russell's a talented
game designer.
Most of my classmates
love his games.
We all wanted to be chosen
to test "Dinosaur World."
You don't know how envious
my classmates are
that I got picked.
So I tried to stay hidden.
I know I probably
won't win the prize,
but I didn't want to get
killed too soon.
I have a son about
the same age as you.
He really loves the games
Russell makes too.
What do you do in
the real world?
You don't look like a gamer.
I'm a bodyguard for
the rich and powerful.
My job usually keeps me
away from home.
I don't get to see
my son very much.
My son was looking
forward to this game,
so I signed up to surprise him.
I thought that if I won
the competition,
maybe I'd be a little bit
closer to him.
I didn't expect to be chosen.
When the game is over,
we'll have a lot to talk about.
Hopefully, he'll be proud of me,
you know?
I would be proud if
you were my dad.
[Alex chuckles]
Let's team up. Come on.
[Eddie sighs]
- [shoulders thudding]
- [both groaning]
[sighs]
Where were you?
I got lost.
Huh.
- [ground rumbling]
- Huh?
What's going on?
- Feels like an earthquake.
- [tree cracking]
Let's go.
[ominous music]
[man panting]
- [tree cracking]
- [man groans]
[raptor screeches]
[man panting]
[explosion blasting]
Whoa. See that?
Man, they thought of everything.
[man panting]
[raptor screeching]
- [beeping]
- [man grunting]
Quick. Shoot him.
Wait. Something's chasing him.
[device humming]
[music continues]
- [man groans]
- [raptor snarling]
[raptor screeches]
- [man grunts]
- [bag clatters]
[raptor screeching]
[raptor snarls]
- [man screams]
- [raptor screeches]
Oh, damn!
Shh.
One less to worry about.
Can't be many more. [chuckles]
[raptor screeches]
We're not the only ones here.
This doesn't feel right.
[scope clicking]
[Eric gasps]
[suspenseful music]
There.
They're camping the supplies,
picking off those
who come along.
[raptor snarls]
[raptor screeches]
- [raptor screeching]
- Hey, over there.
[raptor screeches, snarls]
- This is too easy.
- [raptor screeches]
[Lily chuckles]
[raptor screeches]
[raptor screeching]
[raptor chirping]
[raptor screeches]
- [Alex grunts]
- [kick thuds]
- [hand chops]
- Wow!
- [gun fires]
- [bullet thuds]
- [Eddie gasps]
- [rifle clicks]
- Watch out!
- [- rifle fires]
- [Eddie grunts]
- [Alex groans]
[Eddie groans]
Eddie!
Hang on. [grunting]
[music continues]
[Peter chuckles]
[sighs] Still too dangerous.
Just a bit longer.
They ran after them.
Now's a good time to get a bag.
- Wait.
- [Vivian grunts]
Okay, but let's be quick.
Hurry!
Eddie, hold on.
We have to win, remember?
Just leave me.
Why did you do that?
You could've got away.
You saved my life twice.
I still owe you one.
You're a good kid.
You're gonna be all right.
Besides, if you
still owe me one,
you have to hang on for me,
okay?
Go. They'll be here any moment.
[Eddie groans]
This is painful.
[gentle music]
Hey. Hey!
You're gonna wake up
safe and sound.
Kid, I'll make them pay for
what they did to you.
[Alex grunts]
[monitor whirring]
Weird.
[Lily] I think he was over here.
Where's the other one?
Poor kid.
Better luck next time.
[grunts]
- [sighs]
- [key jingles]
It's our lucky day.
- Look at this.
- You found the key.
Now the jeep is ours. Let's go.
[bag zipping]
Someone's over there.
[rifle clicks]
- [gun fires]
- [Eric gasping]
[Vivian gasps]
They're here! Run!
- [both panting]
- [dramatic music]
[Jeremy]
I don't think they're armed.
It'll be hard to track down
where they went,
but they need to die.
Lily and I will go after them.
You check the supplies.
Okay. I'll check the bags.
Go.
[tense music]
[dart rasps]
Huh? [groans]
- [Jeremy grunts]
- [kick thuds]
- [both grunting]
- [punch thuds]
- [dart thuds]
- [Alex grunts]
Time to pay for what you did.
[Jeremy groaning]
Help.
[both panting]
[Jeremy in distance] Help!
Jeremy.
That guy with the kid we shot.
What happened?
Poison dart.
- [Jeremy groaning]
- [rifle fires]
[Lily groans]
Did you get him?
- He got away. How's Jeremy?
- It's poison.
[coughing]
[laughing]
I threw away the antivenom.
[coughing]
[groaning]
He also took the scope.
Damn it!
This guy's tough.
We need to be cautious.
What about the other two?!
Gone.
Great. [groans]
- [groans] Damn it!
- [headset clatters]
[Alex grunts]
[footsteps rustling]
- [suspenseful music]
- [bugs chirping]
- Hey.
- [Eric gasps]
Shh.
I'm not a threat.
I know who's chasing you.
They're chasing after me as well.
We saw them shoot that boy.
- Was he your friend?
- Mm.
So we should team up and kill
those two and be done with it.
Huh? Weren't there three?
[chuckles]
Managed to poison one. Got him!
So what should we do now?
It won't be long before
the game's over,
and it doesn't seem like
there are many players left.
Those two pose the only threat.
They're professional gamers.
As if that wasn't bad enough,
they've got a sniper rifle.
As things are,
we can't compete against that.
The grand prize means nothing.
I don't even want it.
But I want to make sure
they don't get
their hands on it either.
I promised Eddie
that I will avenge him.
Mm-hm.
So let's assess our situation,
come up with a plan.
Do you have anything in
your bag we can use?
Oh.
I have two hand grenades.
You should take one.
Mm.
Hey, I got the scope.
I don't need it anymore.
Take it.
- [dramatic music]
- [raptor screeching]
- Move! Move!
- [raptor growling]
[raptors screeching]
- [Eric whimpers]
- Hey. Go!
[raptors screeching]
- [Vivian grunts]
- [punch thuds]
[raptor screeching]
[raptor hisses, screeching]
- [kick thuds]
- [Alex grunts]
- [punches thudding]
- [Alex grunting]
[raptor snarls]
[raptor screeches]
- [Eric grunts]
- [raptor screeching]
[Eric grunting]
[rock thuds]
[hologram buzzing]
[both panting]
Take it.
[device beeps, hums]
Something found them.
Maybe the dinos will
kill them for us.
We have to make sure.
They didn't last this long
with only luck.
- [device beeps, hums]
- All right, let's go.
- Mm-hm.
- Clock's ticking.
- [raptor screeches]
- [punches thudding]
[Alex sighs]
Not bad, you two.
Alex, there's one
more over there!
[raptor screeches, snarls]
[raptor screeching]
[Alex grunting]
- [log thuds]
- [hologram buzzing]
- [rifle fires]
- [Alex groans]
Go! This way!
[Eric panting]
[Alex groaning]
[suspenseful music]
[intense music]
[Alex grunts]
- [grenade rattles]
- [gasps] Grenade!
[gasps]
- [explosion booms]
- [both yelping]
[coughing]
- You okay?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
This guy doesn't give up.
Even with a bullet in him,
he nearly took us out.
Are you sure you can kill him?
Yeah.
With those wounds,
he won't be alive much longer.
[gentle music]
We made a good team.
You have to go. Just leave me.
But we haven't helped
you avenge Eddie.
The longer you stay here,
the more dangerous it becomes.
Live and fight on.
Run.
I swear, we're not gonna
let them win this game.
[Alex] Survive till the end,
and get rid of those
two bastards.
Now get going.
[Eric] Let's go.
Don't move!
He's still alive.
I'm sure I got him.
You're a lousy shot!
Your aim was off!
Then prove it!
Seriously?!
Didn't you see your friend?!
You want to end up like him?
You two won't stand
a chance against me.
Listen, how about you step out
and we can talk through
a solution to this?
[somber music]
[suspenseful music]
Is he dead?
One of the best players
I've ever seen.
What about the other two?
We still need to take them out.
- [notification chimes]
- [interface buzzing]
[volcano erupting]
[Peter groans]
There's not much time. Let's go.
- Get the jeep.
- Okay.
[both panting]
We can't stay here.
- It's too dangerous.
- [Tyrannosaurus rex growls]
[Tyrannosaurus rex chomps]
- [dramatic music]
[Eric screaming]
[both panting]
- Man the gun.
- Yeah.
Woo! [laughs]
[Peter grunts]
Let's get those two.
[engine rumbling]
- Yeah! [laughs]
- Yeah!
[Lily] Woo! [laughs]
[insects buzzing]
- Hey, Eric!
- [Eric gasps]
[Eason chuckles]
How's it going down there?
Are you kidding, dude?
You're actually still alive?
Yeah. Pterodactyl dropped me
in her nest and flew away.
I found some Easter eggs.
- Easter eggs?
- Yup.
- Come here.
- [Eric chuckles]
[thrilling music]
Let me show you.
See? There.
I can talk to dinosaurs.
[Eric] Get outta here.
[both chuckling]
Huh?
- Hey, do you hear that?
- [jeep rumbling]
Sounds like an engine.
Over there.
[jeep rumbling]
It's them. They've got
themselves a jeep.
Huh. Of course they did.
And it's got a machine gun.
Then we're as good as dead.
What do we do?
We can't take them on.
[triceratopses growling]
- Triceratopses.
- Huh?
Where?
They're like scale-covered
battering rams.
If only we can use 'em somehow.
I got this.
[Eason grunts]
[Eric sighs]
[Eric chuckles]
- Where are you going?
- [jeep rumbling]
[pterodactyl screeching]
[pterodactyls screeching]
What are you waiting for?!
Shoot!
- [Lily grunting]
- [machine gun firing]
- Yeah! [laughs]
- [pterodactyls screeching]
[machine gun firing]
- [pterodactyl screeching]
- [Lily gasps]
- Huh?
- [pterodactyl screeching]
- [Peter grunting]
- [tires screeching]
- [Lily grunting]
- [machine gun firing]
[pterodactyl screeches]
[machine gun firing]
[Lily grunts]
- [pterodactyl screeches]
- [machine gun firing]
Yeah!
[Tyrannosaurus rex roars]
You gotta be kidding me!
[Peter] Just keep shooting!
[Tyrannosaurus rex roars]
- [machine gun firing]
- [Lily grunting]
[bullets clanging]
- [Tyrannosaurus rex roars]
- [Lily grunting]
[Tyrannosaurus rex snarls]
[Lily grunting]
[Tyrannosaurus rex growling]
[Lily screams]
Huh?
No more ammo!
[Tyrannosaurus rex roars]
[Eason] A man and a woman in
a black jeep heading that way.
All right. Gonna talk to the
pterodactyl and T-rex now.
Thanks, guys.
[Eason chuckles]
Okay, they're gonna help us out.
[Eric chuckles]
You sure they got the message?
You doubt me?
[Eric laughs]
[Eason inhales, roars]
[triceratopses roaring]
- Come on!
- [Eric whimpering]
[upbeat music]
- [tires screeching]
- [Peter grunts]
- [crashing]
- [both groaning]
[tires screeching]
- [Lily screams]
- [Peter grunts]
- [jeep crashes]
- [Peter groaning]
Why are they chasing us?
[coughs, groans]
- [triceratops roars]
- [Peter] It's those two.
I'm sure of it.
[coughing]
[suspenseful music]
[Peter grunting]
[Peter sighs]
[coughing]
[dramatic music]
[triceratops roars]
[gasps]
[yelping]
[panting]
[Lily groans]
- [Lily grunts]
- [headset clatters]
- [ground rumbling]
- [both gasping]
[volcano erupting]
It's the volcano.
We should get to higher ground.
Yeah.
[timer beeping]
The game's nearly over.
Almost there.
Yeah.
[Eason sighing]
[dramatic music]
[Eason sighs]
[Eric sighing]
- [Peter grunting]
- [Eason groans]
- Hey!
- It's over!
- Wait.
- Come any closer, and he's dead!
I win!
- [Eason groans]
- Hey, easy. Easy.
- It's okay.
- Don't you move!
It's okay. It's okay.
- Not a muscle!
- Wait, wait, wait.
- Stay back...
- Forget about me.
...or I'll kill you too!
I swear it!
But I know how you can get
what you really want.
- It's not worth it.
- I know, it's not about the money.
You want to copy the code.
We found an Easter egg.
It's yours.
- What?
- If you let him go.
Don't do it.
Take me. I'll show you.
[music continues]
- [Peter grunting]
- [Eric groans]
Good game.
- Huh?
- Hey, man, Easter egg's right here.
It's a gift from Alex.
[explosion booms]
[fire crackling]
[Eason chuckles]
[sighs]
[timer beeping]
[timer beeping rapidly]
[people applauding]
[people chattering]
Congratulations. You win.
Eric, thank you.
[man]
Congratulations to Eason
for being
the last man standing,
and thanks to all
the chosen volunteers
for their exemplary
participation.
[Eason chuckling]
Thanks.
[man] 35 million viewers
watched your performances
and voted on which
player would receive
an additional five million.
They voted for the person
who most embodied
the virtues of selflessness
and good sportsmanship,
which was the true objective
of this competition.
And the vote went to Eric!
[Eric gasps]
- [man laughs]
- [Eric laughs]
Good job.
[Eason] Congrats, man.
[chuckles]
[man] We always believed
that games were about
more than points
and leaderboards.
You showed that
the determination
to stick to your principles is
more important than winning.
[elegant music]
[music continues]
Dinner's on me tonight!
[people cheering]
- Hey! Congratulations.
- [Eric] Good game, dude.
- Hey.
- Good game.
[man] Jeremy, Lily,
in response to hacking
our systems to secure entry
into the competition,
you are hereby banned from
all Mental Abyss games.
What?! [scoffs]
- This is all your fault.
- My fault?!
It was your idea to hack the
system in the first place! [grunts]
[man] Peter is also banned
from our games
for hacking the system.
Plus, his in-game
conduct was witnessed
by all his customers
and clients.
- [man] Congrats.
- [Eric] Good game.
[people chattering]
Come on.
[Eason chuckles]
[Eric chuckles]
- [Jeremy] Mm.
- See you later.
[Peter grunts]
[both chuckling]
Hey, I was thinking
we'd share the prize money,
but I guess there's no need now.
I mean, I won't say no
to more money.
- Oh, greedy!
- [laughs]
[Eason] In your dreams.
[both cheering]
Let's go!
[triumphant music]
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
[gentle music]
[thrilling music]