Force!  Here we go!
- Can you use that?
- Your father taught me that.
Ok, this way!
[woman] My dad always
wanted me to spend more
time with my mom but I
doubt he had that in mind.
[Nikki] Dear friends and new
readers, I'm Nikki and this is my blog.
After my father's recent death, I
was snatched away from my friends
and ended up in this horrible
situation that I cannot control.
Now, I'm 10,000 meters high,
on a direct flight to the Czech
Republic, a country I don't
know, forced to live with Eve
the woman who brought me into the world.
I know nothing about her
except for some news read online.
I will miss all of you and
our amazing adventures.
Horseback riding, walks, days at
the beach and everything in between.
I'm sure I'll have
tons of meaningless
adventures to share
with you on this blog.
Eve is a scientist.
Dad told me that since he was in
school he wanted to improve the world.
[tv] We are located in the Benesov
District, in the Czech Republic,
where citizens have relied
on hydroelectricity for 60 years
generated by the Ceb dam, but
now there is great news on the horizon.
It is called Helios.  We are in
the Promethean Kinetics lab
with Dr. Carter, known for
her commitment to development
of Third World Countries,
the Helios project.
We are far from the water
collection facilities in Africa.
Can you tell us a little about this adventure?
[Eve] I've always been interested in
new sources of sustainable energy.
My team and I have developed
Helios, a particular mixture of
gases extracted from the
surface layer of the earth's crust.
This combined with hydrogen allows
combustion without the emission of waste.
This happens at a depth
of 70 meters thanks to a
high-power conversion
turbine system we call Medulla.
Why the Czech Republic in particular?
Europe is full of abandoned coal
mines and we want to recycle them.
Our pipe network extends between
coal mines across the country.
Coal?
It is a new 100% safe substance
and it is pure energy produced by the planet.
It looks like the fracturing process that has
caused serious problems in the United States.
It is a new procedure,
completely different from fracturing.
We have achieved splendid results.
There are still those who say you are
exporting a toxic practice from America.
Promethean Kinetics or... PK.
It is not an American company.
Okay, but there is no documentation
on who is actually funding the project.
What I can tell you is that everyone
involved in the project only cares
about one thing, the health and
safety of the planet for all of us.
- Thank you, Dr. Carter.
- Imagine, thanks to you.
[pc] We continue with the debate between
Russia and the United States on oil in Ukraine.
- [Nikki] Who would you be?
- [man] Henrich.
My wife and I own the house
where your mother lives.  Here.
You and Eve were arrested on that
Greenpeace ship in Antarctica, right?
A long time ago!
So, are you sleeping with Eve?
Thing?  No, I'm married, I told you!
- Her name is Olivia.  Now, you will meet her.
- Agree.
[Nikki] As usual, Eve
has let me down again.
In the picture your mother
has, you look younger.
My mother?  I call her Eve.
You know, she was very sorry
she couldn't have come here today.
Let me guess.
Absurd times, time has
flown away, fire,
flames and all the rest.
Absurd times, I think.
[Henrich] This is a
new chapter in your life
Leave the past behind
and live in the moment.
[Nikki] Yes, right!
[Nikki] What could I expect from the
woman who abandoned my father and me
12 years ago.  Now, I am
stuck with her until I am 18.
[Henrich] We're almost there
and there's a surprise at home too.
- [Henrich] You will like it for sure.
- [Nikki] I doubt it.
It seems that Zeus and
Catherine like you a lot.
[Nikki] Perfect, an exciting new chapter
for my blog, Nikki and the chickens.
We have not met anyone
or anything for miles.
Who knows if Eve at least
remembers that I have diabetes!
I wish I could blame her.
But instead I inherited it from my father.
The doctor said
diabetes contributed
to the heart attack
that killed my father.
- Good!
- Thank you!
Good job!
- Did I go well?
- [woman] You were great!
How about?  Didn't I look too
much of an educated monkey?
You were sure of yourself,
with a little bit of caution.
Ok, thanks everyone, let's get
back to work.  So?  All in order?
- Negative.
- Thing?
It's best if you take a look here.
My God, I don't feel like activating the
system on Monday with these numbers.
- Me neighter.  Declan doesn't see it that way.
- Declan!  She always has other ideas.
- What is that?
- From me.
- Declan, won't it be celebrating soon?
- A couple of days.
- Maybe more than two.
- What are you talking about?
Tests still need to be done.
Just as long as these
tests say we can move on.
We will see, but in the
meantime that brings bad luck.
I'll put it in the cooler.
Rather, the consortium appreciated
your way of handling the press.
Good.  Don't you think it's time
to tell us who the investors are?
- I'll tell you.
- When?
At the right time.
On the Internet they are already shouting conspiracy.
You are in a difficult position, my dear.
Look, Europe trusts us
and we don't want to be
compared to a bunch of
Texan fracturing machines.
- Are you done?
- Yup.
- Well, you have some tests to do.
- Okay.
Pretend you don't care.  I don't want
to know where the money comes from.
- Law and sausages.
- Sausages?
You don't want to know where they come from.
Killian, could you take
a look at this for me?
Of course.
- Wait for me.
- Today is the big day, right?
- Today?
- Nikki.
Yes, Henrich picked
her up at the airport.
- Has Henrich gone?
- Yes, Henrich went.
I could not.  Ok?  I had the
interview and this afternoon is the test.
It's just a routine test.
I don't know what to
say to a 16 year old girl.
Try a little.
What did you do when you were 16?
I studied mathematics, equations,
I read chemistry magazines.
- Exciting.
- A party girl!
Go home to your daughter.
Okay, I'll go there when
we're done with the test.
Here we go!  Ok, come on, let's go!
Come on, come on, come on!
I admit, I'm excited to see her.
[Nikki] What is going on around here?
[Henrich] At the end of the street is
the bus stop that takes you to the city.
[Nikki] Good to know.
[Henrich] Eve will be home soon.
Welcome, Nikki.  I'm Olivia.
- Hello.
- Take a seat.
[Olivia] Come on!
The suitcase.
[Nikki] Who expected it!
No trace of Eve!
At least there are Zeus and Catherine.
[animal noises]
- Are you hungry?
- No thank you.
- All right.
- Stop fracturing.
Let's save the whales.
Nothing has changed.
- No at...
- Do you want to see your room?
- Yes, of course.
- This way.
Thank you.
Here we are.
Are we kidding?
Do you think I'm five?
I'll show you the house if you want.
We might as well see the rest.
Ok.  Follow me, I want
to show you your surprise.
[man] What's the matter, guys?
This thing has broken five
times in the past five months.
Relax, Killian is working on it.
In fact, Killian is working
on getting Dr. Carter to bed.
- Are you done there?
- Yes. Let's hope it holds up.
There are two of us, man.
Okay, let's check the resistance.
Killian, increase flow by 10%.
Automatic opening started.
- Pressure set at... 10%.
- Okay.
All right.
Let's bring it to 40.
Twenty, 30...
Forty.
[explosion]
[alarm]
- This was a very strong shock.
- Yeah, it must be the transformer.
- What is the pressure in Medulla?
- 42.6%.
- He's getting up.
- Yeah, ok, we need to decrease it.
Do you think it depends
on the control valves?
- It can be solved, right?
- Probably, but in Medulla the level was
to 42%.
We shouldn't be recording these results.
Okay, check both valves.
We don't continue if it doesn't resolve.
Sure, I'll go right down to take a look.
And you, go home.
Ok.
Wait a second.  A test was scheduled
for Monday.  How long will it take?
We need to check the
security of our systems.
Thing?  For a clogged valve?  If
we do that, we lose a lot of money.
Do you know there could be very
serious consequences, Declan?
Don't think like a capitalist.
This is not your
little science project.
It was probably your idea,
but it was bought and funded
by the people I represent.
Do you know, yes or no?
Yes, of course I know.
And they want it to work, right?
I want it ready and
they want it to work.
For this we have to
do other tests, Declan.
I'm in it too, just like you.
Replacing a sensor
is pretty simple.
So, let's get a move on
and activate the Helios.
No, we're not putting the
Helios into circulation now.
We will continue with the inert gases until
we ensure that all are working at their best.
- Only then can we use the Helios.
- You said it's easy to fix.
I didn't say it's easy.
Let me explain, Declan.
the Helios under pressure
is like a supercharged
flammable liquid and the
Medulla is what regulates
how much we pump
from coal mines.
I don't think you want to risk
the valley being destroyed.  I err?
In fact, we have a control
system and a backup system.
That may not work.  Let us work.
Agree.
Find the cause of the problem and fix it.
- Killian will.
- Killian does what you tell him to do.
Because Killian knows I'm right.
I don't want to make things difficult.
I have some personal matters to handle.
My daughter landed a little while ago.
I have to go home.
Look, that's how she went
today, so let's leave it alone.
Go to your daughter.
- Ok, sure?
- Come on, get out of here.
[cell phone rings]
Can we hurry?  I have an appointment.
- What does it say over there?
- 8.2.  Higher than usual, I don't like it.
We need to solve the problem first.
Goldman, recalibrate the system.
- It's Friday, let's go home.
- Not yet.
[answering machine] Hi, you
called my dad.  Leave a message.
Killian, this is Eve.  I know
you will probably still be
in Medulla but I'm a little
worried.  I don't know, wait.
Okay, there they are.  It's just that...
Do you know what?
It doesn't matter, I
have to go home
and leave work alone.
I'm free all weekend.
See you on Monday.  Hello.
[man] Stop worrying.
She activates that damned Medulla.
- Carter went home.
- Yup.
Is everything okay now?
It appears to have been a software problem.
It's all right.
- The sensors?  The redundancy systems?
- All in order.
Optimal.  So, I want to proceed
with the test and activate the Helios.
- As he said?
- You heard what I said.
Any problems?
But we wanted to do a series
of tests before activating it.
I'm not sure if the software
was the only problem.
And delay again?  Can you
explain it to the investors later?
- Declan!
- I want the system to be activated.
It's clear?  I've been clear?
Or do I have to fire you all
and go looking for a new team?
Proceed with activation.
[woman] Received.
[Killian] We take the commands of the Medulla.
Let's prepare the test.
Let's get to work and don't
think about what could go wrong.
[woman] We shouldn't
do this, he's not ready.
[Killian] Increase the flow to
maximum and release the Helios.
You come.
You will see, you will like it.
And... surprise!
Eve and Killian like to ride
horses up in the mountains.
Why don't you feed him?
So you will quickly become great friends.
- Here, like this.
- So cute!
Good good.  Keep it up.
- Your mother just started it.
-I didn't know you painted.
She looks like him.  A bit'.
I've done it at least 50 times.
You look good.
Me or the horse?
Both of them.
I was showing Nikki
around the house.
- Good.  Do you like your room?
- Not exactly.
You can furnish it as you wish.
I thank you.
- Have you eaten?  Sh
e-she was waiting for you.
Dad and I had dinner together on Fridays.
- Today is Friday, right?
- Yup.
- Loud.
- Here we go.
Let's eat and rest.
Tomorrow we will go to town.
- Good.
- I do.
- As you want.
- Go talk to Nikki.  I do.
No, no, that's fine.
-Where is she?
-In her room.
Has she been there the whole time?
She hasn't touched any food since you returned.
-She is punishing me, I know.
-She is scared.
- From what?
- [Olivia] From you.
- From me?  She doesn't make any sense.
- No?
A woman he does not know enters
his life and pretends to be a mother.
What does this mean?
Me, you and Henrich have
chosen to be activists also to make
a difference but some of us
have chosen not to have children.
Olivia, please!
It wasn't my choice.
Yes, but you decided it was
her father who raised her.
Now, you have to earn her trust
before she is truly her mother.
Thanks for the encouragement, indeed!
Do not mention it!
[Nikki] Hi, friends, check
out this compromising
video about PK and
Eve's latest discovery.
It is shown in detail...
- Man, Eve!  Can't you knock?
- I wanted to see what you were doing.
- I write on the blog.
- For real?  About what?
How bored I am here.  What do you want?
I just wanted...
Thing?
I wanted to tell you that I
am very sorry for your father.
It was a year ago.
I know but we've
seen so little since then.
I received your flowers.
I would have come to the
funeral, but my work stopped me.
That's what you wanted.
You know, I don't know what
your father told you, but...
- It really mattered to me.
- You have a strange way of showing it.
In any case, have you decided
to become a vegetarian?
Not me.  So, could I
have some meat for lunch?
- I did it because you're diabetic.
- Meat, Ive.  I need protein.
Ok.
[Henrich] Ive, there
are people for you.
I arrive.
It will take me a minute.
Don't make them wait.
Am I not entitled
to rest one day too?
The fact that my phone was
turned off could be a clue.
- Sorry, but we need your help.
- In what?
We activated it.
The Helios.
What the hell are you talking about?
Killian?
Perhaps, you have no
idea what risk you are taking.
Will you help us or not?
Help you?  I don't think it helped
when you made that stupid decision!
There are small changes in
pressure that alter the systems.
You have to check them.
He will never forgive me.
Who?
[pc] This new energy company
created by the Czech Republic.
This, ladies and gentlemen,
is a very great CIA conspiracy.
Nikki.
- Come on, go.
- It's about something...
Get out!
[Nikki] She doesn't want to
see me, I don't want to see her.
So, enough, I'm leaving.
[alarm]
I'm sorry you're locked up here.
I have come to greet you.
You don't look like you.
[man] The situation is getting worse.
The pressure on the relief
valve has increased by 49%.
- [Killian] I need to check this data.
- [Eve] Ok, I'm here with you.
- [man 1] What's going on?
- [man 2] Nothing good.
- It's 52%.
- It's all OK?
It is climbing faster than it should.
Fuel pumps are okay, but
pump more Helios than normal.
[alarm]
- Sensor went to number nine.
- Try to disable it.
The back pressure will
damage the whole system.
- That was a bad idea, Declan.
- I did what needed to be done.
- Do you know what happens if everything skips?
- Just a few bangs.  It's working.
- So, we can follow the procedure.
- Damn, Declan.
You don't know what you're saying at all.
Stop everything.
I proceed.
[explosion]
- Very low pressure in the system.
- It's the valve that re-establishes itself.
Do you know for sure, Declan?  Check it out.
[alarm and explosion]
- The system is broken.
- There is no answer from Medulla.
- The whole system is out of order.
- I load the backup systems.
- The rotors are gone.
- It wasn't supposed to happen.
Everyone shut up!
Everybody get out of here!
[Killian] Quick, quick!  Out!
[Killian] Run away, quick!
[shout]
My God!
Copper, Goldman,
Plint, Slater, get ready!
We have to reach Medulla.
We have to manually disable it.
[Copper] We can't go
there, it's too dangerous.
Are you deaf?  Move!  Here we go!
If I were you, I would start thinking
about how to limit the damage.
I think we have a problem.
Do not worry.
It is not at all prudent.
It'll be fine until it catches fire.
Then, nothing can help us.
Concentrate, we have less
than a minute to deactivate it.
[Killian] Check for any leaks.
I have a really bad feeling.
A Helios reflux
is filling the room.
- Twenty seconds, guys.
- This is bad.
- Fifteen seconds.  Slater, fast.
- Here is a leak.
No, don't touch it!
[shout]
Get out of here, get out of here!
Killian!  Killian, what's going on?
- There is a leak of Helios in Medulla.
- How much Helios pumped?
- A lot and still continues.
-He will go to all the tunnels under the city.
Congratulations!  You
just destroyed all our work!
And now?
If the fire reaches the mines, the
whole country will be destroyed.
The whole area will be
uninhabitable for at least 60 years.
[explosion]
Another explosion!
No, worse.
Where are you going now?  You can't leave.
You can't do this, stay here.
- We have to fix it now!
- It's your fault!
[alarm]
Red alert.  Everyone run for cover!
[Declan] Come on, go!
- Open the doors.
- Why don't they open them?
Relax, it will be fine.
The Medulla does not respond.
[Killian] We can't
contain the fire.
[Killian] Again, we can't contain it.
We have to get out of here.
- [Killian] Open the elevator doors!
- Carter is gone.
How do you mean?  He'll call her back now.
It does not matter.
I evacuated all personnel.
Listen, Declan.  Open the elevator
doors and we will find a solution.
No I will not do it.
Declan, what the hell are you saying?
Open the elevator!
I'm so sorry.
Declan, there are people down here.
Let us in.
[Killian] Declan!  We will die down here!
[Slater] Why doesn't he want to help us?
[Copper] To save his ass.
Okay, guys.  We have to take off
these suits.  They are full of Helios.
[Killian] If we're quick,
we'll get to the north shaft.
OK let's go.
[Killian] I hope Carter finds a way to
stop the Helios before he gets to Prague.
- [Goldman] What if he can't?
- [Copper] Game over.
[Eve] Killian, call me!  The Helios is
causing explosions.  How do we stop it?
[man] Declan, did you notice
they're evacuating the city?
There's a bit of confusion.
[man] Confusion?  This
time we got it really big.
Yes, there were some risks.
And now I'm seeing it for myself.
Nikki!
Thank goodness you are fine!
Nikki, are you okay?
We're fine, we're fine.  It looked
like a classic California 6.5 shock.
- [Henrich] You don't look good.
- [Olivia] What happened?
There's been an accident at the plant.  It's
almost sure, there will be another shock.
- We have to leave.
- [Henrich] Because of that idiot?
- There's no use arguing.
- Hell, Eve.  I told you.
They will use your
technology for evil purposes.
- Stop it, Henrich.
- Did your company cause all this?
- Isn't it time to talk about this?
- And when, then?
We get water, torches, matches.
Nikki, I want you to fill this bag.
Take her to the car.
Come on, let's hurry up, come on!
- Come on, Nikki.
- [Olivia] Nikki, go!
Go!
Come on, let's go!  Come on, let's go!  Quick!
[Henrich] We can't let it all
burn.  We must do something.
[Eve] Nikki, jump up!
[nitrites]
Horses!  I have to free the horses!
Nikki!
Do not close the door.  I free them immediately!
- Ok, ok.
- Okay.
I'm taking her out.  We hope he follows her.
- Force!
- Come on, beautiful!  On!
Come on then!  Run Run!
Run!
Good!  Let's go let's go!
Come on, let's go!
[Declan] Can you hear me?  Carter?
- They're calling you.
- Come on, let's go!
- [Olivia] They're looking for you.
- Who?
- [Declan] Can you hear me?
- Get in the car.
- So, did you join Nikki?
-She's fine.  In the car!  What do you want?
What are you going to do now?
I'm taking Nikki to safety and
then trying to fix your mess.
It is late, the fire has destroyed
everything, Medulla and the rest.
- Killian?
- Died.
Son of a bitch!  Why didn't you
listen to me?  I told you it wasn't ready!
- So, what are you going to do now?
- I don't know what I'm going to do either.
- Or rather, what will you say?
- I'll tell everyone the truth.
That you forced Killian to activate
the Helios when he wasn't ready yet!
Your word against mine.
In everything, you will be complicit.
Accomplice?  Is this how he is going to
end?  You know what?  And who cares!
It's your choice.
Let's move!
- Eve, you go.
- How?
- We stay.
- No, what do you say?
- Rightly so.
- It's not safe here.
This is the only place Olivia
and I consider our home.
It is not easy to leave it and
go around the world again.
But let's go!  We have done it so
many times.  We can do it again!
No, by staying here we can still
prevent the flames from knocking it down.
- We'll be fine, Eve.  Don't worry.
- No, please.
- Eve, let's go!
- Go!  You have Nikki and we have the house.
- Are you sure?
- Yes, of course!
- Listen to them!
- [Olivia] Go!
[explosion and coughing]
Christ!
Thank God there
is still some current.
It's madness to take us there.
We are not miners.
- Don't freak out, okay?
- It doesn't seem that strange to me.
I care about my life.
Did you see what happened to Plint?
I don't want to die.
There will be a way out, right?
There is, for sure.
- And now?  Game over?
- Okay, now stop it.
We have 12 hours
before the oxygen runs out.
We need to find the
emergency exit and get to safety.
[Copper] she's too far away.
Look, I don't promise you
anything, but I guarantee
that I'll do what I can to
get out of here whole.  Ok?
- Copper.
- Yes, OK.
Let's stick together and go this way.
Courage!
[Nikki] I'm sorry, but you can't
stop them from saving their home.
- They're important to me.
- I know it!
- How do you find horses?
- Thing?
Do you know Olivia and Henrich's horses?
Frao and Fraulina.
- I never understood those names.
- Are you serious?
I taught your father to ride.
- Everything is fine?
- They'll blame you for all this.
For sure, my boss Declan will.
Perhaps, he is right.
Do you really believe that?
I've seen you maybe
twice in the past two years.
- I know absolutely nothing about you.
- Check on the tablet if there are any news.
- [Copper] Do you think that's true?
- [Killian] What?
[Copper] That the CIA funded
Medulla knowing it would explode.
They try to bring troops to
Ukraine for oil-related issues.
- [Slater] It's ridiculous.
- [Copper] No, not at all.
- We got lost.
- Stop whining, Copper!  Force!
A large leak occurred
from the Helios chemical
plant causing multiple
underground fires.
Could this be the cause of
the ongoing earthquakes?
At these extreme temperatures
the Helios manages to burn
by literally digging uncontrollable
underground channels
just like the fault lines that
in contact cause earthquakes.
This NASA image shows us
how Helios burns underground.
As you can see, it is heading
towards Prague at a great speed.
The Helios fire must
be stopped or else
the city will be
destroyed in 12 hours.
and with it thousands of human lives.
- How long will it burn?
- It's hard to say.
We are trying to
contact Dr. Carter
who created this
substance but we cannot.
We have Declan Glas with us
who will tell us what happened.
My company
believed in Dr. Carter.
You have not only
betrayed our trust
but also that which
Europe placed in you.
This is a blow to
me as I considered
Dr. Carter a dear and
sincere friend of her.
Nikki, what are you doing?
- Nikki!  Nikki, don't do this!
- Let me out!
Ok.
Niki, stop!  What are you doing?
Get back in the car right away!
- I'm done with you.
- Where are you going?
- At home!
- Stop!  Is this your home!
Here?  Right in the middle
of your stupid experiment?
It was not my fault.
My science is safe.
Did you abandon me and dad for this?
When she said, "Your mother
is trying to save the world."
She kept repeating it to me before
she died.  She has always admired you.
Probably, she still loved you.
This is crap.
- I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
- You didn't do anything!
- I'm trying.
- I hope they blame you!
So you get what you deserve!
[explosion]
Let's get back in the car, let's go!
- Force!
- You hurt me!
Sit here next to me!  Enter!
Put on the belt.  Put it on!
- My God!
- What was it?
My God!
Get out of here!  Rapid!
- Open the door.  Open the door!
- I can not make it.
- Come on, get out!
- I can't open it!
- Go out!
- My God!
Damn!
[coughing]
- Henrich, Olivia!  What are you doing here?
- We could ask you the same question.
I do not believe.  I'm looking for Carter.
-He's gone.
- I want to help you.
Do not tell me?
I'm sure with all the problems
you have, you better leave.
But what is all this hostility?
-I just want to make up for the mess of him.
- Was it her?
- Yes why?  What did she tell you?
- What about?
Of the accident.
She said that if anything
someone had come here and
said it was her fault for
not believing a single word.
I had guessed.
I was starting to worry about her.
- Calm.
- Where I am?
You stay calm, in a reception camp.
Welcome...
You are not a doctor!
I am not a doctor.  Luckily,
I found her car in time.
- Where is my daughter?
- Let me guess.  Nikki?
-Yes.
-She's fine.
Her head was spinning a little, but she's fine.
-Where is she?  Take me to her.
-If she calms down, that's what I'll do.
My God, I'm the worst
mother in the world!
Calm down, okay?
I hope that one day she will be able to forgive me.
- My God!
-Why don't you help us by giving us a hand?
Sure, but I don't know what to do.
We haven't been
trained for this either.
- Luckily you're here.
- We lost two trucks
with medical supplies
and we are understaffed.
- Okay.  So what do I do?
- Look around.
These people are terrified.
Try to reassure them.
Captain, come quickly!
Excuse me.
Nikki!  Nikki, are you okay?
Treasure!
Thank God you are fine!
- Everything is OK?
- Yes. There are so many people.
Already.
Is full.
[Eve] And who are they?
[Nikki] I think
they lost their son.
I would like to do something to help them.
- Maybe, I could go talk to him.
- And say what?  What do you mind?
Nikki, what should I do?
I'm really sorry.
You know what?  You have to help
me with the next patient.  Here we go!
So, we need an alternate transport
since you destroyed the last one.
Ok.
Repair engines now?
Dad liked the idea that you
were an all-round engineer.
He tried it with me too.
- Did he succeed?
- In fact, no.
I'm more of a theoretical engineer.
You know, he was
super smart too, Eve.
I know it.  He was very smart.
This is also why I married him.
What do you need?
Give me the wrench.
What's wrong?  Where is the insulin?
I'm fine.  I just have to eat something or...
- Where's your kit?
- I do not know.
- This is serious.
- You shouldn't have had the accident.
I don't... listen, sit down and stay here.
I will be right back.
[Slater] We should be close by now.
- [Goldman] It's super tight below.
- [Killian] Okay, let's keep calm.
[Killian] Here we pass better.
[Goldman] I hope
Diane and her are okay.
[Slater] I'm sure so.
- [Copper] What's going on out there?
- [Slater] I don't know, okay?  Come on, walk!
[Killian] This way, come on!
[Killian] Yes, it looks like the right way!
[man] Close ranks!
Killian, it's me.
I used to come to you looking for answers,
but you... it doesn't matter.  Cabbage!
The dam!
We have five hours before
the Helios reaches Prague.
- Sorry, sorry, I have to see...
- Dr. Carter, what do you think you're doing?
I need to see a map.
Okay, so here we are.  The dam is here.
And if we open the gate like this,
the whole valley will be flooded.
- Female doctor!
- I need to speak to the field officer.
- It's about Nikki.
- Thing?
- Come with me.
- But.... is she okay?  What happened?
[Eve] Nikki!
Nikki, Nikki!  I am here.
- Pope?
-You are diabetic, right?
Yes, I can't find the insulin kit.
I gave her some fruit juice, but
it's not enough to get her back.
Captain, when you found us in
the car, did you see an insulin kit?
- No, no insulin.
- There is not here.
- See what I can do.
- We need some juice.
Look, I'm Captain Hill.  Bring
something sweet to the medical tent.  Now!
Look at me, stay with me.  Stay with me!
Do you know what?
Juice is not enough.  You need insulin.
Look, with all these evacuees,
we're running out of supplies.
- Here you are, sir.
- That's all?  Is that all that's left?
- Yes, that's all.
- Thank you.
- Come on.
- [Hill] Negative, corporal.
[Hill] We need to focus on the injured.  Let
the local forces think about the looting!
- You don't have insulin?
- Look, there's a town nearby.
- Okay?  We will check if there is a pharmacy.
- Can anyone go there?
It is not possible.
Another team will arrive in the morning.
In the morning?
It will be too late in the morning.
- You need insulin now.
- Female doctor...
- I'll go.
- How will he get there?
He will use the motorcycle.
- You'll make it?
- Yup.
- You know, I have a son Nikki's age.
- For real?  What's your name?
Tom.
Look, I have to be honest with you.
I don't think that's a good idea.
I have another plan.
Try to stop the fires.
Flood the valley with water from the dam.
Of course!  And the government?
Do you think he'll let him?
Look, the Helios will burn
for 100 years if we don't stop it.
Look, this goes...
this is way beyond my rank.
Look, if he wants advice, now
he has to think about her daughter.
I know it.
Her face is all over the news.
Remember the plant accident?
What they say?
Look...
You take this and be careful.
- I hate guns.
- Listen to me.
There are many people
who believe it was her.  Ok?
I risk court martial for this.
I want you to be back within the hour.
- I promise.  Thanks, captain.
- My name is Derek.
Good luck.  He will serve you.
- Need help?
- Captain, yes.
I am looking for a woman and her daughter.
I think they were here.
- The Americans?
- Yes, yes.  Can he tell me where I am?
They left the base.
[Goldman] Someone will be looking for us.
[Copper] Declan must
have said we're dead.
[radio frequency signals]
- Didn't you find anyone?
- None, there is no signal.
[Copper] Declan is crazy.
He interrogated prisoners in Vietnam.
- Wait.
- What... what's going on?
This...
this crossroads shouldn't be there.
- [Copper] We walked for hours.
- [Goldman] You mean we got lost?
Let me think.
[explosions]
We have to go, go!
Go! Go! Go!
Come on, come on, come on!  Street!
[Copper] My God!  We are trapped!
Come on, let's go!
- [woman] Over here!
- [man] Over here!
- I need insulin, Eve.
- I know it.  I'm looking for it, ok?
- Stay close to me.
- Because?
Why yes, okay?
Come on, come on, come on!
[sirens]
- Mom, I'm not feeling well at all.
- Don't worry, now we find some insulin.
- How did you lose the kit I had?
- It's not my fault.
It is never your fault.
It is your medicine.
Haven't you learned to look after yourself?
- Thing?
- Excuse me.  Sorry, let's go.
Now, we find a pharmacy.
Come on, let's go!
- Rapid!
- Do you think we'll be safe there?
Force!
- [man 1] It's about to explode!
- [man 2] Easy, easy!
[man 3] Away, away!
- Let's go in here.
- It's not a pharmacy.
- I know, I know, but that's all.  Force!
- I need a pharmacy!
[man 4] What are you doing here?
Go away, go away!
Move!
I do not feel well.
Over there.
- You take!  I have not found better.
- Thank you.
- [man 5] Guys, look there!
- [man 6] Hey, grandpa!
[gunshot]
[man 5] Go!
What was it?
[Declan] Carter!
Carter!
Listen to me.  I have to talk to you.
Who is?
[Declan] I want to help you, Carter.
What happens?
Okay, we have to leave.
Collect everything and follow me.
- Follow me.  Are you ready?
- Yup.
Here we go!
Down, down!
[coughing]
Come on come on!
There is no more time, no oxygen.
It's getting hot down here.
The fire is approaching.
- We ended up in the pan.
- Yup.
- Not in the pan, but on the stove.
- What are you talking about?
- Relax, everything will be fine.
- No, no, no.  What are you talking about?
I just think when we get out of here,
there will be other issues to be resolved.
- Declan wanted to kill us.
- Money pushes us to do bad things.
Yes, but what's stopping
him from finishing the job?
The truth, only the truth.
- We might not say anything to anyone.
- Hey, listen to everyone!
When we get out of here, we'll tell
everyone the truth and what Declan did.  Ok?
- Thing?
- Do you think lying will help you?
The best way to keep a secret is to
get rid of those who know it.  All right?
Ok, ok.
- Received.
- I'm with you.
Good.  Let's carry on and we'll get
out of here in a moment.  Here we go!
Quick, hurry up!
Here we go!
- Turn on.
- Where?
- Turn on!
Come on, get up!
- You can't drive!
- You're not capable either.  So, get in!
[Slater] They look like the
access stairs to the mine.
[Slater] We have to be close to
the surface.  Killian, try the radio.
[Slater] See if it works.
Carter!  Carter, can you hear me?
[Killian] Carter, try.
One two Three.  Carter, come in!
What you are doing?
- Killian?
- Carter!
- Do you receive me?
- Killian!
- Thank God, you're alive!
- Yes, we're fine.
We are at the old mine entrance.
We are looking for a way out.
Only at this point is there a signal.
Where are you?
[Eve] I'm going to the dam.
I know how to stop this!
- Fire?
- The seismic fire.
- Is that what they call it?
- We use the dam.
We can empty it all
and put out the fires.
[Eve] You have to get out of
there before I clear the water.
You will flood the valley
and wipe out the city.
No, listen.  The main
artery of the mine is
east of the lock and
leads to the river.  Right?
It is about 3,000
meters below the lock.
Exactly.  The temperature
there is very high due to the fires.
- Already.
And a huge discharge of
water can get to the river bed
and in this way it will flood
the mines, put out the fires
and will neutralize the Helios.
It is very risky.  If it doesn't get to the
river, the water will flood the entire city.
- You have a better idea.
- No.
- Okay, me neither.
- Listen to me well.  Stay away from Declan.
[Killian] He blocked us
below and tried to kill us.
Tell her to get us out.
-He just tried to shoot me.
- Stay away from him.  You heard me?
Yes. And you be careful.  Ok?  Get
out of the mine as fast as possible.
Received.
We hope well.
The dam!
Okay, guys.
- At least, we've made contact.
- Already.
Well, let's continue.
- So, you want to open a dam?
- Yup.
Nikki, what is it?
Next time tell me first, mom.
Mom.  I would say I like it.
Yes, but don't get used to it, Eve.
Here we go.
This is the access to the old mine.
Lead to the stairs.
We can get out of there!
Here we go!
Come on, move, everything will be fine!
It feels like being in hell.
It will be day very soon.
We need to refuel.
Going straight on that road,
we will arrive at the dam.
If you say so...
Ok, stop.
There is no current.  No petrol.
Let's go in.
Stop!
- All right.
- What do you want?
Just some food.
Gas.
OK Go.  Go!  Eat something.
Can you activate the distributor?
I don't know how to do it.
There is a counter.  I take a look.
- Did your father teach you that?
- Already.
Promethean Kinetics, a chemical
company implicated in the disaster,
has just released a statement.
She grieves over the lives she has lost
but she is not responsible for the
actions committed by Dr. Carter.
Evidence was found of her
involvement in the disaster.
- Do not move!
- No, wait!  That's not how it went.
- It was you!
- Look, don't do this.
[TV] We will give five million
euros to anyone who finds it.
I have five million
good reasons to do it.
- Mom, we have to leave now.
- Don't go anywhere.
[radio] To all units.
We're looking for Dr. Carter.  Caution.
She could be armed.  She
was last seen driving a sidecar.
- Throw it down!
- My God!
- Mom, what do you want to do?  Come on let's go!
- Put it down!
Come on, there's a five
million euro bounty on my head.
I am dangerous!  Put it down!
[shooting]
- What happens?
- Don't shoot!
We heard shots.
- What do you want to do?
- Steal the police car.
Hurray, mother of the year!
Dr. Carter ran away from the back.
[screech of tires]
- [Goldman] What is this noise?
- [Copper] But what do you care?
[Copper] she You die of heat.
I find it hard to breathe.
[Goldman] And what the hell is that?
Get back.
[Slater] My God!  It is more serious
than expected.  We have to go back.
[Killian] No, we can't.
[Killian] We don't have enough time.
[Killian] We have to jump.
It is the only way.
Great!
[Killian] We can do it!
I'm not sure what's going on,
but I think you'll go straight to jail.
- You believe?
- Yeah, sure.
She was here.
She fled when she heard you coming.
- Who?  Carter?
- Yes, it was her.  I recognized her on TV.
- Can I help you, sir?
- No, I'm just a curious citizen.
Ok.
- We can jump.
- Thing?
- It's just over two meters.
- [Killian] We can do it.
- Are you sure?
- Yes, OK.
Ok.
- Okay.
Not bad for an old man, huh?
Ok, quick.  One by one.
- Okay.
- [Killian] Goldman, you go.  Come on!
[radio] Unit 16, we are
heading to the north side of the
mountain to stop the fire and
look for the survivors.  Step.
Who would have thought that!
Dr. Eve Carter!
Scientist, activist...
Mom of the year!
[man] The TV is
all about, Declan.
You need to resolve
this situation immediately!
[Declan] I'm working
on it, don't worry.
- Come on, you can do it!
- Do you know in what subject I was a sucker?
- Gym!
- So?
He is older and he made it.
So, take courage!
[Copper] If he
made it, you can too.
- Are you going first?
- Slater!
See you on the other side, okay?
Good!
All right, are you there?
- Come on, Goldman!
- Here we go!
- Shall I hold your hand?
- What the fuck are you saying?  I can do it!
- Come on!
- You'll do it!
[explosion]
Let's go let's go!
No!
Help!  Help me!  I'm slipping!
Help me!  Hate!  Help me, please!
Don't leave me, please!
God, don't leave me!
Come on, we have to get out of here.
I'm sorry.  Ok?
We are shocked.
But we have to get out of here.  Agree?
Here we go.
There are still a few kilometers to go.
Look'.  Verdi maybe if someone follows us?
No, but I believe there is a helicopter.
[helicopter engine]
[Nikki] And I think he's following us.
[Eve] We need to get to the dam.
[TV] We tracked Dr. Carter
and her daughter aboard a
stolen police car.  Ms. Carter
is found guilty of causing
the explosions at PK
plants thus causing the
seismic fire that spreads
throughout the country.
We have Declan Glas,
the CEO of PK, online.
Declan, does he want to tell us what's going on?
[Declan] Eve Carter is a
very dangerous subject.
She is the only one to blame
for this disaster and I will
personally stop her before she
can cause more irreparable damage.
[Eve] I have to hurry.
Nikki, you stay here
until the police arrive.
We don't talk about it.
I want to come with you.  We are a team.
Ok.
Here we go!
[Eve] Be careful!
[Eve] Come on, run!
[Nikki] Mom, let's go!
[radio] Delta One,
Delta One, take note.
Dr. Carter and her
daughter entered the dam.
This is Delta One.
We are coming to the north entrance.
Received.
Delta Two, I'm entering from the south side.
Delta One, received.
- [man 1] Come on, let's move!
- [man 2] Come on, come on!
Okay, let's try to
find the control room.
Already.  I saw
four gates when we
entered and this is
probably one of the...
[shot]
Maybe, it's here.  Here we go!
The show begins, guys.
Arms out!
Go Go go!
Come on come on!
[tv] Soldiers are entering
the dam to capture Dr. Carter.
Meanwhile, forest fires
are ravaging the country.
The Helios from the PK incident continues
to burn threatening to destroy Prague.
US President Barack Obama
has sent numerous troops to aid the
Czech population, but the fire
continues to spread endlessly.
Hurry up!
- Can you use that?
- Your father taught me that.
They are shooting.  I
repeat, they are shooting!
Honey, over here!
I think the control
room is up there.
- OK let's go.
- Here we go.
- Are you OK?
- Yup.
- Are you sure?
- I'm fine.  Go Go!
We're almost there, we're almost there!
Come on, honey!
Ok.
Slater, you go ahead.
Then, Copper and finally me.
Ninth.  Not this time, Killian.
- I'm claustrophobic, I can't.
- We just have to cross.
No.
Wait a moment.  I see a light above
the tunnel.  Perhaps, there is the exit!
Stay down!
Wait for me there.
- You have to drain the pelvis.
- I have not understood.  What he wants?
You have to... empty the dam!
We are trying to prevent it.
Earthquakes are...
They are caused by underground
fires that need to be put out now!
- How did she get in?
- Do as I tell you!
- It will flood the whole valley.
- Not exactly.
If I release the water from the
dam, it will flow downstream into the
earth and thus put out the fires in
the mines.  We have to do it now!
- Madam, she's crazy.
- So, what do I do?
Madam, please.
Open that valve, activate the
power knob and lower the lever.
Ok.  You!  Go open the valve.  Go!
Come on, let's get moving!  Come on come on come on!
Do it, mom!
Carter!
- Do not move!
- You son of a bitch!
- Won't you shoot me?
- There will be a trial.
A mad army will not
be credible as a witness.
Yes, but you won't get away with it.
There will be Killian.
-He died.
- Are you really sure?
I swear I'll shoot her in the head now!
All the men in position now!
I'm going.  You, follow me.
- Declan, don't you dare!
- Now, I'll shoot her!
- Don't try!
- It's over, Eve!
Don't touch it, let it go!
- What are you waiting for, captain?
- Put the gun down!
- Now, Dr. Carter!
- I can not do that.  Listen to me!
- Come on, shoot her!
- No!
He knows what he is doing!
[explosion]
- Fuck!
- [Slater] It's all collapsing!
[alarm]
- No!
- Fire!
- Force!  You go!
- Go!
Don't lower that lever!
- Tell the truth about how it went.
- No, I'm not leaving you here!
Mom, are you okay?  Mom!
I beg you!
Tell... Carter I love her!
- It worked?
- I do not know.
[man] The water is putting out the fire!
Yup!
Let's get out of here, come on!  Take her out.
- I want to stay with her.
- I love you!
Me too!
[Nikki] This is the blog of truth.
I never really knew the woman
who brought me into the world.
She left when I was very small.
In all these years I have
looked for every reason to
hate her and I thought that
this was enough to know her.
- Mum mum!
- [Eve] Everything will be fine!
[Nikki] They wanted to give her 20 years in prison!
She will be fine!
[Nikki] I thought we could
never make up for lost time.
[Hill] Let's take it
all and go, guys.
[Nikki] But two technicians
survived the seismic
fire and told everyone
what really happened.
[Nikki] Thousands of people died,
but Eve managed to save just as many.
She is considered a heroine
in the Czech Republic.
Declan's death ended
the investigation.
Perhaps, we will never
find out why he did all this.
The country is moving forward and
being reborn, just like me and Eve.
FROM NIKI AND EVE HEALTHY CHOICE
Good evening, welcome to Nikki and Eve.
Have you booked for two?
- Yes.
- Follow me.
This is your table.
[Nikki] Eve has received
important job offers.
I get a ticket back to California.
But we, on the other hand,
have chosen to stay together.
We have faced a lot of things
in the last few months but
the reality is that we have
to make up for a lifetime.
- So, would you like to order?
- Turkey.
Turkey is good, but the
veggie stew is a blast.
Mom?
- Turkey be it!
- Okay.
What are you doing?
I write on the blog.  And what are you doing?
[Nikki] Now, we are a
family, just like Dad wanted.
I have learned to leave the past
behind and accept it for what it is.
She is my heroine.
She is my mom.
Dad, wherever you are, I know
you are watching us from up there.
We love you!