Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
♪♪
[siren wailing]
[fast tempo rock music playing]
[computer chiming]
[Rachel] I love you, Rick.
Get off me. [yells]
[busy signal]
[keyboard keys clacking]
[rapid electronic beeping]
♪♪
[computer beeping]
[man speaking Spanish]
[man whispering] Let's go.
- [keys clacking]
- [computer beeping]
[Rick on video] Don't worry
about falling. Here, go on.
Go on.
♪♪
[tropical music playing]
[discordant rock music playing]
[phone buzzing]
All right!
[Troy] Thank you, Grandpa.
[phone buzzing]
[knocking on door]
♪♪
[computer beeping]
Life's short,
brother. [sniffs]
Let's do this.
I asked for weight.
Oh, yeah, this isn't
cotton candy, brah.
It's Dance Fever.
Fentanyl.
Cut this shit
a hundred to one,
and they come back
begging for more.
No, no. Our deal
was for meth.
Papi, you can make
triple the money.
Fine.
Let's go.
[computer beeping]
No, goddammit!
Come on.
Reggie's
at Radio City tomorrow.
Front row tickets.
Heard you were a fan.
My gift.
You crazy, man.
Okay.
But I accept your gift.
♪♪
[Sapo] Not again.
[grunts]
[Sapo grunts]
[grunting]
[groaning]
[panting]
Shots fired, shots fired!
Send backup!
[Neyo] We're clear!
[panting]
♪♪
[speaking Spanish]
Take it, take it.
Take it, take it, take it.
[panting]
I'm not here
for your trash, Sal.
Where's my wife?
You touched her.
Ella... Ella está
con Manos de Rosas.
Don't move!
[grunting]
[Styles] Move, move,
get out, get out!
Go, go, go, go, go!
Get back inside!
NYPD!
Police.
I'm coming out!
- [Styles] Don't move.
- No, no, no, don't shoot.
Don't shoot, don't shoot.
- [Breslin] Where's the other shooter?
- What other shooter?
Hey, over here.
- [Breslin] Hey!
- [man grunts]
Jerk.
♪♪
[groans]
[grunting]
[panting]
[table crashing]
[groans]
[woman screams]
[grunts]
[panting]
Freeze!
♪♪
[car approaching]
[tires screeching]
[gunshot echoing]
You can drive if you like.
[tires screeching]
Fuck!
♪♪
- Bye.
- Give me the toy.
No, no, dinner time.
Come on.
Thank you, Frank.
[Frank] You let me know when
you have time to talk with Rick.
He should know the truth
about his wife.
[Jack] Yeah, I'll
have a talk with him.
He's still grieving.
Hardly been two weeks.
[Frank] Best we all
move on, Jack.
Here's the pepperoni.
Now we're getting serious.
Pepperoni one.
Pepperoni two.
Pepperoni three.
Pepperoni seven.
Pepperoni four.
Here, a couple of olives.
- Here.
- You need more pepperoni on there.
I know,
he stopped at four.
You keep this young
squire in line.
Here, sprinkle some
of this on there.
I was surprised
to see Frank.
I mean, there was
a raid this morning.
You know how he gets
when we lose product.
- Yeah.
- Troopers seized a lot of weight.
Uh... [stammers]
Here's...
Jack, I didn't get
no warning from Biggs.
[grill sizzling]
The ambitions
of a mediocre man?
He's making moves
and we had an arrangement.
Well, we can't have people
running around unsupervised.
- All right, I'll make some calls.
- Yeah.
Send another message.
Jack, I'm sorry to interrupt.
It's about Rick.
Hello.
Breslin.
[police radio chatter]
Your shrink called
this morning.
Suggested
a bereavement leave.
And what did you say?
I can't afford
to lose a good cop.
You're saying
I'm a good cop?
You're a work
in progress.
Put a Band-aid on it,
big guy?
Oh, yeah,
hearts and rainbows.
♪♪
Still warm?
Oh, always you,
always you.
- Thanks, Cap.
- Yeah.
[distant siren wailing]
Oye! I want a lawyer.
I have rights!
You'd have rights if you
were an American citizen.
No, no, no, bullshit.
[speaks Spanish]
This is bullshit!
[Breslin] Who is he?
♪♪
Why the fuck
you asking me for?
Don't you have
computers and shit?
Facial recognition?
Oh, it seems
this man's a ghost.
No fingerprints,
no records.
Those computers you're talking
about have found nothing.
Sal, when you go missing,
in Cuba is there anyone
that will even care?
Okay, caballito.
But I have to ask
you something.
Were those front row
tickets real?
Best seats in the house.
This is Rick Calloway.
He's a hacker.
One of the best.
That's the reason
he doesn't exist.
He would be a very big deal
for you guys to catch.
Young kid like you,
looking to make his mark?
He knows many,
many things.
All the way to the top.
Where is he?
I don't know.
No one really knows.
We cut a deal...
and I will tell you
where he's going.
[sizzling]
♪♪
- [dance music playing]
- [phone ringing]
[computer chiming]
Sorry, Dad, I'm busy.
♪♪
[bike rattling]
[Rick on video] Son,
are you okay?
[computer beeping]
[computer chiming]
[Shannon] So I just
took the test and...
[Breslin] We've got some news.
- You tell 'em.
- On three. One, two, three.
- [both] We're pregnant!
- [Breslin laughs]
Okay, I'm glad
you said we and not just me.
Is it weird when you say
we're pregnant?
- It's ours.
- 'Cause I'm the one who's pregnant.
[Breslin] We gotta
think of names ASAP.
[Shannon and Mike
continue chattering]
I'm so excited.
You're gonna be a dad.
[Breslin] It's gonna
be a boy, right?
I don't know.
I'm wearing pink,
- so maybe it's a sign.
- It is a sign.
[groaning, screaming]
[screaming]
No, no, no!
♪♪
[inaudible]
[body thuds]
♪♪
[mouse clicking]
- [group chattering]
- [group clapping]
[computer beeping]
Go ahead.
[Troy] Grandpa,
where's my dad?
[Jack] He's gonna be
here soon, I promise.
Now make a wish
and blow out the candles.
Make a wish.
Take a deep breath, make a wish.
Go on. Okay.
[Frank laughing]
- Yay!
- Yeah!
[group chattering]
[Sal] I saw his face.
The guy is fucking nuts, okay?
He killed my guys, and then
came asking about Rachel
with a gun to my head.
What the fuck, man?
I did what you asked.
You said, "He knew
what was going on."
[Travis] What did you
tell the police, Sal?
Nothing, I didn't
tell them nothing,
'cause they had... they saw
video of Rick shooting at me.
He's careless.
What the fuck, man?
I made bail and I expect
your help out of here.
I have to go.
I have to go to Mexico
or Colombia.
You owe me!
Relax, Sal, we'll take
care of it, all right?
[groans]
- [body thuds]
- [computer beeps]
Who else knows?
Frank.
Of course he does.
Fucking mess.
All right.
I'll call Frank,
and, uh...
you go get him
and bring him home.
[Travis] Yeah, yeah.
[phone beeping]
[line ringing]
[phone beeps]
[Frank] Hey, Jack?
Just left your house.
I am not too happy.
I just heard your son's
been shooting up our boys.
Thought you had
a handle on that.
He's my son,
I'll take care of this.
Yeah, well,
you better, Jack.
If I have to get involved,
it could get real messy.
[phone beeps]
[upbeat dance music playing]
Oh, I love these freaky
drug bitches.
What's up?
You wanna come to my club?
Come on, get in there.
Come here.
You looking for a
little bit of Molly?
- Maybe.
- A little bit of Tina?
- I got a table, VIP section.
Tell them
Manos de Rosas sent you.
Bunch of little
nasty bitches.
[speaking Spanish]
[dealer speaking Spanish]
No, no, no. [speaking Spanish]
Don't bullshit me, come on.
- [dealer in Spanish]
- No.
[computer whirring]
[sighs]
- [upbeat music playing]
- [brakes squealing]
Hey!
You wanna move this little
bullshit out the way, please?
Hey, would you...
Oh, shit, it's a bitch.
What's up?
- Oh, hey, baby. How you doing?
- What's up?
Your titty game
is all right.
Uh, your daddy can't come in,
though. We got enough men.
- Oh, that's fine.
- [groaning] Fuck!
[groans]
What the fuck?
Everyone move in!
- [grunting]
- [people screaming]
[groans]
Get the fuck out of here.
Where's my wife?
[laughs] I ain't telling you
a fucking thing.
Okay, okay, look.
Hey, look. All right, okay.
I was moving her,
all right?
I put her on a truck
to fucking Little Rock.
Some dude named
Diego wanted her.
Frank or John?
Come on, man. I told
you everything I know.
[police sirens approaching]
It's your last chance.
Diego, Diego!
Fuck, fuck.
Hello,
Detective Breslin.
Put the gun down, Rick.
Am I under arrest?
[gunshot echoes]
[door opens]
I asked you to come alone.
Yeah, why am I here?
I mean, you have, uh...
what is it, D?
Three lawyers.
And they all say,
you're not talking, so...
Yeah, lawyers.
Um, well, uh...
I know who murdered
Shannon, your wife.
Tell me their names.
We make a deal.
I'm being transferred
to Arkansas,
and a very powerful man has put a
half million dollar hit on my head.
Yeah, I really don't
feel sorry for you.
He's a cheap bastard.
My-my point is, keep me
alive during the transfer,
and I will not only
give you the-the keys
to said
"powerful man's" empire,
but, more importantly,
I will...
I will give you the names
of those who murdered your wife.
Three men...
and one woman
threw her over a balcony.
I'm sorry.
She-she was pregnant.
She was gonna have a boy.
- You're a sick fuck.
- I'm sorry.
Mike.
- Mike.
[door slams]
[Jack] All right,
burn it in here, man.
That was a good...
that was a good one.
Good fast ball.
Maybe I could
be a pitcher.
Why not?
Jack, he's here.
How about-how about a...
a second baseman?
Get in front of the ball.
That's a good play.
Here.
- Thank you.
- Play with Lily for a while?
He's getting good.
John.
Disappointed to see me?
No, not at all.
I'm always delighted
to see you.
You look like you
could use a drink.
- Would you like one?
- Please.
Let me get one for you.
How's your grandmother?
Oh, uh, she's, um...
about as well
as she can be.
She's a kind a woman.
Hmm. She's keeping
her sense of humor.
- Is she?
- Yeah.
Good.
It's good
to see you, kid. Salud.
[glasses clink]
- [John exhales]
- What's on your mind?
Um...
Three more drop houses in New
York were raided this morning.
Yeah, I know.
Frank believes
Rick is talking.
I got the best lawyers
in New York
- who assure me he is not.
- Yeah.
There's a lot of product
that was seized, Jack.
It's not... it's not
like a small deal.
- It's...
- Hey.
- It's, uh...
- I'm well aware of the problem.
Come on, spit it out.
I know it was Rick.
- You personally know?
- Yes.
- Rick has been sending...
- Hey, hey, hey, hold on a minute.
How do you know?
Rick has been sending
information to my father.
What kind of information?
Personal information,
Jack,
that my father has
no business knowing.
Hmm. I understand.
Okay, so it's Rick's...
sending Frank pictures
of you and your boyfriend.
I mean, that's a violation
of your personal sovereignty,
but how the fuck does that
mean he's talking to the Feds?
Because I value
our friendship,
- it's important that I come here...
- Hold that thought.
- ...to tell you your face... I have to.
I'll get you a refill.
That was the cheap stuff.
We can get
the good stuff here, okay?
Now...
What would be in it
for him?
I don't know.
I don't know,
but it's done.
♪♪
[chair squeaks]
[airplane engine roaring]
Detective Carter.
Our transport's this way.
I, um, I need to use
the-the restroom.
You got one minute,
little guy. Be quick.
First time in Little Rock?
- Oh, yeah.
- Yeah.
[Breslin groans]
- [alarm ringing]
- [groaning]
♪♪
[grunting]
[groaning]
[groans]
[grunting]
[DeSimone groaning]
[Travis groans]
♪♪
[alarm wailing]
- Are you okay?
- [Breslin groaning]
[coughing]
[Carter] Breslin.
This way.
♪♪
[alarm continues wailing]
[tires screeching]
[car engine revving]
Adam-4, code 8.
Black Sedan heading north east.
The getaway vehicle
you all reported
was a family of four
scared out of their wits.
All right, look, Rick Calloway is
a bit of a wanted man around here.
Hell, come tomorrow, I'll find him
strung up on a bridge somewhere,
and I'll call you
when I do.
Detective...
Go back to New York.
You're done here.
Thank you, Sheriff.
Hey.
Breslin.
A word?
Chief Taye Biggs,
Arkansas State Troopers.
I heard what happened
to your partner.
I assure you we're gonna
do everything we can
to find out what
the hell happened.
I'd like to stick
around to help.
All right. All right,
we can do that.
We already have some
history here with Carter,
so we're gonna let you act
as liaison with my office.
All right?
In the meantime,
why don't you go
get some shuteye,
and then we can talk?
And just so you know,
this is my jurisdiction.
Huh?
You got it.
[Carter]
Truck's over here.
♪♪
[Breslin]
You all right?
Yeah, I'm okay.
Thanks.
You?
Just lost
one of my best friends.
I'm not sure how I am.
So you're a sheriff?
Yes, sir.
You look like you just
got out of the academy.
Huh, I was thinking
the same thing about you.
Okay, yeah, all right,
I understand.
I'm actually, uh,
the first person in my family
to graduate college.
Arkansas State.
Got a degree
in criminal justice,
applied to Lonoke PD,
worked that
for a couple years,
and applied for sheriff.
You wanna know why Biggs
put you to spy on me?
Sure.
Diminished responsibility.
I have another theory.
What's that?
Well, you see, I have this,
like, special ability, right?
I can, um...
I can tolerate assholes.
- Oh.
- So.
Ouch.
Pretty sure that had
something to do with it.
Well, we'll see if
he's right or not.
[laughs] I guess we will.
♪♪
Uh...
So, when will I
see my, uh, father?
[phone ringing]
[speaking Spanish]
Oh, okay. [chuckles]
Yeah.
- Oh, I don't.
- Sí.
Thanks, I don't smoke.
Yeah, you really
shouldn't do that.
The tobacco corporations
are conglomerates
that cause mass death, see?
Yeah, see, I, uh...
I don't smoke tobacco,
but, uh, I do like mota.
- Uh. Okay, yeah.
- I like that. Yeah.
[chuckles]
Wow, you got pretty
good stuff, huh?
I guess that's part
of the cartel perk.
So, uh...
I'm gonna have
a bad high, huh?
Yeah.
I got you.
- [Jack] The whole thing is a clusterfuck.
- [Troy] That hurt!
- Well, you have your son involved.
- Uh-huh.
Biggs told NYPD
to stick around.
- Get Dodge over there.
- He is.
[Jack] All right.
- All right, and then get Frank on the phone.
- I'm on it.
- Come on, Papa, let's play.
- I gotta work for a while.
You go play with Lily, yeah?
When are my parents
coming to get me?
- Lily!
- Hey.
- Come on, baby.
- Frank.
He doesn't wanna
talk to you, Jack.
Tell them nothing moves
until we talk.
- You sure that's smart?
- Yep.
♪♪
[Connors] They're having the
body flown to Jersey tomorrow.
The family asked if you
would carry the flag.
I won't be back in time.
You need anything?
Styles and some gear.
Mike, make sure
whoever did this
knows not to fuck
with the NYPD.
[phone beeps]
♪♪
[grunting]
Morning.
[birds chirping]
Breakfast tacos?
Eggs and tortilla?
Yeah, sure.
Something like that.
[indistinct chatter]
Thank you.
You said "taco."
Yes, I did.
This is a burrito.
You know, I went
to New York once...
and, um,
when I asked for hot sauce,
they brought me ketchup.
What flavor?
Heinz 57.
Move over.
Move over, man.
- Hey.
- Hey, stop! Stop it!
What the...
Sit down, sit down.
Sit down.
George, Breslin, NYPD.
[scoffs]
NYPD?
I thought he'd be older,
or bigger, or somethin'.
What up,
little white boy?
You got some cars
to work on or something?
- You got some people to shoot for no reason?
- Okay.
- George is my CI.
- Hey, I'm no one's anything.
I do what I do
when I do to survive.
The perks
ain't bad neither.
What the fuck is this?
[Carter] What can you tell us
about Rick Calloway?
- Shit, I don't know nothing.
- George, I'm not playing.
Come on.
Frank Diego made a hit
on him for about 500 grand.
Word is, crews are lined up all down
the highway to take the fool down,
but somebody
got to him first.
- Who?
- Fuck if I know.
But everybody's still looking,
because the hit's still open
and the price has been upped.
How much?
One million dollars.
On one hit.
Let's pay his father
a visit.
- Jack Calloway?
- Yep.
No, we'd need Biggs
to approve that.
If Rick's not dead,
Jack has him.
[laughs] Oh, shit!
Little white boy talk
like he knows something, huh?
Listen, Frank Diego
make a hit,
even Jesus Christ
himself can't stop it.
Nah, brah, Pops sitting
home with his mouth shut,
waiting to identify
the body.
Now you shut
your goofy ass up.
Don't come by here no more.
You're gonna get me fucked up.
[Jack] Is that Simon,
your favorite right there?
Hey, don't-don't
use too much food.
Why not?
'Cause some creatures don't
know when to stop eating.
Do their bellies explode?
Jack, it's Frank.
Frank, Frank, Frank.
We lost another
location this morning.
That's five this week.
I know, I know, I heard.
It's not Rick.
Where's your son, Jack?
Who has him?
You tell me.
I mean, with a fucking half a
million dollar price on his head,
what the fuck did you expect
was gonna happen?
He's gonna run.
I'd expect somebody
to collect that money.
Now I'll bring him in, Frank,
and it's not Rick.
Let me handle my son,
please.
Nah, it's too late
for that, Jack.
Frank...
I'm asking you
as a friend, please.
[phone beeping]
♪♪
Hello, son.
Sit down.
Have a seat.
Manuel.
Dig in.
♪♪
So...
where's Rick?
Uh, I don't know.
No, no, no, hey!
What are you doing?
Dad?
Don't bullshit me, boy.
Dad, stop!
I don't care who
you're fucking, boy,
as long as it's not me.
Now get up and go find Rick.
♪♪
You go after him.
Make sure he does what I say.
[doorbell ringing]
- [Travis] Sorry, he's busy.
- [Biggs] Just a short visit, Paul.
- For my sake.
- Come back with a warrant.
[Jack] All right,
I'm not that busy.
- Hello, Biggs.
- Hey, Jack.
Listen, when your son
was taken,
one of NYPD was killed,
and they just...
they got a couple
of questions for you.
Okay.
Mr. Calloway,
I'm Detective Mike Breslin,
and, uh, we're looking
for your son Rick.
Yeah, well,
I haven't seen him,
uh, and he has been
home for years.
Oh.
Well, you know, if my son came
to town with a hit on his head,
I would wanna make
sure that he was safe.
Well, we had a falling out many
years ago and we don't talk.
What about his wife?
Where is she?
She left him, um...
so if you find her,
let us know.
[Breslin] So she's missing?
[Jack] No, we care about her.
[Breslin] Do you have
her contact info?
No, I don't.
And other than that...
I would say have a great day.
And if you wanna come back,
call the lawyers, yeah?
Thank you, Jack.
Rick's not here.
How do you know?
Oh, just a hunch.
Listen, I got something to do.
I'll see you back at the station.
- Yes, sir.
- All right.
[Breslin] That's a nice ride.
You know, I had one back in college.
How old are you again?
[chuckles] It was
a fixer-upper, Carter.
Okay.
♪♪
Isn't time I start searching for Rick?
Bring him home?
Jack.
Hey, I just got
the system booted.
Hi. Officer Carter.
She's good, Styles.
[scoffs] Excuse me.
You know, I had to pull off
some serious fucking favors
- to get this shit together.
- [computer beeping]
How the hell
did you get that?
[Styles] Ask Detective Nunya.
And there's Rick Calloway.
Wait, go back a bit.
[computer beeps]
Who is that?
That's Dodge.
Where I can find Dodge
on a Friday night?
Jimmy Doyle's.
I'll pick you up
in an hour, okay?
- Sure.
- Oh, and, uh, Breslin,
make sure you have your
dancing boots on, okay?
How long can we track them
after injection?
Two days,
then it dissipates.
Do you even own
cowboy boots?
No, Styles, I do not.
[country music playing]
♪ I know she's lying ♪
♪ I never know
the truth anymore ♪
♪ Yet she's pulling ♪
♪ She pulls all
the strings here ♪
♪ I've been calling her ♪
♪ I told her who I was ♪
♪ The night before ♪
What do you think?
It's, uh,
quite the place.
[laughs] It's good people.
So how long have you
lived in New York?
Born and raised.
Parents moved there
after Woodstock.
- In '94.
- Okay.
So they must be
the hippy-dippy type?
College professors.
- Really?
- Yeah.
So what led you
to become a cop, then?
Because they hated
the idea of it.
[laughing]
Holidays must be fun.
Oh, it's a good time.
[laughs] Fair enough.
You have
any brothers, sisters?
Lone wolf.
To the lone wolf, always
hunting and never full.
- [glasses clink]
- [cheers and applause]
- [groaning]
- [man yells]
[country music playing]
I love this song.
You wanna dance?
No.
- Breslin, come on.
- No, I'm good, I'll watch.
You can't keep this tough
guy act up forever. Come on.
Come with me.
Thank you.
♪ ...every time you ask ♪
♪ Even when in my mind ♪
♪ There was doubt ♪
♪ Would you forgive
and forget ♪
♪ Would you trust in me again ♪
♪ Oh, would you take me ♪
Shoulda put
your boots on, sir.
Hey, partner,
mind if I cut in?
Party of dos, Dodge.
What the fuck, Zo?
I'm just trying to exist.
You know, uh,
Zoe around here
has a little bit
of a reputation.
[whispering] Some say that
she likes it in the ass.
[grunts]
[hoedown playing]
[groaning]
[both grunting and groaning]
[groans]
[song tempo slows down]
Where'd he go?
Son of a bitch!
Are you working
or playing around?
Get your hands off me!
Hey, Mike.
Just here
by yourself, Biggs?
Oh, I'm never alone.
Get him out of here.
Come on.
What the hell was that?
It's a tracker.
Dodge doesn't have Rick.
Are you saying that
as a cop or an ex-wife?
Yeah, fuck you.
You can find
your own fucking ride.
- Really?
- Yeah, really.
[car engine starts]
Get in.
- [Breslin] You're scary.
- [Carter] Good.
♪♪
[man whimpering]
You gotta tell me
where Rick is.
Where is he?
- Where is he?
- [grunting]
Where is Rick?
I know you know.
Tell me where he is.
Just tell me where he is.
[man screaming]
Tell me where he is.
[screaming continues]
[crying]
Where is he?
Tell me where he is.
- Tell me where he is.
- [screaming]
♪♪
[insects chirping]
[water trickling]
♪♪
[phone beeping]
[line ringing]
[phone ringing]
[phone beeps]
Sí.
[Jack] Rick.
Well, hi, Dad.
Hey, you can't come
home now.
[birds chirping]
There's nothing more
I can do.
What about Troy?
I'll keep him safe.
Keep Troy safe?
Why do I not trust
that you can do that?
I'll keep him out of it.
Hmm.
Listen, there's
a car out front.
There's a passport
and some cash in the trunk.
Go.
[phone beeps]
♪♪
[groaning]
Jack won't be calling back.
I need to know something.
The photos that you
sent my father...
Where'd you get 'em?
Uh...
Where'd you get
the photos?
Rick.
Grindr, I don't know.
MySpace, uh, Twitter?
Get the bags.
- How many bags?
- Two.
No, um, ahem, three.
We're gonna keep
your head on ice, Rick.
And then my father's gonna
stuff your head with explosives.
And then we're gonna send it to
your son for his next birthday.
Boom.
Don't-don't you think
that's a little immature?
Fuck your dad. What do you care?
Yeah, you're gay.
You like guys,
who gives a fuck?
Fuck your dad.
Ha.
- Let's go.
- Grow up!
Well, okay, you got
us all out here.
You wanna tell me
what's going on?
Rick Calloway's been
sending me emails
with information
since his arrest.
This morning I received a list
of addresses here in Lonoke.
All right, I'll go fish.
Where do we start?
Here. If Rick's anywhere,
it's there.
It's closest
to the airport.
All right.
All right, y'all,
let's load up.
I'll ride with Will.
♪♪
My father likes to watch.
[phone beeping]
[line ringing]
[Dodge] Jack,
Frank called.
They found Rick.
I'm sorry, man.
It's over.
Please don't.
I swear, I-I don't...
[screaming]
[police radio chatter]
♪♪
[groaning]
[Biggs] Go, go, go!
[groans]
[grunts]
- You okay?
- Yeah.
♪♪
[grunts]
Holy shit!
That's a lot of dough.
Carter, we gotta go.
There's an emergency
at your mom's house.
♪♪
No, no, don't, don't.
[Rick groaning]
[groaning continues]
♪♪
[knife squelching]
Mom.
Are you okay?
- I'm okay, baby. Just look inside.
- Are you sure?
- Did they hurt you?
- No, I'm okay.
- Okay.
- I'm okay.
- You stay right here, okay? All right.
- Okay.
♪♪
[groaning]
[grunts]
[groans]
♪♪
[grunting]
[groaning]
♪♪
[siren wailing]
[police radio chatter]
It was Dodge.
[Carter] How do you know?
[Breslin] Styles has been
keeping an eye on him for me.
The reason why Biggs
assigned you to me
is because I'm expendable.
My famil is expendable.
You wanna find Rick,
get in.
[coughing]
♪♪
Where is my wife?
[Breslin on phone] Styles,
do you have a visual on Dodge?
- [computer trilling]
- Dodge is home.
Looks like
he's making lunch.
[Breslin] Keep an eye on him.
- Yes, sir.
- [phone beeps]
[groaning, panting]
♪♪
Fuck me.
[clattering]
♪♪
[engine turns over]
[rock music playing faintly]
[cocking gun]
[grunts, groans]
♪♪
[grunts]
[grunting]
[grunting and groaning]
[groans]
Motherfucker!
[grunts]
[groans]
[metal clangs]
[both grunting and groaning]
[Breslin grunts]
[groaning]
[gasping]
♪♪
- You okay?
- I can't breathe. [gasping]
I can't breathe.
Slow deep breaths.
Come on.
He's getting away.
Let's just stay calm.
Don't ever tell
a woman that.
- [gasping]
- [dispatcher] Adam 12.
Go for Adam 12.
[dispatcher] There's a 245
at the Broadway Inn.
Back up requested.
You're gonna need to drive.
[coughing]
First time?
♪♪
[Pedro] Frank!
Frank, there's something
you should see now.
[Frank] Remember, fishing
takes patience, boys.
♪♪
John sent the live feed of
Calloway, like you asked.
It cut out for a bit,
but when it came back...
[computer beeps]
[grunting]
[alarm tone]
- Get the car.
- Yes, sir.
[dispatcher] Uh,
can we get a car
at the northeast corner
of Main and Fifth? Over.
All cars in the area,
respond immediately.
[police radio chatter continues]
[phone ringing]
[beeping]
Jack, you there?
I found your car.
[sighs]
Bring it home.
All right.
[phone beeps]
[police radio chatter]
My father, he, um...
he wasn't a very good cop.
I found him one morning
washing blood off of his
hands that wasn't his.
He tried to explain but I...
I didn't wanna believe him.
You're a good man,
Breslin.
But if you don't leave,
this town will eat you alive.
That... that'd be all.
Thank you.
No, didn't see
a goddamn thing.
The-the cameras are off.
- Let me talk to 'em.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Now they're afraid.
These people killed cops.
What's to keep 'em from killing
a motel manager and his family?
Jesus!
And, oh! Now I ran the rest
of the houses on your list.
You got city council
members on there,
you got Sheriff Dodge.
Jack Calloway's on that
list, for God's sakes.
Mike, we know who the bad guys
are, all right?
And they-they-they know where my
grandkids go to school, all right?
They know
where my wife works.
where my mom is.
It's a give and take
down here, okay?
It's not an easy fix.
Now the only thing they saw
was a late model Mustang
driving away after the gunfire.
- Mike, that could be anybody!
- [engine starts]
[Biggs] Goddamn!
- Now I gotta go after him.
- [Carter] I'm going too.
[phone ringing]
- [phone beeps]
- Talk to me.
[Paul] They found Rick.
Dodge is bringing him
here now.
I confirmed
Jack was hiding him.
Then kill Jack Calloway.
I'll pay you double
whatever he's paying you.
But I want his son
for myself.
With pleasure.
[phone beeps]
♪♪
Come on, get up.
[groans]
- Hello, Rick.
- [groans]
You should have
taken my deal.
- Let's go.
- Ow.
[Carter on radio] Mike, you
need to think about this.
You have no backup and these
guys aren't afraid to fight.
- [radio beeps]
- [static]
♪♪
- [meat sizzling]
- Your mother used to sing to you,
every night when you were
a baby, with the cicadas,
while I was cooking dinner.
Dad...
Yeah.
Where is Troy?
Well, there's
a carnival in town.
He wanted to ride
the rollercoaster.
♪♪
[grunting, groaning]
Get my boy down!
Shh... Daddy...
Daddy's here.
Daddy's here,
don't move.
♪♪
Funny,
'cause, um, John...
told me about
Rachel, and I...
John told you about it?
- Oh, yeah.
- Yeah.
The whole story.
I know the truth now.
It's okay, boy.
It's gonna be all right.
- Help me pick him up.
- [whimpering]
I know the truth.
Come on, John
doesn't know shit.
Rachel made a deal
with the DEA.
Frank found out about it
and he had Dodge handle her.
That's what happened.
♪♪
It was you.
[grunts]
[groans]
- [exhaling sharply]
- [groaning]
♪♪
What are you doing?
Well, we don't have
a warrant.
I gotta make a few calls.
Carter!
Goddamn it!
[John groaning]
Get help!
Go get help!
Run, run, Dad.
Run, run, run,
please, run.
- [Frank] What-what's wrong?
- [whimpering]
Dad, run! Run, Dad!
I loved her.
You fucked up!
She was afraid of you!
[sighs]
Hello!
♪♪
[both grunting and groaning]
[grunting and groaning continue]
[grunting]
Freeze!
[groaning]
You kill me,
and they'll fry you.
♪♪
[car engine starts]
You feel it, right?
You feel when somebody
you love betrays you.
She was afraid
of you, bubba.
of you and me.
- That's the truth.
- You're...
kind of a dick.
Just don't lie
to my grandson.
[grunts]
Mike, stop.
What are you doing?
You gonna tell him, Zoe?
I'm sorry, Mike.
Zoe here, she'll do
anything for her family.
Isn't that right, Zoe?
Shoot him, Zoe.
Shoot him now, Zoe.
Do it.
Zoe.
Zoe, you better shoot him.
Whose side
are you on, Zoe?
Zoe!
You better shoot him now!
We blame this whole thing
on Dodge, yeah?
[thunder rumbling]
It's gonna rain.
Fuck.
[insects chirping]
What the fuck?! What...
[Rick grunting]
[Dodge whimpering]
Yo, Rick, I...
it wasn't my fault.
I didn't...
I didn't wanna do it.
Grief feels...
so much like fear.
Frank made me, man!
I-I didn't wanna do it!
I didn't, I swear!
I swear everything,
I tried to not do.
I-I tried to fight.
I'll-I will do anything.
Come on, man!
I'm saying please!
You know...
I'm not being sarcastic
when I tell you
that I...
I absolutely think
that this is gonna be
the best thing
that ever happened to you.
Yeah, just think of it
as a golden opportunity.
[heavy rock music playing]
Yeah.
No, no, come on, Rick!
Don't do this! [yelling]
Rick, come on, please!
Please, don't do this!
Please, Rick, please!
Rick, no!
[Dodge crying]
Come on, please!
Please, don't do this!
Please, Rick, please!
[thunder rumbling]
[joyous screaming]
[thunderclap]
- Troy?
- Dad!
♪♪
Rick!
I never wanna
see you again!
♪♪
Hey, buddy.
How are you?
Good.
- It's raining a lot, huh?
- Yeah.
- Do you want a full-time job?
- Absolutely.
'Cause I gotta...
I gotta tell you that I...
I pay
a pretty good rate.
Let's get out of here, huh?
♪♪
[phone ringing]
[Shannon on recording]
Are you gonna have a belly?
[Connors on phone]
We've had a hit.
I'm forwarding the location
to you now.
He's in Mexico City.
- [Shannon chattering on video]
- Yeah.
[Shannon] I'm so excited.
You're gonna be dad.
It's gonna be a boy, right?
♪♪
- So maybe it's a sign It's a girl.
- It is a sign.
I'm just kidding.
[continues indistinct]
- [Shannon cheering, laughing]
- [Breslin laughs]
- [Breslin] On three.
- [Shannon] One, two, three.
[Shannon and Mike]
We're pregnant!
♪♪
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull