Booster ignition and transfer to
the lead reflector is affirmative.
AP is now in the primary
position for complete control.
On my mark, go to 50-niner.
Stop 4-7-2-2-1
Roger, throttle up. Going
2-5-0-niner, stop, 4-7-2-2-1.
This is it, no more off shore drilling.
From now on clean renewable energy.
Nathan should be here.
Watch the temperature Simon
Throttle up.
Go for main engine start.
Roger that AP,
full main engine start.
You know I invited him to
witness this.
And he didn't want to come?
He said, uh, so many worlds. So much to
do. So little done. So many things to be.
He's quoting Tennyson.
Yeah well what can be more
important then this?
Balloons.
Sir, we're all clear.
Let's go for the infusion.
Keep an eye on the monitors
for a dip in the pressure.
We're all clear for infusion. Take
the level four. 5... 4... 3... 2... 1
We're a go for the main
reactor start.
By channeling the power of
nature, our main reactor is
About to change how the world
consumes energy.
Get the ground line in. Johnny
come on. Let's get loaded and go.
Come on get in.
What's happening?
The beam intensity is
Far greater than imagined.
We didn't expect this.
No, you nailed it! You'll be
on the next cover of Forbes!
No. Something doesn't feel right.
That's how it feels when you're
about to change history!
Boys.
Lewis. I want test results. Numbers
on my desk, 20 minutes Alright.
Then assemble the board because
we are taking this thing from
Prototype to actual energy source.
Simon, tell me the numbers
look good.
I don't know yet.
I'm sure they're fine. Listen
let's call in Senator Bain and
Why don't we call the president
because we are changing history here.
Verifying weather anomalies
in low-pressure altitudes.
Winds at 129 and climbing.
Why didn't we see that?
It just happened.
Whoa, what just happened?
Circular fluid motion of clouds.
Pressure is dropping 13 PSI
Increasing wind and 175.
Shit a cyclone is forming in
the gulf.
How big?
F5. Big. Find out if there are any vessels in
the area and get NOAA on the phone right now.
Copy.
We should think about shutting
down the reactor.
The reactor did not cause this.
Bad mapping caused this.
What's that suppose to mean?
It means that F5's don't magically appear,
okay? And they are not congered by what we did.
Look, it was poor planning on your part because
of the weather but we can still do this.
Okay, this reactor was built to
with stand anything. Anything.
Nathan was right.
We pushed the reactor too hard.
And you know it.
We're not shutting it down.
Damn.
The reactor is malfunctioning.
We've messed with Mother Nature..
Reporting swells of 70 feet.
Range approaching 200mph.
What population centers are
within a 400-mile radius?
Galveston.
What?
That's the direct path of the storm.
The storm is coming.
We gotta land.
It's that bad?
Hold on!
It's gonna be a hard landing.
Hold on tight.
Brace yourself.
Out! Out! Out! Go! Go!
Storms have gathered across
North America, believed to have
Been caused by the government
Apollo Station.
Casualties remain unknown at
this time
While storms continue to
spread throughout the states.
It is unclear at this time what this
storm is and how it will develop
Should conditions continue. This
is Ryan Johnson for Channel 3 News.
Get in the car!
Dad, what about the Balloon?
Forget the Balloon.
You okay?
Dad, what the hell is going on?
I don't know.
Storm. Came outta nowhere.
I've never seen hot air ballons
explode. I mean they exploded!
People exploded! They blew up.
Just calm down.
Go play your game or something.
Mom.
Johnny! Game!
Buckle up!
When we get home and get online.
Everything is gonna be fine.
Dr. Caprisi, we're getting
reading that are high and low
That are off the charts.
We can't shut this down.
What is our footprint?
1,000 square miles and growing.
How long before it hits land?
Days? Hours?
Minutes.
I'm shutting this down.
You don't know that's the problem.
No my chart says we ripped a hole in
the ozone. That rip keeps on going.
It won't stop until we stop.
Ox shut it down.
You touch that machine and you
won't even get a job at Best Buy.
Shut it down!
Oxford 5 7-642 beginning shut
down sequence of core on my mark.
4, 3, 2, 1. Mark.
My game's dead!
In the house.
I'll call my sister in Denver.
See what the weather is like there.
I'm going to check the news.
Good idea.
Dad the TV won't come on.
I've never seen anything like
that before. All those people.
Lights either. Honey the
electricity must be out.
I'm going to make some sandwiches.
I'll fire up the generator.
I'm not hungry.
You gotta eat something.
What do you thing happened to
him mom?
You think he ever made it?
Probably some of them.
I can't eat this it's stale.
The electricity has not been out
that long. Don't be ungrateful.
Come on, we have to go now!
What?
Come on! Come on!
Why?
Pack whatever you can,
as quick as you can. Let's go!
We need shelter.
Are you kidding me?
Just get what you can and get
in the car now!
Don't talk back to me.
Come on.
Nathan, where are we going?
The school.
There's a storm shelter there.
Dad, how far?
10 minutes.
What if the roads are blocked? What if we
can't get in? What if there is too many people?
What if you just focused on the present. What if
you just focus on what's right in front of you.
Nathan stop!
Dad, Drive faster!
We gotta get outta this city.
Look I don't know how fast this storm
is coming or what direction it's going.
You're gonna kill us.
Just everybody shut up!
I need to think.
Honey he's not gonna kill us. I know your
scared. You just gotta be quiet. Just shut up.
This is bad.
At this moment, what are believed to
be tornados or hurricane are causing
Massive distraction across
the state.
Look, I'm too old to be
reporting this kind of news.
Get me back in the studio please.
Conditions are getting worse. I've
never seen a storm this magnitude.
Oh god!
She just got hit!
We need to get to higher elevation.
We'll be outta the storm then.
We'll be fine.
This is so bad.
Dad, this is not good.
This is not good.
It's gonna be fine.
Dad! Look!
Hold on!
Is everybody okay?
I'm gonna throw up.
Dad. Dad what was that?
Can we go home now?
Go home? Did you not see the
trees and the cars coming at us.
We're gonna be safe here. Okay?
That was some pretty sick
driving dad.
I don't ever want to do that again.
Dad. Dad what was that?
We're not going to be safe
in this building.
Severe storms batter the
Southwest United States.
The government has issued a State Of
Emergency for the following states:
New Mexico, Texas and Arizona.
Evacuate lowland towns and
cities as soon as possible
And head for higher ground. Flood begin to
ravage the south as millions of people are still
Without power. An estimated
2,300 homes have been destroyed
as the storm continues to spread.
There's nothing left.
Nothing.
We're still here.
The storm was unpredicted and
the cause of it's existence is
Controversial among
meteorological experts.
Evacuation to s high elevation is strongly
advised by governmental officials.
Ssshh, I hear something.
Yeah, I heard it too.
What?
It's like a low rumble.
Yeah. Dad where's it coming from?
I'm not sure.
I'm trying to pin point it.
Where should we go?
I vote is to go home.
Yeah my vote's home.
Home. we need to go where the low pressure
held the bay, so higher elevation.
Oh, how about the animal preserve.
Is that high enough?
I don't know but we'll give
it a shot.
If we go home I can get on
the Internet...
Honey, there is no Internet!
Probably no home.
I can still here it.
I hear it too now.
Quick, the water's gaining on us!
You gotta drive faster dad.
I can see it, I can see it!
Hold on!
C'mon!
No honey go faster!
I'm going.
I'm going as fast as I can!
I think the water's past us.
Oh God.
Wait, the storm has stopped. I think we're
up above it. I think we're going to be okay.
We'll be fine.
I want to go home.
Johnny.
No. Why didn't he know about this? He's
suppose to know all of that science crap.
The weather.
It's unpredictable.
Not good enough!
How is your father suppose to
know Honey?
It doesn't even matter anymore. Everyone's
gone. My friends. My Teachers. My coach.
Everyone.
Johnny. Johnny quiet.
No. I'm not gonna shut up anymore.
I hear it too.
You hear what?
Get in the car. Slowly.
Okay. Alright, A little faster.
C'mon. Go go go go...
Its getting dark. Looks like
we're here for the night.
What are you working on?
The pressure was too low.
And the adiabatic cooling
must have been too great.
It's gonna get worse.
Much worse.
What like more tornados?
We should probably find
higher ground.
Umm, we leave the state, go North?
Quite a few big mountains.
Good ideas.
I can't believe you only
brought maps.
No documents or pictures.
And an emergency kit.
Let's see what you brought.
Oat bars? Almonds? Kale chips?
At least we are not gonna be
eating maps.
I was just grabbing things.
That's enough.
Okay. Let's go.
Can you fold that up for me?
Buckle up.
No, no, no! Again.
The particle accelerator isn't slowing
down. The storm system has it caught.
Some how in some kind of a feedback
loop. We can't shut it off.
We need to evacuate.
No, no, no.
We're not jumping ship.
Lewis.
We can't runaway from this.
Once the core melts, it's over.
There's nowhere to hide.
We won't survive the nuclear winter.
We have 32 hours before...
Thirty-two hours? No, no. The Apollo was
designed to feed off the earth's energy.
The magnetism natural friction tectonic
stress. The heat from their earth's core and
The storms intensity is causing a feedback
loop, the stronger the storms become
The stronger the Apollo becomes
the stronger the storms.
Both of them are acting as a cause and effectence.
But now it's like a saw blade spinning
Faster and faster. You can't grab it with
both hands. And hope, hope that you can squeeze
It and stop it. We have to find a way to
neutralize both of the causes so we can
Stop both if the effects.
No, no, no, no, no.
Make that just sixteen hours.
At this rate,
these readings are useless.
If that happens again, the core
could go critical at any moment.
I understand that Ox!
We have to evacuate, try to get off
the continent while there's still time.
Simon.
Nathan, thank god I got in touch
with you. Have you escaped the storms?
Yes, Mona, Johnny and I are heading
to Guadalupe Mountains right now.
Nathan! We have a complete core melt
down, and we can't shut down the reactor.
What? Slow down.
We're experiencing some weather
phenomenon. It's the Apollo Mission.
Simon, What are you talking about?
Nathan.
We are controlling the weather.
It's Impossible.
I'm not going to argue the validity of
this; I need to ask you some questions.
What?
Basic fundamentals of the... Flares used...
Models are adjusting and self-regulating.
Simon, I'm losing you!
Dammit Simon,
what did you do to my formula!
Shit! Try and get me the
location on that signal.
Yes Sir.
What's wrong?
I've isolated it.
Okay good. Let me know the
moment it comes through.
Yes Sir.
How much further to Guadalupe?
Not long.
Storms continue to pound the
East Coast. Tsunamis raze Houston.
The president has issued a State Of Emergency.
Be advised, gather all belongings and
find a safe place to take shelter.
Well dad, sounds like it's a good thing we
didn't move to Houston like you wanted to.
We'll be safe on top of the
mountain though, right?
That's right. Perfectly safe.
We just need to get to a high enough
elevation to avoid the tornados.
How do you know?
Once we reach the top of the mountain
there's no hurricane or tornado in all
of nature that could reach
high enough to touch us.
You know he'd know this if he'd
pay attention is science class.
Oh give me a break.
Mr. Latham hated me.
I'm sure he didn't hate you Honey.
You weren't there.
He had it out for me.
I wonder if he made it?
We'll be perfectly safe.
What happened here?
Why don't we go around them?
We've got to try and help.
I'm staying here.
Check over there.
Simon?
Nathan, thank god I got in touch with you.
I need you to get to the Apollo Station right now!
Are you crazy?
Look, I've been over the calculations
one hundred times, Alright?
I'm missing something, okay?
And If we don't get that core cooled,
the whole damn things going
to meltdown!
What are you talking about?
Simon? What did you do?
I used the Nihil Algorithm.
What?
I don't have time to justify
my actions right now.
You were right, I was wrong,
let's just leave it at that.
But I need you to get here now!
Leave it at that? Simon, do you
have any idea what you've done?
Nathan!
Nathan?
You okay?
You gotta teach me that.
Mom are you alright?
Oh god.
The storm is coming.
Get in the car!
What about the dog, Dad?
We're not taking that man's
dog with us!
How long until it gets here Nathan?
Not it, they. There's two!
Holy shit there's two of them.
Less then five minutes.
We've gotta get to the other side.
Dad you gotta drive faster!
I know! Hold on!
Honey!
I know! I know!
We're almost there!
We gotta get to the other side!
Hold on!
Nathan!
Hold on we're going in!
Everyone okay?
Two tornados. If-If the core melts,
the Fujiwhara Effect will kick in.
The Fuji what effect?
The Fujiwhara Effect is when
two hurricanes or tornados
get close enough to each
other to attract
and form one large hurricane
or tornado.
If the core melts, conditions would be
perfect for dozens of hurricanes to spring
across of North America, and they merge.
They would create a vortex the size of Texas.
The winds of excess of 500
miles per hour.
It's called Hypercane.
How long do we have?
I don't know.
It could be at any time.
We'll be safe on top of the
mountain, right?
From the Hypercane, maybe.
But not from nuclear fallout.
I know that model inside and out. I just,
I have to find a way to contact the power
station and I can talk to Simon. We can
figure this one out. I know I can do it Baby.
It's gonna be fine.
We've got get above these storms.
You two will be safe here.
I need you to stay with Johnny.
I know knew it.
I'm going into the city. It's only a
30 minute drive so I won't be gone long.
How can you be talking about
leaving us?
I gotta talk to Simon, Alright?
I think I can help him fix this.
If I don't try I don't know
what will happen.
Just call him! Just call him!
There's no signal! Alright!
I remember there's an airlift
station a few miles back.
I gotta get out of here.
Watch your mother.
Where you going dad?
I'll be right back!
Mom where is dad going?
C'mon. Let's take shelter in the
Ranger's Station until he gets back.
Johnny!
The accelerator has reached
maximum capacity.
Roger that.
How did we loose the signal again?
We are reconfiguring the
satellite communication
to compensate for storm interference.
But the rising levels of radiation may
mean we cannot re-establish the connection.
We have to destroy the Apollo Station.
That's your plan?
That's what you go for me?
It's the only way to stop the
core before it goes critical.
What are you gonna do? Are you
going to call in an air strike?
No, I'm going to redirect the
beam directly below us, okay?
Causing the ocean to swallow
us up.
You know I'd say that's the craziest thing
I've ever hear if it wasn't the dumbest thing
I've ever heard. It's impossible
to redirect the beam. Ok. Impossible.
Not if I reconfigure the reflector
dish by bypassing the safety systems.
Also impossible!
We better hope it's not.
Johnny! Let's go!
Johnny!
Where is everyone mom?
There should be rangers here, right?
Yeah, they probably went home
to be with their families.
Come on. Okay, thank god.
There you are!
C'mon guys, land!
Okay.
Finally!
Hey! Hey!
Unless you're a damn good swimmer,
you'd better come with me right now!
Yes Sir!
Come on then.
Get this information to command.
Yes Sir.
You're lucky we found you when
we did Dr. Sims.
How long till somebody can get
me to the Apollo Station?
As soon as we finish refueling.
What about this equipment?
Can I make a phone call to them?
Negative. All communication including
new satellite uplinks are down.
We got men working on the
cell towers now.
My god. This here...
This is the center of it all.
That's right.
These storm patterns,
they're all centralized.
It's like they are speeding up to some
visual form like some kind of magnet.
Of course! if you can get the Apollo Station
to redirect it's beams to these coordinates
We might be able to end all
of this.
Explain.
It's the heart of the storm system.
We gotta pierce it with a beam.
You want to shine a light up
into the sky. Whoop.. De.. Do.
By concentrating the beam to the center of the
storm, where the pressure is at it's greatest the
two forces will neutralize
each other.
Fighting fire with fire.
Exactly! The problem is that we
don't have anyway of getting
these coordinates to
the Apollo Station.
Sir, another major storm is starting
to form right on top of us.
It should be here in 5 minutes.
It looks like your timing is
a little off soldier.
We can't fly in this but we got
to get you those cell phone towers.
Let's move it out!
Jesus! We just lost Richardson.
Go, go, go!
Aaagh!
Hey, hey, hey!
Come on!
Aagh.
Come on! Come on! Come on!
Go, go!
Come on!
Did we already come this way?
No, that was another way.
How can you tell?
It all looks the same to me.
Who's wearing the bars private?
Now I need to get you to my
guys at the cell phone tower.
If I can get you there, you can
contact the Apollo Station directly.
Run!
Aaaaaaaaggghhh!
Admiral! Captain Wright!
This place is a wreck. It's going to
take weeks to put this back together.
Yeah, I wonder what its like
back down on the base.
You must be Simms.
Where's Captain Wright?
Before we can make nay calls, you boys
will have to climb that tower. Attach and
configure a transceiver to
the top.
I'd do it myself but I gotta stay
here and get the generators going.
When you get to the top call me and I'll
tell you how to configure the transceiver.
Roger that.
Paul will fix this. When they have the
coordinates hits the storm with his beam and
it will be all over.
Oh my god.
It's the park. It's on fire.
My family is there.
Go, Go! I can do this myself.
I can contact Apollo.
If you have any problems call me.
You got it. Go, go!
Mom did you hear that?
Dad.
Johnny! Mona!
Nathan.
Don't you ever do that again!
Good to see you Dad.
Come on, we gotta get outta here.
Wait? Leave? You said the safest
place would be on top of a mountain
and we are on top of a mountain.
There's a fire and it's coming.
We got to get outta here.
Hey! Hey!
Ah! Come on!
What now?
Wait, Wait, Wait. I have a plan.
We have to go back inside.
You guys get the phones;
I'll get the radio.
Lines are dead.
Dad, there's a helicopter.
Guys we gotta go now!
I know. I know.
Dad, there's a helicopter.
I know, I'm looking for the keys.
Uh, Dad!
Let's go.
I know where it is too.
There.
Come on.
Put on your seat belts.
Honey Go, Go!
Dad what are you doing?
Let's go!
Dad, that's supposed to start
it right?
I'm trying. Look I'm turning
on the fuel just a second!
Dad!
Come on. Come on.
Put your headsets on.
Here we go. Come on. Almost there.
Faster!
Hurry up!
Everybody doing okay?
500 mph winds will engulf
North America in 24 hours.
It will be uninhabitable and
we did this. I did this.
Simon. We've done all we can
it's time to go.
Where? Where are we gonna go?
Hey. Hey.
Hey, where the hell are you going?
Come, Hey!
Where the hell are you going?
They're going to die with
their families I guess.
What about you?
No.
Never got along with my family.
Might as well answer it.
Apollo Control.
This is Corporal Nicholas Gentile of
the United States National Guard calling
On behalf of Nathan Sims.
I'm looking for Dr. Simon.
Sims?
Yeah that's right! Listen, You
have to listen to me carefully.
He gave me specific instructions as to how to
stop this storm and shut down the core melt down.
You gotta follow my
directions exactly!
Yeah. Yeah. Okay I'm listening.
Change the trajectory of the
beam to these exact coordinates.
Okay I'm ready.
34.885931 by longitude 1 -104.02500
Ok -104.062500. I got it.
Hold on.
Ox, punch in these coordinates
to the targeting system.
Okay Sir.
If we survive this,
is there gonna be anything left?
Us.
Coordinates locked on and
ready, Simon.
Do it.
Whoa!
Simon, he's redirecting the beam.
Does... Does that mean he
fixed it? It's... It's fixed?
It's exactly what it means.
We did it. It's clearing up.
Good job guys.
Core temperature is almost back
to zero. You tell that lovely
son of a bitch Nathan
I owe him one.
Simon did it. He did it.
Yes!
It's fixed, yeah? Right?
Yeah.
Its over.
Shut down the beam.
Roger that.
Whoo!
Simon. Gage.
It's not shutting down.
Worse. The core is melting at
an accelerated rate.
This doesn't make any sense.
Why isn't this working?
Verify that we got the correct coordinates.
Pull up the satellite feed.
We still can't get accurate
satellite imagery.
Too much atmospheric interference.
So in other words we are
still flying blind.
Yeah but we are getting the
reading of a massive storm.
It's an F10.
The Hypercane.
Corporal, It didn't work!
Are you sure you are hitting the
exact coordinates I said to you?
Yes, but the reactor backfired
and kicked us into overdrive!
What is that Dad?
What's wrong?
Dad, that is that?
You said he fixed it.
I thought you said he fixed it.
He must have missed the center.
How could he have missed the center!
Oh my god!
Mom!
Honey!
That's it. We need to turn the beam
directly beneath us and distroy the base.
Send it crashing into the ocean.
Simon. What? What is it?
Damn! The pistons are fused!
I told you it wouldn't work!
It will work! Alright!
I just need to by pass the
main hydraulics.
Ox, Ox are you there?
Go ahead Simon.
Okay, let me know as soon as the
readings hit 180 degrees from frying.
Roger that.
135.
140.
It's working.
It's working Simon. Wait 145.
Come on, Come on, Speak to me.
Is it there yet?
No, no, no. It's at 160. It's leveling
out. Simon pull it back! The reading are
off the charts.
Hey Hold on, Hold on. Hold on!
Simon. Simon. You are going
too fast. Back off.
I think I got something.
I got, I got it, I got it.
Simon!
Simon come in! Simon!
The hell with it.
Simon! Ox come on! Simon!
Check his pulse.
No!
Come and get me!
Oh god!
What is it?
Hold on! We are going down!
Oh god!
Honey, Do something!
Nathan.
Is everyone okay?
So can you fix it?
The signal was delayed.
What signal?
At the military base they, ah the National
Guard they said the storm would be there in
5 minutes but it was even
less then 5 seconds.
I'm not following Dad.
It's the same reason why our
cell phones aren't working.
So what you're saying is the storm is
affecting out communication and that's why
they can't find the eye of
the storm.
Exactly.
Come on.
Hey Tudor!
Gotta ask you for another favor. Do you have a
GPS tracker I can use so I can send a signal to
the Apollo Station.
Yes.
But if you're trying to pin point your location
for Apollo you're gonna need 3 of them.
Triangulate your signal.
That's right.
Dad what for?
So that the Apollo Station
know exactly where I am.
Yeah, and why would they need
to know that?
Once they can verify the eye
they can stop the storm.
Nathan.
Honey it's my responsibility.
I get to the center of the Hypercane.
I send the signal out, the Apollo Station can
lock onto that signal and they
can send the beam directly there.
They won't miss this time!
And how do you plan on getting that
close? It's gonna tear you to pieces.
I'm gonna go under it.
Alright look, If you're gonna go under it you're
gonna need to have 1 person right here at
these exact coordinates. And somebody else
right here. At those exact coordinates.
Both as high up as possible.
Yeah.
And that means you two.
No, no, no.
That's my family alright!
You're gonna have to help me.
Your military.
No, I need to stay at my post.
What post?
Nathan, it's the only way.
We're in this together.
Whatever your gonna do you
better do it now.
Look, if the signal is off on their
location that's the end of you.
What did he just say?
Let's go!
Dad, what did he just say?
The hell with it.
It's working so that you know
where I'm at at all time.
Dad. Are you sure about this?
No.
Come back to us.
Johnny.
I know.
Mom. You too.
Any further word from Nathan?
Plan?
Just keep monitoring for a
signal all right?
Pray that he's still alive and
call out the correct coordinates.
Copy that.
Come on be at the right place.
Be at the right place.
This is it.
The position is off.
Nathan, why are you stopping?
This is not the center.
Nathan come on. Nathan!
Come on. Come on.
Still no signal. It's empty.
Oh god!
Ah.
Come on.
Come on!
I'm in the eye.
There!
Yeah! Whoo!
Yes! Whoo!
Simon?
Nathan! Nathan! It's Gage.
Simon is dead.
What?
The core is not shutting down.
We're too late.
What is it? What's wrong?
It needs to be shutting down.
It's too late! The core's gone critical.
We're in complete melt down.
Gage we got to take the helicopter.
Take our chances.
Where the hell do you think
we're gonna fly?
Listen, you know radiation
contamination is going to
saturate every form of the planet.
Nothing, not even cockroaches will survive.
Yeah I'm listening.
Gage, there's only one thing left to do.
I need you to turn the beam back on.
Fire it back up.
Roger that.
I need you to aim the beam underneath
the station full intensity and full power.
Can you do that?
Yeah I'll try it.
And I need you to get the
hell outta there.
That I can do.
Come on. Gage, Come on!
Let's go!
Okay! Okay!
Captain.
I need a lift.
So you just plan on shooting
it down? That's the big plan?
No, I had them turn the beam on
and aim it beneath the station.
So what's that gonna do?
We'll see.
So, how do I fire this thing?
I'm no pilot but I do know
this much.
You squeeze this trigger.
But first...
First... Wait for the on board
guidance system is locked on.
Now you only have one missile left.
You better hope it's enough.
Cause if not,
there is nothing left.
You want me to do it?
No!
That was awesome!
Whoo!
You might have made a good
soldier after all.