What is it?
Three grand, cash, in my wallet.
Where is it?
How should I know?
Come here!
Where is it?
Now you, come over here!
No!
Take my stuff!
You bit...
Get over here!
Come here!
No!
No wait, where you going, where you going?
Hey, whatever happened to
for richer or for poorer,
'til death do us part, huh?
Whatever happened to that, Katie, tell me.
What's mine is yours,
and what's yours is yours.
You can't keep gambling away
everything I work for, Reese.
Since when do you tell me
what I can and cannot do?
Where is the money?
I don't know.
- Where is it?
- I don't know.
It's in our bank account!
Huh?
What's wrong with
trying to save something?
Let me tell you something.
Don't you...
No, don't, please!
- Don't you ever...
- No!
Don't put that hand up, don't put it up!
Don't ever touch my money again.
I won't, I won't, I won't!
Hi, yeah, it's me.
Yeah, I checked it out.
Everything's gonna work fine.
Okay.
Hello.
Hey, Charlie.
It's Reese, how are you doing?
Fine, Reese, what's up?
Where you been?
Katie said you've been
gone a couple of days.
Yeah, I've been busy,
been doing a couple of
little business deals.
Listen, Charlie, we still
going hunting tomorrow?
Oh sure, if you want to.
Oh yeah, I do, I'm
looking forward to it.
All right, look.
Be at the ranch around eight,
we'll get an early start.
All right, I'll see you then.
Oh, oh.
You okay?
I'm fine.
That's not what I meant.
I know what you meant.
I'll be okay.
It's gonna be different,
Katie, I promise.
That's the last time.
There's no reason for
me to do that to you,
and I know that, so it stops, as of now.
I didn't mean to hurt you.
I just, you know,
sometimes my temper gets away from me.
I didn't mean to hurt you, I swear it.
I know.
Tell me you understand.
I understand.
Please, Katie.
I've understood every time it's happened.
Charlie, you don't have to do this
if you don't want to, you know?
Oh no, no, that's okay.
The season's winding to a close anyway.
When Reese asked me to take him hunting,
it gave me an excuse to go.
Probably hit you up for money again.
Yeah, yeah well, he usually does.
Oh, the market's up, it's okay.
Hey Dad!
- Mom!
- Hey ya, Tiger!
Guess what?
- Guess what?
- What?
I'm gonna go to the
nursery with Aunt Kate
and help plant trees and things.
Oh yeah?
Well, don't you think
you'd better ask her first
to see if it's okay, huh?
- Grandma said it was.
- I did.
I didn't think she'd mind.
Well you ask her anyway,
she'll be here any minute, okay?
Okay.
Wait a minute, wait a
minute, wait a minute.
Let's go over things.
I wanna make sure you know what to do.
Hey, I'm counting on you, Kate.
You've gotta act the part.
You can do it.
I know you can do it.
How am I gonna know you're okay?
Just watch the mail.
There's gonna be a
postcard with nothing on it
but a return post office
box number and a date.
That way you'll know I'm hiding,
and I'll send it as soon
as I think it's safe.
Come here.
I know you can.
I believe in you.
Okay.
- Okay.
- All right.
Let's go, come on.
You're okay, go, go.
Say!
Hiya, Reese.
Honey, what happened?
Nothing, it was a
branch, it was a branch.
Hi!
Bastard hit you again.
Don't say anything, don't spoil the day.
Hey, big fella!
Maybe we ought to take
you hunting with us.
You'd like that, wouldn't you, big fella?
I can't, I'm not old enough to hunt.
Good to see you, counselor.
Well maybe your Uncle
Reese ought to teach you.
How'd that be?
Ginny, that be all right?
Maybe some other time, Reese.
Joey, go get your stuff,
I'm gonna take you to the nursery.
Yeah, come on, Joey, let's go.
Hey Charlie,
hey, you think you're spending
enough time with the kid?
Sort of seems to me like he's
kinda missing a father figure.
What did you say?
Reese!
Oh, I was just
expressing an opinion, that's all.
I'll see you later, babe.
Okay, be careful.
Hey, not to worry!
There's extra ammo in
the saddlebags, gentlemen,
and water in the canteens.
Good man, Kenny.
Weather Channel's got high
winds on the bluffs later today
so be extra careful up there.
What a couple of old ladies.
Reese, Dokie gets spooked in high wind,
so be extra gentle with him up there.
Make sure and identify your target.
There's a lot of hunters out today.
Got it, I got it, let's ride.
Let me take a look at that eye again.
I'm fine.
Then why are you so nervous?
I'm not nervous!
You've got to do something about him.
You can't go on like this.
- Do what?
- Leave him!
Divorce him!
Get a restraining order
to keep him away from you!
I don't want a divorce!
I don't want your help, okay?
You've hated the idea of
me and Reese being together
from the very beginning.
You don't even like to see it, Ginny!
He is really going to
hurt you one of these day,
do you understand that?
It's not your business.
Not any more.
This is none of your
business either, Kenny.
Yes, ma'am.
Kenny, I'm going into
town, I have some work to do.
Yes, ma'am.
Come on, baby, come on!
Agh!
Damn!
I almost had that one.
You okay?
You seem a little uptight.
Yeah, Kate and me had a
little argument, that's all.
Yeah, I noticed.
What the hell is that?
First your wife, now you?
This is between Kate and me.
Oh, you're never gonna
convince Ginny of that.
I don't have to.
I'll tell you something else.
It's none of her business.
It's none of yours either.
Look, Reese, regardless of
what you think of my wife...
I think she's a nosy bitch.
I think she's jealous of her sister.
You just don't know when
to quit, do you, Reese?
Are you gonna teach me
when to quit, Charlie?
Yeah, yeah, I'm gonna teach you
a little bit more than hunting.
How about right now?
I'm ready to learn, come on, come on.
You need counseling, buddy.
I'll tell you something, man.
I'm not the one that needs the counseling.
And I don't need you or your wife
to teach me how to treat Kate.
Hey!
Slow down!
Still no sign of a body?
So this is where you think he went off?
I don't know the exact
spot where he went over,
I didn't see that.
I saw him floating down
by the rocks, I saw him...
You don't know whether he was alive?
He was floating facedown.
Ginny!
Ginny, what happened?
Tell me he's okay,
please tell me he's okay!
Baby, I'm sorry, I'm so sorry!
Oh my God!
Mrs. Williams, I'm sorry,
the divers are gonna keep at it
until it gets dark and tomorrow.
Listen, there is always a chance.
If they don't find a body,
there is always a chance!
Oh my God!
You and Mr. Williams came up here
to go hunting this
morning, is that correct?
I've got a license.
It's okay.
Did you hunt with Mr. Williams often?
No, no, this was his first time.
He called and said he wanted to learn.
So this was all his idea?
Yeah, yeah, he called,
said he'd been thinking
about taking up the sport,
wanted to give it a try, you know.
So I lined it up for today.
So if he was all new with this,
what was he doing riding on ahead of you?
We'd had a little disagreement.
He got angry and rode
off, I took off after him.
By the time I reached the spot, he...
Wanna tell me what
the argument was about?
I was offering some
brotherly advice, that's all.
He didn't wanna hear it.
Sergeant, my sister and her husband had
an argument last night.
It was nothing unusual,
nothing out of the ordinary.
Couples have arguments all the time.
Do you mind if I take my sister home?
Okay.
I'll call you if the situation changes.
Thank you.
Can I help you with something, sir?
What are you doing with that?
Cleaning it.
Why that one, it wasn't used.
Needed oiling.
Has it been fired recently?
No way to tell for sure.
Why don't you leave those two with me
and I'll clean them up as well.
Yes, yes, of course.
Something wrong, sir?
Well, there are going
to be a lot of questions,
an investigation, I just
don't want any loose ends.
Thought Mr. Williams fell?
He did.
What do the rifles
have to do with anything?
Mrs. Halloran may have
taken some ammunition
for target practice.
She didn't, I'd have known.
Hey Kate, what a surprise.
Hi, Ginny, Alice.
Hi, Kate.
I hope I'm not interrupting
anything important.
No, sit, we're just having coffee.
I wanted to talk to
you about a legal matter.
I can go back to the
office, no big deal.
No, I'd just as soon
you stay and take notes.
If it's a legal matter,
then we wanna make sure that
everything's done properly.
What's up, Kate?
Can I get you anything, ma'am?
Oh, coffee please.
I'll be right back.
This is a huge policy, I had no idea.
Reese took it out a couple of years ago
after he won big in Vegas.
He was in one of those
let's-take-care-of-Katie moods.
You'd need an official
determination of death
for the insurance company
to pay off on this.
I was hoping that you
would know what to do.
Well, I can orchestrate the procedures
and do all the paperwork, but
I can't guarantee the outcome.
Oh, I know that.
There'll be a full
investigation as to what happened.
Of course.
Um, do you know how long that takes?
Hard to say.
I'll move things along as fast as I can,
but only after there's
been a private hearing,
and everyone is satisfied
with the results,
will a judge issue a
determination of death ruling.
And then the insurance company will pay?
After the ruling, the
insurance company has no choice.
What do you think?
There's no body, but we
have a witness in Charlie,
who saw the body floating in the water.
Look, I'll do whatever I can, Kate.
Let me keep this,
and as soon as I get back to the office,
I'll take care of it.
Let's start a file.
We'll do a letter to Solar
State Life this afternoon,
requesting the process begin, okay?
I'll get right on it.
Thanks, Ginny.
Hey Kate, someone wants to see you.
Come on, I'll give you a ride.
Thanks.
You know, you haven't stopped
working for three hours.
There'll be nothing left
for the rest of us to do.
It just seems that the harder I work,
the less I think about things.
Yeah, I know it's been tough,
all the waiting, not knowing.
I keep expecting him to drive up.
I keep thinking that somehow
this is all a mistake.
He's gonna show up here
and pick me up at the end of the day.
Yeah, well work is
a tonic, but you know,
there's no use killing
yourself with it, is there?
I mean, no matter what
happens, you gotta keep going.
- Thanks, Martha.
- Sure, see you later.
Can I help you gentlemen?
Katherine Williams?
Investigators McCaffey and
Logan, with Solar State Life.
We're here about your husband's policy.
We're sorry about your
loss, Mrs. Williams.
Thank you.
Did you know about your
husband's policy, Kate?
Do you mind if I call you Kate?
Yes, I knew about the policy,
and no, I don't mind if you call me Kate.
Okay.
Reese told me about the
policy when he took it out.
Five million, that's a lot of money.
Especially for someone whose
income was less than steady.
Do you know how your
husband was able to afford
such a policy?
He bought it at a time
that he had a lot of cash,
and he prepaid the premiums.
Do you know where he got
the money to buy the policy?
I didn't ask him that.
Well, maybe it was after
a winning streak in Vegas?
Well, I guess you guys have found
a few things out already.
Well, it's not uncommon for someone
with a history of gambling
to take out a big policy.
I mean, sometimes they
feel that's insurance
against a losing streak.
His habits were well-documented
among the various casinos down there.
I see.
Were you aware that
he'd lost quite a bit
in the last few months?
I didn't keep tabs on it, no.
I'm afraid that it's true,
I mean he was deeply in debt.
I think it's even safe to say
that he might've been desperate for money.
What exactly are the
two of you trying to say?
It wouldn't be the first time
that someone tried to
stage their own death
to collect insurance money.
My brother-in-law saw Reese floating
facedown in the water.
We're not trying to imply anything,
or insult your husband's memory.
We have a job to do,
we're trying to do it.
Then do whatever you have to do,
but my husband is dead, and
work is about the only thing
that keeps me going these days,
so if you will excuse me, gentlemen.
Uh, Kate?
We might have to talk to you
again, would that be all right?
Of course.
We might have to talk to you again,
would that be all right?
When did you get so polite?
What are you talking about?
Back there?
Don't even say it!
I can read what's going on in
that little pea-brain of yours
like it was a neon sign
flashing on the Vegas strip.
Oh, is that so?
Yeah, that she's a good-looking babe,
that she makes the last date you had look
like a Boston terrier.
Boston terrier.
Oh, and
wouldn't it be a darn shame
if she was up to her neck
in something crooked?
And that's what I'm thinking, eh?
Oh, when you get to be
doing this long as I have,
young Master Logan, you
get to reading the signs.
Mmm.
You treat your girlfriends
as good as you do this car?
Well, you know, you take care of her,
she takes care of you.
Perfect relationship.
No wonder you don't have a girlfriend.
You know what I am thinking?
Huh?
You're full of it.
Ah, the swami knew that too.
- Hey Mom?
- What?
Can I be done?
I wanna watch TV.
Okay, half an hour,
and then you do your homework, all right?
All right.
Hey Grandma, do you
wanna watch that new show
I was telling you about?
Oh, yeah, I'll catch up with you, okay?
I'd like to propose a toast.
To Katie.
Katie, you are in our hearts
and we pray for you every day.
May your world be one
of happiness and love,
from sunrise to sunrise, forever.
- Hear, hear!
- Cheers.
Better times ahead.
Thanks, Mom.
Two investigators from Solar
State Life Insurance came
to see me at the nursery today.
- How did it go?
- Okay.
Reese sure had a lot of
people fooled, didn't he?
Fooled how?
Well, a $5 million
life insurance policy?
Sure fooled me.
Kate, I hope you don't mind,
I told Charlie about the policy.
He bought it on a whim,
when he was flush with gambling money.
Oh yeah, but he could've
canceled that contract
at any time, assuming of
course that he remembered
that he had one, but I
don't see a guy like Reese
forgetting about five million bucks.
Why is it so hard to believe
that he kept that policy for me?
For my sake, in case something
like this ever did happen?
No offense, Katie, but it
just wasn't exactly his style.
He never gave a thought
to anybody but himself.
I have to go.
Why don't you stay here for tonight?
Don't go back to that
empty apartment, honey.
No, no, I'll be fine, Mom.
- Kate, you sure?
- Yeah.
You know, it's funny, because
the only honorable thing
that Reese ever did, to get
that insurance policy for me.
Now that he's dead, no one
wants to give him credit for it.
I was only asking the same questions
those investigator guys
are gonna be asking.
Charlie, you're the key witness.
You saw the body floating
facedown in the water.
I know and it makes me nervous.
They don't care what you think,
they don't care what I think!
They're only gonna be listening
to those insurance guys.
They're gonna be watching her
like a fox watches chickens.
I know what you're thinking.
Do you?
No, I don't think you do.
Hmm.
I hated that bastard.
And you know, I think I
even hated myself more,
for not doing anything about it.
But there was nothing
any of us could do.
She was in love with him!
You, of all people,
should understand that.
But I know what he was doing to her!
I begged her to leave him.
Oh, Mom, anything, anything
to stop the beatings.
Yeah, but that wasn't
your responsibility!
Why not, she's my sister!
I owe her that, don't I?
I am so happy that you
girls are this close.
It's something that I wished for,
but Ginny, there is nothing you can do
to change what happened.
Katie's gonna have to go
through this on her own.
She'll survive it, and
then she'll come through it
and maybe, someday, find
someone else, God willing,
and all of this will just
seem like a bad memory to her.
Okay?
Okay.
Hey, you.
I have a date with Joey.
Oh, I love you both.
I love you too.
- Come here.
- Reese.
No.
I can't keep doing this.
Sh, sh, sh, look, you're my girl,
and nothing is gonna split us up.
Nothing, never, no.
Reese, please.
Sh, sh, sh, sh.
I've practiced this jump a dozen times.
How long until
we get to Yuma, boss?
Two days ride over those mountains.
You think we'll make it?
Don't know, bad storm,
Indian war parties,
rattlesnakes all ahead of us.
You're very good with
children, aren't you, Mr. Logan?
- Isn't he?
- Yes, he is.
I have a lot of nieces and nephews.
Oh, well you should
have kids of your own
because you have the magic.
You know, children know
when you mean them well
or mean them harm.
Um, we have to ask some
questions about your daughter
and the accident that
killed your son-in-law.
Oh yes, well I don't mind.
Kate said that she
came over here that day,
and that she was with Joey, all afternoon?
Yes, that's right.
Reese and Charlie had gone
hunting up at the bluff,
and she was going off to
the nursery for the day,
so I suggested that
she take Joey with her.
How's Joey reacting
to his uncle's accident?
Well, as I said, children
know when a person means them
well or means them harm
and he had a mean streak.
Of course it's none of
my business what happens
between a husband and wife.
No, that's right, no,
Kate and Joey were together
all afternoon, as I told you.
The whole afternoon.
I believe my daughter's
waiting to see you.
Oh thank you for your time.
Welcome, you're welcome.
Soup is getting thicker!
What?
All we did was confirm that the boy was
with her all afternoon.
Hold this.
Could be the old lady is
lying to protect her daughter.
You didn't notice how
Mama started to wriggle
after she dropped that nugget
about what a mean
so-and-so the deceased was?
If Kate had taken Joey
with her to the nursery,
then it should be fairly
easy, let me have that,
to find eyewitnesses who saw them there.
Well maybe.
The first thing I
learned in this business,
well, is that human beings
are capable of anything.
It doesn't have a damn thing
to do with how nice they look.
I don't know,
I just don't see this
woman committing murder
for the sake of insurance money.
Okay, you're probably right.
Then again, I've seen
stranger things than that.
All right, listen John,
why don't we split up?
You talk to the Hallorans
and I'll nose around out here
with the ranch hands.
I know they're expecting two of us,
but tell her I'm sick.
You don't wanna speak
with the Hallorans?
No, I read the transcripts.
Oh, well, maybe I'll
get them to loosen up.
I doubt it.
You don't think that I can interrogate
without you looking over my shoulder?
She's a lawyer, she
started the paperwork.
They're not gonna say anything
that could jeopardize her sister's chance
at the insurance money.
Well, we'll see.
20?
- You're on.
- Okay.
Mrs. Halloran, I'm from Solar State.
Oh yes, how do you do?
We were expecting you.
My husband will be joining us shortly.
- Please.
- Thank you.
- Please have a seat.
So I understand that you
initiated the paperwork.
Yes, I did.
I would like to see it resolved
as quickly as possible.
My sister has been under
a considerable strain.
Now, is there anything
that you can tell us
about that day?
I saw Reese and Kate when she
dropped him off at the house
to go hunting with my husband.
Then she left and I went
into town to my office,
I had some work to do and
that's where I received the call
that there had been an accident.
Now, I would assume
there's someone downtown
that can verify that
you were at the office?
You make it sound like
a criminal investigation.
No, I'm sorry, I didn't
mean to imply that.
No, it's okay.
We have a sign-in log at the building,
and if you need some character references,
I'm sure I could rustle up a few.
No, I'm
sure it'll be just fine.
Would you
care for some lemonade?
Sure, why not?
Do something for you, Mister?
My name's Mac, oh, McCaffey.
I'm an investigator with
Solar State Insurance Company.
You been working here long?
Couple years.
You knew the fella got
killed the other day?
Aye, nobody liked him much, did they?
I guess it was 'cause of
how he beat up on her.
Yeah, he shouldn't have done it.
I mean, I sure as hell
wouldn't treat her like that.
You like her?
Yeah sure, I like her.
What of it?
I'd bet you'd treat her a lot better
than Williams did, wouldn't you?
You think I had a
thing for her, don't you?
Give me a motive, wouldn't it?
Yeah.
No, she never looked my way.
But I watch things around here.
You know, pick things up.
Now something's bugging
you, isn't it, son?
Why don't you tell me about it?
It can't hurt.
Might even make you feel better.
I'm gonna find out all the
answers, sooner or later.
It's what I do.
Well, after they brought Dokie back,
Dokie's the horse Williams was riding,
I was putting up the saddle
and I couldn't find the
canteen I loaded up.
Now see, I fix everything
up for Mr. And Mrs. Halloran
when they go on a hunt,
so they don't have to do...
What, Mrs. Halloran hunts too?
Sometimes.
Hell, she's a better
shot than any of them.
Not that day, though,
said she had work to do.
Anyhow, there was no
canteen in the saddlebags.
Why is that significant?
You're the investigator,
you figure it out.
Right.
Ah, here he is.
Hiya, gorgeous.
Mr. Halloran, John
Logan, Solar State Life.
Mr. Logan.
I understand
that you were the one
who saw the body in the water?
Yeah, yeah, Reese
was wearing a tan vest,
so I could see him fairly clearly
from where I stood on the cliff.
And you said you saw
him floating facedown,
looking like he was dead?
Well, he looked dead to me.
But you never actually
saw him float away
or get carried away by the tide?
Well no, I had a choice to make.
I could stay there and
watch the body all day,
or I could go call for help.
You see, to do that, I
needed to go to the horse
and get the cellphone from the saddlebag
and those few minutes,
the body disappeared.
I think my husband
made the right decision,
don't you, Mr. Logan?
Yes, I do.
Now, you indicated that,
on the day of the accident,
you heard a gunshot.
There were hunters up on those bluffs,
we heard dozens of shots.
But you never actually
saw Mr. Williams fall?
Oh no, no.
You see, he raced on ahead of
me and by the time I got there
I saw his horse by itself
and I sensed something was up
and when I looked over the
edge I could see Reese's body
floating in the water below.
That's all I can tell you.
Hmm, okay.
That's it for me.
Thank you for talking to us.
Sure thing.
Thank you.
- Pleasure.
- Mm-hmm.
You have a nice day.
Thank you.
Us, what was he talking about?
What do you mean?
Well, he said, "Thank
you for talking to us."
So, who's us?
Well, his partner
wasn't feeling very well,
so he said that he would
wait for him out in the car.
- So?
- So what?
So, what did you learn
from the ranch hand?
Don't touch anything.
You might scratch the car.
One of the guys that I talked to was
a kid named Kenny Evering.
Now, he worked here a couple of years.
We gotta run a check on him.
Okay, and why are we running
a check on Kenny Evering?
'Cause he looked at me
funny as we were walking by.
That's scientific.
How did you fare with the Hallorans?
Learn anything new and hot?
All right, you win.
Thank you.
So what did we learn
about Kenny Evering?
Williams' canteen was missing
when they brought the horse back.
So, what does that tell you?
I mean, he went over the
cliff with the canteen.
Oh, if he's riding fast
on a precarious ledge,
why does he take out a canteen?
All right, he stopped and
he had a drink of water.
I mean, he got off the horse
with the canteen in his hand
and he fell over the cliff with it.
Well, if he's dismounted
and standing there,
then why does he fall?
Because he walks to
the edge of the cliff,
he's peering over and
he loses his footing.
Charlie says that they were only apart
for maybe a minute, two at the most.
So?
Guy rides off in a huff, fuming,
then less than a minute
later, he's off his horse
taking a leisurely stroll
on the edge of the cliffs,
having a sip of water from his canteen.
Loses his balance?
Pfft, I don't think so.
But even if he did, wouldn't
he throw the canteen away
and grab for something to hold onto?
I would think so.
So if that happened,
then the canteen would be on
the ground somewhere nearby.
Only it ain't there!
No canteen!
And what does that tell you?
Nothing maybe.
Or maybe it tells me there's something
that doesn't smell quite
right about all of this.
There, clean as a whistle.
Joey asleep?
Sound asleep, Mom
too, in the same chair.
I didn't have the heart to wake her.
Don't wake her.
You know she loves falling
asleep in that chair.
Coming to bed?
You okay?
You seem preoccupied lately.
I was about to tell you
exactly the same thing.
Oh, it's this whole
business with Kate and Reese.
I think it's making us all a little crazy.
I'm glad he's dead.
God, what an awful thing to say,
but he was a miserable son of a bitch
that ruined a lot of lives.
Yeah.
You've been holding that one
in a long time, haven't you?
Yeah.
Do you think those insurance
investigators really believe
it was an accident?
Why shouldn't they believe you?
You said so yourself,
there were other hunters,
other gunshots.
What if it didn't happen exactly
the way I told the police that it did?
What are you saying?
It's that shot, Ginny.
I just keep hearing that shot over
and over again in my head.
- Ginny.
- What?
Nothing.
Come on, let's go to bed.
Mr. Logan, would you
like to come inside?
I can offer you something to drink.
There's no point in sitting
out here all by yourself.
Am I that noticeable?
Let's just say you are hard to miss.
Well, I'm kinda new at this job.
It's temporary actually.
Here, let me have that.
I'm gonna teach high school
music, I'm a musician.
But see, I needed money
and I saw this notice.
If you wanna teach music,
why don't you teach music?
That's what my friends say.
They said if you wanna play, play,
you wanna teach, teach.
They're right, if you have a
dream you ought to pursue it.
Oh yeah, well dreams
cost money, I got bills.
- There's that.
- Mm-hmm.
Oh wow, this is nice.
You have a terrific sense of style.
Thank you, my husband is...
Well, he was good with carpentry,
and I did all the
decorating and landscaping.
Oh, that's what you
do, isn't it, landscaping?
Yeah, I'm a landscape architect.
Can I offer you something
to drink, Mr. Logan?
You wanna beer or wine?
Oh, iced tea, if you have it.
I'm not supposed to drink on the job.
Well, you're not a cop, you
work for an insurance company.
Yeah well, the company has rules
and I sorta like to play by the rules.
Oh, that's refreshing.
- Here.
- Thank you.
My friends call me John.
Um, you're in my house because you
and your partner are trying
to prevent Solar State Life
from paying my husband's insurance policy,
so I don't think we qualify as friends.
Well, if there's nothing to prove,
then I'm sure that Solar State
Life would be more than happy
to make good on their obligations.
In fact, if there's no complications,
I'm here to ensure that they
pay off in a timely manner,
and I'd still love it
if you'd call me John.
Virginia.
I was going to come
by and see you, Judge.
How's your sister?
That was a terrible thing that happened.
Actually that's what I
wanted to talk to you about.
Oh?
Her husband bought a huge policy
about six years ago, $5 million.
She's going to need a
determination of death ruling.
She's on her own now,
she's going to need
every penny she can get.
So what would you like me to do?
Pick up the hearing off the docket?
Well, I need someone I can trust.
Obviously, Solar's going to
balk at that amount of money.
I can't say I blame them.
But you know I can't
influence the outcome.
Of course not, I'd
never ask you to do that.
I just wanna make sure
that Kate gets a fair shake, that's all.
I don't wanna see them drag
it on, week after week,
if there's no reason not to pay.
Well, okay, I'll have my clerk watch out
for the paperwork.
I enjoy keeping those
insurance boys honest.
Well, I'd better get back to my guests.
Always nice seeing you, Virginia.
Thank you, Eugene.
I really appreciate it, so will Kate.
You're welcome, bye-bye.
Bye-bye, Judge.
Did you ever go
hunting with everyone else?
No, they asked,
but I never wanted to.
Don't believe in
hunting for sport, huh?
No, it's nothing
so politically correct.
I was raised around guns.
You know my mom and dad
are career military?
And Ginny won a Junior
National Riflery Award
when she was a teenager.
- Really?
- Mm-hmm.
She's an expert markswoman.
She won all these trips
to travel and compete
all over the place, Europe, everywhere.
God, I was as jealous as hell.
You don't strike me as someone
who would enjoy shooting guns.
I tell you, I would've shot anything,
if it meant the opportunity to travel.
I wanted to go to Rome and Venice,
you know, places like that?
I just never got the chance to do it.
$5 million would sure buy
a lot of airline tickets.
Is this a formal interrogation?
Or should I have legal
representation present?
I'm sorry, I didn't
mean anything by that.
I guess it's obvious I'm
kinda new at this job.
Yeah.
- It's really obvious!
- Yeah.
You don't really strike me as
the private investigator type.
You know what happened
is I answered this job ad,
and it sounded kind of romantic, you know,
like Fred MacMurray in Double Indemnity.
You've never seen this movie?
- No.
- Oh, this is a great movie,
I've seen it about a million times.
Fred MacMurray and Barbara Stanwyck.
You see, Fred MacMurray plays this um,
private insurance investigator,
and he falls for this
sultry blond, Stanwyck,
and she's this gorgeous,
murdering widow, and she...
I'm sorry, I did it again, I'm sorry.
It's okay, it's okay.
It's getting kind of breezy.
Oh no.
Come on, I insist, put it on.
Thanks.
Dust, dirt, grime from the city.
Gotta keep it off the finish
or it works its way in.
Where were you earlier?
Oh, I don't know, I was out
running around or something,
doing some errands, I'm sure of that.
Sand and saltwater also
causes damage out here.
You know anything about engines?
Yeah, my dad was a mechanic.
He said when I was 16, if I wanted a car,
I'd have to build it from spare parts.
Good for him!
I always had a squad car,
boys in the motor pool
always did the work.
Yeah, you were a cop?
15 years.
Well that would explain it then.
Explain what?
Why you're so good with this stuff.
Oh yeah, I'm great.
You never lose your nose for
the liars and the scumbags.
Once you smell them, it
stays that way for life.
Why'd you stop being a cop?
Long story, morbid
nostalgia, I need food!
Food, food!
Hey, looky here, will you?
Check out these bank accounts.
Each one is in Reese Williams' name.
Three of them!
Really?
And only one jointly with Kate.
So Mr. Williams was hiding
money from the little lady.
Our heroine seems to
instill secrecy in her men.
Okay.
Check out these deposits right here.
Where does a guy like this
get that kind of cash?
Is that gambling?
Well, it wouldn't be so regular,
this looks like a payment.
Hold this.
So this is like blackmail or extortion?
Could be.
You still think this guy
accidentally fell over a cliff?
Maybe not.
Hey, listen to this.
You know the stable boy, Kenny Evering?
He and Reese Williams got
into a fight three months ago
and Reese beat the hell out of this kid.
Oh, and Kenny knew where
they would be hunting.
He packs the horses, loads the weapons,
and keeps track of the ammo.
Ho, ho, somebody else
just arrived at the party!
You know what?
This is just like an Agatha
Christie novel, isn't it?
Hey there!
Is Kenny Evering around?
He was here a minute ago,
then he just all of a sudden
mounted up and took off.
Hm, you know where he's headed?
No, all I know is
he's supposed to be here
supervising this job.
Oh, when you see him,
tell him to call one of us, would you?
Number's on the card there.
Yeah well, next time you guys see him,
let him know that I could use
a little help around here.
I don't think it was a coincidence
somebody didn't wanna do much talking.
So did you know him personally, Colonel?
Oh yeah, as a matter of
fact I was on the trial board
at his court-martial.
Court-martial?
Yeah, he got a dishonorable discharge
and a six-month sentence for
beating the living daylights
out of a bunkmate.
And do you remember what happened?
Well, I'm retired, son, and that's...
It all started
when Williams got the general's
married daughter pregnant.
General's daughter?
Brigadier General Harmon McElvey.
He was the head honcho at the base
when Williams was stationed there.
You know, this goes back a few years.
General's dead now,
but he was a great man.
Harmon McElvey was a soldier's soldier,
straight as a rod, and he
did not like finding out
that his daughter was being
done on a regular basis
by one of his enlisted men,
while her husband was
on assignment in Europe.
So I would assume that
Williams was not well liked.
Not well liked?
Is this grass green?
Nobody had a good word to
say for the son of a bitch.
So what's that got to do
with beating a fellow soldier?
Williams was having the girl pay him
to keep things quiet while
he could arrange an abortion.
Only the bunkmate found out about it,
and blew the whistle on him.
Williams didn't take too kindly to it.
He beat the guy to within
an inch of his life.
Uh, now, whatever happened to the girl?
Messy divorce, then
she went to Switzerland
'til things died down around here.
General McElvey made us
throw the book at Williams.
Switzerland, isn't that
where they make cuckoo clocks?
Come on, Kate's never
been to Switzerland,
I'll bet anything.
Kate, who's Kate?
The general's daughter.
Wrong daughter.
Virginia, Virginia McElvey,
they called her Ginny.
Sisters, their purple past revealed.
Just kidding.
Okay, let's track this.
Williams figures that
he can romance his way
up the ranks, huh?
But he blows his first
chance when he gets greedy,
so he figures the general's
pregnant daughter has gotta be
worth some quick cash.
Yeah, and maybe he needs the
money to cover his gambling,
only his buddy blows the lid
off, and Williams winds up with
no girl, no money, and
six months in the brig.
And Ginny gets sent off to
Switzerland for a safe abortion
and the McElveys, they
have to stay here and that,
to keep things as quiet as possible.
Until Williams returns and decides to go
for double or nothing.
- Whoa.
- What?
There was no abortion!
The boy belongs to Reese!
- Joey?
- Yeah.
Do you think Kate knows?
I don't know, what do you think,
you're the expert on all matters Kate.
Knock it off, how am
I supposed to know that?
Okay, look.
The boy is a living reminder of everything
that happened in the past.
I'd say people might be lining
up to get back at this guy.
Check this out.
What's that?
I found it in the bushes about 50 yards
from where Williams supposedly
fell over the cliff.
Now, a shotgun couldn't reach that far,
but a .30-06, no problem.
You can't prove anything with this!
There's gotta be hundreds
of hunters up there!
Somebody shot the guy, John!
Oh, pfft.
I can feel it, I can taste it!
We're talking murder here!
Where you been?
I was checking out his hind leg,
make sure it was healing properly.
Those two insurance
investigators were here to see you.
I didn't talk to them.
No, you took off when you
spotted them, I was watching.
What's the matter, Kenny?
Nothing, I didn't say anything.
Look, it was kinda stupid to run,
unless you have something to hide.
I was looking out for
you and Mrs. Halloran.
Kenny, Mrs. Halloran and
I appreciate your concern,
but we don't want you running
from the investigators.
Only makes things look a lot worse.
They think somebody
pushed Reese off that cliff,
maybe shot him off.
They're only fishing for answers
because they don't wanna
pay Kate what they owe her.
Now, I know you had nothing to do with it,
and that's the only thing that counts.
Yes, sir.
What's this?
You planning a vacation, Mac?
Oh, not me boy-o, your lady friend.
Where'd you get this?
Those are exact duplicates
of brochures discovered
by a little professional snooping.
What, you broke into her house?
It's called investigating sir.
The woman trusts me and
you broke into her house.
What if she had come back?
I've done this a few times, you know.
You've been following us!
You don't get it, do you, boy-o?
This sweet young thing just
might've killed her husband
for the insurance money.
No.
It's happened before you know,
and not just in the movies!
And you're acting like you
two are going to some prom!
Mac, Mac, you don't know her.
I know what these brochures tell me.
I know that she's not planning
on sticking around here
once she's got our company's money
in her delicate little hands!
Well, maybe she's
planning a trip, you know?
Maybe she wants to get away,
forget her troubles, you know?
No law against that, least
the last time I looked.
Will you listen to yourself?
You sound like a little puppy dog!
I'm trying to keep you from
following Reese Williams
over that same little cliff!
Well, thank you very much,
Mac, I can take care of myself.
I can't believe
you came all the way up here
just to lug these things around.
These things weigh a ton!
If I were you, I'd take advantage
of the fact that I'm here.
Well, I can't pay you.
Wait a second.
That's my card.
I owe you one free dinner,
that's payment enough.
So how'd you get into landscaping?
Oh, while Ginny was off
winning those riflery awards,
I was wandering around
the post making friends
with the landscaping crews.
I became sort of like their mascot.
Oh yeah?
So, did you know Reese?
Yeah.
He was dating Ginny at the time.
Did you know about the two of them?
I know all about them.
I know about the court-martial, and Joey.
What, are you looking for motives?
No, no, I'm just,
I'm trying to figure out how
someone like you would end up
with someone like Reese.
Psychologists would say
that it was sibling rivalry.
I was jealous of Ginny
and I wanted what she
could no longer have.
Would the psychologists be right?
To a degree, I suppose.
But there was a time when
Reese and I were happy,
you know, we were fixing up our house
and making plans for the future.
He was a different person then,
and that was be...
Anyway, do you have
everything that you need
or is there something else
that you'd like to ask me?
Well, I'd like to
think that we're friends.
Reese's death, the
insurance policy, your job,
none of those things are gonna go away
until after this investigation is over,
one way or the other.
There are all kinds of
questions in your head.
I can hear them, I can feel
them every time you look at me.
Reese, what are you doing here?
Tell me, you little bitch!
You think I don't know what's going on?
Reese, I've been
waiting to hear from you.
I've been checking the mail every day.
You think I don't know
what's been going on?
You tried to double-cross me!
No you don't!
You tried to shoot me,
and I've got the bullet in
my shoulder to prove it!
Come here!
You passed out
in the kitchen last night.
Why didn't you just finish me off?
You have to get this shoulder treated.
I'm supposed to be dead, remember,
I can't very well show up
at some doctor's office.
Forget about the money, Reese.
You're badly wounded.
We're not forgetting about anything.
Everybody thinks I'm dead and
we're gonna keep it that way,
do you understand?
It's gonna be true if
that wound gets infected.
I'm not gonna die from it.
I survived the shot and the fall,
I've been living out in the woods for days
with this damn thing in me.
We're too close to quit now.
You're gonna take this bullet out of me.
Reese, I can't do that,
I'm not a doctor, I can't...
I'll make you a list of supplies.
I know what to do, I've
trained for this, remember?
You can do it, Katie.
You can do this.
You could've killed me.
When I passed out, you had the chance.
I'll be goddamned!
She set me up.
Who?
Whose idea you think this
whole insurance scam was
in the first place?
What do I know about legal rulings?
This was Ginny's idea from the get-go.
The bitch double-crossed me.
I don't believe you.
Nobody else knew what
I was gonna be doing
on that cliff that day.
Nobody but the three of us,
you, me, and that lady lawyer.
If you want me to take that bullet out,
then I have to go get supplies.
Hey, I was near death out there,
using every trick I knew to survive,
and the only thought on my
mind was about the money
and the fact that you or your
sister double-crossed me.
You try anything, you
say anything to anybody,
you do anything, and I
swear, I will kill Joey.
I'll be back.
- Ginny!
- Kate!
What are you doing here?
What the hell is going on?
What are you talking about?
I'm talking about Reese.
What about Reese?
He showed up last night,
how do you think I got this?
I was sitting down to work,
and the next thing I know,
Reese is there, and he's
slamming me around the room
and he wants to know why
I double-crossed him,
why I tried to kill him.
What are you talking about?
He thinks that you shot him, Ginny!
He's going on and on about it.
That I shot him?
It's a miracle that he survived,
now what the hell is going on?
Kate, listen to me.
Don't let him do this to us,
don't let him turn us against one another.
Ginny, why did you shoot him?
Why didn't you tell me?
Kate, I did not shoot
him, I did not shoot him,
you've got to believe me.
So what happens now?
Give me a minute to think.
Hi, Kate.
Everything all right today?
Yeah, fine.
See you tomorrow, Alice.
Bye.
Oh, God.
Look, I will try to
accelerate the process,
maybe get a ruling in a week or two,
but you've got to keep Reese out of sight.
Reese will stay quiet.
He wants the money, he'll do
anything he has to to get it.
Oh, Kate.
Thanks.
All I know is there's a
whole truckload of people
who wanted to have this guy dead,
starting with his wife,
whom he beat the hell out of
on a regular basis.
She didn't do it, Mac.
Okay, you know, have it your way, eh?
What about his sister-in-law, Ginny?
Old news, why kill him now?
Well, stuff like this is never old news.
She sees it every time
she looks at her son
or her new husband.
She knew about the hunt.
She waits for the right
moment, blam, past eradicated!
Okay, the problem is
her office building is
a county facility with a sign-in sheet.
There's a 24/7 security guard out front.
He signs her in, he signs her out.
Okay, suppose Charlie
Halloran decides to take matters
into his own hands, huh?
All right.
I mean he hates the guy
because of what he did
to Ginny and Kate, so they're
up all alone on the cliffs,
one quick shot, it's all over.
And just swing it away
from the family tree,
what about Kenny?
But how do you prove all this?
I'll keep working on the Hallorans,
and you keep wining and
dining the merry widow.
Oh no, I'm not gonna do that.
What do you mean you won't?
Because I'm not gonna do it,
I'm not gonna lie and
deceive Kate like that.
It won't happen, period.
Fine!
Go have a good time!
You know, read poetry to
her in the shade of a tree,
but the truth is gonna come out one day
and bite you whether you like it or not.
You talk to your sister?
She says she
didn't try and shoot you.
She's lying!
You were taking money from
them again, weren't you?
I had some heavy debts
so I asked for help.
Hell, that's what family's for, right?
Sit up, she says you threatened
to tell Joey the truth.
He's my kid, I got every
right to tell him who I am.
She's bitter, she's
jealous because I wound up
with you and not with her.
He's a little boy, Reese, it's not fair.
He has a chance for a
normal life with them.
What, no, I wasn't
really gonna tell him.
That was part of the deal that she came up
with the insurance scam.
I was gonna take the money
and keep my mouth shut,
and I agreed, I agreed, I agreed.
And now?
She tried to kill me,
Kate, don't take her side.
You think she cares about you?
She has lorded it over us
ever since we were married.
She's got the ranch,
she's got the position,
she's got the rich husband,
but she didn't get me,
and she's never gonna
forgive you for that, Kate.
You think she tried to
kill you because of that?
She knew exactly where
I was gonna be, and when,
and she's a crack shot.
I'll tell you something,
I gotta message for her.
She's gonna get that ruling
and she's gonna get that money
or she's gonna be even
sorrier than she is now
that I survived.
- Hello?
- Hello.
- Hi.
- Hey, you owe me dinner.
I thought maybe I'd come by tonight
and collect on an IOU.
Tonight's not good,
I'm working on some landscaping drawings,
I'm gonna be working late.
How about tomorrow night?
I don't know.
Are you blowing me off here?
You mean to tell me I came by
and lifted all those
heavy pots for nothing?
Why don't you give me a phone
number where I can reach you
and then I'll call you
when I can get away.
Okay, thanks.
Someone from the nursery.
You've changed, Katie.
What are you talking about?
I don't know, you're different, you're...
More sure of yourself.
Grit your teeth or something
because I'm gonna start.
Wow!
Very impressive.
This is better than any
restaurant I had in mind.
Che Kate.
Hey, terrific.
- Mm, may I?
- Yeah.
How did you...
Oh, occupational hazard.
It was a swinging branch of
a northern California fir.
Oh, Kate.
No, it's fine.
Come on, dinner's getting cold.
Okay, no more questions.
- All right?
- Yeah.
And he said play this, do it!
I said no, he said,
well if you do it again,
you're out of the band forever.
You're staring at me.
Don't you believe
that two people can just
know each other instinctively?
That's sweet,
but I think that things
don't always work out
the way you want them to.
Well maybe you just don't
trust your feelings, is all.
I don't have a lot of practice
in trusting my feelings.
I've been too busy trying not
to get my face smashed in.
It wouldn't take too much investigation
to figure out want our marriage was like.
I'm sorry, we don't have to go there.
No, I don't mind talking
about it, I wanna talk about it.
I feel like my life is changing so fast.
I don't care about the money, John.
I really don't.
I just want a chance to start my life over
and not have to be afraid
of being hurt again.
Can you understand that?
- Oh, no, no.
- What?
Mac says that I can't
discuss the evidence with you.
What, am I a suspect?
I mean, what am I suspected of?
He found a shell from a .30-06
near the spot where Reese fell.
They were hunting.
But he found it in a grove of bushes
with a perfect vantage point.
You think Reese was shot?
I don't know what I think,
but Mac thinks that he
was shot and killed, yes.
He thinks I did it, doesn't he?
Oh no, no, no, not necessarily.
He said there were plenty of
other suspects with motives.
No, no, just ask the question, okay,
because it's hanging over your head.
Let's just get this over
with, just ask the question.
That's not necessary,
I don't have to ask.
I told you, I was raised around guns,
and I can fire a hunting rifle
as well as any man I know,
but I did not shoot my husband,
and I did not kill my husband.
Now you need to ask yourself
what you really believe,
because if you don't believe
that I'm telling you the truth
then you should turn
and walk out of my life
and don't even think of coming back.
Katie?
Kate?
Baby?
You out here?
Who's out here?
Katie?
She had to go out.
Where is she?
I don't know.
You're lying.
I heard her making plans on the telephone
earlier this afternoon.
She's not wasting any time
playing the grieving widow, is she?
Why'd you double-cross me, Ginny?
I didn't.
Pfft, somebody shot me,
this shoulder isn't the
result of a hunting accident.
Ha, trust me, Reese, if it had been me,
you wouldn't be standing here right now.
I carried out my part of the bargain.
If I get the ruling, you've
gotta carry out yours.
You take your share and you leave forever.
What's the matter, counselor,
don't you think I'm a man of my word?
I'd have been happy with
my share, I'd have left.
Somebody else didn't stick to the plan.
Kate will wire half the money,
to a numbered account in the Bahamas.
Reese, if you go back on
your word in any way, shape,
or form, I'll go to the authorities
and I will tell them
exactly where to find you.
No, you won't do that.
Believe me, I don't care
what happens any more.
Oh, looks like I'm not in
any position to bargain, am I?
I guess not.
Looks like you won this one.
Still the same magic
between us, huh, Virginia?
You son of a bitch!
I wish to God you had died!
And leave Joey without a father?
Ginny, what's wrong?
He's crazy.
He thinks we're conspiring against him.
They found a .30-06 shell,
right near the spot where he fell,
and now they suspect that he was shot.
I don't think that they can
prove anything but I'm worried.
This whole thing is
threatening to unravel.
Ginny, he said that if
we tell the authorities,
he'll kill Joey.
We've got to finish this now.
Kate, I think Charlie shot him.
Charlie?
He's been saying things.
He's been leading me with
questions, I don't know.
Somebody shot him, it
wasn't you, it wasn't me.
Kate, I gotta know.
I know.
Hi.
Missed you at dinner.
How's Katie?
Oh, she's okay.
Still a little needy, she wanted to talk,
we lost track of time, I'm sorry.
It's no problem.
Joey and I went to the mall,
had some burgers and fries.
- Charlie?
- Hm?
The other night you told me
that you kept hearing the gunshot,
and that you weren't
sure that what happened
was what you said.
I remember.
You were trying to tell
me something, weren't you?
Joey and I are very close.
He's the son I've always wanted.
And I know that Reese was
threatening to tell him
that he was his real birth father,
and I know that you were not
going to allow him to do that.
Ginny, when I heard the
shot, I just assumed
that you took matters into your own hands.
Me?
You're afraid that I shot him?
Well, yes.
Charlie, I didn't, I swear it.
I was going to confront you,
I thought that you did it.
- Me?
- Yes, to protect me.
I mean, oh, this is so crazy, I...
You really didn't?
No, me?
I hated the son of a bitch but
I'm not gonna shoot anybody.
If you didn't...
Kenny!
Kenny?
Well sure, you know how he liked Katie,
and when those insurance
investigators came
to question him he bolted.
He told me that he was afraid
that he was gonna say something
that might incriminate one of us.
I just assumed he was talking about you.
Of course, he was trying
to protect himself.
Maybe we should talk to him.
In the morning, my beauty.
In the morning.
You're late!
We're not due in the judge's
chambers for another hour.
We ought to go over this stuff again.
Why?
So we know what we're doing.
I know what I'm doing.
John, John.
I need you in there today.
How the hell am I gonna
get the judge to listen
if you and I aren't singing the same song?
I got nothing to say, Mac.
Do you work for this company?
Our job is to take these
findings and convince the judge
that a determination of
death ruling is not in order.
I'm not gonna walk in
there and accuse these people
of murder, when we don't
have any hard evidence.
We're not the cops,
we're not accusing anyone!
We're just trying to
establish enough doubt
to keep the investigation going!
I know what our job is, Mac!
We're supposed to keep Solar State Life
from paying off on the insurance policy!
Well, I'm gonna do exactly the opposite!
You're never gonna
make it in this company.
You don't get it, do you?
I could never live with
myself if I did that to Kate.
Hiyah!
Billy, have you seen Kenny anywhere?
No sir, not since
this morning about six.
He was packing up his stuff.
- Packing?
- Yes, ma'am.
He said there was too much
heat on him around here,
so he was taking off.
He said you two knew about
it, so you'd understand.
Yeah, thanks, Billy.
- Thank you.
- Sure, no problem.
Mr. McCaffey, I have
reviewed your theories,
and your conjectures, and I must admit
that they made for very
interesting reading.
Then again, so does John Grisham.
His books, however, are works of fiction,
and I believe that your
theories are equally fanciful.
Fortunately or unfortunately,
these postulations are supported
by no substantial evidence,
nothing other than the
most circumstantial.
What we do know for sure
is that Mr. Williams went
from up on the cliff down to the water,
facedown according to
our single eyewitness,
and beyond that, there is
no indication of foul play
or untoward behavior on the
part of anyone involved.
I might add parenthetically,
I know the family involved
and can therefore bring
a personal judgment
as to the character of
those giving testimony.
Your Honor, I would like
to lodge a formal protest
on behalf of the Solar State
Life Insurance Company.
Mr. McCaffey, you may
lodge any protest you wish,
however, it is my ruling that
the determination of death
in this case, is consistent
with the accidental fall
of Mr. Williams from
the cliff in question,
as indicated in the
official police report.
Therefore, I hereby
declare Mr. Reese Williams
to be legally deceased.
Thank you ladies and gentlemen,
this matter is closed.
Are you happy now, boy-o?
Somebody just got away with murder.
Can you live with that?
So?
How'd it go?
It's done, your share
is in a numbered account
in First Bahaman Bank and Trust.
Here's the account number.
Well, what do you know?
You two girls finally did your jobs right.
I told you we could pull this off.
You promised to leave.
What's your hurry?
It's all over now.
The longer you hang around here,
the more chance there is
that someone might spot you.
Oh, not to worry, darling.
Besides, you and me and Ginny,
we still have a little
unfinished business.
How stupid do you think I am?
We had a deal once, remember?
Until one of you two witches
decided to try to kill me.
Reese, neither one of us...
No, no more talk.
You call the bank.
And wire your share into my account.
Call!
Right here, stop.
Get out!
Get out, come on, get out.
Reese, what are you doing?
What, do you mean
you haven't figured it out yet?
It was a damn good scheme
right from the beginning,
and it would've worked too,
if one of you two hadn't
decided to double-cross me.
Oh my God!
I made it big
enough for two of you.
Reese, don't be stupid.
You can't kill us, you'll
never get away with this!
Oh, you don't think so?
Gee, I don't know, I'm
just a dead guy, remember?
But I'll tell you something,
you know that insurance dick of yours?
He already thinks that
one of you killed me,
so by the time the two of you disappear
and they discover the money's been wired
down to the Bahamas,
they're just going to assume
the two of you took the cash and split.
And then, if anybody ever
does discover your bodies,
which I doubt,
and identifies them as the
once-lovely McElvey sisters,
by then I'll be...
Well, let's just say I'll be long gone.
Reese!
Oh, God.
Oh, oh man.
Oh, oh God.
Oh God, I had to, he was
gonna kill you, and that...
Mac told me that one of
you two had killed him,
and I didn't wanna believe him
but I didn't know what to think.
Why didn't you say something?
I saw the bruise on your
face the other night at dinner
and I thought well, Jesus,
maybe the guy still is alive,
so I watched, because I
had to know the truth.
How much did you hear?
His fall was staged!
Wasn't it?
And you withheld the truth from
me until after the hearing!
That's not the whole truth, John.
You don't have to do this, Kate.
Yes I do.
The whole thing, the phony
death scheme, it was my idea.
The whole thing, the grieving widow,
and the concerned older
sister, all of it, all of it!
It was all part of an act.
Oh you?
I had to get away from him.
You understand?
I had to get away from him,
and I couldn't find any other way out,
and every time that I
would try to leave him,
he would beat the hell out of me,
and I didn't know what else to do!
Then he needed more and more money
and then finally he
threatened to tell Joey.
That's when I agreed to help her.
He's hurt so many people
for so many years,
he wasn't going to hurt my son!
I knew about the insurance policy,
but I thought maybe there was some way
that we could put him in a position
that he would have to disappear
from everybody's life
forever in order to collect.
We agreed that I would
present the scheme,
so he would think it was my idea.
And it almost worked.
The money is in a numbered
bank account in the Bahamas!
God, I'll make a full statement,
just handle this any
way that you wanna do.
I'll do anything that you want.
I was sure you'd turn out
to be a Class A investigator
when you first came to work here.
Oh, I'm sorry, Mac.
So am I.
I sure enjoyed working with
you though, you're a good man.
Oh, not quite good enough.
Without a body there
wasn't much anyone could do.
Think they'll ever find him?
Chances are slim, about
five million to one.
Yeah.
But you never know.
Jonah popped out of a whale.
Where you headed?
Well, I've always wanted
to see Europe, Italy maybe.
Venice!
Venice?
Ciao.
See ya.
Venice.
Hm, Venice.
So is there anything
else you want me to do
before you leave?
I don't think so.
You have my power of attorney.
There's enough money now for Mom and Joey
to live for the rest of their lives,
and I'm gonna do the traveling
that I always wanted to do.
Italy, I think.
I've always wanted to see Venice.
I'm gonna miss you.
I love you, Kate.
You too.
It was almost a perfect plan.
Hey, it worked out
right from the beginning.
Not exactly, I never wanted
anybody to get hurt, you know?
It was never part of my plan.
I have something for you.
I swear on Joey's life
I did not shoot Reese
and neither did Charlie.
Maybe Kenny, but he had nothing to gain.
It's over now, it doesn't really matter.
I guess we'll never figure it out.
When are you gonna teach me
how to shoot like you, Grandma?
Oh someday, just like
I taught your mama.
But guns kill, Joey.
You must never aim a gun at someone.
You have to be very, very careful.