Woman narrating: MY NAME IS MRS. BASIL E. FRANKWEILER
AND I HAVE A STORY TO TELL.
IT BEGINS WITH AN INVITATION I RECEIVED
TO ATTEND A PRIVATE AUCTION.
A FEW ELITE ART COLLECTORS, NOT TO MENTION A MUSEUM OR TWO,
WERE GATHERED TOGETHER TO EXCHANGE ONE ANOTHER'S TREASURES.
I WENT THERE THAT DAY NOT TO BUY
BUT TO SELL SOMETHING VERY DEAR TO ME,
SOMETHING WITH A SECRET,
A SECRET I HAVE KEPT FOR MANY YEARS.
NUMBER NINE IN YOUR CATALOGUE, AN UNDOCUMENTED SCULPTURE,
POSSIBLY QUARRIED FROM THE SAME MARBLE
USED BY MICHELANGELO,
IF IN FACT NOT SCULPTED BY THE MASTER HIMSELF.
THE COLLECTOR WISHES TO REMAIN ANONYMOUS
AND I HAVE ON THE BOOKS A BID OF $25,000.
WHO WILL OPEN THE BIDDING AT $30,000?
THANK YOU. $30,000.
DO I HEAR $35,000?
$35,000. THANK YOU, INDEED.
DO I HEAR 45? $45,000 IN THE BACK.
THANK YOU.
45. NOW $55,000.
THANK YOU. NOW 65.
DOWN FRONT HERE, 65. DO I HEAR $75,000?
$75,000. NOTHING FURTHER. AND--
SOLD TO NUMBER 115. THANK YOU, SIR.
Mrs. Frankweiler: SO NOW THE FUN WOULD BEGIN.
BUT NEVER IN MY WILDEST DREAMS
DID I IMAGINE THE SALE OF MY MYSTERIOUS SCULPTURE
WOULD BRING ME THE ACQUAINTANCE
OF THE MOST REMARKABLE TWO CHILDREN.
DOESN'T IT EVER DAWN ON YOU TO SAY, "THANK YOU, CLAUDIA.
I APPRECIATE THAT YOU MAKE MY LUNCH"?
TO SAY, "THE LITTLE NOTE YOU WROTE ME WITH MY CARROTS WAS THOUGHTFUL AND NICE"?
THAT NOTE WAS EMBARRASSING. AND I HATE CARROTS!
WELL THEN, LITTLE BROTHER, YOUR EYES ARE GONNA ROT AND FALL OUT OF YOUR HEAD.
BETTER THAN BEING A RABBIT.
MOVE, STEVE. I NEED TO SET THE TABLE.
HEY, DO YOU MIND? I'M STUDYING.
STUDY IN YOUR ROOM. OR CAN'T YOU FIND YOUR DESK IN THE MESS?
MOM, GIVE CLAUDIA SOMETHING ELSE TO DO.
- MOM! - WHY DON'T YOU MOVE YOUR BOOKS INTO THE FAMILY ROOM?
I CAN'T. THERE'S LAUNDRY EVERYWHERE.
CLAUDIA, PUT THE LAUNDRY AWAY FIRST
AND THEN YOU CAN SET THE TABLE.
WHY DO I ALWAYS HAVE TO DO EVERYTHING--
DON'T START, CLAUDIA. YOUR FATHER'S ON HIS WAY HOME FROM WORK,
I'VE GOT TAX DOCUMENTS TO FINISH FOR A CLIENT.
NOW YOU'VE DONE YOUR HOMEWORK; THE OTHERS HAVEN'T.
THAT'S WHAT YOU GET FOR BEING A GENIUS.
WHEN BOTH PARENTS WORK, SOMEONE HAS TO HELP.
IT'S A ROUGH LIFE.
Boy: PLEASE, DAD.
JAMIE, WE'RE NOT GIVING YOU SKYDIVING LESSONS
FOR YOUR BIRTHDAY AND THAT'S FINAL.
- I FOUND THE INSTRUCTIONS. - GOOD.
- BUT, DAD-- - JAMIE, JUST FORGET IT.
I STILL DON'T SEE WHY THEY CAN'T BE A BIRTHDAY PRESENT.
WHY DON'T YOU LET HIM BUY THEM HIMSELF?
HE HAS MORE MONEY THAN ANYONE ELSE IN THE FAMILY.
NO ONE IN THIS FAMILY IS SKYDIVING.
AND CLAUDIA'S BIRTHDAY COMES BEFORE ANYONE ELSE'S.
CLAUDIA?
I WANT A FOUR-POSTER BED WITH AN AWNING
AND A MATCHING DUST RUFFLE.
Steven: COME ON, CLAUD.
YOU DON'T JUST WANT THE BED.
YOU WANT TO ACTUALLY LIVE IN THE 17th CENTURY.
YEAH, THAT WAY SHE'LL BE A PRINCESS.
( all laugh )
Mother: HEY.
BOYS.
Claudia: HERE'S THE PROBLEM:
I DO EVERYTHING RIGHT.
NOBODY APPRECIATES ME.
MY FATHER HARDLY KNOWS I'M ALIVE.
MY BROTHERS THINK I'M JUST A BRAIN
AND MY MOTHER THINKS I CAN DO EVERYTHING AT ONCE.
THE TIME HAS COME TO DO SOMETHING ABOUT IT.
I JUST WISH I KNEW WHAT.
HMM.
Boy: CATCH YOU LATER!
Boy #2: GREAT GAME TODAY!
Driver: STEP RIGHT UP! WE'RE WAITING.
SEE YOU HAD SOME PEANUT BUTTER AND JELLY.
MOVE, BRUCE. I NEED TO TALK TO JAMIE.
TODAY, BRUCE.
I'M GLAD SHE'S NOT MY SISTER.
Both: THOU SHALT NOT SHUFFLE.
( both spit )
Driver: LET'S GET YOUR SEATS.
ALL RIGHT.
HERE WE GO. TIME TO CAST OFF.
JAMES LINCOLN KINCAID, I'M DELIGHTED TO TELL YOU
YOU'VE BEEN CHOSEN TO ACCOMPANY ME
ON THE GREATEST ADVENTURE OF OUR MUTUAL LIVES.
GREAT. WHO BY?
WHO BY?
YEAH. WHO CHOSE ME?
"BY WHOM," JAMIE. "BY WHOM WAS I CHOSEN?"
WAIT A MINUTE.
YOU STOPPED ME PLAYING CARDS WITH BRUCE
TO PLAY A WORD GAME?
I CHOSE YOU, JAMIE.
I CHOSE YOU BECAUSE
YOU AND I ARE GOING TO RUN AWAY.
HUH?
THE TRUTH IS, OUR PARENTS NO LONGER SEE ME AS A PERSON,
RATHER AS AN INITIAL ON THE CHORE CALENDAR.
YEAH-- "C."
THEY DON'T CARE THAT I GET STRAIGHT As
AND AS THE ONLY GIRL, I'M ACTUALLY SUBJECTED TO THE MOST INJUSTICE.
ARE YOU FAMILIAR WITH THE TERM
"ABSENCE MAKES THE HEART GROW FONDER"?
MMM... NO.
JAMIE, WE LEAVE TOMORROW
BECAUSE IT'S MUSIC LESSON DAY
AND THE BEST PLACE TO PACK OUR CLOTHES IS IN OUR INSTRUMENT CASES.
YOU HAVEN'T SAID WHY YOU WANT TO TAKE ME.
Steve: HEY, WHAT ARE YOU GUYS UP TO?
HUH?
LATER.
HI, STEVE.
WHAT ARE YOU INSECTS PLOTTING?
OH, NOTHING.
- THAT STINKS, CLAUD. THAT REALLY STINKS. - JAMIE!
I SHOULD HAVE KNOWN MONEY WAS THE REASON YOU WANTED ME TO COME.
TAKE STEVE.
STEVE IS LAZY AND UNIMAGINATIVE.
TAKE STEVE. HE CAN BRING ALL HIS FRIENDS
SINCE YOU'RE IN LOVE WITH ALL OF THEM.
I'M NOT IN LOVE WITH ANYONE
AND I DIDN'T PICK YOU BECAUSE YOU SAVE YOUR ALLOWANCE
- OR BECAUSE STEVE'S A DORK. - THEN WHY DID YOU PICK ME?
NO ONE ELSE AROUND HERE THINKS I CAN DO ANYTHING.
I PICKED YOU BECAUSE YOU HAVE A QUALITY I DON'T
AND IT'S CRUCIAL FOR AN ADVENTURE LIKE THIS ONE.
OH, YEAH? WHAT?
A SENSE OF DIRECTION.
HUH?
THINK ABOUT IT. YOU ALWAYS FIND MOM'S CAR
WHEN SHE LOSES IT AT THE MALL.
AND YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE IN THE FAMILY WHO OWNS A COMPASS.
YEAH. I GUESS SO.
COME ON, JAMIE, CAN'T YOU JUST SEE US HIDING OUT,
SENDING MYSTERIOUS LETTERS HOME?
WE CAN USE CUTOUT WORDS FROM MAGAZINES
AND MAKE UP CODES.
AMD WE COULD SLEEP OUTSIDE.
AND LEAVE PHONY TRAILS.
- OKAY. - WHAT?
WELL, I SAID OKAY,
AS LONG AS YOU'RE NOT TAKING ME FOR MY MONEY, LET'S DO IT.
WAY TO GO, JAMIE. ALL RIGHT.
Mother: CLAUDIA!
DON'T FORGET THE LAUNDRY.
SURE, MOM.
JUST FOR THE RECORD, JAMIE,
HOW RICH ARE YOU?
ONE-- FORGET TONIGHT'S HOMEWORK.
TWO-- FIND A GOOD HIDING PLACE FOR YOUR TRUMPET.
THREE-- PACK CLEAN UNDERWEAR, SOCKS, AND A TOOTHBRUSH.
OKAY. WHEN I'M DONE WITH EVERYTHING ON THE LIST,
SHOULD I EAT IT?
Mother: COME ON! DINNER'S READY!
THERE'S YOUR ANSWER.
OH, THE KIDS ARE GOING TO LOVE THIS.
WHOA! TAKEOUT!
Steve: HEY, WHAT'S THE OCCASION?
YOUR FATHER THOUGHT YOU DESERVED A BREAK.
AND FOR DESSERT,
WE'RE GOING TO MAKE INDIVIDUAL BANANA SPLITS.
- Steve: WE ARE? - WITH MARSHMALLOW TOPPING?
WE ARE... WITH THE TOPPING OF YOUR CHOICE!
Mother: OKAY, EVERYBODY, DIG IN!
DOESN'T THIS LOOK TERRIFIC, HUH?
Father: WELL, I BET IT TASTES EVEN BETTER. EH, JAMIE?
Mother: BANANA SPLITS WERE MY FAVORITE WHEN I WAS A KID.
Jamie: WERE THEY AS GOOD AS THESE?
Father: NOTHING COULD BE AS GOOD AS THESE.
HEY, CLAUDIA, ARE YOU GOING TO EAT THAT?
- I'LL EAT IT IF SHE DOESN'T WANT IT. - NO WAY. THIS IS MINE!
CLAUDIA, IS SOMETHING WRONG?
I DON'T USUALLY LIKE MIXING FRUIT AND DAIRY.
Mother: SINCE WHEN?
SHE'S CRAZY ABOUT CARROTS, THOUGH.
HEY, JAMESTER, YOU WANT AN EXTRA CHERRY OR TWO?
OH, YOU BET!
Mother: THAT'S ENOUGH. WE DON'T WANT A REPLAY
OF THE PINEAPPLE UPSIDE-DOWN CAKE, REMEMBER?
Steven: MOM, WE'RE EATING.
DON'T FORGET TO LOAD THE DISHWASHER, CLAUDIA.
I KNEW IT. I JUST KNEW YOU'D CHANGE YOUR MIND.
CLAUD, IF WE LEFT NOW, WE'D BE TRAITORS OR SOMETHING.
TRAITORS ARE PEOPLE WHO SACRIFICE THEIR COUNTRY
AND COUNTRYMEN FOR THE SAKE OF THEIR OWN SELFISH GAIN.
WE ARE NOT TRAITORS, JAMIE. WE WERE GOING TO RUN AWAY!
HOW COME YOU WANT TO LEAVE IF THEY'RE BEING SO NICE?
I MEAN, BANANA SPLITS AND TV-- WHAT MORE DO YOU WANT?
I TOLD YOU, JAMIE-- I WANT TO BE APPRECIATED.
I APPRECIATE YOU, CLAUD.
I JUST DON'T WANT TO RUN AWAY.
( sighs )
HEY, JAMIE, COME HERE!
RIGHT ON THE OLD MAN.
( sighs )
Steve: HOW COME IT HAS TO BE AUNT WEASEL?
- YEAH. - IT'S HAZEL, NOT WEASEL.
SO THAT'S WHY WE HAD BANANA SPLITS LAST NIGHT--
'CAUSE YOU'RE DUMPING US AT AUNT HAZEL'S
FOR THE THREE-DAY WEEKEND.
JAMIE, WE'RE NOT DUMPING YOU ANYWHERE.
YOUR FATHER AND I WOULD LIKE TO SPEND A FEW DAYS
JUST WITH EACH OTHER.
WHY?
AUNT WEAS-- HAZEL WAS GENEROUS ENOUGH
TO INVITE YOU ALL TO HER HOME.
I'M SURPRISED TO HEAR YOU SAY SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
YEAH, WELL, I WAS SURPRISED TO GET BANANA SPLITS.
WE NEVER HAD THEM BEFORE.
WE NEVER HAD TO STAY AT AUNT HAZEL'S, EITHER.
OH, FOR HEAVEN SAKE. YOU'RE NOT BEING SENT TO PRISON.
WE'RE GOING TO BE LATE, JAMIE.
YEAH, YOU BETTER GET A MOVE ON. YOU DON'T WANT TO MISS THE BUS.
Father: WE'LL TALK ABOUT THIS LATER.
YEAH, DAD. LATER.
THOSE BANANA SPLITS WERE A SET-UP,
LIKE A PREMEDICATED CRIME.
THE WORD IS PREMEDITATED. AND I COULDN'T AGREE MORE.
LAST NIGHT'S ACTIVITIES DID NOT IN ANY WAY REPRESENT
GENUINE CONCERN FOR US.
SO WHAT'S IT GOING TO BE, JAMIE?
A LIFE OF SCORN AND DEGRADATION
OR MYSTERY AND ADVENTURE?
YOU HAVE TWO MINUTES, JAMIE.
YOUR TRUMPET CASE IS STILL PACKED.
TO THE GREAT OUTDOORS
AND A LIFE OF MYSTERY AND ADVENTURE.
ALL RIGHT, JAMIE!
( loud whisper ) DON'T FORGET YOUR MONEY!
WHAT?
DON'T FORGET YOUR MONEY!
WHAT-WHAT- WHAT MONEY?
- HUH? - JUST KIDDING.
Driver: STEP RIGHT UP.
- MORNING, CLAUD. - HERBERT.
- JAMIE. - HEY, HERB.
MUSIC LESSONS TODAY, HUH?
- YES! - HEY, BRUCE.
HEY, JAMIE.
YOU KNOW WHAT THEY SAY-- PRACTICE MAKES PERFECT.
NEVER HELPED ME ANY.
Herb: ALL RIGHT, EVERYBODY, HERE WE ARE.
HAVE A GOOD ONE.
Boy: BYE, HERBIE.
- Girl: HAVE A NICE DAY, HERB. - BYE-BYE.
ALL RIGHT, IS THAT EVERYBODY?
( siren wails )
- Man: GET A MOVE ON, HERB! - HOLD YOUR HORSES.
MY CLUBS ARE GETTING COLD!
I'M COMING.
I'M JUST CLEANING UP THE MESS.
Herb: THE WAY YOU PLAY GOLF, BOB,
I THOUGHT YOU'D BE GLAD TO PUT IT OFF AS LONG AS POSSIBLE.
WHAT'S THE RUSH?
WE'RE PROBABLY GONNA HAVE TO TEE OFF LATE.
I'M AN ACTOR. I HAVE TO MAKE A STOP--
WE'RE NOT STOPPING ANYWHERE.
( no sound )
( siren wailing )
ISN'T THIS GREAT?
YEAH. WHICH WAY ARE THE WOODS?
- CLAUDIA? - COME ON.
Jamie: DO YOU KNOW WHERE WE ARE?
NOT EXACTLY.
BUT YOU KNOW WHERE WE'RE GOING, RIGHT?
NOT FOR SURE.
ALL RIGHT, WE'RE HEADED SOUTH.
IN BACK OF US IS NORTH, TO THE RIGHT IS WEST
AND TO THE LEFT OF US IS EAST.
I THINK THE WOODS ARE THAT WAY.
THANK YOU, DANIEL BOONE.
HEY, WAIT A MINUTE.
I JUST TOLD YOU THE WOODS ARE THAT WAY.
( horns honking )
I'M GETTING A LITTLE HUNGRY, JAMIE.
ARE YOU HUNGRY?
WHAT'S WRONG?
UH, NOTHING. I'M JUST HUNGRY. ARE YOU HUNGRY?
HOW LONG HAVE WE BEEN GONE, ANYHOW?
- JAMIE? - YEAH?
YOU KNOW HOW MOM ALWAYS HAS A CUP OF COFFEE AT NOON?
UH-HUH. WHY?
( sighs )
I LEFT THE NOTE INSIDE HER COFFEE FILTERS.
IT'S 12:05.
"AND DO NOT UNDER ANY CIRCUMSTANCES CALL THE F.B.I. OR S.W.A.T. TEAMS
OR ANY SUCH THING.
WE'RE FINE. WE'RE UNDER OUR OWN STEAM
AND WE'LL COME HOME WHEN WE'RE GOOD AND READY."
IT'S TYPED, BUT SHE HANDWROTE HER NAME AND JAMIE'S...
WITHOUT THE WORD "LOVE."
YES, I'VE CALLED THEM. THEY'RE ON THEIR WAY.
I KNOW THAT.
IS THAT DAD? I NEED TO TALK TO HIM.
WELL, JUST GET HERE AS SOON AS YOU CAN.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
YOUR FATHER AND THE POLICE WILL BE HERE ANY MINUTE.
WHAT?
CLAUDIA AND JAMIE HAVE RUN AWAY.
OH, COOL.
Jamie: ALL I'M SAYING IS NEXT TIME, DON'T GET A CHEESEBURGER.
I DON'T LIKE PLAIN HAMBURGERS.
THEN GET SOMETHING ELSE.
IF YOU KEEP BUYING SPECIALTY ITEMS, WE'RE GONNA BE BROKE.
YOU KNOW, IT'S GONNA BE COLD IN THE WOODS.
WHY DIDN'T WE PACK SLEEPING BAGS?
'CAUSE YOU KNOW, BURYING OURSELVES UNDER LEAVES AND MULCH,
OR WHATEVER THE NATIVE AMERICANS USED,
IS NOT GONNA KEEP US VERY WARM.
MOST NATIVE AMERICANS SLEPT UNDER HIDES, JAMIE,
OFTEN INSIDE TENTS.
WE, HOWEVER, ARE NOT NATIVE AMERICANS
NOR ARE WE SLEEPING IN THE WOODS.
WE WILL BE SLEEPING IN THE METROPOLITAN MUSEUM.
BALONEY, WE WILL.
YOU SAID WE WERE GOING TO HAVE AN ADVENTURE AND THAT'S WHAT WE'RE GONNA DO.
WE'RE GONNA GO TO THE TOP OF A MOUNTAIN
WHERE MAYBE I CAN BE A HERO OR SOMETHING AND RESCUE A STRANDED HIKER.
YOU SAID WE WERE GONNA LIVE OFF OF SPRING WATER,
WILD BERRIES, AND BEAR MEAT!
I NEVER SAID ANYTHING ABOUT BEAR MEAT, JAMIE.
YOU NEVER SAID ANYTHING ABOUT
SLEEPING IN SOME DUSTY MUSEUM EITHER.
I'M NOT SLEEPING HERE, CLAUD! NO WAY!
FINE. GO WHERE YOU WANT--
THE WOODS, BACK TO THE PLACE WE USED TO CALL HOME.
FOR THAT MATTER, YOU CAN GO LIVE WITH BRUCE
AND LOSE WHAT LITTLE I.Q. YOU'VE AMASSED THUS FAR.
I MADE A DECISION AND I'M GONNA STICK TO IT.
WELL, I GUESS I'LL BE SEEING YOU THEN.
I GUESS.
GOING SOMEWHERE?
I NEEDED TO CHECK YOUR COMPASS.
WELL, WHERE MY COMPASS GOES, I GO.
( sighs )
LOOK, JAMIE, I KNOW IT'S NOT THE WOODS,
BUT IF YOU JUST THINK OF A MUSEUM
AS A PLACE WITH SOUVENIRS
FROM EVERYWHERE IN THE WORLD,
I'M SURE WE'LL HAVE AN ADVENTURE.
I PROMISE WE WILL.
YOU CAN'T EVER TELL ANYBODY I DID THIS.
WHY WOULD YOU WANT TO BE HERE?
TO LEARN SOMETHING NEW EVERY DAY--
IT'S AN IMPORTANT PART OF LIFE, JAMIE.
BESIDES, WE'LL BE SURROUNDED BY BEAUTIFUL THINGS.
MOM'S GOT THAT QUILT HANGING UP ON THE WALL.
DON'T YOU LIKE THAT?
TWO, PLEASE. WE'RE MEETING OUR MOTHER INSIDE.
- WHAT? - THE MONEY, JAMIE.
THERE'S AN ADMISSION FEE.
I'M NOT PAYING A DIME--
JAMIE...
MONEY.
PEOPLE ARE WAITING.
TRUMPET CASE.
BOOK BAG. COME ON!
COAT.
WELL, WHAT DID YOU GIVE THEM OUR STUFF FOR?
DAD'S POCKETKNIFE IS IN THERE.
THE ONE WITH THE SCISSORS AND NAIL CLIPPERS?
I THOUGHT I WAS GONNA NEED IT.
FOR A MANICURE IN THE WOODS?
MY P.J.s WERE IN THERE TOO, YOU KNOW?
RELAX. WE'LL GET THEM LATER.
PEOPLE DON'T CARRY STUFF AROUND MUSEUMS.
IT'S NOT ALLOWED.
WONDER WHERE THE RESTROOMS ARE.
I DON'T HAVE TO GO.
NEITHER DO I.
HERE. TAKE THESE.
OH, HERE THEY ARE.
THIS IS WHERE I'LL HIDE AND...
THAT'S WHERE YOU'LL HIDE
WHEN THEY CLOSE AND OPEN THE MUSEUM.
YOU'LL GO IN A STALL AND STAND ON IT.
STAND ON WHAT?
YOU STAND ON THE TOILET, PUT YOUR HEAD DOWN,
KEEP THE STALL DOOR SLIGHTLY OPEN.
WHEN THE GUARDS CHECK THE BATHROOM, THEY LOOK UNDER THE DOORS FOR FEET.
WELL, HOW DO YOU KNOW THAT?
SAW IT IN THE MOVIES.
WE'LL STAY HIDDEN FOR 15 MINUTES.
BY THEN THE GUARDS SHOULD BE GONE.
WE'LL COME OUT-- SIMPLE.
ACT NATURAL. HERE'S A GUARD COMING NOW.
LOST?
WELL, ACTUALLY--
ARRANGE TO MEET YOUR PARENTS
AND NOW YOU CAN'T LOCATE THEM?
THEY WON'T BE HAPPY WHEN THEY FIND YOU, YOU KNOW.
THEY'LL ACT HAPPY BUT I GUARANTEE YOU'LL BE PUNISHED.
WE'RE HERE WITH OUR COUSINS,
AND THEY'RE USING THE LAVATORIES,
AND WE WERE JUST, UM,
FAMILIARIZING OURSELVES WITH WHAT EXHIBIT'S WHERE
SO WE COULD MAXIMIZE OUR EXPERIENCE FOR OUR LIMITED TIME.
SHE'S A TIME-SAVER.
THE TRUTH IS, WE HAVE TO BE GOING.
BEFORE YOU KNOW IT, THE MUSEUM WILL BE CLOSED
AND THEN WE'D BE LOCKED IN AND WE CAN'T HAVE THAT
WE HAVE TO GO HOME AND COOK FOR OUR FAMILY OF EIGHT.
BYE!
Claudia: THIS IS FABULOUS, ISN'T IT?
DIDN'T I TELL YOU THIS PLACE WAS GREAT?
JUST A LOT OF OLD PAINTINGS AND STUFF.
JAMIE, THIS ISN'T STUFF. THIS IS ART.
ALL RIGHT, WHERE ARE WE GOING?
ONCE WE FIND A PLACE TO SLEEP,
WE'LL SCATTER OUR STUFF IN DIFFERENT LOCATIONS.
THAT WAY IF THE MUSEUM GUARDS FIND ONE THING,
THEY WON'T FIND THEM ALL.
THEY GOT BEDS IN AN ART MUSEUM?
BEDS ARE FURNITURE, JAMIE, AND FURNITURE'S ART.
WHY DIDN'T I KNOW THAT?
JAMIE?
JAMIE!
NOW THESE GUYS GOT THE RIGHT IDEA.
THIS IS WHAT WE SHOULD BE DOING.
PLEASE, JAMIE. WILL YOU FORGET ABOUT THE WOODS?
YOU KNOW, IF THAT ADMISSION FEE THING STARTS CUTTING INTO OUR FUNDS,
I KNOW A WAY WE CAN GET MORE MONEY.
- OH, YES? - YEAH!
I COULD PLAY CARDS WITH THAT GUARD WE MET-- MORRIS.
I BET I COULD WIN A WHOLE LOT OFF OF HIM.
JAMIE, IF YOU PLAY CARDS WITH THE GUARD,
HE'LL REMEMBER YOU.
IF THE AUTHORITIES COME LOOKING FOR US,
HE'D DESCRIBE YOU TO A TEE.
THEY'D GET FINGERPRINTS FROM THE MONEY HE WON FROM YOU
AND THEN WE'D BE IN HANDCUFFS BEFORE YOU COULD COUNT TO THREE.
NOW JUST LOOK AT THIS PAINTING, JAMIE.
ISN'T IT BEAUTIFUL?
YEAH. TERRIFIC.
COME ON.
THIS IS PERFECT, ISN'T IT?
THIS IS WHERE WE'LL SLEEP.
BUT IT SAYS NOT TO STAND ON THE PLATFORM.
DOES IT SAY NOT TO RUN AWAY FROM HOME
AND SLEEP IN MUSEUMS?
AS A MATTER OF FACT, IT SAYS TO SLEEP IN THE WOODS.
JAMES LINCOLN KINCAID, GET OFF THAT BED!
THEY'RE GOING TO BE CLOSING SOON.
LET'S GO.
( door opens )
( door closes )
( whispering ) BREATHE, CLAUDIA.
( door locking )
JAMIE?
I'M HUNGRY.
PRICE OF ADVENTURE.
LET'S GET OUR THINGS.
NO EATING IN BED.
CLAUDIA.
BOO!
GIVE ME THAT.
DIDN'T PUT A FLASHLIGHT ON THE LIST.
- I THOUGHT WE WERE GOING TO BE IN THE WOODS-- - "IN THE WOODS."
"STATE BED.
SCENE OF THE ALLEGED MURDER OF AMY ROBSART,
FIRST WIFE OF LORD ROBERT DUDLEY."
HEY!
A GIRL GOT KILLED IN THAT BED.
( sighs )
THAT'S A PORTRAIT OF LADY SCOFIELD.
SHE WAS MARRIED TO A KING WHO CUT HER HEAD OFF.
THEY SAY SHE WANDERED AROUND THE CASTLE
WITH HER HEAD UNDER HER ARM.
COOL.
UH, I DIDN'T BRUSH MY TEETH.
YOU WILL TOMORROW.
WE'D BETTER GET SOME SLEEP
IF WE'RE GOING TO WAKE UP
BEFORE THE GUARDS COME BACK.
YOU KNOW WHAT? WE HAVE TO FIND A REAL RESTAURANT TOMORROW, TOO.
I FIGURE IF WE ORDER ONE HUMONGO MEAL AND SHARE IT,
WE'LL SAVE MONEY THAT WAY.
AND YOU KNOW WHAT ELSE I THINK?
THEY COULD NEVER GET MY FINGERPRINTS FROM MY MONEY.
WHAT?
YOU SAID THE AUTHORITIES WOULD GET MY FINGERPRINTS FROM THE MONEY
THAT GUARD WOULD WIN FROM ME,
BUT THEY NEVER WOULD BECAUSE HE'D NEVER WIN.
WHY NOT?
BECAUSE I CHEAT.
YOU WHAT?
THAT'S HOW COME I'M SO RICH.
YOU CHEAT WHEN YOU PLAY CARDS WITH BRUCE?
YEAH.
BRUCE IS YOUR BEST FRIEND.
I KNOW.
IT'S KIND OF CREEPY IN HERE,
DON'T YOU THINK?
JAMIE,
I KNOW A LOT OF THINGS ARE SCARY IN HERE,
BUT YOU HAVE TO REMEMBER
THAT IT'S ALL JUST MANUFACTURED
AND THAT NOTHING IN HERE IS ALIVE
OR CAN HURT YOU OR AFFECT YOU IN ANY WAY.
AND IF YOU REALLY CAN'T SLEEP,
WE CAN SIT UP AND TALK FOR A WHILE
UNTIL YOU FEEL RELAXED, OKAY?
JAMIE?
'NIGHT, JAMIE.
( gasps )
JAMIE!
JAMIE, WAKE UP. IT'S 9:00.
MY ALARM DIDN'T GO OFF.
WHERE ARE WE?
IN A BED WHERE A MURDER TOOK PLACE
AND ANOTHER ONE'S GOING TO IF YOU DON'T GET UP AND PUT YOUR CLOTHES ON.
( footsteps approach )
QUICK, JAMIE, GET UNDER THE COVERS!
- Man: HEY, JERRY! - WHAT?
COME AND CHECK THE BOTTICELLI!
WHAT'S WRONG WITH IT?
I THINK IT'S COMING OFF THE WALL.
YEAH, LIKE THE RUBENS LAST WEEK.
JAMIE, WE GOT TO GET OUT OF HERE!
SO WHO WON THE GAME LAST NIGHT?
Man: WE DID, MAN. IT WAS GREAT.
OVER HERE.
Man: AHEM.
THE MUSEUM OPENS AT 10:00,
SO HIDE UNTIL 10:15.
THAT'S WHEN REGULAR PEOPLE LIKE US WILL BE ALL OVER.
THAT'S WHEN TO COME OUT AND MEET ME ON THE FRONT STEPS.
HERE.
I DON'T WANT TO BRUSH MY TEETH. I WANT TO EAT.
EAT SOME TOOTHPASTE FIRST.
AS SOON AS THE MUSEUM OPENS, WE'LL GET SOME FOOD,
ALL RIGHT?
( thudding )
WHERE DID YOU COME FROM?
UH, MY MOTHER ALWAYS SAID HEAVEN,
BUT THEN YOU HEAR ALL THIS STUFF ABOUT CABBAGES AND THE STORK.
OH, NO! IT'S MORRIS.
THIS A SCHOOL HOLIDAY?
NO, SIR. BUT I LEFT MY VIOLIN CASE IN THERE.
AND IT'S MY MUSIC DAY TODAY
AND MY MOM'S WAITING IN THE CAR OUT THERE.
WHERE IS IT?
- WHERE'S WHAT? - YOUR VIOLIN CASE.
SEE, WE THOUGHT SHE LEFT IT INSIDE,
BUT IT TURNS OUT IT'S AT HOME.
AND MOM'S GONNA HAVE A COW. SO SEE YA.
WHAT'S YOUR NAMES?
UH, HIS NAME'S RALPH.
AND HER NAME'S EMILY! BYE!
THERE YOU GO.
WE GOT TO BUY SOME MORE FOOD FOR TONIGHT.
AFTER ALL OF THAT, YOU'RE GOING TO BE HUNGRY?
Man: PICK UP 17.
SOME COOKIES AND MORE CHIPS.
YEAH.
AND SOME FRUIT.
MMM. CAKE. YEAH. DEFINITELY CAKE.
FRUIT!
RODENTS EAT FRUIT, YOU KNOW.
THANK YOU.
JAMIE.
WHAT?
LET'S GO.
LEAVE IT, JAMIE.
I SAID LEAVE IT.
IF WE WERE IN THE WOODS, NO ONE WOULD SEE US AT ALL.
WRONG, EINSTEIN. IF WE WERE IN THE WOODS,
WE'D BE FROZEN SOLID.
AND IN ADDITION TO THAT, WE'D BE COMPLETELY AND TOTALLY DEAD.
NOW COME ON.
GREAT. NOW IT'S GONNA TAKE US HOURS TO GET BACK IN.
BALONEY.
WE'RE NOT GOING TO WAIT
AND WE'RE NOT GOING TO PAY. COME ON.
EXCUSE ME.
I'M ON A FIELD TRIP WITH A BUNCH OF STUDENTS WAY BACK THERE.
WE'RE HERE TO APPRECIATE FINE ART,
BUT ON ACCOUNT OF MY LEG BEING BROKE IN 10 PLACES,
MY TEACHER, MRS. HINEBURGER, WANTED TO KNOW
IF IT WAS OKAY BY YOU IF I WENT IN AND SAT DOWN
'CAUSE I CAN'T STAND FOR LONG PERIODS OF TIME.
AND, UH, THIS IS EVELYN, OUR STUDENT AIDE.
SHE CAME WITH ME BECAUSE I MIGHT BE A LITTLE IRRESPONSIBLE.
YOUR LEG WAS BROKE IN 10 PLACES?
IT WAS AN AWESOME BIKE ACCIDENT.
HEY, I STILL HAVE THE PIN. WANT TO SEE?
NO, THAT'S FINE. YOU CAN GO IN.
IF THERE'S ANY PROBLEM AT THE DOOR,
JUST TELL THEM CORA SAID IT'S OKAY.
THANKS.
HEY, DO YOU THINK SOMEBODY DIED?
MAYBE THEY'RE INTERVIEWING A GREAT ARTIST.
MAYBE A GREAT ARTIST DIED.
Man: EXCUSE US, PLEASE.
EXCUSE US. THANK YOU.
SORRY. BUT...
( sniffs ) EW. FRUITY.
IT WOULD HAVE BEEN YUCKY ON YOUR SHOE.
YES, I SEE WHAT YOU MEAN.
SOMEBODY HERE HAS VERY BAD MANNERS.
DO I MAKE YOU NERVOUS?
NO, MA'AM. I HAVE A SISTER.
I'M USED TO WEIRD STUFF.
I MEAN, YOU'RE NOT SO BAD.
WELL, THANKS.
PARKS.
ARE YOU HERE TO SEE THE SCULPTURE?
UH, I GUESS SO.
WELL, I HOPE YOU LIKE IT.
I THINK YOU WILL.
WHAT SCULPTURE?
I DON'T KNOW.
LET'S FIND OUT.
THE EXPERTS CAN'T AGREE.
IT'S EITHER AN EARTH-SHATTERING DISCOVERY
OR AN ABSOLUTE PHONY.
WELL, IF IT IS BY MICHELANGELO, IT WOULD BE WORTH MILLIONS.
HEY, WHO'S MIKE D. ANGELO?
MICHELANGELO. DON'T YOU KNOW ANYTHING?
IT SAYS HERE THAT NO ONE KNOWS FOR SURE WHO MADE THIS STATUE.
IT'S A REAL MYSTERY.
THE MYSTERY IS
WHY WE'RE STANDING IN THIS LINE.
SHH.
Woman: PLEASE KEEP MOVING, LADIES AND GENTLEMEN.
I DIDN'T KNOW IT WOULD BE SO BEAUTIFUL.
IT'S MORRIS! DUCK!
WHEW.
JAMIE... LOOK.
Woman: PLEASE MOVE THROUGH.
( whispering ) WE CAN COME BACK LATER.
WE HAVE TO BE MORE CAREFUL NOW
ABOUT THE GUARDS AND TALKING TO STRANGERS.
NOW THAT WE HAVE A JOB TO DO,
WE MIGHT BE HERE LONGER THAN I PLANNED.
WHAT JOB DO WE HAVE TO DO?
OUR JOB, LITTLE BROTHER,
IS TO PERFORM A SERVICE FOR MANKIND,
TO REVEAL THE ABSOLUTE AND IRREFUTABLE TRUTH.
DO YOU KNOW WHAT THAT TRUTH IS, JAMIE?
THAT YOU HAVE A WEIRD PERSONALITY?
THE TRUTH IS, THAT SCULPTURE,
THAT PERFECT MASS OF HANDCRAFTED STONE,
IS EITHER THE WORK OF THE GREAT ARTIST MICHELANGELO
OR IT ISN'T.
THERE'S NO IN BETWEEN.
I'M GOING TO SOLVE THAT MYSTERY, JAMIE,
AND YOU'RE GOING TO HELP ME.
I FOUND IT, JAMIE.
NO WAY!
WHAT WE SAW--
WHAT WE SAW ON THE BOTTOM OF THE STATUE
WAS MICHELANGELO'S STONEMASON'S MARK.
EVERY SCULPTURE HE MADE
HAD IT STAMPED ON IT SOMEWHERE.
I LOOKED THROUGH A THOUSAND BOOKS TO FIND IT.
SO WHAT YOU'RE TELLING ME...
IS THE ANGEL IS WORTH MILLIONS?
NO, JAMIE. THIS ISN'T ABOUT MONEY. THIS IS ABOUT ART.
AND ART IS THE MAGIC THAT COMES FROM GREATNESS.
SO IF MICHELANGELO REALLY DID CARVE THE ANGEL,
THEN THAT ANGEL'S MAGIC TOO.
Claudia: THAT'S RIGHT, MR. JORDAN.
I'M SURE THIS IS A FINDING OF REAL SIGNIFICANCE--
A REAL BREAKTHROUGH--
AND I'D LIKE TO MEET AS SOON AS POSSIBLE
TO DISCUSS THE MATTER.
TOMORROW AT 4:00?
YES. I THINK I CAN BE AVAILABLE THEN.
YES. AND THANK YOU.
THIS IS HISTORY IN THE MAKING, JAMIE.
TOMORROW, I SHALL MEET
WITH THE CURATOR OF THE METROPOLITAN MUSEUM
TO DISCUSS THE LEGITIMACY OF MY FINDINGS.
JAME, THIS IS TRULY FANTASTIC.
Claudia: I BET IF MICHELANGELO DID MAKE THAT ANGEL,
HE CARVED IT FOR SOMEONE SPECIAL,
PROBABLY A ROYAL PRINCE OR SOMETHING,
FOR A WEDDING PRESENT.
YEAH, WELL, I BET HE MADE HER FOR AN ANGEL STORE.
THEY PROBABLY HAD 'EM IN THOSE DAYS.
I DON'T THINK SO, JAMIE.
YOU WANT ME TO TAKE A BATH IN THIS?
ABSOLUTELY.
HEY.
WHAT'S THIS?
WE'RE RICH, CLAUD!
THIS FOUNTAIN IS FILLED WITH MONEY!
THAT MONEY'S NOT OURS ANY MORE
THAN THE MONEY YOU CHEAT FROM BRUCE IS YOURS, JAMIE.
I GUESS NOT.
( water splashes )
WHY DO PEOPLE THROW MONEY INTO FOUNTAINS ANYWAY?
TO MAKE A WISH.
YEAH, WELL, I WISH WE DIDN'T HAVE TO TAKE A BATH IN THAT FOUNTAIN.
AND I WISH YOU'D JUST GET IN.
WE HAVE TO LOOK OUR BEST FOR TOMORROW'S MEETING, JAMIE.
BALONEY. YOU HAVE TO LOOK YOUR BEST.
I'M GONNA BE DOWN THE STREET AT THE ARCADE.
BALONEY. YOU'RE GONNA BE MY LOOKOUT, JAMIE.
COME ON. HERE'S SOME SOAP FROM HOME.
LET'S GET IN.
HERE. I COULD FREEZE IN THERE, YOU KNOW.
THEN WE'LL BOTH FREEZE. COME ON.
( sighs )
SEE? IT'S NOT SO BAD.
HOW MANY PEOPLE GET TO BATHE
IN A REAL LIVE FOUNTAIN?
YOU REALIZE THIS IS A UNIQUE EXPERIENCE, DON'T YOU?
YEAH, I GUESS SO.
YOU KNOW WHAT I REALLY WISH?
THAT WE COULD KEEP ALL THIS MONEY?
JUST WASH, JAMIE.
- YOU WASH. - JAMIE!
- STOP THAT! - YOU STOP THAT!
NO!
STOP THAT!
DID PAPA KINCAID EVER TELL YOU
YOU HAD A GOOD LUCK CHARM?
UH-HUH.
WHY?
WELL, HE SAID MINE WAS AN ANGEL.
CLAUD? YOU IN THERE?
CLAUDIA?
( door closes )
( TV playing softly )
CLAUD?
IS THAT YOU?
Man: HEY, THIS IS ABOUT THE MUSEUM.
TURN IT UP, WILL YOU?
Female anchor: ...has arisen from the belief
that it may be the work
of the Italian Renaissance master Michelangelo.
The statue was auctioned anonymously,
but is now believed to have come from
the collection of Mrs. Basil E. Frankweiler,
who currently resides in Nielsen Heights.
Now back to the newsroom.
And on the local scene today, the Kincaid family,
whose children have been missing
for the last three days,
held a press conference today
appealing for their safe return.
We'd just like to say that...
if someone's taken our children,
please let them go.
And, uh...
Claudia and Jamie,
if you ran away like your letter says...
please come home.
We're having a very hard time without you.
HOPE THOSE KIDS ARE OKAY, HUH?
Woman: CHILDREN, CHILDREN, IT'S TIME TO LEAVE...
- WHOA! - WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN?
I'VE BEEN LOOKING FOR YOU FOR AN HOUR.
YOU WEREN'T WHERE YOU WERE SUPPOSED TO BE.
AND YOUR VIOLIN CASE IS GONE.
AND ANYWAY, HOW COME YOU'RE WEARING ALL THIS STUFF?
IT DOESN'T BELONG TO YOU.
NO, BUT YOU DO.
JAMIE, WE HAVE TO PREPARE FOR THE MEETING.
NOT ANOTHER BATH.
Claudia: SO I COULDN'T USE THE BATHROOM
BECAUSE IT HAD REPAIR PEOPLE IN IT
AND THE ONLY OTHER ROOM THAT WASN'T LOCKED WAS LOST AND FOUND
WHICH, BELIEVE ME, WAS SERENDIPITOUS
BECAUSE I NEEDED SOMETHING TO WEAR FOR THE MEETING TODAY.
THEN I WENT TO PUT MY TOOTHBRUSH AWAY.
THE CLEANING CREW WAS ABOUT TO COME IN SO I GRABBED MY VIOLIN CASE
AND THAT'S WHEN I SAW YOU... LUCKILY.
WHAT?
I SAW MOM AND DAD ON T.V. TODAY.
YOU WANT TO GO HOME, DON'T YOU?
I KIND OF GOT THE SHIVERS, AND I ACHE A LITTLE TOO.
JAMIE, IF WE GO HOME BEFORE THE MYSTERY IS SOLVED,
THEY STILL WON'T APPRECIATE ME.
AND ON TOP OF EVERYTHING ELSE,
THEY'LL BE FURIOUS WITH US.
HERE. TAKE THIS.
IT WILL MAKE YOU BETTER.
I'M NOT THIRSTY.
FINE. I ADMIT IT.
I'M A LITTLE WORRIED ABOUT YOU BEING SICK,
AND I KNOW YOU WANT TO GO HOME
BUT YOU CAN'T GO HOME,
BECAUSE I DON'T WANT TO GO HOME YET
AND YOU CAN'T GO HOME WITHOUT ME, BECAUSE...
PAPA KINCAID SAYS ANGELS ARE YOUR GOOD LUCK CHARM, RIGHT?
HE SAID YOU'RE MINE.
PAPA KINCAID SAID I'M YOUR GOOD LUCK CHARM?
YEAH.
THE DAY YOU WERE BORN
AND ABOUT A MILLION TIMES AFTER THAT.
THINK STEVE HAS A GOOD LUCK CHARM?
ASK PAPA KINCAID AT THANKSGIVING.
WE SHOULD BE HOME BY THEN.
Man: AS I SAID, EVELYN,
WE ARE AWARE OF THE CLUE YOU SO CLEVERLY FOUND.
BUT I'M AFRAID WE STILL NEED MORE INFORMATION
BEFORE WE CAN AUTHENTICATE THE SCULPTURE'S HISTORY.
OH. HOW LONG DO YOU THINK THAT WOULD TAKE?
THAT'S DIFFICULT TO SAY.
EXPERTS IN THE FIELD HAVE LONG KNOWN
THAT MICHELANGELO DID NOT CARVE
ALL OF THE MARBLE BLOCKS THAT WERE QUARRIED FOR HIM AND BORE HIS MARK.
SOME EXPERTS EVEN BELIEVE THAT THE STONEMASON'S MARK IS COUNTERFEIT.
THEY DO?
THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR COMING IN, EVELYN.
A MUSEUM CANNOT SURVIVE WITHOUT THE PUBLIC'S SUPPORT.
YOU CAN BE PROUD OF YOURSELF.
YOU'RE AN OUTSTANDING CITIZEN.
IT WAS NICE MEETING YOU, MR. JORDAN.
THE PLEASURE WAS MINE, EVELYN.
JAMIE?
OVER HERE, CLAUD.
I DON'T FEEL SO GOOD.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING BACK HERE?
CAN WE GO HOME NOW?
I FEEL AWFUL.
Claudia: BUT WE CAN'T GO HOME NOW, JAMIE,
BECAUSE WE HAVEN'T ACCOMPLISHED ANYTHING.
WELL, WHAT DO YOU MEAN? WE DID SO.
WE HAD AN ADVENTURE LIKE YOU SAID WE WOULD,
AND WE SOLVED THE MYSTERY
AS GOOD AS ANY OF THE EXPERTS HAVE.
BESIDES, WE'VE BEEN TOGETHER FOR ALMOST THREE DAYS STRAIGHT
AND WE HAVEN'T KILLED EACH OTHER YET.
I DON'T GET YOU, CLAUD.
I MEAN, YOU GET STRAIGHT As,
BUT YOU WONDER WHERE THE PLUSSES ARE.
IT'S LIKE YOU WANT TO BE FLORENCE NIGHTINGOWN ALL THE TIME.
NIGHTINGALE, JAMIE.
HER NAME WAS FLORENCE NIGHTINGALE.
YOU KNOW WHAT I THINK?
HMM?
I THINK I'M GOING TO BE SICK.
WHAT DOES PERSPICACITY MEAN?
I DON'T KNOW.
MAN, IF CLAUDIA WERE HERE, SHE'D KNOW.
IF YOUR SISTER WERE HERE RIGHT NOW,
WE'D BE HOLDING HER IN OUR ARMS...
AND JAMIE TOO.
OKAY, UM...
WHAT DO YOU WANT TO DO ABOUT DINNER?
OH, I DON'T CARE.
DON'T WORRY, MOM. CLAUDIA'S SMART.
I NEVER HEARD YOU SAY THAT BEFORE.
UH, I MEAN, THEY'LL BE FINE,
THE TWO OF THEM TOGETHER.
I HOPE SO.
WHY WOULD THEY DO THIS?
CLAUDIA'S ALWAYS BEEN A DREAMER.
MAYBE SHE GOT SICK OF DOING THE LAUNDRY.
Claudia: LUCKY FOR US HE DIDN'T THROW UP ON HIS CLOTHES.
HE'S ASLEEP NOW,
BUT HE'S SWEATING PRETTY BAD.
HE SAID HE'D BE OKAY.
ANGEL...
I WISH YOU COULD HEAR ME.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO.
WHAT IF HE GETS REALLY SICK?
IF WE WERE HOME--
I KNOW I OUGHT TO TAKE HIM HOME.
I WISH YOU COULD HELP ME.
JAMIE?
( moaning )
WE'RE GOING HOME.
JAMIE? JAMIE?
HMM?
YOU SWEATED YOUR FEVER OUT.
WOW.
WOW WHAT?
NOTHING.
JUST, WOW.
UM...
CLAUDIA?
CAN WE MAKE A PHONE CALL?
MOM! IT'S JAMIE.
JAMIE?
COLLECT.
GIVE ME THAT. JAMIE?
HI, MOM. HOW ARE YOU DOING?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN, HOW AM I DOING?
JAMIE, ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
WHERE'S YOUR SISTER?
UH-HUH.
CLAUDIA WENT AHEAD. THEY'RE FINE.
THEY'RE GOING TO BREAKFAST.
GET YOUR FATHER. HE'S OUTSIDE.
JAMIE, WHY DID YOU DO THIS?
- DAD! PHONE! - WHAT DO YOU MEAN CLAUDIA WENT AHEAD?
UH-HUH? OH, JAMIE, DON'T HANG UP. YOUR FATHER'S COMING IN.
NOW DON'T HANG UP!
RALPH! RALPH!
HEY, BUDDY. ARE YOU REALLY OKAY?
RALPH! RALPH, COME ON!
GOOD.
OH, HEY, BY THE WAY, WHERE'S YOUR GLOVE OIL?
ON MY CLOSET FLOOR, I THINK.
UM, WE GOT TO GO, STEVE.
TELL MOM AND DAD WE HAVE LOTS OF MONEY. SEE YA.
- NO! NO! - STEVE!
HE SAID HE HAS MONEY, BUT HE HAD TO GO.
UH, HIS GLOVE OIL IS ON HIS CLOSET FLOOR.
HE SOUNDED GOOD, REALLY GOOD.
LOOK, JAMIE.
ALL OF THESE PEOPLE ARE HERE JUST BECAUSE OF THE ANGEL.
GOOD. MAYBE ONE OF THEM CAN FIGURE OUT WHO MADE HER.
NO, JAMIE. THAT'S OUR JOB.
Female reporter: Never before has an exhibit
attracted so much attention.
Ticket sales are at a record high
and the museum has hired extra staff for the event.
- but everyone here has-- - THEY'RE ON TV!
JAMIE AND CLAUDIA ARE ON TV!
- WHAT? - THEY'RE AT THE MUSEUM.
JAMIE AND CLAUDIA ARE AT THE MUSEUM! I SAW THEM JUST NOW!
HE WAS WEARING HIS JACKET AND SHE'S WEARING A HAT.
I'VE NEVER SEEN THAT HAT BEFORE.
HONEY, ARE YOU ABSOLUTELY CERTAIN IT WAS THEM?
ABSOLUTELY COMPLETELY CERTAIN. NOW LET'S GO.
UH, HONEY?
- WHAT? - HONEY!
WHAT?
YOU'RE NOT DRESSED.
I KNOW THAT.
WAIT IN THE CAR. I'LL BE RIGHT DOWN.
EXCUSE ME. CAN YOU HELP US?
THAT'S PART OF MY JOB.
WE'RE THE KINCAIDS.
OH, RALPH AND EVELYN.
- YES, THAT'S US. - NO, THAT'S THEM.
- RALPH AND EVELYN? - THE BOY IS RALPH, AND THE GIRL IS EVELYN.
THESE CHILDREN ARE NOT RALPH AND EVELYN.
AND I WANT TO KNOW RIGHT NOW, WHY YOU THINK THEY ARE?
OH, THAT'S EVELYN.
EXCUSE ME. I'M MR. JORDAN, THE MUSEUM'S CURATOR.
THIS IS OUR DAUGHTER.
WELL, YOU SHOULD BE VERY PROUD. SHE'S A VERY GROWN-UP LITTLE GIRL.
HAS ANYTHING HAPPENED TO EVELYN?
I'M EVELYN KINCAID AND THIS IS MY HUSBAND RALPH.
THESE ARE OUR CHILDREN WHO'VE BEEN MISSING FOR THREE DAYS, JAMES AND CLAUDIA.
WE SAW THEM ON THE TV NEWS RIGHT HERE IN YOUR MUSEUM
ONLY AN HOUR AGO.
OH. MORRIS, CALL THE POLICE AND ALERT THE STAFF.
MAYBE IF WE LOOK JUST ONE MORE TIME, JAMIE,
I MEAN, REALLY CAREFULLY LOOK AT HER
WHEN NO ONE ELSE IS AROUND.
HEY.
WHAT'S HE DOING?
OH, NOW WE'RE IN DEAD MEAT.
JORDAN? JORDAN? MORRIS HERE.
I FOUND A BOOK BAG.
IN HERE.
SO FAR THEY FOUND ONE BOOK BAG.
WHAT THAT MEANS EXACTLY, I DON'T KNOW,
BUT IN ANY CASE, THE POLICE ARE ON THEIR WAY.
IF THEY'RE IN HERE, WE'LL FIND THEM.
I'D LIKE TO SAY GOODBYE TO THE ANGEL.
WELL, I'D LIKE TO STAY OUT OF JAIL.
I'M SORRY, JAMIE.
WHAT FOR?
YOU DIDN'T GET TO RESCUE ANYBODY
OR BE A HERO OR ANYTHING.
THAT'S OKAY. THIS IS PRETTY GOOD TOO.
COME ON.
YOU KNOW WHAT I DON'T GET?
WHY WE DIDN'T SLEEP IN THE WOODS.
IF MRS. FRANKENSTEIN OWNED THE ANGEL IN THE FIRST PLACE,
WHY DIDN'T SHE KNOW WHETHER IT WAS REAL OR NOT?
GREAT. NOW YOUR FEVER'S BACK.
THE STATUE HAS NOTHING TO DO WITH FRANKENSTEIN
AND NO ONE KNOWS WHO OWNED HER.
( siren wailing )
OH, GREAT. THIS WAY.
WHEN I SAW MOM AND DAD ON TV YESTERDAY,
THE NEWS LADY SAID SOMETHING
ABOUT A WOMAN NAMED FRANKENSTEIN OWNING HER.
WHAT?
DID THEY SAY WHERE SHE LIVED, JAMIE?
UH, NIELSEN HEIGHTS.
AND YOU'RE SURE HER NAME WAS FRANKENSTEIN?
YUP. UH, NO,
BUT IT WAS LIKE FRANKENSTEIN.
WE GOT TO GET OUT OF HERE.
JAMIE, IT'S UP TO YOU.
IF YOU WANT TO GO HOME, YOU CAN TAKE THIS CAB
AND TELL THEM I'LL BE THERE SOON.
WELL, I KIND OF WANT TO KNOW ABOUT THE ANGEL, BUT...
JAMIE, I SHOULD PROBABLY TELL YOU SOMETHING.
ARE YOU KIDS COMING, OR WHAT?
JUST ONE MINUTE, PLEASE.
I DID WANT YOU TO COME BECAUSE OF YOUR MONEY
AND BECAUSE OF YOUR SENSE OF DIRECTION.
BUT I'M GLAD YOU CAME BECAUSE...
YOU'VE BEEN A GOOD FRIEND.
I DON'T MEAN TO PRESSURE YOU, JAMIE,
BUT THE GUY'S METER IS RUNNING.
UH, THEN WHAT ARE WE WAITING FOR?
LET'S GO.
NIELSEN HEIGHTS, PLEASE.
DO YOU KNOW HOW FAR THAT IS?
WE HAVE A RELATIVE THERE... DYING.
BETTER BE A RICH ONE.
DO WE HAVE MONEY TO PAY FOR THIS, JAMIE?
YEAH, BUT ONLY ONE WAY.
Morris: THEY SAID YOU DROVE THEM HERE ONE MORNING
TO PICK UP AN INSTRUMENT THEY LEFT BEHIND.
- I DID NO SUCH THING. - OF COURSE YOU DIDN'T.
THEN THEY PRETENDED TO WAVE AT YOU IN SOME PARKED CAR.
THEY WERE QUITE A TEAM-- LITTLE CRIMINALS IN THE MAKING.
I BEG YOUR PARDON.
THEN THEY TOLD A STORY
ABOUT HOW THEY REALIZED THEY LEFT IT AT HOME.
LEFT WHAT AT HOME?
THAT WOULD BE THE MUSICAL INSTRUMENT.
I BELIEVE IT WAS A VIOLIN.
SINCE WE HAVE A POSITIVE IDENTIFICATION,
I'D LIKE TO MOVE ON,
FILL IN THE DETAILS LATER.
THANK YOU, MORRIS.
NOW... MRS. SIMMS?
THAT BOY WAS SO BRAVE.
HE WAS?
THEY WANTED HIM TO STAY IN LINE WITH THE OTHERS,
BUT ON ACCOUNT OF HIS LEG BEING BROKEN IN SO MANY PLACES
AND THAT PAINFUL PIN STUCK RIGHT IN HIS BONE,
HE JUST MARCHED RIGHT UP AND SAID,
EVEN IF IT MEANT RIDICULE FROM HIS PEERS,
THAT HE JUST HAD TO SIT HIMSELF DOWN.
SO HE WOULDN'T HAVE TO STAND IN LINE.
WOULD HAVE BEEN CRUEL AND UNUSUAL PUNISHMENT.
I TOLD HIM AND THAT TEACHER'S AIDE TO GO RIGHT IN.
THAT SWEET GIRL NEVER LEFT HIS SIDE.
THEY'RE VERY DEVOTED TO ONE ANOTHER.
Claudia: SO IT'S DEFINITELY FRANK-SOMETHING?
DEFINITELY.
FRANKWEINGER, FRANKROLLINSTEIN...
THAT'S A FRANK-NAME.
BUT IT'S NOT IT.
FRANKWEED, FRANKWEILER--
THAT'S IT. THAT'S THE NAME.
FRANKWEILER.
IT CAN'T BE IT. THERE'S ONLY ONE
AND IT'S A MAN-- BASIL--
E. FRANKWEILER.
THAT'S IT, CLAUD. I'M POSITIVE.
COME ON. LET'S GO.
THIS IS IT. YOUR UNCLE MUST BE LOADED.
ACTUALLY, IT'S OUR AUNT
AND SHE'S COMFORTABLY WELL-OFF, THANK YOU.
UM... HOW MUCH DID YOU SAY THAT WAS?
THAT'LL BE $35.80.
DID YOU TIP THE DRIVER?
YEAH. 17.
17?
IT WAS ALL WE HAD. OH.
THERE'S A BUZZER ON THE GATE.
BUZZ IT.
OKAY.
NOW WOULD BE A GOOD TIME.
Man: How may I help you?
TELL MRS. BASIL E. FRANKWEILER
THAT CLAUDIA ELEANOR KINCAID
AND JAMES LINCOLN KINCAID
ARE SEEKING INFORMATION ABOUT THE ITALIAN RENAISSANCE.
( whispers ) PLEASE.
PLEASE.
( buzzing )
WE'RE BROKE NOW, YOU KNOW.
WE'RE PROBABLY STUCK HERE FOREVER.
YOU SHOULD FEEL RIGHT AT HOME.
THE PLACE LOOKS LIKE A MUSEUM.
I HOPE SHE'S AT HOME.
YEAH. I'M STARVING.
JAMIE, WE DIDN'T COME HERE TO EAT.
( bell tolling )
COME IN.
HI.
YOU PROBABLY DON'T KNOW THIS,
BUT YOUR BOSS HAS AN HONESTY PROBLEM.
SHE GAVE A SCULPTURE TO THE METROPOLITAN MUSEUM
AND NOW SHE'S DRIVING A LOT OF PEOPLE GOOFY,
INCLUDING MY SISTER HERE,
BECAUSE SHE WON'T--
SO YOU'RE THE RUNAWAY CHILDREN.
WE MIGHT BE, BUT WE MIGHT NOT.
MRS. BASIL E. FRANKWEILER, MAY I INTRODUCE
MISS CLAUDIA AND MASTER JAMES KINCAID?
HOW DO YOU DO?
WOULD YOU LIKE TO COME IN HERE WITH ME AND SIT DOWN?
BUT YOU CAN'T BE MRS. FRANKWEILER.
YOU'RE THE LADY FROM THE MUSEUM.
SO I AM,
AND YOU'RE THE BOY WHO WAS WATCHING OUT FOR MY WELFARE.
WAIT. THAT WAS THE DAY THE EXHIBIT OPENED.
- MM-HMM. - YEAH.
WHY WOULD YOU WANT TO GO TO THE MUSEUM TO SEE THE ANGEL?
YOU MUST HAVE SEEN THE ANGEL BEFORE.
SHE WANTED TO SAY GOODBYE.
WHY DON'T YOU SIT OVER THERE?
SO, TELL ME,
WHAT WERE YOU DOING IN THE MUSEUM THAT DAY?
- WE WERE-- - JUST VISITING.
OH? THREE DAYS AFTER YOU RAN AWAY?
WHAT WERE YOU DOING ALL THAT TIME?
WHO WAS LOOKING AFTER YOU?
IS YOUR BUTLER CALLING THE POLICE
WHILE YOU STALL US IN HERE?
OH, ABSOLUTELY NOT.
Claudia: MRS. FRANKWEILER,
WE'VE COME TO ASK YOU ABOUT THE ANGEL.
PEOPLE SAY IT'S THE WORK OF MICHELANGELO
AND THERE'S HIS MARK ON THE BOTTOM.
AND WE WANT TO KNOW,
DID HE REALLY CARVE THE ANGEL?
I SEE.
I'M SUPPOSED TO ANSWER YOUR QUESTIONS,
BUT THERE'S TO BE NO RECIPROCATION.
MM, PARDON?
YOU WON'T ANSWER MINE.
COME ON, CLAUD. LET'S GO. SHE--
I HAVE TO FIND OUT.
IT'S ALL BEEN WASTED OTHERWISE.
I NEED TO KNOW ABOUT THE ANGEL.
OH, WELL, NOW WE BOTH HAVE A SECRET.
VERY INTERESTING.
CLAUD, PLEASE.
I'M GOING TO DIE WITHOUT FOOD.
I HAVE FOOD, PLENTY OF FOOD.
AS A MATTER OF FACT, I THINK IT'S ALMOST LUNCHTIME.
WOULD YOU CARE TO JOIN ME?
- YOU BET! - NO. THANK YOU.
WE'LL FIND OUT ABOUT THE ANGEL, AND THEN WE'LL GO.
WAIT. I GOT AN IDEA.
IF YOU TELL US ABOUT THE ANGEL,
WE'LL TELL YOU WHERE WE'VE BEEN.
THAT WAY, WE'LL BE EVEN.
WE CAN EAT AND GO HOME.
- HOW'S THAT FOR A DEAL? - CLAUDIA?
OKAY, ON ONE CONDITION.
IF WE TELL YOU, YOU WON'T TELL ANYONE.
I HAVE A VERY HEALTHY REGARD FOR SECRETS
AND I SHALL RESPECT YOURS ACCORDINGLY.
IT'S A DEAL.
HOW DID YOU KNOW WHO WE ARE AND THAT WE'D RUN AWAY?
OH, I MANAGE TO KEEP UP WITH THE NEWS
DESPITE BEING A VIRTUAL RECLUSE.
YOU KNOW, YOU'VE CAUSED YOUR FAMILY CONSIDERABLE TROUBLE.
WE LEFT THEM A NOTE.
HECK, I EVEN CALLED THEM.
REALLY?
Claudia: DO YOU LIVE IN THIS HOUSE ALL ALONE?
APART FROM THE STAFF, YES.
IT'S KIND OF BIG FOR ONE OLD LADY.
JAMIE!
WELL, IT IS BIG,
OH, BUT I HAVE A LOT OF THINGS-- TOO MANY THINGS.
I OFTEN THINK OF GIVING THEM ALL AWAY.
BUT NOT THE ANGEL.
IF I'D OWNED THAT ANGEL,
I WOULD HAVE NEVER SOLD IT OR DONATED IT OR ANYTHING.
I WOULD HAVE CHERISHED IT FOREVER.
SHE IS VERY BEAUTIFUL, ISN'T SHE?
Jamie: WHAT'S ALL THIS?
THIS, JAMES, IS MY LIFE.
ALL MY YEARS OF RESEARCH INTO ART,
ANTIQUES, HISTORY, PEOPLE...
LIFE ITSELF--
IT'S ALL IN HERE,
FILED AWAY IN A SPECIAL ORDER
THAT ONLY MAKES SENSE TO ME.
THE SECRET OF THE ANGEL?
MM, THAT'S IN HERE TOO.
IN THIS ROOM, THIS IS WHERE YOU'LL FIND IT.
WAIT. WE'LL FIND IT?
MEANING, WE HAVE TO LOOK?
BY OURSELVES?
THAT WOULD TAKE FOR YEARS.
YOU HAVE ONE HOUR.
ONE HOUR?
THAT'S WHEN LUNCH WILL BE READY.
IF YOU'RE NOT SUCCESSFUL,
NO LUNCH, NO SECRET.
JUST A CALL TO YOUR PARENTS TO TELL THEM TO COME AND GET YOU.
PLAYING GAMES IS FUN, ISN'T IT?
GOOD LUCK.
WAIT. FIVE MINUTES OF PLANNING IS WORTH 15 MINUTES OF WORK.
WE'RE MAKING A LIST.
THE LIST OF SUBJECTS FOR WHICH WE'LL LOOK IS...
MICHELANGELO, ONE.
BUONARROTI, TWO.
WHAT'S THAT?
MICHELANGELO'S LAST NAME.
ANGEL, THREE.
AUCTION, FOUR.
METROPOLITAN MUSEUM, FIVE.
UH, ITALIAN RENAISSANCE?
SIX.
PAINTERS, SEVEN.
SCULPTURES, EIGHT, AND MARBLE, NINE.
MARBLE, NINE.
ROME, ITALY, AND FLORENCE, ITALY, 10 AND 11.
I'LL TAKE THE ODDS.
WHY DOESN'T THAT SURPRISE ME?
WAIT A MINUTE. THERE'S MORE ODDS THAN EVENS.
- SO I'LL TAKE THE EVENS. - TALK ABOUT WASTING TIME.
- TAKE THIS. - OKAY.
MRS. FRANKWEILER ASKS THAT I ADVISE YOU
YOU HAVE THREE QUARTERS OF AN HOUR REMAINING.
I SHALL RETURN AT THE HALF.
MRS. FRANKWEILER HAS ASKED ME TO ANNOUNCE
THE HALF HOUR.
- THIS IS WEIRD. - BUT WE FIT RIGHT IN.
COME ON, WE DON'T HAVE MUCH TIME. HURRY.
HMM.
YOU HAVE 15 MINUTES REMAINING.
GOOD LUCK.
I'M SORRY, JAMIE.
YOU MADE A GOOD LIST.
WE MADE THE LIST,
BUT TO QUOTE YOU, "WE'RE DEAD MEAT."
WE MIGHT AS WELL GO TELL MRS. FRANKWEILER.
I SUPPOSE.
YOU KNOW WHAT I THINK?
I THINK SHE HAD US ON A WILD GOOSE CHASE.
I'M NOT SURE THERE EVEN IS A FILE ON WHAT WE'RE LOOKING FOR.
IF YOU ASK ME,
ALL THIS STUFF IS ONE BIG PIECE OF BALONEY.
JAMIE, WHAT DID YOU SAY JUST NOW?
WHAT?
YOU SAID BALONEY.
ACTUALLY, YOU SAID BAH-LONEY--
BALONEY IS A WORD. I CAN SAY BALONEY.
OF COURSE YOU CAN SAY, JAMIE. OF COURSE IT'S A WORD.
IT'S A LUNCH MEAT...
AND IT'S A CITY IN ITALY.
- BALONEY? - BOLOGNA.
ONE OF THE LIBRARY BOOKS SAID SOMETHING ABOUT BOLOGNA.
HERE IT IS.
COME ON. OPEN IT.
AND AFTER ALL THIS, IT'S IN GREEK.
ITALIAN OR LATIN OR SOMETHING.
IT'S SOME KIND OF POEM, JAMIE.
- WELL, WHAT'S IT MEAN? - HOW SHOULD I KNOW?
HEY! THERE IT IS.
MY ANGEL.
AND AN AUTOGRAPH.
MICHELANGELO.
IT'S HIM. HIS SIGNATURE.
THAT PROVES IT, JAMIE.
SHE'S HIS. HE MADE HER.
HE DREW THIS, JAMIE, 400 YEARS AGO.
HE TOUCHED THIS.
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT. IT'S TRUE.
SHE'S NOT A FAKE.
SHE'S REAL. ANGEL.
( door opens )
WELL, MY DEARS, THE HOUR IS UP.
DO WE HAVE A RESULT?
YOU FOUND IT.
IN EUROPE AFTER THE WAR,
THERE WAS AN ITALIAN NOBLEMAN
WHOSE COMPANY I RATHER ENJOYED.
- WAS HE A PRINCE? - YES, HE WAS.
AND HE GAVE YOU THE ANGEL.
NO. HE GAVE ME MANY THINGS. AND HE COULD DO A LOT.
BUT HE WAS A VERY BAD POKER PLAYER.
YOU WON THE ANGEL IN A CARD GAME.
BUT THE QUESTION IS, DID SHE CHEAT?
ONLY PEOPLE WHO ARE VERY UNSURE
OF THEMSELVES CHEAT, JAMES.
THIS IS REALLY GOOD FOOD.
THANK YOU.
I THINK IT'S MY TURN TO ASK SOME QUESTIONS.
TELL ME, WHAT DID YOU LIKE BEST ABOUT RUNNING AWAY?
UM...
NOT HAVING A SCHEDULE, I GUESS.
YOU KNOW, LIKE, DO YOUR HOMEWORK,
TAKE YOUR SHOWER, BRUSH YOUR TEETH,
DO YOUR SIT-UPS.
WHAT ELSE?
WELL, AT HOME, I ALWAYS SEEM TO GET IT WRONG.
AND EVEN THOUGH SHE ONLY WANTED ME TO COME
BECAUSE OF MY MONEY,
THIS TIME I GOT IT RIGHT.
I KNOW.
CLAUDIA TREATED YOU AS AN EQUAL,
SO THAT GAVE YOU SELF-CONFIDENCE.
YEAH.
OKAY, CLAUDIA, YOU TELL ME NOW
WHAT DID YOU LIKE BEST ABOUT RUNNING AWAY?
DISCOVERING THE ANGEL.
I WANTED TO KNOW EVERYTHING ABOUT HER...
WHERE SHE CAME FROM, WHO THOUGHT OF HER,
WHO MADE HER.
I WANTED TO MAKE HER PART OF ME.
DID IT WORK?
I DON'T KNOW.
THERE'S ONE THING I'VE LEARNED IN MY LIFE--
I BELIEVE YOU SHOULD LEARN A NEW THING EVERY DAY.
I DON'T QUITE AGREE WITH THAT.
OH, I THINK LEARNING IS VERY IMPORTANT,
BUT I THINK FEELINGS MATTER JUST AS MUCH.
THAT'S WHAT THE ANGEL WAS TRYING TO TELL ME.
MAYBE.
YOU THINK YOU SHOULD RING YOUR PARENTS NOW?
YOU BET.
I GUESS SO.
THEY MUST BE VERY ANXIOUS, WANTING YOU BACK.
THE TELEPHONE IS RIGHT IN THERE.
IT'LL ALL BE OVER WHEN MOM AND DAD COME TO PICK US UP,
THE WHOLE ADVENTURE.
WE'LL GO HOME AND EVERYTHING WILL BE AS IT WAS BEFORE.
OH, NOT QUITE.
YOU STILL HAVE THE SECRET OF THE ANGEL
TO ALWAYS REMIND YOU OF THIS ADVENTURE
AND HOW IT'S CHANGED YOU INSIDE.
IF YOU FIND THE MEMORY FADING,
YOU'LL HAVE SOMETHING TO BRING IT BACK TO YOU.
W-WHAT SOMETHING?
MICHELANGELO'S SKETCH AND SONNET.
YOU'RE GIVING IT TO US?
YES, IF YOU'D LIKE.
DON'T YOU THINK YOU OUGHT TO GIVE IT TO THE PEOPLE AT THE MUSEUM?
LET THEM KNOW THE TRUTH?
OH, NO. KEEP THEM GUESSING.
THEY NEED A LITTLE MYSTERY IN THEIR LIVES.
I'D MUCH RATHER YOU HAVE IT.
HEY, I BET IT'S WORTH MILLIONS.
WE COULD SELL IT TO THE MUSEUM,
MAKE A PACKET!
JAMIE!
I'M SORRY, MRS. FRANKWEILER,
BUT MAYBE IT'S NOT SUCH A GOOD IDEA GIVING IT TO ME
'CAUSE I'M NOT THAT GOOD WITH SECRETS,
ESPECIALLY WHEN THEY'RE WORTH MONEY.
OH, BUT YOU'LL BE QUITE SAFE, JAMIE.
I'LL LEAVE IT TO YOU IN MY WILL.
BY THEN I WON'T CARE WHO KNOWS AND YOU CAN SELL IT FOR AS MUCH AS YOU'D LIKE.
BUT UNTIL THEN, IT'LL BE OUR SECRET--
YOURS TO ENJOY THINKING HOW MUCH IT'S WORTH
AND CLAUDIA'S TO REMIND HER HOW SPECIAL SHE IS
AND MINE TO REMEMBER YOU BY.
COME HERE. COME HERE.
Mother: WE MISSED YOU SO MUCH.
HEY, SWEETIE.
Mrs. Frankweiler: AND THAT IS WHAT BROUGHT JAMES AND CLAUDIA KINCAID
INTO MY LIFE.
I LOOKED FORWARD TO SEEING THEM AGAIN.
AFTER ALL, SOMEONE HAD TO TIDY UP MY LIBRARY.
AND I'M PLEASED TO SAY THEY DID,
WITH JUST A LITTLE HELP FROM PARKS AND MYSELF.
AS FOR THE MUSEUM AND ITS STAFF,
THINGS CONTINUED MUCH AS THEY ALWAYS HAD
DESPITE THE FRUSTRATION OF NOT BEING ABLE
TO AUTHENTICATE THE ANGEL AS A MICHELANGELO,
WHICH WAS A CONSIDERABLE LOSS,
BUT WAS PERHAPS COMPENSATED FOR
BY THE UNFOLDING OF ANOTHER MYSTERY,
THE ANSWER TO WHICH WAS ALSO NEVER FOUND,
ALTHOUGH SUSPECTED BY SOME.
I'VE ALWAYS THOUGHT A LITTLE MYSTERY IS A GOOD THING.
IT CAN BRING MAGIC INTO ANYONE'S LIFE.
I SHOULD KNOW.