(soft music)
(tense electronic music)
(light music)
(paint splattering)
(soft tense music)
- [Dispatcher] You know,
I think it's something
that is given to us when we're young,
like implanted in us.
You graduate college, you get
your job, buy a big house,
have 2.5 kids, have a
fence around your yard,
a dog, nice cars.
You don't have anything to worry about.
- [Boothe] I think everyone still uses
like that white picket fence reference,
and in everybody's head
that's what everybody
still wants, you know?
Perfect house, perfect family,
whatever that family may be.
Everybody in their hearts,
they want that on a financial level.
They want to marry that person
that is their true love.
- [Don] The goal of this
country has always been
that everyone can have a home.
When World War II ended
and the great American middle
class started to evolve,
the American dream was that you could be
a middle-class person, have your own home,
have your own four walls,
have your own life.
You're a king in your castle.
Even if the thing's a
thousand square feet,
it doesn't matter, if it's
a nice thousand square feet.
- [Peggy] My parents and my generation,
they all expected that their
children would have more
and be able to do more than
they were able to provide.
Life will progress in such a manner
that we're able to have
more and to provide more
for our families.
And that we will not be going backwards.
- One of the great things about America,
it's one of the few countries
that has the least amount
of obstacles for anybody to make a home,
buy a home, have their family there.
My husband and I have
been married for 29 years.
We have three children,
and we're now at the stage
where we're witnessing our
kids graduating from college,
following their own dreams,
having their children,
doing the whole thing
that my husband and I
have been doing.
The struggles, the triumphs.
We believe in our hearts,
whatever it is that we want
to attain, we can achieve it.
(paper shuffling)
(children chattering)
(soft music)
This is a three bedroom, two bath,
1,460 heated square feet,
and has a split plan.
Master bedroom is over here.
There's two smaller
bedrooms near the entry.
The kitchen is nice
but it's sort of plain.
Nice, big walk-in closet, right?
Take your time, look around,
and ask me any questions, okay?
- Yeah, just give us a few, please.
- Okay.
- Thanks.
So what do you think?
- It's not perfect,
but the longer we wait,
we won't even be able to
afford something like this.
- It's more than we talked about.
- Yeah, but when we move in,
we won't owe on anything else.
Hey, don't worry.
- I can't not worry.
Let's just go.
- Hey.
- What are you doing?
- Come here.
Come here.
Here we go.
Look how tall I am.
(both chuckling)
(soft music)
- [Barack On TV] They
believed in an America
where hard work paid off and
responsibility was rewarded.
And anyone could make it if they tried.
And these values gave rise
to the largest middle class-
- What do we still have to do in there?
We got the bed in there.
We got the bedding in there.
That's it for tonight though?
- Well, maybe a box or two
depending on what time it is.
I'm gonna start, you know,
putting clothes away.
- I'm not gonna stop you.
To our lovely home?
- Mm-hm.
So is it too soon to start talking names?
- Ooh!
Names.
(soft music)
- I can't believe this is happening.
- On three, okay?
- Okay.
One,
two,
three.
(Maggie breathing heavily)
- It was all in your dream, babe.
You all right?
- I am now.
Baby.
- Hm?
- If something were to happen to you,
how long would you want me
wait to find somebody new?
- Where did that come from?
- How long?
- Once I'm underground,
you can do what you want,
but I'm not going anywhere for a while.
- Better not.
- Yeah, what's my statute of limitations?
- Never.
You're gonna mourn my death
the rest of your life.
- So what do we have, five
more days to the weekend?
- [Jonah] Tell me about it.
- [Don] How did your
move go? How's the house?
- It's great.
Won't feel like home
till we get the last
couple boxes unpacked,
but the commute's a lot easier.
Couldn't ask for a better deal, so.
- Fortune favors the bold.
- Somethin' like that.
(phone ringing)
Production, Jonah speaking.
- Jonah Price?
- Yes, sir.
- [Phil] Got a minute?
- Yeah, sure.
- Stop by my office.
- Yeah, okay, should I-
- Thanks.
(phone beeping)
Mr. Price.
Look, there's no real easy way to do this.
It's the worst part of my job.
Revenue has gotten pretty tight.
Corporate has asked us to make cuts.
- Your termination will
be effective in 30 days.
- [Phil] I hold myself
responsible for all of this.
I had to make some tough decisions.
- [Melanie] In this economy,
we've had to right-size...
Health-care coverage,
job placement services.
- [Phil] Every one of our
papers across the country
is eliminating-
- Termination.
- Jonah, I understand your concern.
Anyone would feel the same
thing in your situation.
I'm glad you called, but I
mean, why don't we give it
a few weeks before we start panicking?
- Well, it's not panicking.
I think it's a smart move to
try and reduce the payments
to something a little bit more manageable.
- We've got to know your income
before we can set the terms, right?
Focus on getting a job right now
and talk to me first of the month.
(soft music)
- [Maggie] Do you know any
other places hiring right now?
- Well, not in newspapers,
but there's bound to
be something I can do.
- [Maggie] And what if there's not?
- It's gonna be okay.
- Well, maybe I could pick up
some serving shifts somewhere.
- Yeah, I don't think we
need to worry about that yet.
- I don't know, Jonah.
I really like it here,
and I'd rather just
fix this now than wait.
I'm afraid it's gonna be too late.
(soft music)
I think maybe I should talk to my mom.
- Out of the question.
- It's either another job or my mom.
I'm sorry, but I can't go
back to some tiny apartment
and then just wait for the stars to align
so that we can start a family.
It's either another job or my mom.
(soft music)
- [Ellen] I'd like to
Laura and Cole to Disney
at the end of the month,
but I wanted to ask about staying with you
before I offered Leah.
- That sounds great, Mom, I'm
just not sure how much time
I'm gonna have to play host.
- [Ellen] Well, if it's too much trouble,
I'm sure your brother can
afford to spring for a hotel.
- That is not the issue, Mom.
I just don't know how much time
I'm gonna have to take off.
- [Ellen] Has he gotten any offers?
- [Maggie] He'll get something soon.
- [Arnold] Mr. Price, I
appreciate your interest.
- [Peggy] And I sympathize
with your circumstances, but-
- [Nick] We're more focused on building
our web presence right now.
- Absolutely, you know,
I've had tons of experience
with the web and love training
regarding the new programs.
- [Bernard] We'd like someone with
a more extensive magazine background.
- [Daphne] Unfortunately, we aren't able
to offer relocation expenses.
- [Mark] Yes, I do remember.
We were interested a year ago.
- [Angela] You understand what
it's like for an alt weekly.
- [Trudy] We've had to fight to keep them
from killing our print
edition all together.
- [Ellen] I just want you to be happy.
If you'd stayed up here
instead of following him
all over the country, you
might've had your own kids
to take care of by now
instead of everybody else's.
Every one of the boys you dated in school
had enough sense to find something stable
that would support a family
and will be around in 20 years.
- [Maggie] Nothing in that
place will change in 20 years.
- [Cliff] Unfortunately, we're
on a hiring freeze right now.
- I understand that, sir.
Just thought it might be worth a call.
- [Meredith] We'll keep
your information on file.
- All right, well,
thank you for your time.
- [Woody] I'll be sure to give you a call
if anything comes up.
- If you're so worried, Mom,
you could just write a check.
- [Ellen] I'm sorry, Maggie,
with your dad's health
the way it is, we can't
afford to look after anyone
but ourselves right now.
Besides, you're supposed to be an adult.
What would it teach you to bail you out?
- Business call?
Oh, relax.
I'd be doing the same thing.
- [Jonah] Yeah, what's that?
- Doing whatever I could to
find a new job on company time
and company dime.
- Look, I've also been-
- Look, you gotta cut corners.
Don't worry, I'll back you up.
- I appreciate that, Don.
- The least I could do.
- So what do we got? Anything good here?
Melanie, dropped these in my box for you.
- [Jonah] Oh.
Tremendous.
What's that?
- That is something
I'd like to keep quiet.
- What do you got here, Don?
Don't hold out on me.
- Phil wanted to have
some kind of a ceremony,
even had my wife start
to bake a cake but...
I don't feel quite right about it.
- [Jonah] 25 years, huh?
How does it feel?
- I don't know how to feel.
I mean, I work harder and harder.
I make less and less.
And the suits keep making more and more.
You know, there was a
time they'd talk to me.
They would consult with
me before letting go
the top layout artist I've worked with.
- Well, you enjoy that.
- Yeah.
Listen, seriously,
if there's something you need,
if you gotta knock off
early for an interview,
come in late, whatever.
If there's some way I can make
your life a little easier,
say the words.
- [Ellen] It's not going to be easy.
You're just going to have
to tighten your belts.
Stick to the necessities.
- [Character on TV] You walking along,
not a nickel in you jeans,
you're free as the wind.
Nobody bothers you.
(phone beeping)
Then you get ahold of some dough.
And what happens?
First thing you know, you own things.
You're not the free and
happy guy you used to be.
You got to have money to
pay for all those things.
- [TV announcer] Tonight's
jackpot is $35 million,
and your winning lotto numbers are 47,
44,
42,
41,
seven,
and the last lotto number
is 36.
Now-
- [Jonah] You wanna go to bed, babe?
(soft music)
- [Morty] Jonah, sorry for the wait.
How's the job search coming?
- Well, not so well. Not so well at all.
You told me to give you a call
if I hadn't had found
anything by the first,
so that is what I'm doing.
- So what can I do you for?
- [Jonah] Well, I figured
if I had a longer term
then I might be able to
accept some offers right now.
Bit too low to make the current payments.
- Sounds like you got a good head
on your shoulders there, Jonah.
Let me pull up your file.
Uh-oh.
- [Jonah] What?
- [Morty] Looks like
we're no longer at liberty
to change the terms.
- [Jonah] What?
- [Morty] We don't even
actually own it anymore.
- [Jonah] Whoa, Morty, who does?
- [Morty] You should've
gotten a notice about this.
- [Jonah] I didn't get anything.
(door creaking)
(kids chattering)
- Jonah.
Jonah, will you please talk to me?
What are you doing?
- Buying time.
- What do you mean?
No way.
- Look, I'll do it, okay?
Just go back in the house.
- No way.
- Go back in the house.
- No!
- Look, this could go on for months.
Do you realize how much
money we would save here?
- No.
It's gotta be dangerous.
You trying to get yourself killed?
- No, I'm not gonna get myself killed.
It's not dangerous.
- I suppose you do know
what you're doing, huh?
- Before I was old
enough for a paper route,
this is what we did when
Mom's hours got cut back.
- Jonah.
Come on, we'll find another way.
- Yeah, fine.
(door slamming)
(crickets chirping)
(knocking on door)
- Just forget it.
- [Boothe] And you are?
- [Jonah] Jonah Price.
- Okay, let's see.
And what interests you
about Eagle Staffing Agency?
- As you can see on my resume,
I've worked in extremely professional,
competitive environments
for nearly 10 years.
I have excellent computer skills,
and given my background in publishing,
I think I'd have an edge when
it comes to communication
within a corporate environment.
- I see.
It doesn't look like
you have any experience
as an executive assistant, or a secretary,
even a receptionist, for that matter.
- Well, no, but I've worked
in newspapers all around
the country for nearly 10 years,
and like all my references
are gonna tell you,
I have zero problems
adapting to new challenges.
- You never scheduled appointments?
- No, but I've-
- Maintained a company filing system?
- Well, I've had to adhere
to a common filing system.
- Yeah, but solely for an individual?
Like an executive, for instance.
- No.
- Have you ever had any office
management responsibilities,
such as maintaining an inventory
of office supplies before?
- No.
- What about office machines? Fax, copier?
- I can operate a fax
machine and make copies.
- I see.
How about heavy phones?
Have you ever had to handle multi-line
heavy phone traffic before?
- Yeah, I can answer the phone.
- Make coffee?
- I've had to redesign
entire sections of the paper
at the last minute so an ad
rep can satisfy his clients.
I've dealt with constant
deadline pressure,
day in and day out.
I have done three people's
jobs for weeks at a time,
so I think these are,
you know, the filing, the heavy phones,
these are things that I could handle.
- I understand you possess
some notable qualifications
that many of our candidates
for placement don't,
but we need to fully stand behind
the employees that we place.
I'm not saying that you
won't be considered,
I just, you know,
if your background
check and drug screening
come back clean, then we'll see.
I believe we have your
contact information,
so you know, if we have a
match, I'll be in touch.
(knocking on window)
- Hey.
- That bad, huh?
- Let's just say I'm
not holding my breath.
- [Maggie] I'm sorry.
- [Jonah] Me too.
- [Maggie] I mean, for everything.
- You're gonna find something.
- What am I gonna find that pays enough
to keep the house, Maggie?
I'm sorry.
- Why don't you go camping
this weekend, Jonah?
I just, I think it would
be good for you to get away
and clear your head, regroup.
I think it'll be good for both of us.
(soft music)
(line trilling)
- [Jonah] Hey, it's
Jonah, leave me a message.
(phone beeping)
(waves lapping)
(birds chirping)
(microwave beeping)
- Hey babe, it's me.
Just checking to see where you are.
Call me back, okay?
I love you.
(soft music)
- [TV announcer] Free of charge
with absolutely no
obligation for just 14.95,
but this spectacular-
- [Sterling] What those
companies hope you'll do.
At the Ster...
(line trilling)
- [Jonah] Hey, it's
Jonah, leave me a message.
(phone beeping)
- I don't know what's goin' on here,
but can you just please call
me and let me know you're okay?
- [Jonah] Hey, it's
Jonah, leave me a message.
(phone beeping)
- Jonah, pick up!
Where are you?
Look,
I know things have been hard lately.
Maybe that's my fault.
I don't know, just...
I love you, I'm worried about you.
Please just call me back.
- [Jonah] Hey, it's
Jonah, leave me a message.
(phone beeping)
- Jonah, where are you?
I don't know what to do.
Do I call 911?
Could you please just come home?
Now?
I love you.
(crickets chirping)
(phone ringing)
Hello?
- I didn't think I'd get you.
I was gonna leave a voicemail.
We're coming down at the end of the month.
- Okay.
- [Ellen] Now don't worry,
we're staying at a hotel.
I'll make sure you don't
have to worry about anything.
- You haven't bought your
plane tickets yet, have you?
- [Ellen] Why?
- I haven't heard from
him since Friday night.
- [Ellen] All weekend?
- [Maggie] It's not like that.
- [Ellen] Are you sure?
You don't always know.
- Well, he went camping,
but he didn't come back
when he said he would,
and I couldn't get through on his cell.
- [Ellen] Could there be someone else?
(line trilling)
- This might be weird, but
I need to ask you something.
- Go ahead.
- If Jonah was seeing anybody,
I just, maybe you don't know.
I just feel like a lot
of times I've heard that
that happens a lot.
If I don't hear from him tonight,
I think I'm gonna go to the police.
But when I do, I just don't
wanna be some poor woman
whose husband ran off and
she didn't see it coming.
- Look, if something was
going on here, you know,
he would've been pretty sly about it.
I mean, he could have,
but I really don't think
that's the case.
- [Maggie] I'd say that's a relief,
but the alternatives
aren't relieving at all,
so thanks, I guess.
- I understand.
(soft music)
- [Ellen] You heard from his mother?
- [Maggie] She's not staying with us.
- But-
- No, she's just gonna stay
with a friend who used to go
to their church or something.
- That's ridiculous.
I mean, you're right here.
She shouldn't have to-
- [Maggie] She doesn't like us.
Well, she doesn't like me, you know,
kinda like how you are with Jonah.
(police radio chattering)
- Cell phone and car keys were
both found inside the tent,
as well as some camping gear:
stove, headlamp, cookware,
sleeping bag, water bottles, clothes.
Once we finish the
necessary forensic work,
you can inspect the contents of the tent
and tell us if there's anything missing.
A ranger found his car
up near the boat launch.
Wallet was found inside the
console, looks untouched.
(police radio chattering)
- [Detective] At the moment,
our most likely scenario
is that Mr. Price went exploring
where the river meets the ocean.
Maybe he encountered some trouble-
- Do you think he's out there?
- [Detective] We're
gonna get as many people
out here searching for him as
we can for the next 36 hours.
We need to take other scenarios into-
- What are you saying?
- [Detective] This place has
some powerful rip currents.
Solo swimmer, we don't know
if he had a life jacket on.
- Now who knows if they're right?
You're gonna keep
looking, isn't that right?
- Yes, ma'am.
(waves crashing)
(soft music)
- Hey, we're home, sweetheart.
Come on, honey, just get a little rest.
I promise you'll feel better
with just a little rest after a long day.
Sit down. I'll get your shoes.
- [Maggie] Thanks, Mom.
- That's what moms are for, so I'm told.
Left foot right up here.
Pop up your sweet feet.
I can't give you another
one for a few hours,
so I sure hope you can sleep, okay?
- [Maggie] I love you, Mom.
- I love you, too.
You are my precious girl.
Sleep.
(soft music)
Primary beneficiary, Maggie Price, spouse.
Beneficiary to be paid $500,000.
Hi, dear.
Question for the lawyer in the family.
- Mom, what if by some
miracle he's out there,
who knows where, but
I'm not waiting for him?
- [Ellen] I don't think they
would've called off the search
if they thought there was a
chance they could save him.
- I know, but it's just-
- What?
- There's still a chance.
- Listen, Maggie, I don't
pretend for a second
to know where he is, but it is not here.
And I think it is worth
your while to see if you can
get something for your trouble.
- That makes me feel
like a horrible person.
- I have to deal with horrible people
in this line of business sometimes.
I mean, these are people that
are out for money, right?
They don't care how they're
gonna go about getting it.
You do not strike me as one
of those. Not even close.
But I also deal with people
that have a good case,
but they're either ignorant
or just plain stubborn.
They come to me too late for
me to do anything about it.
All right, so that's why
it's important that we take
the initiative in these matters.
It's gonna go a long way to preventing
an even bigger mess later
that's gonna be a lot harder to clean up.
- I think I need to sleep on it.
I hope that's not a problem.
- No, Maggie, not at all.
I understand.
Just remember,
for the best chance of
a favorable settlement,
we need to get on this right away.
Just give me the word, all right,
and we're gonna put this into action.
- Thank you for your time.
- Absolutely.
Thanks for coming in.
- I don't know what you're waiting for.
I think he would take good care of you.
Even if he's out there,
you should still do it.
Honestly, if I thought he were,
I'd be even more convinced.
Because in that case, where is he?
Why did he leave you to deal
with all of this on your own?
(soft music)
I wish you the best with this.
You know I love you.
- [Maggie] Thank you.
Have a safe trip, Mom.
(soft music)
(crickets chirping)
(soft music continues)
(patrons chattering)
- [Man on TV] Tonight,
all across this state
and all across this country,
there are people working hard
to ensure that their children would have
a better opportunity in this life
than they have had themselves.
And they are blessed to live
in this great and extraordinary society
where indeed that dream is still possible,
and is still true.
(dog barking)
(paper shuffling)
- [Maggie] Who did this?
- You didn't know about it?
- Of course not.
- Maggie, I am so sorry, she said that-
- Who?
- Mrs. Price, I mean his mother.
She said that, she told me that-
- I should've known.
- I thought that you knew everything.
- I'm sorry, Don.
I didn't mean to come in
here and just start...
- I just thought that...
(soft music)
(Maggie crying)
- How's this work?
- Well, there's a remote possibility
that if someone were to
petition for a probate hearing,
your in-laws for example,
that you might lose something,
but all of his assets should
be transferred to you.
Precedent for cases like these, you know,
with a surviving spouse
is pretty airtight,
even without a will.
- [Maggie] What about-
- No, ma'am, not yet.
Look, we're not like a lot
of the other firms out there
who are gonna bill you by the hour
and hope to get rich off of
wasting your time, all right?
We take our share from the back end,
because we do plan on winning.
We're very good at what we do,
and you will not owe us anything
that our performance doesn't warrant.
(light music)
- [Ellen] You're down
there all by yourself.
If you've got to start over,
you might as well do it up here.
- I need to get everything
settled down here
before I can even think about that.
- [Ellen] How long is that going to take?
- Without a body, the courts
generally take five years
to issue a death certificate
so the insurance company
can be sure that the person
in question is actually dead.
- All those people couldn't find him.
- Look, the state can expedite
the death certificate,
all right, as long as we
can prove that your husband
was exposed to imminent peril.
But since this isn't a major disaster,
you know, legally speaking,
it still could take up to a year.
- I'll be out of my house.
- I'll do what I can, all
right, to move this thing along,
but if I were you, I would
do everything in your power
to get out from under that house.
- We were supposed to
have kids in that house.
- The market hasn't changed too much,
but at the same time I see that
you guys still have some work to do here.
The lawn should be mowed,
and it would help if you
would get rid of the weeds.
You wanna make sure that the
house looks like it's been
kept up and you've taken good care of it.
(children laughing)
(engine rumbling)
- Ms. Price.
- [Sterling] Hey, Maggie.
Have a seat, this shouldn't take long.
- [Maggie] So what's this about?
- Miss Price, we've been asked
to take another look at your husband's,
his...
- Death?
- That's right.
- You know how things are
when there's insurance money at stake.
- Now if I recall correctly,
your husband lost his job
shortly before he disappeared?
- [Maggie] Yes, that's right.
- And he was having some
trouble finding work?
Would you say he was depressed?
I'm sorry, Miss Price, but I'm
gonna need you to speak up-
- Yes, he was depressed.
- He wouldn't have done it on
purpose or anything, would he?
- Okay, Maggie, let me restate that.
If Jonah committed suicide,
then the insurance company
would only have to refund the premiums
versus the full benefits.
- He would've said goodbye.
There wasn't even a note, so...
- Forgive me, Miss
Price, but I had to ask.
- Is that all, sir?
- Ma'am, I'm afraid that
there's one more thing.
And again, I apologize
if it is insensitive.
- [Maggie] Go ahead.
- Is there any possibility
that your husband could
be trying to defraud
the insurance company
for his benefit or yours?
- We're done, okay?
Maggie, you don't have to
answer that at all, okay?
- No.
- No chance?
- None.
My husband couldn't pull
off something like that.
I mean, I love him,
but he wouldn't have...
Just something that he wouldn't do, okay?
- Well, I'm sorry to have bothered you.
Miss Price, I think I've heard
all that I needed to hear.
- Glad to hear it.
- Goodbye, ma'am.
- Goodbye.
- I am impressed.
- What?
What do you mean?
I told the truth.
- Doesn't matter you're telling the truth.
Only matters whether you're convincing.
- I think that's the most
cynical thing I've ever heard.
- Yeah well, any cop or lawyer
will tell you the same thing.
A good one, anyway.
- I suppose I ought to
feel good about today then.
- Well, step in the right direction.
You know, they still may come
back and try to only pay half.
They're entitled to without the body.
I mean, hey, it's better
than the alternative.
- Half is more than enough.
- You gettin' by?
- I'll be okay.
- You sure?
I mean, if anything changes,
you know, if you need anything,
you can call me, day or night.
I'm sure we can work out a
mutually beneficial arrangement.
Just keep it in mind.
- I'm gonna go.
(light music)
(microwave beeping)
(water running)
- Maggie.
- Oh my God.
- Maggie, it's me.
(knocking on door)
Maggie, come on, open up.
(thunder rumbling)
Maggie.
Maggie, come on, open the door.
- Oh my God.
- I came back to you as soon as I could.
- What?
- What's wrong?
- You son of a bitch.
- Maggie, look, I would've told you if-
- You should have.
- [Jonah] Maggie, it's not
like I didn't trust you.
- The second that you thought about this,
you should've told me.
I thought I lost you.
- It wouldn't have worked if I told you.
- Oh my God!
I don't think I even know you.
- Maggie, don't you get it?
I did this for us.
- Which part, Jonah?
- All of it.
- Don't touch me!
- I did all of this for us, Maggie.
Yeah.
- The part where I thought you were dead?
Like the part where you
ran off and left me here
by myself to clean up your mess?
That was for us.
- Maggie, everything I did was for you.
- Don't you stand there and
tell me that this was for us.
You did what was easiest for you.
I can't even look at you, Jonah.
I can't believe-
- You think this was easy for me?
Do you have any idea the
things I have been through?
- I want you to leave.
- No, no, no, no, no.
Look.
You're all that matters.
I don't care about anything but you.
- If you cared about me, you
would've never done this to me.
I can't even look at you, I can't...
- You don't get it, do you?
- There is nothing that you could say
that could possibly excuse this.
- Excuse this?
Maggie, excuse this?
What do you mean, excuse this?
- I want you to leave.
- Is that what you want,
you want me to leave?
- I don't want you to be here.
- All right.
I love you,
and
I'm really glad to see you.
(Maggie crying)
(thunder rumbling)
(rain drizzling)
- If you're not out of here by
the time I wake up tomorrow,
I'm turning you in.
Either you leave or I'm calling the cops.
- You are the only one
who knows I'm alive, okay?
The only thing standing between us
and a half million dollars
is some paperwork, Maggie.
- It's a quarter million.
And it's going to be-
- So?
- [Maggie] At least a year.
- Do you have any idea how long we could
make that last someplace else?
- Give it up, Jonah. It's over!
- Are you serious right now?
You would send me to prison?
- Don't tempt me.
I just don't want you here.
- You'd really send me to
prison right now, wouldn't you?
- I just don't want you here.
- Where do you want me to go, Maggie?
- You've been somewhere
else this whole time, Jonah.
Just go there.
(woman moaning)
(fly buzzing)
(TV chattering)
(line trilling)
- [Phone Recording] The wireless
customer you have called
is not available at this time.
Please try your call again later.
(phone beeping)
(soft music)
(grease crackling)
(dishes clattering)
(soft music continues)
(doorbell ringing)
- I'm really glad you could make it.
- Yeah, me too.
- Come on.
This is gonna have to
be a little bit quicker
than I was hoping, 'cause
I have to get back to work
to do a couple things.
It's okay. (chuckles)
But why don't we first give you a tour?
(soft music)
And this is the bedroom.
Look.
I'm sorry.
I think I'm so much usually
better at this type of thing.
I just, by the look that
you're giving me right now,
I don't think you
understand what's happening.
It's my fault, 'cause I really
should've been much clearer.
Yeah, I know you need the money,
so I'm gonna go ahead and
leave this on the dresser.
Everything okay?
Look,
cleaning supplies, right?
The cleaning supplies are downstairs.
They're in the closet right
next to the laundry room.
Okay, 'cause you'll need those.
And it's better this way.
Okay, 'cause you need the money, right,
and then my wife comes
home to a clean house
and I don't have to sleep on the couch.
Take all the time you need.
Okay, you have all day.
Diane, my wife, doesn't
get home till four so,
call me if you need anything.
(soft music)
(vacuum humming)
(soft music continues)
(cleaning tool thudding)
(hand pounding)
(Maggie sniffling)
(carwash beeps)
(tool clanging)
(metal rattling)
(soft music)
- Maggie?
Hey, Maggie.
Maggie?
(door creaking)
- [Dispatcher] 911, what's your emergency?
- [Jonah] My wife's been electrocuted.
- [Dispatcher] I'm sorry,
sir, what's your emergency?
- My wife has been electrocuted.
- [Dispatcher] And the exact
location of your emergency?
- 2121 Sabal Palm Circle, 32820.
- [Dispatcher] I'll have the paramedics
on the way right away.
Now sir, what's your name?
Sir?
(Jonah breathing heavily)
(soft tense music)
(tire squealing)
(soft tense music continues)
(soft music)