Got it.
Gonna work?
Would've work.
All right.
Wanna see what she do?
Dang right.
Get in.
This thing ain't even
close to street legal.
We get out on the
highway with this thing
Sheriff Wilkin's
gonna kick our butts.
Can't kick what he can't catch.
Yeah!
Hey, man, we better head back
and get ready for the party.
I'm ready.
You want to go in this?
Yeah, why not?
You ain't even got headlights.
Hey, hey.
Why don't we just go
back to the lake instead?
Man, this our graduation, Lurvy.
What, you getting
cramped up or something?
No, no, I'm good.
All right.
Here you go, man.
That car is so cool.
Even your daddy's car
won't get you laid, Bryson.
It'll get me to the party.
Here we go.
It's just Bryson.
He just don't know when to quit.
Open your eyes, Lurvy.
Tell him bye bye.
What you stopping at
your Uncle Charlie's for?
I told him I'd bring it back.
Oh, my goodness.
Well, look at this.
How are you, sir?
Good, good to see you, Ty.
So good to see you.
Lurvy.
Come on, Lurvy, stop
messing around, man.
What do we have here?
Said I'd show you the car
that's win state this year.
What you think?
What happened
to all the windows?
Yeah, it's pretty stripped down.
Don't even have headlights.
You think we got a winner?
Yes, sir, I do.
So tell me I'm not
gonna lose my best foreman
to a race car this summer.
No, sir, no, sir.
I'll be full-time
starting Monday morning.
I'm just kidding you boys.
Well, I don't want to
hold you up, Uncle Charlie.
Y'all be careful out
there in this thing tonight.
Yes, sir.
You have fun.
I will.
Come on, Lurvy,
stop messing around, man.
Be careful, boys.
Yes, sir.
Oh.
Oh, hey there, Bryson.
Maybe next time, huh?
Bryson?
Yeah, he's got it.
He's got what?
He's got that look.
Hey, Ty.
Man, I'd be all over that.
I'm in training, Lurvy.
Man, put your tongue
in your mouth.
What are you doing?
You don't never give
her the time of day.
I gave her the time of day once.
That's why she keeps rubbing
on me like a house cat.
You did?
Man, you did?
I don't know what
he's doing here?
Did he build that piece of crap?
Yeah, and his uncle paid for it.
Wrecked the last one.
Thinks he's gonna
go pro or something.
Pro?
We can count on it.
He's gonna end up
drunk in the clay pit
just like his daddy.
Hey, Ty.
Racing's one thing,
my daddy's another.
What's he doing here?
Becky Fleming's
on a date with him.
Shut up, Bryson.
Lookie, lookie.
It's the little engine
that almost could.
Didn't you graduate
about five years ago?
Hey, Ty.
Hey, Becky.
All right, Lurvy.
Screw this party.
Snake's just an asshole.
Yeah, I don't know what
Becky Fleming sees in him.
She's about fine, too.
Yeah.
Well, she was until she
started hanging on him.
Man, look.
There's just some things
that are out of our league.
Like winning the
state championship.
You got to stop all that talk.
We ain't even won
the local track,
and that money your
Uncle Charlie gave you,
ain't nothing up to what Turner
Auto spends on Snake's car.
Yeah, some things you
don't need money for, Lurvy.
And you're a better mechanic
than anybody they got.
Don't you forget that, man.
I wish you'd stop
saying that, too.
Look, Lurvy.
I mean, here it is, right?
Graduation.
People going off to college.
We can't afford that.
Way I see it, I'm only
really good at one thing,
and that's driving cars.
That's the only chance I got
at making something of myself.
I don't want to end up
another drunk in clay pit.
Man, don't say that.
There ain't nobody
that thinks like that.
And forget about Bryson.
He's just a loud mouth.
Yep, and people
that don't say nothing
are pretty loud, too.
Let's get on out of here.
They don't think I
can do it, Daddy.
What about you?
Come on.
Can't do it myself.
How's he looking, Lurvy?
He's looking pretty good.
I'm about to wave him in.
Probably need to take some
weight off the outside though.
Oh, look, there's Snake.
He don't even hot lap, does he?
No, not usually.
Well, good luck
on the money run.
I appreciate it.
Come on, man, you ready?
I'm almost done.
You like the tires?
No, that'll have to do.
You raise that right
top four link bar?
Yes, man.
Come on, it's time to go.
It's a little different than
a lawnmower engine, isn't it?
Like you anything
about an engine.
Bring Daddy's
mechanics with you?
You know you can tinker with
that junkyard piece of crap
all you want.
When you're ready to
run with the big boys
why don't you come on out.
I might not put you
in the wall again.
You ready?
Yeah.
Bastard's mine.
All right, folks.
We got the street stop feature
coming out of the gate.
Local boy, Ty Hargrove, is
back and I mean way back
after a bad crash against
the wall a couple weeks ago.
He's got a new sponsor
Aldwin Tow and.
Let's see if he can get some
points back on the board.
On the first row taking
the inside position
is our point leader, Snake
Turner, in the number 15 car.
On the high side is Lloyd
Briggs in the number 12 car.
Easy on turn one, Ty.
Don't take it too low now.
Coming down the
front stretch is Snake Turner
in the lead with Ty Hargrove
breathing hard down his neck.
Stay high.
Catch him on the straight away.
Don't you do it, Ty.
Come on, you know better.
Come on, man, get back in there.
I got mine over
at the gift shop.
Whoa, that's cool.
You have fun tonight, buddy?
Yes, sir.
Do you think you can beat Snake?
I was just warming up tonight.
Hey.
You want to get in bed?
What time is it?
About one in the morning.
I was close tonight, Dad.
So close.
It was right there.
I can beat him, I know it.
I'ma ride up there with
you on the next one, son.
You said last time.
She's kicking my butt, boy.
Well, kind of looks like
you're kicking your own butt
around here.
Y'all know nothing about this.
It made you taught me.
I know if anybody's quitting
right now, it's you.
Just won't stick.
I ain't got the right stuff.
But you did.
You still do.
Tell you what, I'll
make a deal with you.
All right?
I qualify for state,
you gotta get straight.
How about that?
That's fair, right?
Ain't gonna be
nothing if I got at it
all worried about you anyway.
Just not right in my head
when you're like this.
Come on, Daddy.
I'm afraid to make that deal.
Why?
Because I know you gonna win it.
And when you do, I
will let you down.
Ty, can you
come to the office, please?
Ty, will you come to the office?
Hey, Cindy.
Hey, Ty.
Come on in, son.
Hey Uncle Charlie, Aunt Paula.
Morning, Ty.
How are you, son?
Good to see you today.
I'll just leave
the two of you alone.
You have a good day, sweetheart.
Thank you.
You, too.
Aunt Paula.
Sweetheart.
Tomato sandwiches, huh?
Oh, she's been
making these for me a long time.
She's a good one.
Yes, sir.
You sure have been
moving a lot of poles
across the yard lately.
I'm really proud of
the job you're doing.
Thank you, sir.
I appreciate that.
I sure wish Frank
would've taken to this place
like you have.
Well, I know Frank wants
to go to college first, sir.
And knowing Frank
he's probably goofing
Well, it is college, sir.
I'm sure he'll be just fine.
Yeah, well I don't
want to talk about that.
We got a lot of good stuff
going on around here.
We've been meeting
with investors,
and we're gonna start
making concrete poles.
We just closed on a piece
of property up the road.
We're looking for a man
to run the operation.
I told them that I think
I've got the right man
for that operation.
Okay.
And I think that man's you.
Me?
If you're interested in the job.
Well, yes, sir.
Yeah.
I tell you what.
We're gonna have a
little cocktail party
with the business men tomorrow.
Why don't you leave
work a little bit early
and go home put some
nice clothes on,
and I'll pick you up
about six o'clock.
Sound good?
You serious, Uncle Charlie?
Absolutely.
Thank you, sir.
Get on out of here
and go back to work.
All right.
I'm gonna do what
I can with this intake.
See if I can get some
more horsepower out of it.
How much for a new carburetor?
Well, about $400.
Dang.
She can suck up some dough.
Tires be another
thousand, right?
Yup.
Well, I might get
the money next week.
Why don't you give me what
you can on the intake now.
I'll just hold it on turn one,
she'll still be in
the race, right?
Oh, yeah.
Hey, Daddy.
Hey, son.
Please tell me you boys
still think about girls.
I do.
So I'm gonna end up like you?
Some floozy I gotta shake.
Easy on your old man, boy.
Guess who Uncle Charlie's
making manager of the new plant?
What?
That's right.
Well, well, well.
I'm proud of you, son.
Got some big
meeting tomorrow night
with all the investors.
We're gonna have to
get you cleaned up.
Right, yeah.
Right.
Hey, maybe something
with some buttons.
Might need a suit.
Yeah, Ty.
Hell with that.
Come on, Daddy, let me
show what we got done.
Come on in.
How are you, Jack?
Trying to get this
place cleaned up, Charlie.
I'm almost ready, Uncle Charlie.
Take your time, Ty.
A little bit early.
How's the dirt
business, brother?
Man, I can't complain.
Been a long while, man.
Yeah, too long.
You know I appreciate everything
you've been doing for him.
Not doing him any favors.
He's worked hard for
everything he's got coming.
He's the best hand I
got at the pole plant.
Will you look
at that lady killer.
What you think?
Looks good, Ty.
I ironed the hell
out of this shirt.
And you impress them, son.
Yes, sir.
You just be yourself.
You ready?
Let's do it.
Good to see you, Jack.
Good to see you, brother.
Y'all be good now.
How many people are
gonna be here, Uncle Charlie?
Not too awfully many.
The investors are gonna be here.
I don't really want you
to be too nervous now.
I know this is real important.
I know, Uncle Charlie.
But you know, you
just be yourself.
And just be respectful, okay?
Yes, sir.
This Becky Fleming's house.
Yeah, Lyle Fleming is
one of the investors.
I've known the man for
30 years, and I do trust...
Excuse me.
There they are.
Good to see you, Lyle.
Good to see you.
This must be our horse, Charlie.
This is Ty Hargrove.
Nice to meet you, Dr. Fleming.
I hear you knew about everything
there is to know about poles.
Trying to know as
much as I can, sir.
Charlie says you're quite
a race car driver, too.
Well, yeah.
I guess you can call
it a hobby, sir.
Is it like the NASCAR
I've seen on television?
It's mostly homemade
rigs all on a dirt track.
NASCAR will do some dirt, but
that's mostly asphalt stuff.
Hi.
Hey.
What are you doing here?
You know, Ty?
Yeah, from school, Daddy.
I thought you're
spending the night over
at McCane's house tonight?
No, mom wanted me to stay.
Help with the party.
Ty's gonna be plant manager
of the new pole mill
in my with Charlie Hargrove.
That's right.
Uncle Charlie wanted
me to meet everybody.
Excuse us.
You look like you'd
rather be anywhere but here.
Hey, Becky.
Na, I just get the
feeling they think I'm
the only one who knows about
making telephone poles.
Well, then you must know a lot.
I just know what
Uncle Charlie taught me.
Well, it's obvious you
know a lot about cars.
I think Snake's actually
worried about you.
Your daddy don't know
you go to the races, do he?
It's not really his thing.
What's the thing about Snake?
He hasn't said much.
But he knows his daddy
owns a Dodge dealership
in Atmore, right?
That makes him okay.
I'm sorry, what does that
have to do with anything?
Nothing.
I'm just kidding.
Well, maybe I'll see
you around the track.
Okay?
Oh, tell Snake to watch his ass.
I will.
Well, the lake
models are about to line up
for the money run, folks.
Will our local boy, Ty Hargrove,
beat out our board
leader Snake Turner?
Well, we'll see.
It's gonna be a great race.
Let's have some fun.
Can our local boy, Ty
Hargrove, do it tonight?
Ladies and gentlemen,
I don't think so.
Come on, Ty.
Right now.
Now.
You don't have him.
Well, that's it, folks.
Hope you can stay around
for the big party tonight.
Donnick is back, and we've got
cold drinks, snacks, shirts,
decals, Indian blankets,
jams and jellies,
and left-handed
nostril inhalers.
Hey, Ricky.
Hey, man, you got a
tuner bar I can borrow?
Yeah, actually I do, man.
It's over in the trailer
on the left side.
Just whenever you get done
if I'm not over there,
just put it back in there.
Appreciate it man.
Yeah, Charlie
bumped me out there.
Knocked something loose.
Weld it all this last week, too.
Man, it's always
something, right?
But don't worry about it, man.
You did great tonight.
Thanks, man.
I still can't get up
there with Snake though.
We're gonna change
out the carburetor this week.
Man, it's definitely
a horsepower problem.
You're getting through
the corners sweet.
You got the driving,
you got the handling.
Good job.
Thanks, Ricky.
All right, Lurvy.
Wanna grab that bar
and call it a night?
Yup.
♪ So you're riding
down the road ♪
♪ Windows start creeping down ♪
♪ Pops into your mind ♪
♪ You know what it is ♪
♪ Hey there boys ♪
We need some good tires, man.
Yup.
♪ Hey there boy ♪
♪ Do your daddy let you date? ♪
♪ We're gonna stay out, stay
out, stay out, stay out late ♪
You think Sherry's here?
How would I know, man?
Did you really give
her the time of day?
No, man.
I just kissed her one
time in the backseat
of Gen Harley's car.
Hey, hold on one second.
♪ Hey there boy ♪
♪ Where do you come from? ♪
♪ Because you mighty,
mighty, mighty, mighty pretty ♪
Hi.
How are you doing?
Fine.
Did good tonight.
I can do better.
Yeah, well.
Everyone around
here's been slick.
Yeah, well they like
me better if I won.
Snake's tough.
Oh, well he left already.
He said he had to
work on his car.
All right.
Y'all want some drinks?
You can get drinks here.
I can get whatever I want here.
Sure.
What are you doing?
Relax, man.
Her dad's my new boss.
Yeah, and Snake's her boyfriend.
Well, listen to you
Mr. Sherry My Dreams.
I'm not Mr. Sherry My Dreams.
She's right over there, man.
Looking at you.
She's not looking at me.
She's looking at you.
Four beers.
You just keep that.
I'm going over there, man.
Keep her some company.
That's right, man.
One for her one for you.
That's how it works.
Wanna dance?
Yeah, sure.
Can you hold that?
I'll be right back.
♪ Maybe I spoke too soon ♪
♪ Before I said yes ♪
♪ I should've
thought it through ♪
You're a really good dancer.
Who taught you?
Mama.
Daddy would never dance with us
so she used to swing
me around the kitchen.
She sounds like fun.
Yeah.
Then she ran out on us.
♪ If I talk about how we
used to dance in the rain ♪
♪ Laugh about the time when
I got stuck in the swing ♪
Sorry.
Don't be.
Would've been worse
if she stayed.
Things got so bad for two
years I didn't go to school.
But you graduated.
Yeah, a little late.
Bet your ass I was
going to that party.
Your Uncle Charlie's
your dad's brother.
Yeah.
Taught me a lot.
Yeah, he's like a nice guy.
Best one I know.
Probably one of the
best jobs in town.
I've tried to.
What about you?
What do you do?
I work at my daddy's clinic.
Front office stuff.
It's really not interesting.
How'd you get
involved with Snake?
He asked me out.
It's that easy.
Pretty much.
You must get asked out a lot.
Not really.
Doesn't really
seem like your type.
Okay, and how do
you know my type?
Well, it sure ain't jackasses.
Daddy's list of approved
colors isn't very long.
Does he approve
of race car drivers?
♪ Talk about sitting
on the hood of my car ♪
♪ Covered in a blanket ♪
♪ Looking up at the stars ♪
Oh, you got to be kidding me.
You gonna make me
ask, aren't you?
Don't worry about it, man.
Man, when did all that start.
It started when you saw it.
You better be careful.
He's gonna run you into
the wall again, Ty.
Not if you fix it
so I'm ahead of him.
You know my wife has
your number on her car.
No kidding.
Yeah, we're rooting for you
to go to the state championship.
All right.
- Appreciate the support man.
- Sure.
You been calling her or what?
Yeah, I've been calling her.
What's her daddy think?
I don't think
she's told him yet.
How she gonna go to the
race with both of you there?
My truck.
Well, that's it, new carburetor.
Ought to give us
40 more horsepower.
All right.
How much money we got left?
Enough to buy a tank of
gas and some peel offs.
Gotta get some tires.
Yup.
Well, believe we've done
all we can on the carburetor?
Unless you've got $1,200
more bucks for a TCC custom.
Yeah, what's Snake at?
He's got a TCC custom
and $1,200 more dollars
that's for sure.
Well, just have to
get a heavier foot.
Man, it's all you tonight.
Got a new carburetor,
suspension's dead on,
Snake's a no-show.
Man, that pisses me off.
I ain't complaining.
Dude, this is our
chance to catch up.
He knows he can blow
off an entire race
and still roll out of here
with more points than me.
Man, if we win tonight
we're almost tied with him.
Yeah, you're right.
Let him get cocky,
I'm right on his ass.
Can our local boy Ty
Hargrove do it tonight?
I think he might.
Ladies and gentlemen,
there doesn't look like
there's much competition,
and Snake Turner
didn't even show up.
- We need those points, man.
- That was awesome.
- We need those points.
- I know.
We're good now, we're good.
Oh, great.
Oh, cool it, partner.
Are you with this loser, Becky?
Oh, you got something
you want to say to me?
You bitch!
Ty, Ty, stop.
No, leave it.
Come on.
Stop.
Stop it.
Stop, knock it off.
Wanna play that way?
You might have a
slight concussion.
Is that bad?
He'll be okay.
He needs to stay
with us tonight.
Let me have a word
with you, Becky.
What were you doing
at the race track?
That's what he does.
I was with him.
That might be what he does,
but that's no place
for a nice girl.
Daddy, when you
say nice you mean rich.
I mean nice.
You're going to
college next year.
You're not gonna work
at a grocery store.
It wasn't about you, Ty, but
this isn't a place for Becky.
I get it.
You okay, man?
Yeah, take me home, man.
You should go to
the hospital tomorrow
and have that checked out.
Man, that was about me.
What do you expect
from a man like that?
Hey, cuz, what's up?
Good to see you, man.
Looks like dad's been
a little rough on you.
Oh.
Yeah, little scuffle.
Nothing serious though.
Thought you were up
at university, man.
I have been.
I'm just in for a little bit.
How's it looking up there?
Making the team or what?
I don't know, man.
I really don't know
what I'm gonna do.
I don't think I'm
gonna go to school
if I can't play football.
I mean, you can try your
odds somewhere else though.
Yeah, we'll see.
Anyway, I just want to stop by.
See how things were going.
Yeah, man, it's going all right.
You know.
Well, I'll see you around, man.
Good seeing you, Frank.
You, too.
Okay.
Come on in, Ty.
I hear you're quite
the attraction.
Oh, well.
Just a couple of us
are local down there.
Ah, yeah.
You heard.
I heard.
I can see, too.
I might have messed up, sir.
It happens.
I could've helped this.
Yeah, I hear you might
even be going to state.
I don't know about that.
I mean, even if I did I'm not
sure what I'd do about it.
You know, I got
responsibilities around here.
Can't just leave.
Oh, don't make me
have to fire you.
All this will be waiting
on you when you get back.
This chair to be yours some day.
I'm serious, you know.
You're like a son to me.
I've always felt that way.
No different than my own kids.
Thank you, sir.
You still pulling that car
around with that old 1500?
Yes, sir.
Well, sometimes.
Lurvy and I'll switch out
so we don't burn up
our transmissions.
Tell you what.
Why don't you take
that old diesel?
I know it's old.
It's got about
250,000 miles on it,
but she still runs good.
A lot of power.
That old beast in the yard.
Yeah.
All right.
Thank you, sir.
I'll get her cleaned up.
What else do you need, son?
Na, we're all
right, Uncle Charlie...
Ty, what do you need?
We need tires, sir.
Is that all?
Just need tires, sir.
Why don't you go up to Sweats
and pick out what you want,
put it on the account, okay?
Wow.
Thank you, Uncle Charlie.
Really appreciate it.
You seen Frank?
Yeah, I saw Frank.
I don't know if he's
gonna turn out to be
the big football star he
thought he was gonna be.
I think he's a little
bit embarrassed.
Maybe he'll come back here
and go to work for you.
Uncle Charlie, I just
wanted you to know that
I appreciate any opportunity
you have for me here.
I just hope you know that.
You just tell me what
you want me to do.
I want you to win that race, Ty.
Yes, sir.
Hey.
Trying to get me in trouble?
No, I just wanted to see
what all the talk was about.
The big investment.
Don't you have work?
No, we close at
noon on Tuesdays.
There's not too much to see yet.
Has my daddy stopped by
to give you a hard time yet?
Na.
It's a fight, right?
What time do you get off?
About four o'clock.
What do you usually
do afterwards?
Go home, work on my car.
Every day.
Yeah, pretty much every day.
Well, what about today?
What you got in mind?
Let's go somewhere.
What's your daddy
gonna think about that?
Shouldn't have said
those things to you.
Yeah, probably right, you know?
You're going off
to college and all.
Well, I didn't say I
wasn't going to college,
but I'm not gone yet.
Okay.
I'd get cleaned up first.
That's fine.
You can just pick me
up when you're done.
Whoa, wait, your house?
Sure.
Why not?
Okay.
- Hey.
Your daddy's not home is he?
No, but he will be
when you drop me off.
Uncle Charlie owns
about 500 acres.
Daddy used to come out
and fish right here.
Why not anymore?
Daddy's not in real good health.
So you tell Snake?
Yeah.
How'd he take it?
Not well.
I just don't get it.
Why Snake?
I mean of all the guys in town.
Snake.
It's a small town.
A girl can have a little fun.
God, Ty, you act
like I married him.
It was nothing.
Okay.
Can you please, please
not think of anything
about Snake or
racing for one night?
Just one.
I just know how I'm
supposed to beat him.
I mean, he's got
everything money can buy.
I mean, money gets
you more horsepower.
More horsepower gets
you up to the front.
And not to mention he's
got a whole car dealership
full of mechanics
working for him.
Full of tires.
I mean, tires are probably
the most important part.
I mean, I...
Well, you're lucky
somebody shut off that loader
before you killed
yourself in it.
I told them to take
me back to the office,
they took me here anyway.
Come on, Daddy, not everyone
can tell the difference
with heatstroke and
passed out drunk.
I know.
Well, how are we
gonna pay for this?
We'll be all right.
Yeah, if somebody can keep a job
when he's smashed on bourbon.
We ain't got doctor's
insurance, right?
Dang.
Well, I mean, we got what?
Three hundred a month
around the office, right?
We got payments on at
the loader and the pit.
I guess, I can stop
putting money into the car.
You ain't just sit there
and get pickle all day
while I pay for everything.
I guess, I'll live there, too.
You don't even
talk like that, son.
Don't make me think
like that, Daddy.
Dang, Daddy.
You look ridiculous.
Get up.
This place is too expensive
to lie there and dry up.
Bye, Ty.
All right, man.
Hey, brother.
Cause some heart
attacks around here.
Hey, check that out.
Yeah, got a fan.
Whatever.
So you have a number
all over town.
It's like you were Kyle
Petty or something.
What you know about Kyle Petty?
I underestimate
you, Tyler Hargrove.
I figure you did your
shopping in the city.
Family practitioners aren't
exactly millionaires, Ty.
All the money's in the
specialty practices.
Come on, it can't be that bad.
You got some pretty nice stuff.
Yeah, no, it's not that bad.
But with college
expenses coming up
it doesn't hurt to be frugal.
Oh, hey, look.
Oh, I have no idea.
I think you'd look
good in anything.
Thank you.
Damn, this thing's fine.
How long did he say
you can keep it for.
I don't know.
He said he didn't need it.
Dang, man.
Hey, how long you got for lunch?
About an hour.
Is that gonna give us
enough time to get these tires
and take them back
to your place?
Man, if we just got
enough time to buy them,
throw them in the truck, and
stare at them a little bit
that'd be enough for me.
Good luck, Ty.
Thanks, Betsy.
Good luck tomorrow night, Ty.
Bringing the whole family.
Thank you, Mr. Chase.
Welcome.
We put your car magnet on.
Thank y'all for supporting me.
I really appreciate that.
Go get them, Ty.
Thank you, sir.
You're like a dang movie star.
Come on, man.
Huh?
Oh, yeah.
That's the one.
Oh, look here.
Hi, Lurvy.
Hey, Becky.
He's been dreaming about engines
since the day he was born.
I'm telling you, Ty.
It ain't shiny, but
it might be as good.
Well, so what?
You think you can
beat Snake now?
I said might be as
good, not as good.
What's Snake's real name?
Well, I don't know.
But you went out with him.
Okay, so I forgot to ask.
I hate calling him that.
It's like agreeing with
him that he's good.
Right?
Lurvy can do magic
with an engine.
Now he squeezed out every last
bit of horsepower possible.
If we ever had a chance to
beat Snake, we got it now.
It's a long shot.
What the hell, man?
We ain't find the heat.
I don't know.
Maybe bad gas.
Bad gas?
Been on the same tank all night.
You boys having car trouble?
I said something to Sherry.
Son of a bitch.
I want to kill him.
You think he did it?
If he did, we can
get him disqualified.
Can't prove nothing.
Let's get back on the trailer.
We got to get back in the race.
We ain't in the race, Lurvy!
What are you doing?
Waiting on him.
He's on the winner's block, man.
Got to come this way
eventually, don't he?
Come on, you're just gonna
get us all kicked out of here.
I can't let this go, man.
Yeah, you can.
I got a better idea.
What?
Come on, follow me to the car.
What, man?
Come on.
Okay, just sit
down and cool off.
This better be good, man.
Turn one, Ty.
You can spin him on turn one.
What are you talking about, man?
I'm talking about Snake.
I watched him race tonight,
and he almost lost
it on turn one.
He still won, didn't he?
Well, yeah, but he's
slow through the turns
and fast on the straight aways.
Two times Ike Smith was right
on his tail, slid past him.
Snake got nervous then
almost lost it for no reason.
Don't you see?
No, Lurvy, he still won.
What are you trying to say?
Snake's fast, but he
can't handle the pressure.
You're fast you
don't have pressure.
You can beat him on the turns.
With these tires, hell, you
can even get low on turn three.
This car's perfect.
Yeah, except it doesn't run.
To hell with that, I
can clean out the bad gas.
You're ready to go
again in no time.
Son of a bitch.
Why don't you just
ask her to dance?
Who?
Sherry.
Oh, Sherry.
He won't ask her.
Why not?
I don't know.
Why not man?
Well, I just thought...
I don't know.
You talk to her enough.
You might as well, right?
She's right there, man.
Go ask her.
Go ask her, man.
Okay.
I will.
You seem distracted tonight.
You think?
I'm sorry.
You still have a
chance, don't you?
Statistically, yes.
But realistically it's over.
Oh, come on.
All you have to do
is win next weekend.
Snake can't do any
better than third place.
Two things I've
never seen happen.
Well, I think you can do it.
Still hasn't asked her.
You're no fun tonight.
Sorry.
Just wore out and pissed off.
Wanna get out of here?
Do this another night?
Sure.
I'll walk you to your car.
Hey, Blake.
Hey, Ty.
Man, I am sorry
about last night.
What happened?
Car trouble, man.
Well, you still got
a shot though, right?
It's not looking good, you know?
It's a long shot.
Oh, come on.
There's always next year.
I mean, think
about it, right now
you have an incredible job,
the most awesome sponsor,
dude, it's just
a matter of time.
Yeah, you're
probably right, man.
I appreciate it.
Thanks, brother.
Have a good one, man.
Yeah.
Hey, Daddy.
Daddy!
I know how much he meant to you.
You think it would've been
me have a heart attack.
Me, right?
I don't want to
talk about it, Daddy.
All right?
Yeah, you might as
well get started.
Don't hold back
on account of me.
Put that down.
Hey, put it down.
It ain't right you were too
damn drunk to go see him.
What I got now, Daddy?
Daddy, what I got now?
Nothing.
Hey, Ty.
Hey, Frank.
Aunt Paula.
Just thought I'd come by
and see if there's
anything I can do.
I don't know what
all this is, Ty.
He always took care
of everything himself.
You know that.
Customers are calling
asking me questions.
Lyle Fleming called, wants
to know what's going on
at the concrete plant.
Oh, isn't there like a manual
or handbook or something?
Look, you guys deal with Cindy
and all the office
procedures, all right?
I'll take care of everything
outside the office,
the yard, everything else.
Tell Dr. Fleming to
come see me, all right?
You want me to go
out there with you,
I'll go out there with you.
Sure, man, come on.
Thank you, Ty.
I hope you like
tomato sandwiches.
Yes, ma'am, thank you.
It's become a habit.
Ty, thank you for everything.
Welcome, ma'am,
least I could do.
Come on, Frank.
Bye, sweetheart.
I can do this.
What a mess.
Uncle Charlie meant
a lot around here.
They'll come through for him.
Who's in charge now?
I guess Frank.
I mean of this place.
I don't plan on quitting.
Are we gonna stay on schedule?
Unfortunately, I had to
miss a day for the funeral.
Yeah, all right.
Ready to lay in about a month.
Hey.
I'm really sorry, Ty.
How are you?
Been better.
Daddy said you're in charge now.
I guess for now I am, yep.
You'll be okay, Ty.
Na.
Na, I won't be crap.
The only guy who gave
me a chance is dead.
You'll be all right, though.
What you doing coming
around here anyway?
I came to see you.
Your Daddy was right, okay?
You're out of your
league with me.
Why don't you stop
messing with my head?
I don't need it.
That's not fair, Ty.
Fair?
Fair's in your life, not mine.
I gave you a chance.
All right.
Where the hell you been, man?
How do I get into this thing?
Oh, Daddy must have locked it.
All right, look.
Go find me a crowbar, then
let's go over everything again...
No, forget all that, Lurvy.
That's done, man.
What are you talking about?
The championship's
in two days, man.
What's the point, man?
Even if we win, which we won't,
we can't make it
to Phoenix City.
Costs money, Lurvy.
Fuel, hotels, crew.
We got none of it.
You got money for gas,
hotel rooms, crew?
Do you?
No.
Then it ain't
gonna happen, is it?
We ain't got the God
danged entry free.
Just forget it, man.
Listen, Ty.
I'm sorry about Uncle Charlie.
I really am, but you can't just
come in here and quit on us.
I'm tired, man.
I'm tired of trying.
All right, I'm done with this.
We're done with this.
Okay, fine.
If you can find me a key to
this thing you're gonna feel...
I told you it's over!
Try your way.
I'm gonna do my part.
Forget Phoenix city, we
could at least win locals.
All right, I'm just
gonna get it on out there
for everybody to see.
I don't want nobody saying
I didn't do my part.
I do what I say I'm gonna do.
Ty, excuse me.
Ma'am.
Alabama utility wants to
know if they're order is ready.
Yeah, it's bundled
up in the back lot.
Thank you.
Aunt Paula, you know
there's a radio inside
you use to call down here.
You don't have to
keep coming out.
I'll have to remember that.
Maybe I just wanted to get out.
You don't look so good.
I'll be all right.
We both will, won't we?
Yes, ma'am, we're just fine.
Thank you, Ty.
Hey, Ty.
Hey, man.
Hey, do you still have
the keys to this truck?
Yeah.
Cool, can I just get
them back from you.
I'm trying to get everything...
Sure, man, it's your truck.
I'll just grab a ride from Reed.
Yeah, you're done
with it, right?
It's yours, man.
Thanks.
All right, brother.
Hey, where's Ty?
He ain't coming.
What?
Look, you tell anybody
who asks I was here,
and I had it ready.
What happened?
I don't know, Sherry,
he's just messed up.
Look, you better go
back in the stands
before they close
the gate on you.
Your daddy said you'd be here.
Lurvy came by my
house before the race.
He's dragging that
thing out there?
Says he is.
You know he also says
you're not going.
That's right.
You know Uncle Charlie
would want you to.
You know, Ty, there's two
kinds of people in the world.
People that watch things happen,
and the people that
make them happen.
I thought that was you.
I thought you were
the one to say
to hell with the
cards I'm dealt,
I'm making my own way, and
anyone who wants to go with me.
You know my daddy's taking
me to the race tonight?
You even got him
believing in you.
What do I say to him now?
Ladies and
gentlemen, welcome to the
Deep South Speedway.
We're about to rock and roll
in a country sort of way,
and if you're lucky,
you'll get dirty.
And first place in the
modifiers go to Jimmy Hacker
out of Kansas.
Now ladies and gentlemen, the
even we've all come here for.
The street style championship,
but I'm sorry to
say that Ty Hargrove
is not in the out suit.
He's cutting it
awful close, isn't he?
Well, if you're ever looking
to join the winning team...
I ain't looking.
If you change your
mind... Son of a!
Hey, man, get in here.
You're a dead man Hargrove!
You're dead.
She said you're coming,
I didn't believe her.
You got it ready?
Hell, yeah, I got it ready.
Hey, remember turn one.
I remember.
Hey, I'm sorry, man.
It's all right, man.
Come on.
Oh, she said to give you
this when you got here.
Knock them dead.
Well, tonight's
the night, folks.
Defending champion Snake
Turner takes on local celebrity
Ty Hargrove for the
Newberry automotive cup,
and I take it that the state
championship in Phoenix City.
Snake Turner keeps the lead,
but Ty Hargrove's
right in his backyard.
Keep the pressure on him, Ty.
You got it.
Snake's.
Ty Hargrove takes the lead.
Yes!
And Ike Smith moves
into the second.
What an upset!
And Ty Hargrove
wins the Newberry
Our boy's going to state.
We'd like to thank y'all
for coming out tonight.
We got refreshments and
barbecue in the back,
and don't forget the
t-shirts and decals
with all your favorite drivers.
We hope you all had
a good old time.
Yeah, what you say, boy?
I love you, man.
You know, doctors are known
for making stupid investments.
I hope this isn't one.
Serious?
I guess I can trust
you with my money,
I can trust you
with my daughter.
I think you got
that backwards, but
I was wrong, I admit it.
You make us proud at state.
What about the pole mill?
It'll wait on you.
Oh, yeah, we're
going to Phoenix City!
♪ Let's get dirty ♪
♪ He got dirt tattooed
on his right forearm ♪
♪ D-I-R-T ♪
♪ He used to be a
NASCAR fan until he lost ♪
♪ D-A-L-E ♪
♪ But on Saturday night
with all his redneck friends ♪
♪ As far as you could see ♪
♪ Sitting in the grand
stand screaming out ♪
♪ Let's get dirty ♪
♪ Ten thousand race
fans loud and proud ♪
♪ Screaming let's get dirty ♪
♪ Let's get dirty ♪
♪ Let's get down ♪
♪ We gonna watch them little
boys go round and round ♪
♪ Let's get dirty ♪
♪ Let's get down ♪
♪ Line them up ♪
♪ Let's get crunk ♪
♪ Let's get loud ♪
Yes, yes!
Yes!
Oh, yes!
Ty, yes!
You did it, man!
You did it!
Yes, yes!
Sherry!
Yeah, Snake, you like that?
That's how you drive.
Yes!
Too much?