Heard anything
from back home?
No, I don't want to
talk about it.
I reckon
my folks gonna be okay.
Big gun collectors,
you know.
Nobody is gonna get within
half a mile of their place.
Can you just stop talking?
Hear that?
Yeah,
it sounds like a rabbit.
Should try to shoot it.
Rations are running low
around here.
Oh, crap!
Shit!
Sir, wish to report.
-What's happening?
-Sector C, sir.
Just got a breach
about one of those things
-off the news.
-How widespread?
I don't know, sir.
I only saw a handful.
Want me to do
a quick recon, sir?
-Affirmative.
-I'll go with you.
Go.
We're barricaded
inside the officer's mess.
We're holding out,
but I don't know for how long.
Call Camp Northolt.
Request immediate air cover
and evacuation.
- Yes, sir.
- We're not secure here, sir.
I'm not leaving my post,
Lieutenant.
I don't think we're gonna
make it to anywhere safe.
You hesitate again
and I will fucking shoot you.
Sir, yes sir.
Sir, Northolt
is under attack as well
and unable
to provide support.
-Any other bases we can call?
-Not at this time, sir.
Sir,
Lieutenant Jenkins calling.
Lieutenant, report.
with four others, sir.
Prepared
to take back the camp.
-Good man.
-I hope he gets here in time.
He will.
I haven't been bitten,
it's just a burn.
Fine, leave it.
We seem to be
regaining control, sir.
What levels casualties
have we suffered?
Many personnel were unable
to access weapons.
The enemy are moving so fast,
most never stood a chance.
How long
until we regain control?
Unsure, sir.
But if you'll excuse me,
I'll get back to just that.
Of course, Lieutenant.
It's clear. Come on.
Come on.
Oh, shit!
Go back, go back, go back!
Come on!
This just in.
All citizens
are to remain indoors.
The military
are on the streets.
But initial reports say
they are unable
to maintain control.
The military
has advised everyone
to barricade their home
and stay inside.
There's no need to go out
to try and find guns
or weapons
to protect yourself.
Emergency services
are doing the best they can,
but they are being
overwhelmed
by the sheer magnitude
of the disaster.
Ramifications
of this situation
stretched far beyond
the current instability
with the production
of oil at a standstill.
People have been setting fires
in a desperate attempt
at creating
some form of barricade.
This has been working,
but the fires have spread.
Just as the world
has recovered
from one virus,
we now have to
deal with another.
A virus,
unbelievably,
that seems to be
bringing the dead
back to life.
Can I have you look up?
- Yeah. To the side.
- Attention!
As you were.
What's the status report,
doctor?
Well, as of right now,
General, we're fine.
92% of surviving personnel
suffered scratches,
62% serious cuts.
Most, if not all,
suffered possible infection
of said wounds
through hostile blood
or saliva.
So nearly all my soldiers
could be infected?
Could be,
we're monitoring them.
How you feeling,
Corporal?
I'm fine, sir.
I wish I was back outside,
though.
I feel like
I'm wasting my time here.
Well, we need you
back outside,
but don't rush it.
You aren't feeling
any changes?
Let's be honest, sir,
I'm not sure
how I should be feeling.
This whole thing
has left me feeling shook up.
You'll get used to it.
How's the burn?
Healing well, sir.
Nothing else, thankfully.
Very good.
It sounds like you'll be fine.
Yes, sir,
I'm sure I will be.
-Sit tight for a minute.
-Okay.
If anything did occur,
how fast
would you expect it to happen?
I'm not--
not entirely sure, sir.
It's just
new territory for us.
We do know
that in death...
it's immediate.
Deep bites,
nearly as fast.
However, with infection,
we don't offer
natural immune system
to fight it off.
And that's why I've had
Captain Wahta brought in here.
You think
the taser's going to work?
Taser will work.
They ain't fully turned yet,
then yes.
Well, maybe.
We got the mask
we placed over their head
the first sign
of any trouble.
Then we can place handcuffs,
try to restrain them.
Then what?
Then we try
to change 'em back.
And if we can't...
we may have to kill them.
Very good, doctor.
You keep me updated
and check
all exposed personnel
every two hours.
Yes, sir.
I had the guys in bayonets
build it
as strong as possible.
Very good, Captain.
Sir.
one more time.
What is it?
Sorry, sir,
I've got Lieutenant
Henderson's wife outside.
He's still the only one
unaccounted for.
Can't the welfare officer
deal with this?
The welfare officer
is out there with her.
Very well, send her in.
I'm sure you must be
very busy right now.
With everyone else, sir,
they know what happened.
They can now go through
the period of mourning
and adjustment.
I'm sorry to disturb you,
General,
but I'd like to know
what has happened
to my husband?
He remains unaccounted for
at this moment, I'm afraid.
The thought of him,
out there,
turned into
one of those things.
It's unlikely.
What little
information we have
tells us they don't retreat,
they just keep coming.
So you think
he might be alive?
We are trying to
ascertain his whereabouts,
all we know for sure
is that he hasn't turned.
Sir, I'm reporting
on camp security.
-How's it going?
-Good, sir.
The barbed wire is back up.
Every mine we have
is forming an outer perimeter.
Only clear way in
is down the main road.
What's to stop them
from coming that way?
Explosives, sir.
We have them
planted in the road
points.
They need to be
detonated manually.
Who's in charge
of the explosives?
That Norwegian civilian,
sir.
The one who came
to teach that course.
Right,
when he's finished,
tell him to report
to Lieutenant Whitmore.
-Yes, sir.
-You are dismissed.
Morning, sir.
Lieutenant Whitmore
sends his apologies.
-Is your team ready to leave?
-Yes, sir.
Lieutenant Whitmore
would like me to submit
a request for more supplies,
sir.
Sergeant, we gave you
what can be spared.
Reinforcements
will be arriving in 48 hours.
Thank you, sir.
In the midst of chaos,
there is also opportunity.
God help us.
We're running
really low on fuel, Sergeant.
Any idea
how much further?
Shouldn't be
too much farther.
Sarge, just how long
are we expected to be here?
You think
there's somewhere better?
Well, it's just not too safe
of a place, that's all.
What,
do you feel safer in camp?
-You know what I mean.
-No, I don't.
We'll be fine.
Should be about there.
Good. Copy that.
It's about time.
Shit, my ass done went numb
fucking miles ago.
enough.
Enough?
Man, you've been bitching
the entire way,
can we get about
five minutes?
Enough.
Can it, you guys.
What do you reckon?
The wooden pilings
will be no problem.
That doable?
Sure.
Right. Hernandez.
I want you and Eckland
to wire the bridge.
Yes, sir.
The rest of you,
I want sandbags,
right across here.
There's bags and shovels
in the back
of the second Humvee.
-Yes, sir.
All right, good.
What's the story
with the ring?
Oh.
Yeah,
it's the law of nature.
Life eats life.
Look,
I got your back out here...
but we can't be friends.
LT.
You notice that?
Okay, Lynn, Rudd,
I want you guys
to scout ahead.
If you encounter any hostiles,
do not engage.
Understood?
-Yes, sir.
Go.
The rest of you,
I want
filling those sandbags.
I want a defensive position
by nightfall.
Sir.
Is that all we got?
It's what I was given.
These cables and detonators
are, like, ancient.
Whatever happened
to the ordinance
I was given for my course?
They are probably planted
around the camp's perimeter.
This is what was left.
Can you do this?
I can rig it up...
but I don't know
if it will work.
Okay.
Get to it.
Go on.
So, he's good to go?
Well, Colonel,
yes, he's fine.
Whoa, not you.
Have a seat.
I feel fine, sir.
I haven't been
within a mile of those things.
It doesn't matter.
I need you to have seat.
Get your gear,
get ready to leave.
Yes, sir.
Sir, if you're good,
the General would like
to see you now.
Colonel Cherone, sir.
Good to see you, Colonel.
General,
I just wish it was under
-better circumstances.
-Indeed.
How many men
have you brought with you?
My driver.
Colonel,
my ranks were heavily
depleted yesterday.
I need the National Guard
to assemble immediately.
General, I understand.
My communications are down.
What men I do have
are searching for what's left.
I'm not even sure how many men
are still alive, sir.
Very well.
What intelligence
have you gathered?
Little, unreliable
and prone to rapid change.
What's a safe zone today
could be attacked
-and change in an hour.
-Understood.
That's what happened
to Northolt.
24 hours ago.
Before that base was overrun,
they made a report
of a large number of hostiles
heading their way.
Sir,
if Northolt was overrun,
the enemy's ranks
are likely much higher now.
I'm assuming so.
They were last seen
heading south.
Providing
they don't change direction,
they'll soon be
hitting the river.
The only way across
is that bridge there.
I'm sending Lieutenant Whitmore
and his team
to defend that bridge
or blow
if absolutely necessary.
I'm relying on you
to provide
enough reinforcements.
All due respect, sir,
why not just blow the bridge
straight away?
Because,
after this area's cleared,
I plan on
taking back this country
piece by piece.
I need
all infrastructure intact.
Understood, sir.
Colonel,
this has to be done quickly.
-Godspeed.
-Thank you, sir.
Any update
on the fuel search, sir?
Nothing so far.
And they keep on moving
further and further out.
We just have to get lucky,
just one time.
Well, how many times
have we been unlucky, sir?
That is none of your concern,
Lieutenant,
when they find gas,
they'll bring it in.
Have they tried
siphoning it out of cars?
My men
have done everything
apart from digging for oil.
When they find it,
they'll bring it in.
I'm sorry, sir,
but I really need that fuel.
You and everybody else.
I have the National Guard
begging me for supplies.
The National Guard?
Well, then,
how are they supposed to
send reinforcements
to the bridge?
Then I guess
you better start
praying for them,
Lieutenant.
Yes, sir.
-You reckon we take this?
-Yeah, I guess so.
All right.
Get off, you creep!
At the end
it's always yes.
Hey!
Get off of her.
Look what we got here,
honey.
Soldier boy.
Get off of her.
Just walk away.
Seems to me,
you boys need to
wait your turn.
Back off, now!
I'll be back.
Hey, don't even
think about it.
-Back off!
-If I don't?
I'll put you down.
I don't think
you boys got the balls.
Don't do it.
Back up!
Dammit.
What did I tell those two?
Do you want me to go?
Stay here with Eckland.
Make sure
the bridge gets wired.
And if a hoard approaches,
blow the bridge.
What about you?
If a hoard of those things
makes it to the bridge,
we're dead already.
-Just worry about the bridge.
-Will do.
Sharrock,
you're on guard.
The rest of you, on me.
I can get the Humvee, sir.
Leave it.
We're on foot.
I wouldn't trust
driving across this bridge.
Hey, you okay?
Are you alone?
No, uh,
there's a group of us.
Over at Lacquerie.
Okay,
let's get you there.
What the hell
happened to you?
It's okay.
None of your business,
Will.
These two
do something to you?
Would we be here if
we had?
Was I asking you?
Les, go get Big Jim.
We got trouble.
Some soldiers have turned up
with Susan.
I'll deal with it.
What happened here?
What did you do to her?
This girl here
almost got raped,
-that's what happened.
-No, no, it wasn't them.
It was Dale Harper.
What's that about, Dale?
No way,
my husband wouldn't do that.
I'll speak with him later.
Yeah,
that's gonna be hard.
You need
to get out of here.
Put that gun down,
little girl.
Put down,
we don't want this.
Enough.
Erin, step back.
I'm trying to protect us.
I'll deal with this.
Step back.
- We ain't afraid to die!
- No!
Back off!
They can't shoot us all.
Back off. Back off! Back off!
We're going to
tear you apart!
Enough!
Enough, all of you!
Get the fuck out of here.
Now get back.
Stand down.
Looks like
we have enough now.
Lin, enough.
Now, what started
all of this?
This woman right here,
she was being attacked, sir,
and we had to step in.
That's right, Lieutenant.
We gave him a chance.
What do you mean,
you gave him a chance?
Sir, he tried attacking us.
I had to put him down.
You shot Dale?
You shot my husband,
you China--
- Get off of--
- Help!
Oh, hell no.
You stay down!
Hey, what do you think
you're doing?
Nothing,
just came for a look.
Hey,
you drop that knife.
Think I'll hold on to it
for now.
You drop it
or I'll drop you.
Please don't.
It's true.
They stopped Dale.
You be saying anything
when they got guns on us.
Chet, drop the blade.
Susan, get back.
-But, but--
-Go on.
Lower your weapons.
I should warn you,
you're not safe here.
A large number of hostiles
is headed this way.
You need to pack up
and get across the river.
Hm, I think
we're safer off here.
Yeah, you ain't exactly
made a good first impression
coming in here like
a bunch of storm-troopers.
Let's go. Come on.
Yeah, like I said,
get the fuck out of here.
Fucking assholes.
All right, man,
let's all calm down.
Let's go back
to whatever you're doing.
What happened?
It was Dale,
he tried to--
I'm so sorry.
I should have been there.
I freaking knew
he was trouble.
If those soldiers
hadn't turned up...
I don't know
what would've happened.
She was a pretty hot kid.
I kinda wished
I had saved her.
Oh, knock it off,
will you?
Well, you might just be in
for a thank you later.
-How we doing?
-Okay.
Got one line rigged.
If it works,
it should be enough
-by itself.
-Sure.
While you're doing that,
I'll try and make contact.
-Sure.
-Carry on.
Echo-Five-Whiskey.
Calling Eagle One. Over.
Excuse me, General,
Lieutenant Whitmore
calling, sir.
Echo-Five-Whiskey,
this is Eagle One.
Is the location secure?
The bridge is secure.
No sign
of any hostiles here, sir.
We did encounter civilians.
A refugee camp nearby.
Did you offer them
protection?
Yes, sir. Refused.
Then they are not your concern.
Stay in position.
Any news
on the reinforcements?
Not yet.
You'll be advised. Out.
You keep trying
to raise the guard.
Yes, sir.
Shit.
That's-- that's that.
Yeah.
-Hey, Sanders.
-Yeah?
You ever wonder what's going on
with your folks?
What do you mean?
Mine are in Sacramento.
There aren't any friends
or relatives nearby.
-They don't even own a gun.
-Stop.
Stop, you have to get that
out of your mind, all right?
-My folks are in Chicago.
-Mm-hmm.
Even before
all this madness,
I had to force myself
to stop worrying about 'em.
It'll just drive you crazy.
Like Sharrock?
Hell no,
not like Sha--
Look, I knew Sharrock
from back in the day.
He was just as big
an asshole then,
than he is now,
if you can believe that.
, right?
- He's a terminal asshole.
- Yeah.
Lieutenant!
Shit!
What is it?
Something pulled the detonator
over the edge.
I'll get it.
Oh, shit!
Pull! Pull him up!
Pull him up!
Oh, what the fuck?
What the hell
could've done that?
It's heading
for the riverbank.
I want this animal killed.
Hernandez, Eckland,
stay here
and recover the detonator.
- Yes, sir.
- Come on.
Spread out.
-What is that?
-I don't know.
-What are you shooting at?
I saw something moving,
but it was so fast, I, uh--
What kind of animal was it?
It wasn't an animal.
And it wasn't one
of those things either.
Then what was it,
Sanders?
I don't know.
Wait.
Where's Frost?
He was behind me, LT.
Spread out. Find him.
We'll meet
back at the bridge.
Shit!
Oh, shit!
Here we go again.
I hate doing this shit.
Don't worry Sanders,
if you turn,
I'll take care of your ass.
Uh, thanks.
That makes me feel
a lot better.
Sure, man.
What are friends for?
We got lucky.
It's still attached
to the cables.
Good job.
Man, if you ask me,
you just throw him
over the side.
-What's wrong with you man?
-Nobody's asking you, Sharrock.
Nobody ever asks you,
Sharrock.
Yeah, whatever.
Did Frost show?
No.
Just put him
out of your mind, kid.
Lieutenant!
Sir,
something took Rudd's body.
Jesus, what next?
It must have been that animal
from last night.
What is this thing?
It doesn't matter.
I want his body found.
Start searching.
Sir, it took his body
this way.
All right.
Spread out.
- All right.
- Sir.
Shit!
Oh, crap.
Well, at least we know
what it is now.
You think this thing
was underneath the bridge
last night?
No way. Unlikely.
Are you an expert now,
Lin?
No, ma'am.
Sarge, we're going to
have to deal with this.
He's gonna turn.
I'll take care of it,
Sarge.
I've been wanting to
do this anyway.
Not you, Sharrock.
I'm now in charge.
This falls on me.
Eagle One,
this is Echo-Five-Hotel.
Come in, over.
Sir, we have Echo-Five-Hotel
on the phone, sir.
-Hotel?
-Yes, sir.
Echo-Five-Hotel,
this is Eagle One.
Where is Echo-Five-Whiskey?
Dead.
With one other confirmed dead
and one missing.
By hostiles?
Echo-Five-Whiskey, yes.
The other, uncertain.
Uncertain?
Yes, sir.
Some sort of animal.
Awaiting
further instructions.
Stay on mission,
Sergeant.
Yes, sir.
Any news on reinforcements?
None yet.
You'll be advised. Out.
Still no news
on reinforcements?
No.
So, they're at least
two days out...
-Perhaps.
-...if they come at all.
They're coming.
Even with just
the six of us,
we only have
enough supplies
for no more
than two days, Sarge.
Hey, Sarge,
why don't we just pay a visit
to the families?
Requisition
whatever food they got.
So if they had a lot
then the lieutenant
would've taken some yesterday.
They probably
haven't eaten in weeks.
Shit,
if food was that short,
I'd hide it in the woods.
Okay, tomorrow we go.
Locklin and I
will go to camp,
you two
circle through the woods
and then Eckland will stay here
and guard the bridge.
And what about Lieutenant?
I think the body
would be gone by tomorrow.
We stake it out tonight.
Locklin,
you're on guard duty first.
Roger that, Sarge.
-All right, let's head out.
-Yes, ma'am.
Where's Locklin?
I think
that was him that screamed.
So I guess that's it, huh?
We can just leave.
Right, Sarge?
-Negative.
-God, you gotta be kidding me.
The reinforcements
will be here soon.
That's bullshit
and you know it.
Here's the deal.
You're gonna call this in
and if they can't give you
a definite answer, we leave.
That's it.
I'm not making deals
with you, Sanders.
Oh, God.
We don't have the fuel
to get back, okay?
How long do you think
survive out there?
- Longer than here.
- Right.
I know that.
No, Sanders,
I think we should stay.
I don't want to
go out there.
There's something there.
Hold your fire.
-It's this way.
-Okay.
-So what's she like man?
-She's okay.
I'll tell you what, man,
she's got a freaking heartbeat,
I'm interested.
Don't try
like that.
Come on, man,
Sharrock can't be too picky
these days,
you know what I'm saying?
We gotta be civilized.
In this?
Sarge, on the left.
More of you?
Ain't you done
enough damage already?
We're not here
to see you.
I know
you ain't here to see me.
I ain't some sad bitch
you can push around.
Hey, hey,
take it easy, tough guy.
Yeah, I'm a tough guy.
We all are.
We know
you don't want us here.
- Want you here?
- Mm-hmm.
Shit,
you'd be torn apart.
Why don't you give it a rest,
huh, man?
Calm down.
What are you doing here?
One of your men
kills my husband,
you just walk back in here,
like nothing happened?
I'm sorry for your loss.
It was regrettable.
- Regrettable?
- Mm-hmm.
You call my husband's murder
regrettable?
Look, it wasn't a murder.
He had no choice.
You just talk to the girl,
she'll tell you what happened.
I don't need
to speak with her.
to hear her lies.
Maybe you should.
-How is she doing?
-Not good. Not good at all.
She's too scared
to come out of the tent
most of the time.
I can imagine
how hard it is.
This has been hard
for all of us, this business.
But this...
this is the end.
-Why not leave?
-And go where?
My son's a good man,
but when his wife died--
If you come with us now,
you and the girls
will be safe.
There's nothing
he can do with us here.
I can't do that.
He's so good
and he's been trying
so hard for us.
And he's so tired,
we're all so tired.
I know.
Sarge.
Why are you people
back again?
It's just a courtesy visit.
We encountered a couple
of those things yesterday.
Bound to be more
in the area.
Yeah, well,
we'll be fine.
How many spare rounds you got?
Enough.
Look, if they come through,
it's gonna be fast.
You and a couple of handguns
ain't gonna cut it.
You know,
you need to leave.
Every time you come here,
you bring trouble.
Look, man,
we're sorry about all that,
but you just talk to her,
she--
I don't wanna
talk about that.
How you doing for food?
Barely surviving.
Was hoping
maybe you guys help--
can help us out here.
Wish I could.
We've got nothing.
Yeah, well...
we're pretty much
near the end.
And soon we'll know
if we've been deemed
worthy or not.
Look...
whatever you do have,
start rationing.
Keep an eye out
for hostiles.
We'll take a look
around at the perimeter.
You can do that
if you want, but...
we're pretty much
in the hands of fate right now.
Let's go.
Hey, where do you think
they hid the food?
Probably a pie.
To keep it away
from the animals.
-Yeah, that's a good idea.
-Yep.
Hey, apples.
Think they're edible?
Oh, yeah.
They're in season.
Take your ass up there
and get some.
Fine.
What are you gonna do?
Make a sweep.
Make sure everything's secure.
I'll meet you
right here, man.
-Okay.
-You're okay?
I got it.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
hold up, old man.
What are you doing
out here?
No-- nothing.
Nice little stroll
through the woods.
Yeah, yeah,
that's what it is.
Where's the food stash?
I don't know,
I'm looking for it myself.
So there is one?
I think so, yeah.
-Great.
-Yeah, I think--
-Well, it's not for you.
-What?
Oh, fuck.
-Get outta here.
-But--
-Now! Go!
Go! Go!
What now, kid?
Shit.
Yeehaw, motherfucker.
Die, bitch.
All right, motherfucker.
Oh, oh.
Thank God.
Thank God?
Thanks, Sharrock.
Now shut the fuck up
and let's get
the fuck outta here.
-What about the families?
-Man, fuck the families.
You need to start thinking
about your fucking self.
You think we should leave?
I can't.
I need to take care of
father and grandma.
I hate to say this,
but don't you think
we should be a little selfish?
I can't.
That soldier
seemed to like you.
He may be the only one.
God knows
what the rest of them are like.
Maybe father was right.
Maybe it is
the end of times.
Maybe...
we're all waiting
our turn for judgment.
So how are you guys doing?
Okay, I guess.
If you'd like to leave,
we can escort you.
I guarantee
that you'll be safe.
No, thank you.
Okay.
Let's go.
Sir, I have
Lieutenant Colonel Charone
-on the radio.
-Well done.
Colonel,
this is General Vasquez,
I hope you have
good news for me?
Right now, General,
my communications
are still down.
I only have
a few men here.
Colonel, we have
a large number of hostiles
headed towards
that choke point.
I need your men there now.
Understood, sir.
My men are proving
hard to reach.
Then get anyone that can stand
and pull a trigger.
Most of them
are gonna want to stay
with their families, sir.
Tell them to bring
their families,
they'll be safer
in the camp.
Do we have the supplies
to support that, sir?
No, not at all.
But if we don't get
this area secure,
it won't matter.
Out.
hear something.
There he is. Go, now.
Hey, guys, come look.
Hey, let's go.
Wait,
I need to check the charges.
All right.
- Oh, terrific.
- It's all gone.
What kind of animal
eats that fast?
You should see the guys
in my neighborhood.
So what now, Sarge?
We take it,
we throw it into the river.
It's only good
for attracting flies.
No, no, I mean,
what the hell
do we eat now, Sarge?
We still got water,
we can hold out.
For how long?
-Well, a couple of days.
-Sarge, I can go out there
and get us some apples.
-Hey.
-Good.
-I got a great idea.
-What's that, Sharrock?
Why don't we go down
to the families and, uh,
take it by force
this time?
-Lin, you and I go tomorrow.
-Yes, ma'am.
Sanders,
get to cleaning this up.
Move, let's go!
Terrific.
What kind of animal
leaves a trail like this?
I've never seen
tracks like this before.
I don't know,
keep looking.
- Damn it!
- What?
Most of the charges are gone.
What do you mean, gone?
Did they fall off?
They were secure.
If the bridge
is still here,
the charges
should still be here.
It knows what it's doing.
-What have you got left?
-One set.
Okay, get it off
and up top.
That won't bring
the bridge down.
I don't care.
Need eyes on it at all times.
It will at least
blow the pilings.
Oh, okay, where then?
Okay, see that sand bag?
Go, right there.
Jävla helvetes!
Hold it!
Keep the cans.
I want them filled
with stones and hung by wire
-underneath the bridge.
-Yes, ma'am.
A bit old school,
ain't it, Sarge?
We do everything we can
to stay safe.
Well, why don't we just
blow the damn bridge
and get the hell
outta here?
I told you,
this mission's vital.
People's lives
are at stake.
Well,
I'm not so convinced.
It's not my job
to convince you, Sharrock.
It's to just
give you orders.
Yeah, orders.
Go, stones, now.
-You, too.
-Yes, ma'am.
It's just me, kid.
What you got?
I heard something.
I think it was that thing.
Well, maybe.
Look, kid,
I'm no Harvard scholar,
but I know
when I'm being played.
And right now,
we're being played.
Get what you gotta get,
and let's get outta here.
Looking kinda hungry,
Sarge.
Thinking about
going back to that camp?
If we go in,
we have to go in hard.
They won't just give it up.
Roger that,
but there may be casualties.
Unfortunately.
We gotta do
what we have to do.
You ain't coming here.
Big Jim!
Empty.
They're here to kill us.
You aim those guns,
you better be prepared
to use them.
That guy carrying
the shotgun was just
- carrying it for show.
- Hmm.
-I don't think they have shit.
-You don't wanna find out.
You've got the mag, tough guy.
Show us what you got.
It must've been
a rough road getting here.
Must've had to shoot
a lot of people.
Yeah.
Got no problem
shooting more.
Drop it.
Okay, boys.
Put 'em down.
On the ground.
Go. Ground.
It's not even loaded.
All clear, Sergeant.
So what do you want?
Any supplies that you have.
They're coming with us.
Yeah, and you're just gonna
leave us here to starve, right?
Staying here
with no weapons...
I figure you got
about a day or two at most.
Get out!
Hurry up!
Oh, hell.
I heard about you.
They said you was fine,
girl, but...
you don't smell so good.
What do you expect?
We're running low
on water.
Well, maybe
that's where I can help you.
We've got plenty of water
down by the river.
You wanna go?
-No, I'm okay.
-You sure?
Hey, you know,
you can just leave her alone.
Well, shit.
Two of y'all.
You gotta hygiene problem,
woman.
You don't smell
too fine yourself.
-Excuse me?
-Hey, Sharrock, knock it off.
Came here
for supplies only.
-Let's go.
-That is supplies, brother.
What did they want?
Our food.
Look, right now, everybody,
we're all out for ourselves.
If you give it to them,
they're just gonna leave you.
They're gonna drop you flat.
So what are we going to do?
Stick with family,
all right?
Shit, she's coming.
Smells like cooking.
So, is this
the camp's kitchen?
When we had food,
it was.
You can't go in there.
Yeah, you think
you can stop me?
If you didn't have
that gun, yeah.
Look, I grew up
with little boys like you
getting all tough
and pushing around girls.
I'm sorry,
you've been misinformed.
You have no idea
what I'm capable of.
Move.
You believe us now?
You've got something
somewhere.
No, we haven't.
It doesn't look like
you're starving.
Shit.
No, it's okay.
He's just sick.
He looks infected to me.
It's the fucking flu
or something.
You checked him for bites?
No, I haven't checked him.
Check him yourself.
Sarge,
that's not a good idea.
I know.
Look, if he dies, he'll turn.
He'll bring
all of you down.
No, I'll be fine.
Deal with this.
If anything goes wrong,
this is on you.
So, that means
I want everybody
on half rations.
Sanders, Lin, listen up.
Half rations,
no full apples anymore.
Also,
I want charges checked
so make sure that
you check with Eckland,
I want everything intact.
-Sanders?
-Yeah.
You'll be first
going down to the river,
collect water, bathe,
do what you need to do.
-We'll take turns doing that.
-Okay.
And then on duty tonight,
Sharrock, it's you.
Okay.
Go, go, go!
Go!
-They're coming!
Evacuate the bridge.
Get ready to blow it!
Move! Go!
Go, go, go!
-Come on, bitches.
-It's not working.
, it's two!
Everyone,
every single shot counts.
I'm out, I'm out!
Shit.
Sharrock's got this.
-Nice shooting, Lin.
-Nice job.
Although, that leaves us
pretty low on ammo.
So Lin's out.
What about the rest of you?
One in the breech, Sarge.
Okay, copy.
Sharrock, ammunition report?
Me too,
one in the chamber.
-Okay.
-How about you?
-I got enough.
-What does that mean?
-You gonna share?
-Not right now.
They're staying here
with me.
Oh, come on, Sarge,
wouldn't it make more sense
if we all had ammo?
In case we get
a surprise attack?
They're staying right here.
Hey, Sanders...
do you think
we should let Sarge,
uh, torch the Humvees?
No, no.
Hey, look,
you did good back there, kid.
-Pretty good shooting.
-Thanks.
-But what now?
-Well, who knows?
Everybody
just keep on walking
and get
the hell outta here, huh?
So what happened
with the charge?
- I don't know.
- You don't know?
No,
it could be the cable,
it could be the detonator.
-Shit.
-They're all...
Right. Okay.
Here's what
I want you to do.
I want you to cut off
the best piece of cable
and rig it
straight to the detonator.
But...
that would mean
you would go up with it, too.
It might not come to that.
Do it!
Eckland!
Oh, shit, it's got him.
-You three, guard the bridge.
-Wait, what?
Sarge,
you don't want to do this.
He has the last detonator.
He's under my command.
I will do the same
for any of you.
If he's still alive
when you get there,
-he won't be worth saving.
-I'm doing this.
Sarge, we've only got
two rounds left here.
-Take my gun...
-No!
...and take my ammo,
stop it.
- I'm going.
- This is a bad idea.
-Sarge, no!
-Yes, yes! Out of my way.
Sarge!
He's definitely
on his way out.
What are we gonna do?
You know
what's gonna happen
-if he dies, right?
-Want me to take care of him?
Won't do it here.
Take him out to the woods.
Yeah, just leave him
out in the woods.
Snap his neck.
Bury him real deep.
What are you,
a serial killer?
I just work in an abattoir.
You get used to it.
What is this making us?
It's making us survivors.
- Oh, my God!
- Just go!
Man, I don't know
about y'all,
but we need to
get the fuck outta here.
I hate to say it,
but I think he's right.
But what about Sarge?
Well,
she ain't coming back, kid.
You saw
what that thing can do.
Get back,
you son of a bitch.
No!
They're in trouble,
we've gotta go help them.
Man, fuck that, Lin.
By the time we get over there,
they'll be fucking dead.
Sanders, please.
No.
All right,
come on, let's go.
Oh, hell no,
I ain't dying for your bad.
Come on, guys.
Hey, hey!
Hey, guys, knock it off.
- Motherfucker!
- Come here!
We're on the same team,
knock it off.
Sharrock, enough!
Knock it off!
-You outta control, man.
-Oh, yeah?
Oh, you want to do
, huh?
You wanna die?
Come on,
you sons of bitches!
Oh, my God,
it's Peter Ryan.
Oh, no,
they've got Peter.
Peter! Peter!
No! Peter.
Fuck.
Fuck!
- I'm sorry, man.
- Sorry?
-I'm sorry, man.
-You stabbed me.
-I'm sorry.
-What the fuck--
I didn't mean that.
What did you fucking do,
man?
He was outta control, man,
I didn't mean it.
-Fuck you, Sanders!
-I didn't mean it.
Yeah, fuck you, dude.
I'm sorry.
Fuck.
No, no, no.
It's on me.
Sorry, brother.
No!
Oh, shit!
This ends now!
Thank God you arrived.
I thought
we were going to die.
We're still
not out of the woods yet.
Oh.
Where are the keys?
Oh, no.
My dad has them.
Oh, crap.
-Thanks, kid.
-Yeah, no problem.
Got 'em, let's go!
♪ Only the blind will see ♪
♪ Only the fools will know ♪
♪ Only the meek shall ♪
♪ Inherit the world ♪
♪ If they just ♪
♪ Hold on ♪
♪ Only the good die young ♪
♪ Making a living,
killing time ♪
♪ Only the good die young ♪
♪ Making a living,
killing time ♪
Stop the car!
Sanders, stop! It's Sarge.
Sarge,
where have you been?
Just drive.
Go!
Stop.
Stop the car!
You need to let me off
at the bridge.
I need to detonate it.
Sarge, you'll die.
Look at me.
Look at me, Lin!
I have to do this.
Did you really think
I'd survive this?
Go. Go.
Go!
Oh, my God.
What happened?
Go! Go!
Go around.
I'm stuck!
It's over.
We can't go anywhere.
No! No!
What?
Oh, my God!
Help! Help!
- No! No!
- Oh, my God!
Go!
There's nothing I can do!
Sir, we've got
some live ones!
Take 'em down!
Yes, sir!
Check our tail.
Come on, go!
Go! Go!
Come on, watch your step,
it's a long way down.
Here you go, you're good.
Go, go, go!
Come on, buddy,
you got it.
Good. Come on.
here we go.
I wasn't really sure
they could pull this off, sir.
If the goal
is big enough,
a calculated risk
is acceptable.
Did you really think
they were gonna do it?
I figured
they had a chance.
Well, you take
enough calculated risk,
you have enough success
to make it worthwhile.
-Isn't that right?
-Indeed.
All right, here we go.
Watch your step.
Ma'am, were you bitten?
No, he didn't get me
-Are you sure?
-Yeah.
Oh, my God, but I thought
I was gonna die.
All right, Craig,
let's take care of this lady.
Make sure
she's checked out by the doc.
Yes, sir.
You come with me, ma'am.
It's gonna be all right,
ma'am.
Shit.
Sir,
it's good to see you.
Good to see you made it,
what of the rest?
Eckland, nobody knows.
He's presumed dead.
Looks like
you've still got it, Major.
It would appear so, sir.
Sir, Lieutenant Jenkins
reporting, sir.
Sir, we just found out
the civilians were
from a camp up ahead.
Would you like us to scout
ahead for any survivors?
Negative,
just secure the bridge.
Copy.
Sir,
there could still be hostiles.
Do you want us
to scout it out,
hunt 'em down?
No need,
they'll come to us.
Got it.
Watch out
for that one right there.
-Doug!
-Yes, Colonel!
Check out
this woman in green.
She's showing
signs of infection,
she needs to be quarantined.
Get away.
Get away from her.
It's too late.
Listen to me!
It's too late!
-No! No!
-Come on, go!
Let's go.
Listen to me.
Get her off the bridge!
Get her off
the goddamned bridge!
Colonel, the next time
you kill one of these things,
do it so their heads
don't explode.
Now we have
vaporized blood in the air,
and we could all
get infected!
-Nakamura!
-Yes, sir.
Clear this goddamn bridge.
At least something
went right about her.
Sir.
What about Hernandez?
I'm turning.
General,
we've got one of yours, sir.
I'm turning.
You gotta
take care of this, General.
Not yet.
She needs to know.
Sergeant...
you achieved your mission.
You should be proud.
You won't be forgotten.
So many were lost.
But so many will survive now.
Because of you,
they will.
General...
please,
take me out of my misery.
Please, General.
Please.
What now, sir?
Now we secure the bridge.
And later, we're gonna
take back this country.
Everybody good?
♪ We walk alone ♪
♪ Alone in the darkness ♪
♪ In the darkness ♪
♪ The blackness is real ♪
♪ Like inside a grave ♪
♪ Creeps look around ♪
♪ Waiting for victims ♪
♪ If they get you ♪
♪ You can't ♪
♪ Cannot be saved ♪
♪ What doesn't kill me ♪
♪ Doesn't kill me ♪
♪ I'd better start running ♪
♪ to thrill me ♪
♪ So you'd better kill me ♪
♪ Or better start running ♪
♪ Running ♪
♪ We will survive ♪
♪ With hiding in shadows ♪
♪ They're coming to get us ♪
♪ The threat is so real ♪
♪ They won't seem to die ♪
♪ We must unite ♪
♪ And stand together ♪
♪ To survive this ♪
♪ It's time
for fight or flight ♪
♪ What doesn't kill me ♪
♪ Doesn't kill me ♪
♪ I'd better start running ♪
♪ to thrill me ♪
♪ So you better kill me ♪
♪ Or better start running ♪
♪ Running ♪
♪ What doesn't kill me ♪
♪ Doesn't kill me ♪