When I was 14, my sister found
20 bags of crack
and a gun in my closet.
She threw them in the river
'cause she didn't know if I had
shot somebody or not.
She warned me not to keep
going down that road.
I didn't listen to her.
I got arrested and I went up
north for five years.
She came to see me,
tried to make it look like
everything was alright.
But I could tell she started
using again.
I looked at my whole life
and what I've done.
People just trying to get by
and how I used to prey on them.
And now they preyed
on my sister.
When those gates opened
and I got out,
I wasn't the same person
that I was when I went in.
'Cause now I have something
I never had before.
I have a reason.
Whoa, what's up, bro?
Where you coming from?
A friend's house.
What are you doing in the back
of this alley by yourself, man?
You know how dangerous
it is back here?
Going home.
Where the hell is your
parents at, man?
I don't know.
Look, you remind me when
I was little, man.
You can't be walking
around here.
People gonna take
advantage of you.
You're gonna have drug dealers
promising you things,
you're gonna be
doing dumb things,
you're gonna be robbing people,
disrespecting old people.
I'm fed up seeing kids
walking the streets
doing this and nobody cares.
I'm tired of doing dirt,
I don't want to do dirt no more
and I don't want to see
you out here no more,
you understand me?
Yes.
Now, I'm gonna give you
some money
'cause I know you probably
didn't eat.
And you can tell you parents
or don't tell them,
but here, here you go.
Make sure you spend it
on some food, man.
Don't give it to nobody else,
you understand me?
And I better not see your ass
back here again.
Now, get out of here.
And put some pep in your
fucking step,
get to steppin'.
Find some friends
to play with, boy.
My brother ain't shittin', man.
We done like... like five armed
robberies and shit, right?
On the last one,
when we was coming out,
a customer was coming in.
I tell my brother,
"Yo, we gotta snatch this cat"
"'cause he's a witness."
You know what I'm saying? "Let's
put this dude in the trunk",
"you know what I'm saying?
If not,"
"you know what I'm saying, 9 out
of 10 we gonna get knocked."
But my brother said,
"Nah, man, fuck it. We good."
So, I said,
"Alright let's go."
We jumps in the whip,
we riding through Nine.
All of a sudden,
I look in the mirror,
I see the police but he don't
put his lights on.Word.
So, my brother like,
"Yo, it's the police!"
I said, "Yeah, chill, chill,
relax, relax."
Alright? So, as we sitting there
at a red light,
all of a sudden the light
come on, "Whoo-whoo-whoo!"
So, my brother's like, "Yo, what
you want me to do?"
I said, "Pull out, nigger!"
He said, "Go through the light?"
I said, "Yeah!"
So, my brother just pulls out
behind the other cars
and just shoots across on 9-W.
That's what I'm talking about.
Right? So, we flyin'.
Next thing I know, I look...
We got, like, 15 police cars
behind us. Shit was crazy.
So my brother's like,
"Yo, son, I don't wanna die."
I'm telling him to go
through the road block.
You know what I'm saying?
He's like...
"Yo, you lived your life,
I ain't trying to go to jail,"
yada-yada-yada.
He said,
"Yo, man!" I thought about it,
I was like, "You know what?"
That's the only reason
I surrendered.
'Cause I was gonna go
through the roadblock.
Ah, man.
So, we threw the gats
out of the car and all that,
we surrender. I end up getting,
like, 12 years for that.
That's what I'm saying, man.
The game ain't no joke.
That's why this shit now
that we're doing with Ulysses,
I ain't got time to play games,
know what I'm saying?
'Cause I'm batty-batty with them
guns, you know what I'm saying?
Yeah, man.
Life is real.
I'm Keisha.
Hey.
Thanks for seeing me.
No problem.
I heard about what happened
to your sister.
I'm sorry about that.
Uh, Tammy said maybe
you could help me.
What's going on?
Do you know Derek Young?
No.
Oh.
Well, I started seeing him
about six months ago.
You know want to
tell me about it?
Yo.
You seen Derek Young?
No.
No, I haven't seen him.
What's up?
You seen Derek Young?
Yo. You Derek Young?
That's me.
Is there a problem?
Yo, man, that cookout
last night?
Yo, that shit was off
the fucking chain, man.
Seen that bitch with the fat ass
with the dookie shoot ass?
White pants?
Yeah, yo, that's the one I was
telling you about, nigger.
You put your dick up in
that ass too fucking fast
you gonna shoot
all over the place,
that's what I call
the dookie shoot.
Yo, did you see them
punk motherfuckers
over there trying to act
like they was tough?
We need to get them
motherfuckers, though, man,
I'm telling you. Stick 'em up,
lay 'em down. It's on.
Be easy, dawg.
What the fuck is these
motherfuckers doing?
Yo!
I should have known it was
your motherfucking ass.
What you got, some crack head
bitch up in there?
Some little whore? Your dick
gonna fall off, man.
You better calm down with them
nasty ass bitches,
that's what I'm gonna tell you.
Who the fuck you got
back here anyway, man?
I'm tired of this bullshit.
What's good?
How you doing?
How you doing, brother?
Yo, some real serious shit
we got to talk about
and it has to be handled with.
Talk about? It's a tight situation.
Help me out with this story.
Maybe we can end it together.
Those are blue bags right there.
Alright, so, check 'em out.
This shit is soap.
Those are beads, man.
I ain't gonna be
the only motherfucker
standing on the street
that gonna have to pay for this
bullshit that's going on.
No, this shit's a problem.
Hold on.
This is the mystery.
Who the fuck is selling
the clear bags?
That's Rex's shit.Motherfucker.
Where you find these at?
Same place.
Wow.
And when I find these behind the
motherfucking, uh,
art centre in the alley,
motherfucking crack head
Christine,
I see her, I'm like,
"Hey, girl, what's up?
"I ain't seen you." You know
what that bitch told me?
What did she say?
I ain't fucking with you
motherfuckers,
y'all are selling soup.Wow.
And I'm not
gonna be standing out there
by my motherfucking self
while y'all sit here and
collect the money.
I respect y'all gangster,
y'all game and everything,
but y'all gotta understand where
the fuck I'm coming from.
I think that's Rex's shit
right there, man.
Rex's name's all over that.
Yo, this shit is getting
out of hand, man.
- There's this dude, right?
- He says, "Honey,"
"I'm in that mood,
I wanna go down."
She say, "Honey, it's that
time of the month."
He like, "I don't care."
She said, "Well, if you don't
care, I don't care."
So, then he starts
6-9ing, right?
Like rabbits.
Doorbell rings.
Mailman. She said, "Honey,
go get the door."
He said, "Look at my mouth!"
She said, "Baby,
it ain't nothing."
"Just tell 'em I was
a jam sandwich."
So, he go to the door,
it's the mailman.
He said, "Look, sorry about
my mouth."
"I was eating a jam
sandwich." He said,
"Man, I ain't worried about the
jam sandwich on your mouth."
"I worry about the
peanut butter on your forehead."
You get it?
Peanut butter.
6-9?
Excuse me.
It's my idea that you
go back to work.
What do you think about it?
Hey, what's up? What we got
going on over here?
Car won't turn over.
He said he got it
fixed yesterday,
I don't know what happened.
Alright, well, why don't you
pop the hood
and let me take a look
up under here.
Glad to. I ain't doing
this no more.
Okay.
Alright, look, get in there
and turn it on now.
Okay.
It won't even start.
He said he got the car
fixed yesterday.
It won't start.
Okay, um, hold on.
It started!
Yeah, there we go.
It's the cable. Your cable
is rusted out.
Look, what I need you to do
right now
is go down to the garage
and tell them you need
a new connector
because the battery
is rusted out.
What's up?
Hey, what's your name?
What you got there?
It's mine.
Yeah, let me see that.
Come here.
Get off!
Get over here.
Get off me!
I ain't gonna take it,
I just wanna see what it is.
What's your name?
Lawrence.
Lawrence, let me see
what you got there.
If I gotta take it from you,
I'm not gonna give it back.
Come on, now.
What's this?
That's not mine.
Whose is it, then?
That's for Rex, I'm gonna
throw it over his fence.
Why you gonna do that?
'Cause he's gonna get me
a football.
Here, you take this.
Get the fuck out of
my fucking face!
You gonna get me what?
I want all my money now!
You need it? I don't know who
the fuck is gonna get it.
Shut the fuck up, bitch,
like I fucking told you
unless you got my fucking money.
Get the fuck up on out of here.
Get the fuck up on out of here
and get out of here now.
You have free samples today?
Not you, motherfucker.
See you back from
South Carolina, huh?
Got back Sunday.
What's it to you, bro?
You know you in
a school zone, right?
210 yards away, still ain't got
nothing to do with you.
What's all this information for?
I'm talking to you,
motherfucker.
What the fuck is the problem?
You gonna sit there and look
fucking stupid now?
Answer me, do something
or get the fuck off my
fucking corner.
I don't need none
of this shit here.
All I need is fucking
money and crack heads.
I don't need no fucking body
coming here chastising me.
Alright? So, see you
later, man.
Can't get with you
right now, brother.
Well, you see,
I figure like this.
Got these kids out here
pushing your shit,
these females strung out
on that shit,
man, you best take your shit
on back to South Carolina.
First of all, motherfucker,
ain't nobody making me
motherfucking go
no fucking where.
Do you understand what
I'm telling you?
I'm here to motherfucking stay,
I'm gonna get all the cheddar
that's out this motherfucker.
Do you understand?
That's how it is?
You gonna do what you do
and things just happen
the way they happen?
You wasting my
motherfucking time.
Get the fuck off my
motherfucking block, alright?
Before some shit start popping
off outside this motherfucker
and some shit you ain't gonna
be able to handle.
Come on, baby, let's get moving.
Lawrence, come on.
I'm gonna be late for work,
come on.
Lawrence.
Let's go.
Come on.
Have a good day.
I love you.
We were going to move to this
place and it was above a bar
and I didn't want Lawrence
to be around that.
And how much were they trying
to take you for that one?
1450. It's...
And it was a one bedroom,
so I mean...
I can't believe it.
It had a side room that could
have been used as a small office
or Lawrence's room, but...
That sucks if it's up on top of
something like that.
Oh, hold on.
How are you?
Good morning, guys.
How's everything?
It's alright.
Pleasure to see you.
How are you guys doing today?
Oh, okay.
My momma used to say,
"Fair to middling"
whatever that means.
Good, what are we gonna
have this morning?
What you got?
Menu hasn't changed.
What, you can't figure
it out, Sherlock?
Oh, there she goes again.
She's always busting my balls.
Man, all the time.
Every time we come here.
That's what they call me,
"Ball Busting Keisha."
You keep that up, I'm gonna
take you in the back room
and I'm gonna work you over
at the station.
Oh, what do you do,
do you tickle people?
You take out your little night
stick, is that what you do?
We bend... we bend people over.
Yeah, okay. Spank them.
Smack 'em on their ass
and pull all that long,
pretty hair you got.
That's what we do
in the back room.
I want to ask you a question.
You hear what happened
to your ex-boyfriend?
Derek?
No.
Got the shit kicked out of him.
Got beat fucking real bad, too.
Stomped out.
You filed a complaint
against him.
Oh, you think I did it?
Is it that time of the month?
Look, I don't know what
happened to Derek, okay?
How long have you been
through with him?
None of your business how long
I've been through with him.
Oh, it could be my business.
Hello? This is
Detective Boldt.
And we will talk at the station
if you don't make it my
business.
Yeah.
Okay, where?
Okay. We're on it.
Wow. We have a situation.
We gotta get the hell
out of here.
'Sup, fellas?
How you doing?
How's everything, alright?
How's everything, Carver?
So, you can see we got
a dead body,
so, doesn't look natural at all.
Basically, got a 911 call.
She's walking through the woods
in this direction right here
and she stumbled across
the body.
Looks like a homicide, you know,
just from plain sight.
I checked him...
No ID, no wallet.
And, um, no phone. Called the
ME, like, 10 minutes ago,
should be, like, 45 minutes.
They're backed up right now.
Ma'am, just get behind
the crime scene tape.
Where my strap at?
It's in the car, son.
Fool's gonna get the
homie filthy,
cut his neck open
from ear to ear.
We gotta take care of this ASAP.
Listen, killers, slow down.
Hold up, son, we need to
take care of this business.
Listen...
Yo, I went back with him
since eight years old.
Yo, put the strap away,
put the strap away.
What we gonna do about this?
Put the strap away.
'Cause we gotta do this shit
the right way, dawg.
God damn, man.
So, how we gonna handle this?
Yo, Rex got to die, man.
Straight jacket.
We can't fucking run out there
like wild cowboys.
This is fucking business, man.
We need a fall guy, man.
That's what we need.
Somebody that's gonna
do this shit
to keep our names out of it.
It's on you to decide
how we do this,
but my man, something
gotta be done.
I'm ready to get stoked,
you know what I'm saying?
I got the perfect motherfucker
for this one.
Are you Earl Coleman?
Yeah, I am.
What's up?
Well, do you know
the Columbia Apartments?
Rough away over there?
Yeah.
Well, some of us are on
hard times, you know.
Not me so much because
I'm retired.
But some are on assistance.
And I don't think what they're
doing to them is right.
They're getting greedier
and greedier
and they're taking advantage
and they're ruining it
for everybody.
It ain't right.
Okay, so what's been
going on over there?
You know Mylo and them?
I know Mylo. What's he
been up to?
How you doing?
What's up?
Yo, is Mylo here?
No, he's not.
You know where he's at?
No, I haven't seen him,
I don't know where he's at.
Hey, Earl.
Hey.
How you doing?
This your son?
This is my son.
Lawrence, say hi.Hi.
Hey, Lawrence, nice to
meet you again.
You two know each other?
Just around.
You get that football?
What football?
No.
Nothing.
So, what are you
doing around here?
I'm just waiting for someone.
Lawrence, go inside.
I wanted to thank you
for what you did.
You having any trouble?
No, but I heard what happened.
I thought you were just
going to talk to him.
Well, he didn't feel
like talking.
Sounds like Derek.
Can I ask you something?
Sure.
Can I take you out to dinner?
If you're busy, you know,
you don't want to,
you can't make it,
I mean, you know,
it's okay.
No, we could do that.
How about tomorrow night?
Okay.
Um, but, promise me
I can pay for it.
Here he comes now, man.
Hey, homie, what's up, man?
Yo, what up, what's up?
Chillin', baby.
Yo, you know my man Z, right?
Yeah, I know him.
What's up, what you
doing out there?
Man, yo, I just want to holler
at you, baby, for a minute.
At me? Yeah, you got a minute?
Relax, bro, relax.
Alright, go ahead, holler, then.
What?
Not here, do you think
we could go in the crib?
Just me and you.
Yo, Z, hang back.
I got you.
Yeah, alright.
Come on.
So, you still down at the
motherfucking garage and shit?
How they treating you
down there?
The garage is treating me good.
Look, man, I ain't trying to
knock your hustle and all that,
man gotta eat but, man...
11 bucks an hour? That just
ain't making it, dawg.
It's better than being up north
making 50 cents a day.
Dude, the boy just down there,
holding doors at the donut shop,
he made more than that.
Is that right?
Listen. You know
Skull, right?
Well, they found him, man.
Found him in the woods.
Cut the fuck up, dawg.
In that game, baby, that's
how it is.
Bump all that, man.
Real problem,
real reason I'm here...
Yo, this kid Rex from
around the way,
this dude is pushing
up on me, man.
I'm hearing shit about,
yo, he got a crew
that he trying to
bring through to the Valley.
Come on, man, this is
where we from
and you know I can't let it
go down like that.
When I make moves,
I'm gonna need a soldier
like you, man.
So, check this.
That's 10 stacks.
Don't mean shit to me, dawg.
You sending me 10 stacks
for what?
Means you got a fucking problem?
That's the problem right there.
It's your word, huh?
Yeah, that's my word, man.
That's my word. Come on, dawg.
You can't be liking this shit
right here, man.
Living in this small ass
apartment.
Look at this shit, B.
You know what?
I go to bed at night
knowing that what I'm doing,
I'm doing it for the cause
and not for the because.
Motherfucker, I'm not
asking you to do nothing
against your nature, dawg.
You used to be... you used to be
a O.G. in the hood, man.
Like, you was somebody
I looked up to.
You gotta be fucking
kidding me right now.
I try to get you back
in the game, get you right,
you know what I'm saying?
And this is how you act?
And one bid ain't enough?
You do one fucking bid, son.
One bid and you turn soft!
One bid is all it takes, man.
Wake up. You up in my house.
Fuck that, man. You in my house.
What's the problem, man?
Tell me what the problem is.
You just ain't man enough
to do a real job.
What's up?
No bueno, son.
He didn't go for it, huh?
Nah, man.
Wow.
So wat are we gonna do now?
Shit, the show don't stop.
Fuck him. We gotta do what
we gotta do.
So, you gonna call that girl?
Yeah, I think Ariel
need to get on this one.
I can't believe this faggot, yo.
Fuck it, man.
That's what it is.
Come on, man, let's
get out of here.
When we gonna do something
together? I need some guap.
We gotta take care of this
business with Ulysses first,
you know what I'm saying,
but we can get up.
Yeah, if he ever fucking
call us and shit.
Man, it's hotter
than the bitch...
Where you get this
old ass shit from, anyway?
Yo, this shit is crazy, man.
Tell me you had this shit
before you went in.
Mmm. Yeah, man, I still be on
my grind, man.
Shit has changed over the years,
man, you know what I'm saying?
Nigger gotta be careful,
you know what I'm saying?
I ain't trying to
go back to jail.
You break my nigger off with
60/40 and that's it!
My nigger just came home.
He's supposed to get
bread off Fred.
Yeah, I'll be on the block,
don't worry about that.
I'll be out there.
You just make sure my man
got his bread, that's all.
Bye, Rex.
I guess I holler at you later.
Alright? Later.
How do you know
that guy out there
that was giving out
them tennis balls?
Cubby told me about him.
Who's Cubby?
He's my friend at school.
He ain't your friend.
You know what a friend is?
Yeah.
No, you think you know
what a friend is, right?
We gonna do this, this is for
all the marbles now!
Ready? Ready?
Here we go.
Hut, hike!
Come on, here we go.
Get it! Get the ball,
get it!
Come on! You gotta
be tough!
Slam right, on three.
They're coming in!
There you go... touchdown!
Ha! Come on.
You see those woods over there?
Yeah.
You know what be in them woods?
Birds.
You know what be
eating them birds?
Cats.
And you know what be
eating them cats?
Dogs.
Let me tell you something.
One day, there was these birds
up in there flying around.
Right?
And they see the cats
and they can see the dogs
coming over the hill.
And they know that the cats
are afraid of the dogs.
So, the bird go down there,
he fly down there to
the boss cat,
and he say to the boss cat,
he goes,
"Listen. I want to make
a deal with you.
"We can see them dogs
coming over that hill.
"So, how about this?"
"We'll warn you, but there's
only one condition to this."
And the cat asked,
"What's that?"
He said, "That you can't eat us."
"You gotta leave us be."
You hear me?
Yeah.
So, the cat thought about this
for a second and said,
"Okay, it's a deal."
So, now the birds and the cats,
they getting along
just fine, right?
Why? Because they ain't got to
worry about the dogs no more.
So, the birds are flying around,
they're watching the cats
who were eating the mouse,
getting all fat and everything.
Laying all about without
a care in the world.
And one day,
the bird come down there,
he fly down on one of
them low branches
and the cat jump up
and bite him on the neck.
So, the bird look up
at the cat, he said,
"Now that you bit me,
"you gotta worry about the dogs
coming over the hill now."
"Why did you do that?"
So, the cat is just
sitting there looking
with this stupid look
on his face.
He said, "It's my nature."
"I'm a cat."
You hear me?
Yeah.
Nursing?
I get my degree in the fall.
The fall? That's good.
I'll be working a whole lot
less hours,
making double what I make now.
You know, sometimes the nurses
are more smarter than the
doctors.
Doctors always be messing up.
I mean, my aunt is
an R.N.
You don't even want to
know the stories.
Right, right.
You really could have
gotten hurt with Derek.
He's got friends.
You know,
if I get hurt,
you can be my nurse.
Right.
I'm serious.
Maybe I'll get hurt on purpose.
Maybe you should wait until
I get my degree.
Well, if you ever need
someone to practice on...
You know what?
That champagne don't pop.
Can you imagine?
Anyway, so my boss, Frank,
is always, like...
"You know what? I really need
you to clean the menus."
But, I mean, at the same time,
if there's nothing
that's on the menus,
then I'm not going to
clean them, you know?
So, he looks at me and he says,
"Have you cleaned off
all the menus?"
And I say, "Of course I've
cleaned off all the menus."
So, he goes over to
my section, right?
Picks up the menus that are
supposed to be in my section,
gets the menus out... I'll be back.
Yo, what's your problem?
What's my problem?
You like throwing shit
at people? Huh?
Pick that shit up, man.
Why don't you fucking
pick it up, man?
Yo, back the fuck up.
Back the fuck up.
Pick the can up, man.
You ain't got no fucking
respect for yourself.
Pick that motherfucking can up.
Relax, man!
Back the fuck up. What?
This motherfucking
thing over here...
Fuck. What?
What? What?
Back the fuck up.
What?
What? What the fuck you
motherfuckers doing, man?
You'd better go sit the fuck
down somewhere.
Alright.
What the... what the
fuck are you doing?
Fucking Hot Wheels.
What the fuck is
that car doing...
Look, I'm sorry about tonight.
That's okay.
Tell Lawrence I said hi.
Vitamin D is from the sun,
so, I mean, that's...
Oh, shit.
You think I'd let you go?
Look, I just want to talk.
I ain't come here for no drama.
Put that... you know,
put it to rest, you know?
So, come on, let's
sit down and talk.
I'm not sitting down
with you, Derek.
So, you don't want to
know what happened?
You ain't even gonna
ask what happened?
You ain't got nothing
to do with that?
What happened, Derek?
Oh, you don't know? No, I don't know.
Well, I seen the cat
that you been running with.
You think I don't know?
I know everything you're doing.
I'm gonna call
the police, Derek.
Oh, you want to call the police?
Alright, come on, now.
Let's talk about C.P.S.
I know all about this cat.
C.P.S. know that he's
around Lawrence,
C.P.S. know that,
hmm?
He's on parole, you tell
his parole officer?
You got a kid?
You think this guy
can keep you safe?
That's what you think?
You think this... you think
this bum motherfucker
gonna do what I do?
This is my job, this is how I...
I don't care about your job.
I don't give a damn
about this job. Please stop.
I don't even want
you working. Please stop.
You don't represent me right.
I don't want you working.
My girls don't work!
Please...
Come on, baby, I don't
mean to make you cry.
Come on, now.
Come on. Let's give it
another chance, right?
Please. Let's work it out,
come on.
Please stop!
Come on, I don't
mean that, come on.
Just one more time!
It's my job.
Please stop!
Alright.
It really mean that much to you.
You fucking that cat?
That's none...
That's none of your
business, Derek.
Oh, it's my business.
I need you to go.
Alright, I'm gonna go.
I love you.
I want to work it out.
Come on, give me
another chance, alright?
Please? Just one more time.
Please, Derek, please go.
Why don't you tell that cat
it ain't over.
How you doing today, B.?
What's up?
Ah, we'd just like to
have a word with you,
talk with you for a few minutes.
How you doing today?
Mind if I call you "Earl"?
Let me ask you about somebody.
You know a guy
named Derek Young?
Yeah, I know a Derek Young.
You know him, right?
How well do you know him?
Not at all.
I don't know.
I got somebody said
you guys were having rough sex
in the back of Beamer's
on Thursday night.
I was asleep, man.
You go to bed early, huh?
Sleeping by yourself?
Watching Debbie Does Dallas?
You ever hear of a kid
named Donald Weams?
He's dead.
Wasn't he the guy that was
dealing to your sister
when you were in prison?
Like his sister?
Don't remember, huh?
- Don't remember him at all?
- Never heard about this?
You didn't hear that she got a
hotshot from old Donald?
That would piss me off.
Piss you off?
You know what? Let me
tell y'all something.
I feel sorry for y'all.
Is that right?
Yeah. 'Cause y'all are off.
Y'all are way off.
Alright, listen, listen.
Earl.
What I need you to do
from now on,
don't do police work,
don't do what you're doing.
Leave it to us. Okay?
You got a problem,
anything going on,
I know you want to
protect the neighbourhood
and all that stuff,
it's all good.
But you pick up the phone,
you call us, you understand?
You know already the rules
of this game, man.
You been up north
for how many years?
You know if you got
any kind of issue
you know it's gonna be
called to us,
let us do what we
supposed to do, man.
How much they gonna charge me
to do that?
Hold up, hold up, now you're
acting like an asshole.
What the fuck you talking
about, man?
That's how it is, man.
What you talking about...
What ways, what ways, what is?
Put that fucking thought across
that we're doing
something wrong.
I will drag your fucking ass
down to the station
in two fucking seconds!
I could take you down
right fucking now
and put you in the back
of that fucking car
no fucking problem, man,
you understand me?
You understand me?
You're lucky you're walking
away from this right now,
so shut the fuck up!
You look I'm calming
this motherfucker down right now
because you know... you know you
definitely don't want to
get locked the fuck back up,
man. You know it.
Three strikes, Earl?
Tough guy.
Aw, man.
Mylo?
What up, Earl?
What are you doing
out here, man?
What do you mean what
am I doing out here?
What are you doing out here?
My girl lives here.
I hear you swiping
benefit cards.
You see there's 20
families out here, man.
You getting $100 a pop.
That's $2000 a month.
$2000 a month is peanuts, man.
I'm out of here.
It ain't right, man.
What the fuck you mean
it ain't right?
You better back up, man.
This shit is bigger than you.
The game is over,
you're out of here.
I said get out of here, man.
Yo, Earl, man!
Come on, man!
You're getting
out of here. Let my arm go!
You're getting out of here.
Yo, this ain't even me, man.
It's Wescott's shit, man!
Wescott?
Yeah, man!
Let me go!
Ah. Fuck.
Let me tell you something, man.
Get off!
Get the fuck up
out of here, man.
You gonna get your shit...
Get the fuck out of here!
You hear me?
It's over.
I'm getting tired.
Word?
Word, man.
Yo, where's Wescott at?
Earl, man, don't bring that
bullshit up in here, man.
Shit, man!
Yo, where the fuck is Wescott?
What the fuck is popping?
Don't come down Columbia no more
with that bullshit.
This stuff's not in
your fucking...
You finished.
You? Fuck you.
Shut the fuck up!
Your boy coming down there
at Columbia Apartment
swiping benefit cards, alright?
That shit is over.
You don't run shit around here!
I'm telling you... You know...
Stop it, motherfucker.
What the fuck you gonna do?
What? What?
Fuck! What? Bring it.
Don't disrespect me.
Go ahead.
I don't want to see that
no more!
You'd better fucking
control your boys!
Fuck you, man! I'd better not
see you around there again.
Control your fucking boys.
It's over!
They ain't making a
motherfucking thing
no more.
It's over.
Fucking nobody.
I see you down there again,
you going to hell.
You know a kid
named Donald Weams?
The kid that got killed?
Yeah, that's right.
Nah, um, what are you
asking me for?
Donald had, uh, some kids
who were selling crack for him
down at the high school.
Well, that wasn't Lawrence.
Would you mind if he
took a drug test?
Yes, I do mind.
You know kids 9, 10 years old
getting high, smoking, doing all
kinds of nonsense out here?
Well, Lawrence isn't into that.
It's only a drug test.
Hey, there he is.
How are you, buddy?
How you doing?
Come on over.
You mind if I talk to him
for a sec?
Good looking kid.
Looks like his mom.
Come here, buddy. I gotta ask
you a couple questions, okay?
You know a guy named
Earl Coleman, Lawrence?
Lawrence, go back to your room.
Lawrence, come here, it's okay.
It's okay, I'm not
going to bite you.
Come here.
Big guy, right?
You ever throw a football
around with him?
I thought this was about
the kid in the woods.
It is.
Hey.
Sorry for coming over so late.
That's no problem.
Can I get you something?
Did you kill that guy?
The one they found in the park?
I didn't kill nobody.
Who said that?
These two detectives,
they came by my house.
They're just looking for
somebody to pin this on.
I just got out of jail,
so they're
looking for a scapegoat
and I'm an easy target.
I just wanted you to be careful.
Look, I'm sorry about
the other night.
Yeah?
Earl, listen.
I can't be with a guy like you.
Why is that?
You could go to jail.
Do you ever think about that?
That ain't happening,
I ain't going to jail.
Oh, you're not going to jail?
Let me tell you something.
The people that I see,
the people that I come across,
they ain't going to go back
and tell anybody anything.
Nobody cares.
I gotta be going.
Lawrence is waiting for me.
She probably all
busted out, man.
What?
Man, once a chick
has a kid, man,
it changes up the whole story.
It's like there's some weird
obsession with the kid, man.
It's like that's
all she cares about.
Lawrence is a good kid.
Man, fuck Lawrence!
What are you talking about,
Lawrence is a good kid, man?
Lawrence don't know shit!
I've dated bitches
that have kids, man.
It ain't nothing but
turmoil and trouble, man.
But you know what?
You my boy.
I'm gonna help you out, man,
I'm gonna help you out.
And how's that?
What the fuck's
her name, Keisha?
I'm gonna take Keisha out,
that's what I'm gonna
do for you.
You know what I mean? Just to
warm her up a little bit.
See what she's about.
Take her on a date,
give her roses.
'Cause women love roses.
See, Keisha is like my mother
when I was a kid.
If you gave her some roses,
she gonna suck your dick.
I used to go to
sleep to that, man.
But that's besides the point.
So, I'd get these... I'd get
Keisha these roses.
She gonna suck my dick.
For you, though.
Fellatio.
Shit.
This is for you, man.
This is for you, calm down.
See if she's up to speed,
'cause you don't want
to be dating no bitch
that's not up to speed, man.
She gonna suck my dick
for that fellatio
and we be all good.
Man, if you don't get
the hell out of here...
I'm just saying, brother, like,
you don't think it's a good...
What's up, man?
I don't know, man.
She might be broke down
or something, man.
I don't know.
A couple wires loose,
lights went out. Yeah?
Problem might be back here.
Back where?
Back over this way.
What?
Get this motherfucker.
Derek! Derek!
Bring that bitch out!
Bring his ass out!
Bring him out now!
I want you!
Come on, now!
Bring that bitch out now!
You think...
What you thinking, man?
You think I wouldn't be back?
That's what you thought?
That's what you thought,
I wouldn't be back?
You think you can fuck
with my girl?
Fuck no!
Hell no!
Who the fuck do you
think you are?
You want to make
fucking sheriff?
That's what you think?
You think...
You! A fucking broke-ass
motherfucker like you!
You ain't in my league!
I'll fucking kill you!
Get him!
Never, never!
She's mine! She's mine!
God dammit, she's mine!
Open his mouth!
Open your mouth, bitch.
Hey.
How you doing?
Can I talk to you for a minute?
Sure.
What you said to me
made a lot of sense.
But how am I supposed to
believe you?
Because I'm asking you
to give me another chance.
You can't do this for me.
You have to want to change.
You can't do this for me
regardless of what I do.
Okay.
Okay what?
I mean, me doing what I do,
it's causing nobody
harm and problems but myself.
And...
I can't just think I can...
change the world like that.
Well...
I gotta stop
letting things get to me.
You're right.
You can't keep letting these
things get you down and bothered
and messing with your life
that you're trying to create.
So how are we doing?
Earl.
Paycheque.
And I gave you a raise.
What's this for?
Oh, because you're a bad worker
with a shitty attitude
and I feel sorry for you.
Okay.
So this is your sister's place?
Yeah.
She died four months
before I got out.
And they let you
take over the lease?
- I know the landlord.
- I used to live here.
Hm. Do they have
any two-bedrooms?
Yeah, they have
some two-bedrooms
but they're going
for like, around 1100.
Oh, really?
That would be nice.
Yeah.
Hey, I can ask Mike about it
and, um, I'll let you know
something tomorrow.
You know it's not
your fault, right?
I know.
But if I wasn't in jail,
this would have never happened.
You're just feeling guilty.
Feeling guilty
makes you a better person.
Makes you realize.
You just made it worse!
Excuse me?
What you did.
Now they upped the payment
to 150 a month.
Hundred and fifty?
Hundred and fifty to who?
To Mylo and them!
We complained and now
they upped the payment.
I don't know what we gonna do.
I'm sorry about that.
Ain't nothing you can do?
Maybe it's best
I just stayed out of it.
You mean to tell me you
not gonna talk to them again?
Look, why don't you
call the police, you know?
Maybe they can help.
What's wrong with y'all, man?
Why you niggers frowning?
Well, you know you left
a nice little surprise
for us this morning, man.
Real, real nice leaving
that body out there like that.
Yo, last time I checked,
it was you motherfuckers' job
to take care of Rex.
You niggers must need
a new profession or something.
Now, we in the right profession.
See, we clean up
your fucking mess, man,
you know what I'm saying? And
when you do shit like this,
you got to
come to us first, man.
What the fuck
am I supposed to do?
I'm supposed to stand around
while this motherfucker Rex
is pumping beats on my strip?
Nigger's bodying my soldiers?
Rex been nipping
at my heels for months.
And what y'all do?
What about that girl that was
gonna turn State's evidence?
We gave you that girl.
Motherfucker,
that's why you get paid.
Hold up, man.
You gonna act like straight
like a fucking asshole, man.
You ain't talking to
any motherfucker about it.
You ain't just rate
regular corner niggers.
Ain't nobody soft
over here, man.
Not my corner nigger, right?
Well, who the fuck
got you eating lavish?
Answer that shit.
All right, all right, enough.
All right.
Bottom line here is,
you're not gonna start a war
in our district.
You're not dumping bodies
in our district, okay, Ulysses?
You got that?
I got a business to run and
I'm gonna do whatever the fuck
I gotta do to make sure
my shit runs right.
Now you listen to me.
You start acting like
some fucking crackhead,
we got a problem,
you understand me?
And that's what
you've been doing.
We gave you
too many passes, Ulysses.
What the fuck are you
talking about?
This thing's gonna collapse
if you fuck around!
You start doing whatever
you fucking want to do,
it's gonna collapse.
So you got a game plan, huh?
Yeah!
This is my point.
As far as your fucking game
plan, the game plan is,
is if y'all motherfuckers
are gonna take my money,
shut the fuck up
and earn your keep.
- Hey, buddy!
- What's going on, buddy?
How you doing today?
Good to see you.
Everything all right?
Are we still like that?
Listen, man.
What you want?
We need to talk. For what?
We gotta talk about this.
Glad to see you
cleaned up for us.
You have any weapons
around this motherfucker, boy?
You hear about Rex Raynor?
Everybody did.
Mm-hm. I told you,
you're go start doing
that vigilante shit,
it's gonna come back
at you, bro.
I ain't into that anymore.
Mm?
That's your job.
What are you saying, you done?
Done just like that.
Is that what you're saying?
I got other things
going on, man.
Like?
I work for a living.
What you need to be looking at
is Mylo Shrugs over there
in the Columbia Apartments.
Gotcha, gotcha, gotcha.
We'll look into that.
Got the people
down there terrified.
All right. Got it.
My friend, take a look at this.
You know what that's from?
That's from Derek Young.
He came by the station this
morning, said you assaulted him
last week in the parking lot
in Beamers.
And then he said
he was gonna let it go
and then you came by
and decided to do it again.
He's lying.
That's a first-degree assault.
That's a third strike for you.
He's got a witness
and the witness said
you went after him, too.
Who's that?
Same guy you jumped.
You tell me who's that.
Mm-hm. Read the piece of paper.
You know what happens to
three-time losers, baby.
Well, you know,
we've left Ulysses man
for quite some time
right now, you know.
Let me just say something
about your sister
real quick here, man, 'cause
this correlates with Ulysses.
She's on her way
to becoming a CI, man.
She's trying to come
work with us to help you.
What are you talking about, man?
We're saying we don't blame you
for what's starting to
happen to Ulysses' guys.
I mean, your sister
was a hell of a woman.
And what happened to my sister
happened to your sister.
I could see why you'd be
doing what you're doing.
My sister ain't no snitch, man.
She ain't telling on nobody.
Who put you away?
Tell me that she wouldn't
want to take him down for that.
She did.
She wanted to get you paroled.
Wanted you home, man.
And then all of a sudden
she comes to us
talking about getting you parole
and guess what happens?
She gets a hotshot.
You think Skull was the only one
behind that shit?
Tell you what, man.
Tomorrow morning, man,
you need to be at the precinct
around nine o'clock.
AM, not nine o'clock PM.
9 AM.
You tend to dance to your own
motherfuckering scheduled tunes.
9 AM.
Listen, my friend.
I want to talk to you
about something.
He brought your sister to me
when all this stuff
was going down.
She's a good girl.
She got herself clean, man.
She did a 180.
Do you have any idea what
Ulysses and those guys
did to her when she was using?
Forget it. And the shit she had
to do to get drugs, man?
My sister?
I can't even tell you
how I feel about it.
Man-to-man,
you go seeking some sort of
retribution this time...
it's okay with me.
You got my blessings, bro.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Hey, Scott.
Hey, how you doing?
All right. Yo, listen.
Um, you still got that apartment
available over there
in building five?
I think it is available
but I think it's 1150.
I'll check for you.
I got someone who's interested.
Is it all right
if I bring them by?
Yeah, definitely.
But try to make it in the next
hour, all right, if you can?
All right. All right. Thanks.
Hey, Keisha, what's up?
Hey.
Yeah, listen.
I spoke to him.
He says he's gonna be
in his office for another hour.
What guy? EARL:
The superintendent.
I told him you was interested
in an apartment so, you know,
he says he's gonna wait there
and we get over there
and see him
and we speak about this.
Hold on one minute.
Hey, Tammy, can I get the car?
I thought you was gonna
meet him tonight.
I was but he just called
right now.
I really can't do it.
I work.
Hey, can you come pick me up?
Yeah, I can come pick you up.
That's no problem.
I'll see you in a bit. All right, bye.
Is it the blue?
Is it the gold
and the pink dress and the...
I think the blue
is a little much.
The blue is too much? Too much.
- Say, what's up with that plan?
- What's your plan?
Get your cup, man.
Is going on?
You know how I do.
This shit is gonna be
your irons, man.
- Whoa, man.
- You need to get your weight up.
What you need to be doing
with your...
Yo, son, we gonna get another
game going on or what, son?
Yeah. You got
your partner, right?
Get some more sticks out here.
That's all ya'll are doing.
Easy doing 35s, try picking up
them 50s there.
What the fuck?
What the fuck is he doing here?
Who is that?
- Fucking Earl, man.
- This fucking clown.
Can't tell by his dumb-ass walk?
What's up?
Wha...
Yo, fuck him up!
Come on, fuck him up!
Oh, shit!
Hey, come on, man!
Ugh, shit!
Come on, man! Get him!
Get him!
Oh!
Come on, man!
Fuck. Get up, man.
What's fucking wrong with you?
Let's go, baby.
Bring his ass down!
Get him!
Don't let him get back up.
What? Come on, boy.
Ugh!
Get up, U!
Unhh!