-Music-
Everything he came with is in
here.
John, come say goodbye to Cory.
-Music-
Amtrak silver here. For your
safety, please remain inside the
yellow line
and wait for the train to come
to a complete stop.
Passenger service continues now
Norwood and Sycamore.
You must be Cory.
I'm Miss Hanks your case worker.
And these are your new foster
parents Mr. and Miss Kepperman.
Hi Cory. I'm Michelle.
I'm Dan. Let me get that for
you.
Well uh, this just says that you
received the child and
everything is in order.
If you would just sign here
please.
So Cory I will be seeing you on
Saturday.
We have a group called Foster
Friends,
and we do all kinds of exciting
things.
We sing at hospitals and nursing
homes.
We go roller skating. Now
doesn■t that sound like fun?
It'd be fun to see you fall and
watch you try to get up.
Tudaloo everybody.
Well um, the cars over this way.
So...
Got a surprise for you.
These are for you.
Thanks. I'll save the bag for
the next kid.
That will teach you to defy me!
Why can't I destroy you?
I am a Titan! I am invincible!
Your weapons can not harm me.
Nothing can hurt me!
Cory, for the seventh time this
month your teacher called.
She's concerned about your
grades.
Cory!
I know it's only been 4 weeks,
but I thought maybe we could
spend some time on your math
today.
But its Saturday!
Perfect day to get in some
batting practice.
Honey its kind of rainy.
It will stop.
How bout we play some and work
some
when Miss Hanks brings you back.
I don't wanna go with Miss Hanks
and her fractured friends.
Foster Friends Cory.
Do I have to?
[car horn] Yes you do, there she
is.
Oh Michelles so nice, why don't
you wave to her.
Well your very lucky to be with
the Keppermans.
Why at their age and no children
of their own,
they might just be thinking of
adoption!
WOO! Wouldn't that be
wonderful?!
That■s it right up the stairs.
Cmon, cmon.
Ok now hold on. Now don't be
nervous, and smile.
And don't you ruin it.
Go on in now everyone knows were
coming, and the patients are
very excited.
Welcome Miss Hanks, welcome
children.
Edgewaters, these are the foster
children
who will be entertaining us
today.
Thank you Miss Cybil.
The children have two songs
they'd like to sing for you
today.
The first number is that
inspiring piece from the civil
war era,
"The battle hymn of the
republic".
"Mine eyes have seen the glory
of the coming of the lord,
He is trampling out the vintage
where the grapes of wrath are
stored,
He hath loosed his fateful
lightning of his terrible swift
sword,
His truth is marching on.
Glory! Glory! Hallelujah!
Glory! Glory! Hallelujah.
His truth is marching on!
[canon explodes]
■ Music ■
Yes!
Woo!
■ Music ■
You better stand up straight and
sing, and I mean it.
Wasn't that lovely Blaine?
Elcie?
We have some refreshments.
Perhaps the children would like
to serve them.
Oh, I■m sure they would.
I■m sure they wouldn't
[snoring]
[sigh]
I saw you turn down her oxygen!
You have now turned all of us
into zombies.
Carlotta, now behave. Have
something to drink
I do not want any of that!
It tastes like dishwater, ugh!
Now you call that entertainment?
In our show we had children
younger than you,
Juggling on the high wire.
Do not quit your day job first
of May.
Oh, Cybil who do you have for us
in act 2?
Dr. Kevorkian?
If you cant fit in peacefully,
you'll have to leave.
What? And miss the moldy
macaroons and the Macarena
lesson?
Oh how could I possibly live
without that?
I watched you. You did not sing.
So?
But I understand.
I do not like to sing in this
place either
oh, ohhhh.
Were off!
Make sure she has her
medication.
Oh, be gone before someone drops
a house on you!
[car horn]
Hey Cory
[phone rings]
Oh, Ill get it.
What'd I tell you, is this
baseball weather or what.
Oh hey.
Why do you always wear that
raggedy old hat?
Well sit down,
This isn't just any old hat
Cory.
This is an official New York
Yankees baseball hat.
My dad got this for me at Yankee
Stadium a long time ago.
Yankee Stadium, the house that
Ruth built.
One of the greatest dynasties in
sports history.
Well, whats a dynasty?
A dynasty is when you have a
really great team that just
keeps winning,
and they pass it on year after
year
some teams can keep it up for a
couple or three years,
but the Yankees did it for 30
years in a row
started out with Babe Ruth, the
Bambino. the Sultan of Swat
then it went on to Lou Gherig,
the iron horse
and then, the greatest all
around baseball player of all
time.
The Yankee clipper, Joe
Dimmagio.
Could do everything Cory.
He could hit for power, hit for
average, run, field, throw.
My dad said that he saw him play
once
Danny, its for you.
Be right back.
How was your singing debut?
Sucked eggs.
Did you make any new friends?
Nope, all geeks and zombies
I picked up some flashcards,
I thought we could work on math
facts together.
Why don't you just poison me?
Its more humane.
Could be fun?
Us foster kids may be a little
dumb,
but we know whats a good time
and whats not
I understand Cory.
No you don't.
Yes, I do.
There■s something that people
don't know about me...
One of the supervisors called in
sick and I gotta go to work.
No!
I■m sorry I tried. They're
heartless.
Maybe we can do this next
Saturday huh?
Doesn■t matter
Cory i'm really sorry.
Its ok.
■ Music ■
Hello? Anybody home?
Cool.
Hey you boy!
What is that you have?
A turtle.
Bring it here! Come! I will not
bite!
You are the boy who came not to
sing this morning.
Yea.
What does it do?
Nothing but hide?
So? Hes invincible.
He does not seem like much of a
pet
I had an elephant.
One step and you would be flat
like a pizza.
An elephant, sure lady.
No, no, no it did not belong to
me.
It belonged to the circus but I
was there when she was born
and I got to name her.
Yea I called her Annabelle.
I joined the circus when I was
16.
Started out selling cotton
candy.
Then I became the magician's
assistant
and later I was madame sargosa,
fortune teller.
Sees all, knows all.
And after that the circus
changed.
What is your name young man?
Don't you know? Some fortune
teller!
I know you have a smart mouth,
but not much else is smart!
Tell me your name
Cory Wainwright.
So, what's my fortune?
Well, there may be things in
your future you do not want to
know.
Look Cory Wainwright, your
turtle is running away.
It wants to be free it does not
want to be your pet.
Everything wants to be free.
You, me, even that old turtle.
Well did you let your elephant
go?
Carlotta?
Is that your name, carlotta?
Yes.
Whats your last name?
Just carlotta.
Why carlotta dear, what on earth
you are going to catch your
death.
Weren't you one of Mrs hanks
children?
Yea.
What is that thing?
Its a turtle.
Well get it out of here it can
carry all kinds of diseases.
You oughtta go on home now. This
is a quiet place.
A place for the elderly.
Go on now.
Ill show you something tomorrow.
Did you know that the sea turtle
can swim 20mph
and a smooth soft-shell turtle
can out run a man on solid
ground.
Wow!
See what a library card and a
little digging turns up.
Yea but he doesn't look like he
can out run anything.
Well he's a box turtle. He's
built for comfort not speed I
guess.
So what does he eat?
Um, just about anything it says.
They especially like fruits
I learned the hard way that they
like vegetables.
One used to sneak into my garden
and take a bite out of.
My best vegetable before it was
perfect and ripe.
Dan wanted to get rid of it but
I thought it was cute.
But not as cute as you
I got to find a place where I
can keep him.
Here, this might work for
tonight.
There you go.
Yea this will be a good home,
for...
What are you gonna call him?
Well um, how about Mr. T?
Lets see if Mr. T. likes this.
Here it goes again.
There you go, open up.
Huh?
How come he wont eat?
I don't know.
Do you think he's lonely?
Maybe he is.
Well tomorrow ill go find him a
Mrs T.
What if he is a Mrs t?
What page is that on?
Hey guys, whats for supper?
Oh turtle soup huh mmm
[baseball chatter]
Strike 2!
Your the new foster kid in ms.
Fukes class aren't you?
Yea
I hear your going to flunk.
Strike 3! He's dead meat, he's
toast, stick a fork in him, he's
done!
Rained out huh?
Worse, struck out.
Mind if I sit down?
Sure
I want you to know that hitting
a baseball is a very difficult
thing to do.
What do you know about baseball?
A little
I had a couple brothers that
were pretty good.
Baseball has always been very
important to my family.
Yea well I don't have a family.
I■m just a foster kid.
There was this ball player.
A big lefty outfielder
I saw him a couple of times.
He grew up in a home for boys,
And he struck out a few times
himself
1,330 times.
How'd he stay on the team?
In between, he hit 714 home
runs.
Who was he?
Ever hear of Babe Ruth?
Sure who hasn't?
Lots of people consider him the
greatest ball player that ever
lived.
My new foster dad says its some
other old dude, was the greatest
Joe D something.
Your foster dad sounds like a
very smart fellow.
Whats your name?
Cory.
Whats yours?
My name is Joe. nice to meet you
Cory.
Listen to the people that care
about you, even the old dudes.
And when you go to swing, keep
your head in.
Always watch that ball try to
make contact with the bat.
Now you'll never see that
happen,
But that■s the idea. With
confidence.
And shoulder to shoulder. Don't
forget that.
Shoulder to shoulder.
Show me how you would swing.
That■s the idea, but keep your
head right on that ball.
That should do the trick.
Yea way to go Cory!
Ehh lucky shot lucky shot.
Luck had nothing to do with
that.
Ah, we'll see buddy.
Ok here■s the deal, you hit this
one, I do dishes for a week.
Shoulder to shoulder.
Hit it downtown Cory!
Safe! Safe!
Tackle baseball he's out!
Is this the circus you were in?
Yes, this was the great circus
in the age of great circus'
And here is my dear friend
Dingy.
Dingy, Dingy the clown.
Is that your elephant?
Yes, this is Annabelle. here she
was just two months old.
Is that your right there?
Yes.
And who's that?
Peter John
Peter John sent me this from
Burma.
Did you marry him?
No.
Now tell me about you
well I live in a foster home
right down the street
oh, are they good parents?
They are my fourth set. Michelle
and Dan
I need you to pull a job for me.
Here, here.
Three cups of un-hulled sesame
seeds and.
Pistachios, if you can find
them.
And I have to get into the
kitchen at night, and that can
be tricky.
I could get caught.
[gasp]
You don't want to know what they
do to prisoners here.
What are you making a bomb?
No, halva.
Halva?
Halva is Turkish candy. Its what
angels eat in heaven.
Makes you wise. ill give you
some.
So is that where your from?
Turkey?
I come from many places.
Carlotta your not out here
giving your money away are you?
No, no
I saw you hand money to him.
I wasn't aware you were keeping
money in your room dear.
Young man its not right to take
advantage of the elderly,
So just give me the money she
gave you.
Its his money
I don't know what your talking
about its my money.
Do you want me to call miss
Hanks and put you into a home
for children who steal things?
Young man you better come back!
Go to your room
-music-
[knock knock]
psst, psst
I got it, I got it.
So you did not forget.
Carlotta, what are you doing?
I just wanted some fresh air.
Oh you got plenty of air, just
lay down and go to sleep huh
psst, psst.
So was that?
The night nurse. she pretends to
check on us while she steals our
desserts.
Here.
Now you meet me tomorrow at 4,
over by the woods,
And I will reward you with
halva.
Tomorrow at 4.
Its been 2 hours. if you see him
will you let me know?
Ok. Never mind he just walked in
the door. Thank you.
Where have you been?
The store on the corner was
closed so...
No no! I told you to come
straight back its been 2 hours.
Don't worry about me ok.
We were worried.
Dan's sister and her two girls
were here.
We waited dinner as long as we
could.
Well, you should have gone ahead
and eaten without me
I wanted to have dinner
together, you know?
Like, like a family.
And now Dans gone out looking
for you.
Is he here?
He just got here
Cory what are we supposed to do?
You don't listen in school, you
don't do your homework and now
you don't come home on time?
Well how was I supposed to know
you'd be stupid enough not to go
ahead and eat without me?
Go to your room.
No supper tonight, no television
tomorrow.
Go on!
Go now!
This is my favorite hideaway.
This is great.
Did miss Sybil see you go into
the woods?
She's busy showing some poor
souls children around.
Oh everything in life circles in
life and comes back at you
I think you mean, what goes
around comes around.
Children become the parents, and
lock the parents in their rooms.
What can miss Sybil do to you
for coming out here?
One man calls too frequently for
the bedpan,
and now they give him an extra
sleeping pill
I only pretend to take their
pills
I spit them out later.
How did you get stuck in this
place?
Weak heart they said
well, what about your family?
I have no family
well
ill be your family.
And I will be yours.
Hey!
Come here you stud muffin.
I hate it when you do that.
I■ve been waiting for you to get
home.
Wheres Cory?
He's out.
Ok lets go.
Not that silly
I wanted to show you something.
What?
This.
Whats that?
Don't you know?
Yea, sure this is the perfect
shade of blue for the kitchen.
come on lets go.
Try the babies room.
The what?
Were pregnant. if it turns blue
were pregnant.
Oh my god your blue and I'm
pregnant
I mean.
Really?
We did it! We did it!
I■m sorry, I■m sorry, I■m sorry,
I■m sorry! You got to sit down
ok!
There■s really... there■s a
baby.
Can I listen?
You cant hear anything yet!
I have a doctors appointment on
Thursday if you want to go.
Hell yes!
Shhh. don't swear in front of
the baby.
Hey Cory! How you doing?
Hey Cory.
Whats up?
Hey well um I got my test back
85 that■s great, way to go!
Let me see that.
I sure wish I got marks like
this when I was in school.
Let me put this up on the
refrigerator huh.
Uh, Cory listen, um.
Why don't you go upstairs and
check on Mr. T I don't think he
had enough water in his cage.
That■s a good idea.
Yea, can you do that?
Ok.
Hello, Mr. T.
I■m so excited about the baby I
didn■t even think about how Cory
is going to take this.
Oh this is really going to throw
him.
How should we tell him?
Well I've seen it happen.
People will adopt a kid, wife
gets pregnant, they have a baby
of their own
and they say what heck we'll
send him back to the agency.
Ok, lets make it official before
we tell him.
Ill call miss hanks in the
morning.
I am invincible.
Your weapons can not touch me.
Nothing can hurt me.
They can not hurt me.
They wont get rid of you
Michelle thinks your cute
[knock knock]
Carlotta are you awake?
Carlotta?
Cory.
I■m running away. I just wanted
to say goodbye.
Why are you running away?
I heard them say they were
sending me back to the boys
home.
This time it will be for
delinquence.
I■m not going back there.
You cannot go.
Listen don't try to stop me. ill
get away sooner or later.
I■m not going where people tell
me to go anymore.
That■s the mistake you made.
You cannot go alone.
Why not.
Because I'm coming with you.
You are?
Yes.
Can you get out of here?
The door is locked at 8pm, but
the night nurse has the key.
Only she can open it.
Now, I need what you call a
diversion
[doorbell]
Poppa's pizza.
Who is it?
Poppas pizza, that'll be 12.50
for your large supreme pizza.
No, I didn't order any pizza.
Are you sure nobody here ordered
this ultimate, super deluxe,
Double pepperoni, triple cheese
pizza?
Did you say double pepperoni?
Double pepperoni.
Uh, oh ok. come on in let me see
it.
That'll be 12.50.
Young man are you sure someone
ordered that pizza from here?
If they had I would of known.
Everybody's on a very restricted
diet.
Well uh, I guess I could take it
back.
Or, I could give it to you for
our preferred customer price of
$10.00
10.00?
No tax.
You know you seem a little young
to be doing this kind of thing.
Yea well that■s what my wife
said once I shaved my beard off.
Um ma'am?
It looks like you might have a
leak back there.
What the?
Ooo, ooo.
This is ridiculous, whats going
on around here?
Hey hey!
The doors jammed.
Hey pizza boy! pizza boy! get me
out of here.
Cmon cmon!
Woo!
Yea!
Freedom!
Hey pizza boy!
Um 2:45 for Greenville,
Monticello, orangedale and um...
Lantonville.
Oh lantonville, that should be
far enough.
Sometimes it pays to be too
young or too old.
Your ticket and my ticket. both
half price.
Well how much do I owe you?
You have money?
$27.00 plus 2.75. Profit on the
pizza.
[laughter]
Oh that■s good. Oh Cory.
■ Music ■
Come on son. better wake grandma
up or you'll miss your stop.
Grandma, wake up.
Oh what?
Were in Lantonville.
Were there?
Were here.
What did you call me?
Bus driver said grandma,
So I thought id better call you
grandma.
That■s a good idea. You must
always call me grandma.
Whenever we are around people.
That way it will not be
suspicious.
What do you think they'll do
when they find out your gone?
They'll call the police, and
announce it on television.
An elderly woman has wandered
away from the Edgewood nursing
home.
Last seen she was wearing a blue
nightgown.
They never think old people can
decide to go someplace. they
just wander off.
Suppose they'll figure we went
together?
It is not likely.
Oh look look.
Look Cory a cricket.
Its time for us to find a room,
come on.
But first,
Lets find a nice place to eat.
So what can I get for you?
Ill have a cup of coffee please.
Cream, sugar?
No, just black
and uh, Ill have a root beer
please.
My grandson will have a glass of
milk
I didn't ask for milk, ill have
a root beer.
A growing boy needs milk. It
would not do for you to get
sick.
Me and my grandmother will have
two milks.
That's two milks? You sure?
Yea yea, two milks.
That■s it! That■s it! That■s it!
What are you doing? Sit down!
Well you know that halva you
make?
We can sell it in restaurants,
and you know make sides just
like...
Behind you.
These!
Do you think they would buy?
Yea sure they would, its great
stuff, but who do you ever see
selling it?
We could sell to groceries too.
Yea, and I could deliver it to
all the customers.
You know, I have many many
recipes from all over the world
I have them all right here.
And maybe we can even have our
own bakery, and we'll name it
after that cricket you saw.
Here drink up, drink up we have
much to do.
It only has one bed.
Wait, hold up so it ain■t got
but one bed.
Look I could rent you the
rollaway for the boy.
Well how much is the rollaway?
8 dollars a week. we don't have
no kids here.
So we cant have a lot of noise
and no writing on the walls and
such
I don't write on walls.
No 8 is too much
ok.
Grandma I can sleep on the
floor.
How bout I give it to you for 5
dollars a week just.
Just as long as you don't go
telling anybody.
Well do you have a kitchen and a
bathroom?
A kitchen and a bathroom to
share, yes ma'am, right down the
hall.
How's a person supposed to fix
anything in this kitchen?
You're spread out all over the
place!
You can ask, Eleanor, and we
will move.
Here! Try some of this! It's
really good stuff.
Don't take up so much space next
time.
You ever have any kids?
No.
So you never had any
grandchildren.
No, you must have children to
have grandchildren
I know how it works, its just I
never knew if I had a
grandmother.
Whats it like to be old?
Sybil calls old age golden
years.
What a silly thing that is.
There was nothing golden at that
place
I call them the black years.
There■s nothing golden about bed
pans and sleeping pills.
But.
These days Cory,
These days,
I call golden.
May I help you madam?
Yea, would you like to order
some of our homemade desserts?
its halva.
Very sweet, very delicious.
We make all of our desserts here
on the premises.
We will not be the least bit
interested.
Why don't you try some?
Madam, please leave.
Or I shall be forced to...
To what?
Look! there■s a roach! right
there!
What roach?
Its right by, its right by that
huge rat!
Tats?
[screams]
Come on grandma lets get out of
this dump.
Its alright, its nothing!
Nothing really.
Huge rat!
Call the exterminator
I hate rich people.
He is a business man. We must
show him this is good business.
Then we can do business.
■ Music ■
Well she didn't say no.
She did not say yes.
And no yes is a no.
Carlotta, I think I can do this.
What?
Yea I can do this but I need
your help
Cory?
■ Music ■
No!
Sir, this is the distinctive
dessert item that you absolutely
must have
our customers don't like to try
new things
I beg your pardon!
I have always liked the new and
the exotic.
Would you like to try some halva
ma'am?
Oh yes, yes I would. Thank you
young man.
Halva. mmm oh my. Its wonderful.
You know I believe the ladies at
the junior league would enjoy
this.
We could serve it at our next
tea and.
At the males reception. Where
could I get more of this?
Um, right here madam. You could
order all you want through us.
Wonderful!
Excuse us.
Who makes this?
We do. in our own private
bakery.
We don't give out locations.
See this is a very secret recipe
from the king of halistan
himself.
Its been in the family for
generations and generations.
How much per pound?
Only 11.29.
Ill take 6 pounds a day starting
Tuesday.
Are you sure you can make
deliveries on time?
No problem. Pleasure doing
business with you.
Alright thanks. See you next
week.
Got five more restaurants signed
up
28 dollars and 31 cents.
You know something is wrong.
What?
There should be more halva,
And the bacon is less than there
should be.
Well I had two sandwiches for
lunch
I know about that.
What do you smell?
Ah ha!
Where did that bacon come from?
From a pig what do you think?
Hm, you stole that from us.
Come on who knows who's is what?
You got your stuff all over the
kitchen.
You'd know if you bought halva
or a pound of bacon,
And you saw it had a cricket
stamped on the package that it
was not yours!
You know you got some nerve
going around accusing decent
hard working folk old woman.
Hey! Who you calling old woman.
Id like to know why a kid your
age ain■t in school.
Maybe I should just call the
children officer.
You know who that is?
William Shakespeare. he wrote
plays for the theater
you know like Romeo and Juliet,
and Hamlet and a Mid Summers
Night Dream.
Oh look Cory. Look! Look at that
color. Isn't that interesting?
Yea, but I just don't get it you
know
Cory. Cory art is important. now
we must, uh, we must think about
school for you.
School? Why do you even bring
that up?
What kind of a grand mama am I?
I did not even think about
school until that Eleanor witch
brought it up.
You know I've been too happy
enjoying your company to think
what you need.
I don't need it, I hate it!
Now what grade, what grade are
you in?
I■m in fourth, I'm really
supposed to be in sixth.
Well then that■s where we will
put you, and we will go there
tomorrow.
You cant do that! They'll want
my tickets from the other
school.
You'll tell them that I taught
you at home.
Well then who's going to deliver
the halva, and the bread,
and who's going to get us the
new customers.
Who's going to do that?
You will make the delivery in
the morning before school.
And I will tell them your birth
records were lost
[sigh]
I think your taking this
grandmother thing a little bit
too far.
Oh I see.
You, you want to fire me as your
grandmother?
We are no longer family?
No
I didn't mean that.
A grandmother would not let you
run wild!
If we are family than I must
treat you as family.
Well look, look at this. its
wonderful.
Do you see inside each square is
a different design.
There he is right now, go get
him!
No Cory! No Cory! Cory!
■ Music ■
Come here kid!
Hey, wheres my halva order!
■ Music ■
Hey!
Go kid!
Come here. Stop!
[car horn]
If I get my hands on you!
Grandma!
Cory! Cory!
Are you alright?
I■m fine.
Look I packed some things in a
hurry, but we must move on.
So what now?
Well we have no money for a bus
ticket...
Wait.
I have an idea.
No, no Cory!
Yea, come on!
Don't do that.
Just trust me alright
yes!
Where did you learn to do that?
Kenry Heights home for boys.
Get in!
Hey kid, what are you doing by
my truck?
Sorry I was just admiring these
nice cars you got here.
Get away from the truck
[car horn]
Cory! Cory!
Here grab on!
Come on!
Cory! Cory!
That■s it! Hold on!
So what do you think we should
do now?
I■m tired we will have to go to
the shelter this time.
It will be hard. its always hard
to make due with less.
When you've had more, but we
must try.
Look!
Oh!
■ Music ■
I want you to take a look at the
ropes on number 3, 5 and 8.
Hurry up!
What can I do for you lady?
Well I'm looking for a job.
What experience have you had?
I was with the filo Demetrius
circus.
You know, I bought that circus
twelve years ago and to this day
I wish I hadn't.
What did you do?
Well I was with the concessions
and wardrobe and I was a cook.
And she was a magician's
assistant and a fortune
teller...
Sounds like she did a lot.
Look uh,
Were filled up lady.
Filled up. There■s just nothing
available for you here.
Oh ok. Thanks. Thanks.
Well I tried. I wish you good
luck.
Thanks.
Boss! We just lost the cotton
candy girl.
Cotton candy girl gone. She ran
off with the sugar salesman.
Oh your kidding.
This is serious boss.
Serious. Real terrible serious
I mean there■s a line all the
way to the elephant ride.
Backed up, line, elephants,
backed up.
Come on! Backed up to what, the
elephants?
And the girl runs away! Quiet
will you!
Tom and Hank. Go on back ill
take care of everything.
Will ya!? Go on!
Hank or Tom. Tom or Hank. Twins.
Geez.
Hey lady!
Hold it just a minute.
Yea?
I■m going to let you stay in the
back of the wardrobe truck.
You too. And I'm going to give
you a week.
No longer than that. just one
week.
Lady you better sell a lot of
cotton candy.
Well that■s her specialty.
Oh it is huh? Whats your name?
Cory.
Well you better stay out of my
way Cory.
One week!
Thanks.
Sell a lot of that cotton candy
lady.
I hire an elderly lady, and a
first of May.
Woo!
It's great!
Can we go back and get seconds
after this?
No, you do not act like a pig on
your first day, first of may.
Excuse me?
Yes?
Could you possibly be Carlotta?
Dingy? Dingy!
What kind of a fortune teller
are you?
You told me I would grow up to
be rich and handsome!
Oh Dingy!
Oh Carlotta!
How long has it been?
Oh much too long. Forever.
Dingy. I want you to meet my
grandson, Cory
Cory this is Dingy, the orlds
dizziest clown
I haven't used that name for 20
years.
I■ve met a few dizzier than me.
And besides I'm getting a little
long in the tusk for clowning,
But I still love it. I teach the
young ones.
I■m very pleased to meet you
Cory.
Its nice to meet you too
I didn't even know you had
children.
Oh well, I kept a few things to
myself.
Your grandma was the best
costumer.
Oh yes. and I think the most
incredible cook a big top ever
had!
Lots of paprika!
The goulash, middanoodles!
Now you going to join us? Yes?
Well the boss says he'll give me
a chance at selling concessions.
Oh good!
There■s someone else here
I bet he remembers you.
Yes? Oh yea.
Yea Yea!
Come on ill show you.
Hurry!
Cool, an elephant.
No, no Cory. This is Annabelle!
See Carlotta she remembers you!
Oh of course you do. oh
Annabelle I have missed you so
much!
Look I want you to meet someone
very special, my grandson Cory.
Hey Lady!
Listen I'm going to have someone
introduce you to the
concessioner manager.
Ok? And as for you, I'm going to
have someone introduce you to
school.
School?
Yea, and keep your grades up up
I don't want the welfare
department on my neck.
Ill show him where it is. Ok
fine.
Italy was the heart of the old
roman empire.
It was the political and
cultural and economic center of
the world.
Excuse me miss loralie, but I
brought you a punipal.
No I mean a stew nudent.
This is Cory, he comes from one
of finest and oldest of circus
families.
Hi Cory, were very glad to have
you.
Whats your last name?
Wai-...Rider.
Rider? Ok. Is that r-y-d-e-r?
R-i-d-e-r.
Oh ok.
And how old are you?
Eleven.
What are you going to be doing
in the show?
My grandmas selling cotton candy
and stuff.
Why don't you take a seat right
over there.
Concession people, ugh.
Don't let him bother you.
He's just a little filled with
himself.
Be back for you later. Good
luck!
Ok don't forget your oral book
reports are due Friday,
And you better be working on
your science projects,
And don't worry Cory ill help
you get caught up.
Don't worry Cory, well teach you
to make the correct change
Sebastian! That■s enough!
We were reading about Italy.
Portia thank you.
Begin at the top of the page,
and as she reads
I'll point out the geography on
the map
Italy is bordered by France, in
the northwest.
The Langranian sea and the
Tyrinian sea in the west.
Pull it tight.
Hey Cory! I told you not to get
in anybodys way!
Whats the matter with you?
No boss, he was just helping.
No Steve, that's nice of you to
say that
but I told him not to get in
anybodys way
I was just trying to help.
Hey, you see that little booth
over there?!
You think you can sell some
cotton candy?!
Cant you give me a job in the
big top?
You are going to be the main
cotton candy seller. now go on!
Alright! Alright!
Get those nickels and dimes!
Oh, you look magnificent. Now
remember, you are part of the
show.
You are going to sell more
cotton candy than they could
ever imagine.
Go, make me proud of you.
Yea.
Ladies and Gentleman! Children
of all ages!
Welcome to the worlds largest
circus under the big top!
From Mexico, celebrated stars of
the flying trapeze. The Luna
family flyers!
■ Music ■
[applause]
Ladies and gentleman, aerial
ballet extraordinaire. Lauralie
kunjano
[applause]
Presenting, the incredible
bareback riders. Featuring the
amazing Sebastian.
Hurry up you fool!
The daring Rodriguez brothers
and their wheel of destiny.
Cotton Candy.
Acrobatic prodigy, eleven year
old, Portia.
Oh Annabelle! you naughty girl!
Don't tell me you sold it all
again so soon!
Yea well its not that hard,
But if this was our halva it'd
sell even better
I think it has more to do with
the salesman
who could say no to you?
I■m afraid your going to break
many little girls hearts.
Come on, here you take some of
this
Cory, Cory what did you do?
There■s twice as much money here
as there should be.
Well a lot of the customers said
keep the change.
Does that mean I can keep it?
Yes! For your college fund
[sigh]
Cotton candy right here, cotton
candy.
The children's favorite. Those
lovable k9. Presented by
stephana and company.
A little clumsy there aren't we
candy boy?
No, no no. Not now!
Get that picked up. come one
Cory. Rod pick that up.
Mans best friend. most lovable
k9's.
Are you sure Sebastian did this
on purpose?
Yes, I'm absolutely positive.
Well some people can only think
they are big.
If they make some one else feel
small.
The world is full of Sebastians,
but things have a way of
working.
There way around and coming back
to you.
You mean what goes around comes
around.
I■ve only got a minute, but I
heard what happened.
I■m really sorry. Sebastian is
such a jerk.
Are you alright?
Yea, thanks.
I■ve got to go.
As they say, what goes around
comes back at you.
Zacharius, the fastest human on
two wheels.
Thanks
[applause]
Zacharius!
Carlotta, Cory. there is
something I have to tell you
both.
Uh huh.
There is a rumor going around
the grounds.
That you two are doing very
well!
Oh that■s great dingy!
I told the boys to put some
stuff in your place
to fix it up a little bit.
So does that mean we can stay?
Boss says he has no choice.
Concession sales are up 61%.
Woo! 61%! Woo!
Oh no stop fooling around! You
have to work on your spelling!
Grandma?
We were so beautiful.
Stay, stay.
Yes dear. you have remembered
everything. Peter John taught
you.
Do you remember the night that
Peter John and I danced
together.
Right here it was.
The music came from the pier
across the lake.
It was if they were playing only
for us.
■ Music ■
Thank you, Peter John
I knew you would come home.
Thank you.
Good good! Keep your hands low,
good!
That■s the way! good good good!
Hey dingy, who's your buddy?
This is Cory. he and his
grandmother joined us last week.
She used to be with us in the
old show.
Nice to meet you Cory, I'm Zack.
Hey what are you doing with this
no count clown?
I am teaching him the ropes
Zack, and he learns real fast.
Oh yea? Well I might need an
assistant.
Listen when I'm done courting
the school mom.
Ill give you a ride on my Harley
if you help me.
I■m building something secret
for my new act, what do you
think?
Uh yea sure.
Cool
[engine revving]
Ok lets go.
Good.
Does Zack like ms Lauralie?
Well who doesn't?
But does she like him?
Well uh, that■s a matter of
interpretation.
You've known my grandmother for
a long time haven't you?
Oh yes a very long time.
Well uh, did you know a man
named peter john?
It was 1944, and peter john and
I were in the same outfit.
Our job was to hack a supply
line right through the Burma
jungle.
All the way to China.
Did you ever hear of the lido
road?
No
Peter John, he sold our major on
the idea of using elephants to
clear the way quicker.
The last time I ever saw Peter
John,
I led a patrol, and somehow we
stumbled right into the
Japanese.
We tried to outrun them but
they, they had us backed into a
revene
and they began picking us off
like sitting ducks
all of a sudden Cory, the ground
starts shaking.
Son of a gun if I don't see a
stampede of elephants
ripping right through the
Forrest
and guess who was sitting on the
back of the head elephant?
Peter John
Peter John.
Riding that elephant into the
heart of the Japanese camp
was the last time I ever saw
Peter John.
So Peter John and my grandmother
never got married.
No. Even after the war ended,
She never could accept the fact
that he was dead.
She kept working at the circus
day and night.
Waiting for him to come home,
but Peter John never did.
Now don't be looking down there
you'll miss the one down there.
Now come on, once again! lets
see.
Hey cor man!
Miss Lauralie, I was wondering
if I could do my next report on
Burma?
Yea that'll be fine.
You ready for your ride?
Sure. I guess.
Lets go.
Helmet on dude
[revving engine]
Lauralie, hows the little fellow
doing?
Well he's doing great, but
there■s something I cant figure
out.
Whats that?
I cant get any legal information
from him or his grandmother.
You cant? well you better stick
to it.
Get some legal information cause
I cant hire a minor that■s
undocumented.
You know what they'd do to me!?
Stick to it.
Alright.
Cory Wainwright?
Wainwright.
■ Music ■
An amazing partnership of man
and animal. The breathtaking
exotic Bengal tigers.
In a rare breed of four color
varieties.
All eyes on this man.
■ Music ■
Sebastian is about to come on. I
thought you'd might want to
watch.
Are you kidding?
No, he's got a new act except he
doesn't know it. Come on!
Ladies and gentleman, in the
rich grand tradition of the
circus. the bareback riders
featuring the amazing Sebastian
[applause]
Woa!
Put me down you fool! You're
ruining my act!
Payback time Sebastian!
[applause]
Oh its just what I told you.
What comes in a circle, hits you
in the back of the head!
She means what goes around comes
around.
Boss Ed! Boss Ed!
Will you tell me what idiots is
responsible for this?
What are you talking about
idiots? They loved you.
You needed a hook, and you found
it tonight.
Let me tell you something, I
want those responsible for this
fired immediately.
Oh you do, do ya? Well you
listen to boss Ed and you listen
good.
I want every performance from
you the same way every night.
What?
Night after night the same way!
Understand?
■ Music ■
Woo!
Alright! Woohoo!
You did great dude.
I wonder what Michelle and Dan
are doing right now
I wonder what happened to your
turtle.
Mr T?
Oh Michelle would have taken
good care of him
Michelle, she sounds like a good
person. I bet she's worried
about you.
Yea but what can I do? I mean, I
cant call her
I think you owe them an
explanation.
Why do I owe them?
I heard them planning to send me
back to the agency.
They were going to call miss
Hanks that night.
You and the circus were the only
family I've ever had.
I■m not going to a deliquencent
home for kids, or even worse
another foster home.
Can we talk?
Sure
I found out something about Cory
Rider.
He signed his paper Cory
Wainwright.
I■m sure he didn't realize he
had done it.
But when I got no help from him
or his grandmother on getting
his records
I called the state education
records office,
And I asked them to find eleven
year old Cory Wainwright.
They came up with this. Its his
complete history up to a year
ago.
You■re better than Magnum P.I.
He's gone from institutions to
foster homes for the last five
years.
He never stayed anywhere more
than a few months.
Seems like the only thing
constant in his life is that
nobody wanted him
Zack...
At four he witnessed his fathers
death.
His father was driving a
motorcycle.
And then a year later his mother
abandoned him.
He's the kind of kid that
usually gets lost forever.
You got to give carlotta the
credit, but there■s not mention
of a grandmother in here
somethings wrong
I requested an update on the
last twelve months
and that should give me some
answers.
He's a natural on a motorcycle.
That■s why you're so important
to him.
So what should I do?
Just keep on doing what your
doing.
I■m going to get some
professional advice.
This is just way out of my
league.
■ Music ■
Dear Michelle and Dan,
I■m sorry I left without saying
goodbye
I found a really great home with
great people
I hope you are all fine and your
new baby will be fine too.
Thank you for giving me a good
home.
Love Cory.
P.S. Please take Mr. T to the
woods.
I know now that he really wants
to be free.
Who you writing?
Nobody. just some old folks I
used to know.
Oh, where'd you used to live.
Different places
I cant wait to see zack's new
act. Whats it like?
Oh you'll see when we get to
Norwood.
■ Music ■
Ladies and gentleman, for the
first time in our long and
celebrated history
Clyde Beatty Gold Brothers
proudly presents.
Zacharias and the death defying
conquest of the Thunder Globe of
Doom!
And now, Zacharias will attempt
to defy gravity and
achieve a new world's record
with 15 vertical orbits in the
Globe of Doom.
Join with me, as we witness the
impossible.
[applause]
Performing this incredible feat.
The worlds youngest daredevil.
The one and only eleven year old
sensation
Cory the Magnificent!
Ladies and gentleman its
official. A new world record!
Wow! You did great!
Way to go pal!
That■s what you two have been up
to all the time. you little
devil.
Isn't grandma here?
Ladies and gentleman, boys and
girls we would like to thank you
and your family for choosing...
Grandma!
Grandma wait wait! That■s my
grandma.
Grandma wake up.
[ambulance siren]
Wheres the grandson.
Thanks.
Your names Corey right?
Yeah.
Well Cory there 're some things
we really need to know.
Wheres you grandmothers nearest
adult relatives?
And where are your parents? We
need her medical records
I don't know. Just make her well
alright.
We're doing everything we can.
Thanks.
Hello Cory.
Hi.
Hows your grandmother?
I don't know.
Look I want to tell you Cory,
that your grandmother is.
Well she needs somebody to take
care of her.
She's too old to start something
new and try to work in a circus.
And Lauralie, she knows about
you being a runaway.
And if the state ever found out
I hired a run away.
They would close me down just
like... like that. huh?
You wouldn't want that, would
ya?
No
I took her clothes, I want you
to know this, and your things
too
and I put them down in a locker
down at the bus station.
Here is the key.
Now you take care of that
because all your things are in
that locker.
By the way I got something here
for ya, now you be careful with
this,
Because its your severance pay.
you know? that■s for you and
your grandmother.
And it'll get you back to uh,
wherever home is.
Take care.
-MUSIC-
You've got to get well. you've
got to, the circus will take us
back.
Its my fault I should have taken
care of you
I tried my best
I did.
I didn't tell you this..
But I couldn't have loved you
any more if you were my real
grandmother
-footsteps-
Hey, you dress really cool.
Thanks.
Here, you can have it.
Geeez thanks, does it have any
super powers?
I wish they did.
-CAROL SINGING-
-MUSIC-
God bless you.
Why, God bless you young man.
No my grandma, God bless my
grandma.
-CAROL SINGING-
-MUSIC-
thanks.
Oh, Hello my first of May.
Do you feel better?
Oh I am so full of pills. I
think..
I think sybal found all the
pills I did not take and gave
them to me all at once.
Listen, we got to get out of
here soon, alright?
No, no Cory
I'm sorry Cory.
I can no longer look after you.
But I'll look after you then.
No, no someone younger,
stronger.
I should have never have done
this.
We did great together, remember?
Yeah, but no more
Cory, Cory, you must do
wonderful things.
You're so, you're so strong and
so clever.
Look at me now. I could never
love you more,
If you were my real grandson.
-MUSIC-
Oh, I'm so so ti... tired now
-medical beeping-
NO
No! No!
..I don't know her last name but
she should be in intensive
care...
CORY!
Cory, Cory! Cory!
Aw...
Grandma she's dead.. she's dead
and, its all my fault!
Its not your fault, Cory, Cory
every things gonna be ok.
Cory.
No Cory please stop.
How'd you find me here.
You've got some very special
friends that care a lot about
you.
Please we.. we just want to ask
you one question.. alright.
What?
Why did you leave us Cory? Why?
You know...
No we don't know...
Your gonna have your own kid..
And me?
You said "what the heck, send
him back to the agency".
You did, I heard you.
God. no Cory no, we were talking
about me when I was your age.
I... I was raised in a home for
girls.
I had lots of foster parents but
I was never adopted.
And I swore that some day I
would take at least one child
out from all that.
We wanted you to be that child
Cory. and we still do.
We want you to be our son.
We've been worried sick.
Dan quit his job to look for
you.
You did?
Can always find another job,
Can't find another Cory.
What about your new baby?
All I know is she is really
looking forward to seeing her
big brother.
-MUSIC-
Lets go.
-medical chatting-
(Grandma's voice) You can't go
alone.
(Cory's voice) Why not?
(Grandma's voice) Because I'm
coming with you!
(Cory's Voice) But I couldn't
have loved you anymore if you
were my real grandmother.
(Cory's Voice) I'll be your
family.
(Grandma's Voice) And ill be
yours.
-Beeping starts-
(doctor): GOT her.
Mmhm looks pretty good.
Lets try some shall we?
Can she have some?
I don't think shes quite ready
for halva.
Mm almost as good as me and
grandma used to make.
Ill be the judge of that Cory
Kepperman.
Good morning grandma
-baby cries-
Hows the little one?
Ohhh.
Mom can you help me with the
frosting?
Ya sure.
You're so cute.
Hey mom.
Hey Dan.
Nice work, you want to play some
catch?
Ya.
Isn't today some national
holiday or something?
I don't think so.
Oh ya sure.
HAPPY BIRTHDAY CORY!!
That's what it was.
Well Cory don't just stand
there, we're gonna have a family
picnic.
That a boy, son happy birthday.
Get in here.
Happy Birthday Cory.
Come on everybody on three. Say
cheese.
On 1, 2, 3.
CHEESE!!
[Music]