(waves crashing)
(lively piano music)
- [Reporter Voiceover]
Famous model socialite
and owner of The Tides
hotel, Louis Balfour,
the mistress of art deco, was found dead
in her suite at The Tides in
Miami's posh Deco District.
- [Banker] Very well, Miss
Balfour, that should be it.
The trust will take care of the hotel
if anything should happen to you,
but as your banker I should tell you
that this is rather an unusual approach.
However, it does appear to be legal,
so we'll keep the title
deed safe in a deposit box
and you can keep the keys.
- [Louise] To a safe deposit box.
- [Reporter Voiceover] Rumors abound
concerning her despondency
over a broken love affair
with philandering
photographer James Farentino.
(lively piano music)
(people whispering)
- [Louise] The title deed.
- [Child] Title deed.
- [Louise] Title deed.
No, no, no, no!
- You haven't--
- Blood!
Blood, blood--
- Forget blood,
blood--
- No!
- [Banker] We'll keep the title deed
safe in a deposit box
and you can keep the key.
(key clangs)
- [Man] Night, Miss Balfour.
- [Louise] Goodbye.
(pounding piano music)
His hands touching my breasts,
warm hands touching my breasts.
- I'm an asshole.
- You go around
with a slut--
- Yes.
- [Louise] You've been
talking to all the models
you work with?
- That's what I do.
That's what I like!
- What are you doing to me?
Tell me.
- [Man] We used each other.
It's over, it's over, it's been over.
- [Louise] Yeah, that's right, it is over.
This is over.
- Goodbye, goodbye, Louise.
- [Reporter Voiceover] Famous
model socialite and owner
of the The Tides hotel, Louise Balfour,
the mistress of art deco, was found dead
in her suite at The Tides in
Miami's posh Deco District.
The tragedy--
- Miami's celebrated model
Louise Balfour, a suicide,
at the Deco District hotel
to which she was proprietress.
Closed, The Tides hotel, which once stood
as a magnet for the glamorous and powerful
now stands as a lonely
sentinel to her memory.
(speaker fades out)
(lively piano music)
(lightning cracks)
- I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I just can't take it.
I can't stay here any
longer keeping you company
with an old desk clerk's memories.
Just ain't enough.
A hotel needs people, new people,
lots of people.
They're going to demolish you.
They're going to turn you
into rubble and rubbish.
You're on your on now.
We're both on our own.
(lightning cracks)
(whispering voices)
(eerie instrumental music)
(lightning cracks)
(electricity buzzes)
(whispering voices)
- [Louise Voiceover] Where am I?
- [Ghostly Voice] Help.
- [Ghostly Voice] Help us.
- [Louise] I'm dead.
What's happened to my hotel?
It's a dream, isn't it?
It's not true, it just can't be true.
This can't be for me.
I don't want to remember.
No.
Why am I alive?
(whispering voices)
- Redeem your soul.
- [Louise] I was wronged.
I should have killed him.
(whispering voices)
He wronged me.
Why didn't I kill him?
(whispering voices)
- [Ghostly Voice] Life.
Take it back.
Feed us.
- Feed you?
Who are you?
- [Ghostly Voice] Redeem your soul.
- [Louise] How can I redeem
myself if I'm already dead?
- [Ghostly Voice] Restore me
back.
- Sounds like I was better off dead.
(whispering voices)
- [Ghostly Voice] Remember.
- [Louise] Why didn't I kill him?
- [Ghostly Voice] Save me.
- [Louise] The safe deposit box.
- [Ghostly Voice] Kill, now.
Now.
- I can never love again.
- [Ghostly Voice] Kill him, now.
- [Louise] Now, why him?
- [Ghostly Voice] Kill, now.
(pulsing electronic music)
- Are you okay?
- I'm so sick of trying to make money.
It drives me crazy.
(pulsing electronic music)
Just leave the lingerie,
I'll do it tomorrow.
- I'll believe that when I see it.
(pulsing electronic music)
Do you think someone will
buy the pictures this time?
- [Photographer] I hope so.
That was my last roll of film.
I'll see you later in the week.
(pulsing electronic music)
(water patters)
(percussive instrumental music)
- How can you work in this light, Carlos?
It's not good for your eyes, man.
- Hey, man, who's this girl here, man?
She look good, man.
Does she give you good head, man?
- Thank you, man, thanks.
That was my best one.
I'm gonna have to work all night.
Stay away from this, Zippo.
- Zippo, do what the man says.
Otherwise, you might not
like what you find, man.
Carlos, how is your mother, man?
Do you still send her money?
- What's the matter with you, Johnny, huh?
You got nothing better to do?
- What's the matter?
Here you are in this great studio.
How long have you been here now, Carlos?
Seven months.
You owe me $10,000 rent.
First you think you're some kind of hero
because Time Magazine prints
your pictures of dead bodies.
Then you escape to America.
You think it's gonna be easy?
- You told me it was gonna be easy.
- You start by making the girls
take their clothes off, man, you know?
- [Zippo] Yeah, yeah.
- Take the clothes off.
You cannot face up to your life, man.
One way, that is it.
Carlos,
don't fuck with me, huh?
Otherwise, Rico here will give you a smile
that's gonna narrow your face, man.
(Johnny speaking foreign language)
(door slams)
♪ Every day ♪
(singing in foreign language)
(Zippo speaking foreign language)
- [Zippo] How about a little Cuba, man?
- Hey, you, I know you!
You work for Johnny.
You used to go out with my sister.
I'm gonna tell her that you insulted me!
- [Zippo] Woo!
(jagged pop music)
- [Woman] Thank you, bye
bye, have a good night.
- [Waiter] There you are,
special compliments of your waiter.
Is there anything else you would like?
- No thanks.
- Hey, is that real antique lace?
- Hey!
- Is there something
else I can do for you?
- Yeah.
Eat my steak.
- Hey, hey, wait a minute.
(waiter retches)
- No, no, no, Mama, everything's okay.
I don't wanna talk about myself.
Yeah, Mama, I love you, too, bye bye.
(knocking)
It's open!
(door creaks)
(soft piano music)
(dramatic musical flourish)
- Oh, Byron.
The king of terror seized her as his prey.
Not worth, no beauty of her life retained.
(Louise sighs)
- You know Byron?
(Louise gasps)
- [Louise] Some.
I like your studio.
It's very nice.
(soft piano music)
Do you need a model?
- I doubt it.
So who sent you?
Murray?
- No, I just sort of got wind of you.
The key.
Wow, geez.
This is really interesting.
Did you make it?
- Yeah.
You know, to pass the time.
- Where'd you find all these keys?
- The junk shop, anywhere.
Everywhere.
So, anyway, what have you done?
- Little here, little there, nothing much.
I'm just starting.
- You walked in here cold, right?
- Well, if you wanna put it that way.
- [Carlos] So you think
it's easy being a model?
Right, I try one roll.
But, here's the deal, anybody
want to work with you,
which is pretty unlikely,
I pay you regular rates.
Otherwise, it's no deal.
- I think I can do it.
- [Carlos] Let's start.
So what's your name?
- [Louise] Louise.
- All right, you hold it just like that.
(camera pops)
You've got to move your
hair out of your face.
I can't see your eyes.
(camera pops)
Change behind the screen.
(soft pop music)
Okay, these are playful, you know?
Real simple.
Not too sexy.
If you can't do it, just humor me, okay?
(soft pop music)
Okay.
(camera pops)
Good.
That's good, yeah.
(camera pops)
Okay, now we do the beach scene.
(soft pop music)
Okay.
Okay, relax.
Good.
(camera pops)
(whispering voice)
- [Louise Voiceover] His
hands touched my breasts.
(whispering voices)
Stupid, so stupid, believing this shit.
- Tell me something.
The alcohol and the kissing,
does that make your job easier?
You photographers are all the same.
- Tell me who sent you, huh?
Johnny?
- I don't think so.
- 24 exposures, time's up.
Give me your address
and your phone number.
- [Louise Voiceover] The key.
(bell rings)
(percussive music)
- [Ghostly Voice] I can see the light.
- [Louise] I can't believe I lost the key.
- [Ghostly voice] Bad.
(whispering voices)
- Leave me alone!
Leave me alone.
(whispering voices)
(jazzy instrumental music)
- [Carlos] She looks good there, right?
- [Man] The photography is
not so hot, but she is it.
You've outdone yourself.
Christ, Carlos, where did you find her?
- She's just another model.
- I had a girlfriend like this once.
Beautiful.
Got into a car wreck.
Her face, it never quite set properly.
I mean, every time I looked at her,
her jaw wouldn't come together,
and I was a little disgusted every time
I would smile at her.
We were engaged, I had to get rid of her,
and that was it.
This girl is perfect, and I want her
at the beach tomorrow morning, we shoot.
- I need an advance.
- (sighs) Nine o'clock Friday morning,
but I want the negative.
I want her face out on
the street by tonight.
- [Ghostly Voice] I need life.
- [Ghostly Voice] Life!
- [Ghostly Voice] Bring me back.
(whispering voices)
Feed us.
- [Louise] Stupid, stupid.
(whispering voices)
(jagged instrumental music)
(banging)
(men chattering)
(belching)
- Henry, give me your
cigarette. Don't flick it.
- I didn't, jerk off.
- Holy shit.
- Get out of here.
- Guys, guys,
I'm gonna see you later, okay?
- [Man] Shit, shit, shit.
- Woo wee!
Excuse me, excuse me.
Do you got a match?
- Sure do
if you got some cigarettes.
- Well, this is my last one,
but maybe there's another in the car.
- Well, if there ain't, you
could always take me for a ride.
- [Henry Voiceover] Woo
whee, I am gonna like
raping you, you dumb little bitch.
If you're lucky, I may even give it to you
up your tight little butt.
- Maybe, maybe.
Sure.
Hop in, why don't you?
Shazam!
So now you tell me, what's a
pretty little girl like you
doing out walking alone at night?
- Why don't you just drive
on to a grocery store
and get us some cigarettes?
- [Henry Voiceover] Man,
something about the way
she talks makes me
wanna fuck her real bad,
cutting her a little more than usual.
Take the tip off her cute little nose.
- Tell me something,
do you mind if I touch
those cute little fangs of yours?
(car revs)
Off we go.
(jagged instrumental music)
- Yeah, I took that shot, huh?
It's my first ad, what do you think?
- Well, I think it's absolutely unique.
I think there's an extraordinary
creative feeling about it.
It has an ambience and it's very akin
to a sort of system called linearism,
which is lines, as opposed to
pointillism, which is dots.
There is a mystique about it.
The whole ambience comes
right through the creativity.
It really hits you.
(bright rock music)
- [Henry] Well, here we are.
- [Louise Voiceover] Kissing me.
(whispering voices)
Touching my breasts, touching my breasts.
So stupid, so stupid.
(whispering voices)
- [Henry] Now don't squirm, okay?
- Henry, Henry! (giggles)
- [Henry] Just shut up
or I'll cut your stinking little nose off.
(Louise laughs)
- Holy cow, Henry!
How old were you when you first raped?
You were eight years old.
- Shut up!
- Isn't that right?
- Bitch!
(Louise chuckles)
- Oh, poor Nelly on that farm next to you.
- [Henry] You dirty whore,
who have you been talking to?
- Broke her neck afterwards, didn't you?
Told everyone she fell. (laughs)
But why, Henry?
She would've done it
with you anyway. (laughs)
She liked you.
She thought you had pretty eyes.
- Now I am definitely going to kill you.
I am definitely going to kill you!
I'm definitely going to kill you!
- Shut up.
I'm gonna take some
weight off your shoulders.
- [Henry] No.
(neck cracks)
(Louise grunts)
(whispering voices)
- [Louise Voiceover] Love, love, love.
Stupid, stupid.
- [Man Voiceover] Goodbye, goodbye.
(whispering voices)
(soft instrumental music)
(electricity buzzes)
- First time to make money off my work,
and I don't even remember her name.
I'm such an asshole.
(soft rock music)
(banging)
- Did you sell my pictures?
- No, I sold someone else's picture.
- Carlos, do you think I'm pretty?
- [Carlos] Sure, I think you're pretty.
- Do you like my body?
- [Carlos] Come on, Mandy, what is this?
- Carlos, why don't you like me?
Baby.
We could be so good for each other.
I could cook for you.
I can turn you on.
- [Louise Voiceover] Stupid, stupid.
(whispering voices)
- Move out of this place
and come and live at my sister's.
- I just can't move out of here.
- All these problems.
Do there have to be all
these problems all the time?
Come and live with Jeanette and me.
- Tell me!
- We use each other.
(shouting voices)
(whispering voices)
(panting)
- [Mandy] Come inside me.
Come inside me.
That's it, baby.
You don't care, you
don't care about sharing!
- Come on, Mandy, get up off the counter.
- [Mandy] You say that I'm the one.
(whispering voices)
But it's not me.
Stop, quit!
You're spoiled, Carlos.
- That's right, that's
fucking right, Mandy!
(whispering voices)
- We use each other.
- No, no, no, no.
(shouting voices)
(percussive electronic music)
- Carlos, you disturb my gaming.
What is the matter with you, huh?
She very nice, so what?
- So what, Johnny, you tell me.
You send her to me or no?
- You think I'm gonna send a
girl like this to you, man?
(Johnny chuckles)
You're crazy.
- Just give me the picture back, man,
come on.
- Wait.
Let me see it.
Did you shoot this?
It's out of focus.
But still,
she looks good enough on the outside.
But what's she like on the inside?
(screeching instrumental music)
(panting) Who is she?
What is she?
(panting) Real angry lady, man.
(grunting)
The stench!
The stench.
That's easy cash.
But the stench.
(rattling)
(droning ambient music)
My first reading's free.
You consult me twice, you pay the price.
100 bucks a pop.
- [Louise Voiceover] Save the key.
- [Ghostly Voice] Key.
(funky instrumental music)
Save the key.
(lightning cracks)
(doors creak)
(whispering voice)
(wind rustles)
(tinkling piano music)
It's time.
Help me.
(whispering voice)
- [Man] Hey, kid, need some help?
(screeching instrumental music)
Are you okay?
- No, I'm fine, thank you.
(phone rings)
- [Bud] Carlos, this is it.
I want that $500 tomorrow, tomorrow!
(phone rings)
(beeping)
- [Girl] Carlos, Carlos, thank
you so much for my dress.
I love it.
Mama's mad, she says it's too sexy,
but I'm so glad, I miss you so much.
It's only half a birthday without you,
but I love my dress, so get rich soon
so you can send for me.
I want to go to school
in America badly, badly.
I got to go now.
I love you, I love you.
(pulsing electronic music)
- You're having a bad trip, you know.
(Carlos chuckles)
- I was missing my little sister.
I thought I'd died and she'd gone,
I'd never see her again.
No, she's lost. (laughs)
And I was trying to find her.
- I'm lost, too.
Maybe you can find me.
(pulsing electronic music)
- [Ghostly Voice] Help me.
(whispering voice)
(panting)
(gibbering)
(electricity buzzes)
(pulsing electronic music)
- You know what?
- Tell me.
- You know, we both have
something in common.
We're both looking for something.
- We're both looking for ourselves, right?
- Yeah.
Except for I think it's
time to change our luck.
(pulsing electronic music)
Listen, I'll see you later, okay?
- Who's gonna help find me now?
(eerie instrumental music)
(banging)
- It's open.
(door creaks)
- [Louise] Hello.
I'm back.
- You should've given me
your telephone number.
(Louise gags)
I can't work with that kind of attitude.
Tell me something, you come in here
like something the cat drug in,
you're unreliable,
and, for some reason, I
always get this feeling
like you're lying to me,
so tell me, why should I give you a break?
- Carlos, cut the crap.
- Look into my eyes.
- What is this?
- Just come here and look into my eyes.
- I would just like to use your bathroom.
- Just tell me what you see, first.
- I see a frustrated little boy.
(Louise chuckles)
- Very good.
Are you in some kind of trouble?
- No, I would just like to
powder my nose and leave.
What do you want from me?
- I want to know why
you want to be a model.
I mean, a girl like you could do anything.
There's no creativity in modeling,
there's no heart in it.
- Well, at least you're not trying
to sell me on the glamor.
I think that might be the
first honest thing you've said.
I'll tell you.
I want to become the ultimate object.
- (snorts) You're very funny.
I tell you what, I give you a break,
but on my terms.
You get here exactly 9:30 every morning.
You give me your address,
your phone number,
your mother's phone number.
That way, I can always get ahold of you.
And if you ever mess
with me, you're fired.
(Louise chuckles)
- These are the terms.
We work only at night.
No locations.
I don't want to meet any of your clients.
You don't get my telephone number,
and you don't get my address.
And if you ever see my after work,
you will never see me again.
And, on that note, when
do you wanna start?
- I'll see you tomorrow, Louise.
- Oh, one more thing,
did you find a small key?
I may have lost it here.
- No.
- Carlos.
- [Carlos] Yes?
- When a girl asks to use your bathroom,
you shouldn't keep her waiting.
- [Ghostly Voice] Help me.
(whispering voice)
Restore me.
- I can't.
Not anymore.
(whispering voices)
- No, huh?
- Look, Bud, you've already give me $500,
which I can't give back right now.
But if you give me the
lingerie for the shoot,
I come back tomorrow with contact sheet.
You got nothing to lose.
- What insane asylum
did you rent this girl
from anyway, Carlos?
- Bud, look, I got two
weeks' worth of work
lined up with this girl.
Her picture, it gets all over town,
it's gonna cost you twice as much, man.
- You know I don't care about that.
I like to meet the models
that are gonna work for me!
Give them a few tips, that's all.
- Everybody else has
agreed to the terms, man.
Nobody gets to meet her.
- All right, Carlos, I can't tell you
how you're really starting
to fucking bug me, okay!
I don't like playing these games.
Now take that and get outta here!
(dramatic piano flourish)
(tinkling electronic music)
(knocking)
(pulsing electronic music)
(door creaks)
- [Johnny] Carlos.
I see your model is back
and you're working again.
That's nice, man.
- Johnny, I'm right in the middle of it.
I see you tomorrow.
- Rico, tell me something, didn't we
already have to come back, man?
- We sure did, Johnny.
- [Carlos] Louise, please, excuse us.
You can wait in the kitchen.
- Carlos, there is no
need to bother your work.
Just the money.
Let her leave us.
(Johnny speaks indistinctly)
- I don't think I
understand your game here.
- [Johnny] It's very simple.
I need my money.
- Maybe you should ask Zippo about it.
- Ask me, man?
What are you talking about, man?
I don't know nothing, man, you understand?
- Perhaps you can enlighten me, Carlos.
- Somebody broke into
my apartment last night
and burnt my money.
(laughing)
- You should write books, man.
You got great stories, you know?
Carlos, we are now
(speaking foreign language).
I gave you a break.
You live better than me.
And now you're trying to
insult my fucking intelligence!
(speaking foreign language)
When you don't pay, I gotta pay, Johnny.
(grunting)
You got one more day, Carlos, huh, okay?
Warn him, Rico.
- Bet you couldn't do
that with a kitchen knife.
I think Carlos has had enough, don't you?
- This is the most exciting
night I've had in a week.
Okay.
Let him go.
- Say goodbye to your buddies.
- It turns me on when
you breathe in my ear.
- Don't force me.
It gets me too excited.
- Okay, the fun is over.
Everybody out.
Carlos, the rules remain the same.
Tomorrow, or you're history.
Adios, Carlos.
- Is it bad?
- I think we got some good pictures.
- [Louise] I can't stay.
You'll have to take care of yourself.
- Then wait.
(Louise moans)
- Are you waiting for me?
- You know, Johnny wanna
buy you a drink, man.
You handled yourself pretty good up there.
You and the photographer have
a lot of good times, huh?
- I wouldn't say that.
I'm going for a walk on the beach tonight
before I do anything.
Would you like to come?
(tinkling instrumental music)
(whispering voices)
- [Man Voiceover] That's what I do,
that's what I like!
- What are you doing to me?
Why didn't you tell me?
- We used each other.
- No, no, no, no.
I wanna douse you in paraffin.
I'm gonna set you alight.
Wish, wish, wish, wish.
Goddamn you! (laughs)
(Louise grunts)
(people chattering)
Hello, Johnny.
- [Johnny] I didn't expect you so soon.
- You invited me over
here, isn't that right?
- Yeah.
Sit down.
I guess you thought I was
a little rough on Carlos.
- No, I thought you handled
him just about right.
- Then why the fucking
thing with the knife, huh?
- Yes, it was just a little head release.
Just trying to get your attention.
- You like something to drink?
Some tequila, rum?
What would you like to drink?
- Do you have any blood?
- Maybe some red wine.
- Couldn't you slit your
wrist a little for me?
I'm so thirsty.
(Johnny chuckles)
- You better be careful, huh.
This kinky talk really turns me on.
- I don't wanna be careful.
I wanna bleed your memory
of every experience
that ever turned you on.
- Show me what you can do.
(laughing)
(lights buzz)
- So, Johnny, what's
the most exciting thing
you've ever done?
- When I was 14, I fucked
both my mother's sisters.
- Mother's sister, huh?
Are you sure that's
the most exciting thing
you've ever done?
- [Johnny] Yeah.
- Are you sure?
- [Johnny] She was the private
secretary for the general.
Sex, something, it's the
government's secret weapon.
You can train the private, though,
to protect himself from a
girl's tricks and a man's.
But no man is ever safe (indistinct).
(grunting)
(buzzing)
- [Louise] Weren't you
in jail for a while?
Didn't something in jail happen
that was more exciting?
- What is this?
- Didn't you and your gang
tie up a boy and rape him?
Didn't you say then that was
the most exciting thing
that ever happened?
Oh, Johnny.
Where's that boy?
Did he kill himself afterwards?
- You're fucking sick.
(Louise chuckles)
Who fucking sent you?
- No, you're sick.
Johnny, can I ask you something?
Do you know Fu Manchu?
Come on, Johnny, come on!
Go ahead, feed me!
(panting)
(grunting)
(Johnny screams)
(light buzzes)
(wind whistles)
(water splatters)
(machinery hums)
- I wanna meet this girl.
I'm sending the negatives
to the printer today,
and then I'm giving thought
to a national campaign.
This is a big break for you, Carlos, okay?
But I have to meet the girl.
- Look, man, it's out of my hands.
She doesn't wanna meet with anybody.
- What, you think that I'm gonna invest
in a major campaign if I
haven't even met the girl?
I'm talking about a $10,000 fee.
- [Ghostly Voice] Redeem your soul.
Help us feed.
Redeem.
- Okay, look, man, I'm
working with her tonight.
- Thank you.
- I'll talk to her,
but I don't know.
- You don't know, you
prick son of a bitch?
If you don't arrange a meeting for me,
believe me, I will find a
way to go directly to her.
Okay?
Don't embarrass yourself, and
don't waste my goddamn time.
Look, here, this is 1,000 bucks, okay?
We're square.
Now, if you ever wanna work for me again,
you're gonna deliver the goods.
You understand?
Remember.
(whispering voice)
(engine whines)
(door creak)
(whispering voice)
- Hello?
How are you feeling?
I thought you'd be a bit
too bruised to work tonight.
- My cousin Johnny was
murdered last night.
It's okay, you don't have to say anything.
You want a drink?
- No, thanks.
Carlos, would you read me a poem?
- [Carlos] You came by to sink your talons
in a little deeper, huh?
- Please, you're getting way off track.
- I'm not even touching you.
Why are you so defensive, huh?
- That's not what I want from you.
- Well, at the risk of
losing my only model.
(whispering voice)
(Louise gasps)
You are so weird.
I'm going to show you something.
It's my first portrait.
(whispering voice)
- [Louise Voiceover] Touching my breasts,
his warm hands touching my breasts.
(whispering voice)
Stupid, so stupid believing this shit.
Falling for this shit.
(whispering voice)
- You think you can seduce me
with your little romantic tricks?
- Is there no end to your attitude?
It's very simple with me.
My thoughts are not as
strong as my feelings.
My words are not as true as my touch.
- You're making this up.
At least be honest.
I might have more respect for you then.
- I'm being as honest as I can.
If you don't believe me,
can you read my mind?
- No.
- Tell me, can you read my mind?
Am I lying to you?
- No, no, I don't know.
Sit down.
(soft instrumental music)
- [Ghostly Voice] Feed us.
- [Louise] No, stop, please.
(whispering voice)
(low instrumental music)
- [Carlos] Where are you going?
- [Louise] Get some sleep, Carlos.
- [Carlos] What's the matter?
Louise!
(tinkling instrumental music)
(screaming)
(tinkling piano music)
- Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
Hey!
I just want, I need to talk to you.
(tinkling piano music)
Hello?
Hey, hey, hey!
Wait a minute, will you, please?
(tinkling piano music)
- Hey, man, did you see a girl?
- Sure, I've seen her many a time.
Often wish she could be mine.
- Hey what is this?
- Take the key and you will find
that it will save your sweet behind.
- Come on, man, did you
see the girl or not?
- I said I'd seen them.
You heard me well.
Impatience will take
you on the road to hell.
- What did you say, you seen
them? She was with somebody?
- Give way to jealousy and you're doomed.
On an island of fear, you'll be marooned.
Take the turning that I have picked.
You'll find her in the hotel.
It's derelict.
(shouting voice)
(whispering voice)
- [Louise Voiceover] Stupid, so stupid.
- What kind of fucking nightmare is this?
Look, if I scared you out there,
believe me, I didn't mean to.
You're just so goddamned beautiful,
I had to meet you.
Where are you, anyway?
Louise, right?
I'm Bud from Amazon Lingerie.
I am Amazon Lingerie.
The last thing on earth I want
is for you to be shy with me.
- [Louise Voiceover] Stupid, so stupid.
- Who else is in here?
(Louise whimpers)
Is that you?
Oh, I don't even wanna think about
a pretty little thing like you crying.
Maybe I can help you.
Stop crying now.
(Louise whimpers)
- I look such a mess. (cries)
- You could never look a
mess, you're so beautiful.
- Oh, but I do!
And I know you like pretty girls. (cries)
- Hey, I promise, I don't
care what you look like.
I don't.
- You really don't care what I look like?
- I promise.
(dramatic instrumental music)
(Louise laughs)
- What's up, Bud?
Remind you of someone?
Maybe your soul!
(Bud screams)
- We used each other.
(screaming)
We used each other.
(bluesy harmonica music)
(bottle shatters)
- Amazon Lingerie, please.
Hi, this is Carlos, can I speak to Bud?
Is he expected back?
No, that's fine.
No, no, no message.
Okay, thank you, bye bye.
Flagler Trust, please.
- I'm fed up, I'm changing banks, sorry.
- You have a lovely day, too.
Next, please.
Can I help you?
- [Carlos] Yes, I want to
open my safety deposit box.
- That's an old key.
- Yeah, it is.
- That way, please.
- My family, they've lived
in Miami for a long time.
- [Man Voiceover] We used each other.
(shouting voices)
We used each other.
- No, no, no, no.
(shouting voices)
(lightning cracks)
- We used each other.
- No, no, no, no.
(shouting voices)
- We used each other.
- No, no, no, no.
(shouting voices)
- We used each other.
- No, no, no, no.
(shouting voices)
- We used each other.
- No, no, no, no.
(shouting voices)
- We used each other.
- No, no, no, no.
- [Carlos] Are you here?
Is there anybody here?
(whispering voices)
(eerie instrumental music)
- [Louise Voiceover] Stupid, so stupid
for believing that shit.
(whispering voice)
(eerie instrumental music)
- Louise, are you in there?
Louise, you maniac, answer me.
(whispering voice)
(eerie instrumental music)
(door creaks)
Jesus Christ.
- You shouldn't have come!
(Louise roars)
We made a deal!
(Louise shouts)
- You're crazy.
What happened to Bud?
- Bud. (gags)
Hey, hey, wait a minute.
You think I really want to kill you?
- Louise, I wanted to help you.
- You can't help me!
(Louise groans)
- So you need the deed, right?
- What have you done?
- I found your key.
So tell me, what does it mean?
The building gets sold, it gets restored?
- Something like that.
- Tell me why you came to me.
- Maybe
because we need to be saved.
- Me or you?
- Both of us!
- [Carlos] I need to be with you.
(Louise gags)
- You can't be with me!
- Look, I don't care what you are!
I love you.
- I don't believe in love anymore!
(Louise groans)
Don't you understand?
(rumbling)
Go away!
Okay, okay.
Carlos,
there's only one way you can be with me.
But you have to do something
you've never done before.
- [Carlos] Yeah, and what is that?
- Commit yourself.
- I can do that.
- Forever?
I don't think so.
- [Carlos] I can.
- Maybe you can
be with a woman that's killed?
- I don't care what you are.
- You might not survive the initiation.
- Try me.
- You said it.
- [Ghostly] Redeem us.
(eerie instrumental music)
(sign buzzes)
(rumbling)
(eerie instrumental music)
(singing in foreign language)
- Carlos, Senora Louise.
Pleasure to meet you.
Even more beautiful than you described.
- Thank you.
- [Man] Shall you girls join us?
- Maybe later, I'm too busy right now.
- [Man] I love this place.
- Take a look at this.
- Where did you get this?
- It's mine.
My grandmother left it to me in her will.
- Her grandmother was a
famous model who disappeared.
- [Man] Do you want to sell it?
- But of course.
She would like to have it restored
and full of people as soon as possible.
Don't you?
- Do you?
- Yes, my soul depends upon it.
(soft instrumental music)
(lively piano music)