( distant wolf howls )
♪ ( jaunty-creepy music ) ♪
AAHHH!
( savage snarling )
WHO DARES DISTURB ME?
WHAT DO YOU THINK YOU'RE
DOING, COMING IN HERE?
NOBODY LEAVES HERE
UNTIL I TELL THEM TO GO
BECAUSE I REALLY,
REALLY LIKE COMPANY HERE
IN THE SHADOW ZONE.
THE SHADOW ZONE
CAN EXIST ANYWHERE--
IN YOUR NEIGHBORHOOD,
AT YOUR SCHOOL,
EVEN IN YOUR OWN BEDROOM.
IT'S WHERE YOUR WORLD
MEETS MINE,
WHERE THE EVERYDAY WORLD
MEETS THE THINGS
THAT LIVE IN THEIR
WORST NIGHTMARES.
THERE'S ONLY ONE REQUIREMENT
TO ENTER THE SHADOW ZONE--
A TOUCH OF EVIL.
THAT'S ALL IT TAKES.
IT'S AS EASY AS STEALING,
AS SIMPLE AS CHEATING,
AS MERE AS A LIE.
LIKE ZACHARY HERE--
HE DOESN'T UNDERSTAND
THAT LYING CAN GET YOU
INTO TROUBLE...
AND INTO THE SHADOW ZONE.
( police siren wails )
OH, GREAT.
GUESS THAT'S GAME.
FOLLOW ME.
GREAT AGAIN.
I'M NOT GOING IN THERE.
I SAY WE JUST FORGET
ABOUT THE BALL.
AND I SAY...
ZACH, I DON'T LIKE THIS.
CAN WE GET OUTTA HERE?
WHAT? IS SOMETHING GONNA
COME AND STAB YOU OUT OF
THE SHADOWS?
AAAHH! ZACH, HELP ME!
ZACH, HELP ME!
ZACH! ZACH, HELP ME!
ZACH! ZACH! ZACH!
ZACH! ZACH! ZACH, HELP ME!
AND WHAT'D YOU DO THEN?
I GOT LOOSE FROM THE ARM
AND I... PULLED GABE
AWAY FROM THE THING AND...
I THREW IT INTO THE QUICKSAND,
AND J.T. USED IT
TO CLIMB OUT.
TO CLIMB OUT?
YEAH, TO CLIMB OUT.
( faint chuckle )
I SEE HERE THAT YOUR MOTHER
IS AN EXECUTIVE WITH
AN ACCOUNTING FIRM
AND YOUR FATHER IS AN ARTIST.
YEAH.
AND THEY RECENTLY
GOT DIVORCED.
YEAH.
ACCORDING TO YOUR TEACHER,
YOU HAVE TYPICALLY
A RATHER, UH, LET'S SAY,
IMAGINATIVE APPROACH
TO THE TRUTH.
IT SEEMS LIKE THE TRAUMA
OF THE DIVORCE MIGHT HAVE
TRIGGERED SOME COMPENSATORY
DENIAL AND INAPPROPRIATE
ACTING-OUT BEHAVIOR.
HOW ARE THINGS GOING AT SCHOOL?
SCHOOL? FINE, YOU KNOW.
SCHOOL. HEY. IT'S GREAT.
WHY DON'T YOU TELL ME
ABOUT YOUR FRIENDS-- GABE, J.T.
GABE AND J.T.?
YOU TOLD HIM ABOUT US?
I TOLD HIM YOU WERE
DYSLEXIC.
WHY?
BECAUSE YOU ARE.
WHAT'D YOU TELL HIM ABOUT ME?
I TOLD HIM YOU WERE
A COMPUTER... GUY,
THAT, UM, YOUR REAL NAME
WAS JEREMIAH ANTAEUS.
WHAT?! WHY?!
HE'S A DOCTOR.
HE WON'T TELL ANYBODY.
YEAH, RIGHT.
ZACH, DO YOU WANT TO DO
THE RESEARCH FOR THIS PROJECT
OR WHAT? IT'S DUE NEXT WEEK.
YEAH, RIGHT. SCHOOLWORK
ON A FRIDAY?
WE CAN HIT THE ARCADE.
NO CAN DO, GUYS.
IT'S AN "UP" WEEKEND.
WASN'T LAST WEEKEND
AN "UP" WEEKEND?
WHICH WOULD MAKE THIS
A "DOWN" WEEKEND.
NO, THIS WEEKEND'S
UPTOWN AT MOM'S.
SO MAYBE DOING THE RESEARCH
FOR THE PROJECT ISN'T SUCH
A BAD IDEA.
"UP" WEEKEND AT MOM'S?
BUMMER.
ONE OF HER CLIENTS
GAVE HER NICKS TICKETS.
UM... WE'RE GONNA SIT COURTSIDE.
I MEAN, THEY'RE PLAYING
THE LAKERS, RIGHT? I MEAN,
TH-THOSE PEOPLE ARE GONNA
BRING US FREE DRINKS
AND, UM, HOT DOGS AND STUFF.
COOL.
THEY'RE PLAYING THE BULLS,
ZACH.
WELL, YEAH, WHOEVER.
I MEAN, I GET TO MEET THE TEAM.
OKAY, WELL, I'LL SEE YOU LATER.
♪♪
HEY, HARV! MR. CHAN!
HEY, ZACH, HOW YOU DOING?
GETTING BY.
THE USUAL?
EGG ROLL, WITH THE MUSTARD.
THANKS. I'LL SEE YOU
LATER, HARV.
HEY, ZACH.
HEY, MEL. ANYTHING NEW?
REISSUE OF FREAKS,
CLASSIC BLACK-AND-WHITE
HORROR FLICK, THE ONLY FEATURE
OF ITS KIND.
( scoffs ) SEEN IT.
WITH INTERVIEWS?
WE'VE GOT A COLORIZATION
OF ERASERHEAD.
BEEN THERE, DONE THAT.
DOESN'T WORK.
WHAT TIME IS IT?
"UP" WEEKEND?
DON'T SWEAT IT.
YOU GOT PLENTY OF TIME.
AH, COOL!
BLOOD CURSE OF THE VAMPIRE?
MEL, YOU WEREN'T EVEN
GONNA TELL ME?
I KNEW YOU'D FIND IT.
THEY SAY IT'S OUTSTANDING.
WATCH IT WITH THE LIGHTS ON.
YEAH, RIGHT.
MEL, SEE YOU LATER.
♪♪
COOL.
( distant, unearthly groan )
( eerie clanking sound )
( small animal shrieks )
WATCH IT!
DID YOU SEE THAT?
IT'S A RAT, KID.
WELCOME TO THE BIG CITY.
CLEAR THE DOORS.
SO, HOW'S DR. GOMES?
( sighs ) YOU KNOW.
YOU KNOW, I WAS TALKING
TO AN ACCOUNTANT YESTERDAY.
SHE SAID HER WHOLE FAMILY'S
IN THERAPY.
IT'S-- IT'S NO BIG DEAL ANYMORE.
IT'S JUST... HOW PEOPLE
EXPRESS THEIR FEELINGS.
( telephone rings )
HELLO.
WHAT?
NO, THE SUTTON ACCOUNT
IS IN THE CENTER DRAWER,
EXACTLY WHERE I LEFT IT.
NO, I CAN'T JUST
DROP EVERYTHING--
I'm sorry, honey,
it's corporate accounts.
YEAH, THAT'S WHY YOU GET PAID
THE BIG BUCKS.
UH, LOOK, I REALLY
AM NOT GONNA JUST...
JUST LET ME TALK TO DEE.
DEE, I CANNOT KEEP BABYSITTING
THESE GUYS...
HONEY, I'M REALLY SORRY.
YOU'RE GOING OUT?
I KNOW I PROMISED YOU,
AND I'M GONNA MAKE IT UP TO YOU.
I DON'T KNOW-- I'LL--
I'LL GET SOME--
SOME TICKETS OR SOMETHING.
YOU LIKE BASKETBALL.
NO, IT'S OKAY.
I'VE CALLED MARIO'S.
THEY'RE GONNA SEND UP PIZZA.
I'M SORRY, HONEY.
NO, I'LL JUST WATCH
A LITTLE T.V.
OKAY, 'BYE.
( woman screaming
on television )
( snickers ) LIKE HE'D
REALLY GO IN THERE.
( traffic sounds )
WE GOT EGGS, WE GOT BACON,
WE'VE GOT TOAST,
WE'VE GOT GRAPEFRUIT.
( kisses Zach )
UH... ZACH, I GOT SOME BAD NEWS.
( sighs ) YOU GOTTA GO
BACK TO WORK, RIGHT?
YEAH, ONE OF MY CLIENTS
IS MERGING WITH TWO OTHER
COMPANIES, AND THE LAWYERS
WANT A REVISED FINANCIAL
STATEMENT BY MONDAY, AND...
HEY, IT'S COOL.
WELL, I-I DIDN'T WANT
TO WAKE YOU. I WANTED TO
LET YOU SLEEP AS LATE
AS YOU COULD, BUT, UM... IT'S
ALMOST NOON, AND I GOTTA GO.
IT'S ALL RIGHT. I UNDERSTAND.
UH... TAKE A CAB.
IT'S, UH...
HERE WE GO.
LIKE USUAL.
YEAH, JUST A DAY EARLIER,
RIGHT?
( sighs )
DON'T WORRY.
YOU'RE STILL THE BEST MOM I GOT.
( faint chuckle )
Okay. Bye-bye.
GOOD MORNING, SIR.
OOPS!
( indistinct chatter )
TAKE IT EASY, BOB.
NICE DAY.
IT'S COOL.
I'M GONNA TAKE THE SUBWAY.
EXCUSE ME.
I-I DIDN'T MEAN TO SCARE YOU.
I'M SORRY.
UM, DO YOU KNOW WHERE
THE NUMBER 6 LINE IS?
DOES IT STOP DOWN THIS WAY?
NUMBER 6?
OH, THE NUMBER 6!
YEAH, YEAH, I CAN SHOW YOU.
I'D BE HAPPY TO. MY PLEASURE.
IT'S, UH, IT'S... THIS WAY.
COME WITH ME.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO SHOW ME.
( screaming )
( stammering ) ...WHO...?
VALENTINE CUTTER,
AT YOUR SERVICE, SIR.
W-WHAT HAPPENED?
WHEN?
THAT GUY?
W-WHAT WAS HE DOING?
WHAT DO YOU THINK
HE WAS DOING?
HIS FACE... WAS A...
A SKULL.
I KNOW YOU.
YOU THREW THAT RAT AT ME.
ARE YOU SURE IT WAS A RAT?
IT WAS A RAT.
YOU LOOKED AT IT CAREFULLY?
WELL, NO...
WELL, IT COULD HAVE BEEN
SOMETHING ELSE.
IT LOOKED LIKE A RAT.
PERHAPS IT WAS AN ILLUSION.
THINGS ARE NOT ALWAYS
AS THEY SEEM, YOUNG MAN.
I GET IT.
YOU'RE DOING A MOVIE, RIGHT?
IS IT RICK BAKER?
GREAT MAKEUP AND EFFECTS.
DON'T LET HIM GO!
I WON'T TELL! COME ON!
IT'S RICK BAKER, ISN'T IT?
OR IS IT CLIVE BARKER?
DWAYNE WANTS TO APOLOGIZE
FOR SCARING YOU,
DON'T YOU, DWAYNE?
I'M SORRY.
NO, THAT'S OKAY.
UH, I WAS JUST LOOKING FOR
THE NUMBER 6 LINE.
MAY I SUGGEST YOU FOLLOW ME.
GABE AND J.T.
AREN'T GONNA BELIEVE THIS!
THAT'S YOUR TRAIN, I BELIEVE.
ARE YOU CATCHING THIS ONE?
NO, MY, UH...
MY FRIEND AND I WILL WAIT.
OH.
BON VOYAGE.
WELL... THANKS ANYWAY. UH...
WHAT? H-HOW DID YOU--?
I SAW YOU BACK THERE
ON THE PLATFORM WHEN...
IT WAS YOUR STUNT DOUBLE.
IS THAT IT?
IS THIS TRAIN HEADING DOWNTOWN?
I BELIEVE SO.
DOES IT STOP AT CANAL STREET?
NOT ANYMORE.
WHAT DID HE SAY?
HE ASKED IF IT STOPPED
AT CANAL STREET.
( laughter )
WHAT? IT GOES TO BROOKLYN?
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
TH-THIS IS A MOVIE SHOOT,
RIGHT, AND YOU GOTTA
WEAR COSTUMES AND STUFF,
AND, UH...
O-OR YOU GET TO PICK A DOOR
TO A T.V. SHOW, RIGHT?
T.V. SHOW?
I TOLD YOU, MAN,
IT'S LIKE ALL JUNK, YOU KNOW?
EXCEPT GILLIGAN'S ISLAND.
THAT'S A TRIP.
OH, YES.
THE LITTLE BOX WITH PICTURES.
VERY FUNNY.
UH... THIS SOUNDS WEIRD,
BUT THIS KIND OF LOOKS LIKE
A GHOST TRAIN,
WITH GHOSTS.
( Valentine chuckles )
THAT'S VERY CLOSE.
BUT NOT QUITE RIGHT.
NOT DEAD PEOPLE.
NOT DEAD AT ALL.
WELL, GOOD.
GLAD TO HEAR IT.
UNDEAD.
WHAT?
ZACHARY, HAVE YOU NEVER
HEARD OF NOSFERATU?
YEAH, YEAH, HE'S
IN THAT MOVIE--
BLACK AND WHITE, 1920s.
HOW'D YOU KNOW MY NAME?
YOU'D BE AMAZED
AT WHAT I KNOW.
AND NOSFERATU ISN'T A "HE,"
IT'S A "THEM."
VAMPIRES.
REAL VAMPIRES.
WELCOME ABOARD
THE UNDEAD EXPRESS.
( laughter )
AAH!
( vampires clamoring )
( savage growl )
HE IS MINE!
YOU NEED NOT WORRY,
MY FRIEND.
YOU ARE UNDER MY PROTECTION.
WHY SHOULD THEY LISTEN
TO YOU?
BECAUSE I AM THE FIRST.
WITHOUT ME, THEY WOULD NOT
KNOW THE PLEASURES OF OUR WORLD.
HOW'D YOU GET HERE?
( faint chuckle )
HOW DID I GET DOWN HERE?
I WAS RICH, ONCE.
THESE TUNNELS...
THIS, UH, CAR...
I OWNED IT ALL.
THE SUBWAY?
GET OUTTA HERE!
GET OUT OF WHERE?
OH, THE VERNACULAR, YES.
I, UH...
NO, I, UH, BUILT ALL THIS.
IT WAS 1905.
I LIVED ON FIFTH AVENUE,
IN A LARGE TOWNHOUSE.
♪ ( chamber music plays ) ♪
I HAD BUILT RAILROADS
ALL OVER THE WORLD,
SO WHEN THEY PROPOSED
AN UNDERGROUND RAILWAY
HERE IN NEW YORK,
I WAS ONE OF THE FIRST
TO SUPPORT IT,
RAISE MONEY,
INVEST IN IT.
AND I BECAME FAR WEALTHIER
THAN I HAD EVER IMAGINED
I WOULD BE.
I COULD PROVIDE FOR MY WIFE
AND MY SON, AND...
MY SON, JOHN.
( crowd reacts happily )
( applause )
I WAS THE PROUDEST MAN
IN NEW YORK, ZACHARY,
AND THERE WERE VERY MANY
PROUD MEN HERE.
IT WAS THE GREATEST NIGHT
OF MY LIFE.
WE WERE GOING TO THE OPERA...
BUT THE SHADOW ZONE BECKONED.
HIS NAME WAS BARNABAS.
HE WAS MORE THAN
A THOUSAND YEARS OLD
AND HAD WALKED
THE WORLD
FOR FIFTY GENERATIONS,
SEEN SO MUCH,
KNOWN SO MANY GREAT MINDS.
( man groaning )
THAT EVENING...
THAT EVENING WAS THE LAST TIME
I SAW MY SON.
WELL, WHICH ONE'S BARNABAS?
HE IS NO MORE.
HE WASN'T, UH...
CONTENT WITH LIFE
HERE UNDER THE STREETS.
HE SOUGHT ESCAPE
INTO THE LIGHT OF DAY.
I WASN'T QUICK ENOUGH
TO SAVE HIM, AND...
WELL, YOU SAW WHAT
HAPPENED TO DWAYNE.
YEAH. UNFORTUNATELY.
WELL, YOU SEE,
DWAYNE WASN'T IN THE LIGHT
LONG ENOUGH FOR THE EFFECTS
TO BE PERMANENT,
BUT THERE ARE OTHERS
WHO WEREN'T SO LUCKY.
YOU MEAN WHAT HAPPENED
TO DWAYNE HAPPENED TO THEM?
WELL, IT...
HELPS EASE THE OVERCROWDING.
THAT'S ONE WAY TO LOOK AT IT.
ZACHARY, THEY WERE FOOLS.
WHY RISK LOSING THE POWER,
THE MYSTERY, THE NIGHT?
BLOOD.
BLOOD IS OUR FOOD, OUR DRINK.
AND IMMORTALITY
IS OUR PRIZE.
IT'S A WONDERFUL LIFE.
A RAT!
THERE'S A RAT!
( vampires clamoring )
LADIES FIRST! HA HA!
LEMME HAVE IT!
I'LL PAY YOU TWICE
WHAT YOU WERE OFFERED!
( vampires moaning )
YOU NEEDN'T WORRY, MY FRIEND.
I TOLD YOU-- I'M PROTECTING YOU.
THANKS.
CAN I-- WHERE CAN I GET OFF AT?
THIS CAR RUNS ON
VERY OLD TRACKS.
NO ONE EVEN REMEMBERS
THEY'RE HERE.
SO, HOW DO YOU GET FRESH--?
OH, PEOPLE GET LOST.
THAT CORRIDOR
WHERE YOU MET DWAYNE
HAS PROVED TO BE VERY FRUITFUL.
SO THEY GET LOST, AND YOU...?
ME? NO, NO.
I, UH, I MUCH PREFER RATS.
PEOPLE ARE TOO, UH... RICH.
I'M SORT OF
A "VAMPIRE VEGETARIAN."
BUT, UH...?
OH, THEM?
OH, THEY... THEY MUCH PREFER
HUMAN BLOOD.
WHY ARE YOU--
I MEAN, PROTECTING ME
FROM THEM?
I WANT TO GET OUT OF HERE.
I HAVE TO KNOW WHETHER
IT'S DAY OR NIGHT,
AND I CAN'T GO
UNLESS AN INNOCENT
LEADS ME OUT.
AND YOU, MY FRIEND,
ARE GOING TO BE THAT PERSON.
( vampires moaning )
NO! NO!
CONDEMNED BY HIS OWN MOUTH!
( vampires clamoring )
( bell dings )
AAAHHH!
( brakes screech )
( vampires clamoring )
( indistinct comments )
( vagrants coughing )
DAD!
( faint chuckle )
YOU SCARED ME.
YOU SCARED THE HELL
OUTTA ME TOO! WHAT'S UP?
YOU'RE NOT SUPPOSED TO BE HERE
TILL TOMORROW. YOU ALL RIGHT?
Y-YEAH. I WAS ON THE SUBWAY.
YOU WOULDN'T BELIEVE
THE RIDE I HAD.
SUBWAY?
AT THIS TIME OF NIGHT?
YEAH. THERE WAS THIS GUY.
GUY? WHAT DID HE DO?
DID HE TOUCH YOU?
WHAT HAPPENED TO YOUR HAND?
I-I CUT IT. IT'S FINE.
NO, DAD, HE WAS A VAMPIRE.
HE HAD THE TEETH AND THE CAPE.
VAMPIRE?
YEAH, THEY WERE ALL VAMPIRES,
THE WHOLE CAR.
THEY KEEP GOING ROUND
AND ROUND UNDER THE CITY.
DID YOU RENT ONE OF
THOSE HORROR MOVIES?
MY BACKPACK.
I LEFT MY BACKPACK
ON THE SUBWAY.
ZACH, DO YOU KNOW
WHAT THAT COST?
DAD, I-I'M SORRY.
I DIDN'T MEAN TO FORGET IT.
IT'S JUST... LISTEN, I'M TRYING
TO EXPLAIN SOMETHING TO YOU.
I'VE TRIED TO TELL YOU
A MILLION TIMES-- YOU GET ON
THE CAR THAT HAS
THE CONDUCTOR IN IT.
SOMEBODY BOTHERS YOU,
YOU TELL HIM. HE'S THERE
TO PROTECT KIDS.
I'M TRYING TO TELL YOU
SOMETHING! I'M NOT A KID!
THERE ONLY WAS ONE CAR!
AND THE CONDUCTOR,
HE WAS ONE OF THEM-- THE UNDEAD.
DON'T START, ZACH.
THERE ISN'T A TRAIN ON THE WHOLE
NEW YORK SUBWAY SYSTEM
THAT HAS ONE CAR.
HEY, STAY RIGHT HERE--
THIS ISN'T OVER YET!
( telephone rings )
HELLO?
YEAH, HE JUST GOT IN.
HE MET SOME WEIRDO
ON THE SUBWAY.
CAB?
WHAT, YOU MOVE UPTOWN,
YOU'RE TOO GOOD FOR
PUBLIC TRANSPORTATION?
NO, THAT WASN'T A CRACK.
LOOK, WHEN ZACH HAS
AN "UP" WEEKEND,
YOU ARE RESPONSIBLE.
HE'S NOT SUPPOSED TO BE HERE
A DAY EARLY.
YEAH, AND ANOTHER THING--
WHAT'S THIS THING
WITH THE, UH, THE VAMPIRES.
HE KEEPS WATCHING THOSE MOVIES.
WHAT'D I TELL YOU--?
YEAH. RIGHT. WE'LL TALK
ABOUT IT LATER, AS USUAL.
'BYE.
AND THEN HE TOOK THE RAT
AND BIT IT RIGHT IN HALF...
( makes slurping noise )
AND STARTED SUCKING THE BLOOD.
IT WAS REALLY COOL.
( Gabe sighs )
WHAT? NO, COME ON, TELL ME.
LOOK, ZACH, WE KNOW
THAT YOU EXAGGERATE THINGS.
EXAGGERATE?
WE KNOW YOU'RE STILL SHOOK UP
BECAUSE YOUR MOM AND DAD
BROKE UP. I MEAN, THAT'S
WHAT THEY SAY ON ALL
THE TALK SHOWS.
WE KNOW THAT YOU HAVE A LOUSY
TIME WHEN YOU GO TO YOUR MOM'S,
AND WE DON'T MIND THAT YOU LIE
TO US ABOUT IT.
ALL RIGHT. MAYBE I DO...
EXAGGERATE ABOUT THINGS. BUT...
YOU LIE LIKE A RUG.
( school bell rings )
THIS IS DIFFERENT!
I SWEAR, IT REALLY HAPPENED!
I GOT IN THE SUBWAY,
AND THEY WERE ALL VAMPIRES!
DID YOU DO THE RESEARCH?
YOU DIDN'T, DID YOU?
ZACH, I THOUGHT YOU SAID
YOUR MOM HAD THE BOOKS!
I HAD MY CAMERA READY
AND EVERYTHING!
IF I FAIL HISTORY
BECAUSE YOU WENT OFF TO GO--
NO, NO! I GOT AN IDEA.
HISTORY OF NEW YORK, RIGHT?
WHAT'S MORE NEW YORK
THAN THE SUBWAYS?
WE CAN DO OUR PROJECTS
IN THE OLD SUBWAYS
UNDER THE CITY.
COME ON, ZACH.
NO, NO. THE OLD CITY HALL
STATION, I KNOW WHERE IT IS,
AND I KNOW HOW TO GET IN TOO.
Y-YOU COULD TAKE PICTURES.
IT'S UTTERLY COOL.
YOU GOTTA SEE IT.
I'LL EVEN DO THE WRITE-UP.
THAT DOES SOUND COOL.
YOU REALLY KNOW
HOW TO GET IN?
I SWEAR.
HERE?
YEAH. IT'S THE ONLY WAY IN
I KNOW.
HOLY COW.
NICE PLACE YOU'VE GOT HERE,
ZACH. I LOVE WHAT YOU'VE
DONE WITH IT.
AMBER AND I ARE DOING OUR
PROJECT ON THE HISTORY OF
SANITATION WORKERS.
IT STINKS.
( camera flash whirrs )
SHH.
( distant clanking sound )
WHAT, ZACH, ARE WE LISTENING
FOR THE CHILDREN OF THE NIGHT?
OR THE PITTER-PATTER
OF LITTLE WINGS?
YOU KNOW, I WASN'T LYING.
YOU KNOW, FRIENDS SHOULD
BELIEVE FRIENDS.
WEIRDOS, I BUY.
WHO WOULDN'T?
BUT VAMPIRES?
COME ON, GIVE ME A BREAK.
YOU WAIT. I MEAN,
I'LL BET THEY'RE AROUND HERE
RIGHT NOW. YOU KNOW,
ALL THEY DO IS RIDE AROUND
UNDER NEW YORK
ON THE FORGOTTEN TRACKS.
AAH!
I FORGOT! I WAS SUPPOSED
TO MEET AMBER AFTER SCHOOL!
AW, SHE'S GONNA KILL ME.
YEAH, AND I'VE GOT
TO BABYSIT.
UM, YOU COMING?
NO. I THINK I'M JUST
GONNA WAIT AND TAKE SOME
PICTURES OF THE VAMPIRES
'CAUSE IF YOU WON'T BELIEVE ME,
MAYBE YOU'LL BELIEVE
YOUR OWN EYES.
IT'S UP TO YOU.
YOU KNOW HOW MY MOM GETS.
MAYBE I WON'T EVEN SHOW YOU
THE PICTURES! MAYBE I'LL SELL
'EM TO THE NATIONAL ENQUIRER
AND MAKE A BUNCH OF DOUGH.
YOU'LL HAVE TO PAY TO SEE 'EM,
LIKE EVERYBODY ELSE.
YEAH, THAT'S WHAT I'M GONNA DO.
YOU KNOW, I'M NOT AFRAID
TO BE DOWN HERE BY MYSELF.
DOESN'T SCARE ME.
NOPE, NOT ONE BIT.
( scoffs ) WHO'S SCARED, ME?
YEAH.
PRETTY FUNNY, HUH?
ZACH TRYING TO CONVINCE US
WE SAW VAMPIRES?
YEAH, HE USUALLY DOESN'T
CARRY HIS STORIES
ON FOR SO LONG.
THERE'S NO SUCH THING
AS VAMPIRES, RIGHT?
HEY, I SHOULD KNOW?
SO THERE COULD BE.
I'M NOT THE ONE TO ASK.
MAYBE THERE'S SOMETHING
ON THE 'NET.
( eerie scraping sound )
( small wings fluttering )
WHAT AM I DOING HERE?
AAH! AAAHHH!
GEEZ, HARV, YOU SCARED ME.
MAKES US EVEN.
HEY... WHAT'S UP?
YOU LOOK LIKE YOU'VE
SEEN A GHOST.
NO, A VAMPIRE.
WHAT?!
FORGET IT.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING DOWN HERE?
HEY... IT DON'T RAIN.
THERE'S NO COPS.
AND IT'S... IT'S REAL QUIET.
LISTEN, ZACH,
UM, I'M A LITTLE SHORT
RIGHT NOW, YOU KNOW?
DO YOU THINK YOU COULD...?
WHAT?
YEAH, SURE.
LET ME SEE WHAT I GOT.
THANKS, ZACH.
THIS IS JUST UNTIL
MR. CHAN PAYS ME
FOR SWEEPING UP.
NOW, YOU BE CAREFUL DOWN HERE.
I'LL SEE YOU, LITTLE PAL.
GREAT. ALL I NEED
IS TO BREAK GABE'S CAMERA.
THAT'S ALL I GOT, HARV.
CATCH ME TOMORROW.
BUT I'VE ALREADY
CAUGHT YOU...
TODAY!
( eerie fluttering )
COME ON!
STAY STILL!
YOURS, I BELIEVE.
AND MINE.
GO FIND A RAT.
I WANT HUMAN BLOOD!
YOU ARE HOLDING ME BACK!
I COMMAND YOU.
( low snarl )
HE WAS... I WAS DINNER.
( Valentine clicks heel )
MM-HMM.
ZACH, I'M HURT.
I TOLD YOU I'D PROTECT YOU.
I REMEMBER.
I JUST... DON'T BELIEVE IT.
MM-HMM.
I THINK THIS IS YOURS.
EVERYTHING THERE?
YEAH. THANKS.
NOW, WHY DON'T YOU
BELIEVE ME?
YOU'RE A VAMPIRE.
WHY SHOULD I BELIEVE YOU?
THAT'S A GOOD POINT.
HMM.
THAT'S THE FIRST RULE:
TRUST NO ONE,
NOT EVEN YOUR CLOSEST FRIENDS.
WELL, NO.
I TRUST GABE AND J.T.
I'VE KNOWN THEM FOREVER.
MMM.
WELL, FOREVER'S
A LONG TIME, ZACH.
DO THEY TRUST YOU?
OF COURSE!
WELL... I TOLD 'EM
ABOUT YOU, AND...
THEY DIDN'T BELIEVE ME.
BUT, WHAT? I MEAN,
YOU ARE PRETTY UNBELIEVABLE.
A FRIEND... WOULD BELIEVE...
NO MATTER WHAT.
VALENTINE, WAIT...
ME AND MY FRIEND GABE
ARE DOING A PROJECT
IN HISTORY TOGETHER.
UM... IT'S ABOUT THE--
THE OLD SUBWAY.
ACTUALLY, YOU GAVE ME THE IDEA.
I DID?
OH. I'M DELIGHTED.
PERHAPS I CAN HELP.
WELL, SURE, YEAH.
UM... I'M DOING THE RESEARCH
RIGHT NOW. SEE, I DO
THE WRITE-UP,
AND GABE TAKES THE PICTURES.
MM.
YOU SAY YOUR FRIEND...
GABE... TAKES A FEW PICTURES,
AND YOU HAVE TO DO
ALL THE WRITING?
DOESN'T SOUND FAIR.
WELL, SHE DEVELOPS THEM TOO.
SHE'S DYSLEXIC.
AH. FROM ANOTHER COUNTRY,
IS SHE?
NO, NO. UM...
IT MEANS SHE HAS TROUBLE
WITH READING AND WRITING.
I SEE.
WELL, IT'S FORTUNATE
SHE HAS A FRIEND SHE CAN
TAKE ADVANTAGE OF.
IT'S NOT LIKE THAT. SHE...
I HAVE A SPLENDID IDEA.
WOULD YOU LIKE TO SEE
OTHER ABANDONED STATIONS?
THERE'S MORE?
OH, YES, MANY MORE.
AND I CAN GET TO THEM.
WELL, COOL. I MEAN,
CAN GABE COME TOO?
SHE HAS TO TAKE THE PICTURES.
NO.
NO, NO, NO.
NO. ONLY YOU, ZACHARY.
I TRUST ONLY YOU.
( sighs ) WELL, I MEAN...
I DON'T KNOW... I DON'T THINK
MY DAD WOULD LET ME.
OH, ZACHARY.
LESSON NUMBER TWO:
YOU SHOULD NEVER,
NEVER HAVE TO GET PERMISSION
TO LIVE.
WELL, I HAVE TO GET GOING.
MY TRAINMATES MUST BE WANDERING.
IF YOU WANT THE TOUR,
I'LL MEET YOU HERE TOMORROW.
WHAT? WAIT-- WHAT TIME?
OH, I'LL KNOW WHEN
TO COME TO YOU.
WHATEVER YOU SAY.
( snarling growl )
I DIDN'T MEAN...
I WAS, UH...
JUST SURPRISED, THAT'S ALL.
I'M SORRY.
I MEAN, I SHOULD HAVE ASKED.
VALENTINE?
( small wings fluttering )
( small creatures
chittering )
BOO!
MESSED UP!
REALLY MATURE, ZACH.
NOTHING.
WELL, I'M CONVINCED.
WELL, I KNOW I TOOK
THE PICTURE OF HIM.
I ALREADY GOT A SHOT OF
THE SIGN, AND A BETTER ONE TOO.
THAT PROVES IT.
HE'S NOT IN THE PICTURE.
WHAT?
IT PROVES THAT HE'S
A VAMPIRE. I AIMED THE CAMERA
RIGHT AT HIM, LIKE THIS,
AND HE WASN'T IN THE PICTURE.
THEY DON'T SHOW UP ON FILM.
THAT PROVES IT.
AND IT'S OUT OF FOCUS.
I KNOW IT'S OUT OF FOCUS.
I MEAN, IT'S NOT LIKE I HAD
ALL THE TIME IN THE WORLD.
I MEAN, HE WAS LEAVING--
I HAD TO TAKE IT.
YOU KNOW, YOU'RE NOT THE ONLY
ONE WHO KNOWS HOW TO TAKE
PICTURES.
LET'S TALK ABOUT THIS
OUTSIDE.
HE WAS THERE.
ZACH, GIVE IT A REST.
I MEAN, I TOOK HIS PICTURE.
I HAD A CONVERSATION WITH HIM.
A VAMPIRE?   YEAH.
LOOK, ZACH, EVERY SO OFTEN,
YOUR LIES ARE FUN, OKAY?
BUT THIS ONE ISN'T.
( scoffs ) LIES?
YES, LIKE ABOUT MEETING
SOME CELEBRITY, OR GETTING
TICKETS TO A SOLD-OUT GAME,
OR GOING ON A SAFARI TO AFRICA
WITH YOUR MOTHER.
SHE IS!
ZACH, SHE CALLED MY MOM.
SHE WANTS TO TAKE YOU
TO SAFARI WORLD IN FLORIDA.
SHE ASKED IF I COULD GO!
SHE ASKED IF YOU COULD GO?
ALL RIGHT, SO MAYBE SOMETIMES
I EXAGGERATE A LITTLE,
BUT THIS IS FOR REAL.
I'D LIKE TO SEE SAFARI WORLD.
LOOK, ZACH, YOU MET SOME GUY
AND HE TRIED TO SCARE YOU.
THAT I'LL BUY, OKAY?
BUT YOU HAVE TO GO
AND BLOW IT UP INTO SOMETHING
BIGGER AND BETTER THAN
IT REALLY IS. MEANWHILE,
WE HAVE A HISTORY PROJECT
DUE NEXT WEEK, AND YOU HAVEN'T
EVEN DONE ANYTHING YET.
THE SUBWAY WAS MY IDEA!
SO WHAT?
MY MOM WOULD LET ME GO.
LOOK, ZACH, IT WAS A GOOD
IDEA, OKAY, BUT YOU'VE GOT
TO FOLLOW THROUGH.
I SPENT TWO HOURS IN THE LIBRARY
THIS AFTERNOON DOING RESEARCH
AND KEEPING MY BROTHER QUIET,
AND YOU WERE IN SOME ABANDONED
SUBWAY STATION TALKING
TO SOME GEEK.
ZACH, MAYBE IF YOUR MOM
CALLED MY MOM--
Both: SHUT UP!
LOOK, I TOOK THE PICTURE!
ONE PICTURE, AND IT'S
OUT OF FOCUS!
YOU'VE GOT A LOT OF NERVE.
ALL YOU HAVE TO DO
IS TAKE PICTURES.
I'VE GOT THE HARD PART.
JUST BECAUSE YOU CAN'T WRITE...!
I didn't know you felt
that way.
WELL... WELL, I DO.
WELL, THEN, MAYBE WE
SHOULDN'T BE PARTNERS, THEN.
WELL, MAYBE YOU'RE RIGHT.
FINE, FINE.
FINE.
HERE!
AND THESE ARE IN FOCUS!
I DON'T NEED ANYTHING
FROM YOU.
AND I NEED EVEN LESS
I KNEW YOU'D COME.
YEAH. WELL, I FOUND OUT
WHO MY FRIENDS REALLY ARE.
YOU'RE LEARNING.
ZACHARY, THE SECRET OF LIFE
IS TO ACT.
FOLLOW YOUR OWN BLOOD.
TRUST YOURSELF.
DID YOU BRING YOUR CAMERA?
THAT'S EXCELLENT.
LET US BEGIN.
THIS WAS ALL MINE.
MY OFFICE USED TO BE
UP THOSE STAIRS.
THE BUILDING'S GONE, NOW.
I HEARD THEM TEARING IT DOWN.
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
THIS IS JUST FOR YOU.
IF PEOPLE WERE TO SEE PICTURES
OF THIS PLACE, THEY WOULD
COME LOOKING FOR IT.
I WANT IT TO REMAIN AS IT IS...
FOREVER.
PERFECT.
BEAUTIFUL.
YEAH, THAT'S OKAY.
I'VE GOT ENOUGH ALREADY.
WOULD YOU CARE TO JOIN ME?
AWESOME!
BUT WAS IT "COOL"?
TOTALLY, OFF THE SCALE.
LISTEN.
( distant indistinct sounds )
BATS?
PEOPLE.
ABOVE US.
I HEAR THEM WALKING...
ENJOYING THE CITY...
LIVING.
Man: WELCOME HOME!
EVERY DAY...
EVERY NIGHT.
I CAN FEEL THEM.
Listen, Zachary.
Can you hear the beating
of their hearts?
No, but I'll take
your word for it.
( distant siren wails )
I want to walk there...
among them...
Zachary, is it night?
Yeah.
Take me up there.
UH... THAT'S NEW YORK,
AND YOU'RE A VAMPIRE.
I DON'T THINK YOU GUYS
ARE READY FOR EACH OTHER.
WE HAVE A PROBLEM.
WHAT?
WE MADE A BARGAIN.
I SHOWED YOU MY WORLD,
NOW I WANT YOU TO SHOW ME YOURS.
I NEVER SAID ANYTHING
ABOUT TAKING YOU OUT OF HERE.
BUT YOU TOOK WHAT I OFFERED.
NOW... YOU MUST REPAY.
ZACHARY, I PROMISE YOU,
I WON'T HURT ANYBODY.
I DON'T WANT TO HUNT.
I just want to see...
the stars. Please.
SURE.
COME ON, IT'S JUST UP AHEAD.
AND OUT THERE IS, UH...
NEW YORK. COME ON.
( sirens wail )
AHH!
THE LIGHT IS SO SWEET!
YEAH, MAYBE FOR A GUY
WHO EATS RATS!
THANK YOU FOR
LEADING ME OUT.
COME ON.
( indistinct comments )
( laughter )
HEY, KID, YOU WANNA BUY
A WATCH?
( clocks ringing )
WHAT'S WITH THE TIMES?
HEY! HEY, WHAT'S GOING ON?
WHAT THE...?
WHAT-- WHAT--
WHAT'D YOU DO TO MY WATCHES?
THANK YOU, FRIEND ZACHARY.
THANK YOU, FRIEND VALENTINE.
WHOA. VALENTINE. LOOK.
SIMS. HE'S GONE
FROM THE TUNNELS.
HE MUST HAVE FOLLOWED US
OUT THE DOOR.
WE HAVE TO FIND HIM.
HE'S HUNGRY.
WELL, WHICH WAY?
I DON'T KNOW.
THIS WAY.
SO, WHERE DO WE LOOK?
THE CEMETERY.
A PLACE WHERE THERE ARE CRYPTS.
WELL... THERE'S
TRINITY CHURCH.
IT'S A COUPLE OF BLOCKS
THAT WAY. LET'S GO.
( distant dog howls )
YOU'RE FAST.
HE MUST BE HERE SOMEWHERE.
WELL, WHAT DO WE DO
WHEN WE FIND HIM?
VALENTINE?
VALENTINE!
WE MEET AGAIN!
( low growl )
LEAVE HIM.
I CAN'T DO THAT!
ALL I'VE EATEN
IS ONE LOUSY DOG...
SO FAR! HA HA HA HA!
( low growl )
I ORDER YOU...
TO RETURN!
NEVER! AAAHHH!
♪♪
LISTEN TO ME--
THE DAWN IS COMING.
WE MUST GO.
LOOK AROUND!
THERE ARE MANY PLACES
FOR US TO REST!
TAKE US HOME, ZACHARY.
PLEASE.
I SAW A BEAUTIFUL AUTOMOBILE.
I COULD HAVE BOUGHT IT,
IF I'D ONLY SOLD SHORT.
I KNOW.
( distant dog barks )
WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN?
WHAT HAPPENED TO YOU?
MOM. HI.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
WHERE WERE YOU ALL NIGHT?
I WAS WALKING AROUND
NEW YORK WITH VALENTINE.
I MET HIM ON THE SUBWAY.
HE'S A VAMPIRE.
YOU WERE WITH SOME WEIRDO
ALL NIGHT?
D-DID HE...?
WHAT HAPPENED TO YOUR HAND?
NOTHING. IT'S ALL RIGHT.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
HE WOULD DO THIS.
I SHOULDN'T HAVE
TO ASK PERMISSION TO LIVE.
I SHOULD BE ABLE
TO FOLLOW MY OWN BLOOD.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
YOU STAY AWAY FROM HIM,
YOU HEAR ME?
THIS IS ALL YOUR FAULT?
OH, REALLY?   YES.
WHO LETS HIM WATCH
THOSE HORROR MOVIES?
NO, WHO INSISTS ON LIVING
IN THE MIDDLE OF CRIMINALS
AND FREAKS AND...!
STOP IT!
VALENTINE IS NOT A FREAK,
HE'S MY FRIEND!
HE SAID THE MOST IMPORTANT
THING IN LIFE IS
TO TRUST NO ONE.
( scoffs ) HE WAS RIGHT.
( Zach walks away )
ZACH.
ZACH, I-I-I'M SORRY
I LOST MY TEMPER.
IT'S JUST THAT, YOU KNOW,
I WAS... WE...
WE'RE WORRIED ABOUT YOU.
IT'S DANGEROUS OUT THERE.
YOU'VE GOT TO REMEMBER THAT.
I KNOW. THERE'S VAMPIRES.
THERE'S THINGS A LOT WORSE
THAN VAMPIRES, ZACH.
WE JUST DON'T WANT
ANYONE TO HURT YOU.
AND REMEMBER THAT
WE BOTH LOVE YOU.
MOM.
HMM?
WHY'D YOU COME OVER HERE?
WELL, BECAUSE DAD CALLED
AND SAID YOU WERE MISSING.
OH.
I THOUGHT YOU TWO WERE...
YOU KNOW...
UM... YOU'D BETTER
GET SOME SLEEP, OKAY, HONEY?
'NIGHT, SPORT.
( excited chatter )
( panicked breathing )
WHAT ARE THESE?
NOTHING!
ARE THOSE THE PICTURES
YOU TOOK? NOTHING CAME OUT.
NO, THESE ARE THE PICTURES
I TOOK. THESE ARE
SOMETHING ELSE.
I'M KIND OF BUSY RIGHT NOW,
ALL RIGHT?
YEAH. OKAY. SURE.
I'LL CATCH YOU LATER.
( scoffs ) WHATEVER.
( background chatter )
ALL RIGHT, SETTLE DOWN,
CLASS.
EXCELLENT WORK, GABRIELLE.
I'M QUITE IMPRESSED.
THANKS.
YOU MUST HAVE SPENT HOURS
IN RESEARCH.
WELL, YEAH.
GREAT, THANK YOU.
THANK YOU.
LET'S HELP YOU OUT HERE.
OH, THANKS.
ALL RIGHT, WHO CAN WE
HEAR FROM?
ZACH KINCAID.
UH, MS. POTASHER,
I'M REALLY NOT READY YET.
YOU'VE KNOWN ABOUT THIS
FOR WEEKS, ZACH.
I-I KNOW. I JUST NEED
ONE MORE DAY.
I'LL TELL YOU WHAT.
YOU CAN WORK ON IT AFTER CLASS,
IN DETENTION.
YES, MS. POTASHER.
VERY WELL.
ELLISON, IS YOUR PROJECT READY?
Zach!
What?
I just wanted to tell you
not to worry.
Worry about what?
I told Gabe
about your pictures.
WHAT?! ( coughing )
I'm okay.
Nice save.
Did she laugh?
Laugh? No.
She said she wanted to help.
Help? Help how?
She went down to the old
City Hall station,
to take new pictures for you.
WHAT?! BUT SHE CAN'T!
I'M GONNA THROW UP!
TUNA BURRITO FOR LUNCH!
TOO MUCH!
( mouthing silently )
I THOUGHT YOU WERE
IN DETENTION!
GABE WENT UNDERGROUND
TO THE OLD STATION?
SHE SAID YOU NEEDED PICTURES.
BUT THERE'S VAMPIRES
DOWN THERE!
ZACH, IS THIS A LIE?
J.T., I'VE KNOWN YOU
MY ENTIRE LIFE,
AND MAYBE I'VE LIED TO YOU
BUT THIS TIME, THIS ONE TIME,
I'M TELLING YOU THE TRUTH.
OKAY. THERE ARE VAMPIRES
IN THE SUBWAY.
YEAH. WELL... I'VE GOT
TO GO DOWN THERE AND GET HER.
JUST COVER FOR ME, ALL RIGHT?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
GABE'S DOWN THERE!
YOU DON'T HAVE TO COME.
IT'S MY FAULT SHE'S DOWN THERE.
WHAT ARE FRIENDS FOR?
IF THERE REALLY ARE VAMPIRES,
THAT EXPLAINS A LOT.
WHAT?
I CHECKED OUT THE 'NET.
PEOPLE ALL OVER HAVE SEEN 'EM
AND BELIEVE IN 'EM, SO,
YOU KNOW, MAYBE THERE'S SOME
TRUTH TO WHAT YOU SAY.
BUT, ANYWAY,
ON ONE OF THEIR PAGES,
IT SAID IF A VAMPIRE TASTES
YOUR BLOOD, THEY'RE, LIKE,
IN YOU,
AND YOU DO VAMPIRE THINGS
AND WANT VAMPIRE THINGS.
AND YOU KNOW YOU SAID--
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
BUT WHAT DID IT SAY ABOUT LIGHT?
DID IT SAY ANYTHING
ABOUT WHY IT BURNS 'EM?
IT'S THE ULTRAVIOLET,
THE U.V.
IT'S LIKE A TANNING BOOTH.
ALL FLUORESCENTS
HAVE A LOT OF IT, AND SUNLIGHT.
BUT NOT REGULAR LIGHT BULBS?
NOPE. DON'T HURT 'EM.
LET'S GO.
YOU SEE ANYTHING?
NAH. YOU?
NAH.
REMEMBER,
VALENTINE WILL PROTECT US,
BUT THE OTHERS...
WE SEE THE OTHERS, WE RUN,
RIGHT?
RIGHT.
WHAT?
I THOUGHT I HEARD SOMETHING.
IT'S PROBABLY A RAT.
ARE THERE LITTLE MIDGET
VAMPIRES?
OR...
THIS IS JUST A THOUGHT, BUT DO
BATS BECOME VAMPIRES?
NAH. I MEAN,
I DON'T THINK SO. MAYBE.
LET'S GO.
SHH!
WHAT?
OVER THERE.
I DON'T SEE ANYTHING.
I DON'T, EITHER.
WHAT DO WE DO?
GO ON, I GUESS.
HARV.
HOWDY, ZACH.
J.T.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING DOWN HERE?
I MEAN, WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN?
MR. CHAN'S BEEN WORRIED
ABOUT YOU.
JUST TAKING A BREAK.
EVEN GUYS LIKE ME
NEED A VACATION SOMETIMES.
UH... DID YOU SEE GABE
COME DOWN HERE?
GABE?
YEAH.
GREAT. WELL, WHEN DID
SHE COME THROUGH?
WHERE DID SHE GO?
SHE'S WITH VALENTINE.
GOOD. HE'LL PROTECT HER.
VALENTINE?
YEAH.
HE DOESN'T LIKE HUMAN BLOOD.
WHO TOLD YOU THAT?
HE DID.
AND YOU BELIEVED HIM?
( laughing )
HARV, IS THERE SOMETHING
THAT YOU'RE NOT TELLING US?
COULD BE.
WHY DON'T WE TALK ABOUT IT
OVER LUNCH?
JOIN ME FOR A BITE?
RUN, ZACH!
( Harv growling )
AHH! AHH! ZACH!
OH, NO!
GOTCHA!
I'M YOUR FRIEND!
ZACH, YOU'RE MY LUNCH!
AAAHHHH!
I DON'T BELIEVE THIS
IS HAPPENING.
THAT WAS CLOSE!
I DON'T NEVER WANT THAT
TO HAPPEN AGAIN.
IT'S ALL MY FAULT
SHE'S DOWN THERE.
IF I WASN'T SO MEAN TO HER,
SHE WOULD HAVE NEVER
TOOK THOSE PICTURES.
AND IF WE DIDN'T CARE, WE
WOULDN'T BE TRYING TO SAVE HER,
BUT SHE DID, AND WE DO,
AND WE WILL.
SO, WHAT DO WE DO NOW?
JUST GO BACK DOWN THERE,
WALKING UP AND DOWN
THE TUNNELS?
NO. VALENTINE'S GOT HER,
AND I THINK I KNOW WHERE.
CAN WE GET THERE BY SUNLIGHT?
I ONLY KNOW ONE WAY.
ZACH?
WHAT?
HOW LONG WE BEEN DOWN HERE?
I-I DON'T KNOW. A LONG TIME.
LIKE, A COUPLE OF HOURS?
AT LEAST A COUPLE OF HOURS.
YOU KNOW WHERE WE'RE GOING?
YEAH.
YOU SURE YOU KNOW
WHERE WE'RE GOING?
ABSOLUTELY.
OKAY, ZACH.
WHAT?
YOU'RE NOT LYING AGAIN,
ARE YOU? I MEAN,
I CAN UNDERSTAND IF YOU--
YES! I'M LYING, ALL RIGHT?
WE'RE LOST. I DON'T KNOW WHERE
WE'RE GOING. WE'RE GONNA WANDER
AROUND DOWN HERE UNTIL WE STARVE
TO DEATH OR THE RATS EAT US, OR
UNTIL HARV OR SIMS OR ONE OF THE
OTHER VAMPIRES FINDS US AND
FANGS US, AND WE JOIN THE UNDEAD
FOREVER! YOU HAPPY NOW?!
AS LONG AS YOU KNOW
WHERE WE'RE GOING.
( Zach scoffs )
LOOK!
THERE SHE IS.
ZACH!
MMM. ZACHARY
AND HIS LITTLE FRIEND.
WE'VE BEEN EXPECTING YOU.
LET HER GO, VALENTINE.
TAKE ME INSTEAD.
WE DON'T BARGAIN
WITH THE LIVING.
WHY SHOULD WE LET
ANY OF YOU GO?
HOW COULD YOU DO THIS?
YOU TOLD ME YOU DIDN'T DRINK
HUMAN BLOOD.
I LIED.
( laughter )
ZACHARY, I'M A VAMPIRE.
DRINKING HUMAN BLOOD
IS MY NATURE.
I WARNED YOU.
I TOLD YOU:
TRUST NO ONE.
I EVEN GAVE YOU A CLUE.
WHAT CLUE?
WELL, I STARTED
THIS LITTLE FAMILY.
NOW, HOW COULD I DO THAT
WITHOUT DRINKING HUMAN BLOOD?
( sighs ) HE'S RIGHT.
I'M SO STUPID.
NO, YOU JUST HEARD
WHAT YOU WANTED TO HEAR.
SHE IS SO... SWEET.
WAIT, WAIT, WAIT A MINUTE,
MAN. WE WERE GONNA SHARE HER.
THIS IS A COMMUNAL THING,
ISN'T IT?
BUT NOW THERE ARE TWO MORE.
SIMS.
WELL, YOU COULD JUST...
YOU KNOW... DO WHAT YOU
WERE DOING, AND WE'LL
TAKE GABE AND GO.
YES, WE COULD DO THAT,
BUT WE'RE NOT GOING TO.
( laughter )
SHE IS SO SWEET,
JUST LIKE A ROSE IN BLOOM.
CAN THE POETRY,
COUNT CHOCULA.
SHE DOES LACK MANNERS,
THOUGH, DOESN'T SHE?
LET HER GO.
I MEAN IT, VALENTINE.
OHH! LET HER GO, LET HER GO.
NO, I THINK NOT. NO.
WELL, UNLESS...
WHAT? WHAT DO YOU WANT?
WE'D BE VERY GRATEFUL
IF YOU COULD DO ONE
TINY LITTLE THING FOR US.
THAT IS, TO THROW
ONE LITTLE SWITCH,
ONE TINY SWITCH
THAT WILL CONNECT
THE UNDEAD EXPRESS
TO THE REGULAR SUBWAY LINES.
WHAT?
BUT IF I DID THAT, YOU COULD--
YOU'D BE ABLE TO ATTACK
NEW YORK.
ACTUALLY,
THAT OCCURRED TO US.
( laughter )
THINK OF IT AS A BARGAIN.
YOU HELP US, AND WE HELP YOU.
WE'D BE... SO GRATEFUL FOR IT.
I CAN'T DO THAT!
I CAN'T LET A TRAINFUL
OF VAMPIRES LOOSE ON NEW YORK.
WHY NOT?
THEY'D PROBABLY BE
A LOT SAFER THAN
THEY ARE RIGHT NOW.
IN ANY EVENTS, ZACHARY,
IT'S A VERY SIMPLE THING,
REALLY.
EITHER YOU DO THIS
LITTLE FAVOR FOR US,
OR YOUR FRIEND HERE
BECOMES ONE OF THE UNDEAD
RIGHT NOW.
Don't do it.
OH, THAT'S BAD ADVICE.
I CAN'T LET 'EM DO IT.
I CAN'T. I CAN'T LET THEM
DO THAT TO YOU, GABE.
I DON'T WANT MY MOM--
YOUR MOM--
LIKE THEM.
OH, THAT'S SO SAD.
THAT'S SO SAD-- SHE DOESN'T
WANT HER MOM TO BE LIKE US.
ZACHARY, SAY GOODBYE
TO YOUR FRIEND.
STOP.
I'LL DO IT.
GOOD CHOICE.
WHY DON'T YOU ACCOMPANY US?
BRING HER,
AND THE OTHERS AS WELL.
FAR OUT.
I'VE BEEN WAITING
60 YEARS FOR THIS.
HARV WAS ONLY AN APPETIZER.
SINCE YOU BROUGHT HIM UP,
YOU MIGHT HAVE CHOSEN SOMEONE
WITH MORE BREEDING.
THIS IS AS FAR AS
WE VAMPIRES CAN GO, ZACHARY.
I CAN GO BACK TO WALL STREET
EARLY. START TRADING.
BITE A BROKER.
FEED AND GROW RICH
AT THE SAME TIME! HEH HEH HEH!
AND I COULD GO BACK
TO THE FALLS.
THEY REALLY ARE GORGEOUS,
AND THE TOURISTS...
HAVE SUCH GOOD TASTE!
( Sims hisses )
JUST AHEAD, ROUND THE CORNER,
THERE'S A SWITCH.
IF YOU THROW IT,
WE CAN ROUTE THE UNDEAD EXPRESS
TO ANY OF THE REGULAR LINES.
AND THEN YOU START...
FEEDING.
YOU AND YOUR, UH,
LITTLE FRIENDS WILL BE SAFE.
PEOPLE?
Sims: DEFINITELY!
Vampire Woman: CERTAINLY!
( vampires murmur assent )
YOU CAN'T GO INTO THE LIGHT?
YOU SAW WHAT HAPPENED
TO DWAYNE.
WE CAN'T REACH THE SWITCH.
WE NEED A LIVING HUMAN
TO DO THAT,
TO INVITE US OUT
INTO THE WORLD,
TO SHUT OUT THAT LIGHT.
ME?
IT IS FORTUNATE THAT YOU--
THAT YOU VOLUNTEERED.
PERHAPS A, UH,
A LOCAL, NOT AN EXPRESS.
WHAT DO YOU THINK, ZACHARY?
I DON'T KNOW.
HOW 'BOUT THE, UH...
THE NUMBER 7.
FINE. SEVEN.
SEVEN. I LIKE THAT.
BIBLICAL, SEVEN,
DON'T YOU THINK?
NUMBER SEVEN!
THAT'S MY LUCKY NUMBER,
ZACHARY,
SEVEN.
♪♪
AND?
I DID IT.
GOOD.
NOW, WE WILL BOARD
THE UNDEAD EXPRESS.
YOU SAID YOU'D LET US GO.
ONLY IF YOU DID
WHAT YOU WERE TOLD,
AND WE AREN'T QUITE SURE
OF THAT YET, ARE WE?
NOW, NOW, NOW, NOW,
LET'S NOT HAVE A SCENE.
( vampire woman
laughs softly )
NOW WE CAN GET UNDERWAY.
( vampires react
with delight )
BETTER NOT HAVE TRIED
THE OLD DOUBLE-CROSS, BOY!
UNLIKE YOU, SOME PEOPLE
CAN BE TRUSTED.
( chuckles )
I'M SURE YOUR LITTLE FRIENDS
WILL AGREE.
WHY DON'T YOU... TAKE A SEAT.
DID YOU DO IT?
YEAH, NUMBER SEVEN.
WHAT TIME IS IT?
I DON'T KNOW.
I CAN'T WAIT!
IT'LL BE SO NICE
TO HAVE PEOPLE FOR DINNER!
( laughter )
TO HAVE PEOPLE
WITH GOOD TASTE!
HEY, GREAT TASTE,
BUT LESS FILLING, MAN!
( laughter )
IT'S ALL MY FAULT.
IF I'D HAVE NEVER LIED
TO YOU GUYS. I'M SORRY.
I'M NEVER GONNA LIE AGAIN,
I PROMISE.
FOR THE REST OF MY LIFE,
I'M GONNA PLAY IT STRAIGHT.
WE'RE ON!
WE'RE ON THE MAIN LINE!
( laughter )
"THE REST OF YOUR LIFE"?
THAT'S, LIKE, A MINUTE!
( vampires murmuring )
YOU SAID YOU'D LET US GO.
DID WE SAY THAT?
I DON'T RECALL SAYING THAT.
I MUST HAVE BEEN ON SOME
HEAVY STUFF, MAN! HA HA HA!
VALENTINE, STOP 'EM!
WE HAD A BARGAIN.
THERE'S TOO MANY OF US.
WE WON'T LET HIM STOP US NOW.
IT'S ALMOST OVER, ZACHARY.
IT'S ALMOST OVER.
( vampires murmuring )
VALENTINE, YOU OWE ME!
AND I AM GOING TO REPAY YOU!
( vampire woman laughing )
( vampires screaming )
J.T., QUICK!
BEHIND THE DOOR!
( vampires screaming
and groaning )
♪♪
FAR OUT, MAN! AAAHHHH!
AAAHHH!
YOU...!
THANK YOU, FRIEND ZACHARY.
♪♪
( snarling )
( explosive sound )
HE KNEW.
HE WANTED TO DIE...
BUT HE COULDN'T KEEP
THE REST OF THEM ALIVE.
I WAS SCARED THAT
THEY WOULD...
I KNOW. ME TOO.
I THOUGHT THEY WERE
GONNA BITE YOU AND...
I KNOW.
♪♪
GUYS, WE'VE GOT A PROBLEM!
PUSH SOMETHING!
WHAT?
I DON'T KNOW! ANYTHING!
"STOP," NOT "GO"!
WE'RE GONNA CRASH!
( air brakes hiss )
Woman: WHERE DID IT
COME FROM?
WONDER IF ANYBODY'S HURT?
( spectators remark )
WE MADE IT!
( all reacting joyously )
WE MADE IT! WE MADE IT!
WE MADE IT! YES!
( excited chatter )
OH, CHILDREN!
HOLD ON, HOLD ON,
WHAT'S GOING ON?
IT WAS AWFUL!
HE JUST--HE JUST CAME OUT OF--
THE DRIVER!
THE DRIVER'S IN THERE!
ALL RIGHT, STICK AROUND!
STICK AROUND!
WHAT'S IN THERE?
CAN YOU SEE?
THE SMELL IS AWFUL!
LOOK AT THE SMOKE!
YEAH, I'M DOWN AT 33rd.
WE GOT SOMETHING REALLY WEIRD
GOING ON HERE.
SO WE TOOK THE BUS HOME,
AND GABE HELPED ME
WITH MY PROJECT.
I GOT A "C."
I MEAN, THAT'S BETTER
THAN I USUALLY DO, AND THAT'S
WITH A GRADE MARK-DOWN.
THAT'S GOOD.
HOW 'BOUT YOU AND YOUR PARENTS?
THEY'RE TALKING--
I MEAN, WITHOUT FIGHTING.
AT LEAST THEY'RE
FRIENDLIER NOW.
AND THE LYING?
NOPE. NEVER AGAIN.
I LEARNED MY LESSON.
GOOD MAN.
DO YOU BELIEVE ME?
ABOUT THE VAMPIRES?
YEAH.
AS A MATTER OF FACT, YES.
YES, I DO.
I DON'T THINK I NEED
TO COME BACK HERE ANYMORE,
DO I?
NOPE.
IT'S GREAT. I MEAN...
I'M SORRY.
( chuckles ) IT'S OKAY.
OH, AND ZACH,
SAY HI TO YOUR FRIENDS
FOR ME, GABE AND J.T.
YEAH, SURE.
I'LL SEE YOU LATER.
♪♪
FOR A WHILE THERE,
I REALLY THOUGH ZACH
WAS GOING TO JOIN ME HERE
IN THE SHADOW ZONE PERMANENTLY!
WELL... MAYBE NEXT TIME.
Woman: AAAAHHHHH!
IF YOU'LL EXCUSE ME,
I BELIEVE I HAVE OTHER GUESTS.
YOU KNOW, PEOPLE ARE JUST
DYING TO GET IN HERE!
HA HA HA HA HA!
MAYBE NEXT TIME,
IT WILL BE YOU.
♪♪