(GENTLE CHIMING)
Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
(DIAL TONE HUMMING)
(TONE BEEPING)
(TONE RINGING)
OPERATOR: 9-1-1.
What's your emergency?
CALLER: Shit. Shit.
OPERATOR: Sir, could
you try to remain calm?
What is your emergency?
CALLER: I-
- OPERATOR: Let's start
by giving me your name
- and your address.
- Don't tell me what to do.
Don't you ever tell me
what do, do you understand?
OPERATOR: I do understand.
How can I help you?
CALLER: I won't
let her take my kids.
She can't take them.
She can't. They're mine.
OPERATOR: Sir, I need
to know where you are
so that I can send help.
CALLER: 14
Independence Square.
I'll fucking shoot
her if she leaves.
You have to stop her.
If she tries to take my
kids, I'll fucking kill her.
(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
BISHOP: So
what? It's chicken.
Don't fucking judge me.
WILKENS: It's not me.
Adam asks his
guests all the time.
Okay, what do you
have against chicken?
Nothing. Nothing.
Bake it, fry it, barbecue it.
Just don't put it in a taco.
You're crazy, it's delicious.
Oh, my god, whatever.
You know what?
You get a pass.
You get a pass
'cause you grew up
around mostly white people.
Oh, well, I'm sorry
I didn't grow up
eating lengua or barbacoa.
Besides, look at you.
You're eating rabbit
food in a wrap.
Eh!
I love meat.
It's just Maria wanted us
to try this vegan shit,
so what am I supposed to do?
I don't see Maria here.
Yeah, but I'm gonna go home
and she's gonna ask me
what I had for lunch,
so what am I supposed to
do, lie to her every day?
You tell Maria what you
had for lunch every day?
DISPATCH: Available units,
we have a domestic dispute
in progress at 14
Independence Square.
Repeat, domestic in progress.
14 Independence Square.
BISHOP: Shit, that's close.
(WILKINS SIGHS)
Unit 451 responding.
We're two minutes out.
(SIREN WAILING)
DISPATCH: Suspect
is armed and hostile.
Turn right.
DISPATCH: Suspect believed
to be holding family hostage.
BISHOP: All right,
go over here. Yeah.
DISPATCH: Number
of hostages, unknown.
BISHOP: Left on Path.
WILKINS: Okay,
kill the lights.
BISHOP: Right here, right
here, right here, right here.
Unit 451. We're on location.
DISPATCH: Unit 451,
set up a perimeter
and standby for SWAT.
(TENSE MUSIC)
MAN: No.
No, no! Come on!
(GLASS CRASHES)
(GIRL SCREAMS)
Came from around back.
This is Unit 451. We
got a hostile situation.
What's your ETA on SWAT?
DISPATCH: SWAT
is five minutes out.
Shit. Bishop.
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC)
MAN: Get your ass up, now!
Somebody's gonna get killed!
(HANDLE CLACKS)
(TENSE MUSIC)
BISHOP: Police! Get
on the fucking ground!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
(GUN FIRES)
Fuck!
This is Unit 451. Shots fired.
Shots fired.
DISPATCH: Copy.
Bishop!
Bishop.
Shit, shit, shit.
BISHOP: Don't
you fucking move!
Let me see your hands!
Keep your hands
where I can see 'em!
Are you hit?
He's bleeding out. Call it in.
Are you hit?!
I'm fine! Call it in!
This is Unit 451. Shots fired.
- Suspect down.
- Stop resisting!
WILKINS: We
need an ambulance.
- Repeat, shots fired.
- Give me your hand.
- Turn around.
- Suspect down.
Request for an
ambulance immediately.
(GIRL SCREAMS)
- (DOOR CRASHES)
- Swat: All right, let's go!
- Let's go, in every closet!
- Check upstairs.
Suspect down.
(POLICE RADIO CHATTERING)
- Get her outta there!
- Get the girl.
SARGENT WARD: You did good.
I'm glad you and Wilkins
made it outta there safe.
You may have saved that
girl's life tonight.
Dispatch said the guy talked
about burning the house down.
(BISHOP SIGHS)
Are you all right?
I know this was the first
time you've had to...
BISHOP: I'm fine, Sergeant.
It's okay.
It's not supposed to be easy.
Most officers are lucky,
they go their whole careers
without firing a weapon.
It's a difficult
thing to prepare for.
It's part of the job.
I'm here if you need me.
Don't have to talk to
some stranger about it
if you don't want to.
Get some rest.
Someone from HR
will call tomorrow
and walk you through everything.
(DOOR CLACKS)
- JAN: Are you okay?
- Yes, I'm fine.
Okay.
(JAN SIGHS)
Why didn't you call me? Had
to hear it from Wilkins?
Had to give my
statement to the FID,
and then Sergeant
wanted to talk to me.
I wasn't thinking.
I got really scared
thinking about losing you.
(GENTLE MUSIC)
Can we, um
Can you just come home?
Can you come home?
I can't.
Wilkins and I, we have some
paperwork to finish, so...
That's fine. I
mean, come back home.
Jan.
I'll call you tonight.
Okay.
Really glad you're all right.
(SIREN WAILING)
(UPBEAT HIP HOP MUSIC)
BISHOP: I did not
see this one coming.
WILKINS: Yeah, I should've
been there with you.
You should've waited.
Wasn't going in, I
was just trying to hear
what he was saying
through the window.
Then he kicked the door open,
almost took my fucking face off-
- You got lucky.
You're gonna get yourself
killed pulling the hero shit.
Fuck.
Fucking wired.
What makes a guy do
that to his own family?
Gonna get another drink.
I'm good.
WILL: Yeah?
DAVON: Hey, hero.
Celebrating your big day, huh?
All right.
What?
Andre was my guy.
Yeah. We played ball
at Central together.
Good man.
- Good family.
- Okay, it wasn't like that.
It was self-defense.
(DAVON CHUCKLES)
You even got the black
chick vouching for you.
- That's cute.
- Okay, who the fuck are you?
Hey, tell me something,
do you get like a prize
for every brother you
kill or something,
or like a cake,
or like stickers.
How many niggas do
you have to kill-
- You motherfucker!
- Get the fuck off me!
- (PUNCHES THUDDING)
- Fuck you, man!
(PUNCH THUDS)
(WILL GROANS)
(DAVON CHUCKLES)
- What?
- Fuck you!
What? Hey, what's wrong?
- What's wrong?
- You weren't there!
- What's wrong with you?
- Fuck you, motherfucker!
- We all on the same team.
- Hey, hey!
He's an asshole, all
right? He wasn't there.
He wasn't. He doesn't
know what happened.
BISHOP: Fuck you!
You weren't there!
- You weren't there!
- Hey, he wasn't, all right?
Let it go.
Come on.
- Listen to your girl, huh?
- Chill the fuck out!
Come on. Chill the fuck out.
Bishop!
Bye, hero.
(WILKINS SIGHS)
BISHOP: What a day.
You've been here a week,
and you didn't tell me?
Nice place, right?
You can't keep
pulling this shit, man.
Fuck it, give me one of those.
Just...
Gonna be good.
What was it this time?
It's always the same.
You know, Jan doesn't get it.
Get what?
Us.
Our job.
The law, what we do.
She just wants to find
the good in everyone.
She wants to fix everyone.
Well, you married
a social worker.
What do you expect?
Don't opposites attract?
You're asking a lesbian
if opposites attract?
- Yeah.
- Look, all I know
is you gotta stop.
You can't keep
pulling this shit.
I mean, one of these days,
she's gonna smarten up
and she's gonna leave your ass.
Then what?
Yeah, I know.
You know? Then what
the fuck are you doing?
I mean, you gotta fix
it, make it right.
(BISHOP MUMBLES)
(BISHOP SIGHS)
(CUPBOARD DOORS THUDDING)
(WATER SPLASHING)
(ALCOHOL SPLASHING)
(CELLPHONE BUZZING)
(CELLPHONE CLICKS)
(MELLOW MUSIC)
♪ Ooh, and it's that time ♪
♪ To wait for the sun ♪
(BOTTLE CRASHES)
(REFRIGERATOR RATTLING)
(DINNERWARE CLATTERING)
NEIGHBOR: Hey!
Knock it off before
we call the police!
- (HAND THUDDING)
- I am the fucking police!
♪ And the devil comes
around, we all go down ♪
♪ Hey ♪
(MAN GROANS)
(GIRL SCREAMING)
(BISHOP GROANING)
(BISHOP COUGHS)
(VOMIT SPLASHES)
(BISHOP GROANING)
(BISHOP SPITS)
BISHOP: I'm sorry. Fuck.
Hey, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa.
Bishop. What are you doing here?
I just wanted to
talk to Sergeant Ward.
That's not a good idea, all
right? He's busy right now.
Fine.
I just wanna look
at my report again.
You're fucking
wasted. Go home.
Okay? Please.
Why?
WARD: Excuse me
for just a moment.
Take them to my office.
What's going on?
What are you
doing here, Bishop?
I thought I was clear yesterday.
You need to take some time.
(GENTLE MUSIC)
ROSIE: Lucy.
Lucy.
Lucy, is that him?
Is that him?
Is that the man that
killed my husband?
- Mrs. Hughes, listen to me.
- No, no.
Is that him?
- I wanna talk to him!
- Okay.
- I wanna talk to you.
- No, no, no.
- Go, you should go.
- Okay, listen-
- You killed Andre!
- I know.
- You killed my husband!
- Be careful, wait, wait.
He's the one who killed Andre!
ALBERT: I know,
I know, I know.
I wanna talk to him!
Why did you do
it?! I wanna know!
Why did you come in my
house and kill my husband?!
I wanna know! I wanna know!
- ALBERT: Let's go in-
- ROSIE: I wanna know.
ALBERT: Wait, come on now.
Come on, let's go in.
Now, listen, I've got a
family in mourning over there.
I can't have you here
right, you understand?
I've got to get back
and sort this all out.
You go home and get some rest.
- Are you defending him?
- No, ma'am.
No.
That man murdered my husband.
SERGEANT WARD:
Ma'am, ma'am, please.
ROSIE: Don't touch me.
If you would just
take your seat.
Just take your seat,
we'll talk, we'll talk.
Officer Wilkins,
- you can step out.
- Hey, what do you know?
ALBERT: Rosie,
wait. Wait, Rosie.
Sis, what do you know?
You have to tell
me what you know.
Look, can you tell
me what you know?
- Please?
- Let her go, come on now.
Come on. Sit down.
Sit down.
Sit down, now.
All right. All right.
I'm terribly
sorry for your loss.
We want to be completely
- transparent.
- You don't get to be sorry.
Tell me why your officers
were at my house.
They were responding
to a hostage call
from your residence.
Now, the footage from
my officer's body camera
showed your husband
with a broken bottle
exiting the backdoor where
the altercation took place.
Altercation?
You mean the one where
my husband was killed?
I wanna hear it.
I wanna hear that tape!
That was not Andre!
That's not what happened!
You can ask my...
You can ask my daughter.
She was there the whole...
She was there the whole time.
GRANDMOTHER: This is
what we talked about.
Okay?
ANDRE: No.
No, no! Come on!
Get up, get up, get up.
Come on. You got it, you got it.
No.
Fire this guy.
(TELEVISION CHATTERING)
Come on.
Yeah, that's it. Come
on, let's get it.
Let's get it, let's get it.
Ah, shit. Come on.
Language, Daddy.
I'm sorry, baby.
Hey, it's 8:30.
Gonna get your schoolwork done?
It's all done.
Okay, well, go on
up and get it out
so your mom can check
it in the morning, okay?
And brush your teeth.
It's almost time for bed.
Hey.
Don't play me now.
(ANDRE CHUCKLES)
Come on. Hustle.
(ANDRE SIGHS)
ANNOUNCER: And he will be
the lead blocker for Hughes.
He's got breakaway speed!
ANNOUNCER: Bye-bye.
(BALL THUDS)
(GLASS CRASHES)
(LUCY SCREAMS)
No, it's okay, baby.
Daddy just got excited.
I'll be up after I
throw this mess outside.
- (GLASS CLATTERING)
- Over eight points
defensively here
in the four games
that have led to this
six-eight championship.
Oh, come on.
Somebody's gonna get killed!
This playbook is trash!
(WATER SPLASHING)
What are you doing?!
Get your ass up, now!
BISHOP: Police,
get on the fucking-
(GUN FIRES)
(LUCY SPITS)
(GENTLE MUSIC)
Dad?
- Dad.
- Shots fired.
BISHOP: Let me see
your fucking hands.
WILKINS: Repeat, shots
fired. Suspect down.
Request for an
ambulance immediately.
BISHOP: Give me your
other fucking hand, now!
Give it to me!
(ANDRE GROANS)
Turn around. Give
me your other hand!
(LUCY SCREAMS)
(DOOR CRASHES)
- Let's go, in every closet!
- Check upstairs.
- Suspect down.
- Get her outta there!
OFFICER: Get the girl.
(CELLPHONE BUZZING)
(CELLPHONE CLICKING)
(ALCOHOL SPLASHING)
(CELLPHONE BUZZING)
(CELLPHONE CLICKS)
Hey.
How's it going?
BISHOP: Fucking great.
Right. Sorry.
BISHOP: What's up?
They brought in the girl to
give an official statement.
They wanna open up
an investigation.
Investigation? Into what?
The wife says it
doesn't make sense.
There were no hostages.
She says she was at the
hospital visiting a friend.
He was the perfect husband.
What did the girl say?
She said she was upstairs.
BISHOP: You heard her
scream, though, right?
Yeah. Yeah, I heard her.
Okay, so why was he on
the porch with a bottle?
I mean, can they explain that?
He broke the bottle
watching the game.
Look, I got one of the guys
to send over a copy
of the Hughes call,
but you gotta delete it
after you listen to it.
I don't think the
family's heard it yet.
Did you listen to it?
WILKINS: Yeah.
It's messed up.
So you just gotta be careful
'cause it can't leak out.
Of course.
I just wanna know what happened.
Okay. I'm sending it now.
BISHOP: Thanks
for this, all right?
(CELLPHONE CHIMES)
(CELLPHONE BUZZES)
OPERATOR: 9-1-1.
What's your emergency?
CALLER: Shit. Shit.
OPERATOR: Just try
to remain calm, sir.
What is your emergency?
CALLER: I...
OPERATOR: Start by giving
me your name and your address.
CALLER: Don't
tell me what to do.
Don't you ever tell me
what do, you understand?
OPERATOR: Sir,
yes, I understand.
But how can I help you?
CALLER: I won't
let her take my kids.
She can't take them.
They're mine.
OPERATOR: Sir, I need
to know where you are
so that I can send help.
CALLER: 14
Independence Square.
I'll shoot her if she leaves.
You have to stop her.
If she tries to take my
kids, I'll fucking kill her.
OPERATOR: Where are you now?
CALLER: In the kitchen.
OPERATOR: Okay.
And where is she?
CALLER: In the closet.
Are you sending someone?
OPERATOR: Yes, officers
have been dispatched.
Now, I'm gonna-
(TELEPHONE CLICKS)
(GENTLE MUSIC)
NEWSCASTER: Police are
expected to make a statement
tomorrow on the incident
that took the life
of local football
coach Andre Hughes.
Police received a distressed
call that brought them
to the Hughes residence
just after 9:00 p.m.,
when an altercation began,
resulting in the death of the
well-respected football coach.
He is survived by
his wife Rosie Hughes
and their daughter Lucy,
as well as his parents
Gayle and Albert Hughes.
When we return, we'll
go to Alison Wade
who was with the Hughes
family earlier today.
I've covered a lot of
stories on the school
and... Andre over the years.
He was such a kind man.
So sorry for your loss.
Okay.
(ALISON SIGHS)
Ready?
Yeah.
Whenever you're ready.
(ROSIE SIGHS)
Andre Hughes
was a loving husband and father.
He was the light of our family
and he was a part of this
community his entire life.
I want answers.
We all lost a great
man last night,
and I wanna know why.
Andre loved everyone,
and everyone loved him.
Why was my husband murdered
by the police in his own home?
Is that him?
Lucy, is that him?
Is that the man that
killed my husband?
- Mrs. Hughes, listen to me.
- No, no.
Is that him?
(CELLPHONE BUZZING)
(BISHOP SIGHS)
WILKINS: Hey, it's Wilkins.
You gotta come in.
Sergeant Ward needs
to talk to you.
It's urgent.
(BISHOP SIGHS)
(GENTLE MUSIC)
CROWD: We want justice!
We want justice!
BISHOP: Did you
see everyone outside?
WILKINS: Yeah, there have
been suits here all day.
Fuck.
Look, I know Sergeant
Ward wants to talk to you,
but they're not telling
me what's going on.
They think I shot him
because he was black.
I shot him because
I felt threatened,
because I was doing
my fucking job.
Yeah, I know.
But listen, man, they're tired
of being seen as a threat.
I mean, they wanna know
were you threatened by him
or what he looks like.
You get that, right?
Are you saying I'm a racist?
Did I say that?
- Did I say that?
- No, what the fuck
are you saying, then, Wilkins-
- SERGEANT WARD: Good morning.
- Morning, sir.
- Hey, Sarge.
Officer Wilkins, could we
speak with Bishop alone, please?
Yes, sir.
This is Mr. Smith. He's
the department lawyer.
- Morning.
- Will.
Morning.
Okay. Please.
Bishop, are you all right?
I didn't expect any of this.
- (WILL SIGHS)
- You responded to
a distress call about
a violent situation
and you acted with bravery.
Not many people realize the
burdens we volunteer for
when we take on
this job every day.
It's a heroic responsibility
just to put on a badge.
Now, we received some disturbing
information this morning
and we're still
investigating its legitimacy.
But I wanted to
sit down with you,
give you the news first,
so that I can answer any
questions you may have.
An email came in.
It contained a recording of
some people playing video games
the night of the Hughes call.
Went on for hours.
There are pages and
pages of arguments
in the transcriptions here.
At first, it made no sense,
but then one of the players
threatened to send a SWAT
team to someone's house.
That address was 14
Independence Square.
(GENTLE PIANO MUSIC)
(SERGEANT WARD SIGHS)
I just don't understand
- how assholes these days-
- You know,
I know this is a lot to take in,
but what's important to remember
are the facts of the situation.
Take a look at that.
Now,
from the footage,
from your body cam,
Andre Hughes was
angry that night
when he came through
the door at you.
You and Officer
Wilkins both reported
hearing the shattering
of glass inside the house
and a girl's scream.
As you secured a perimeter,
you encountered the
suspect at the door
holding a broken
bottle in his hand.
You announced yourself
as a police officer
and instructed him to get
on the ground, correct?
Mr. Bishop?
Yes.
MR. SMITH: He
disobeyed those orders
and threw the bottle at you,
causing you to fire
at the suspect.
Is that correct?
Officer Bishop?
Officer Bishop,
these are the facts
that we must be very clear
about before your hearing,
do you understand?
(WILL HEAVES)
(VOMIT SPLASHES)
Jesus Christ.
(SERGEANT WARD GROANS)
I'm sorry, Sergeant.
- It's okay.
- I'm sorry.
It's okay.
It's okay. Let me go get
something to clean this up.
It's all right.
I'll be right back.
(BISHOP SIGHING)
(GENTLE MUSIC)
Oh. Excuse me, Sergeant, sir.
Can you tell me what's going on?
Like, what's the
suit doing here?
We got an email.
The call was faked.
Some assholes online.
Jesus Christ. We got swatted?
What did Bishop say?
Nothing yet.
He got sick.
Oh, my god, how is
this even possible?
How does this happen?
I don't know.
People are fucked.
Shit!
I'll go check the parking lot.
God dammit, Bishop.
This is a big liability
for the department, Sergeant.
Those news stations are
growing out there too.
This guy was a local legend.
You need to make Bishop understand
he acted in self-defense.
Get him in line.
This can't look like blindfire.
If not for him, for the
rest of the department.
He needs to be at
that hearing next week
and he needs to
have it together.
(SERGEANT WARD SIGHS)
He's gone, sir.
They said he
grabbed a few things
from his desk and took off.
Did he talk to anyone?
No, sir.
Oh, God dammit, Bishop.
If he's AWOL, I can't
do anything to help him.
Well, I'll go find him.
No, no, no, no,
no, no. Stay here.
We need you here.
Have you seen that
crowd outside?
It's getting bigger.
I understand.
Dammit.
(PAPER TOWEL ROLL THUDS)
- (TONE RINGING)
- Come on, Bishop.
(LOCKS CLACKING)
(CELLPHONE BUZZING)
BISHOP: Hi, you've reached
- Will Bishop.
- Shit.
(TONE RINGS)
BISHOP: Hi, you've
reached Will Bishop.
WILKINS: Son of a bitch.
BISHOP: I can't
get to the phone,
so leave a message and
I'll get back to you.
Thanks.
(TONE BEEPS)
Bishop, it's me.
Come on, man, you
gotta talk to me.
You gotta talk to me, okay?
I know what kinda cop you are.
I know you.
We can work this out together,
but you gotta call me.
(TONE RINGS)
- Hi.
- Hey, it's Wilkins.
JAN: What's going on?
I need your help.
Yeah, there's people gathering
outside of our house with signs.
They have been
for the last hour.
I've called Will,
he's not answering.
What's going on?
I can't get ahold of Will.
He just left the station and-
(TOMATO THUDS)
- We want justice!
- Jan?
(GENTLE MUSIC)
ChayMoney.
(BISHOP MUMBLES)
(LIGHTER CLICKS)
NEWSCASTER: As tensions
rise in the community,
we go live to Alison Wade who
is at the police precinct.
- Alison?
- Want justice!
We want justice!
- We want justice!
- The protest remains peaceful
as the numbers continue to grow
outside the police station.
Students have been arriving
wearing football jerseys
and the schools colors
in support of the coach.
(GUNS FIRING)
GAMER: Yo, flank left.
GAMER: I don't know if I
have it. They're right there.
They're right there.
GAMER: Yo, I'm
coming. I'm coming.
GAMER: You get the drop.
GAMER: Where's
the other team?
GAMER: Look at tunnels. Take
the stairs, take the stairs.
GAMER: What are
you doing? Come on.
- (CHARACTER GROANS)
- Ah, shit.
GAMER: God dammit.
Yo, this guy sucks.
Hello? Hello?
Hello.
Can you hear me?
- Hello?
- Yo, who is this guy?
I'm looking for
ChayMoney. You know him?
GAMER: Piss off.
I'm looking for
ChayMoney or the Grinch.
You know where they are?
GAMER: Yo, quit the
game, you fucking noob.
Hey, can you just
tell me where they are?
GAMER: Are you joking? This
is the internet, you pleb.
Hey, man, I'm in the
middle of a game with them,
so can you just tell
me where to find them?
GAMER: Oh, my
god, this guy sucks.
Hey, grandpa, go
back to the main menu
and add them to
your friends list.
Thanks. Thanks, man.
(CONTROLLER CLICKING)
(INTERFACE CHIMES)
(INTERFACE BUZZES)
(CONTROLLER CLICKING)
(INTERFACE CHIMES)
(INTERFACE BUZZES)
Fuck.
(GENTLE MUSIC)
ANDRE: Wolverine Nation!
I wanna thank everyone for
your support this season.
Coaching football has
always been a dream of mine
and that's a dream
that comes with both
the wins and the losses.
Now, we may have
come up short today,
but I want you to
know this is a season
I will never forget, okay?
I can only hope
that when the pain
of tonight's game wears off,
that each and every one of you
has as many fond
memories as I do.
I want every one of these
young men to understand
the impact they've had on
me, on their teammates,
the impact on the other students
and the whole
community around them,
and on the memories
that you created
that we will cherish
for a lifetime.
Hey, cupcake.
Come here.
You wanna say something?
- Go Wolverines!
(BOTH MIMICKING GROWLING)
(ANDRE CHUCKLES)
(GENTLE GUITAR MUSIC)
(BISHOP SIGHS)
(CONTROLLER CLICKING)
(INTERFACE CHIMES)
(DOOR KNOCKING)
JAN: Hey, it's me.
Wilkins told me
where to find you.
Come on.
(DOOR KNOCKING)
Let me in.
Your car's in the parking lot
and I can smell the
cigarettes from here.
♪ Hold me, hold me ♪
I'll stay out here all
night if I have to.
What are you doing here?
JAN: I love you
and I wanna help.
You can't fix this one, Jan.
Please let me in.
(DOORKNOB RATTLING)
I can't.
Okay.
Okay, then we can
talk like this.
♪ It all sends us along ♪
♪ Round the swamps and moor ♪
Do you remember when we
first started dating,
and we'd just would,
like, drive circles
around the city
with nowhere to be?
(SIREN WAILING)
You know, those were some
of my favorite nights.
Yeah, you know, stick it to him.
Makes me feel better about
sleeping my comfortable bed.
Where are we going?
I told you. Just trust me.
This guy is the best.
You always had some
local hero or urban legend
you couldn't wait to show me.
(JAN LAUGHING)
(WILL LAUGHING)
- Hey.
- What's up?
- What's up, man?
MCRITCHIE: Officer Bishop.
BISHOP: This is Jan,
this is my friend Jan.
MCRITCHIE: What did I do to
deserve you two tonight, huh?
It was like the world
wasn't a dark place anymore
'cause you had this light
that made everybody
else around you shine.
- He's a musician hot dog man.
- Why'd you come here?
- Yeah.
- For a dog and a song.
And that's the man
I fell in love with.
(JAN SIGHS)
♪ Hot dogs and whiskey
makes me feel frisky ♪
♪ Holding her hand
on a Saturday night ♪
♪ Said hot dogs and whiskey,
maybe she'll kiss me ♪
♪ Looking into her eyes
in the cold moonlight ♪
(LIVELY MUSIC)
That's the man I wanna spend
the rest of my life with.
And I know you're still there.
We used to stay up
all night laughing
at each other's stories,
and now, we barely speak.
I wanna find a way to start over
and remember the
people we used to be.
(JAN LAUGHS)
You never told me
your pet peeve.
(BISHOP LAUGHS)
Oh, yeah, I don't have any.
Come on, you must have one.
No, I'll do it in a second.
(JAN LAUGHS)
(BANGS LOUDLY)
(CAR BANGING)
Will.
Hey, hey, hey. It's a car.
It's a car.
I hate what this
job has done to you.
Jan, I can't
drag you into this.
You're not dragging me into
anything I'm not already in.
I'm your wife.
There's people screaming
outside of our house.
Tell me what's going on.
(INTERFACE CHIMES)
- You don't understand.
- Oh, I don't understand.
I've been married to you for
five years, I don't understand.
What do you want me to say?
Don't you get it? I
don't want you here!
You can't fix this!
Just leave me alone.
(SOMBER MUSIC)
I love you, Will,
and you have to pull
yourself outta this.
If you won't talk to
me, talk to Wilkins.
(HAND THUDS)
(INTERFACE CHIMES)
I love you too.
(INTERFACE CHIMING)
(CELLPHONE BUZZING)
WILKINS: Hello?
Okay.
Okay, okay, calm down.
What did he say?
No, no, no. He loves you.
He's probably still drunk.
Just try and let
him sleep it off.
Yeah, we'll go together
in the morning.
Okay?
I'll call you in the morning.
Try to get some rest.
(SWITCH CLICKS)
(WILKINS SIGHS)
Is Jan all right?
She's a mess.
I mean, you know, the
protestors were outside
her house all day, and then...
This swatting thing has really
got Bishop pretty fucked up.
What are you gonna do?
I don't know.
People want me choose sides.
I can't.
(MARIA SIGHS)
Come on, babe, let's
try to get some rest.
Come on.
(SWITCH CLICKS)
(GENTLE MUSIC)
(CONTROLLER CLICKING)
(INTERFACE CHIMES)
(BISHOP SIGHS)
(CONTROLLER CLICKING)
(KEYBOARD CLACKING)
(DOOR KNOCKING)
Come on, Bishop.
GAMER: They're
up in the tower.
Someone's gotta get
them outta there.
We gotta get around.
I hear voices inside.
I'll try calling him again.
(DOOR KNOCKING)
Hey, it's Wilkins.
We're just here to help.
He's not answering.
He's probably passed
out, honestly.
(DOORKNOB CLICKING)
(DOOR CLACKS)
(BELL CHIMES)
Listen up, everyone.
I'm sorry for the inconvenience,
but the store will temporarily
close at this time.
I'm here on an official
police investigation,
so you come back in an hour.
Sorry for the inconvenience.
Thank you.
JAN: I shouldn't have
left him last night.
A suspect is still at large.
We know his phone number
originates from this carrier,
but I need his address.
Now, I spoke to your supervisor
and he said you can get
it for me no problem.
I should call someone first.
I've never done
- anything like this.
- This is an emergency.
One man is already dead.
We don't have time, do
you understand that?
Yeah, just give me a sec.
(KEYBOARD CLACKING)
(COMPUTER BEEPS)
Okay, the name on the
account is Beverly Miller.
(GENTLE MUSIC)
Thank you.
What's it say?
BISHOP: I wish I
could bring back the man
you fell in love with.
When I look in the
mirror some days,
I see the same stranger as you.
I'm sorry for everything I said,
I didn't mean a word of it.
I wasn't strong enough
to open the door,
and I'm sorry for that.
Remember us smiling.
(JAN SIGHS)
(KEYBOARD CLACKING)
- (LAPTOP BUZZES)
- Ah, shit.
It needs a password.
Have you seen him
like this before?
Drunk, yes.
But not like this.
(KEYBOARD CLACKING)
(LAPTOP BEEPS)
Okay, you're in.
♪ We vowed to explore
and take a breath ♪
♪ That breath sure is
something I won't forget ♪
♪ Oh, tell me a secret ♪
Oh, he's looking
for the gamer.
I gotta call this in.
JAN: Shit.
I'm just gonna
need an address.
I can find him.
(LAPTOP CLACKING)
(GENTLE MUSIC)
(DOORBELL RINGS)
(FOOTSTEPS PATTERING)
(FLOOR CREAKING)
(DOOR KNOCKING)
Police Department!
Good morning. I'm
Officer Bishop.
Hope I didn't wake you.
No, no. It's okay.
I'm here investigating
a homicide.
Sorry, I didn't get your name.
Chase Miller.
All right, Chase.
Do you know anyone who goes
by the name of ChayMoney?
No.
I don't.
Sorry.
(DOOR THUDS)
What are you doing?! Stop!
BISHOP: You
know what you did!
- It was just a prank call.
- A prank?!
A fucking prank?!
CHASE: I'm sorry!
Do you know what you did?
Do you have any fucking idea
how many lives you ruined
that night with your
fucking prank call?!
DISPATCH: Available units,
we have a domestic
dispute in progress.
Do you know what you did?!
Do you have any fucking idea?!
DISPATCH: Suspect
is armed and hostile.
(SIREN WAILING)
People are dead
because of you!
We were the first
ones on the scene.
ANDRE: Somebody's
gonna get killed!
BISHOP: How were
we supposed to know
the call was fake, huh?
What's your ETA on SWAT?
SWAT is five minutes out.
(HANDCUFFS CLICKING)
BISHOP: Say something!
Please, it was an
accident. I didn't mean to.
I'm sorry!
No, no. No, no, no.
It was just a...
Listen. Listen!
I didn't know that
was gonna happen.
I didn't mean for
any of it to happen!
I'm sorry.
Shut the fuck up.
(MOUSE WHEEL CLICKING)
His name was Andre Hughes.
Look at him.
Look at him!
He's dead!
He was a husband,
father, teacher, coach.
He's gone.
You said it was a
hostage situation.
You said he was armed.
I heard him yelling
from the street.
ANDRE: Let's go! Come on!
I thought he was holding
his family hostage.
That's what you said!
What the fuck was I
supposed to think?
Why would you do this?
Tell me why!
(TAPE RIPPING)
Why?!
I'm sorry, it was a...
It was the wrong house.
It was supposed to
be this guy online.
People do it all the time.
We were just playing games.
Do you know what you did?
Do you have any fucking idea?!
Yeah, keep talking shit.
Kill all of you,
except you, Grinch.
I'll make you my bitch.
You don't know me.
I'll show up with my AR.
(CHARACTER GROANS)
Oh, fuck!
GRINCH: That's right.
Suck a dick, motherfucker.
Hey, Justin Bieber,
where you at, man?
Come on, bring it.
This dude thinks he's hard.
Keep talking shit, man.
You guys suck.
If teams were even,
we would fuck you up.
GRINCH: Fuck me up, you
haven't fucked anything.
Beat your ass, bro.
GRINCH: Beat my ass,
only thing you beat
is your own dick, virgin.
(MARK LAUGHS)
You gonna let him talk
to you like that, man?
Tell him what's up.
Where you from?
GRINCH: I'm from L.A., but
stay at your mom's otherwise.
I'll come fuck you
up with these hands.
Where do you live?
I'll send some of my
squad to come fuck you up.
Wouldn't be the first time.
GRINCH: Squad
with the Mousketeers?
I've killed before
in Afghanistan.
(MARK SNORTING)
GRINCH: You've killed before?
What, did you go on a
fucking high school trip?
Suck a dick.
Bunch of fags in L.A.
Talk that shit in Arizona,
you'll get fucked up.
I'll drive down, put one in you
tonight if you keep talking.
GRINCH: 14 Independent
Square, bitch.
Oh, damn. This guy fucking
challenged you, dude.
You should SWAT him.
Fuck this cock, dude.
He doesn't even
think you'll do it.
(KEYBOARD CLACKING)
Think this muppet gave
me his real address.
(MARK CHUCKLES)
What an idiot.
Yo, do you still have
that shitty prepay phone?
- Yeah.
- Oh, perfect, dude.
Use that.
Yeah, just gimme a second.
I gotta find the
police number for L.A.
All right.
What a fucking dumb ass.
You know, dude, we
should record his stream
so we can upload it.
Oh, shit.
Fucking hilarious,
man. Can you imagine?
(MOUSE CLICKING)
(COMPUTER BEEPS)
Okay, shut up,
dude. I'm dialing.
Shut the fuck up.
OPERATOR: 9-1-1.
What's your emergency?
Shit. Shit.
OPERATOR: Just try
to remain calm, sir.
What is your emergency?
I...
OPERATOR: Start by giving
me your name and your address.
Don't tell me what to do.
Don't you ever tell me
what to do, you understand?
OPERATOR: Sir,
yes, I understand.
But how can I help you?
I won't let her take my kids.
She can't take them.
They're mine.
OPERATOR: Sir, I need
to know where you are
so that I can send help.
14 Independence Square.
I'll shoot her if she leaves.
You have to stop her.
If she tries to take my
kids, I'll fucking kill her.
OPERATOR: Where are you now?
In the kitchen.
OPERATOR: Okay.
And where is she?
In the closet.
Are you sending someone?
OPERATOR: Yes, officers
have been dispatched.
Now, I'm gonna need
you to stay on the-
(CELLPHONE CLACKS)
Yes.
Oh, shit.
What do you think it's like
to pull a gun on someone?
Is this what it's like
in your fucking game?
It's hard to breathe,
your heart races?
Can you hear it
pounding in your ears?
I heard a glass break, a
girl scream, he was yelling.
I had to do something!
They say, "Stick to the facts."
He was angry, he had a weapon,
he didn't respond
to instructions.
The fuck was I supposed to do?!
He took his last breath,
scared and alone,
without anyone who loved him.
- And you stole him from them.
- No justice, no peace!
- They deserve justice.
- You did this to him.
- Fucking say it.
- No justice, no peace!
No justice, no peace!
- You killed him.
- No justice, no peace!
- Say it!
- No.
Look at me. Look at me!
You killed him!
I didn't kill anyone!
- No justice, no peace!
- Say it!
- I said say it!
- No justice, no peace!
I'm fine! Call it in!
This is Unit 451.
(LUCY SCREAMS)
Shots fired. Suspect down.
We need an ambulance.
Repeat, shots
fired. Suspect down.
Police! Get on
the fucking ground!
What?!
(GUN FIRES)
OFFICER MAYO: FBI!
Clear?
Hello?
This is Federal Agent
Mayo. Is anyone home?
(GENTLE MUSIC)
Kitchen.
Here. All right.
Clear.
Officer Bishop?
Stay close.
FBI.
Stay on it.
Clear.
(UPBEAT ROCK MUSIC)
Ready.
- Cover me.
- Mm-hm.
On three.
One.
Two.
Three.
(DOOR CLACKS)
We got a body!
(CHASE GASPS)
Where's Officer Bishop?!
I don't know.
Where is he, you little shit?!
God dammit.
(GENTLE MUSIC)
(DOOR KNOCKING)
(DOOR CLACKS)
ALBERT: What
do you want, man?
Sir, I want you and
your family to know
exactly what
happened that night.
Well, if you're
here for forgiveness,
I think it's best you leave.
No, that's not my
intention at all.
Andre was a better son than
I could've ever asked for,
and you took him,
you took him from us.
You know what it's like raising
a son to fear the people
who are supposed to protect him?
You know what it's like to
live with that fear? Huh?
ROSIE: Papa Al?
Who's at the door?
Oh, it's the cop.
He wants to tell
us what happened,
tell us how he killed my son.
Ain't that what you wanna do?
Papa Al?
(ROSIE SIGHS)
Let him in.
(DOOR CREAKS)
(DOOR THUDS)
BISHOP: And when Andre
opened the door that night
and saw me, I panicked.
I saw his jersey
and his tattoos,
and he had a broken
bottle in his hand.
I was scared.
I judged what I
saw and I shot him
- on his way to the trash.
- Oh!
- Just stop it.
- Come on.
Let's go, let's go.
Come on, let's get some air.
Come on, now.
I just wanted you
to know the truth.
Your husband was a good man.
I took his life.
And I know there's nothing
nothing I can do
to bring him back.
And I'm so sorry for that.
Mm.
Andre is gone
because of you.
You killed my husband.
And now, you just walk
in here and apologize,
and expect for
everything to be over?
Why is it always us?
What do you see
when you look at us?
I mean, it's not anything new.
But everyone always wants us
to accept your
apologies and move on.
I won't do it.
(SOMBER MUSIC)
I'm sorry, Sergeant.
I fucked up.
Glad you called.
People of the State of
California versus William Bishop.
Case number BA19107.
The matter is here
for arraignment.
All parties are present.
I've reviewed the
evidence in this case
as well as the obstruction
of justice charge
against Chase Miller.
Absolutely senseless.
Tragic.
These are the words
that come to mind
on a case the details of which
I've never seen this before.
Will the defendant please rise?
Mr. Bishop, your attorney has
indicated it is your intention
to enter into a not guilty plea
to count one of this complaint,
voluntary manslaughter,
a violation of Penal Code
section 192, subsection A.
Correct?
MR. SMITH: Yes.
JUDGE: Is that
correct, Mr. Bishop?
No. No, Your Honor.
Counsel, what's going on here
Your honor, may I have a
moment to speak with my client?
JUDGE: Yes.
You can't do this.
You need to plead not guilty.
Do you understand the risk
you're putting on the department?
This is a complicated case.
No jury will find you guilty.
- I made up my mind.
- Your honor,
if we could have a short recess?
I would like to
speak with my client.
Your honor, I'm guilty
of the charges against me.
Mr. Bishop, sir, this
is your arraignment.
It's unheard of to enter into
a guilty plea at this time.
Are you sure that's what
you want to do, sir?
Yes, Your Honor.
Mr. Bishop, do you
waive and give up
your right to a jury trial,
the right to confront and
cross-examine witnesses,
and to present evidence and
testimony on your own behalf?
Yes, I give up my
right, Your Honor.
Let the record reflect
that the defendant willingly,
knowingly, and
understandably has entered
into a plea of guilty to
the charge of manslaughter.
The clerk will have
him initial and sign
a formal plea agreement.
Counsel, do you waive
time for sentencing?
MR. SMITH: Yes, Your Honor.
Formal sentencing will be
held one week from today.
Mr. Bishop, your OR
status is hereby revoked.
Bailiff, he is to be remanded
into custody forthwith.
We're done here.
Court's adjourned.
(GAVEL CLACKS)
You just hung yourself
and the department. Nice.
♪ We'll find a way to go back ♪
♪ We'll find a way home ♪
♪ If you leave me
when I'm down ♪
♪ I'll make it up
to you somehow ♪
♪ 'Cause we're only as good
as we let ourselves be ♪
WILKINS: Bishop.
I'm floored. I'm floored.
Listen, just talk to Jan.
You can't just
leave her like this.
I don't know
what to say to her.
She still loves you.
Thank you.
♪ We'll be all right ♪
I'm sorry.
This is the right thing.
♪ I'll make it up
to you somehow ♪
I love you.
JAN: Oh, god.
(HANDCUFFS CLICKING)
♪ Only as high as I
let myself to find ♪
♪ Hoping tomorrow comes ♪
♪ And we'll be all right ♪
(LIVELY MUSIC)
Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
♪ And I say, when was the
last time someone ever said ♪
♪ That you were special
and you were blessed ♪
♪ The streets that I was raised
in, you could do no harm ♪
♪ Be unarmed and
cops would shoot ♪
♪ Before they
reached for tasers ♪
♪ You'd be good if you walk
among us & speak the language ♪
♪ Love always shines every
time, remember smile, LASERS ♪
♪ But if these things
will change up ♪
♪ And if my team's in danger ♪
♪ I will act a fool,
bleed black and blue ♪
♪ But all I'll
see is strangers ♪
♪ Tell me what my
life is worth ♪
♪ Get shot or we
get beat to death ♪
♪ Nigga with an attitude,
middle finger to the feds ♪
♪ Yeah, I do this for Oakland,
Cali, and Oscar Grant ♪
♪ It takes a public enemy
to fight the power ♪
♪ It takes a nation of
millions to hold us back ♪
♪ In fact, we hella live,
just not on your screen ♪
♪ 'Cause they tell us the
revolution will not be televised ♪
♪ But they won't tell us why ♪
♪ I'm so glad ♪
♪ So when was the last
time someone ever said ♪
♪ That you were special
and you were blessed ♪
♪ I hope that when you
cry, somebody's there ♪
♪ And I hope that when you die ♪
♪ Somebody cares ♪
♪ And I'm so glad ♪
♪ There is just no
country for old men ♪
♪ Where brothers feel
comfortable in they own skin ♪
♪ This here ain't gravy, nigga ♪
♪ 'Cause in my city, if them
boys need someone to harass ♪
♪ I'll fit the description ♪
♪ Where I'm from, we don't call
'em, hate when they show up ♪
♪ One shot make you forget ♪
♪ What you'd wanna
be when you grow up ♪
♪ Resisting arrest is
what they call it ♪
♪ Another family
buries a brother ♪
♪ Another girl grows
up without a father ♪
♪ It's my society ♪
♪ Cops that shoot blacks
as routine for notoriety ♪
♪ The media don't cover that ♪
♪ Judge will find 'em innocent,
the system is against us ♪
♪ Imagine being a victim,
be considered the problem ♪
♪ The product of
where I came from ♪
♪ So even if we came up,
we're seen as damn crooks ♪
♪ Sam Cooke until
the change comes ♪
♪ Trigger happy police,
hate instead of embrace us ♪
♪ But trouble
don't last always ♪
♪ That's what I pray for ♪
♪ And I'm so glad ♪
♪ So when was the last
time someone ever said ♪
♪ That you were special
and you were blessed ♪
♪ I hope that when you
cry, somebody's there ♪
♪ And I hope that when you die ♪
♪ Somebody cares ♪
♪ And I'm so glad ♪
♪ Eh eh eh ♪
♪ Oh oh ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Mm ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Oh oh ♪
♪ Oh oh oh ♪
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
♪ Whoa ♪
♪ Oh, na na na ♪
♪ Na na na, no ♪
♪ Oh, no, no, it won't last ♪
♪ No, no, it won't last ♪
♪ Oh, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no ♪
♪ And I'm so glad ♪
♪ So when was the last
time someone ever said ♪
♪ That you were special
and you were blessed ♪
♪ I hope that when you
cry, somebody's there ♪
♪ And I hope that when you die ♪
♪ Somebody cares ♪
♪ And I'm so glad ♪
♪ Eh eh eh ♪
♪ I'm so glad ♪
♪ No, it won't last ♪
♪ It won't ever last ♪
♪ Oh, no, no ♪
♪ Oh ♪
(SINGER VOCALIZING)
♪ Oh oh ♪
♪ Oh oh oh ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Hey, yeah ♪
♪ Whoa ♪
♪ Hey hey ♪
♪ Na na na na na na ♪
(SINGER VOCALIZING)
♪ Oh oh oh ♪