( music playing )
( cell door clanking )
( man speaking
indistinctly )
( overlapping chatter )
( phone dialing )
Hello. Dr. Arlen?
It's Albert,
Albert De Salvo.
I must say I didn't
expect to hear from you.
How have you been?
Actually,
I've been doing well.
You know, Walpole...
ain't so bad after all.
Well, I'm very happy
to hear that.
But listen.
If you wouldn't mind
relieving me
of my curiosity,
why are you
calling me?
I got some things I want
to get off my chest.
Well, I'm sure they
have mental health
professionals there
who can help you.
This is different.
I want to tell the truth
about the Boston
Strangler murders.
I see.
Look, Albert,
let's not do this
over the phone,
all right?
I'll arrange
to meet you
at 9:00 A.M.
tomorrow morning.
I'll set up a private
therapy room.
We can talk there.
That'd be great.
Thanks, Doc.
Hey, thanks a lot, huh?
( piano music playing )
Now, now.
That's enough
for now.
Come on, Jennifer.
Don't stop me now.
- I'm begging you.
- It's late.
I got to get up early.
- Just a while longer.
- ( laughs )
Stop your groveling,
Romeo.
It don't look
so sexy on you.
You're right.
I shall be like a Knight
of the Round Table
and ride off
into the cold, dark night.
Farewell, young maiden.
( laughs )
You okay?
Well, if I'm not,
can I come in?
Send the king my best.
- ( car horn honks )
- ( motorcycle passes )
( laughs )
Mrs. Jennifer Foster.
Mrs. Jennifer
Mitchum-Foster.
( laughs )
Nah, too long.
Jennifer Foster.
Jen Foster.
Mrs. Jennifer Foster.
( laughs )
( gasps )
Such a klutz.
( gasping )
No. Stop.
Mrs. Jennifer Foster.
( sobbing )
No. No.
( grunts )
( gagging )
( police radio chatter )
Captain, would you
look at this?
A front-page guide
to the Strangler murders
right there
in black and white
for every criminal
in Boston to read.
Why don't we just hand
the investigation over
to Ms. Fineman?
It's my fault.
I let out
the information.
I'm sorry, John.
I just been under
all sorts of pressure
to get this case solved.
Winfield is threatening
to take over
not just our department,
but every department
in the county.
So I figured,
what the hell,
why not get
everybody involved?
Yeah, but you know
what you done, Cap?
You compromised
my entire investigation.
Investigation, John?
We've got
no investigation.
We've got no fingerprints,
no witnesses,
- nothing!
- ( knock on door )
Captain Parker,
lineup's set.
They're waiting on you,
Detective Marsden.
Let's just
get this over with.
All right.
Don't be scared.
Over here.
It's all right.
He can't see you.
Okay.
Woman:
Just take your time.
( no audible dialogue )
The joker with
the sunglasses
is Albert De Salvo.
Couple years ago,
he was charged
with assault,
spent 11 months
at Middlesex
before they let him
go on parole.
Who's the serious one
on the end?
Frank Asarian.
I'm really surprised he's
even out on the streets.
He's got a record
a mile long.
That's... it's him on...
he's over there.
He's on the far right.
He's on the end.
It's him. That's him.
- And, oh, my God, it's...
- Make sure.
He grabbed me.
He grabbed me,
and he punched me
across the face.
I could never
forget his face.
I'll never forget
his face.
Look. He even looks
like a criminal.
Where are you?
I know you in there.
Look at him.
I hope he burns in hell.
That's fine.
I'm going to come back
for you.
- Yeah.
- You know that?
- Get over here.
- Where's my lawyer?
Have a seat, fellas.
Finish filling out
your paperwork,
and you're
free to go.
And what if
I can't read?
Sir, if you need help,
we'll find you
an assistant.
Yeah, I'd rather
you assist me.
- I'm sure you would.
- ( laughs )
What are you
looking at, penguin?
What,
he's a fucking penguin,
walking around
in suit and tie.
That's a tuxedo,
asshole.
What?
It's a tuxedo.
Penguins always look
like they have
tuxedos on, asshole.
You trying to make
an ass of me?
Don't you think
I know that?
It's a literal-
fucking-ation.
I didn't mean nothing
of it, all right?
Albert:
It makes no difference.
Got that burn
in my stomach.
Got to find some food,
if you know what I mean.
You have a good one.
Your eyes forward,
Asarian.
Keep moving.
What are you
looking at?
Keep moving.
Woman:
You're not even done.
Albert:
Someone stole
my sunglasses.
I don't care about that.
You gotta finish
your paperwork.
Come home and help me
do it, will you?
Ah, jeez.
( bells tolling )
Hi, Mary Beth.
Oh, hi, girls.
How are you?
Good.
( whistles a tune )
- Hey, beautiful day, huh?
- Hi. Yeah.
Hey, I got
a new office here
on campus.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
I been meaning
to introduce myself,
but I just
been really busy
with the agency.
- Agency?
- Yeah.
Things are
easing up a bit
ever since
Jackie took over
the White House.
They been making me
search for girls who
look just like her.
You're in
the fashion business?
You could say that.
I'm a modeling scout.
Modeling scout?
Yeah. You know,
I find girls.
I measure 'em,
I photograph 'em,
and then I introduce
'em to the agency.
Oh. Sounds interesting.
You know,
now that I have
a moment alone with you,
you do sort of have
the type of build
the agency's looking for.
What size are you?
Thanks.
Actually, I'm a four.
No frigging way.
You're not a four.
Yes, I am.
( scoffs )
I got to get to work.
- ( laughs )
- Wait.
You can measure me,
and I'll
prove it to you.
What, you'll prove it
to me, eh?
Yeah.
Well, it's
a cutthroat industry.
You sure
you can handle that?
Don't know
if I don't try.
Well, that's true.
- Yeah.
- Uh...
Oh, sorry.
Susan.
Susan. Why don't you
follow me to my office?
You know,
on second thought,
it's probably not
a good idea, you know,
getting measured in
a strange man's office.
Maybe another time, huh?
Well, hey...
follow me.
My room's
just upstairs.
Come on.
- You sure?
- Yeah, come on.
Measure me upstairs.
Okay. I got
a few minutes.
- Let's make it fast, huh?
- Okay.
It's too beautiful
outside, right?
Susan: Yeah.
So what agency did you
say you're from?
The Black and White
Modeling Agency.
It's downtown.
I'll give you my card.
How much does it pay
if they accept me?
$40 an hour.
$40 an hour?
- Mm-hmm.
- Are you kidding me?
I could pay
my entire tuition
at that rate.
$40 is just
for the modeling in town.
They pay you more if they
fly you out of town,
plus they pay
all your expenses.
- Really?
- Mm-hmm. Sure, yeah.
Lots of girls fly
back and forth to Paris
on a regular basis.
- Paris?
- Mm-hmm.
Oh.
( sighs )
Here's my apartment.
Okay.
( giggles )
Do you mind?
No, not at all.
34 inches.
Really? I thought
I was 32 inches.
Nah, you're a...
you're a 34.
( giggles ) Well,
what's my cup size?
How do you
measure that?
Well, there's no,
you know,
physical measurement
for cup size.
You have to...
well, you know,
by hand.
Yeah?
You're the professional.
( laughs )
To get an accurate
measurement,
I have to...
Oh, yeah. Okay.
( laughs )
You have
a gentle touch.
Well?
What's my cup size?
Just a moment.
You really
should know by now.
Sorry.
You're a "C" cup,
definitely a "C" cup.
What did you say
your name was?
Oh, it's Johnson.
It's Mr. Johnson.
You can call me Gary.
And where's the agency?
What's the address?
It's downtown,
71st Street, 853.
Well, wouldn't
the address
be in the 70s?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, 753.
You know, I'm sure you're
a good student and all,
but maybe, you know,
modeling's just
not for you.
Maybe you're just
not cut out for it.
Maybe you're not really
a modeling agent.
- Oh, yeah?
- Yeah.
I think you
should go now.
- Really?
- In fact,
maybe I should
just go ahead
and call the cops.
You're not
going to do that.
- ( gasps )
- You're not going anywhere.
- Wait. ( sobbing )
You know, the agency
doesn't like girls
who talk back, you know.
They put girls like you
right back on a plane
and send you
where you came from.
Oh, where you think
you're going, huh?
I know there's
no way out of here.
What are you going
to do, jump? Huh?
What, do you got wings?
My boyfriend'll
be here any minute.
( laughs )
When I was
stationed in Germany,
I used to hear
that one all the time.
Only, it was in German.
( speaking German )
Shut the fuck up.
( laughs )
There's money
in my dresser.
You can
have it all.
Top drawer.
Left side.
( sobbing )
Just please
go away!
Please just
leave me alone.
Why don't you go ahead
and do me a favor
and come on
on out of there
so I don't have
to come get you, huh?
Open the door.
( moans )
Open the fucking door.
( scream echoing )
Open the fucking door,
bitch!
Open the fucking door!
- Fucking whore!
- ( Susan screams )
( sirens blaring )
( clears throat )
Would have been here
an hour ago.
Traffic was all backed up
on Common Avenue.
Ah, it's all right.
Been upstairs?
- Yeah, I been up there.
- How's it look?
It's not
a pretty picture.
You'll see.
- What's up, guys?
- Hey, John. How are you?
Hey, John. Samans,
Beverly Samans,
early 20s.
This one is
not strangled,
even though
the stocking is up
around her neck.
She was stabbed
in the neck.
Well, that's creative.
And the killer
left her body
splayed out for all
the world to see,
dress pulled up,
legs wide open.
Mr. Marsden.
( chuckles )
When are you going
to catch the Strangler?
Stranglers.
There's clearly
more than one man
at work here.
And how can you be
so sure of that, John?
How can you be so sure
it's just one man?
How long have you been
doing this, John, huh?
It's called M.O....
sexual assault,
strangled by stockings,
break-ins,
no witnesses,
et cetera,
et cetera, et cetera.
I can keep going, John.
Well, forgive me,
Mr. Winfield,
but his M.O.
isn't that clear.
The first five
were elderly.
The sixth was
young and black.
- Mary Brown and now...
- Beverly Samans.
Beverly Samans, it appears,
were stabbed to death.
Doesn't sound like
one particular M.O.
to me.
John, I need you
to listen to me,
because I'm trying to be
painfully
crystal clear to you
so I can get through
that thick skull of yours.
( elevator dings )
Just a second, guys.
I'm running
for a Senate seat
next year, John,
and the last thing
I need
is a crime-happy dick
hot-bopping around town,
telling everyone
that there are
multiple murderers
running rampant
in my streets.
The city's position
is that there's
just one,
just one...
and I intend
to catch this
one monster
and send his ass
so deep in jail,
the devil himself
can't find him.
Therefore,
my city will be happy
about life again.
You understand me,
John?
You can have
any theory that you want.
The fact is you
got no jurisdiction
over my department,
and my department
will continue
the search
for multiple killers.
You trying
to oppose me, John?
I don't work
for you, Art.
I work for the people.
You know, it's amazing
you've lasted this long.
Apparently you have
someone taking care
of you on the force.
'Cause I've never seen
a more naive detective.
Enough of this nonsense.
( baby crying )
Good day,
Mrs. Lucino.
Why, thank you, Albert.
How's that beautiful wife
of yours?
She's doing okay,
if you mean
adjusting and all.
Thanks for asking,
huh?
You know,
us Italians and Germans
were partners in the war.
It's a good match,
makes for beautiful kids.
Thank you, Mrs. Lucino.
Michael and Judy
certainly are beautiful.
But, you know,
the war's been over
for almost 20 years
now, you know?
I mean,
we may be Italian,
but always be proud
to be an American.
Hey, I didn't join
the military to fight
for Mussolini
or the Nazis,
for that matter.
Of course, Albert.
You're a decent young man.
See you on Sunday?
Yes, ma'am. Hey...
be careful
out there, huh?
- That Boston Strangler...
- Don't worry.
I've got protection.
- Certainly do.
- ( laughs )
Good day,
Mrs. Lucino.
You too.
Claudia?
Claudia, where are you?
Claudi...
Claudia?
Michael?
Where are you?
Where the fuck are you?
Claudia?
Michael? Judy?
Where are the kids?
They're
at your mother's house.
Don't you
remember anything?
I brought you
some flowers
and chocolates.
That was Munich,
Albert.
This is Boston.
The romance is over.
Be a man.
I am a man.
No, Albert.
You are not a man
until you can act
like a responsible
husband and father.
Claudia, I go
to work every day
to bring home
money for you
and the kids, right?
Half of the time you
tell me you're at work,
you're having a beer
at the bar,
or worse, you're
screwing other women.
Ah, Claudia,
come on now.
Albert,
don't you realize
that I can feed
the children
breakfast, lunch,
and dinner
for the price
of all your beer?
Baby, please, huh?
I swear to God
I can make it better.
I swear to God.
When, Albert?
When?
You dragged me
all the way across
the Atlantic Ocean.
Why would you
do that?
So you
could be a bum?
- Albert.
- Hmm?
Do you remember
the promise
that you told me
back in Germany?
- Mm-hmm.
- That you told my parents?
Mm-hmm.
I promise, baby.
- Albert.
- Mmm.
Albert.
Albert!
Stop it.
- ( moaning )
- ( crying )
- Albert!
- What?
- Stop it!
- ( grunts )
I got needs!
I'm a fucking man!
You're my wife!
Fuck you.
Don't you ever
touch me again.
Is this the treatment
I get for being a man?
I got fucking needs,
damn it!
Again, different knot.
- You sure about that?
- Positive.
The first five
were tied into a bow.
This one was tied
into a knot first.
Then the bow was tied.
And while we're
scratching our asses,
there are women dying
all over the city.
And there's nothing
we can do about it.
There is,
if I can help it.
Hey, Captain,
hand me those tweezers,
will you?
Thanks.
What are you
going to do with that?
This is evidence,
Captain.
I'm going
to save it.
Maybe we can
match it up
to the killer
under a microscope.
Not in my lifetime.
Anything?
Do we have anything?
Not a thing, sir.
There was not
a fingerprint anywhere
in this apartment.
Witnesses?
Not a one.
As far
as I can tell,
nobody heard
or saw anything.
Family been notified?
Yes, they have.
Find out if she had
any ongoing disputes.
Find every friend
and family member
and get 'em
down to the precinct
for questioning.
Don't you worry,
sweetheart.
We're going
to figure this out
if it's
the last thing we do.
John, maybe we
should let forensics
come in, do their thing,
and why don't you head
back to the office?
I don't need to head back
to the damned office.
You know,
that attitude
is the reason
we can't find
these girls'
killers.
Everybody wants this
to just go away,
sweep it
under the carpet.
Well, it's not
going away.
It's not going away,
'cause the killer
isn't just
going to stop.
People kill
each other.
I mean, all we are
is animals
in a fucking
suit and a tie,
no difference,
and all
of you detectives
need to think
about why you're
on the force.
What about you,
Spinelli?
Why are you here?
What's motivating you?
What motivates me?
( snorts )
Job stability.
There it is.
It ain't about
catching the bad guy
any more than it was
when my father
was a cop.
It's about
job stability.
We're all
just trying to provide
for our families here,
every one of us.
Yeah, yeah. Well,
you know what, Joe?
Maybe you should have
been a bricklayer,
'cause they get
great fucking benefits.
- Oh, get...
- Hey, hey, hey.
Hey, John. John.
Try that again,
I'm going to make sure
you're cleaning
convicts' cells
for the rest of your
career. You got me?
You got me, Joe?
( train horn blowing )
♪ Just a moment, sir ♪
♪ A moment of your time ♪
♪ Been dreaming of you ♪
♪ Is that such a crime? ♪
♪ I know that
I'm foolish... ♪
- ( hair dryer whirring )
- ♪ To look back on ♪
♪ Our romance
that ended so wrong ♪
♪ But I can't forget
your touch ♪
♪ Or that crazy smile
that meant so much ♪
♪ All of you that's here ♪
- ♪ Are wishes... ♪
- ( hair dryer stops )
Hello.
♪ They're so easy
to make... ♪
Mark?
Is that you, honey?
I don't remember
giving you a key.
♪ Come true ♪
♪ Yes, wishes... ♪
Mark?
Honey?
♪ I had you instead ♪
- ♪ Of my wishes... ♪
- Mark, this isn't funny.
( gasps )
Oh, my God. What...
Stop. Please.
( grunts )
Shh.
If you only
make a sound,
I'm going to tear out
your tongue,
and you will
never speak again.
Do you understand?
Good.
Now, I wasn't intending
on being so rough and all,
but seeing
you is a fighter,
I'm going to have
to make sure
you ain't capable
of using those hands.
( both grunting )
No.
( sniffs )
Oh, you smell good.
No. Please stop.
That was
the wrong decision.
( gasping )
No.
No, stop, please.
I was going
to make love to you.
♪ They're so easy to make ♪
♪ Yet so hard ♪
♪ To make come true ♪
♪ Yes, wishes ♪
♪ If only I had ♪
♪ You instead ♪
♪ Of my wishes... ♪
If you only
just behaved.
♪ But the only wish
I have ♪
♪ Is you. ♪
( police radio chatter )
( sirens blaring )
Winfield is calling it
the seventh one.
Strangler?
It's got all
the earmarkings.
Matches the M.O.,
but on close
inspection,
there are
some incongruities.
Really?
Like what?
John,
she's strangled
with the stocking,
all right,
but that bow is not tied
like we'd expect.
It's a copycat.
The first five were killed
by the same guy.
Sophie Clark
and this girl
were killed
by jagoffs who actually
read the papers.
Woman:
New Year's Eve.
At least we know
the Strangler doesn't
take holidays off.
Well, technically
it's not a holiday
until tomorrow.
Technically
it is tomorrow.
Hold on.
Who are you?
And how the hell
did you get access
to my crime scene?
I'm Jana Fineman.
I'm with "The Record."
Oh, you're
with "The Record."
You're a reporter.
We prefer
to think of ourselves
as public disseminators.
It's our duty
to inform the public.
Well, you know what?
I'd prefer to think of you
as somebody who's gone.
Donovan, get her
out of my face.
Detective Marsden,
would you mind
commenting on why,
after seven murders,
you have no leads,
no witness,
no evidence.
How do you know
what evidence we got?
All right?
The department is
not in the habit
of sharing details
on investigations
with the papers, miss.
Our sources
are telling us
that you have
absolutely nothing
to go on.
I don't give a damn
about your sources.
Get her out.
She's going. She's going.
She's almost gone.
She's gone.
Radio: Fellow citizens
of the Commonwealth
of Massachusetts,
someone please
call in to my show.
I want to hear from you.
Someone tell me what is
going on in this town.
Why can't the cops
find this guy?
He's strangling women
all over town.
The list,
it's just despicable.
Anna Slessers,
she's 55 years old.
She was the first to die.
She was strangled with
the cord of her bathrobe,
her very own bathrobe,
around her neck,
on June 14, 1962.
A nylon stocking was used
to kill 68-year-old
Nina Nichols on June 30,
and Helen Blake, age 65,
was found the same day.
- A stock...
- ( radio clicks )
How was the party?
It'd have been
a lot better if you
had been there.
You'll catch him, John.
Don't lose focus.
I can't catch "him."
Of course you can.
You're the top detective
on the force.
It's not that I don't
believe in myself, babe.
I can't catch "him,"
'cause I don't think
it's one man.
The M.O.
changed drastically
between Jane Sullivan
and Sophie Parker.
Jane was 67.
Sophie was 19.
But they were
all strangled.
The first five
were the same guy,
but I'm 100% sure
that he stopped.
The last two
were copycats.
Basically the papers
have printed
a how-to book on
the Boston Strangler.
"Just follow
these instructions,
and you too can
be the Strangler."
Have you told anyone else
how you feel?
Michelle, this is
not how I feel.
John, I'm not
questioning you.
Calm down.
This is your wife
you're talking to here.
Sorry, babe.
I'm a bit tense.
Yeah, no kidding.
This is political.
The papers, the public,
the mayor,
and the attorney general
all want it
to be one man.
Nobody wants to hear
there's a...
( chuckles )
there's murderers
running rampant
out there.
Well, we can't
solve anything tonight,
so why don't you...
you just focus
on investigating me, huh?
( door closes )
( overlapping
conversations )
Hey, why don't you
get on over there?
All right.
All right, simmer down.
( crowd murmurs )
Look, I know it's odd
for all of us to be
here in the same room,
but perhaps Mr. Winfield
can enlighten us.
Winfield:
Morning, gentlemen.
Let's try and act
like professionals.
Now, as you all know,
there's been
12 Strangler murders
without any real leads.
Now, I know you all
have been working
very hard
investigating
your cases,
but it's simply
not working.
I've got so much
pressure up my ass,
I'm about to crap
out of my mouth.
So I have devised a way
to give us a chance
to catch
this murdering bastard.
As of today,
the entire
Boston Strangler case
will be handled
by a new bureau of
the commonwealth.
This bureau will be called
the Strangler Bureau.
Every department...
and I mean
every department...
will be
working together...
providing the bureau
with every shred
of evidence,
witness testimony,
et cetera.
The head of this
new bureau will be...
Mr. Fred Addison.
What? Addison?
Are you kidding?
What is this,
a joke or something?
What does he know
about law enforcement?
Huh? Has he ever
been on the street?
No offense,
Mr. Addison,
but what the hell
does he know about
police business?
Sergeant Donnely,
are you questioning
my judgment?
Do I look
like a joke to you?
I suggest you put
a sock in it right here
and right now,
or you will be at home
with your wife,
baking cookies
and doing laundry.
- You understand me?
- Yes, sir.
Does this look like
a fucking classroom
to you, Mr. Smith?
Put your hand down.
No questions
will be answered
until I'm finished.
Now, I will tie
your hands to your belt,
you try
that shit again.
Also leading this bureau
will be Detective
Phillip Bloom,
Special Officer
John Marsden
of the Boston State Police,
and Andrew Tuney
of the Mass State.
Alongside
these fine gentlemen
will be a medical advisory
made up of experts
from around the state.
Finally...
the press
will be informed
of a $10,000 reward
for any information
leading to the capture
of the Strangler.
You all look as if
you want to kill me.
You have any questions,
Mr. Addison will take them.
He's your man.
I just delivered
the message.
Fred.
Now, gentlemen,
we all have to work
together on this,
and we will explore
every option possible
to gather as much
information as we can
to capture this criminal.
Now, I'd like you all
to meet me back here today
at precisely 2:00 P.M.
to discuss further details.
Good morning.
2:00?
All right, ladies,
you heard him.
- Yeah, great.
- See you back here at 2:00.
See you later.
Why don't you go
and see if he's
got everything.
Look, we'll try
to keep you up to speed
here on this.
I'm sorry about that.
John, maybe
we can have a... yeah,
we need to have a talk.
Your office or mine?
Oh, whoa.
- You all right?
- Yep. Yeah.
Here it is, Mr. Addison,
all 37,000 pages.
Well done, Richie.
I would imagine
that everything is collated
and labeled
to my exact specifications.
You betcha.
And the computer folks
have their copy?
Yes, sir.
Delivered it
this morning.
37,000 pages?
Not 370?
That's right,
Mr. Marsden.
This is every single
bit of information
about the cases
organized into
one master book.
And the scientists
over at MIT have been
gracious enough
to help compile all
of the information
on their
mainframe computers.
Computer? Whoa.
What the hell
are you going to do
with a computer?
Organization,
Mr. Marsden,
organization.
Well, Mr. Addison,
takes a hell of a lot
more than computers
and organization
to solve a case.
Well, whatever it takes,
Mr. Marsden,
you haven't found it,
have you?
How the hell
would you know?
Frigging Poindexter.
Well, it looks like MIT's
going to be solving
all our cases.
( chuckles )
37,000 pages.
( laughs )
- No, no, don't.
- No, no, no.
It's a one-way street.
You can't...
They'll never see me
on a one-way street.
- ( siren blaring )
- ...on a one-way street.
Shut up! Shut up!
Ah, this fucking...
Albert, you can't
go down this way!
- It's a one-way street.
They'll never know I went
on a one-way street.
- Shut up.
- What are you doing?
Albert, you're taking
our lives in your hands.
- Pull over!
- ( car horns honking )
You could kill us
all, Albert.
- Michael, tell him...
- Shut up!
Just shut the hell up,
Sondra! Shut up!
- Johnson. Mr. Johnson.
- Paris?
I done some bad things, man.
I got some problems.
What kind of bad things?
You've got the cops
after you.
Some fucking problems
with the broads.
You know that.
Susan: You're in
the fashion business?
I made some mistakes,
okay, Mike? You just...
- What's... oh, my God!
- ( crashes )
Oh, shit!
Shit, I'm sorry, guys.
Oh, fuck.
God, I'm a prick.
I'm an asshole.
Slow down. It's fine.
Come on, Sondra,
let's get out of here.
No, no.
Where you guys going?
- Where you going?
- Albert.
Albert, what did
you do, Albert?
- Buddy, don't you go anywhere.
- You're arguing with them.
- Don't you go anywhere!
- What did you do?
- Mikey!
- You're bleeding.
What have you
done, Albert?
Now look what you
gone and done.
You're a mental case,
Albert De Salvo.
- A mental case!
- ( sirens blaring )
Claudia, don't you
go anywhere!
- Don't you leave me!
- I can't do it, Albert.
Don't you
fucking leave me!
I've had enough of this.
I'm sick of this.
Sondra:
I don't want to be here
when the cops get here.
- Just give yourself up.
- Mikey.
Please, come on,
Albert.
- Please. I'm sorry, Mike.
- What'd you do?
- What'd you do?!
- Did some bad shit, man.
You're innocent
till proven guilty, right?
You get... they got
nothing on you, right?
They're coming right now.
I'm in trouble.
- Turn yourself in.
- Mikey!
What am I gonna do?
Mikey!
Come on,
just turn yourself in.
- But... what are you doing?
- Please, Albert.
- Please. Just please.
- I can't do it!
What am I gonna do?
Mikey!
Come on,
just turn yourself in.
Officer on bullhorn:
We have you surrounded.
Turn off the ignition
and step out of the car.
- What'd you do?
- Put your hands up...
Shit, get out of here!
Go! Go! Go!
- You cannot get away.
- ( engine sputtering )
You are under arrest,
Mr. De Salvo. Please...
God damn it! Start,
you fucking thing!
Damn it!
Keep looking
straight ahead,
Mr. De Salvo.
I'm looking.
So this is
the loony bin, eh?
It ain't so bad.
Go faster, Mr. De Salvo.
All right, all right.
So where do they keep
the broads in this joint?
( laughs )
Just keep walking.
Hey, hey, how long
this guy been in here?
Ain't none
of your business.
All right. Just asking.
I thought I said
no roommates.
Shit.
You better clean up
in that sink over there.
Nice to meet you
too.
Gorgeous, huh?
Hey...
I know you.
Nah, you don't know me.
( chuckles )
Nah, I know you.
I never forget a face.
Yeah?
I don't either, and...
you don't look
too familiar to me.
That's because you
ain't paying attention.
You can't remember nothing
if you ain't watching.
February of last year.
Yeah, that's it.
You're... you're
the little joker
in the lineup.
I ain't ever been
in a lineup.
Sure, you have.
Bitch chose me...
thought I was
the Boston fucking
Strangler or something.
Imagine that,
a nice guy like me,
the Boston Strangler.
Now wait a minute, now.
Yeah, now I remember.
Yeah, that's right.
Man, was I glad
she chose you.
When I was walking out
of the jail that day,
I met this little honey,
and... ( sighs )
I'm just saying.
( laughs )
I'm really happy
for you.
Ah, no offense. I don't
mean no disrespect.
I'm just saying,
you know.
Those were some
serious charges, huh?
You're telling me.
How'd you beat the rap?
Had a winning ticket
on a horse at a track,
perfect alibi.
Sure, yeah.
It's perfect.
So which bed is mine?
Don't bother me.
I don't sleep
in the bed.
Yeah, where do you sleep?
Sleep with the fish?
( laughs )
I don't
really sleep much.
And when I do...
I sleep
on the floor.
Hey, wait.
What is that,
some Buddhist shit, huh?
Hey, hey.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Nah.
- ( pats back )
- Bad back.
( laughs )
I see.
So...
what are you
in here for?
Why are you in here, Al?
How do you know my name?
Memorized it.
Where?
From the lineup card.
From a year ago?
Come on.
I ain't that smart, Al.
You see, while I was
at the police station,
I stole the lineup card,
just in case my alibi
didn't hold up,
'cause if
it didn't hold up,
I was going to make up
some cockamamie story
about it being
one of youse.
Ah, that's
frigging brilliant.
You're like your own...
very own lawyer, huh?
What, you study law?
What were you,
a copper?
Nah.
Just always
thinking, you know?
Can never
stop thinking.
You got to think
like a rat
if you want to stay
out of shit holes
like this.
What are you
in here for, anyway?
I shot a guy...
six times in the head
point-blank.
Holy shit.
For what?
Before that...
I stabbed him
five times.
Spoke to your grandmother
yesterday.
No, I don't want to go.
No, not you.
Winnie.
I'm not going to talk
about this any further.
You're not going
to Marianne's party.
I don't care
what you say.
- I said I'm going.
- You're not going.
I don't like
that woman's morals.
Why? It's just a party.
You can't go.
When I talk to your father,
you're gonna find out
how you're not gonna go
anywhere for two years.
- Get in the car.
- Fine.
Ma, what's happening?
- I don't know.
- That guy's bleeding.
- Ma, go help him.
- Oh, my God.
( groaning )
Get on your knees.
Mom, go. Go.
- Stay calm. Stay calm.
- But he has a gun.
- Don't look, honey.
- Come on.
Beg me for your life.
Beg me. Beg me
not to shoot you.
On your knees.
Don't kill me.
Please don't kill me.
Take the money.
Don't kill me.
( sobbing )
No.
Lock your door.
That's much better,
much better.
Unfortunately,
beggars
can't be choosers.
No. No.
( wails )
- Come on! Oh, my God!
- My God!
- Ma, he shot him.
- Mom, go, please.
- ( engine sputters )
- Mom, what the hell?
- Stay calm.
- Let's go. Please.
- It's okay.
We're getting
out of here.
- He's coming.
- ( screaming )
Come on. Mom, go.
- ( sobbing )
- Oh, no. Please, God.
( gun clicks )
Frank:
He tried to be a hero.
I was just
robbing the store.
That damn clerk
wouldn't open up
the register.
So you just stabbed him?
You're damn right I did.
What, you telling me
you never killed nobody?
I mean, not really.
What does that mean?
What do you mean,
"not really"?
Well, there was
this one woman,
you know, and I...
I think I scared her,
you know. She...
I think she
had a heart attack
right there.
- She dropped dead.
- ( laughs )
( laughs )
That ain't murder.
You're funny.
Ah, I mean, you know,
I'm just saying if I
hadn't snuck up on her,
well, she'd still
be going to church
this Sunday, you know.
I mean, I didn't call
an ambulance or anything,
so I figured
I killed her.
( scoffs )
And that's why they
locked you up?
Nah.
What for?
I like the broads,
you know?
Frank:
Tell me who doesn't
like the broads, right?
( whimpering )
( gasping )
( traffic passing )
John.
Go to sleep.
I heard a noise.
So what?
This is the noisiest
neighborhood
in all of Boston.
Now go to sleep.
You're a cop,
for God's sakes.
What are you afraid of?
I worry about you
when we're not together.
I can take care
of myself.
Oh, yeah?
You can take on a 6'2",
200-pound man, can you?
Yeah.
Sure.
I could take him on.
Kick him in the balls,
and then I'd bite out
his jugular,
just like
you taught me to.
Right.
John, it's
a quarter past 5:00.
I'm going
back to bed.
Did you hear that?
Now you're
losing it, John.
I didn't
hear nothing.
Look,
it's the Strangler case.
It's getting to you.
It's not getting to me.
You're only human, John.
Murdering people
gets to people.
Ain't nothing strange
about that.
Somebody's getting
murdered out there
right now,
and there's
not a damn thing
I can do about it.
Two years I been
working on this case,
and I got nothing.
I can't solve
this thing.
No one can.
I'm not nobody,
Michelle.
You solved 10 cases
since this investigation's
been going on.
- This is different.
- How?
This is the biggest case
we've ever had.
This is bigger
than Jack the Ripper.
What?
- Wha...
- I've heard enough.
I'm sleeping
downstairs.
What's the matter?
You're scaring me,
John.
That's what's
the matter.
Is it really necessary
for you to walk me
all the way there?
It's for your
protection, sir.
Yeah. You cheater.
( knock on door )
Mr. De Salvo,
you have a visitor.
Oh.
Get the cards.
- I got 'em.
- Get the cards.
Here.
Mr. Whitmore.
I'd like you to meet
the newly infamous,
famous the world over,
soon to be
a wealthy man,
Albert De Salvo.
Certainly is
a pleasure to meet you,
Mr. Whitmore.
Frank's told me
a lot about you.
This is the Boston
Strangler?
( chuckles )
In the flesh,
Mr. Whitmore.
Can you believe it?
Not really, no.
All right.
Well, let's get down
to business.
Okay.
You know,
the city has spent
millions of dollars
trying
to track you down.
The D.A. created
a special task force
just for that purpose.
For three years,
they've been looking
for you,
not a trace.
It's pretty impressive.
Frank:
Sure is.
Albert is like a cat.
He could sneak
in and out
of any apartment
in Boston without
being noticed.
No witnesses...
ever.
Then why confess, hmm?
Family man, wife, kids,
a dog,
probably even
a goldfish.
No one even
suspected you.
Guess you could say
it was a career move.
Ha. A career move.
Now, look,
Mr. Whitmore...
we got client-attorney
privileges here, right?
- I mean...
- Frank, you know the score.
Anything you say
in this room stays
in this room.
That's the way
it goes, guaranteed,
confidential.
Good, because...
the way
that we see this,
Winfield...
is offering
$10,000 per murder.
Now, that's
over $100,000.
See, I tell Frank,
Frank tells the cops,
and we split
the reward money.
- Simple.
- And you,
you become
a world-famous litigator.
I mean,
any publicity
is good publicity,
right?
It's going
to be messy.
It's a huge story.
I mean, the press
and the public,
they're going to want
to crucify Al,
crucify him.
They're going
to have the grave
already dug.
Unless...
Whitmore:
Unless what?
Unless you
claim insanity.
For me, or for him?
See, I'm going to jail
for life anyway,
so we cop
an insanity plea.
They don't execute me,
and I live out
the rest of my life
in a hospital,
and the best part
is our families
get to keep the cash.
( laughs )
Jesus.
( chuckles )
Then I'll do it.
( laughs )
Perfect.
- That's great.
- Perfect.
Ah, thank you,
Mr. Whitmore.
Thank you.
On one condition.
Sure, yeah.
Whatever.
If you guys
get the reward,
we split it
three ways.
- Three ways.
- Ho. Ho.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Three frigging ways?
What is this? Frank.
Calm down.
Mr. Whitmore.
Frank, I'm doing
this for free.
It's pro Bono.
I don't see a dime
off of this.
It's the least
you can do.
Before you know it,
there's nothing left.
Wait. Hold on.
That'd be plenty
of money, Al.
We can't do it
without him.
Don't you see?
The plan is
already in motion.
There's no turning back.
He's the only one
that could keep you out
of the electric chair.
Hey...
Mr. De Salvo,
I don't think
you realize
what the public
really thinks of you.
They don't want
to just see you
get electrocuted.
They want
to tear you to pieces.
to string you up from
the nearest lamppost
and cut your guts out.
That's what they
want to do to you.
Now, you let me
handle the legals,
I'll make sure
that you live a long,
comfortable life.
Yeah, but, Mr. Whitmore,
the thing is,
see, I got kids,
and I got a wife
who I know still loves me,
and I got a family.
I'm the one taking
a chance here, right?
I'm the one
taking a risk.
All right.
That's it.
Al, it's going
to be fine.
Either way,
there's no going back
to the way things was,
so why not let
Mr. Whitmore here
make sure you go somewhere
that's comfortable?
And don't he deserve
some of the money too?
I mean, I know him.
He works real hard.
He'll do anything
and everything
in his power
to take care of you.
Al...
come on.
We're running out
of time here.
You're running out
of time.
So...
ahem.
We got a deal
or what?
We got a deal.
( laughs )
Frank, I'll be in touch.
Okay.
That's what
I'm talking about.
- Okay.
- Guard!
( sirens blaring )
Detective Marsden!
Sorry.
You know Albert De Salvo?
Yeah, sure, I do.
Measuring Man,
Green Man.
Why? What's up?
Well, come on.
Spit it out,
for Pete's sake.
Albert De Salvo
confessed to being
the Boston Strangler.
He confessed
to what?
To the Boston Strangler.
I mean, isn't that great?
We got our man. That's it.
He confessed.
It's over.
It's finally...
it's over.
( bells tolling )
Thought you'd be happy,
Detective Marsden.
I thought you'd be
jumping for joy right now.
In fact, everybody else
is downstairs celebrating.
They're shaking hands.
- Are they?
- Yeah.
So are you
coming downstairs
and celebrating?
Yeah, 'course I am.
Matter of fact,
I'm going to come down
and buy you a drink.
I'll be right down.
You got it, sir.
Ahem.
Michael, Sondra,
I want you to meet
a very good friend
of mine.
This is Frank Asarian.
Frank, this is
my brother Michael
and my sister-in-law
Sondra.
My pleasure.
Al, it's a family meeting.
Nah, nah, nah, nah.
It's all right.
No, Frank is
my family in here.
Come on, come on,
let's sit down.
So?
Michael:
I just don't get it.
I mean, I just
don't know what to say.
There is
nothing to say.
I made
some mistakes.
Some mistakes?
You call killing
innocent women mistakes?
Listen, Albert,
we just don't understand
how and when
all this happened.
I mean, I know that
you got your problems
with the broads and all,
but murder?
See, look, you don't
understand, okay?
There's a lot to the story
I ain't telling you.
Okay, it's very
complicated.
All I can say,
though,
is I'm going to make
a whole lot of money
off this deal.
And I'm already
pretty famous, right?
You're not famous,
Albert.
You're infamous.
It's different.
Sondra.
Look, I know
we never seen
eye to eye
on a few things,
okay, but...
any sort of fame
is all right by me,
you know?
No, I just
don't get it.
There's reward money.
Frank's going
to collect that.
There's going to be
television interviews.
There's going
to be book deals.
I even got a call
about a movie.
I mean, no, listen,
they want to make
a frigging movie
about me.
And guess who's
going to play me.
Tony frigging Curtis.
This is crazy.
You kill people,
and all you could
think about is being
a movie star?
The way we're
looking at it is that
I'm already gonna
be in jail for life
for other crimes.
Why not make
the best out of it?
And Frank's come up with
this really good plan
for my incarceration.
Tell 'em, Frank.
Go ahead.
Ahem. Well...
we decided
with our lawyer,
Stuart Whitmore,
to go for
an insanity plea.
Mr. Whitmore
made a deal with
the Attorney General
that nothing Albert
says about the Boston
Strangler case
can be used against him.
I mean, they already
got him in the court of
public opinion anyway,
so why bother
trying him in court?
So they're going
to try him for
the Green Man offenses.
Now, what's going on here?
Is Asarian here
your legal
representation too?
He's a smart guy,
okay?
So just let him speak,
Mike, all right? Come on.
Go ahead, Frank.
As I was saying,
Mr. Whitmore's
going to suggest
to the jury
that Albert is
completely insane.
And instead of
going to Walpole,
he's going to go
to a country club
run by the state.
It's brilliant.
It's frigging
brilliant.
Michael,
I've had enough.
They're demented.
( sighs )
Why you giving up
so easy?
Let them
prove you guilty.
This is an opportunity.
I got a chance here
to make the name
Albert De Salvo
mean something.
I mean, Ma worked
her whole life for us
to mean something.
Nah, nah, this ain't
what she meant, Albert.
I'd rather just be
a plumber my whole life...
than be in the mess
you're in right now.
I love you, Albert.
I'll visit you
every week.
Promise. Well,
maybe next time
we could just
play some cards
or something
like the old days.
- Yeah.
Sure, Mike,
just like
the good old days, huh?
Don't worry, Al.
You're making
the right decision.
He ain't in
your predicament.
He don't know.
He's a plumber.
Yeah, you're right,
Frank.
He doesn't know
my predicament.
No.
She mapped it all out.
Look at all the details
she got here.
You'd think she
committed the murders.
Now listen to this.
There was
a pack of cigarettes
sitting on the ground
underneath a pink chair
with flowers on it.
Mm. Yeah, see,
now this is the kind
of information we need.
We need
to know the murders
in more detail
than anyone else.
Exactly. Look.
Right here,
it says Ida Irga
was wearing a blue robe
with flowers sewn on it,
not pictures,
but actual knitting.
That's what
I'm talking about.
What are you doing?
What? I got
to look at it.
You know,
I got to see it.
I got to let
the picture sink in.
What the fuck
are you talking about?
What? I got a, you know,
photogenic memory.
You got a photographic
memory, you moron?
What, are you serious?
Why didn't you tell me?
What? I thought
everyone had one.
What are you
talking about?
( laughs ) This is
like a gift from God.
Do you know
what that means?
No.
Just look at that one.
Look at that one.
- I'm looking.
- Oh, my God.
They're going...
you're going to know
better than the murderer.
Well, look. Right here,
you see these pictures
right here.
Yeah, just look at it.
Just look at it, okay?
- Fine.
- Okay?
All right, I got...
I got... oh, my God.
- You got it?
- I got it.
- Perfect. Look at that.
- Okay.
( laughs )
Next. Next.
We've got through the...
that fast?
- Come on.
- Here you go.
- Okay.
- Jesus Christ.
( door opens )
So you're Albert De Salvo.
Certainly is a pleasure
to meet
someone so famous.
The most famous person
I ever met
was Miss Ohio of 1957.
Uh...
I didn't agree
to no lie detector test.
Relax, Albert.
It's a tape recorder.
For the record,
we're going to record
your confession.
I ain't afraid
of no lie detector.
I'm just saying we
never agreed on that.
Don't worry about it,
Albert.
We all have secrets.
We're only interested
in the ones
you're confessing to.
Ready?
Sure.
( recorder clicks )
Mr. De Salvo...
Oh, please,
call me Al, huh?
Let's get
this thing started off
on the right foot, huh?
I couldn't agree more.
Albert...
when was the first time
you met Anna Slessers?
Well, I wouldn't
say, you know,
I actually met her.
She was just
a pretty girl that...
Pretty girl?
But Anna Slessers
was 55 years old.
Yeah, yeah.
Anna Slessers.
You know, but she
was a real looker
for 55.
See, you know, I was...
I was hiding
in the closet, right,
and I watched her
walk inside.
Usually I'm hiding
in the...
in the bedroom
or something,
but this time, I was hiding
in the foyer closet,
and she was...
she was holding
a bag from Gimbels.
Addison:
Oh, well, that's strange.
Because I'm sure that...
it was a bag
of groceries.
Albert:
Yeah, that's right.
Yeah, it was
a bag of groceries.
You know, it was
meat, milk, and
all that stuff.
James,
are you home?
So after she finished
putting the food
and stuff away,
I stayed in the closet.
You do remember
that you killed her
in the bedroom?
You're talking about
Anna Slessers, right?
Yes.
Right. Yeah.
So she walked
into the bedroom,
and I followed her
very quietly.
You know,
she didn't know
I was there.
( drawer thumps )
James?
( gasps, yells )
( muffled screaming )
Stop. Help!
Help me! Help!
( yelling )
Help! Help!
Someone help me!
God help me!
( screams )
( gags )
Oh, God!
Help me! Stop!
Addison:
So when did you
use the stocking
to strangle her?
Where'd you get it?
See...
( laughs )
see, now you're
trying to trick me,
Mr. Addison.
See, I remember
this one very clearly.
So I took the tie
to her robe.
I wrapped it
around her neck,
and I'm pulling
on it, and I'm
pulling on it.
She's fighting me
and fighting me, right?
She even scratched me
with her nails.
It was terrible.
But, you know, I mean,
it was necessary, and...
Okay. That's lots
of information.
We might have to go back
a few steps, though,
just to make sure
we got it all right,
I mean, we got it all.
You know how judges are.
Sure. I understand.
( tape rewinds )
So...
let's take
a step back.
You said that,
on the night
of the Slessers murder,
you hid in the closet
and then you followed her
into the bedroom.
Is that right?
Yeah. Yeah, sure.
That's exactly
what happened.
( sighs )
I'm sorry, Al.
Sorry?
Is that all
you got to say?
You see, I'm the one
who's going to go
to Walpole.
The appeal is
already in motion.
Did you see the faces
on those jurors?
Did you see them,
those God-fearing
people?
They hated me.
They want
to see me fry,
sent me
right to the chair.
And we'll appeal it.
Look, it's just...
everybody's all
in a frenzy
about the Strangler.
Just too soon.
Oh, yeah?
Is that your
professional opinion?
At least you'll be
with Frank in Walpole.
Frank's going to
the frigging electric
chair, and you know it!
That's on appeal too.
Look, Albert, you're still
going to get your money.
You're going to get
your book deal,
your movie deal.
All of that is still
coming through.
But Walpole,
for Christ's sake!
Walpole! They will
fucking kill me there!
I'm going to die there!
Albert, this is your life.
You did this,
not me, not anyone else.
I've done everything
that I could, everything.
Do you want me
to appeal the verdict?
I don't know.
Does Frank think
I should do it?
For God's sake, for once,
forget about Frank.
I'm your attorney!
I am.
Listen to me.
We can appeal this thing
and get you
in an institution.
Okay?
Is that what
you want? Hmm?
Yeah.
Yeah, maybe
you're right.
By the time the court
hears the appeal,
this whole Strangler
thing will be...
old news, right?
Yeah.
Right.
Stay strong.
Lay low.
Everything
will be fine.
This is my world.
We'll get you
out of it, brother.
Need a little money
while you're in here? Hmm?
40 will last you.
Not enough
for the fucking casket.
Man on radio:
Albert Henry De Salvo,
the 35-year-old
mental patient
who says
he murdered 13 women
as the Boston Strangler,
was found guilty tonight
of armed robbery,
assault, and sex offenses
involving four women.
He was sentenced
to life imprisonment.
De Salvo's lawyer, who had
asked the jury of 12 men
to find the defendant
not guilty by reason
of insanity,
told newsmen bitterly,
quote, unquote,
"Massachusetts has
burned another witch.
No fault of the jury's,
of course.
It's the fault of the law."
His case was built
on the argument
that De Salvo was
a schizophrenic
personality.
Although
the 13 murders committed
in the Boston area
from mid-1962 to early 1964
were not a part
of his trial,
De Salvo's lawyer tried
to inject testimony
relating to them.
He said he felt these
crimes were so monstrous
that the jury must agree
that his client was insane,
but the court refused
to permit testimony
relating
to the stranglings.
De Salvo, a former
military policeman
and former middleweight
boxing champion
of the armed forces
in Germany,
stood erect and wan
as the jury foreman,
F. Hunter Rolley
of Concord,
a brokerage firm analyst,
reported him guilty
on each count
of a 10-count indictment.
The jury deliberated
three hours, 45 minutes...
Albert:
I just can't take it
no more, you know.
I just can't
take no more.
It's time, man.
Six years is
enough time.
I'm a changed man,
you know.
I ain't the same man
I used to be.
I help
the old people now.
I work
in the infirmary.
I haven't
had a drink
since I broke out
of Bridgewater.
And what's
the difference
if I tell
the real story now?
What's the difference
if I tell that I ain't
the Boston Strangler,
that I never was
the Boston Strangler?
Man, I don't need
the fame no more,
and I ain't
seen a dime from
any of this mess,
not a...
not a frigging dime.
You know...
maybe if
I tell the truth,
my family'll talk
to me, you know?
You can't say nothing,
nothing to nobody.
And that's for the rest
of your life.
But why, Frank?
I mean, why?
What's the difference?
Because I'm telling
you not to.
I'm in this too,
you know.
I don't want no problems,
no press, no nothing.
There's no sense
in rehashing the past.
In my book...
it's over.
You're talking like
you got something
you don't want me
to know, Frank.
You hiding something?
You better shut up, boy,
before I grab your head
and I bust it
against those bars.
Sounds like
you got a secret.
Sounds like you been
holding on to something
for all these years.
( laughs )
I'm done talking.
I've said enough.
( whistles )
( buzzer sounds )
You can do with it
whatever
the fuck you want.
Claudia:
You even know
what you've done?
( bell tolling )
Frank:
You're running
out of time.
- ( woman moans )
- Why you giving up so easy?
- ( screams )
- I got needs!
I'm a fucking man!
You're my wife.
I ain't the same man
I used to be.
Guard!
( phone dialing )
Hello. Dr. Arlen?
It's Albert,
Albert De Salvo.
I must say
I'm surprised
to hear from you.
How have you been?
Actually,
I've been doing well.
You know, Walpole...
ain't so bad after all.
Well, I'm very happy
to hear that.
But listen.
If you wouldn't mind
relieving me
of my curiosity,
why are you
calling me?
I got some things I want
to get off my chest.
Well, I'm sure they
have mental health
professionals there
who can help you.
Nah, nah.
This is different,
Dr. Arlen.
I want to tell the truth
about the Boston
Strangler murders.
I see.
Look, Albert,
let's not do this
over the phone,
all right?
I'll arrange
to meet you
at 9:00 A.M.
tomorrow morning.
I'll set up a private
therapy room.
We can talk there.
That'd be great.
Thanks, Doc.
Hey, thanks a lot, huh?
( cell door clinks )
Who's over there?
Who's there?
Who are you?
- ( grunting )
- Ow! Oh!
What are you doing?
What the fuck
are you doing?
( blade slicing )
Oh, yeah? You going
to fucking talk now?
- ( Albert screaming )
- ( grunting )
Fucking snitch.
( door closes )
Guard, we're done here.
Man on radio:
Albert H. De Salvo,
who became known
as the Boston Strangler,
was found stabbed to death
at Walpole State Prison
this morning.
The prison authorities said
that the 40-year-old
inmate's body was discovered
in his cell bed in the prison's
hospital wing at 7:00 A.M.
De Salvo, who worked
as an orderly in the hospital,
was said to have died
of multiple stab wounds.
The Norfolk County
District Attorney
said tonight that
a possible suspect
had been questioned,
but that no arrests
had been made.
Although De Salvo
confessed the details
of the slayings
of 13 women
from the Boston area
to a psychiatrist
and became widely known
as the Boston Strangler
through a book
and a movie release...
( instrumental music playing )