Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
Greg, alcoholic.
Hi, Greg.
You know, I really didn't
want to come today.
My whole drive here
I was thinking,
"This is bullshit.
I can skip just one more day."
But that's what I got
to tell myself, right?
Because those thoughts,
I mean, that's...
that's my fucking disease
talking,
that says that I don't need
to be here,
I don't belong here,
I'm not like you.
You people are fucking losers.
(melancholy music)
Natalie, breaks are
seven minutes.
It's been nine already.
She was a fucking loser
who just dragged me down,
right?
I was just a sucker
who got caught
acting like a loser.
I don't need to be here.
I'm not like you.
And then I look in the mirror,
and I go, "Oh, shit,
that fucking loser is me."
How was the mission trip?
Your mom told me
it was quite an adventure.
- Nigeria, right?
- Nicaragua.
Right, that's what you said.
I always get those two confused.
Well, good for you
doing the Lord's work.
Must have been so depressing,
though.
All those poor people.
I want to do
something like that,
but I just worry
about the mosquitoes.
Weren't you worried
about the mosquitoes?
But, today, I know
that the day I actually start
believing that I don't need
this program,
that I don't need other people
to help me stay sober,
that's the day
that I take my next drink.
Guess who my roommate was.
- Guess.
- Who?
Cassie Rubinec.
If they'd had "most likely
to end up in rehab,"
like, I definitely would've
voted for Cassie.
So I have to tell
those thoughts that tell me
that I don't belong here,
that I don't need you people
to shut the fuck up
because that is
my disease talking,
and my disease is trying
to fucking kill me.
And it will, I've seen it.
It does. It killed her.
My sponsor is always saying
that, um,
some must die
so that others may live,
and that's just
some really heavy shit.
I don't know.
I'm just... I'm just gonna
keep coming back,
because I didn't end up
in these rooms by accident.
Right?
None of us did.
(coughing)
(squeaking)
(knocking)
- Nat?
- Yeah.
Can I come in?
- Guess what I found?
- Mm.
- Honey, don't pick.
- I'm not picking.
- Now, look, it's all red.
- It's fine.
What did you find, Mom?
Well, Anya needs
some photographs
for her campaign,
so I was going through
all our old albums
and I found this.
Do you remember this?
Mm-hm.
That was your last dance concert
in New York.
You were so beautiful.
Makes me wish you hadn't quit.
Yeah? You like me better
with an eating disorder?
Oh, stop it.
You didn't have
an eating disorder.
Okay, Mom.
How was the meeting?
It was fine.
Did you find a sponsor?
Uh, I think, yeah, maybe.
What's her name?
He. Greg.
Greg. I always liked that name.
Yeah, we'll see.
Uh, honey, we have some takeout
from that place on Main Street.
Can I... can I bring you a tray?
No, I'm tired.
I'm just gonna go to bed.
- Okay. Little soup?
- No. Thanks, Mom. Good night.
- Hot tea?
- No, thank you.
Okay, good night.
(intense music)
(music stops)
Ooh, I can go all night.
Wishin' that you'd know
where to find me.
Ooh, I can't hide.
Wishin' that you'd know
where to find me.
Feed me lines, feed me lines.
Feed me lines.
Go on, feed me lines.
(guitar music)
(bell jingling)
Oh, hi there,
do you have an appointment?
Um, hello?
Excuse me.
Can I help you?
Family dinner tonight,
5:30 at Anya's.
I can't, Mom,
I've got a meeting at 6:00.
Excuse me.
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait.
It's time.
I'm sorry?
You owe me.
Um...
I'm so sorry,
we don't take walk-ins.
Um, Laurie will take you
back to the desk
and make an appointment for you.
I have an appointment
with her.
(soft music)
You want to do this
in front of everybody?
I... sorry,
that took me a minute.
It was a free trial, right?
Like, it was eyebrow threading.
Let's just get you set up
in the pink room, okay?
I'll be right in.
I'm ready to collect.
Yeah, no, that sounds great.
Just give me one sec.
(door opening and closing)
You guys, her wristband says
"Paradise Lane Nursing Home,"
so just look 'em up and see
if they're missing a patient.
Okay. Do you know her?
Of course I don't know her, Mom.
She's delusional.
Can you just call them, okay,
and I will keep her company.
Are you really gonna give her
free threading?
Do we do that?
(dryer whirring)
I know I know you, I just...
I can't place it.
Oh, for fuck's sake.
You worked for me.
Ramona's Lavender Farm.
Oh.
Right, right, right,
right, right, right, right.
Okay, to be fair,
that was, like, high school.
Wait, no, no, no, hold on.
It was the summer
after high school
because I was saving up
and I was, like...
God, somebody that I knew
or did ballet with
or something, was it Caitlyn,
did her aunt...
Ramona.
Ramona. There you go. I got it.
Okay.
So...
- You owe me...
- I owe you.
- ...and I'm here to collect.
- Uh-huh.
Uh-huh.
Um, that was, what,
that was 15 years ago?
- That's a long time.
- Not to me.
Okay, well, it is to me.
And I don't really remember...
...really anything
from that summer
or, like, that time of my life.
Um, honestly, I was...
I was really fucked up
back then,
so I have no idea
what I could owe you.
"To Eleanor Magnus,
I'm sorry I stole your money.
I promise to make it right.
IOU."
Signed Natalie Grillo.
Oh my God, this is amazing.
I don't remember signing this.
But you did.
This is so funny.
This is so... you know what,
I am really impressed
that you held on to this
this whole time.
Like, you might be
the first person
in the history of IOUs
to actually collect on an IOU.
Are you dim?
That's the point.
Read it. IOU.
Yeah, no, I get it.
I was just...
That's so funny.
Okay.
Okay, how much?
And I'm really sorry
about that, by the way.
That is fucked up,
but how much?
I will pay you back.
I don't want the money.
What do you want?
I want you to help me die.
(chuckles)
Wait, wait.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Read it, IOU.
Mm-hm, yeah.
No, I know what that says,
but that is not an IOU
kind of thing.
Where does it say in that
that you have approval...
This is not legally binding,
and I was...
You know what? I was chasing
my Adderall with vodka
when I signed this, like,
that's just not the headspace
one should be in
when promising things.
Well, that's not my problem,
is it?
Wow, God, I think
I'm being really cool
just offering
to pay you back at all.
Are you under the impression
that we're negotiating?
Okay, can we just think
about this for a minute?
I have thought about this
for a long time.
You want to die?
As soon as possible.
You did the right thing,
you did the right thing.
I'm very proud of you.
Hey, hey.
Did you guys call?
Yeah, they're on their way.
- She's so old, it's so sad.
- Yeah, it's really sad,
she doesn't even know
who she is.
God, if I ever get like that,
promise me
you're just gonna take me
outside and shoot me.
(laughing)
I could've kicked you out
when I caught you,
called the cops.
Ramona wouldn't let me.
Okay, I'm trying
to remember Ramona.
Was she like a real hippie
with lots of freckles?
She wasn't a hippie.
She just had freckles.
Yeah.
Yeah, no,
I totally remember her.
She liked you.
Never understood why.
That's where we're gonna do it.
The lavender farm.
Oh.
Yes.
Okay.
How?
Well...
I figure enough of that
Addall stuff that you do.
Adderall?
Is that what you meant,
Yeah.
Not gonna kill you.
Sorry. Big shot of heroin,
that'd do it.
Okay, heroin.
Dude, I haven't done that shit
in a really long time.
Okay, like,
I wouldn't even know.
I'm sober.
So, another way.
- How?
- I don't know.
Just not in that horrible place.
So, what, you live in,
like, a nursing home?
It's not a home.
It's a torture chamber.
They pump me full of pills
to keep my heart beating.
For what?
They get paid every month
to keep me laying there,
dying slowly.
I want to be still
the way I want to get still.
That's all.
(knocking)
Ms. Magnus?
(tense music)
What did you do?
- I...
- What did you do?
- Ms. Magnus?
- Hi.
- No.
- It's okay.
- No, please!
We're here to take you
back home.
- No.
- It's okay.
No! Don't touch me. No!
We're here to help you,
it's all right.
No! No!
Don't let 'em do this, please!
Please, don't let them take me!
It's not gonna be okay!
Don't let them!
(sustained high-pitched tone)
Young lady?
Young lady...
Would you like to share?
Young lady?
Um, yeah, sorry.
Um, I'm Natalie.
Mm, yeah, alcoholic and addict.
Hi, Natalie.
And?
Um...
I... I don't know,
I've got, like, um...
I mean, like, I think
tomorrow will be, like,
uh, is it like... I think
six weeks,
something like that.
Congratulations on six weeks.
- Yeah.
- Mm-hm.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Sorry, what?
You can pass if you want to.
Great, yeah.
I want to.
Okay.
Andrew.
(birds chirping)
(intense music)
(music stops)
I told you
that she would be late.
This is ridiculous.
(indistinct chatter)
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Come on, it's weird, right?
Hey, hi, Natalie!
So you found
an earlier meeting, huh?
- Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Oh, happy to see you.
Okay, shoes off.
Okay, why are you freaking out?
I just had the floors redone.
Did you not see my note?
What note?
Did you lock the door?
Yes, Anya, we're safe
in the suburbs.
Don't worry.
- Hi, Daddy.
- Oh, hi.
- Hey.
- Hi, guys.
It's so good to see you.
- How are you?
- I'm good.
Hi!
- Can you say hi?
- Hi, Chloe, hi.
Ooh, those look good.
Wow, she's gotten so big!
Okay, could we just... hi.
There's some things
that we need
to go over, everybody.
So, Natalie, we have all
discussed this already.
Oh, this is a family meeting.
Mom, I thought you said
it was a family dinner.
Oh, it i... it's a family dinner.
- It's a family meeting.
- And a dinner, Anya.
Which this pizza is getting
pretty cold, everybody.
Come on, let's grab a plate.
(clanking)
Um, Natalie was telling me
how she, uh,
she may have found a sponsor.
- Oh, that's great.
- Yeah, it's hard work.
Uh, Greg?
Greg? Was that it?
I thought that women
were supposed to sponsor
other women.
Well, Anya, it depends.
Well, so tell us
all about him.
Actually, I don't think
it's gonna work out with him.
I'm a little bit worried
he might be hitting on me.
That's why women
are supposed to sponsor women.
Do you want to be
my sponsor, Anya?
Do you want to go
and fuck yourself, Natalie?
Hey, can we try not to use
F-bombs, please?
- Little ears.
- I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. She's, you know...
Am I the only one
eating pepperoni here?
Nat, let me fix you a plate.
- I don't eat meat, Daddy.
- Still?
Haven't eaten meat
since I was 13.
Oh, he knows that.
Ed, you know that.
I know that.
Did you see? We got a whole one
of just mushroom and spinach.
Great, I'm gonna get a piece
in a minute, Mom.
And I have salad.
Do you want me
to make you a plate?
Oh my God, Mom,
she can get her own food.
Okay. Okay, Nat, so is there
like a central sign-up,
or how does
the sponsor thing work?
Uh, Dad, would you like
to join this conversation,
or...
Ed?
Are you paying attention?
I'm listening, I'm here.
I'm finishing a message,
thank you.
- Yeah, he's listening.
- Okay.
So my campaign is heating up,
and I'm going to need
everybody's help.
Oh, cool, I can help.
No, Natalie, I don't nee...
Okay.
I need to know that you are not
gonna fuck this up.
Oh, Anya, please.
Mom, I'm serious!
How would I fuck it up?
Are you joking? Is she joking?
Let's do that, yeah.
I think what Anya is doing
is huge, right,
and I'm only gonna speak
for myself.
I know that I don't want
to mess it up for her.
- Yeah.
- And I think if we all
work together as a family
to do our best,
that it would be good to know
that you're doing
the same, right?
What does that mean?
- Maybe I'm not...
- No, what is it?
I'm really asking.
What does that mean?
Mom, go ahead, go ahead.
What?
Mom, what?
As long as you are
living at home...
...and make no doubt about it,
you are welcome to live at home
for however long it takes,
but, um, as long as you are
living in our house...
Weekly drug tests, Natalie.
Are you kidding?
We all feel
like we deserve to know
whether or not you are using
or drinking.
I have not had a drink
or, like, anything in, I mean...
Tomorrow is gonna be six weeks.
- That's great!
- But why
isn't that enough for you?
Ugh.
Nat...
Nat, we are so proud of you.
I have to get this, okay?
Dr. Grillo.
Uh-huh.
- How long?
- Seriously?
- He's on call, honey.
- Oh my God.
Just tell me that you get this.
If one of those tests
comes back positive,
they are gonna kick you out,
Natalie,
and this time it's for real.
- Oh, Anya, please.
- What?
Mom, this is what we agreed to.
Oh, no, no, I haven't
agreed to anything.
Okay, but, Nat, you have
nothing to hide, right?
- So what is...
- Are you...
There's a clinic in the city.
It is very hush-hush.
Jeremy has some connections.
Jeremy. Is that
your fuck buddy?
Jeremy, my campaign manager.
- Who you used to fuck.
- Oh my God!
Natalie, that was in college.
- He's gay now.
- He's gay now?
No, see, I don't think
that's politically correct.
I think the LGBTQ community
would argue
that he was always gay
and find that statement
offensive.
So, you know,
maybe I'm not the one
you need to worry about
fucking up your campaign.
I also need you
to start volunteering.
- Oh, you need me to start.
- Just in case
someone gets wind of anything,
we can point out the contrast
in your life
between then and now.
I'm already volunteering.
You are? Where?
An old person's home.
A geriatric facility.
- Which one?
- Uh, it's called Paradise Lane.
Look it up.
Paradise La...
Pa...
Was that the place today
with the lady?
- What lady?
- There was this lady,
this homeless,
yeah, crazy lady,
and she just comes waltzing
into the sal...
Mom, she's not crazy
and she's not homeless.
Okay, her name is Eleanor.
- So you do know her?
- Yeah, okay, I...
I didn't want to make
a big thing of it.
This is why we can't trust you
because you are constantly
being caught in lies.
- Oh, come on, she...
- Anya, stop. Okay, come on.
I just started
volunteering there
when I was an inpatient,
it's like this program
where you can choose
where you want to do service.
It's like this huge piece
of recovery.
- That's it.
- That's wonderful.
Why didn't you tell us that?
I just...
Look, I didn't think you guys
were gonna understand
'cause, like, you know,
I've got to work every day,
but I'm supposed to go
to a meeting every day.
And, you know,
according to the program,
like, service is
really important.
And Eleanor knows
I work at Bella's.
I think she just wandered out
and got lost.
You really expect us
to believe that?
- Jesus Christ, Anya.
- Okay, listen, you know what?
This has all been
very productive, okay?
I will let Jeremy know
that he can make arrangements
for the weekly drug tests.
I will tell my team
that you already have
a steady volunteer position
just in case anybody wants,
you know, some proof
that you're no longer
a criminal and a drug addict.
- Oh, Anya.
- Hmm?
Great, that was smooth enough.
Yeah. Oh, and, Nat,
if you don't die
from a drug overdose,
but you do die from lung cancer,
that is really gonna
piss me off.
So why don't you just get
a fucking nicotine patch
and cut this shit out?
- I don't smoke.
- She doesn't smoke.
I don't... I have
an early morning.
She doesn't smoke.
She doesn't smoke,
and I can walk on water.
Jesus.
Oh my God,
she needs to get laid.
All right.
Well, I got to get Chloe back,
so, um...
- Well, I've got to find your...
- This was great.
Real fun.
I got to find your dad.
- Mom, she's...
- You okay?
No, she's out of control.
Ed?
We have to go now, honey.
(distant barking)
(drumroll)
(intense music)
(music stops)
Okay.
(guitar music)
Fuck.
(buzzing)
(telephone ringing)
Can I help you?
Uh, yeah.
Hi, Jillian.
I'm here to see Eleanor Magnus.
- Are you family?
- Yeah.
Really? I didn't think she had
any family except her son.
- Are you her...
- I'm her son's daughter.
I'm her... so her granddaughter.
Wow, I did not know
she had a granddaughter.
- Mm-hm.
- From Midland, right?
Mm, yeah, it's a good memory.
Well, I remember thinking
it was strange
he put in her a home
so far away,
but who am I to judge?
When was that?
Had to have been
about three years ago now.
Wow.
Yeah, no, three years,
that's about right, that's...
Well, she's not the only one.
Tons of them like that.
Nobody comes to visit,
not one single soul.
Anyway, what's your name?
Uh, Anya.
- Magnus?
- Yeah.
Hm, I don't see your name
on the visitor list.
- Really?
- But I can add you.
- Okay, that'd be great.
- Can I see your ID, please?
Oh, this is so stupid,
but my wallet was stolen
a couple of days ago,
so I don't have anything.
I don't have a bank card or...
Oh, that's okay.
Let me just call your dad
- and he can verify that...
- No, can you not do that?
Um...
Sorry, that's awkward,
but he just doesn't know
that I'm here.
Um...
Look, I drove all the way
from Midland to see her.
Please?
She's my grandmother.
Nurse?
(telephone ringing)
- Nurse?
- No, I'm not...
Let me see if I can...
- Nurse?
- Um...
Oh, hey, hey, I think
she might need something.
Oh, she's fine.
Nurse?
(beeping)
I'm sorry.
I want you to leave.
I panicked, I just...
Look, I didn't mean
for that to happen.
You're a monster.
Okay, yeah, that's fair.
Yeah, I'm a monster,
you're absolutely right.
Get out of my room.
Okay, here's the thing.
I can't.
- Nurse!
- Okay, first,
have you met the staff in here?
Like, good luck getting
any attention from them.
Okay, and, second,
I can't leave, okay, I can't
because if I leave,
then all I have ever done
is just destroy everything
and, like, everyone,
and I haven't followed through
on anything ever,
and that just can't be my life.
It can't.
And I do realize that...
...that killing you
might not be the best example
of doing good,
but I'm pretty sure
it's better than doing nothing
and, like, leaving you
in here to rot.
And I might also need
some urine.
- Oh, God.
- Hey, look at me.
This is not... this is not
a deal-breaker.
It's not.
That is nothing
for breaking you out of here
and murdering you.
(dinging)
Come on.
Side door.
By the trash cans.
Midnight.
(lively music)
What's, uh, what's going on?
Um, so, Mom,
I think I found a s...
I mean, no, I know
I found a sponsor.
- That's wonderful.
- Yeah.
- Is it a woman?
- Yes.
Good, good.
- What's her name?
- Jillian.
Oh, I've always liked that name.
Yeah, yeah.
So, here's the thing,
she thinks that I need
to, like, immerse myself more
in the program,
and I think she's right.
Okay.
Okay, uh...
What does that mean?
Well, there's this, like,
woman sobriety group
that she thinks
that I should join,
that you, like, meet
once a month
in, like, different places.
It's like this
weekend intensive, I guess.
And this weekend
they're meeting in South Haven.
So, I just thought, you know...
I mean, since the condo
is there
that maybe I could just go.
(soft music)
(sighs)
You know, honey,
if this were just up to me...
I mean, I...
I'm fine with you missing work,
obviously, but...
But your father
and the other kids,
we agreed to these rules,
honey, and we agreed
that we are going
to stick to 'em
if you want to move back home.
I know, I know.
And the doctor
was the one who...
who helped us with those rules.
I mean, we didn't make them up.
And you are not supposed
to spend nights alone, right?
Right.
And, you know, that is why
Jillian suggested
that we both stay
at Campbell's.
Campbell's?
That place is so overpriced.
I know, that is why
I offered up the condo
just because, you know,
it's there.
(sighs)
So, so...
Jillian would be staying
with you at the condo.
Yeah, yes.
No, I would be with sober women
the whole time.
Okay, sober, Christian women.
It's a church thing.
I know.
It's good.
I, uh...
We're gonna talk
about this tonight.
No, I can't, actually,
that's the thing.
I'd have to leave
this afternoon
because they have
this welcome dinner
and this opening prayer,
and it's all tonight,
and I guess if you miss that,
then you can't participate.
So...
Okay. It's okay.
I'm just going to tell Jillian
I can't this weekend
and, um...
Honey, just... just wait, wait.
Uh...
It's just for this weekend,
right?
Yeah.
And, like, I'll leave
a urine sample behind for Anya.
Could we meet Jillian?
It's anonymous, Mom.
But maybe I could
have her call you,
like, I don't know,
she might be willing to do that.
- Maybe?
- Okay.
Uh, that would be
my stipulation.
Okay, she... she has to call us.
Okay.
This is, uh, for an emergency.
If you need gas, no,
if you need anything.
- It's fine.
- You have been living
on such a tight budget lately,
and, uh, just...
This is...
This is between us, okay?
Okay.
I'm gonna figure this out, Mom.
Run to the storm.
Get the wind in your hair.
Let it take you.
Whoa, oh, oh.
Run to the storm.
When the sky falls down,
it will break you.
Whoa, oh, oh.
They might call you a sinner.
When the fire hails,
everybody is guilty.
I'll pray for the winter.
You'll be long gone
if the angels see ya.
Ooh.
Run to the storm.
Run to the storm, don't say
no goodbyes, oh, no.
Run to the storm.
The reaper don't sleep,
don't close your eyes, oh, no.
Run to the storm.
So run to the storm,
don't say no goodbyes, oh, no.
Run to the storm.
Ain't nobody gonna speak,
won't hear no lies no more.
Run to the storm.
So run to the storm, don't say
no goodbyes, oh, no.
No goodbyes.
The reaper don't sleep,
don't close your eyes, oh, no.
(panting)
(crickets chirring)
Okay, come on, hi.
Come on.
Oh my God.
Hey, come on, get in.
Jesus Christ.
(car door closing)
(heavy breathing)
Where are your pants?
Laundry day.
(funky music)
Oh my God, you're alive.
You know, I actually started
to wonder if you died.
And if you had, I was gonna be
super happy for you,
like, mission accomplished.
Jesus.
They keep a very tight control
over my fluid intake.
That's all I could get.
Just never seen pee this orange.
No, no, no, it's good,
it's good.
It's just... it's gross,
but it's good.
(music resumes)
Oh my God, I wish I could
see her face in the morning.
Okay, I would like to have
this finished by tomorrow,
Sunday at the latest.
Okay, uh...
Here.
Get that thing off.
Just let me do it.
(clacking)
Thank you.
You're welcome.
(bluesy music)
Go to the mountain,
we need higher ground,
where rivers and valleys
won't break us down.
Mothers and brothers
all gather round,
look up to the...
So how are we gonna do this?
What?
Close my final chapter.
Oh, I don't know.
Have you thought about,
like, how you want to...
I don't want any surprises.
Okay.
- I don't want to suffocate.
- Uh-huh.
Or cut my wrists,
anything bloody.
- Right.
- And I don't want
to be in pain
when it's happening.
- Okay.
Is that it?
Is that all you got?
I'd like to hear your thoughts.
Oh. Um...
I think, like, um...
I mean...
Illuminating.
Look, it's been
a really long day, okay?
I mean, my homicidal instincts
would be
way more impressive
over coffee.
Save yourself.
Don't hide in the shadows
that hit the room.
Save yourself.
Don't run in the shadows,
run to the moon.
(music stops)
(drumroll)
(intense music)
(music stops)
(crickets chirring)
(clicking)
(whooshing)
(wind chimes tinkling)
(upbeat music)
He rocks in a treetop...
Oh, make it stop.
Hoppin' and a-boppin'
and a-singin' his song.
All the little birds
on Jaybird Street
love to hear the robin
go tweet, tweet, tweet.
Rockin' robin,
oh, rockin' robin.
- Tweet, tweet.
- Rock, rock, robin.
Tweet, tweet.
Oh, yeah.
(coughing)
What the fuck?
Those things will kill ya.
Want one?
(honking)
What does that say? Trudy?
- Truly.
- What does that mean?
You don't know
what "truly" means?
No.
Obviously, I know what it means.
Why did you get it tattooed
on your arm?
It's none of your business.
Oh my God, what's your problem?
We have no fucking plan.
I'm thinking.
(coughing)
(birds squawking)
Oh, shit.
- Oh, I completely forgot.
- What?
Here, put it out,
I need a favor.
Just put it out, please.
It's the last favor,
I promise.
Please put it out,
please put it out.
It's gonna be fast.
Okay, so just remember, Jillian,
and we just met yesterday,
and you are very Christian.
Only idiots believe that shit.
Well, my mom believes
that shit.
Well, she must have
a small brain.
Can you...
Okay, okay, just please
get it right, okay?
Just say that we're here
and it's all good.
- And then...
- What?
Okay, okay, we can kill you
however you want.
- Go.
- Natalie?
Uh, no, this is Jillian.
I'm Natalie's sponsor.
Yes, yes, of course!
It is so good to hear from you.
I have been calling Natalie
over and over,
and it just... it goes
to voicemail.
You know, I keep telling her,
"Don't let your phone die,"
but I don't know,
maybe the program feels
differently about that,
I just...
You know, I just always go
to the worst place
when I don't hear from her.
I understand.
So, you, uh,
you're at the condo.
Yes, it's beautiful.
- Such a lovely home you have.
- Thank you.
I'm so glad
this all worked out.
So, is Natalie there?
She's in the other room,
praying.
- Really?
That's wonderful.
I know you must have been
through a lot with her.
Yes. Yeah, we...
We all have.
It's been very hard, yes.
What was the hardest thing?
Well, I think the hardest part
has been on her.
I can't imagine
what she's going through.
I'm not an addictive person
and neither is her father,
so we're just... we're just
so confused.
Anything you tell me
remains between us.
It's the lies.
She lies about so many things.
Maybe not anymore.
Oh my God, that'd be wonderful
for all of us, but...
The hardest part is the lies.
She's my baby.
I love her.
I want to trust her.
I want to trust her too.
(coughing)
You don't have to do this,
you know?
Like, I mean, I sprung you.
You're out of that shithole.
I should just run off
into the sunset?
You're obviously not gonna run,
but, you know, yeah.
My time is almost up
now that I've stopped taking
all that crap.
I'm a dead woman walking.
God, that's a great name
for a band.
Jesus.
What's wrong with you?
They say I have
a big, baggy heart.
So, why don't you just wait?
I mean, if your heart
is just gonna give out anyway.
Because people are saved.
The body might want to go,
but folks intervene.
They can't bear
to let it happen.
So the poor old sucker ends up
in intensive care
on life support.
You ever seen that up close?
Well, I have.
With Ramona.
And I'm not letting
that happen to me.
(crinkling)
Okay, um...
Well, what about your son?
I don't have a son.
Yes, you do.
- No, I don't.
- Yeah...
So...
You have a son.
And I just feel like...
...like whatever your situation
is with him,
like, I don't know,
but I just think
that he should be me,
you know?
Like, he should be the one
who is with you in the end.
- Absolutely not.
- Well, he should
at least get a chance
to say goodbye.
He doesn't want to say goodbye.
Are you sure?
I mean, sometimes I worry
that my parents think
I hate them, but I don't.
And I would be
really, really hurt if they...
He lives in Midland, right?
I know he lives in Midland.
- You manipulative little shit.
- That's three hours...
We are not going to Midland!
You are taking me to the farm!
(upbeat music)
Pull the trigger,
draw the line.
Stay on your side,
and I'll lie on mine.
Gun, gun, gun.
Whoa.
Pull the trigger.
So what's your son's name?
Stop talking about him.
I can't even ask his name?
Henry.
I always liked that name.
So what happened with you guys?
Oh, shit, just don't say
anything, okay?
I just got to deal with this.
- Hi, Mom.
- Oh my goodness!
Oh! I am so glad
you answered, honey.
Uh, yeah, I'm on speakerphone
here with your dad.
- Hi, Nat.
- Hi, Daddy.
We, uh, we wanted
to just check in
and see how everything was,
and, uh, is the group good?
Yeah, it's great,
I'm learning a lot.
What's that noise?
Are you driving?
Yeah, we're just driving
to an...
It's an overnight meeting.
Um, at a church
in Grand Rapids.
Well, that sounds like fun.
Yeah, it's kind of like
sleep-away camp
but without the alcohol.
But with Jesus.
That's what we say.
No to alcohol, yes to Jesus.
I like the sound of that. Ooh!
So, Jillian, does this group
have a name?
Oh, we don't believe in labels.
Okay, good.
Look, Nat,
I have to take this call.
I'll see you soon.
Okay, honey, so I forgot
to tell you,
Anya's campaign is doing
a video about the family,
and they went
to the nursing home
because they wanted
to get a sound bite about you
and that sad, old lady
you take care of.
Wait, what?
Hey, no, Mom,
she is really private, okay?
That's... can Anya not do that?
Can she just wait
until I get home?
I think she's there already
maybe,
but I know she tried
to call you,
so don't worry about it.
Everything is gonna be fine.
Um, all right.
Okay, I love you.
Take care of each other.
Bye-bye.
Am I the sad old lady
you take care of?
How sweet.
(intense music)
Why are we stopping?
I got to get something.
(music stops)
- What are you doing?
- Uh, nothing.
Just hold on one minute.
(clicking)
- Who are you writing?
- No one.
Can you just please
give me a minute?
The only thing you should be
focusing on right now is me.
Anything else can wait.
Okay, here's what I don't get.
Why aren't you just going
to someone
who can help you die?
I mean, they have
assisted suicides, right?
I told you, I am not dying
in the hospital.
- Yeah.
- I am dying
in the lavender farm.
All I'm saying
is that the drugs exist.
Not around here they don't.
Um, Oregon.
You want to take a side trip
to Oregon?
- Canada!
- What?
Yeah, Canada.
Canada. I could steal them
for you.
And how do you propose
to get us into Canada
without passports?
I'm not.
I'm not proposing that...
Look, you know what?
We don't even need
to steal them.
I don't even need to steal them
because I know a guy
and he's...
He's in Canada,
but I know him
because I've gotten stuff
from him before
and he could just, like,
meet us at the border
and get us the drugs,
so that's just...
God, I mean,
that's a great plan, right?
Okay.
Fine.
Call your guy.
(clicking, whooshing)
All right, I just texted him.
(dinging)
That's him.
We're all good.
Good.
What are you waiting for?
(sighing)
Okay, here's the deal.
I will get those drugs for you,
I promise, okay?
We have to drive
through Midland...
- No, no.
- ...and see your son.
- I already said no.
- We have to.
Come on, and then
we could just like
- jump over to Canada.
- No!
It is basically on the way.
Do not ask me again.
Look, I don't wanna
have to play this card,
okay, but you need me.
Please?
And I won't back down
to my father's call.
Wolves in the valley,
and the furnace on.
I know...
I know.
(vocalizing)
(breathing heavily)
(knocking)
Can I help you?
Are you Sarah?
I'm Mrs. Magnus, who are you?
I'm Eleanor,
Henry's mother.
Oh.
Does Henry know
you're here... Henry?
What are you doing here?
I came to say goodbye.
Goodbye.
What... come on.
(car door closes)
What happened?
Exactly what
I said would happen.
Now I've done what you've asked.
What?
No, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no.
Nope, that's not happening.
No, no, no.
(knocking)
Who are you?
Uh, I'm a friend of your Mom's.
Okay, what do you want?
Um.
She's dying.
Hmm.
And she wants to die
even faster than she's dying,
and that is really fast.
I understand.
I thought that...
...that if I got her here
that you could stop her,
or that you could
help her, or that...
that you'd just know what to do.
Hmm, all I can do,
all anyone can do
is pray for her.
- Wait, no, no, no.
- No, look.
I did my part.
I found her a home.
Um, that place that you
put her, that's not a home.
If she would rather
die on the streets,
that's her prerogative.
How can you...
I mean, she's your mom!
My mom died
nearly six months ago,
and her name was Karen.
My father married her
when my biological mother
abandoned me.
She what?
She made her choice,
and I have been living
with it my whole life.
She has to live with it now.
Now please get off my property.
(door closes)
(drumroll)
Canada, here we come.
(uneasy music)
(wind chimes ringing)
(car engine humming)
(engine clunking)
Oh, shit.
- What?
- Oh!
I think we're, like, out of,
- out of gas.
- You've got what?
Oh, no, oh, shit,
shit, shit, shit, shit.
- You're... you're outta gas?
- I mean, I don't... I have, like...
- You ran outta gas.
- Shit!
- How did ya let that happen?
- I didn't let...
My car stopped working, okay?
I mean, usually there's, like,
this little light that comes on
that tells me that
it's getting low,
but it didn't,
or, like, I didn't see it.
You didn't see it.
No.
Great, that's just great.
(railway crossing
bells dinging)
(train horn blaring)
(phone ringing)
(drumroll)
Hey, oh, dude,
where have you been?
- I'm dying over here.
- Sorry, my bad.
- Shit's been busy.
- I don't, I don't give a fuck.
I just need to know
if you know anybody
in eastern fucking Michigan.
No, I don't.
Fuck, fuck, okay, uh, all right,
well, what are you up to?
Can you come, like,
I mean, I don't give a fuck.
I will, I will do anything.
I will pay you double.
I don't care, you tell me.
Dude, what?
No.
Matt?
Fuck!
What?
(upbeat music)
(horn honks)
Come on before he
takes off, come on.
Do you know him?
How would I know him?
You want us to get into a semi
with a complete stranger?
Uh, maybe he's a psycho killer,
and he'll solve our problem
for us, now come on.
Ah, what a bad idea.
You are the hardest person
to help, come on, this way.
He's this way.
(coughing)
- You okay?
- Yeah.
(truck beeping)
- Uh, hi.
- Hey, hi, hi.
Um, our car ran outta gas.
Oh, shit.
Yeah, I know,
so we need a gas can.
And some gas.
Yeah, both would be good.
I've got a gas can.
- Really?
- Yeah, where's your car?
Oh, it's just,
like, a couple miles,
like, up that way.
Oh, that's easy,
I can give you guys a lift.
Wow, thanks, um,
all right, just the gas then.
(phone ringing)
Here ya go.
Thanks.
So, uh, where you two headed?
We're, uh, headed to
the Upper Peninsula, actually,
but sort of by way of Canada.
Whew, that is a long drive.
What's up in Canada?
Death.
Is that some kind of online
thing that I don't know about?
No, just death.
Like, death, death?
Yeah, death, death.
Whose death?
My death.
Oh, your death.
Hey, so, uh,
pump nine is good to go.
- Do you, uh, want me to...
- Yeah, yeah, that'd be great
so I don't soak us all
- with gasoline.
- Yeah.
Although.
(railway crossing
bells dinging)
(coughing)
Thank you again so much.
My pleasure.
It was nothing.
Eleanor.
My mom died about
three years ago.
We all knew it was coming, but...
She was a lot like you.
She was ready, unafraid,
and I was lucky enough
to be there
when she crossed over.
It was one of the true
miracles of my life
being with her in that moment.
You know, I think,
I think the way we die
is just as important
as how we live.
(gentle music)
And you have to promise me
to stay strong for her.
We need to give our
loved ones permission to go.
They stick around for us,
so you just have to tell her
everything's gonna be okay.
I'll take that.
(train horn blaring)
(railway crossing
bells dinging)
(gentle music)
(coughing)
(phone ringing)
Hey, listen,
I think that we should,
uh, get a place for the night
'cause, you know,
it's just late,
and, um, we're not gonna get
all the way to the farm tonight.
Like, we can't, so I
just think that we should
get some sleep, you know?
Get the drugs in the morning.
Well, if you think we should.
(coughing)
Yeah, I do.
We need a room.
Fantasy suite?
No, just, like, a regular room.
All our rooms
are fantasy suites.
Okay, yeah, then,
yes fantasy suite.
$67.84 with tax.
Okay, Martina, you got ID?
- I don't, I...
- We have cash.
That's $80.
20, 40, 60, 80.
Ya got five, ya got ten,
- eleven, twelve, and sixteen.
- That's right, thank you.
(car alarm blaring)
(faucet running)
(door closes)
(breathing heavily)
You're trying to get us caught.
(drumroll)
She can trace us
through that card.
They can find us
if you use the card.
Oh, my God.
You are so paranoid
it's ridiculous.
- Really?
- Mm-hmm.
There is no going
to Canada, is there?
Is there?
Okay, so.
What's gonna happen to me?
You just gonna...
abandon me?
Just one more thing
you didn't follow through with?
One more big lie?
(phone ringing)
God, leave me the fuck alone!
- Who can blame 'em?
- Oh, don't, don't,
don't, don't.
You have no idea how fucked up
everything is right now.
Okay?
Oh, you poor little thing.
You really wanna
antagonize me right now?
- Yes, I do, yes, I do.
- Is that what you wanna do?
- Really, why?
- Yes!
Because I am so
- angry at you.
- At me?
I am risking everything for you.
I mean, if this goes bad,
my family will
literally cut me off.
And, like, that matters to me!
Like, you could give
a fuck about your family.
You don't know anything
about me and my family.
Except that you
walked out on them.
Get out!
Get the fuck outta here!
Fine.
(door slams)
Fuck.
Fuck!
(phone dinging)
(drumroll)
Natalie, it's Mom.
I don't know, I just
thought maybe if I called
on Dad's phone you'd answer,
but I don't know
what's going on.
I don't know where you are.
I don't know...
I feel like such a fool.
No one in that nursing home's
ever heard of you.
God, I have tried so hard,
but this is it.
I'm, I'm, I give up.
I never thought I'd say that,
but I just...
I won't do this anymore.
I love you, Natalie,
I'll always love you.
And I have to...
I'm gonna say goodbye to you.
But you need to fix yourself.
And until you do,
I won't be a part of your life.
(intense drumming)
(car speeding)
(mellow music)
I spend days in a haze
cryin' over you, babe.
Well, those days are gone.
I hope you know
I ain't lonesome no more.
I spend nights wronging rights
without you by my side.
So if you stay,
I hope you know
I ain't lonesome no more.
Well, I know I'm hasty,
but time is wasting.
Baby, I've gotta know.
Oh, if you hear
what I'm sayin',
'cause darlin' I'll be waitin'
with no tears on the floor.
If you hear, hold me close
like the way you did
when I was low.
At least I'll know
that I ain't lonesome,
lonesome no more.
(mellow music)
(energetic music)
These eyes ain't no fool.
What you do,
I see right through.
Heart shinin' so
pretty when broken.
On edge, don't come any closer.
Call me alley cat,
you wanna take home.
Make my day, fill up my bowl.
I'm a bad dog you wanna own.
Everyone asks you
where I bury my bones.
Grip, grip,
I've got you in my grip.
Oh, la la,
now I've gone too far.
Hey, hey, now
I've got your picture.
Oh, la la,
now I've gone too far.
Oh, la la, now
I've gone too far.
Hey.
It's you, right?
This is crazy,
I thought you guys
- would be long gone by now.
- Oh, yeah, no,
we decided to get a place
for the night,
- so.
- Oh, that's cool,
that's very cool.
It's kinda cool.
What are you drinkin'?
Oh, PBR.
Do you want one?
(upbeat music)
(breathing heavily)
You're in the spotlight.
The night is ageless.
So...
what's your thing?
My thing,
- like?
- Like, I know you work
- at a gas station.
- Kinda, only on the weekends.
Okay, wait, oh my...
Please tell me
you're not in high school.
No, no, no, no,
I'm in college, I'm 21, I'm 21.
Okay, 21 is, like, slightly
better than high school,
but at least, you know,
flirting with you
is not illegal.
So, cheers to that.
You're flirting with me?
Apparently not very well
- if you have to ask.
- No, no, sorry, I just...
Cool.
(energetic music)
Okay.
Tryin' it again.
- What's your thing?
- I don't know, I guess I'm,
I'm just tryin' to...
I guess the thing is, like,
- I just wanna get outta here.
- You wanna get outta here, okay.
I really want to, but...
no, I just need to save money.
I just need to save up,
and make sure that I can,
like, stay afloat,
and, you know, not end up
falling back over here.
Yeah.
What about you,
what's your thing?
(energetic music)
I'm a dancer.
- No way!
- Yeah.
Like, like a pole dancer?
No, no!
Not a pole dancer.
Well, I shouldn't
say it like that.
I mean, not professionally,
not a professional pole dancer.
No, I do modern dance
with this company in New York.
That's where I live.
- That is so fuckin' cool.
- Yeah.
Is it just like, you know,
like in the movies or TV?
It is the shittiest
place on Earth.
But I am madly in love with it.
(breathing heavily)
(groaning)
(tense music)
(door handle jiggling)
(thumping on door)
(tense music)
So do you have
anything stronger?
- Like, what?
- Like,
I don't... like, anything really.
I mean, I don't
really do that much.
Like, I'm not that into, like,
coke, coke, or E, or...
No, no, I know
that shit's disgusting.
I just, I mean more like, um,
painkillers,
or like, pills, like Xanax.
Yeah, actually, my Dad
he had this
surgery for his knee,
and they gave him
something for the pain,
and he didn't
take any of it, so...
I don't know, I mean,
I don't know if you wanted
to come back home with me.
Gettin' high just
to live for the weekend.
See me live, baby.
I know what you're thinkin'.
Sure.
Knockin' at your door.
You want a winner.
Well, I'm a winner.
When you think you know,
you ain't never gonna get her.
Oh, playin' in your walls.
Wait a minute,
what about the pills?
I'll get 'em after,
I'll get 'em after.
Get 'em now,
get 'em now, get 'em now.
Get 'em now.
I'll be so much better,
trust me.
Trust me, okay?
You want a winner.
- Okay.
- When you think you know
you ain't ever gonna get her.
- Hey, hey.
- I got something.
What, what?
Wait.
Let's take a pill together...
...and make love,
come with me.
I'm okay.
No, come on,
I want us to experience
this whole night together.
Do it, do it.
Okay.
- Hey, hey, hey.
- What?
You're great,
come here, come here.
How 'bout you close
your eyes for a second?
Close your eyes for a second.
Close your eyes
Okay, okay, okay.
- All right.
- Just trust me.
Trust me, there you go.
You just gotta
let it kick in, okay?
Okay.
Feels good.
My mom used to do this
when she tucked me in.
You're a good guy, Dillon.
You're good.
No, I'm not.
Sorry I lied to you.
I really wanna stop lying.
It's just...
I feel so trapped, you know.
I guess I just need
to wake up tomorrow morning,
and just...
...decide I'm not
gonna lie anymore.
If I could just tell
the truth for a whole day.
Then maybe for a whole week.
Then maybe for a whole month.
Maybe for a whole year.
I could do that.
Yeah, I could do that.
(bird cawing)
(groaning)
What the fuck?
Oh.
(retching)
(mellow music)
Hey, Eleanor?
(knocking)
Eleanor?
Hey, Eleanor?
(energetic music)
Hey.
Hey!
- Hey!
- What?
You know that
woman I came in with?
- Look who's back.
- Do you know where she is?
(energetic music)
I am so sorry.
I'm so sorry to hear that.
Well, like I said,
I am so sorry to hear that.
I need to see Eleanor Magnus,
she was admitted last night.
I'm so sorry.
I really am so...
Now, how may I help you?
I need to see Eleanor Magnus.
- Eleanor, okay.
- Okay, I think she had
- a heart attack.
- Eleanor, you said?
- Uh-huh.
Uh-huh.
I don't see a... what was
the last name again?
- Magnus.
- Are you family?
- I...
- Oh, fuck me.
- I'm sorry?
Look, I said I wasn't
gonna lie anymore, okay,
and I'm really trying not to,
so just please
don't make me lie.
Just ask me something else.
- I'm sorry, I...
- Please, just anything else.
- Okay, I don't know...
- Just ask me anything.
- You can ask me anything else.
- Okay, I'm sorry,
I'm afraid I don't understand
- what you're...
- Hey, that... that is Eleanor.
- Oh, that's Eleanor.
- Yes, that's Eleanor!
No, we've been
trying to figure out
- who she is.
- Wait, is she okay?
Uh, let's get you
checked in, and you are?
- Natalie.
- Okay.
Grillo.
- "l-l-o"?
- Yes.
- And you said Eleanor Magnus?
Oh, do you have
her Social, off hand?
No.
Okay, she have insurance,
Medicaid?
I honestly don't know.
Okay.
Uh, primary residence?
Um.
Does she have a residence?
Not really.
Is she homeless?
Yes.
- Yes!
- Oh.
That is not a lie.
Sorry, I didn't mean
to get that excited,
but no, yes, she's homeless.
Uh, and your relationship is?
She's my friend.
The bad news is
your friend's heart
is way too weak on its own.
What we call cardiomyopathy
with a-fib.
But if she sticks
to a strict protocol,
she's got a good shot.
A good shot at what?
Time.
That's what it's all about.
Right.
You can go in there
for a while if you want,
but let her sleep, okay?
She needs to rest.
Hey.
- Sorry.
- Get the fuck off me.
Hey, don't go back to sleep.
Hey, can you just
open your eyes please?
Come on.
Hey.
(machines beeping)
You're still here.
I'm just sort of sitting here
trying to figure out
how I'm gonna break
you out of this place.
(chuckling)
I mean, you know, I could
go get a wheelchair,
and I could just,
like, strap you into it,
and just, like,
wheel you outta here,
you know, when
they're all distracted.
I mean, that probably is,
like, the best plan, but...
...I mean, you know,
I think they have
cameras and stuff, and so...
I'm pretty sure
that's kidnapping.
And then, and then
they'd be looking for me,
and then they find me,
and then you're dead,
and I think that,
I think that's
probably murder, so...
Just sort of, you know,
going over
everything in my head.
- Just trying to figure out...
- Stop.
(machines beeping)
It's over.
What are you talking about,
no it's not.
- It's over
- No, it's not.
- It is.
- No, it is not.
Hey, I got the drugs.
- What?
- Yeah.
I got the drugs.
I mean, I didn't,
I didn't get the drugs... Fuck!
You know, this telling the truth
thing is so fucking hard.
I got drugs...
...and they'll
definitely do the trick.
So give 'em to me.
No!
No, you're not dying in here.
You're dying
in the lavender farm.
It's where she is, right?
Ramona?
Okay.
Then that's where
you have to be.
And I have to get you there.
It's the only thing
in my life...
...that means anything.
Just please.
What are you doing?
No, please don't call them,
please don't call them.
I will just sit here,
I won't talk, okay.
I won't say anything if you
don't want me to bother you.
I'm just gonna
sit here with you.
Hi, Eleanor,
do you need something?
I'd like to check out.
Oh, God.
Oh, okay.
I'll get the doctor.
They're not gonna
let you just check out.
It will be all right.
Fuck.
You're awake.
How are you feeling?
I wanna check out.
That's not advisable,
Ms. Magnus.
I wanna check out.
Now.
Wait, you can do that?
Sorry, I'm sorry,
can she do that?
Of course she can,
but she'd be leaving
against medical advice.
Ms. Magnus,
you have a very
serious condition.
Even with treatment,
it's tenuous,
and it would be unethical
to allow you to leave.
But you just said
she doesn't need
your permission, right?
You know what,
why don't we go outside,
and let's let her
get some sleep.
I don't need sleep.
I need to get
the hell outta here!
You heard her.
Okay, put your head back.
Is that comfortable?
- It's cozy.
- Okay.
It's good.
Okay.
Here.
I can't take it with me.
Don't spend that on drugs.
I mean, this wouldn't
buy me even one drug.
I won't.
So...
that's...
$60 and 16 cents
you've taken from me.
That seems right.
For everything.
Yeah.
Hold up, are you saying
that I only stole $50 from you?
Only?
This whole thing
started over $50?
Well, technically,
this whole thing
is ending over $50.
(laughing)
(hopeful music)
Okay.
We are glorious, glorious
like a burnin' red sky.
And we are champions,
champions.
We're gonna dance in the sun.
There are stories of us
about the fire in our eyes
and the battles we've won.
We're forever young,
forever young.
Oh, we are glorious, glorious.
Oh, we are champions,
champions.
When we walk into the light,
I can hear the callin',
and in my heart
it's like a beating drum.
When there's nothin'
left to fight,
even if we're fallin',
jump in yourself,
they've come to take us home.
We are glorious, glorious.
Oh, we are champions,
champions.
Oh, we are young,
and we are free.
We are glorious, glorious.
Glorious!
(hopeful music)
Down there.
(peaceful music)
Okay.
All right.
Okay, hang on.
(peaceful music)
You ready?
Yes.
(peaceful music)
I don't know
how long this will take.
Well, I've got nowhere to be.
Okay.
(peaceful music)
I don't want you to go.
I'm sorry, I know that
that's selfish.
It's not selfish.
And you're not a monster.
(peaceful music)
- Okay.
Okay.
(peaceful music)
It's okay.
You can go.
(birds chirping)
(sobbing)
(laughing)
(soft music)
(energetic music)
(tattoo needle buzzing)
Hey, um, can people get
addicted to getting tattoos?
Absolutely.
Shit.
(lively music)
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
Wipe that look
off of your face.
What the hell
is your beef, anyway?
Oh, oh,
as if I give a damn
'bout anything you think.
Check this look
I got on my face.
(laughing)
Oh, the more I piss you off.
Oh, the less my choices cost.
Oh, so it ain't no big loss.
Oh, 'cause I'm livin' like a,
livin' like a boss.
I don't fit your Midwest mold
'cause I'm of California gold.
Oh, and I don't give a damn
about what you think of me.
I don't think about you
that's why I'm free.
(laughing)
Oh, the more I piss you off,
Oh, the less my choices cost.
Oh, so it ain't no big loss.
Oh, 'cause I'm livin' like a,
livin' like a boss.
(upbeat music)
Let the will to die
I breathed in,
I think it's poison.
Let the will to live, yeah,
pass by a door half open.
A kiss for an extra
handful of almonds,
all motives to keep me inside.
Last bit of lavender picked,
there is nothing,
there's nothing,
there's nothing to hide.
Now some pray to the angels,
our spirit guides our backs.
We'll do pirouettes
on train tracks
and laugh ourselves to death.
Laugh ourselves to death.
I think I spend too much time
lost in thinking.
We're either
running out of time,
there's only time left.
On my way out, I made a plan
to knock all the doors
to say my goodbyes.
There is nothing,
there's nothing,
there's nothing to hide.
While some pray to the angels,
our spirit guides our backs.
We'll do pirouettes
on train tracks,
and laugh ourselves to death.
Laugh ourselves to death.
I don't know who
you think I am,
but nice to meet you.
I was about to leave,
but now I think I'll stay here.
Is this a memory
that we are both making?
These are the measures
we think about taking.
Now I am sleeping,
so, darling, don't wake me.
There's nothing,
there's nothing,
there's nothing to hide.
While some pray to the angels,
our spirit guides our backs.
We'll do pirouettes
on train tracks,
and laugh ourselves to death.
Laugh ourselves to death.