(suspenseful instrumental music)
(thudding) (loud banging)
(footsteps thudding)
(suspenseful instrumental music)
(cart clinking)
(objects clattering)
(soft thudding)
(suspenseful instrumental music)
(soft clattering)
(objects clattering) (footsteps
thudding)
(suspenseful instrumental music)
(keypad beeping)
(card scraping)
(suspenseful instrumental music)
(door whooshing)
(footsteps thudding)
(object clattering)
(clicking)
(suspenseful instrumental music)
(beeping)
(keypad beeping)
(door clicking)
(door thudding)
(suspenseful instrumental music)
(papers rustling)
(camera shutter clicking)
(suspenseful instrumental music)
(alarm blaring)
(papers rustling)
(alarm blaring) (suspenseful
music)
(footsteps thudding)
(machine whooshing) (alarm
blaring)
(suspenseful instrumental music)
Hey!
Yo!
Leave.
What the hell's
going on down here?
(alarm blaring) (guard coughing)
(suspenseful instrumental music)
(gas hissing)
(footsteps thudding)
(suspenseful instrumental music)
(water sloshing)
(gun popping)
(footsteps thudding)
(suspenseful instrumental music)
(upbeat instrumental music)
(chess piece whooshing)
(suspenseful instrumental music)
(chess pieces clonking together)
(clicking) (object whooshes)
(suspenseful instrumental music)
(chess pieces clonking over)
(helicopter whirring)
(suspenseful instrumental music)
(birds chirping)
(clock ticking)
(dogs barking)
(clock dinging)
(pillow thuds) (clock dinging)
(banging) (Lance grunts)
(clock ticking) (dogs barking)
(thudding)
(clock ticking)
(sheets rustling) (dogs barking)
(birds singing)
(suspenseful instrumental music)
(clattering)
(electronic beeping)
Famous undercover agent,
Codename Eagle Don,
senses the presence
of an enemy agent.
(electronic beeping)
Prepare to exterminate
that enemy
agent with extreme
prejudice. (electronic beeping)
(suspenseful instrumental music)
(gun clicking)
(cracking) (thudding)
(objects clattering)
(birds singing)
(suspenseful instrumental music)
(Lance groans)
(boy grunts)
(both grunting)
(sheets rustling) (Lance grunts)
[Boy] Get off.
(both grunting)
(boys panting)
(gun clicking)
No!
Don't do it!
(gun clicking)
Nice try, Billy.
Talking about nice try?
I coulda had you
from back there.
Yeah, but you didn't.
Yeah, that's not
the point, is it?
How did you know I was here?
That's all part of the job.
(gun clicking) (water squirting)
This job's gone
straight to your head.
What?
- Nothing.
- What'd you say to me?
Nothing.
Get out.
[Boy] I'm going.
Out.
(paper rustling) (footsteps
thudding)
(Lance pants) (Lance sighs)
(equipment
scraping) (birds singing)
(door clicking open)
(footsteps thudding)
Mom, Lance is picking
on me again.
(equipment
scraping) (dogs barking)
(air hisses) (engine roars)
(Mrs. Elliot pants)
- Hundred.
(air hisses) (dogs barking)
(clattering)
(dogs barking)
(door creaks)
- Uh.
(dogs bark) (lawn
mower whirring)
(dogs barking) (antenna
clicking)
(phone beeping)
(phone rings)
(phone clattering)
Good morning.
Why can't you be
nice to your brother?
(objects clattering)
[Mrs. Elliot] Lance?
Lance?
(screen clicking)
Lance.
Hello, dear.
It's mother, remember?
(electronic beeping)
We're having a lovely breakfast.
[Lance Voicover]
East German immigrant.
- Female.
- Cranberry.
[Lance Voicover]
Disguised as cross-country ski
expert has infiltrated
safe house.
(laughs) Why don't you drop in?
(shutter clicking) (electronic
beeping)
(birds singing) Lance?
Are you listening to me?
(phone clattering)
- Lance?
Lance?
Can you do something
with your brother?
Can you do something with him?
Just tell him that I love him.
Sometime when you're
alone, alright?
Are you listening?
(objects clattering)
(birds singing) (footsteps
thudding)
(door creaking) (slamming)
(pages rustling)
Lance?
Lance, honey?
I know you're up
there, (birds singing)
so there's no point ignoring me.
I won't say a word, dear.
Nothing.
But can you come to
breakfast once a week?
Or once a month?
Or something? (footsteps
thudding)
(soft rustling) (birds singing)
I want to talk to
you, is that wrong?
I want to talk to my son.
(birds singing)
(suspenseful instrumental music)
Hey, you can't take my bike.
Mom, Lance is stealing my bike!
(suspenseful instrumental music)
Eagle Don escapes
from Interrogation Center.
Headed to Mission Headquarters.
(suspenseful instrumental music)
(car horn beeps)
[Man] Whoa!
(suspenseful instrumental music)
[Boy] Lance, get off my bike!
You're gonna break it!
Lance, come on!
(suspenseful instrumental music)
[Lance Voiceover]
Red alert, red alert!
Enemy vehicle in pursuit,
closing in fast.
[Boy] I'm warning you, stop!
Lance, come on, you're
gonna break it!
(suspenseful instrumental music)
(car horn honks)
I don't know what's gotten
into you, young man!
You stop that bike!
(suspenseful instrumental music)
Stop that bike right now!
(phone ringing)
Good morning, sir.
You're late.
Four minutes, 23 seconds.
Look, I was being chased.
People in station
wagons were chasing me.
I had to lose 'em, and I had
to take a detour here.
- Get some coffees.
- Sure.
- Mine is straight black.
- Of course it is.
Well, I'll send the files over.
(door clicking)
I'd like to get moving on
the Harrison case.
Wednesday.
11:30.
(phone clicks)
Yes, Trout, what is it?
We need a signature.
Additional surveillance
equipment.
Well, I have
permission to extend
the duties of the
summer recruitment program.
Pamela, I don't know why you're
so obsessed with these kids.
Now, don't get me wrong.
I think the program
is a great idea.
The kids spend the
summer off the streets,
good experience for
them, but don't
you think you're taking this
a bit too seriously?
What about this
young kid, Lance?
I don't know.
There's something
strange about this kid.
Really?
He's only been with
us for three weeks.
He's a bright kid.
Give him a break.
Maybe you're right.
(door clicking
open) (phone ringing)
[Pamela] Oh, hello, Lance.
Mrs. Lomax.
(door slams)
- Thank you.
Sure.
The one on the left.
Why?
Well, it's your
usual, straight black.
(spoon clinking)
Did you spit in it?
[Lance Voiceover]
Lance, you sly dog.
He fell for it.
A combination of strip
nine and carbon-10.
Colorless, sweet-tasting death
within seven seconds.
Lance, we have a
few (Trout gags)
(Trout coughs) - How
much sugar's in this?
Oh, that's mine, I'm sorry.
Four packets.
Here you go.
This one's yours, sorry.
Lance, we have a few assignments
we'd like you to do today.
I'm putting you under
Trout's supervision.
[Lance Voiceover]
Oh, this is bad.
This is very bad.
I should've poisoned him.
We have a number of
assignments for you.
These early assignments are
for character building.
PDPD.
Perception,
Discipline, Patience.
The three qualities
of a solid agent.
[Lance Voiceover] An assignment.
Lance Elliot sent to Paris under
the codename Eagle Don.
Lance, you have a
lot of potential.
But you need to learn
how to channel
that energy in the
right direction.
[Lance Voiceover] The mission?
Meet a girl under
the Eiffel Tower.
Her name, Charlene.
Ask her is she has a
tourist map of Nice.
You'll know if she answers no.
But I have a parrot named Buzz.
Especially if you plan
to join the agency.
After all, that's
what this summer
program is about, isn't it?
Lance.
Are you ready to start?
Absolutely.
Yes.
(sharpener whirring)
(gentle instrumental music)
Eagle Don joins
forces with Charlene.
Tonight, the mission begins at
the Cafe Mar-suh-lee-ay.
A romantic candle-lit
dinner with
red wine, passionate dessert.
The mission is to find the
parrot named Buzz.
I suggest we start
by searching her apartment.
(gentle instrumental music)
Cheers.
(sharpener whirring)
(gentle instrumental music)
(engine rumbling)
(birds chirping)
(brakes squeal)
I thought for years, for years
I thought that
perhaps you harbored
some resentment against me.
Oh, don't be silly, Rudi.
We were both young, reckless.
Look what you made out
of my little idea.
Out of a single home computer,
you've built an empire.
Oh, well, darling.
We have a guest.
Rudi Kseenbaum.
Rudolph Von Kseenbaum.
Rudi, it's certainly
my pleasure.
The pleasure is all mine.
Well, you really don't need
to get out, darling.
So, Rudi, it's been
about 17 years,
I think, since we
first became associated, and.
I take it you
obtained the FAA codes.
Of course.
Excellent.
(briefcase clicking)
Then we can proceed
to the second stage.
(footsteps thudding)
(tape clicking) (birds singing)
I have been hired
by an international
consortium of
businessmen to create
a very special computer virus.
Well, you've come
to the right place.
We still have a lot of
fun with computers.
Boo boop.
(laughs)
(laughs) So I hear.
A little bird told
me that you were
personally responsible
for the March
the 5th Michelangelo virus.
Well, I'm impressed.
That's not common knowledge.
(remote clicks)
[Narrator] Never
before has our world
come closer to the
brink of destruction.
An area of rainforest
the size of
a football field is being
cut every minute.
Carbon dioxide levels have
never been higher.
The UN Security
Council has elected
a Science Committee to
produce the Green Alert Report.
153 countries have
agreed to legislate
the findings of the report in an
effort to save the globe from
what is certain to.
Well, I know all that.
So let's get to the
interesting stuff.
The consortium
fears that the Green
Alert Report and the subsequent
legislation could seriously
damage their business interests.
Now, the Scientific Committee is
presently engaged
in a world tour.
In two days' time,
they will be flying
from Brazil to Atlanta, and
this is the plan.
(thudding)
The consortium would
like a scientist
to disappear unexplainedly in
the Bermuda Triangle.
Oh, that's a very nice tough.
(laughs) That's
where you come in.
We wish to have this done by an
untraceable, specialized
computer virus.
They are prepared
to pay $12,000.
I suggest we split
it fifty-fifty.
Seven for me, five
for you. (laughs)
(laughs) You haven't
changed, Rudi.
If the plane leaves in two days,
that's a tough schedule.
The fee's a little light.
But it'll be a
nice challenge, so I accept.
You're a great
sportsman, you know.
But I'm not business.
Let me show you something
I've been toying with recently.
May I leave this here?
[Cashpot] Of course, we'll
be right back!
(games beeping) Yep.
(laughs) This is my fun room.
(laughs) Incredible.
And you see, all these games are
linked up to my
central computer.
(games beeping)
Ah.
(Cashpot laughs)
Ha, ha!
Yes, oh, this is
a wonderful one.
You just get in there
next to Ursula.
This is gonna kill ya.
(Rudi laughs) It is great.
Alright.
(door slams)
Isn't this fun?
Absolutely. (laughs)
How does it work?
Well, put on your seatbelt.
(seatbelt clicking)
(beeping)
I'm gonna put a quarter in here.
(clicking)
(playful instrumental music)
(engine roaring)
Isn't this fun?
(Rudi laughs)
(engine roaring)
(playful instrumental music)
(tires squealing)
(Rudi laughs)
Whoa!
(car horn beeps)
(woman screams)
(engine roaring)
(tires squealing)
(playful instrumental music)
Whoa.
(tires squealing) (glass
shattering)
(Rudi yells)
(Rudi sighs)
What kind of game is this?
This brakes don't work.
It's not a game.
(creepy instrumental music)
Why are you doing this to me?
Oh, nothing personal.
It's just good business.
Have a nice trip, Rudi.
(engine roaring)
Help me!
Help me, someone!
(glass shattering)
(light instrumental
music) (Rudi groans)
(light instrumental music)
(tires squealing) (Rudi
screaming)
(loud banging)
(engine rumbling)
(door slams)
(engine putters)
(papers rustling)
Pamela, you called?
Oh.
Yes.
Have you heard from Wynberg yet?
He should've received
the package by now.
Oh, I forgot to tell you.
There's been a delay with
delivery personnel.
You mean he hasn't
received it yet.
Well, it'll arrive
today for sure.
What time?
(dialing)
Early afternoon.
Good.
Jim, early afternoon.
(laughs) No, of course we didn't
send it Federal Express.
(beeping)
About the tapes.
We did a computer analysis on
the Stylos tapes.
They were definitely recorded
under duress.
Well, we thought he was a man.
(door thuds closed)
(footsteps thudding)
Come here.
Gimme those.
I was gonna file those.
I know, I know.
Take this.
This package contains
highly confidential
documentation, level
three security.
You shouldn't even
be holding it.
No.
In fact, this is
really the FBI's business.
I shouldn't even be holding it.
I need this delivered
to Wynberg Mycronics
in Los Angeles, and I want
you to hand-deliver
it to Sam Wynberg,
no one else, okay?
Okay.
I've booked you on a
10:30 flight to LA.
You're gonna arrive at 12:40.
You catch a cab, and you
deliver the package.
Wynberg's is about
35 minutes from the airport.
You depart LA at 2:30.
You'll be back home
by 10:30 tonight.
- Okay.
(papers rustling) Now
here is $200.
So go to LA, come back.
This was supposed to be
delivered yesterday.
The address is on the package.
You'll be home before anybody
realizes you've even left.
Look, don't let on
to anybody, - No.
- Especially Mrs. Lomax.
- Of course not.
- Can you handle this?
- Of course.
Get outta here.
(plane engine roars)
(tires squeal)
(upbeat instrumental music)
♪ Livin' it up on
the Western side ♪
♪ No matter what you do
it's all justified ♪
♪ You can spend 25
hours in a rock cafe ♪
♪ And know you lose just
a minute to the following day ♪
♪ There are no exceptions ♪
♪ Everywhere worldwide the one
thing that we're doing here ♪
♪ On the Western Side ♪
♪ Livin' it up ♪
(door clicks shut)
What can I do for you?
Yes, we're here
to see Mr. Wynberg.
We are here to appeal
to his generosity
to help the starving,
underprivileged children of Bolivia.
Mr. Wynberg's real
busy right now.
However, our mission is
a most urgent one.
True, sister.
(dialing)
There are two people here
from St. Andrews
parish for underprivileged
children.
I'm on a deadline.
Have 'em come back tomorrow.
I'm sorry, but we
will be praying tomorrow.
Bless you, bless you.
I'm sorry, where were we, John?
John, let me call you back
a little later, okay?
Bye.
(clattering)
Sister, Father.
Well, ya caught
me at a bad time.
Well, this needn't take long.
(suspenseful instrumental music)
Is there something
I can do for you?
How about a donation
to the church?
Mr. Wynberg, we
were thinking about
something a little
more specific.
I don't understand.
We wish to acquire an
FAA security keycard from you.
The church will pay generously.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I can't help you.
- [Secretary] Mr.
- Wynberg, a Lance
Elliot is here with a package.
Excuse me.
Send him in.
This'll only take a minute.
(door clicks open)
Mr. Wynberg, package
for you, sir.
Thank ya, Lance.
Father, sister,
sorry to interrupt.
[Sam] Oh, Lance?
Sir?
Lance, take this.
That's not necessary.
Please, do.
Get some ice cream.
[Lance] Thank you.
(footsteps thudding)
(door clicks shut)
Okay, Wynberg, let's
cut the bullshit.
Now, we know that you are
cleared for level three security.
Hand over the key card.
I don't have one.
I only designed the system.
I don't use 'em.
Once last chance.
(suspenseful instrumental music)
Alright, take me
to the card file.
(Wynberg grunts)
Move it.
Listen, could you hold
all calls, please?
Because we're gonna
be praying for a while.
(suspenseful instrumental music)
(creepy instrumental music)
(thudding) (man grunts)
(both grunting)
(thudding)
Mr. Wynberg?
Confess, you prick.
Look, I used to
keep a card around
here, but I don't do it anymore.
Please, ya got to believe me.
Shit!
That kid!
He slipped it to the kid?
(suspenseful instrumental music)
You stupid bastard.
(thudding) (Wynberg groans)
(suspenseful instrumental music)
Mr. Wynberg, are you okay?
(gasps)
Hello?
(suspenseful instrumental music)
(gun popping)
(heels clicking)
Thank you.
You saved my life.
(girl panting)
Wait, don't you want my number?
(suspenseful instrumental music)
Okay, that's a
double cheeseburger,
a bacon and chili
burger, two fries,
a Diet Pepsi, and
a regular Pepsi.
That's $8.30.
Here's a 10.
Keep the change.
Thanks.
(keys clacking)
A Lance Elliot,
he's 17 years old.
Male Caucasian.
231 Pinewood Road, Philadephia.
(suspenseful instrumental music)
(keys clacking)
(phone ringing)
(suspenseful instrumental music)
(machine whirring)
(paper rustling)
Delivered package.
I think Wynberg is
in serious trouble.
Being pursued by a
nun and a priest.
Eagle.
This kid's living
on another planet.
Did he make the plane?
(keys clacking)
Is he booked on
any flights home?
He missed the plane.
He could be anywhere in LA.
Shoulda nailed the little punk
when you had the chance.
Any relatives, friends, hotels?
(keys clacking)
(beeping)
(phone ringing)
Yep.
Yeah, we have a slight problem.
We had to terminate.
Also, a delivery
kid dropped off a package,
and we think that Wynberg
slipped the key card to him.
So you haven't got the key card?
No, Lance Elliot must have it.
Well, I assume that you'll
be sorting it out.
Of course.
There's another problem.
The airline computers require
a thumbprint ID.
Can't we generate the fingerprint
from the police files?
No time.
It's 29 hours 'till we kick off.
But I think we'll be alright.
Our FAA contact agreed
to sell us his thumbprint.
So take this down.
Meet a Dr. G. Radley at
the Los Angeles Zoo
tomorrow at 1:30 at
the Chimpanzees.
What is it?
1:30?
And take $20,000.
Alright.
Consider it done.
Okay.
(phone clicks)
(light mood music)
(thudding)
Hey, you assholes!
(light mood music)
(engines rumbling)
The Amazon Basin
today, and leave
for Atlanta to conclude their
3-month world tour.
Many prominent
businessmen predict
that the implementation of
the Green Report
could slide the world
into another economic recession.
Hi.
I'm Debbie.
Call me, and I'll let you in
on my deepest fantasies.
1-900-769-9665.
Together we can
take a ride through
my wildest and most
intimate secrets.
Hi.
I need some room service.
Yes, I need, why
don't you give me
a hamburger, come
with French Fries?
(suspenseful instrumental music)
Hey, good evening, sir.
May I have your keys?
Look, I'm sorry, I
got to move the car.
Don't move it.
(water trickles)
(suspenseful instrumental music)
(door handle clicking)
(faucet creaks)
(door clicks open)
(suspenseful instrumental music)
(device clicking) (Lance grunts)
(dish clinks)
(light instrumental music)
Aha!
- Hey, young fellow.
- Hey.
Your dinner.
Apple pie.
Thank you.
And I just need your signature.
Alright.
So where you from?
Philly.
Well, welcome to Los Angeles.
Thank you.
Here you go.
- Thanks a lot.
- You have a good day, dude.
(hands slapping)
Alright.
(man talking on the TV)
(dish clinks)
[Man On TV] Build
the Brooklyn Bridge.
(laughs)
(playful instrumental music)
(door handle clicking)
(suspenseful instrumental music)
(key jingling)
(door thudding)
(footsteps thudding)
(man talking on TV)
(suspenseful instrumental music)
(footsteps thudding)
(door clicks open)
This must be the wrong room.
(dish clinks)
(silly instrumental
music from TV)
(suspenseful instrumental music)
Okay.
(gun clicks)
Okay, kid.
The game's over.
(suspenseful instrumental music)
Now we're not here to hurt you.
We just want the key card.
And then we'll be on our way.
(suspenseful instrumental music)
You listening, kid?
Now we ain't got all night.
(suspenseful instrumental music)
Now where's the key card?
(footsteps thudding)
(device clinking) (man
screaming)
(suspenseful instrumental music)
You little dick!
(banging) (crashing)
(men shouting) (upbeat
instrumental music)
(knife clicks)
(pillow thudding) (man grunting)
(dish clattering)
(Lance grunting)
(gentle instrumental music)
Why don't you beat up on
someone your own size?
One last chance.
Where's the key card?
I don't know what
you're talking about.
(grunting) (Lance pants)
What card, man?
Oh, that card.
(laughs)
Finish him off.
(upbeat instrumental music)
(Lance grunts)
(men grunting)
(thudding)
(upbeat instrumental music)
Tyler, let go, man.
Tyler.
(grunts) (thuds)
(Lance grunts)
No, no!
(Lance screaming)
(suspenseful instrumental music)
(soft clicking)
(ripping)
(car horn beeps)
(soft thudding)
(suspenseful instrumental music)
(ice thuds)
Tyler.
Come on, man.
I'm sorry, come on.
Come on, hey, buddy,
I didn't mean it.
Come on.
(lamp shattering) (man grunts)
(suspenseful instrumental music)
[Lance] Aha, wheels!
(thudding)
(suspenseful instrumental music)
(light instrumental music)
Look at you.
(thuds) (man grunts)
You pitiful piece of shit.
(suspenseful instrumental music)
Hey, man, where's my car?
It's right there.
Oh, good.
Hey, wait a minute,
that's not your car.
That's my uncle's.
- It's a family car, man.
- You weren't with those guys.
It's my uncle's.
I'm gonna fill it up
with gas, you know.
Come, it's not your, come on,
come on, come on back!
Shit!
(upbeat instrumental music)
♪ Every night by twelve ♪
♪ There'll be 20 Cinderellas
waiting by themselves ♪
♪ The next street corner
has a neon sign ♪
♪ Givin' you a plan for
a real good time ♪
♪ There are no exceptions ♪
♪ Everyone worldwide ♪
♪ Wishin' they were
here with us ♪
♪ On the Western side ♪
♪ Livin' it up ♪
♪ When on the western side ♪
♪ Life is amplified ♪
♪ Livin' it up ♪
(engines rumbling)
(birds singing)
(tire clinking)
(footsteps thudding)
(birds singing)
(dialing)
Do you see the car?
Okay, move in on it.
Yeah, move in.
And don't let his
age deceive you.
The kid's a pro.
(blades scraping ground)
(thudding)
(bag rustling)
Shit.
(money rustling)
Radley at chimps.
Right thumbprint.
(phone ringing)
Hello?
(beeping)
(birds singing) (phone clicks)
(suspenseful instrumental music)
(door clicks open)
(door thuds closed)
(kids shouting)
[Boy] Yeah!
(kids cheering)
(suspenseful instrumental music)
(kids shouting)
(upbeat instrumental music)
(door thuds closed)
(engine rumbles)
(thudding)
(car tires squeal)
Get off my car!
(upbeat instrumental music)
Oh my god, the windshield!
(tires squealing)
(upbeat instrumental music)
(blades scraping ground)
(tires squealing) (engine
roaring)
Get off my car!
(kids shouting)
(tires squealing) (boxes
thudding)
(hockey sticks scraping car)
Watch out!
Stop!
(glass shattering)
(blades scraping ground)
(upbeat instrumental music)
(glass shattering)
(woman screams)
No, no!
(hockey sticks
banging against car)
(woman shouting) (tires
squealing)
(upbeat instrumental music)
(blades scraping ground)
(kids shouting)
(upbeat instrumental music)
(blades scraping ground)
(woman screams) (tires squeal)
(engine roars) (crashing)
Oh, you've got to
help me, please!
- Get out of my cart!
- Look, these
guys are chasing me.
I hurt my ankle.
Please.
Just go, go, go!
(upbeat instrumental music)
Go, go, go!
[Girl] Oh, shit!
(upbeat instrumental music)
(car horn beeps)
(crashing)
(upbeat instrumental music)
(kids shouting)
(boy shouts)
(boy screams)
(crashing)
(upbeat instrumental music)
(cart thudding) (boy yells)
(kids yelling)
(upbeat instrumental music)
(thudding)
(boy groans)
(suspenseful instrumental music)
What the hell was
that all about?
(blades scraping ground)
(suspenseful instrumental music)
Okay, I'm really
sorry about this.
You must've really pissed
those guys off.
Yeah, I guess so.
(suspenseful instrumental music)
Shit.
Now what are we gonna do?
(suspenseful instrumental music)
(kids shouting)
(clicking)
(suspenseful instrumental music)
(hissing)
(kids shouting)
(flames whooshing)
(suspenseful instrumental music)
(engine roars)
(car tire squeal)
(kids shouting) (thudding)
(kids shouting)
(engine roars)
(thudding)
(car horn honks)
(engine rumbling)
(engine roars)
Where are we?
Downtown somewhere.
Listen, I appreciate your help.
I got to get out of here.
Hey, wait a minute.
Now, I think you
are forgetting something here.
Right.
I'm sorry.
And the groceries, huh?
(rustling)
Here.
Alright, bye.
Hey, wait a minute.
You know, we haven't
even introduced ourselves.
Elliot.
Lance Elliot.
Melinda Blake.
It's a pleasure.
(rustling)
Hey.
You know, you almost
got us killed.
Yeah, but I didn't.
You're fine and I'm fine.
Yeah, well, thanks
to me, because I saved us.
You know, that little
stunt you pulled.
I could sue you.
Or have you arrested,
you know that?
Let's see.
Reckless behavior,
disturbing the peace.
Damage to private property.
(bag rustles)
Hey, hey, hey, wait, wait, wait.
What do you want?
Half.
Half?
I can't do that.
Oh, no, you mean you
don't wanna do it.
No, no, I mean I can't
do that 'cause it's not mine.
Well, if it's not yours, then
why did you just give me $300?
(Lance sighs)
Oh.
I get it.
You stole this money, and that's
why those guys are chasing you.
It's not as bad as it seems.
I don't have time for this.
I have to go.
Can I have my money?
Please?
No, I wanna know
what's going on.
That's classified information.
If I tell you, I'm gonna
have to kill you.
(light instrumental music)
Hey, where you going?
I can't say.
Why not?
It's confidential.
Well, I'm going with you.
Okay.
Good.
(light instrumental music)
(elephant trumpeting)
(bird cawing)
(light instrumental music)
(elephant trumpets)
So who are we supposed
to meet, anyway?
I don't know.
You don't know
who we're meeting?
No, not exactly.
But I know when we
see him, we'll know.
You know, there must be
something you're not telling me.
I mean, for all I
know, there could
be like this drug deal going
down or something.
You're out of your mind.
It's not a drug deal.
(light instrumental music)
(monkeys chattering)
(people chattering)
This is the time it said.
Now all we have to do is look
for someone suspicious-looking.
(chimps chattering)
(suspenseful instrumental music)
That guy over there.
(chimps chattering)
Just stay here.
(footsteps thudding)
(chimps chattering)
(chimp squeals)
Jesus, Lance.
What's going on?
I mean, you don't
know who you're
supposed to meet,
what for, or even
where you're supposed
to meet him.
I mean, for all you know,
it could be a her.
Yeah, it could be, huh?
(Melinda scoffs)
I don't believe you.
Excuse me.
(suspenseful instrumental music)
Shit.
- Whoa!
(both yelling)
(footsteps thudding)
(chimp squeals)
Don't look back,
don't look back.
He was dead.
Oh my god.
That explains why
he missed the appointment.
Yeah, but it doesn't explain
why he was dead.
(both panting)
These guys are playing dirty.
Oh god, his thumb was gone.
Did you see that?
Somebody cut his thumb off.
That's one way of
getting a thumb print.
What?
Forget it, nothing, let's
just keep moving.
Shit, Lance.
I think somebody's following us.
Don't look back.
But I think someone is
really following us.
Yeah, I know someone's
following us.
You know?
How long's he been there?
Since the chimps.
Oh my god, do you
think he has a gun?
Probably.
Oh, shit, let's run.
No, let's not run.
Just be calm.
We're gonna go right
here and just hide, ready?
Go, go, go, go!
(suspenseful instrumental music)
Freeze, dirt bag.
You got a piece?
(gun clicks)
Turn around really slow.
No, don't shoot.
Don't shoot.
Trout!
Lance, Trout.
What are you?
The hell do you
think you're up to?
- What are you doing...?
- Are you
- completely out of your mind?
- You
know him?
Did you hear me?
I said get straight back.
Nobody was to know.
Now everybody knows.
The FBI knows, I got
Lomax all over me,
my job is on the,
Who is this?
Melinda, Melinda, Trout.
And your mother
is completely hysterical.
Trout, I'm onto something
really big here.
- Yeah, really big.
- Forget it.
I don't know what game you think
you're playing, but it's over.
I'm putting you on the
first plane back.
Just say goodbye to
your girlfriend.
- He's not my boyfriend.
- She's not my girlfriend.
What is the matter with you?
What is this, what
is this, what is
this strange little
espionage life?
We're going this way.
(birds chirping) (suspenseful
music)
Lomax is gonna have
your job, my job.
Don't tell Lomax.
Tell her nothing.
You better not have tried.
- See!
- Let's get out...
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
(suspenseful instrumental music)
What are you doing?
Come on.
Wait a minute,
Lance, Lance, come on.
Stop this.
Lance!
(suspenseful instrumental music)
Alligators!
(upbeat instrumental
music) (Melinda screams)
(footsteps thudding)
(suspenseful instrumental music)
(men yelling)
(alligator grunts)
(bird cawing)
(yelling)
(suspenseful instrumental music)
(man yelling)
Why did you guys interfere?
You made the kid run away.
Who's the brat to you?
Seamus Muh-goh-ick-uh-tee of
zoo security.
You wouldn't believe the kind of
things that happen here.
We're trying to
protect the animals
from reckless
behavior, these kids
that come, feeding
the chimps with junk food.
(elephant trumpets) (monkeys
squealing)
You guys got a problem here?
(suspenseful instrumental music)
It's getting a little crowded
around here, hmm?
Let's go.
(suspenseful instrumental music)
(car engine rumbles)
(footsteps thudding)
Lance, come on!
Lance!
Come on, get over here.
Move it.
We'll take care of you.
Come on, get in here.
Get 'em out out of here, now!
Move it!
(car engine roars)
You okay?
Yeah, think so.
You?
I'm okay.
It was close.
It was too close.
- I
hope that guy's
gonna be alright.
Who, Trout?
It's gonna be fine.
He can take care of himself.
(Melinda panting)
You know, I really
wish you would
let me know what's
going on here.
I'm with the CIA.
I'm a new recruit.
This right here, this is
why we're being chased, okay?
All that fuss for this?
Well this, this breaks into
some pretty
heavy-duty computers.
Sorry I drug you into all this.
It's alright.
It's actually been
kind of exciting.
(car engine roars)
So what are you gonna do now?
Probably go back
to Philly and try
to explain this whole mess.
Yeah, well, I kind of figured
things weren't going as planned.
It could be worse.
(light instrumental music)
(gun clicks)
So, where are we going?
Excuse me.
Where are we going?
Shit.
(popping) (popping)
(suspenseful instrumental music)
(car engine roars)
We're at the zoo.
Trout, now, listen
to me very carefully.
You found him once.
You can find him again.
It's gonna be difficult.
And Trout, I don't need to tell
you this is to be kept quiet,
no FBI, no local cops.
Just you and Lance.
(phone clicks) (birds singing)
(engine rumbles)
(door clicks open) (heels
clack on bricks)
(door clicks open)
(heels clack on bricks)
(door squeaks)
(computer beeping)
(keys clacking)
(switch clicking)
[Cashpot] Hmm.
Hey, hey.
(Melinda groans)
You okay?
Oh, where are we?
I don't know.
What happened?
I don't understand.
Those guys that picked us up
in the limo, they
weren't with the CIA.
I mean, I should have known.
Goddamnit, how could I
have been so stupid?
I thought they were with Trout.
Obviously that's what they
wanted us to think.
(car engine rumbles)
(doors click open)
(doors thudding)
(door slams)
(shoes clacking on bricks)
(briefcase clicks open)
A six million dollar deposit.
We will provide
the remaining six
when the plane crash
is completed.
Now, this is the part I enjoy.
Is Rudi Kseenbaum joining us?
Well, didn't you hear?
He was crushed in a
most unfortunate car accident.
Just two days ago.
(heels clacking)
(speaking in foreign language)
Well, darling.
Sorry to be breaking up
your little party,
but we should be linking up
in about 15 minutes.
Well, Rhonda, this is
Martin Luh-buh-son.
And this is Mr. Tim
Lacey, his associate.
- Pleasure to meet you.
- They've been
sent by the consortium to
observe our progress.
I was explaining to Martin that
we've had a slight delay.
Yes, but everything is under
control and on schedule.
Well, let's go, then.
Let's do it.
Thank you, gentlemen.
Shall I take care
of this for you, sir?
You keep a beady little eye
on that, now, Eddy.
Yes sir.
(footsteps thudding)
(door slamming)
(machine beeping)
The children have woken.
(machine beeps)
Mr. Lance Elliot.
I've waited for this moment.
I am Cashpot.
And your companion?
Melinda.
She's not a part
of this, though.
Well, of course she's not.
And she'll be
treated accordingly. (chuckles)
(man laughs)
Gentlemen, I would
very much like
you to meet my good
friend Melinda,
and secret agent in
training, shh, Mr. Lance Elliot.
I think you probably
deserve to know
what all this fuss
has been about.
(plane engine roaring)
(satellite whirring)
(beeping)
The plane carrying the
Science Committee
is now flying
approximately here.
Well, in about
seven minutes, the
plane will be moving
into the region
known as the Bermuda Triangle.
As we speak,
these environmental scientists
are probably being served lunch.
Filet mignon, Crème de
Champignon, and red wine sauce.
Or perhaps some
grilled sole squeezed
with a slice of fresh
lemon (laughs)
Is there some point
to all of this?
As you know, I'm in the business
of designing very specific
computer viruses,
and for today's
operation, we have
designed a virus
to intercept the
flying controls and cause
the plane to crash.
(men laughing)
Mighty nice, eh?
Rhonda will demonstrate.
(keys clacking)
(squealing) (beeping)
Ah. (clapping)
So you're gonna kill
all these people?
That's the general idea.
(computer beeping)
How can you do that?
Those men are trying
to save our environment.
How sweet.
You really are so naive.
These praised scientists are
only doing this for themselves.
Not to help you. (laughs)
Or the planet.
And this virus?
Yes, what about this virus?
Well, if it's so powerful, you
can infect other planes.
So what is your point?
My point is you'll be killing
hundreds of innocent people.
(laughs) Killing
innocent people.
You know, let me tell
you something, my little friend.
There's only one problem
with this planet.
Overpopulation.
This world is a vortex
of degradation.
A cesspool of
corruption and greed.
Billions are
starving, others are
gorging themselves into a
consumer oblivion.
Man is the cancer of the globe.
(laughs) And you're
worried about a
few thousand people dying
in plain crashes.
Well, personally, I
don't give a shit.
(beeping)
Man, you need some serious help.
Alright.
That does it.
(suspenseful instrumental music)
(footsteps thudding)
(door slams)
(creepy laughter)
[Melinda] No, no!
Now this game, you have to find
your way through the tunnels of
the pyramid into
Truh-ih-puh-tuh-on Commons Tomb.
That sounds like fine.
Oh, yes, it's great fun.
Especially if
you're not playing.
(evil laughter)
Wait a second,
no practice round?
Wouldn't do ya any good.
No one's ever made it out
of this room alive.
Good to know.
[Man] Welcome to Cashpot's
Pyramid of Doom.
(light instrumental music)
(evil laughter)
Crazy bastard.
[Man] Naferatutu is your guide.
Using your control,
lead him through
the passages of
time, for only he
can save you from the
obstacles of doom.
(footsteps thudding)
(suspenseful instrumental music)
(door creaking)
(door slams shut)
(clattering)
(suspenseful instrumental music)
Shit.
(axes whirring)
(game beeping)
(machine beeps)
Locking in satellite position.
Locking in.
Gentlemen, the excitement is
about to begin.
(grunting)
(keys clacking)
We've intercepted
and have control
of the satellite, gentlemen.
(game beeping)
(whirring)
(ominous instrumental music)
(rattling)
(clattering)
(ominous instrumental music)
(Lance panting)
Key card?
Okay.
Now to gain access
to the airline
communication
system and wait for
it to to track flight QS337.
(card scraping machine)
(beeping)
(keys clacking)
(rattling)
[Man] Congratulations.
You survived the
chamber of death
and entered the royal tomb.
But 3,000 years of purification
have produced a
highly toxic gas.
(ominous instrumental music)
(gas hissing)
(creaking)
(footsteps thudding)
Sweet thing.
Sorry I treated you so bad.
Just doing my job.
And now they're
so busy up there,
we can both use a
little time out. (laughs)
(shovel clanging) (man grunting)
(ominous instrumental music)
(whirring)
(gas hissing)
(beeping)
Entering codes.
(gas hissing)
(clanging)
(ominous instrumental music)
(Lance panting)
Now get me out of here!
(beeping)
[Woman] Codes accepted.
The thumb?
(clattering)
(beeping)
(thudding)
(whirring)
(beeping)
We're in!
(clapping)
- Ha-ha, yes!
(beeping)
Gentlemen, we've entered flight
QS337's computer.
(plane engine roaring)
We're flying at an
altitude of 31,266 feet
at a speed of 617 miles per hour
against a crosswind of 26 knots.
Gentlemen, the world
is about to witness
another mysterious phenomenon.
(beeping)
Stand-by for virus transmission.
(machine whirring)
10, nine, eight, seven.
(loud whirring)
Get the screens back.
I have to see this.
We've lost satellite
communication.
We've lost the link.
What?
How could that happen?
Wait, shut down!
Now, immediately!
(man laughs)
What happened?
Just a precaution, gentlemen.
A virus without a
path through it
might backfire into
our own system.
(man grumbling)
It's the satellite.
Oh. (laughs)
Not to worry, gentlemen.
It's a minor malfunction.
Probably just a loose
connection. (laughs)
(keys clacking)
(ominous instrumental music)
It's him.
It's Lance.
He's destroying the
satellite dish.
How did he get out of there?
This is impossible.
It's impossible, it's
impossible, it's
(slapping)
(ominous instrumental music)
(whirring) (footsteps thudding)
Get Tyler.
The kid's out.
Find him, shoot him
on sight, squash
him, cut him into
a million pieces,
I don't care what you do,
just get rid of him.
Now, this is outrageous.
I didn't pay you
millions of dollars to...
Oh, will you stop bleating
like a lost goat?
It's all under control.
See, gentlemen?
Tea and strawberry scones in
the computer room.
Let's lock into the backup
dish and continue.
(keys clacking)
(beeping)
(ominous instrumental music)
(gate squeaking)
(gun clicking)
(ominous instrumental music)
We should've done
this a long time ago.
(footsteps thudding)
(ominous instrumental music)
(Lance panting)
We got to get out of here
and get some help.
Yeah, easy for you to say.
They've got guys everywhere.
- I know.
- And they have guns.
- And we don't.
(sighs) I know.
(ominous instrumental music)
(gun clicking) (footsteps
thudding)
Ooh, I'm glad to see you kids
are still hanging around.
(Lance sighs)
Ah.
(keys clacking)
Satellite link complete.
Let's get back into the flight.
(keys clacking)
(beeping)
(ominous instrumental music)
Oh, my ankle.
(man groans)
(man screaming) (thudding)
Hey!
Hold it!
(ominous instrumental music)
Hey!
(grunting)
(locking clicking)
(ominous instrumental music)
Open the door!
(banging) (loud clattering)
Hey, what the
hell's happening out there?
[Man] It's Lance
and the girl, sir.
They've locked themselves in
the games room.
What do we do now?
Well, they can't go anywhere.
We'll deal with them later.
(creaking)
(playful instrumental music)
Don't touch anything.
(machine beeping)
(keys clacking)
(upbeat instrumental music)
(playful instrumental music)
(ominous instrumental music)
Back up.
(clanging) (ominous
instrumental music)
(keys clacking)
(upbeat instrumental music)
(ominous instrumental music)
I don't get it.
I'm trying to get access into
Cashpot's computer.
(upbeat instrumental music)
(electronic whirring)
(keys clacking)
Cashpot.
(upbeat instrumental music)
(machine beeping)
Locked in.
Okay.
Let's proceed with
virus transmission.
Stand by.
(ominous instrumental music)
(keys clacking)
(upbeat instrumental music)
[Man] Opponent confirmed.
Cashpot is not playing chess.
Do you still want to play?
(keys clacking)
(upbeat instrumental music)
(machine whirring)
Oh, we got in.
I can't believe we got in.
How is that possible?
You see, Cashpot, he linked up
all these games to
his main computer
to make sure nobody could win.
Aw, that's brilliant.
(beeping)
Transmitting the virus.
(keys clacking) (beeping)
Stop!
Stop the transmission.
Pawn to Queen four?
What's going on here?
(beeping) (upbeat
instrumental music)
It's our move.
Move the knight.
Knight to King four.
Will you shut up?
(keys clacking)
(laughs) Cashpot!
You little shit!
Well, it's your move.
(keys clacking)
No, don't touch.
You might confuse the computer.
What happened?
Will you shut up?
(upbeat instrumental music)
Now what?
They're not moving.
He'll move.
He'll play the game.
(beeping)
- There's
nothing we can do until he
switches off that game.
Should we interrupt the
virus transmission?
It's too late.
The virus is in our buffer.
It might leak into
our own system.
But if we move, we might be able
to transmit while the kid's
making his move, so let's move!
Knight to king three.
Pawn to queen four.
- The pawn?
- The knight.
The knight?
(keys clacking)
(upbeat instrumental music)
Oh, no.
[Man] Transmitting virus.
Yeah, they moved and
they just gave us the virus.
All we have to do is
just move and give it
right back to them,
and let's do that.
Look, you guys are
making a big mistake.
I will give each of you
a million dollars.
I think I'm gonna take your
Queen out, Cashpot.
No.
Don't move.
Just switch off that game.
(keys clacking)
No!
That's a check.
(ominous instrumental music)
(beeping)
(Cashpot sighs)
The virus has
infected our computer.
(chess piece boinging)
(ominous instrumental music)
(beeping)
[Man] Sir, there are some
people at the gate.
Tell 'em to piss off.
As a representative
of the consortium,
I demand to know
what's going on.
(ominous instrumental music)
Well, gentlemen,
Rhonda have certain
things that we're
going to be dealing
with, and we'll be back shortly.
You can't leave.
You can't abandon the mission!
(man grunting)
You're not going without us,
- goddamnit.
- Goddamn right, you're not.
(ominous instrumental music)
(gate whirring)
(footsteps thudding)
(ominous instrumental music)
All units, we're in.
Shawn, start sending the
rest of your men in.
Wait a minute.
Your guys know Lance
and the girl are in there?
They're just fine.
Tell 'em to be careful, will ya?
I don't want those
kids getting hurt.
Will you relax?
I've got the situation
completely under control.
Shawn, look out
for the two kids.
We want this as
clean as possible.
Freeze!
(gun popping)
(splashing) (gate creaking)
Freeze!
(rapid popping)
They're shooting at us.
Yes.
(upbeat instrumental music)
Lance, are ya in there?
(men shouting)
[Man] Hey, beat it!
(rapid popping) (loud popping)
Ahh!
(upbeat instrumental music)
(door clicks open)
Hey, hey, this is my money!
Six million dollars!
(clicking)
What?
My god, there's a bomb in there.
There's a bomb!
(helicopter whirring)
Come on in, let's go!
(helicopter engine roaring)
(ominous instrumental music)
This way, come on!
Close in fast!
They're getting
away in a chopper.
Lance and the girl are
in there somewhere.
I got to go in.
(helicopter whirring)
(ominous instrumental music)
(man yelling)
(gate squeaking)
(man grunts)
(man screams)
[Man] Freeze!
[Man] On the ground,
on the ground.
(grunting) (helicopter whirring)
(gun clicking) (footsteps
thudding)
Lance?
(door crashing in)
(clock ticking)
Lance?
(helicopter whirring)
You know, this isn't so bad.
We've still got 6
million dollars.
Sure do.
And the beach house off
the coast in Chile.
When in Rome.
Know it.
But don't forget new identities.
A bit of plastic
surgery might help.
Good idea. (laughs)
I was thinking, what about
banks in Monaco?
Doesn't that have a
nice ring to it?
Monaco, banks.
Sounds fabulous to me.
(ominous instrumental music)
(beeping)
(light instrumental music)
Lance?
Lance, can you hear me?
(beeping)
(upbeat instrumental music)
What does that mean?
(beeping)
(helicopter whirring)
(phone ringing)
Hello?
(chess piece boinging)
(whirring)
Who's that?
I don't know.
Hello?
(helicopter whirring)
Something wrong here.
There's something wrong!
We've been infected!
Infected?
- I'm losing control!
- No!
- We're going down.
- No, no.
(Cashpot whimpering)
Do something!
(helicopter whirring)
I'm losing control!
Help me out!
Do something!
(Cashpot screaming)
(both screaming)
(yelling)
We're gonna do down!
(woman yells)
(woman screaming) (helicopter
whirring)
Going down!
No!
(helicopter whirring)
(chess piece boinging)
(men yelling)
[Man] Come on, to the car!
[Man] That means you're
(footsteps thudding)
You got to believe us.
We had nothing to do with this!
- Forced us into it!
- [Man] In the car.
Lance?
(beeping)
Lance, where are you?
(car engines roaring)
So, what's it like
in Philadelphia?
(gentle instrumental music)
♪ You win some ♪
♪ You lose some ♪
♪ You know that's
what they say ♪
♪ But nothing and no one ♪
♪ Can take our love away ♪
♪ All I had to give ♪
♪ I just put in your hands ♪
♪ It'll get back to me ♪
♪ You make me wanna live ♪
♪ And give our hearts a chance ♪
♪ So you know ♪
♪ I know ♪
♪ Baby ♪
♪ We'll go ♪
♪ Above and beyond
the call of love ♪
♪ Anything else can
never be enough ♪
♪ Gettin' it together
has lifted us ♪
♪ Above and beyond
the call of love ♪
♪ It's startin' inside you ♪
♪ The wild world is calling ♪
♪ In a heartbeat you give me ♪
♪ The strength to carry on ♪
♪ And if you start to fall ♪
♪ I'll be there to cradle you ♪
♪ And make you fight again ♪
♪ I'm about to kiss the one ♪
♪ So many dreams to prove ♪
♪ We'll make it ♪
♪ Baby ♪
♪ We'll never let go ♪
♪ Above and beyond
the call of love ♪
♪ Anything else could
never be enough ♪
♪ Gettin' it together
has lifted us ♪
♪ Above and beyond
the call of love ♪
♪ Call of love ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Not believin' ♪
♪ You found me back
when I was givin' up ♪
♪ You're the inspiration
no matter what ♪
♪ We'll come through ♪
♪ I'll show you ♪
♪ We're gonna be working ♪
♪ Above and beyond
the call of love ♪
♪ Anything else could
never be enough ♪
♪ Gettin' it together
has lifted us ♪
♪ Above and beyond
the call of love ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Whoa ♪
♪ Gettin' it together
has lifted us ♪
♪ Above and beyond
the call of love ♪
♪ Whoa, whoa, whoa ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Gettin' it together
has lifted us ♪
♪ Above and beyond
the call of love ♪
♪ Whoa, oh, oh ♪
♪ Gettin' it together
has lifted us ♪
♪ Above and beyond
the call of love ♪
♪ Oh, oh ♪