Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
[man] Punching in
two grades right.
Two grades right.
Letting go in 10, 9, 8...
Ready to make
history, gentlemen.
[robot clanking, whirring]
NFX is in position.
Affirmative.
Initiate excavation.
Initiating excavation.
How we doing, Wilson?
Never better.
Thanks for asking.
Careful.
Careful, Dr. Marietta.
Tenth time's
the charm, Dr. Lopez.
The MEDUSA AI is not
fully uploaded to the NFX.
Still programming
field commands manually.
It takes time, gentlemen.
[alarm blares]
Really? Guys?
Guys, what's going on?
[loud whine]
[rapid beeping]
Dr. Lopez?
Wilson?
Damn it, guys.
What happened this time?
Wilson!
Can you hear me?
Loud and clear.
I had a total shutdown inside.
I believe the shutdown was
triggered by Dr. Lopez,
but I can't reach him
to confirm.
Well, I'm not gonna
stay in here!
Just hang tight.
Let me get over
to the mainframe.
Is MEDUSA acting up again or...
Dr. Marietta?
[feedback whine]
Great.
[beeping]
Agh!
Abel, what happened?
I don't know.
One minute, I'm initiating
the platform response.
And the next, MEDUSA
starts seizing my computer
and creating
a directive profile separate
from operating the robot.
MEDUSA should be following me,
but instead... it's driving.
System update received.
NFX is rebooting.
Guys, what's going on?
All right. Did you take
the NFX robot offline
to make sure it
doesn't malfunction?
I just did, but MEDUSA seems
to be one step ahead of me.
- Are you reading this?
- Copy Wilson, we read you.
Let's look at the code.
Switching to automatic systems.
I'm losing some
serious control here!
Wilson, are you doing that?
Wait... That's...
That's new code.
I see that.
You need to implement
a stop-gap firewall now!
Yes! Implementing now!
Well, somebody
hacked our system.
No. I checked.
Firewalls are tight.
She's coming up
with her own code.
That's impossible!
This looks like a data dump.
No, that's not possible either.
No, we can't
be reading this correctly.
Guys, there are a thousand
ways this could go sideways.
The variables are immense.
But when it's too complicated,
the best answer is the simplest.
It's not writing its own code.
It can't, at least
not at this level.
The AI doesn't have the...
[loud noises]
We need to shut MEDUSA down now.
It's already ahead of me.
I've calculated that
it's writing three million lines
of code every eight seconds.
That is exponentially increasing
by 42% every five minutes.
At that rate...
It's already run
the calculations
you referenced into.
Doctors, I can see it from here.
It's counting down
from three hours.
It's setting its own
benchmark for firewalls!
Those are all
smart-system firewalls.
Now it's working on
the military drone system.
Look. Its next
benchmark are the ARES robots
they just launched.
ARES robots
were never a good idea.
And all smart missiles,
global military networks!
It's outlining a strategy to
take control of them one by one!
It's not programmed to take
over the world's military.
Now it can!
If MEDUSA updated
its programming
to take over global militaries
without human programming,
without our programming,
that means...
It's become sentient, hmm?
That is impossible!
If it was, it would
carry out its own directive
to its logical conclusion.
It would use
the military to...
It would wipe out
all life on earth!
Everything goes offline now!
Ow! Damn it!
- You okay?
- I'm fine, fine.
Guys?
Dr. Lopez?
Marietta?
Marietta!
It's got the local network!
We don't have much time!
Look... Look!
MEDUSA has identified
us as a target.
- Why?
- We gotta go.
It's already breached
the military drones!
Get outta here! Go!
- Guys?
- Update complete.
Guys, go for Wilson!
Guys?
Returning to Spaceport
in T-minus five minutes.
All personnel must
vacate the premises.
Lose all tech!
Anything it can use to ping us!
Phones, tablets, ear pods,
anything with a chip!
Dr. Lopez!
Marietta!
Okay, I'm abandoning Zone 39.
I'm heading back to camp!
[grunts]
Okay, I'm out.
Doctors, can you hear me?
Guys? Damn it!
Years ago I created a device
that could override
the bunker's mag-locks.
Hopefully, it's still
hidden here.
Found it!
I just need to enter
the right code.
It's not shutting it down.
Let me try.
Once we get inside, we need to
contact NSA, DoD, all of them!
Abel, I'm trying to focus!
Wait. Let me try this.
All right, listen.
Once we get inside,
maybe we can use
the bunker's computers
to hack in...
[door opens]
I got it!
- Drones are inbound!
- Crap!
I'm on my way.
Wait!
Abel!
No!
One...
Agh!
You okay?
I got the signal.
I told you to stay underground.
Let's go.
You're shaking.
Did they malfunction
and MEDUSA targeted
Lopez and Marietta?
A robot that holds a grudge?
What did they do to it?
I don't know.
I'm probably a target.
You're not a target
unless someone
programmed you as a target.
Maybe it thinks I know
how to work the NFX robot.
- But you don't know.
- I know I don't know!
You know who does?
You broke up over a year ago.
She can't still be upset.
Her dad just died...
I...
It's better if it comes
from someone she knows.
Yeah.
She's a bad-ass.
She can handle this.
[banging sound]
Okay, you are in invisible mode
and inside the firewall.
[man] Got eyes on the package
heading south on 53rd.
Sending coordinates.
Got it!
Rerouting now.
Got it, sending a ping
to the intersection.
Threading the needle.
Landing in five, four...
Three, two, one.
Punch the feed.
All yours.
Hello, everyone.
Free food delivery
courtesy of Silicorp.
Yes, that's right.
We were gonna serve
this high-end surf and turf
food truck to our
executive staff today.
But in the spirit of giving,
we thought you
all should enjoy
a wonderful holiday
meal instead.
And remember, "At Silicorp,
you're not just a
binary number, you're family."
Wow, that was touching,
Gray Scout.
Okay, everyone log out of
there, and cover your IP trail
before Silicorp realizes
that it's been hacked.
That must be
a new record, Tara.
Whatever.
She had a head start.
I got stuff to do.
Wow.
Still a sore loser just
like he was in high school.
You want me to send him
some malware?
Malware?
Jorge, no.
Come on, no!
Hey, remember what I told you.
A good hacker doesn't go after
every dog that barks, okay?
As much as I like
to see him squirm,
he'll be back again tomorrow.
He can't resist us.
You.
He can't resist you, you mean.
[beeping]
Couldn't keep off the board,
could you, Cube?
Tara? You there?
Tara?
Is that Wilson?
He knows he should
be calling you by
your hacker name,
Gray Scout.
Do you have a private line
where I could talk to you?
It's about your father.
My dad?
Why don't you just call
me on the...
We were testing our
NFX rescue robotic unit today
and, uh...
there was an accident.
He...
He... there was a drone.
A drone?
It came from nowhere,
a military drone.
Dr. Marietta got into
the bunker, but your father...
he didn't make it.
I don't understand.
Wh... why would a drone...
I don't know.
I don't know if
this was sabotage.
I don't know if somebody
hacked into the mainframe,
but he was definitely targeted.
Probably Marietta as well,
probably me.
Wilson, I...
Tara? Tara!
Hey, come in!
Tara?
Tara, what are you doing?
You can't do that!
Don't touch me!
What even is this?
I've never seen this before.
Is that a CryptoMix?
No.
It's a Qbit language
my dad taught me.
He said if anything
suspicious ever happens,
enter that language here on
this computer to protect myself.
You think you're in trouble?
Not as in trouble as the
assholes who killed my father.
What are you doing?
I just sent a bullet
to take out 3.6%
of the nation's drone
coding program.
What?
At least they can't
keep killing people.
Tara, don't!
You happy now?
You think that's gonna
solve everything?
Get out!
You probably just signaled
4,000 NSA mainframe computers
to this location!
So maybe you shouldn't be
here when the FBI arrives!
My DNA is all over this shit!
This is what they live for!
There's probably some jacked up
computer targeting us right now!
Oh, no, no, no!
Tara, what did you do?
Wilson, she hacked
the Pentagon.
She's screwed.
I think we're all screwed.
What's happening?
Bastards.
I used Qbit code and they
echoed it right back at me.
Great.
So what do you think?
50 years in prison
for shutting down
our nation's
military drone program?
100 years?
200?
They just killed
half our system!
What is this?
Oh, my God,
photos from my smart phones.
Why?
I'm gonna try
to reverse the ping.
Get an IP on it!
Sending over to you now.
Check it out.
Oh, shit.
What?
You're not gonna like it.
Spaceport, where your dad
works... worked.
I'm sorry.
That's where MEDUSA is?
Damn!
What's MEDUSA?
Jorge, we have a lot bigger
problems than going to prison.
It's the quantum AI
my dad was working on.
It can find anyone.
We need to hit
the kill switches now!
And grab our go bags!
What?
The drones.
- Here?
- No.
Gray Scout.
Tara!
Gray Scout, come in!
We're a little busy right now.
There's no time!
You have to get outta there now!
What? Why?
We tracked three
tier three military drones
- to your location!
- What? How?
How, what do we...
I don't know!
It senses heat!
Are you near a power plant?
Go hide in there!
Destroy everything.
Hibachi style!
Tara, Jorge, can you hear me?
You need to get outta there now!
What about us?
Get everything ready.
If we have to leave,
we'll do it quickly.
Run!
[alarm blaring]
Drones!
Help us!
Robot apocalypse!
Active shooter!
Everybody out back!
Jorge!
Listen, it's dangerous!
You don't have to do this!
If you want, you can
just go out!
Tara, we're in this together.
Fine.
We're trapped.
I have an idea.
- Hibachi.
Hey!
You gonna pay for all that?
Hurry up, Tara!
Light the fuse!
[explosions]
Whoa.
You ever seen one
of these before?
Never been this close
to one before.
It's an entire drone brain.
It's got a whole control panel.
Hey, that thing
just tried to kill us.
But I think it's dead.
We should take it.
Come on.
It's okay.
Oh...
You know what to do with it?
Yeah.
Yeah, I do.
Let's go.
Hurry!
I can hear more drones!
[rapid beeping]
Wait.
They turned around?
Wilson...
We didn't make it to
the power plant.
The drones immediately
found us.
Are the drones
still chasing you?
No, their targeting systems
must be overwhelmed.
I think we lost them.
Good. The grid is freaking
out over here.
Plus, I don't know
if you've seen the news.
But there are rolling
blackouts in New York,
Chicago, San Francisco
and Alabama.
They just had a blackout
in London.
Wilson, listen.
Just before Jorge and
I escaped from the drones,
we received a D.M. from
the NSA server
directed to me by name,
putting me at the top
of the terror watch list.
It seized my computer,
then put out a pin for
the entire DoD to track.
Yeah. I saw that when I was
controlling the NFX robot.
Look, virgin code
was being written
at an astronomical speed.
We figured it was MEDUSA.
I was afraid of that.
The IP was scattered but
I tracked it back to Spaceport.
But how could MEDUSA be
responsible for all of this?
What if someone hacked into it?
It's gotta be.
No. The coding strings
were unlike anything
that I've ever seen.
They were shorthand,
like a stenographer.
This...
This coding doesn't exist!
But why would it
be targeting us?
It's targeting me.
Because it knows you're
Dr. Abel Lopez's daughter!
I think it came
after me
because I used the exact
same quantum language
as my dad when I hacked
the DoD.
Tara sent a bullet
into the heart
of the US Military
Cyber system.
We saw.
But this isn't the military.
MEDUSA has gone rogue and it's
not just targeting you.
It's targeting everyone.
Look, I don't have long.
This place is
crawling with drones.
I'm the only one now
who's perfectly fluent
at coding in my
dad's Qbit language.
MEDUSA runs at a quantum system,
so its language is Qbit based.
I might be able to hack it,
but I need hands-on access.
But, Tara, that's not an
impossible language to crack.
The Pentagon has programmers
who work on those systems.
My dad added variants
to the code,
variants that I know
from him teaching me.
Not even Marietta is as good
as I am at this kind of code.
It will take other
programmers way too long
to figure it out,
including him.
Listen, the AI wants to target
and kill every possible threat.
We need to stop it.
Now.
So who's gonna stop it?
We are.
We gotta work quickly.
Wilson, we used to hang out at
the spaceport in the summer.
Remember? We know this place.
We used to look up
at the stars there.
I remember!
But there's no way.
Listen, I'm not asking you
to go back.
I'm going.
No! Gray Scout, you don't know
what you're saying!
Listen, if I don't
stop it before
the upload sequence completes,
the possibility of MEDUSA
overriding all
computers and satellites,
basically everything,
in a relatively short time is...
You're not a one-person army!
They have people for this!
A system like that has
totally unique hardware, Tara.
Z's right.
Its circuitry
and subzero-Kelvin cooling
are one-of-a-kind.
Yes, that's why I have
to go Spaceport directly.
No, Tara, we need
tons of processing
and an open-source platform.
No. If I hack it over a network,
that would allow it
to track me down
as soon as I enter
a single line.
Its nationwide networking
defenses are too powerful
and too advanced for
me to hack it remotely.
I need to be there in person
to patch it in directly
and set
a quantum-data bomb.
Tara, you're gonna need help!
Any smart weapons
there will kill you
as soon as you get close
to the AI!
No, no, no.
Don't try to help.
Anybody who tries to help
is gonna get us traced,
targeted and killed.
Tara, I'm not just gonna
let you die out there!
You're too important
to all of us!
Plus, you're only
a couple hours away.
If you need a direct patch,
then you'll also need someone
to map out the mainframe
to send out the data bomb.
If everyone at the Spaceport
gets killed,
you'll still need someone
to help you get it.
If you're going, I'm going.
We're gonna stop it with you.
When you reach Huntsville,
we'll be there.
You may be a genius hacker,
but you can't do this alone.
You're gonna be outnumbered,
so you're gonna need people
that you can trust.
Let us help you.
Hey, we're gonna need
all the help we can get.
All right.
Meet us at the Spaceport.
I'm going to need my Dark Web
contact to make this happen.
We're gonna need Red Dragon.
Red Dragon?
Really, Gray?
Are you sure about that?
Do we have any other choice?
It's at least a six-hour drive
for us to get there
and we'll need every second
to get ahead of the AI
as it smashes firewalls.
To do that, we'll need gear
to fight against the drones
and anything else MEDUSA
throws at us.
Plus, she owes me a favor.
I don't know, Tara.
No one messes with Red Dragon.
Not even the Feds!
Her and I have
an understanding, okay?
Wilson, meet us,
but be careful. No tech!
Okay, remember
they will find you.
There's cameras everywhere.
So don't bring any microphones,
internet connections,
anything with digital cameras,
anything that
can trace you to me.
Tara! Tara!
They found you!
You're on my screen!
And if you're on my screen...
That means they found us.
Zee! Zee!
Go! Go! Go!
I'm on it.
Come on, come on, come on!
Okay, we gotta go! Come on!
Come on!
Wait.
Do you hear that?
Drones.
Now what?
I can hear them.
Come on, come on.
It's not pretty, but I have
something that will protect us.
What is it?
They're getting closer!
Two seconds.
What was that?
Invisibility cloak.
Military grade.
How did you get your
hands on that?
They're not available.
I wasn't waiting.
I created my own.
Okay.
Red Dragon should be here!
This way, hurry.
This is gonna take all day.
That's it!
The antenna!
[Jorge] You're crazy.
No one's here.
There it is.
Okay, but how do you know that?
GMC Automotive put on an early
camper prototype in the 80s.
They called it the Dragon.
Really?
That... and I can see a
grounded hub of CAT7 wires
underneath the chassis.
And about four, five,
six routers attached
to the roof,
not to mention three remotes
in the surrounding trees
there, there, and there.
You missed 10
satellite transmitters,
and about three miles of
cabling and ground wires,
and a whole lotta scramblers.
Come on in.
It's okay.
You're safe here.
Come on, Gray Scout.
Let's go.
I've been monitoring
you for a while.
You're in an anti-EMP
van, fully-loaded,
lead-lined, off the grid.
MEDUSA can't see us,
at least not yet.
Off the grid?
With that electronic footprint?
Catch your breath.
Thanks.
Drink.
I saw what happened.
Good job with those drones,
by the way.
I must say, I really am
impressed you made it here.
I didn't think
you'd still be here.
Well, not after this.
You two have more heat
on you than an LHC
in a pressure vacuum.
If MEDUSA hasn't
figured out already, she will.
She'll be in full control
within the next couple hours,
maybe even sooner.
I'm sorry about your dad,
but screw him.
Excuse me?
Hey, it's his machine that's
going to destroy the world.
Look, I'm sure
he's a cool guy and all
and took you to Space Camp
when you were younger.
But he gets no passes.
My dad was creating machines
to help save people.
Yeah, it wasn't his fault.
MEDUSA's the one who...
Really?
Because if he didn't exist,
the MEDUSA wouldn't exist.
But he did and it does,
so here we are.
We're trying to stop it.
You can't.
- We're trying.
- It's self-aware.
It's building an army.
It's...
A machine.
No. Then you go unplug it, but
you know it's not that easy.
It's not just a machine.
It's a cancer
that's metastasizing.
We can stop it before the
upload sequence completes.
I know what it's capable of.
We've already seen it.
It's gonna seize
the world's military.
Of course it is.
Okay.
So that means it not only
needs to run a search function
to find weapons.
But it also has to teach
itself to break the firewalls,
then it has to hack
them around the world.
Even on a quantum system, that
buys us, what, 15, 20 minutes?
That gives you nothing.
It's something.
Even on your best day,
it took you 10 minutes
to hack the World Bank.
It's gonna take us at
least that amount of time
to hack a quantum AI,
so we don't have
10 minutes to waste.
We're gonna need
analog transportation
and as much analog tech
and weapons as we can carry.
You can't hide
from surveillance.
You've been telling me you
liked my Qbit-level coding
and reference-free algorithms.
Oh, come on.
That's not fair.
I gave you every
closed-source Q codes
to get you an
unbreakable ghost IP.
I knew this day would come.
It always does.
Desperate and
morally compromised.
You still owe me.
That IP got my place swatted!
I hope the heist was worth it.
Hey, I ran a trace
of MEDUSA's first few lines
of code under your IP.
It crashed my burner system.
I need to be there in person,
no networks!
It's the only way.
It'll have to be a Sysconfig
databomb sliding-base
so I can mess
with its power.
Only then can it be
destroyed, physically.
Okay, but you'll need
someone to map the interface
to make that bomb
deliverable, though,
assuming the AI
doesn't kill them first.
I'm not willing to
fall on that sword.
We're not asking.
I assume you destroyed all your
traceable software and info?
Hibachi style.
Yeah, it's all fried.
What we didn't burn,
the drones did.
Good, yeah.
Well, if anything happens
to me, I have Black Fire.
It's my kill-all virus.
I have one,
my cousin Derek has the other.
He's my fail-safe.
Hey, here.
We got one of the drones.
It was pretty banged up
from the fireworks.
But Jorge managed
to rip out the brains.
I figured it's configured for
military networking commands,
so I can probably use it to hack
the system over at Spaceport.
Let me see that.
Yeah, this is nothing like what
we've seen on the black market.
Besides having an obscene
amount of memory,
it's got an unusual
audio receiver right here.
Its sensitivity is measured
in 10,000ths of a hertz.
I can't really figure out why.
And a weird looking solenoid.
Yeah. That hooks up
to a capacitor
that takes
its electrical load way up,
but I'm still not sure why.
Almost like defibrillator.
It closes in on a person,
then electrocutes them
in the chest or the head.
Quite an efficient killing
instead of blowing someone up.
Here, look.
It didn't shoot 'em.
Right, but the targeting
system of the drones
show a huge electrical spike.
Heart attack maybe?
Maybe.
I've never seen that
on a military drone before,
but it could be.
Tara, this AI is
nothing to play with.
Yeah, it's probably
how it killed my dad.
I'm sorry I showed you that,
but if it helps,
I don't think he suffered.
It's like he shut down
and you were right to
keep the drone brain.
If you hard patch this to
a security network
you can gain access
to a restricted area
if it thinks you're a drone.
So although the AI
has insane ability
to make very accurate
probabilistic choices
and track everything you do,
it still sees people as
people and tech as tech.
And don't forget, it can track
you almost everywhere you go.
You mean, like
via orbital satellites?
No, no.
It's working its way
to that, but no.
Tara, it knows
everything about you.
It knows everyone
you've ever known.
It knows our history online.
So that it probably knows
that I'm here.
Yes, and when it's
looking for you,
it uses things like that drone
that can hear a fly
in a beehive.
It's not gonna let
some hacker stand in the way
of it destroying the world.
Do you get it?
This is an EMP pulse grenade.
Once activated, you have
five seconds to hit your target
before an EMP blast,
canceling out all electronics
within a 50-yard radius.
So, you wanna stay way
clear of it.
Do you have your
quantum tablet on you?
This is your
father's technology.
I'm gonna download a Nano cloak
shield to your quantum tablet.
Also, this not only
refracts light
to make you invisible
to cameras,
but is also a Penrose polymer
which cancels out
all heat signatures
and that includes
radar or sonar.
- You got all that?
- Invisibility. Copy.
We need firepower.
It thinks we're terrorists, it
keep on firing missiles at us.
You have to stop
taking this personal.
To MEDUSA, you are only an
answer to a binary question.
And what's the question?
How do I stop
her from deprogramming me?
Either way, you'll need this.
This is an AK-47,
fully automatic.
Safety's here, trigger's here.
They're hard to come by,
so you're gonna need it.
You know how to shoot?
My dad was a gun guy, took me
to the range a few times.
Good.
Here, look at this.
This is happening now,
all over the world?
Damn, that's MEDUSA?
Yes, and this is just a start.
MEDUSA is throwing
Moore's Law out the window.
Once it seizes access to it,
it's gonna take advantage of it.
This is nuts.
MEDUSA was created to help
my dad's NFX rescue robot.
It was designed
to help save people.
Maybe it is.
Maybe it's saving us
from ourselves.
No one deserves this.
Maybe not.
Red Dragon!
Come in, Red Dragon!
Come in.
This is Red Dragon.
It's me, Derek!
Can you hear me?
It's my cousin Derek.
You were right, Red Dragon.
Medusa isn't just using drones.
I'm headed back
to the compound.
I'll call you when I get there.
Look alive, boys!
We're getting hit
from all sides!
We're dealing with
cyborgs here.
I can hold them off for now,
but hurry!
Derek!
What is he talking about?
What cyborg machines?
It's the ARES project.
I don't know much about it.
It's Black Ops.
Used for military
high target asserts.
I was afraid that if MEDUSA
was able to control the system,
this would be the first thing
it would control.
- What?
- Jorge, come on.
What makes these ultra scary
is that they shoot microchips.
What?
Microchips that take over
your body and control you.
Wait.
Control you how?
They're designed to attach
to the central nervous system
of humans, controlling
and subduing them.
If MEDUSA is able to hack
into those chips,
they can directly
control human behavior.
Kill yourself,
your fellow soldier, anything.
It just gets worse and worse.
All right, so if MEDUSA
has control of the ARES project,
then that means she's gaining
control faster than we know it?
MEDUSA is seizing
networks across
the entire globe right now.
Damn it!
The drones have entered
my five-mile perimeter.
Medusa found us.
Jorge, drive the van!
Go!
Hey!
Take this, take this.
Everything is fully supplied,
all right?
Listen, this is a map to my
cousin Derek's compound.
Wave this out of the window
as you approach so
they know I sent you.
Hey, thanks, Brenda.
It's Red Dragon.
But you can call me Brenda
if you make it back alive.
Come on.
Keys are in the wheel well.
It's old school.
No electronics.
No power steering, no power
brakes, no satellite radio?
Thanks, Red Dragon.
Don't thank me.
Just go save the world.
Shit, I think I hear the drones.
- Go!
- What about you?
Just go!
Tara!
They're going to lock onto us!
- Hold the wheel!
- What?
Hold the wheel!
Woo!
Let's go!
What was that thing?
Just another pause
in the time clock.
Woo!
Oh, no, no, no.
What are you doing?
No!
This is gonna feel so good.
[screams]
[gasps]
Hey...
We got a job to do.
It's only a matter of time.
Shh!
There are phone lines
going into that tunnel.
We hack them and lure
as many of those things
down there as we can.
Then we blow up the tunnel.
You like to blow
things up, right?
You know I do.
Come on.
Hey, a couple more exits.
I gotta pee.
Tara?
Hey, you good?
Huh?
You want a drink?
No, I'm good.
Was that a camera flash?
Huh?
Jesus!
Tara, we got company!
MEDUSA...
Ah, this is not good!
This is not good!
Jorge, listen to me.
I need you to grab the AK-47
and use it.
Yeah.
I got it. I got it.
You ever use an AK-47 before?
What? No!
Today's your lucky day.
Take it!
But I don't know...
I don't know how to use it!
Jorge, take the wheel
or use the gun!
We have very limited
options here!
I'm running out of bullets!
Shit!
Next exit's ours!
[laughing]
Woo!
Shit.
[Wilson] I can hear them,
they're almost here!
[Zee] Done.
The bomb is armed.
There's an exit above us.
Hurry!
[screams]
Nice moves.
Whoa, yeah.
We did it.
How many do you think we got?
Dozens.
Come on.
- Let's go to the Spaceport.
- Okay.
Whoa.
Get the map from my bag.
Red Dragon's cousin
is here somewhere.
Take a right here!
You think we outran 'em?
In this truck? No.
Look out!
Ares!
Take a right here.
Welcome, Gray Scout.
Here's some coffee.
Cici makes it strong.
Thank you.
You guys got an update
on the drone situation?
Yeah. They came in about
half an hour ago.
My sources are saying that the
drones, they're not listening
to any commands from the DoD
and they're starting to patrol
in all cities.
Large and small.
Pretty messed up, right?
We got a distress call
coming from the east coast.
They're all over Europe, going
from building to building,
street to street,
wiping 'em all out.
Wait, are these
the ARES sentinels
that Red Dragon mentioned?
Yep.
We just can't stand down,
not without armor-piercing
ammo at least.
Just to know what you guys
are up against,
they're taking out
oil refineries, gas stations,
just blowing 'em up.
Uh, listen...
We know.
We knew about Red Dragon
the second it happened.
Years back, she sent me this.
What is it?
It's a fail-safe.
One lights up blue to check in.
Red for help,
green means she uploaded
some kind of info into
our private server.
If both are black...
Means her heart stopped.
She talked a lot about you.
She told me to give this to you.
Thank you.
There's an RIFD chip
on the back.
I know.
Do you know what for?
No.
You're safe here for a minute.
Relax for a second and
take anything you need.
These walls are lead-lined.
And there's cameras up
all over the place.
It used to be a mechanic's shop.
We can put your truck on stilts,
check it out if you like.
Shit!
Yeah.
Yeah, all right, as long as
there's no oil or gas leaks.
We don't wanna
waste too much time.
Maybe we could check if
there's a tracker on it?
Hopefully, this is enough
to get us to the Spaceport.
Let's hope so.
Especially with what
you're up against.
And we'll stock the truck
with gas, food and water.
Yo, look at this!
Hey, hey, hey!
It's loaded, man.
Is that a good luck charm?
Sort of, yeah.
It's kind of helps center me.
It was my dad's.
He was spinning it
the first time
he taught me quantum computing.
I thought I knew so much about
hacking and coding as a kid.
Like I had all the
secrets to the universe
figured out in zeroes and ones.
- Then he showed me.
- Showed you what?
If I asked you to call it
on a flip, heads or tails,
could you do it?
Sure.
Heads.
Tails?
Derek's right.
Heads.
And that's basic code.
Its either a one or a zero
and it's a 50-50 shot that
either you or I get it right.
But what if it was spinning?
Could you call it?
I don't know.
- Heads?
- Tails.
You're both right.
See, when it's spinning,
it's in a state
of super position,
which means that it's both.
See? Tails. I called it.
In the quantum world,
Qbits become entangled,
so no matter how they land,
they always influence and
affect each other.
It's kind of like us.
Whoever we become
entangled with
eventually becomes part
of our solution.
I'm more of a heads
or tails guy.
I like to know my odds.
Quiet!
I don't hear it anymore.
Maybe it's gone.
[steady beeping]
I think that's Dr. Marietta
trying to give us a signal.
Tara? You there?
Tara?
Wilson, get off the line.
We have a few minutes.
I'm doing some IR bouncing,
back to my ghosting days.
Where are you?
Right outside Spaceport.
Zee's been working out
the Qbit functions
to determine MEDUSA's
rate of expansion.
We got a little less than
85 minutes before it's too late.
Can you do that?
I don't think I can do
much without you.
Yeah, I can do that.
Tara, you're the only one
truly fluent in its language,
but you will need me to map
that interface for you.
You might need
Dr. Marietta's help.
So he is alive?
Last I saw him.
He was heading in the bunker
with your father.
The bunker looks
like an ancient doorway.
I don't know why.
It has a smart lock system
that I powered down.
But it can't be opened
unless he powers it up,
drawing the drones.
We'll get there ASAP.
We're armed with
mechanical weapons
and an old school car
they can't trace.
As for Dr. Marietta, we'll
bring tools and manpower
to pry open the lock manually.
No, no! He's sealed
until it powers up.
If I engage the locks
and try to leave,
it'll instantly attract
their attention.
We got inbound hostiles!
We need to get you packed
and out of here now!
Wilson, I...
[static]
What's happening?
You lose connection?
No, this is on her end.
And, remember,
they can't get in.
Are you sure about that?
Holy shit!
I'm gonna activate the shield.
It's go time!
Guys, we gotta get out of here.
Shh!
They know we're here!
We gotta go now!
[shouting]
Move!
Ah!
Cici!
What are you doing?
[screams]
No!
I seen the specs on ARES.
We can't outrun 'em,
we can't outfight 'em.
The Red Dragon software!
Did you download it?
The invisibility cloak?
Doing it now.
What are you doing?
This shield refracts
light and absorbs heat,
making us invisible to them.
I hope this works!
Red Dragon gave us this
old school car
so we wouldn't be detected.
That's why I drive
these type of cars.
You guys have
everything you... ah!
- Oh! Derek!
- Shit!
- I got it, go!
- Damn it!
Go!
[grunting]
Ah!
How are you doing?
What the hell is that?
You gotta be shitting me.
What do we do?
Let's see what Derek gave us.
RPG Grenade Launcher!
You ready for this?
Keep it steady!
I'm trying!
Get closer!
- Closer!
- I'm driving!
Jorge!
I'm trying!
Ah!
Yah!
This is bad, Zee.
There's ARES and drones
patrolling this whole area.
I hope Tara has
more firepower than this.
Hey, my IEDs got us
this far, didn't they?
She's tough, okay?
She kicked our butts in
the hacking competition.
She'll be here.
You know you can't use that,
not now,
not when we're so close.
I know. I...
I just wanna know if she's okay.
She's fine.
- Oh! Damn it!
- Whoa!
- Jorge!
Jorge!
Oh, my God, you scared me, man.
Where's Tara?
She still at
the bunker or...
No.
What?
She... she...
The ARES, they're
getting massive updates
every nanosecond.
They came out of nowhere.
I'm so sorry.
We need to find Marietta.
He can put a stop to this.
Just grab what you need.
I don't know what I need.
Then don't grab anything, right?
Come on!
Let's go!
Okay?
[Jorge] Are you sure that
using the drone brain
to trigger the lock
is going to work?
I mean, it still shares
the same formatting protocols
as the AI.
[Wilson] That's exactly why
it won't get the AI's attention.
The AI will read it
as a drone trigger
in the lock instead
of a person
as part of its
safety protocol, right?
So if we do want to destroy
the ARES and the drones,
then Jorge and I already
worked it out. All right?
Even the smartest AI
doesn't think like us.
It does everything
in the most perfect
way possible.
It doesn't take into account
the quantity of people
or the amount of those
who are heavily armed.
So once we destroy that ARES
and we get the doctor out,
we send Jorge with the
majority of our weapons.
And then Zee, you and I,
we go to the Spaceport.
What do you mean,
the majority of our weapons?
Whoever has the most weapons
and is using them
on the robots will be perceived
as the bigger threat.
Yeah.
MEDUSA is constantly calibrating
its responses to our decisions.
It knows we're headed here.
It knows that
we can't hack into it
from the outside and
it knows that we're armed.
So it's going to assume
that we'll shoot our way in.
It'll break ranks.
And when it does that,
it'll send the most robots
after whoever
has the most weapons.
Can't go after
every dog that barks.
But once it runs
facial recognition on you,
MEDUSA's gonna ignore
every distraction
and just send all the drones
straight to you.
Doesn't matter.
It'll buy us some time.
I'll do it.
I'll be the bait, not Jorge.
No, no!
It should be me!
The two of you need to get
to Dr. Marietta.
I got the weapons
to distract it.
Wow, I...
Thank me by destroying
these things.
Okay, we crossed
a bridge back there.
I'm gonna draw them to it
and use it as a trap.
See you guys soon, right?
Yeah.
Come on.
Dr. Marietta is
in a bunker over there.
Come on.
Kind of conspicuous for
a hidden underground bunker,
don't you think?
That's the logic.
Hide things in plain sight.
Plus, if people do
go up to it...
They get in trouble.
No.
It triggers MEDUSA.
That's Zee.
She's still shooting.
Just focus.
Wilson!
Wilson?
I can't believe it, Wilson.
And I don't know who you are,
but you're my favorite
person in the whole world.
I'm Jorge.
I used to work with...
Tara's dead.
One of the ARES got her.
I'm sorry.
It's all my fault.
Doctor, what do we need to do?
- [banging sound]
- What's that?
I think they're trying
to get in!
They're getting smarter.
Look, when I locked myself in,
I figured I could take
the communications tunnel
directly to base.
But there are probably
robots already
approaching through there,
We'd all be trapped.
What if we trigger
the EMP grenade in here?
No, no, no.
The bunker is steel
reinforced, lead-lined.
It's three feet thick.
The pulse wouldn't even
kill a phone on the roof.
But it would surge
through the computer console,
blow up and likely kill us all.
Ah!
But you can
communicate wirelessly?
Yes, yes.
There's a central antenna
that runs
from the console
to a patch.
- And it carries a current?
- Exactly.
Okay, well, if the pulse
is electromagnetic
then we get a couple of copper
wires and create a solenoid.
Yes!
So the pulse we
transferred from
electromagnetic into electric.
We fry them with electricity.
It's a Tesla coil!
But those grenades, they go
off in only a few seconds!
Not this time.
I've got a bomb
and I'm gonna recalibrate it
to its original base function,
give us enough time
to reach the tunnel.
But if you turn it on,
won't it trigger more robots?
The pulse will take them out.
Jorge, I'm going to need
you to go over there
and grab the antenna wire.
Marietta?
Grab the cable and plug
it up to the computer.
Go, go, go!
Move quickly, gentleman.
Come on!
Let's go, let's go!
Right, uh... How much longer
'til MEDUSA fully takes over?
20 minutes, maybe less.
There's like a
thousand wires over here!
Which one do we use?
Uh, that one! That one!
That one! Come on!
Go, go, go, go, go!
Wrap it around!
Come on, guys!
- Go, go!
- Go!
When we get in the tunnel,
I'll open the door!
We bought some distance
from the robots.
Not much, but some.
Are there more on the way?
The AIs already sizing up how
much EMP firepower we have.
It has to keep a radius until
it can figure that out.
It's probably already
figured that out.
Our electrical engineers
have installed
a punch code lock
in the south doors
to the electrical
distribution room.
It's an analog lock, a fail-safe
in case of a major power outage.
It's also protected by
an electromagnetic shield.
Your heartbeat can't be
detected once you're in there.
Once we're inside the building,
we need to access
the main programming room
to access MEDUSA.
I can enter the coding.
There's a lot
of ground to cover.
And what if we can't stop it?
What if we can't stop it?
The three of us may die trying.
But if we stop MEDUSA,
the world lives.
If we don't,
if we do something wrong,
MEDUSA lives and the world dies.
Either way,
there's no turning back.
Let's finish this.
We're gonna pass
three security cameras.
Once we pass the first one,
it's gonna trigger an alarm
and MEDUSA will send
the robots to stop us.
If we can enter into
the program room fast enough,
then we could shut the
steel door and get to work.
And hope that ARES
doesn't break through
before you finish the hack?
I'll hit it with a powerful
kill-all switch and distract it.
What's that?
Um, dog tags.
Red Dragon and her
cousin Derek gave us.
Tara was wearing them
when we were attacked.
Wait.
I need some time
to enter the Sysconfig
and turn off the analog motors
and switch the capacheats.
[alarm blaring]
The programming
center's just ahead.
Look, if the ARES robots
start firing,
you shield Wilson,
but don't stop firing back!
Now wait here!
Access denied.
It's denying my security access.
Shut it off manually!
We'll have to get into the wall,
but we don't have the tools!
Oh, I got this!
Hurry!
Which one trips the shut-off?
I'll cut them all!
Access granted.
Let's go.
Closing shield doors.
All right, there's a large
port on the back of the console.
You can access MEDUSA
directly from there.
Right, right, right!
What is that?
That's the NFX,
a rescue robot Dr. Lopez,
Dr. Marietta and I were working
on to help rescue people.
It was designed
to pull people
from collapsed buildings
in disaster areas.
We pulled it offline once
MEDUSA malfunctioned.
You hear that?
Access granted.
The door!
Ah!
Wilson, you cannot stop this.
Jorge!
Ah!
Jorge! Jorge! Jorge!
No, no, no!
Jorge!
Help him!
Jorge, come on, man!
Come on, wake up, Jorge!
- Jorge?
- Keep the pressure on it!
- Keep the pressure on!
- Jorge!
Jorge, come on, can you hear me?
Jorge!
MEDUSA is about to take over
the world's military weapons!
Doctor, Doctor, hand me the
tablet! Hand me the tablet!
Here, here, here.
- All right.
- Come on!
That was Tara's dad's
quantum tablet.
But once you start
entering the code,
it's going to start
trying to hack
the quantum firewall
on that tablet.
- Oh...
- Hang in there, buddy.
The kill-all virus will take a
few seconds for it to stop it.
But that'll give me just enough
time to enter in the data bomb.
MEDUSA's system will shut down
and stop its systems
from frying.
But that'll give me
enough time to go at it.
Hurry...
MEDUSA has entered
standby mode.
Is it...
No, not yet.
It wouldn't work that fast.
We were seconds away
from MEDUSA
taking over
the world's nuclear arsenal.
Hey...
- Hey.
- Oh, welcome back.
Oh, man, dude.
They shot this at you.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Why is it still blinking?
What?
Let me see that.
Doctor?
MEDUSA transferred
her AI into this...
Oh!
Come on, come on, come on!
Come on!
[Jorge] Why isn't it dead?
MEDUSA transferred
itself to another system!
- What system?
- It's just gone!
Look, the kill-all virus
should have slowed it down.
But MEDUSA transmitted itself
to a different mainframe.
That shouldn't be
possible unless it...
unless it...
it changed itself
once it deployed.
Oh, man, that means it wouldn't
have slowed it down at all.
So your virus didn't
kill it at all?
It turned into
a modular firewall.
It didn't slow it down.
I helped it escape.
I need help.
Come on, come on,
we're taking you outside.
No, no.
Just set me down in front
of the computer here.
- Be more use here.
- All right.
So what's the plan?
MEDUSA is not going anywhere.
And what makes you think that?
Because she still wants us dead.
There's only so much tech
with a sliding base
parallel to her Qbit shell.
It has to be hiding
in the machine at Spaceport.
I'll find it.
No.
You click one
button on that computer,
MEDUSA will find you.
Stay here.
I'll look.
Reinforce the door
and turn your radio on
just in case I need you
to go online.
I'm coming with you.
[explosion]
Found it.
MEDUSA's in that?
That?
Yep.
Run!
We need to split up!
No, we need a plan!
I have a plan!
All right,
turn on your radio!
All right.
All right, listen for my orders
and get the ARES to follow you!
- Okay?
- Got it.
Ah!
[static]
Dr. Marietta!
All right, I'm here.
MEDUSA is in
the NFX rescue robot!
You said you'd get here and map
a mainframe to help me.
Well, now's your chance!
Lead me to MEDUSA's new brain.
All right, mapping now.
Have you found it yet?
Do a heat scan,
see where most
of the heat is generating.
All right, the
mainframe is located
in the chest cavity
of the robot.
I knew it!
What?
Wilson!
Jorge?
Jorge, can you hear me?
Oh...
Ah!
Wilson?
Jorge, are you okay?
Yeah, I'll live.
Are you in an area where you
can make a lot of noise?
Uh, yeah, I think so.
I need you to lure
the ARES robots away.
Can you do that?
Yes.
Yeah, I can do that.
Hey! Hey, robots,
I'm down here!
Come and get me!
I'm in!
Good.
Where's you friend, Jorge?
Hopefully safe.
Robots!
Hey!
Wilson!
Oh, no.
How far are you?
Close, I hope!
What are you trying to do?
This thing's got a brain.
Well, I'm about to
give it a heart.
What, make it nicer?
No. Make it a target.
What's that?
We are running out of time here.
I'm here!
I'm in front of the motherboard
and I'm prying it open!
All right, once you pull
that processor,
we can hack it directly.
All right, it's out!
Wilson, it knows
you're inside the robot.
MEDUSA is launching
nukes across the globe.
It's now or never.
Yeah, well, now it's going to
have my heartbeat inside of it!
And every robot within firing
distance is going to detect it
and shred this thing!
I've got it!
It's coming from the intercom!
It's feeding into the system
as an algorithm!
All right. Climb inside
the steel reinforced casing
and hurry!
MEDUSA is transmitting
your heartbeat
to every robot in the world.
The robots think it's
a living human being now!
It'll use every robot
to attack itself!
It's working, Wilson, but
you're still inside the target.
Brace yourself.
Come in, Wilson.
Wilson?
Are you okay?
I'm on my way.
A little help here, guys?
Zee! Oh, my God!
You're both alive!
Barely.
That was just...
Well...
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
I'm proud of you.
You did it!
I always told you,
you're all heart.
So what do we do now?
There's a lot of work to do.
Where do we start?
Just log in.
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull