[wind whistling]
[falcon screeching]
["Habibi Taal" by Alsarah
& The Nubatones]
[engine grumbling]
[speaking Arabic]
[Hilal speaking Arabic]
♪
- [Cai] The jellyfish.
- [Tariq] Yeah.
[Cai] There are so many.
♪
- [Cai] That was great.
- [Tariq] Yeah.
[Cai] That was, like, a meter.
[both panting]
[Cai] 'Cause you liked her?
You're crazy, man. Never.
[sighing]
What do you think
your favorite animal is now?
My favorite animal?
The grizzly bear, I guess.
'Cause it's so...
It's like a beast.
It's the definition of a beast.
- Yeah.
- [Tariq] Why, though?
What's your favorite animal?
I think it changed.
I saw a sea turtle
the other day.
Isn't he here, actually?
But, um...
yeah.
They're just swimming around.
Gracefully, you know?
Just seem kind of...
at peace and,
just, I don't know...
quiet. Calm.
What I love is that
whatever beach they hatch on,
um, they always go
back to that same beach
to then lay their eggs.
Um, and they go for
miles and miles and miles
but then they always come back.
It's like this...
homing instinct.
- I really like it.
- Yeah.
[boat engine rumbling]
[speaking Arabic]
[Tariq] Check out his arm.
[Cai speaking Arabic]
[speaking Arabic]
[Middle Eastern music playing]
[bar din]
[Tariq] Always here.
[Tariq chuckling]
[woman] Doesn't
it defeat the purpose
if you did it with
a plastic knife?
[Tariq] No, we're...
We're just kind of
working our way up
to a real knife.
Oh. Can I try?
[Cai] Mm.
[speaking Arabic]
For example, if it's in a cage,
it's just being
constantly fed food.
It doesn't understand
it has to go out and actually,
like, get it itself.
Birds of prey, for example,
especially falcons,
if they're kept in cages
the whole time, they lose this,
um, muscle mass here,
which is the pectoral muscles,
- [woman] Mm-hmm.
- Which they need
to actually fly.
So, as soon as it
gets let out into the wild,
you know, it tries
to catch its prey and...
and it just can't.
And then these animals,
they'll starve after,
like, three days.
So, you need to build that up
over time by training it.
[woman] So, Tariq.
Do you love animals
as much as Cai here?
Nobody loves animals
as much as Cai.
- [Cai] Whatever, Tariq.
- [woman laughing] Really?
Are you going here
for university?
Uh, I don't know.
Probably not.
I wanna,
um, study animal conservation.
- [woman] Mm.
- So, um...
there aren't that
many good, like,
- programs here for that.
- [woman] Mm, yeah.
[Cai] So, I kind
of want to go outside.
Uh, maybe to New York?
[woman] How about you, Tariq?
Uh...
I... I want to finish
high school.
I had to take a break.
[woman speaking Arabic]
Um...
[Tariq speaking Arabic]
[speaking Arabic]
Oh.
What was your favorite
thing about her?
She was... she was funny.
[woman] Well, I'm pretty
sure she was very lovely.
Well, I think I need to get
back to work before I open...
We might have
a good story for you.
- Really?
- [Tariq] Yeah.
It's about a cove near here
where this one-armed guy,
uh, who smuggles animals,
lives there alone
with his birds.
Um, his arm got bitten
off by a leopard.
He has a deal with a jinn,
he made a deal with a jinn...
[Cai] We don't actually know
if any of that's true.
[Tariq] You were there with me.
It's true.
[woman] Well, actually, this is
a big problem in the region.
[Tariq] See?
The jinn is a big
problem in the region.
[laughing] No, not the jinn.
Stop it. Not the jinn.
I mean, like, the whole animal
smuggling thing is a problem.
They're trying to figure
out who's doing it.
- Stop doing that. Stop laughing.
- I gotta pee, man.
[woman] No, it is a good story,
Tariq. It is.
[Tariq] I told you
it's a good story.
Yes, it is.
Just watch out
for the jinn in the bathroom.
[Cai laughing]
- He's so scared.
- [woman] Why?
[waves lapping]
[birds chirping]
[engine grumbling]
[gentle music]
♪
- Bye, Mom.
- [Cai's mom] Love you. Have fun.
♪
[people singing & shouting,
drums banging]
[car horns honking]
[drums pattering]
[Tariq] Hi!
- [Cai] How are you, man?
- You look good, man.
What do you think? Hey,
can you help me tie my masar?
Yeah, sure, sure.
- This way, right?
- Yeah.
Hey, how's your sister?
Uh, it's her wedding.
She's probably stressed
but I'm sure...
I'm sure she's fine.
[crowd shouting]
[gentle music]
[Omani music playing faintly
under gentle music]
♪
[crowd cheering]
[inaudible conversation]
♪
[music fading out]
[Cai] Coming from you.
Uh, I'm saving myself
for someone special,
and you know that.
[rock clattering]
- That's the target?
- Yeah.
[crickets chirping]
- [rock clattering]
- [Tariq] Yeah.
How did your mom and dad meet?
[rooster crowing]
Uh, I don't know exactly.
My parents are weird.
Sometimes it feels
like their main love
is their work here, you know?
[rock clattering]
Hey, I like your parents.
Yeah, they're cool, it's just...
I don't know,
sometimes I feel like-
Whatever, man.
They leave you alone,
you get to do whatever you want.
You're lucky.
Was tonight the first
time that Alia met Ahmed?
No, they met a couple
of times before.
His father was
a good friend of my dad.
What's he like?
- Ahmed?
- [Cai] Yeah.
He's fine, I guess.
Shit. What time is it?
Uh, I think it's the morning.
I'm not sure.
[Cai] Yeah. Oh.
You're just leaving
'cause I'm winning.
[Cai] Yeah, that's it. I'll let
you have this one. See you.
All right, man,
see you in a bit.
[Cai speaking Arabic]
[speaking Arabic]
[laughter]
[Tariq speaking Arabic]
[speaking Arabic]
[Tariq] You work at a zoo, Cai.
You're not the savior
of the animal kingdom.
Look...
almost all of these animals
were born in captivity.
And I didn't put them here.
I work here because...
I want people to
care about them more.
I work here.
Twice as much as you do,
because even though the pay
is shit, it still pays.
[birds cawing & squawking]
You have more time than
I do to care about these things.
We're not gonna go extinct.
We're smart people.
[rooster crowing]
We figured it out.
And even if it's all true...
people are just trying to live,
you know?
[Cai] You care about these
animals more than you admit.
I never said I hated animals.
I just care about people more.
[Cai] I know it sounds
like a bunch of bullshit.
And people suck.
They don't care about things
until they're this close
to their face.
And since they're all here,
they can learn about them.
Keep them healthy.
This one's still my favorite.
There're all these other animals
who would die in the wild.
They can't hunt,
they can't fend for themselves.
They'd be prey in an instant.
Or they would starve to death.
This one is...
- This one would survive?
- [Cai] No, look at it.
It's weak.
I need to train it. Properly.
[birds cawing & squawking]
Hey, have a look at this tiger.
[animals bleating & chirping]
Fucking motherfucker.
[Cai laughing]
[Tariq] Oh, I'm getting you.
- Mine's wet, man.
- [Cai] That's disgusting.
[bees buzzing]
[car horn honking]
[speaking Arabic]
[people arguing in Arabic]
Alia?
[Alia] Tariq.
[speaking Arabic]
[taxi driver speaking Arabic]
- Alia?
- [Alia speaking Arabic]
[Tariq's father speaking Arabic]
Alia?
[Arabic trap music
playing on speakers]
[birds squawking]
Oh, oh, just leave it.
It's not for you.
You try it, then.
I don't want to
get my shoes dirty.
Do you know how much this costs?
[splashing]
What are you doing?
- Improving them.
- Serious?
Didn't even pay for shit, man.
Your parents bought
them for you.
Oh, wow.
Well, at least my parents
can afford new shoes for me.
[skateboard rattling]
I'm gonna get a snack.
Can anyone spot me?
Uh, yeah, I got some
cash in my pocket if you want.
♪
[Faris] What is this?
[Cai] Oh, wait, no, no, no.
Give it back, give it back.
Faris, Faris.
Mo, Mo, Mo, Mo, come on.
Give it back.
- Give it back.
- [Mo] What are these?
They're gauntlets.
♪
- And that's pigeon meat.
- Ew.
[chuckling]
Yeah. Cai has been making
friends with one of the falcons.
He wants to steal it
so he can train it
and then set it free.
Don't set it free.
You should sell it.
Let's do it now.
[Faris] Yeah, come on.
We can help you train it.
- No.
- Why not?
I'm not doing it now.
[Cai] Guys, it's a bad idea.
I'm doing it by myself.
Guys, guys.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm not... I'm not gonna do it
with you shitheads here. No.
[birds cawing & squawking]
How much did
the zoo pay for this?
Not much.
It's not worth much untrained.
You know, my uncle paid
5,000 for one like this.
[Tariq] Your uncle's an idiot.
No, I hate to say it,
but Mo's right.
I mean,
when these things are trained
they can go for quite a lot.
Take it now.
I'll give you 50 if you take it.
Fifty.
[Cai] Shit.
[rooster crowing]
[crickets chirping]
[birds cawing & squawking]
[tense music]
♪
[speaking in Arabic]
You guys just go ahead,
all right?
You're gonna blow my cover.
I'll meet you outside.
[birds chirping]
[banging on door]
[speaking Arabic]
[Ahmed speaking Arabic]
[door opens]
[ball bouncing]
[woman speaking Arabic]
[boys and woman speaking Arabic]
[speaking Arabic]
[pensive music]
[bees buzzing]
[Tariq] Alia.
[speaking Arabic]
[Tariq] Mm.
♪
[music fading out]
- [Cai] What's going on?
- Just give me a second.
[dogs barking]
[speaking Arabic]
[men speaking Arabic]
[gentle music]
[birds chirping]
[call to prayer playing faintly]
♪
[snipping]
[birds cawing & squawking]
[wings flapping]
Tariq,
what the hell are you doing?
What's going on?
It's private.
You can tell me.
It's a family thing, Cai.
You don't understand.
What do you mean
I don't understand?
Okay, fine.
It's Alia.
She needs my help.
She told me she wants
to get a divorce.
Why? What happened?
I don't know.
[birds cooing & chirping]
[Tariq] It's not like
she just dislikes him.
He actually seems really scary.
I'm sorry to have to ask, but...
what does this have to do with
you trying to steal a pigeon?
I promised her I would
help her get the money.
- For what?
- To get a divorce.
She needs to bring
him back everything
he gave us at the wedding.
How much is it?
- A lot.
- How much is a lot?
A lot a lot.
And your dad just can't...
[birds cooing & chirping]
- I'm gonna ask my parents...
- No.
- [Cai] Why not?
It's a very private thing, Cai.
- I need to solve this myself.
- Okay.
So, we're stealing pigeons...
and then what?
- Selling them.
- Just pigeons?
Just pigeons, right?
What else have
you tried to sell?
Couple of pigeons...
two of the cats,
and a few other birds.
- What else?
- That's it, I swear.
I swear, that's it.
Okay.
They have to have
been born in captivity.
So, animals
that wouldn't survive
- if we just set them free.
- Yeah.
Um, definitely no
endangered species.
- Okay.
- And,
ideally,
we send them to a good home.
So, pretty much all of these.
Let me add,
let's be smart about this.
We both know what we can
and what we can't
get away with here, so...
let's just not lose our jobs.
We're not going
to lose our jobs.
We know this place
better than anyone.
It's just a side business.
[dark Arabic music]
[speaking Arabic]
Yeah, we got it.
[man speaking Arabic]
[Tariq speaking Arabic]
♪
[Cai] Do you feel
how soft it is?
That's why it's so...
- expensive.
- How much?
[Cai] Well, normally
they go for about 30 rial.
♪
[Cai speaking indistinctly]
[Cai chuckles]
♪
[children chattering excitedly]
[Tariq speaking Arabic]
[woman speaking Arabic]
[speaking Arabic]
[woman] Thank you.
Shukran.
[speaking Arabic]
- Are you selling pigeons?
- Yep.
Can I have a look?
- Uh, yeah. It's the Zajal.
- The Zajal?
Yeah.
How much for that white one?
- [indistinct]
- Yeah.
- Shukran.
Shukran.
♪
Hey.
Seventy rial... for two pigeons.
[laughing] Shukran, habibi.
[engine grumbling]
[goats bleating]
[Cai] Easy, easy.
It's all right. It's all right.
Tariq, Tariq.
Oh, my God. Okay.
Can you... can you help me?
- What is it?
- [Cai] I need your help.
- [Tariq] Like this?
- No, I need-
I need to put these dresses
on her, but I don't...
I don't think
I can do it on my own,
so I'm gonna need
you to hold her, okay?
- Yeah? Look...
- Just tell me how.
If you get your right hand...
I want you to hold her.
You see how
I'm holding its legs?
- [Tariq] Yeah.
- [Cai] Get your right hand
and put it...
Put it where mine is.
And then make sure
you get its legs.
Okay.
And your left hand the same.
- Think you've got it?
- [Tariq] Yeah.
[Cai] Nice, nice, nice. Okay.
Okay, sit down here.
And then turn around.
Okay.
[Cai] Okay,
perfect, perfect, perfect.
[Cai mumbling faintly]
[rooster crowing]
Poor thing. Okay.
Soon it'll be over.
Okay.
So, once I put
this rope through...
then I'm gonna attach it to my...
My gauntlet.
And then we're
gonna hoist her up.
I'm gonna have her in my hand.
Okay?
Be very fast, but...
we should be okay.
Okay.
Just like this?
Stand up.
We're gonna let her go,
she's gonna come to me.
Okay.
There we go. Okay.
There she is. Whew.
[inspiring music]
[chuckling]
Isn't she gorgeous?
I can't believe it worked.
[chuckling]
It's all right.
It's okay, it's okay.
It's okay.
It's okay. Yeah.
[chuckling]
Isn't she beautiful?
♪
So, grab... grab this
with your right hand.
Okay, I'm gonna hold this.
Slowly I'm gonna
wriggle my hand out.
Okay, okay.
Perfect, perfect, perfect.
Nice, Tariq, nice. Nice.
[Cai chuckling]
Perfect.
- How does she feel?
- Man... I have no words.
[Cai] Okay.
This is our living space.
Here are the stairs.
So, part of the... the
manning process is that...
you've got to
keep talking to her
so she gets used to your voice.
This is our beautiful hallway.
[Tariq] Our entrance.
Our entrance. Very grand.
Yeah.
My God, she's doing so well.
- She's so calm.
- Yeah.
[music fading out]
[traffic din in distance]
[dog barking in distance]
[forlorn music]
♪
[phone ringing]
[phone beeping]
[crickets chirping]
[Cai] What did she say?
How is she?
[Tariq] She didn't answer.
[goats bleating]
Do you think she's okay?
[Tariq] I don't know.
Today was a good day.
Made about 50 bucks.
[Tariq] It's too slow, Cai.
It's too slow.
Do you have a better idea?
[Tariq] I don't know.
But I've been thinking
about that guy.
What guy?
The smuggler Hilal showed us.
[Cai] Yeah?
Do you really think
he cursed that place?
[Cai] Do you mean do I think
there's a jinn protecting
his pirate's cove?
[Tariq sighs]
[Cai speaking Arabic]
[Tariq] No, shut up.
I'm not afraid of the jinn.
I'm afraid
of that one-armed man.
You wanna send
him these rabbits?
No.
I want to send
him something bigger.
[tense music]
[snake quietly hissing]
[Tariq] Hey, Lara. Come here.
I thought you loved all animals.
I do, I just...
I don't prefer snakes.
Actually...
I hate to say it, but
this one's worth quite a lot.
- Are you sure?
- [Cai] Yeah.
The zoo has no idea
how much it's worth.
[Tariq] Give me your backpack.
It's not going to fit.
Wait, wait,
you're gonna do it now?
Wait, Tariq.
Listen, I mean... I mean... I mean
we don't even know if what
they say about that guy is true.
I mean, it sounds
like a bunch of bullshit to me.
How else do you think
he lost his arm, man?
I believe Hilal.
Okay, what are you
gonna say to Amal
when he realizes
his snake's gone?
No one's even gonna notice, man.
I'm the one who feeds her.
I can't believe
we're doing this now.
It's not like we're
selling a tiger.
Are you sure it's
worth a lot of money?
It's an albino pied.
[suspenseful music]
Can you give me the bag?
♪
Let's go.
Yeah, it should...
Yeah, there it is.
- [Cai] This white one?
- [Tariq] The white one, yeah.
I think if we get it
back by Sunday, it's all good.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
You sure you know
how to hot-wire a car?
- Yes.
- [Tariq] Yeah, awesome.
- It's all on you, man.
- [Cai] Okay.
[dog barking in distance]
Yeah.
- So, Cai?
- [Cai] Yeah?
[Tariq] What's happening?
[Cai] These wires are supposed
to start the ignition...
I think this can help you
start the ignition.
[keys clattering]
[Cai] Idiot.
[Tariq] Oh, no, no,
no, no, no, I'm driving.
No, I said I was going to drive.
[Tariq] No. Come on.
[Tariq chuckling]
[engine revving]
["Maculelê" by Mait Inaê
& Ben Goldstein playing]
[Cai] Tariq.
Open the door.
Tariq.
[Tariq] I'm sorry, man.
- The door doesn't work.
- [Cai] Thank you.
[engine revving]
♪
[song fades out]
Shit, shit.
Stop the car, stop the car.
Shit, Lara's out.
Why was the bag open?
[Tariq] I left it open
so she could breathe.
[unzipping]
Can you not do that again?
[Tariq] Hey, Lara.
[Lara quietly hissing]
- Look at her.
- No, no, don't...
- Cut it out.
- [Lara hissing]
[Tariq] Why are you
so scared of her, man?
- Because she's big.
- [Tariq] She's friendly.
She's not, she's...
unpredictable.
Can you fully
close it this time?
[Tariq] Lara...
just get in the bag for a bit.
[engine revving]
How... So, how do you think
this works?
We're just gonna show up,
give him the snake,
and he'll give us the money?
[Cai] I don't know, man.
This is my first time selling
a snake on the black market.
To a smuggler.
What should we do
with the extra cash?
If it's $20,000.
It's your money, man.
- Whatever you want.
- Maybe we should...
buy a boat. A small boat.
And just, like,
take tourists out for rides.
- Yeah.
- We should do that.
- [Cai] Yeah, that'd be cool.
[Tariq] Yeah.
[Cai] I've been meaning
to tell you, I, uh...
I got into U.B.C.
[Tariq] Canada?
- Are you gonna go?
- Yeah, I think so.
It's one of my top
schools and, uh...
it's got a great animal
conservation program.
When are you leaving?
Classes start
in September, so...
late August.
[waaves lapping]
[fire crackling]
There's no future for you here.
I can't leave.
Even... even if I could
get a visa to the States.
You can't leave your family.
I don't wanna leave.
At least I don't...
I don't know.
But you know how
much I love it here.
You love it here
because you can leave.
Every summer you get
to travel and meet girls.
Do whatever you want.
While I am here
shoveling monkey shit.
I'm gonna finish school, too.
Maybe...
maybe even get a decent job.
In ministry.
[Cai] You're a smart guy.
I have faith in you.
[pensive music]
♪
[water lapping]
[waves lapping,
music fading out]
[ominous music]
Ready?
Yeah.
♪
[music fading out]
[birds chirping]
[Tariq speaking Arabic]
[smuggler speaking Arabic]
[speaking Arabic]
[Tariq speaking Arabic]
[bag zipping]
[birds chittering]
[glasses clinking]
[Tariq speaking Arabic]
[speaking Arabic]
[Lara hissing]
[Cai speaking Arabic]
[smuggler speaking Arabic]
[speaking Arabic]
[Tariq speaking Arabic]
Yeah. You told me it was
worth $20,000.
Yeah, that's what I thought.
[solemn music]
[bag zipping]
[birds chirping]
[smuggler speaking Arabic]
[speaking Arabic]
[tense music]
[motor rumbling]
♪
[birds chirping]
[rooster crowing]
[Cai] So, I did some research...
and the guy was right.
Lara's just an albino python,
not an albino pied python.
Their markings are just
a little bit different.
It was a super
easy mistake to make.
[Mo speaking Arabic]
[Tariq speaking Arabic]
[Mo scoffs]
So, how are you?
- I'm fine.
- Just fine?
What do you want?
[speaking Arabic]
Yeah.
[Mo] Hmm.
[Cai] Okay, A me era.
You ready?
Yeah?
All right,
you want me to take this off?
This is it.
What do you think?
You like it? Come on, come on.
What's it like seeing
everything this high up?
Whoa, come on, come on.
Come over here. Come on.
Soon you'll be able
to fly wherever you want.
One month, okay?
When you're ready.
[dog barking in distance]
[speaking Arabic]
[birds chirping & screeching]
[footsteps crunching]
[pages rustling]
[birds chirping & screeching]
Hello. Hello.
- [A me era cawing]
- It's okay.
- It's okay, it's okay.
What are you doing here?
[lighter flicking]
[gentle music]
♪
[bees buzzing]
[Tariq's father speaking Arabic]
[speaking Arabic]
♪
Okay.
Maybe you can catch it. Yeah?
What's that?
You're gonna hunt for it, yeah?
You see it?
You see, just up there, yeah.
Straight ahead.
[birds chirping,
music fading out]
Shit, shit, shit.
[dramatic music]
No, no, no, no...
Tariq, call me back. Um...
I think...
I think someone
stole my falcon. Um...
Yeah, just call me
back when you can. Okay.
♪
[rocks clattering]
Tariq, what are you doing?
I found a buyer for A me era.
He's gonna give me
$5,000 for her.
- You can't do that.
- I have to.
- [Cai] Tariq, she's my bird.
- She's not your bird.
You took her from the zoo.
Tariq, this is stupid.
She's not trained.
A falcon isn't like a pigeon
or a rabbit!
- I know that.
- No one's gonna pay shit
for an untrained falcon!
They're gonna want to see
her fly free and come back!
And you take that hood off
and she's gonna be gone
in an instant,
and she's not gonna come back!
'Cause
she's gonna starve to death!
Then help me train her.
No.
No, I'm not gonna help you.
I am done selling animals
to God knows who!
And I didn't feel good
about it to begin with,
and I don't feel
good about it now.
I just did it 'cause
I wanted to help you.
♪
[A me era cawing]
[boys grunting]
You always act like you know
better than anyone.
You're always sending me
these things about the world
like I'm an idiot.
I know things too!
You don't understand
anything about me.
Or my family.
You think it's all a big game,
and then you complain about
how are these animals
going to be treated
as if I give a shit
when my family's in trouble.
You know what?
You're just a selfish rich kid
like Mo.
And I don't care
that you're moving to Canada.
Fuck you, Tariq.
♪
[goats bleating]
[birds chirping]
Hi.
I wanted to give you this back.
I've been looking for this.
Yeah. I saw your bird
and I was curious. Sorry.
[birds chirping]
I wanted to ask you
about something.
[Alia] This word.
- [Cai] Oh, creance.
- What is that?
It's basically like a leash,
except much longer.
So, it allows the falcon
to feel like it's flying free
without the risk
of it getting away.
Oh, okay.
[rooster crowing]
I don't know if
Tariq told you, but...
I left Ahmed.
For good. And...
I know I should be scared,
and I know what
that means for my family, but...
[sighing]
I feel relieved.
[Alia] I'll see you around.
And Cai?
When you set her free,
can I be there?
- Okay.
- [Alia] Great.
♪
[animals bleating & cawing]
[rooster crowing]
How's A me era?
[animals bleating & cawing]
[Cai] You tried feeding
her pigeon instead of chicken?
[Tariq] I've tried everything.
Maybe it's her location.
Birds in the wild have
their favorite perches.
And sometimes they won't
eat unless they're there.
She isn't flying, either.
[Cai] You've been weighing her?
She needs to be
hungry to fly, but...
she won't fly
if she's not healthy.
[animals bleating & cawing]
[Cai] Who are
you selling her to?
Uh...
Mo's uncle wants to buy her.
But he needs to
see her fly first.
Also, I have no idea
how the leash works.
My hand is covered in scabs.
[animals bleating & cawing]
Look, I don't know if, um...
I think I can help you.
[animals bleating & cawing]
[rooster crowing]
- I'm gonna miss this place.
- Really?
[rooster crowing]
[Cai] Not really.
I'll miss the creatures
that live here, though.
[birds chirping]
- Take these two shorter ones.
- [Tariq] Okay.
[Cai] You see this one
and this one?
And you just want
to pull them equally.
To loosen the hood, okay?
Nice, and then
just pull it forward.
In one smooth motion.
There we go.
Nice, nice, nice, nice, nice.
[Alia] I know
what you guys are doing.
- [Cai] What do you mean?
- Cai.
Are you really sure about this?
I'm sure, yeah.
Okay.
I've been doing some reading
and we need to change this whole
aviary.
We need to change the windows.
The shredded wire will hurt her.
-We need to put bars instead-
-[Tariq] Alia.
Alia. What are you doing?
- I want to help.
- No.
Cai and I are going
to solve this. Not you.
You didn't ask me if
I want you to sell her or not.
Look, this is how things are,
and I don't have
a better solution,
so I want to help.
But you can't
just come in here and...
Tariq...
[speaking Arabic]
We named her A me era.
Hi, princess.
♪
It's too loud for you here.
Let's take you out, okay?
Let's take you out.
Don't be scared.
♪
Hah!
Okay, can you stand there?
Yeah, thanks.
Okay.
Hah!
♪
Hah! Hah!
I really don't know
what's gonna happen.
Let's hope she chooses
to come to us, but...
equally she could choose
to fly away and not come back.
Uh... and then we'd
be really screwed.
We've done everything we can,
now let's just hope
for the best, Tariq.
Hold this. Don't shorten it.
Okay.
Hah!
♪
[Cai] Put it behind your back
so she can't see it.
Hah! Hah!
♪
Hah!
Hah! Hah!
♪
Guys, I'm not sure
she's gonna do it today.
Hah!
[wings fluttering]
[soft music]
- Hey, A me era.
- [indistinct]
- [Cai] Oh, my God.
- [chuckling]
[Tariq chuckling]
Now you like me, huh?
♪
[Cai yelping]
[panting]
[sighs]
- How's it going?
- [Cai] Good, good.
Getting there.
[guinea pig squeaking]
Mo called.
His uncle found another bird.
A me era is not ready.
He's gonna buy the other one.
Okay.
Think she's ready?
I don't know.
She might not come back.
[hood rattling]
[Tariq] I see a car coming.
I'm not sure if it's them.
[Tariq] It's Mo.
- [Alia] Oh, it's him.
- Yeah. Let's go.
[greeting each other in Arabic]
Will it come back?
Yeah, I mean,
uh, she's a great bird.
We've been training
her for about a month now.
Um, she's got
a fantastic personality,
she's great around people.
Uh, she's at the right weight
as well, today, and...
yeah, I think
she will come back.
- Zayn.
- Let's see it.
[indistinct] Let's see.
[footsteps]
[rocks crunching]
Let's go this way for the wind.
Okay?
Alia?
You ready?
♪
Just like we did before, okay?
I'm gonna unhook her Jesses.
Okay.
When you're ready,
take the hood off.
You can do this.
♪
[Alia] Hah!
[Hada Jil by Aziza Brahim:
Lyrics in Arabic]
♪
[Hada Jil by Aziza Brahim:
Lyrics in Arabic]
♪