Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
JOHN F. KENNEDY: We are confronted
primarily with a moral issue.
It is as old as the Scriptures
and is as clear
as the American Constitution.
The heart of the question is
whether all Americans
are to be afforded
equal rights
and equal opportunities,
whether we are going to treat
our fellow Americans
as we want to be treated.
If an American,
because his skin is dark,
cannot eat lunch in a
restaurant open to the public,
if he cannot send his children
to the best
public school available,
if he cannot vote for the public
officials who represent him,
if, in short, he cannot enjoy the full
and free life which all of us want,
then who among us
would be content
to have the color of his skin
changed and stand in his place?
Who among us
would then be content
with the counsels
of patience and delay?
MAN: Yes. Yes, Mrs. Stevenson,
I understand.
Well, no, ma'am,
I haven't seen today's paper.
Mrs. Stevenson, I assure you,
you have nothing to be
- concerned about.
- Sir?
- No, I assure you...
- Sir.
Excuse me, Mrs. Stevenson.
[PAPER RUSTLES]
Mrs. Stevenson, I...
I'll have to call you back.
Well, I guess that's it.
[SLOW ROCK MUSIC]
- [GIRL 1 SPEAKS INDISTINCTLY]
- GIRL 2: Wow!
- Oh, look at this lighthouse.
- Wow!
- So neat.
- Yeah.
- I'm gonna get one, too.
GIRL 1: Hello.
GIRL 2: Hi.
Hello, girls.
Oh, good. Sinatra.
[RECORDS RUSTLE]
[CHUCKLES]
What do you think
about these, Rosie?
Rosalee, look at these.
- What do you think about them?
- They're nice.
Uh-uh, that ain't gonna work.
I mean, I'm trying to be
homecoming queen.
I need something spectacular.
You know, something
that's gonna make me shine.
- I heard your father enlisted.
- GIRL: He did.
Okay. What about these ones?
[SLOW ROCK MUSIC CONTINUES]
What's wrong?
Do you ever feel like
you deserve more?
Like what?
We pay just as much money
as they do.
- All right. Thank you so much.
- Thank you.
- ...for me.
- I will.
[CHUCKLES] That's just
the way things are. So?
- I like those.
- Me, too. [CHUCKLES]
Hey, baby.
- Hey.
- I've got some good news.
Early votes for
homecoming king and queen.
Oh!
Rosalee, me and Arlo
is in the lead!
[CHUCKLES]
Another week, and we got it
made in the shade.
[CHUCKLES]
Speaking of which...
these... These
will look good on you.
Mmm, I don't know.
Uh, me and Rosie
already picked out these.
- Aren't they cute?
- Darling.
You want to win
homecoming queen?
You let me do the thinking.
You just keep on
looking good, okay?
What are you all
doing here anyway?
Y'all still practicing
that pretend radio show?
Lady-D practices
after school every day.
[SCOFFS]
Well, you're not Lady-D.
You're just gonna end up in the
butcher shop, like your dad.
Arlo, don't.
- Mmm-mmm.
- I mean, I'm being honest.
Am I lying?
Don't say that.
[FOOTSTEPS]
Excuse me, sir.
I'd like to buy this.
[FOOTSTEPS]
What is it?
[NEWSPAPER RUSTLES]
[OBJECT THUDS ON DESK]
$4.50.
[COINS JINGLE]
Put it on the counter.
[COINS SCRAPE ON DESK]
Things have been peaceful
around here.
Last thing we need
is somebody stirring the pot.
ROSALEE: It ain't right.
BRIANNA: Yeah, it is.
ROSALEE: Let's ask the people.
Today on Get Real with Rosie,
let's talk about fairness.
Is it fair that colored people
have to use the back entrance
and sit at the back
of the movie theater,
even though we spend just as
much money as the white folks?
I want to hear from you.
Ring, ring, ring.
Caller number one,
you're on with Rosie.
I don't see a problem.
I mean, they don't
wanna be around us,
and we don't wanna be
around them, either.
So you're saying
segregation is a good thing?
Mmm-hmm.
I mean, we got ours
and they got theirs.
So why do we need
to be together?
Mmm, we can't be equal
If we're separated.
Why not?
Let's say you had
two of the same book.
This one's in good condition,
this one, not so much.
Now, this one goes
to the white school,
and this one go
to the black one.
Is that fair?
- No.
- Both schools get the same book.
Yeah, but this one's
missing pages.
[SCOFFS] Doesn't matter.
Both schools
getting the same book,
so it's considered
an equal education.
Just because you have
two of the same things,
that doesn't make
the things equal.
That's right.
We got to be the change that
we wish to see in the world.
[CHAIR SCRAPES ON GROUND]
- You going to tidy up for me, Rosie?
- I got you.
[DOOR SQUEAKS]
Hey, what time is it?
BOTH: Lady-D!
LADY-D: And that was the latest from
Smokey Robinson and the Miracles.
♪ You really got
a hold on me ♪
I love that song.
As you may know, I'm Lady-D,
bringing you the sound to boogie on down.
Now, pigs must be flyin', 'cause St. Julian's
High School is accepting colored children.
I'll clue you in
on that later.
But for now, let's listen to...
Little Eva and the Turkey Trot.
Okay, it's my turn.
You know that's gonna be you
one day, Rosie.
Hey, y'all.
if the diva herself, Foxianna,
and today we're gonna discuss
open-toed sandals.
Is it a friend or is it a foe?
You want to comment, Rosie?
I wanna go to St. Julian's.
[HEADPHONES CLACK ON DESK]
- [BOOK SLAMS SHUT]
- Are you out of your mind?
- No. I just feel like it's the right thing to do.
- [SOFT PIANO MUSIC]
Well, it ain't.
St. Julian's is whites only.
You heard Lady-D.
They're integrated now.
That don't make it safe.
You're gonna still be
the only colored girl there.
So?
I'm so tired of being lowered down
and mistreated because I'm black.
If we're all the same,
why aren't we treated the same?
Okay. I get
what you're saying, Rosie.
But why can't you do that
at Mitchell's High?
Why you got to go all the way to St.
Julian's to make a change?
Plus, what am I
to do without you?
I need you with me.
You can come, too.
They probably have real equipment
that we can actually practice on.
You know I wanna be
homecoming queen.
But, look...
I'll be behind you
every step of the way. Okay?
What your folks say?
I ain't told them yet.
Ooh. Okay.
I think you should just...
You should just tell them.
I mean, what's the worst
they can say?
- No!
- But, Dad...
It's out of
the question, Rosalee.
Otis, we can play the dozens all
day or you can let her speak.
[SIGHS]
They are the number one school in the
country, for both math and science.
I mean, you're always
telling me and Junior
how important
good education is.
You can get a good education at Mitchell's
High School. Me and your mama did.
Mitchell's was the only option
when we were coming up.
If going to St. Julian's can give her better
opportunities, I think she should go.
What's this?
That's my history book.
I mean, how are we supposed
to get a good education
when we're learning
from books like that?
It's not the right time.
Will it ever be?
There you go. [SCOFFS]
You... You're trying to undermine
me in front of my own child.
- That is not what's going on.
- [SOFT ORCHESTRAL MUSIC]
Now, May, listen. I... I have put up
with a lot of stuff all these years.
I'm not going to tolerate you
undermining me in front of my own kids...
One-hundred-ninety-seven,
198, 199,
- 200 signed voters registration forms!
- [GASPS] What?
This is the largest turnout
this year.
You know, that's 'cause Lady-D was
bringing the sounds to boogie on down.
- Oh, please.
- [LAUGHS]
I'm sure you knocking
on those doors
at the crack of dawn
had a lot to do with it.
You think so?
They knew if they didn't show up,
that you'd just keep coming back.
What I don't understand is why
you kept knocking on my door.
You know, it gave me
an excuse to come and see you.
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
- [CHUCKLES] Uh, there's a lot of voters registration...
- All gone. [CHUCKLES]
[LADY-D CHUCKLES]
[GROANS] Ro...
So, uh...
I'll see you
at the drive, then?
Yeah. [CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY]
Go on and get home safe now.
Bye.
[FOOTSTEPS]
[EXHALES]
MAY: ...I'm just telling you
we need to listen.
This could be
a great opportunity for her.
- Whoa, what's going on?
- OTIS SR.: ...talk about this school...
I just told him that I want
to go to St. Julian's.
- Really?
- Yes. Shh.
- [WHISPERING] Really?
- [WHISPERING] Yes.
- [OTIS SR. AND MAY ARGUING]
- See, he's not taking it too well.
OTIS SR.: Listen!
Leave me alone. I...
Can you convince him for me?
[WINCES]
Look, I don't think I'm gonna be much help.
I ain't one of his favorites...
- Junior, please. Just try.
- All right. All right.
All right, I'm gonna try.
[HAND SLAPS]
Junior, what do you think about
your sister going to St. Julian's?
[INHALES]
I think she should go.
[OTIS SR. LAUGHING]
He thinks she should go.
Of course he gonna say that.
- Did you think about her safety, Junior?
- [SIGHS]
Dad, her going to St. Julian's
don't put her in no more danger
than her being black.
Do tell me about being black.
You see, I've been black
before you was even thought of.
Dad, I'm sorry.
I didn't mean no...
Why don't you
go pass out your pamphlets
and leave us to our daughter?
[INHALES]
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
[SIGHING] Rosalee, listen.
Baby, this is...
This is about
more than just an education.
What if something happens to you?
We won't be able to protect you!
I can take care of myself.
We know you can.
But I just need to know that you've
thought this all the way through.
I have. I have.
I can do it, Dad.
I'll tell you what.
[SOFT ORCHESTRAL MUSIC]
You put together
a list of all the reasons
why you think you should go
to St. Julian's,
and me and your mama,
we'll think about it,
All right?
Thanks, Dad.
ROSALEE: I don't know
what to do.
[OTIS JR. SIGHS]
[SCOFFS] You go on
and make a list now.
Now, you know
no matter what I say,
it's never gonna be good enough.
That's Senior for you.
So what's the deal
with you two anyways?
[SIGHS]
He shut me out ever since I
got involved with civil rights.
He's been that way ever since.
You ever tried talking to him
about it?
Plenty of times,
but he always finds an excuse.
You should try again.
Maybe he might listen.
[SIGHING] No.
I made my peace with it.
Besides, I mean, this is all...
This is is all about you.
How can you make Senior believe
that you're gonna be okay?
- [LADY-D SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY OVER RADIO]
- Hey, it's our girl, Lady-D.
LADY-D: ...we signed up
243 voters.
If you missed it,
it's not too late to register.
Now, this next groove
to make you move
- goes out to the dreamers.
- [CORN SHELL TEARING]
Keep dreamin',
but with your eyes open.
[ROCK MUSIC ON RADIO]
I gotta go.
Hey, hold on.
I thought you was helpin'.
I will. I will, tomorrow.
- [BIRDS CHIRPING]
- [SOFT ORCHESTRAL MUSIC]
[WATER DRIPPING]
[FOOTSTEPS]
Oh, that's beautiful, sweetie.
But why are you shaking?
You have to relax. May I?
Now that's it.
Slow and steady. You see?
♪ You are my sunshine
♪ My only sunshine
♪ You make me happy
♪ When the skies are gray
♪ You'll never know, dear
♪ How much I love you
♪ Please don't take
♪ My sunshine away ♪
[INHALES]
[HUMMING]
[RICHARD HUMMING]
[MUSIC SWELLS]
BILL: What do you
think you're doing?
I was just painting.
I told you not to touch this.
- [FOOTSTEPS]
- [LUNCHBOX BANGS ON TABLE]
[CHEST CLOSES]
[LOCK CLICKS]
[FOOTSTEPS]
[PAPER RUSTLES]
Maybe it's not so bad.
[LUNCHBOX SQUEAKS]
Do you know what natural law is?
It's a principle
of human conduct...
- passed down to us from the creator of the universe right to us.
- [OBJECT RATTLES]
In our society, there's a fine
line between chaos and order.
- Whites...
- [LARGE DRUM BEATS]
we were never meant
to live with coloreds.
[CHUCKLING] If we were,
God never would have given us...
Segregation?
Exactly.
When everybody follows a divine
order, things run smoothly.
But when we don't...
when someone throws
a wrench in the works...
[CHUCKLES]
Things start to go haywire.
- They get out of control.
- [ORCHESTRAL MUSIC BUILDS]
Before you know it...
[FIST SLAMS ON DESK]
no more society.
Clean up this mess.
ROSALEE: Reason 10, not only was St.
Julian's giving me access
to a better education,
but it could also help open the doors
for future African-Americans.
[JAZZ MUSIC ON RADIO]
What do you think?
It was just okay.
What was wrong with it?
It was dry.
- You need to loosen up.
- Loose?
- I'm loose.
- Yeah.
[SCOFFS] You call that loose?
Girl, you're gonna have a lot of
problems if you call that loose.
[BRIANNA CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
You know what? I got an idea.
[UPBEAT JAZZ MUSIC PLAYING]
[CHUCKLES]
What are you doing?
What does it look like?
Come on.
No. I don't have time.
I need to study.
[BRIANNA SIGHS]
What you need to do is relax.
You've been working on this
for days.
Come on.
That's it.
All right.
[CHUCKLING]
That's right.
There you go.
Now you groovin'.
[ARLO CLEARS THROAT]
Oh. [CHUCKLES]
Hey, Arlo.
[BRIANNA CHUCKLES]
Everyone is meeting
at Poppy's Diner.
We could get some
major campaigning in.
- Okay.
- All right.
Hey, Rosie.
You want to go to Poppy's?
She can't come.
Why not?
I mean, look at her.
ROSALEE: It's okay.
I gotta practice anyways.
Now, that's a real friend.
Come on, let's go.
ARLO: Brianna?
Brianna, come on.
Let's go.
I didn't mean
to rattle your cage,
but you gotta stop spending so much
time with her. It's not a good look.
What are you saying?
I'm saying she's a square.
People will start to think you're a
square if you keep hanging with her.
- Squares don't win homecoming...
- You know what?
What's wrong?
I'm so tired of you
talking about her like that.
Do you not realize she's out
here risking her life for us?
And you worry
about stupid stuff.
So what are you saying?
What I'm saying, Arlo,
is that if I got to choose
between my best friend...
and being homecoming queen...
then I choose Rosalee.
And you can get lost.
You two oddballs
deserve each other. [CHUCKLES]
BRIANNA: Yeah, well...
wipe the grease off the side
of your forehead, jerk!
Ain't you supposed
to be studying?
And ain't you supposed
to be campaigning?
Nah. [CHUCKLES]
This is more important.
Okay, now do it again,
and this time, have fun with it.
[FILM PROJECTOR CLICKING]
Rosie, you're on
in three, two, one!
- All right, y'all, you are now tuned in to
- [JAZZ MUSIC PLAYING]
Get Real with Rosalee.
Coming to you with words
so sweet that you would swear
it was your grandma's apple pie.
You know, word around town is...
Y'all trying to send y'all kids
to the all-white St. Julian's?
Let's talk about that for a minute.
Caller number one.
You're in with Rosie.
Come on, let's hear it.
Speak your mind.
Hey, Rosie. Um, this is Eddie.
I just moved here
from downtown Mississippi,
and I keep hearing
about this old St. Julian's.
Don't sound like it's the
best place for my kids to go.
What's so good about it?
Well, Mr. Eddie, your kids,
they'll be learning from books
that was made in this decade.
That's for sure.
But not only that,
we're talking
new classes, new desk.
I mean, it sounds like
a good idea to me.
Hmm. Well, I guess
I'll think about it.
- Thank you, Rosie.
- Yeah, no problem. No problem.
Make sure you make
the right choice.
All right, caller number two.
Hi, Rosie. My name is Patricia,
but everybody calls me Patty,
and my daughter,
she's a toddler.
So how are the extracurricular
activities over there at St. Julian's?
You know, that's a good
question, Miss Patty.
She'll be practicing
in one of the best gym
with some of the best coaches
in town.
All I'm saying is,
with training like that...
I don't see her
not going to the Olympics.
Caller number three.
Let's hear it.
MAN: Do you really think
now is the time to integrate?
I mean, look what just happened
in Arkansas.
You know, I feel like
the timing is perfect.
Think about those kids.
Those kids in Arkansas
were probably so scared,
but they knew
that it was time for a change.
And if you're not going to
do it now, then when?
[INAUDIBLE]
Ah! Unfortunately,
we are running out of time.
But before we go,
in the words of
the great Gandhi himself...
"Be the change that you wish
to see in the world."
Okay?
Remember that.
Rosalee, signing off.
- And that is why I should go to St. Julian's.
- [ORCHESTRAL MUSIC]
What do you think?
You've definitely put
a lot of thought into this.
- It's a yes from me.
- Yes!
Well, I'm still concerned
about your safety...
I'll be careful.
Uh, I promise.
- All right, you can go.
- [CHUCKLES]
Thank you, Senior.
If I feel like
you're in any danger,
I'm going to pull you out.
That's fine.
That's... That's fine.
[PAPERS RUSTLING]
OTIS JR.: Voters registration
meeting on Tuesday night.
We need you all to come on out
and let your voice be heard.
Good evening, ladies. Voters
registration meeting on Tuesday night.
Y'all come on out
and let your voices be heard.
Voters registration meeting
on Tuesday night.
Come on out
and let your voices be heard.
We got a voters registration...
Why am I not surprised?
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
- How long you been here?
- Long enough.
What's with the signs?
You know, I'm just trying
to get the word out.
- Oh.
- You think it's too much?
Just a little. [CHUCKLES]
You should come on out.
You know, we made
a pretty good team last time.
I just might.
- Then it's a date.
- That's not what I said...
Voters registration meeting
on Tuesday night.
Y'all come on out
and let your voices be heard.
- Voters registration meet, Tuesday night.
- [CROWD SINGING AND CLAPPING]
We need you all to come on out,
let your voice be heard.
Voters registration meeting
on Tuesday night.
Y'all come on out
and let your voices be heard.
[ALL SINGING]
- Be strong and courageous.
- CONGREGATION: Yes.
Do not be afraid or terrified
because of them.
CONGREGATION: Right. Yeah.
For the Lord, your God,
is with you.
He will never leave
nor forsake you.
CONGREGATION: That's right.
- Be strong and courageous.
- CONGREGATION: Yes. Yes.
- You see, He didn't say it would be easy...
- That's right.
...but what he did say is,
- is that he would never leave nor forsake you!
- Yes. Amen.
No matter how bleak
the situation may look,
- God is still in control!
- Yeah! Yeah!
- So you have to be strong and courageous,
- [CLAPPING]
knowing that he will never
leave you or forsake you!
- March on!
- Yes! Yes!
Whenever you're feeling afraid,
remember, God did not give us
the spirit of fear but of power!
- Love! And of sound mind! So march on! March on!
- [ALL CHEERING]
- We are all in this battlefield! Yes, Lord!
- Yes! Amen!
CONGREGATION: Amen!
Hallelujah!
[REVERED MCDANIEL
SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
[FOOTSTEPS]
You don't belong here.
MAY: Rosalie?
Rosalie?
[BOOK CLOSES]
[FOOTSTEPS]
Why do you want to go
to St. Julian's?
Because I deserve a good education,
like the kids who go here.
Will that be all?
Yes... you can go.
Your daughter's a baseball fan?
- Yes, she can't get enough of it.
- [CHUCKLES]
What's her favorite team?
- The Atlanta Crackers.
- [CHUCKLES] Mine, too.
Why, as a matter of fact,
we're going to a game Saturday.
- [BRACELET CLINKS]
- [ORCHESTRAL MUSIC PLAYING]
What's this?
My lucky bracelet.
Any time I wear it,
the Crackers win.
And we're gonna need that win
this Saturday. [CHUCKLES]
Thank you.
[FOOTSTEPS]
[BAG RUSTLES]
- [BIRDS CAWING]
- [DARK ORCHESTRAL MUSIC PLAYING]
[PAPER RUSTLING]
- RICKY-C: What do you mean, why am I taking this so seriously?
- [JAZZ MUSIC]
- This is a serious situation.
- LADY-D: It is.
- But, come on...
- Yeah, yeah, it is. But, anyway... Aight y'all.
So we got a good turnout from the
people in this area right here.
When we get over here,
- it goes cold.
- Because it's the heart.
It's the most
racist area in the city.
It also has the highest
concentration of the black vote.
Mmm-hmm.
That's the point right there.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
They ain't coming out.
Police got them shook.
You can't take a piss down there
without getting arrested.
And that's the fear that they're
counting on to keep people from voting.
We got to get
to those neighborhoods.
And how you think
we're going to do that, Junior?
We're just gonna
walk on in there?
Man, we'd be dead
before we hit the streets.
Not if they don't see us coming.
What about a night march?
We go straight in
through downtown.
Have you lost your mind?
We can't ask the people
to stand with us
if we're ain't willing
to stand for them.
And a dead man can't stand.
- Are y'all hearing this?
- I think it's a good idea.
- You would think it's a good idea.
- Shut up.
Stop it!
- They need to know they're not alone.
- That's right.
- Mike?
- [SCOFFS]
Man, if the police get
tipped off...
- we'll be committing our own suicide.
- Thank you.
What about a radio announcement?
You wanna broadcast
an illegal protest on the radio?
We'll use a code song, right?
And we'll spread the word out for people
listening to the Lady-D Show at 9:00 p.m.
- Hmm. That may not be a bad idea.
- [RICKY-C SIGHS]
The best way to hide something
is in plain sight.
Now you're thinking.
- What do you think, Lady-D?
- I dig.
OTIS JR.: Yeah.
Ricky. Ricky, man...
it's going to be okay.
[SOFT ORCHESTRAL MUSIC]
Our Father, which art in heaven,
hallowed be thy name,
thy kingdom come,
thy will be done
on earth, as it is in heaven.
ALL: Forgive us our trespasses
as we forgive those
who trespass against us,
and lead us not into temptation,
but deliver us from evil.
For thine is the kingdom,
and the power,
and the glory,
for ever and ever,
Amen.
Hope you know
what you're doing, Junior,
Thanks for coming out.
[FOOTSTEPS]
[BREATHES HEAVILY]
You nervous?
Oh, no.
[LAUGHS NERVOUSLY]
- Yeah.
- Kind of.
Ricky will come around.
He's just concerned
about everyone's safety.
Right. Of course.
Lady-D?
LADY-D: Hey, hey!
Who do we have here?
This is my little sister,
Rosalee.
And, like, your biggest fan.
I listen to your show every day.
- Is that so?
- Yeah.
I... I wanna be a radio host,
just like you.
We sure could use another sister
on the airwaves.
But how can you hear
with this gear?
Oh, no. Let me show you
what you need.
These.
Are those original Charlie Davis
headphones?
Mmm-hmm.
Autographed by him, too.
- You like?
- I love them.
They're yours.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Nice meeting you.
And I'll see you later.
You didn't tell me
Lady-D was gonna be here.
And you didn't tell me
you was going to be here.
Oh, yeah.
I needed some advice.
- What's going on?
- [SOFT PIANO MUSIC PLAYING]
There's this boy
at St. Julian's.
- He told me I ain't belong there.
- [CLICKS TONGUE]
- Now, you know you're just as smart as he is.
- [SIGHS]
I know.
But what if that's not enough?
[SIGHS]
I know how you feel.
Yeah, right.
You know, I'm one of the youngest people
to ever head a voters drive committee.
The older members,
they don't think I'm experienced enough.
And the younger ones want me
to just change things overnight.
Sometimes I feel like
I could just...
[SIGHS WEARILY]
roll over and quit.
How do you do it?
You got to remember
what you're fighting for.
Then you can break through.
Let me show you something.
I want you to imagine that that glass is all
the people who say you ain't good enough.
And these pebbles, this is you.
Go on and break it.
This little thing
ain't gonna break nothing.
David beat Goliath
with a pebble.
[ROCK THUDS AGAINST GLASS]
Told you.
Hey!
It looked like something to me.
Go again.
- [ORCHESTRAL MUSIC PLAYING]
- [GLASS CRACKS]
[GLASS SHATTERS]
[CHUCKLES] See?
Rosie, you got everything you
need to break through right here.
Let's go on
and get something to eat.
[WATER FLOWING]
Let's go.
[DARK ORCHESTRAL MUSIC PLAYING]
[TACKLE BOX FALLS OVER]
You just gonna stand there?
Like a goddamn moron?
- You clean that up.
- Yes.
[ROSALEE AND BRIANNA LAUGHING]
Natural law.
Here it is.
- ROSALEE: Where are we?
- This is my secret place.
I love to come here
when I need to think,
or when I need to be alone.
So, I thought this
would be good for you.
Come on.
[BRIANNA GIGGLES]
ROSALIE: This is so beautiful.
Ain't it, though?
[BRIANNA CLEARS THROAT]
BRIANNA: Come on, relax.
Isn't it peaceful?
[SIGHS] It makes you feel like
you ain't got a care in the world.
[FOOTSTEPS]
BILL: Hey!
What the hell
y'all coloreds doing here?
- Y'all can't read?
- Uh...
Sir, I've never
seen that before.
Uh, uh, uh. Sir, I never saw
that sign before.
It's there now.
Ain't she one of them coloreds
I saw at St. Julian's?
- [ROSALEE AND BRIANNA
WHIMPERING]
- [INTENSE ORCHESTRAL MUSIC
PLAYING]
[BILL GRUNTS]
[GRUNTING]
- [BRIANNA WHIMPERING]
- [BILL GRUNTING]
[BILL SCREAMS]
God damn!
Y'all gonna pay for that!
Stay in your goddamn town!
[RECORD PLAYER TURNING ON]
[SLOW POP MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUSIC CONTINUES]
[DOOR OPENS]
Rosie, what happened?
- Get her some water! Get her some water.
- All right. All right.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
What happened?
Take a deep breath, baby.
Take a deep breath.
Here, drink this, Rosie.
What's... What is the problem?
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Take your time.
- [ROSIE BREATHING HEAVILY]
- Take your time. Take your time.
[GASPS]
What happened?
[SNIFFLES]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[CRYING] Me and Brianna,
we were at a park, and...
this man, he...
He just really attacked us.
It's okay, baby.
- Oh, no, no, no!
- It's okay, it's okay.
It's okay, baby.
You're safe now. It's okay.
- It's okay. It's okay.
- [ROSIE CRYING]
[GRUNTING]
[MUTTERING]
Dad, what's goin' on?
A man attacked Rosalee
and Brianna at the park.
- What? She okay?
- Yeah, she is.
- [CHUCKLES] But he won't be for long.
- Dad. Dad...
That ain't gonna fix anything.
Did I ask
for your permission?
Dad, you do this, you gonna be a
coward, just like the man at the park.
[SCOFFS]
What did you call me, boy?
Get off me!
- So you wanna disrespect me in my own house?
- Help me!
- Huh? You wanna... in my house, huh?
- Oh, my God! Otis, stop it!
This is my house!
[SCREAMING]
Stop it! Otis, stop it!
- If you ever disrespect me like that again...
- Stop it! Stop it!
- ...I'll kill you myself!
- Stop it!
What's wrong with you?
My God!
Junior baby, you okay?
- Breathe, boy. Breathe, it's okay. It's okay.
- [OTIS JR. GRUNTS]
Just... just breathe, baby.
Just breathe.
Otis Wimbush Sr.,
what the hell is wrong with you?
You gonna kill your own son?
[CLOTHES RUSTLING]
Please...
- don't leave, Junior.
- [SUITCASE SLAMS SHUT]
[LOCKS CLICK]
[SIGHS]
I love you, Rosalee.
[SAD ORCHESTRAL MUSIC PLAYING]
[DUCKS QUACKING]
Hey.
Does it still hurt?
A little.
It looks worse
that it is, though.
This ain't right.
But, I have a plan...
Mama don't want me
hanging around you no more.
You know, just until
things calm down.
I'll talk to her.
Ain't no use.
She's made up her mind.
Does she blame me for this?
No, she don't blame you.
She just...
She just worry.
Do you?
I could've died, Rosalee.
That man knew you
from St. Julian's.
I'm so sorry.
You know what, I gotta go.
[FUNK MUSIC PLAYING]
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
[CHORUS SINGING]
OTIS JR.: ♪ Pick 'em
up and put 'em down!
PROTESTORS: ♪ Pick 'em
up and put 'em down
OTIS JR.: ♪ You know
we are freedom bound
PROTESTORS: ♪ You know
♪ Pick 'em up
and put 'em down
♪ You know
we are freedom bound
♪ Pick 'em up
and put 'em down
♪ You know
we are freedom bound
♪ Pick 'em up
and put 'em down
♪ You know
we are freedom bound
♪ Pick 'em up
and put 'em down
♪ You know
we are freedom bound
♪ Pick 'em up
and put 'em down
♪ You know
we are freedom bound
♪ Pick 'em up
and put 'em down
♪ You know
we are freedom bound
♪ Pick 'em up
and put 'em down
♪ You know
we are freedom bound
♪ Pick 'em up
and put 'em down
♪ You know
we are freedom bound
we are freedom bound ♪
[HEARTBEATS]
[PROTESTORS SCREAMING]
[GUNSHOT]
[MAN GRUNTING]
[SCREAMING CONTINUES]
[FOOTSTEPS]
[SOFT ORCHESTRAL MUSIC PLAYING]
[SNIFFLING, CRYING]
♪ Precious Lord
♪ Take my hand
♪ Lead me on
♪ Let me stand
♪ I, I'm tired
♪ I, I'm weak
♪ I...
♪ I'm alone...
♪ Through the storm
♪ Lord, through the night
♪ Lead me on
♪ To the light
♪ Take my hand
♪ Precious Lord
♪ And lead
♪ Me on ♪
ROSALEE: How's heaven?
I bet it's beautiful.
I know...
Grandma and G'dad
was happy to see you.
[SNIFFLES]
You know, Mom...
Mom still...
Mom still cries a lot.
And Dad...
[CHUCKLES]
Yeah, well...
He's still Dad.
[CRYING]
Please don't be mad at me.
But, I decided not to...
Not to go to Julian's.
I won't be able to do it
without you. [CRYING]
Just come back.
Please.
[CONTINUES CRYING]
- Please, Junior, just...
- just come back! [DOOR SQUEAKS]
- Just come back.
- [FOOTSTEPS]
Junior, it's me.
It's Dad.
- Never thought I'd be talking to you like this.
- [SOFT PIANO MUSIC]
I was hard on you.
I know.
I...
I was scared.
Scared that the movement
would take you from me.
And I was right.
[ROSALEE CRYING]
I kept...
- I kept this.
- [PAPER RUSTLING]
From your first
voter registration drive.
And you, uh...
You stayed up for weeks.
Researchin' and plannin'.
And the day of you,
you came to me
and you said, "Papa...
"I'm gonna make you proud."
Well...
I wasn't there to keep you safe.
[VOICE BREAKING]
Wasn't there to keep you safe.
I would've kept you
away from the movement.
Now, I know we...
We can never be safe.
There's gotta be
some kind of change.
I miss you, son.
I miss you.
[CRYING]
Junior...
[BOTH CRYING]
God, I miss you, son.
- [BOTH CONTINUE CRYING]
- Junior...
[ROCKING CHAIR CREAKING]
[PAPER RUSTLING]
HARVEY: Things have been
peaceful around here.
Last thing we need
is somebody stirring the pot.
ARLO: You're just gonna end up in
the butcher shop, like your dad.
You're just gonna end up in the
butcher shop, like your dad.
You don't belong here.
HARVEY: Things have been
peaceful around here.
ARLO: You're just gonna end up in
the butcher shop, like your dad.
RICHARD: You don't belong here.
BILL: Natural law.
MAY: Junior, see what you did?
Junior! Junior!
Come back!
ROSALEE: Please,
don't leave, Junior.
OTIS JR.: Rosie...
[CHUCKLES]
You got everything you need
to break through, right here.
Let's go on in.
[FOOTSTEPS]
[PEOPLE TALKING]
[SIGHS]
One week ago, today,
Otis Wimbush Jr. was killed.
He was gunned down,
protectin' a protestor at the march.
You may be gone,
but your legacy lives on.
If you're listenin',
please take a moment of silence with me.
[SNIFFLES]
This one is for you, Junior.
[SLOW MUSIC PLAYING]
Because of the courageous
actions of a few,
in September of 1963,
St. Julian's High School
was the first school in Marion
City, Alabama, to be integrated.
But the change
didn't come easy.
Life-altering decisions and sacrifices
were made, and even lives lost.
Are you willing to be the
change you wish to see?
[WOMAN SINGING]
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull