♪♪♪
No!
Where are you?
♪♪♪
[panting]
[crying]
♪♪♪
I'm behind you!
Get on your knees.
What?
Do it.
And see what happens.
[menacing laugh]
♪♪♪
Good.
Now, take the knife...
And kill yourself.
♪♪♪
[crying]
[rustling leaves] [crying]
♪♪♪
[church bells in distance]
Monroe, now you slow down.
Look, you need to take it easy.
Come on, Monroe.
Keys?
Look, why don't we just
go back to the house.
Now!
Where are they?
Monroe -
Where is that little
bitch and her mother?
Monroe, please.
Tell me where they are, Michael,
or I swear to God, I'm
going to snap your neck.
Ted's.
They're at Ted's.
♪♪♪
[tires screeching]
Don't worry, Evelyn,
he'll never post bail.
[giggles]
Oh...
he'll come.
You've got us.
It'll be all right.
No, it won't be all right.
[door squeaks open]
You get that lying little
whore away from me.
She ruined my family.
She ruined my life.
Evelyn, you don't mean that.
Yes, I do!
Just get that
whore away from me.
Oh, honey, let me
take you down stairs
and show you to your room.
I'll be back, but
for God's sakes,
put that bottle
away and consider
what your saying to your child.
I damn well know
what I'm saying.
She destroyed our lives.
Just an evil little whore!
Your mother doesn't mean that,
she's just upset.
She doesn't know
what she's saying.
[crying] Just an
evil little whore.
♪♪♪
You tell on me!
Here, I come to you...
[shower running]
[knocking on door]
Hurry up, Sheryl.
Dad, I've literally
just got in here.
And you about to just get
out, it's been 20 minutes.
I'll be out in a minute.
Geez! I can't even
enjoy a shower anymore.
♪♪♪
You're all going to
get what you deserve!
All of you.
[menacing laugh]
Everything's going to be okay.
There's no way he's
going to post bail.
I hope you're right.
But the things I've learned
in the last couple of hours,
if they're true...
Let's just make sure Claire
and Evelyn are taken care of.
I put Claire in Lauren's old
room across from Sheryl's.
I'm going upstairs
to talk to Evelyn.
How is she?
How do you think she would be?
I can imagine.
No, I don't think you can.
Claire.
Come here, honey.
Everything's going to be okay.
Why don't you go
back up to the room?
♪♪♪
[heavy breathing]
[cocks gun]
♪♪♪
[bangs on door]
Claire!
Monroe,
what are you doing here?
Where is she?
I don't know, I haven't see her.
Not... her.
Tomorrow we'll...
What is it, honey?
Claire.
Where is that little...
Monroe, look, you've
got to take it easy.
Take it easy.
[mencing laugh]
[thud]
Hey, dad, I'm...
[screams]
[thud]
♪♪♪
[heavy breathing]
He's here.
Impossible.
Stay here, I'll see
what's going on.
Monroe?
Where's Ted?
Where's Claire?!
I don't know. Where's Ted?
[menacing laugh]
♪♪♪
Oh my God! [thud]
[panting]
Where is she?
You mean, your whore?
[heavy breathing]
I hate you.
I fucking hate you.
[wrench drops on floor]
[heavy breathing]
Where...
is Claire?
Fuck you.
[menacing giggle]
Where is my daughter?
Fuck you!
Get off of me.
Let me be!
[pounding on Monroe]
Get off of me!
[crying]
[grunting] [crying]
[pounding on Monroe]
[heavy breathing]
♪♪♪
Come out...
I'll be quick.
No?
Then what I've done to
you is nothing compared
to what I'm going to do to.
Come here.
Come here!
[crying]
[heavy breathing]
[sobbing]
You're going to burn,
you little bitch.
I'm going to make sure of that.
[menacing laugh] [sobbing]
I'm going to make sure
your life's a living hell.
Every day, I'm
going to be there.
[sobbing]
Oh, yeah.
[sobbing] No.
Oh, yeah, because
I'll be there...
because I ain't never
going back to jail.
[gunshot]
[crying]
♪♪♪
[slaps man]
[panting]
♪♪♪
[birds chirping]
[leaves crunching]
♪♪♪
[leaves rustling]
[crickets chirping]
♪♪♪
[crying in woods]
[rustling in distance]
♪♪♪
[crickets chirping]
[sobbing]
♪♪♪
[crying]
[echoing whispers]
Frank?
Hello?
Tommy?
[echoing whispers]
Kristen?
Frank?
Frank!
Tommy!
Kristen!
[echoing whispers]
No.
[panting]
♪♪♪
No!
This is impossible.
I want out.
I need to get out!
You can't.
You're not real.
Am I going crazy?
I don't know.
I just know you can't get out,
not until it's time.
When is it time?
When it's time.
That's not an answer, damn it.
You'll know when it's time.
How will I know?
You just will.
It's coming for you.
There's nothing you can do.
What's coming?
It is.
It?
The evil.
It's coming.
[crying in distance]
♪♪♪
[laughing in distance]
Do you have a two?
Go fish.
[echoing whispers]
Do you have any tens?
Do you have any aces?
[annoyed sigh]
[echoing whispers]
How about some threes?
He's cheating.
There's a mirror
just behind you.
Tommy Carter!
What?
You know what happens
when you cheat, don't you?
You get the tickle claw.
Cheater, cheater, pumpkin eater.
No!
Yes, you do!
You do!
[laughing]
Yeah, okay.
I say we get some ice cream.
Ice cream.
I scream -
You scream -
We all scream for ice cream.
Come on, kiddos.
[giggle]
[echoing whispers]
[sobbing] I'm sorry.
[sobbing]
The kid's play is
tomorrow night.
Oh, that's right.
Tommy's playing Tiny Tim.
And Kristen's playing...
The Ghost of Christmas Present.
That's right.
Aw, our budding thespians.
My little one's better not
grow up to be thespians.
[laughs]
What time's the debacle?
I mean the play.
Who says it's going to be awful?
I do.
[scoffs]
You don't remember last year?
[laughing]
Oh, you do.
[laughing] Yeah...
Listen, I love my little
ones with all my heart but...
I don't think you have
to worry about them
being full-time thespians.
As I recall, you used to act.
[scoffs]
If you could call it that.
[giggling under covers]
[shower running]
[sigh of relief]
[dog barking in distance]
[echoing whispers]
You're not real.
You can't be.
It's too late.
Too late for what?
It's here.
Now.
What's here?
[demonic growl]
♪♪♪
[gasp]
Come to me, my child.
[screams]
[sobbing]
Mommy.
Kristen?
[leaves crunching]
How did you get here?
Kristen!
Kristen, please!
Kristen, baby,
please come back to me!
Kristen?
[screams]
♪♪♪
Kristen?
No.
You can't be here.
I need to show you something.
What?
Something.
Take my hand.
No.
Then, I can't help you.
Wait.
Don't leave me here.
I don't know what's going on.
[gasps]
[menacing laugh]
[heavy breathing]
Wait here.
[door slams]
[muffled discussions]
Okay, thank you.
Thank you.
♪♪♪
I want you to get
out of the car,
and go out into the woods,
and if anybody asks
what you're doing,
you tell them you're
going to the restroom.
Do you understand me?
Yes.
And no matter what you hear...
you stay there until
I come and get you.
Understand me?
Yes.
I asked you, if
you understood me?
Yes.
Good.
Now go on.
♪♪♪
Sweetheart, where are you going?
Little girls' room.
Well, I can go with her,
if you want me to.
She'll be fine.
Besides, I might need your help.
Both of your helps, not
as young as I used to be.
[nervous laugh]
Claire,
go on, honey.
She'll be fine.
Why don't you show me
where that spare tire is,
let's get you back on the road.
[crunching leaves]
♪♪♪
[distant screams]
[crunching leaves]
[screaming]
Please!
[screams]
Please, help me!
I don't want to die!
Please help!
Oh, my God!
[yelling]
[whacking]
[heavy breathing]
She's dead...
[menacing laugh]
She won't ever come back.
[heavy breathing]
Don't worry, Claire...
I killed her.
But, I didn't touch her.
You know you're my one and only.
[evil laugh]
But understand something,
you tell anybody about this,
your momma,
anyone...
and you're going to
end up just like her.
[whimpers]
Do you understand me?
Yes.
[crying]
It's just like that other stuff,
something we don't talk about.
[heavy breathing]
[sobbing]
Why?
Why do you have to show me that?
[crying]
[echoing crying]
[echoing whispers]
So glad you could make it.
What is this?
Christmas dinner.
Please join us.
So glad you could make it.
All right,
all right, I'll sit.
Just stop saying that.
Carve the turkey, hon.
No.
We want turkey.
You always carve the
turkey on Christmas.
[gasps]
[gasp]
Why, mommy?
[crying]
Claire.
What did I do?
Nothing.
You've got to talk to me.
I'm worried about you,
the kids are worried about you.
You haven't come out
of the bedroom all day.
Kids are too afraid
to even come in here.
Don't say that.
Please, talk to me.
I keep hearing things,
and seeing things.
Kind... what kind of things?
Things that happened
to me as a kid,
things that I
haven't talked about.
I love you, baby.
The kids love you.
No matter what you tell me,
that's not going to change.
I just...
Please do share, Claire.
You're hurting me.
I like hurting you.
[scream] [demonic laugh]
You again.
Why are you doing this to me?
You're not real.
I am real.
No, you're not.
It's impossible.
I'm here to show you things.
To help you.
You damn well aren't helping me.
I am.
You just don't know it yet.
It's after you.
What is It?
What do you keep talking about?
It is -
What, that demon thing?
No.
Not again.
I'm not going to do that again
if you're going to show
me something awful.
You have to.
It's the only way to keep
it from getting to you.
I don't understand.
I don't understand
what's going on.
But you will.
I promise.
♪♪♪
[crying]
Don't turn around.
I just want to come home, Frank.
I just want to come home.
I know, sweetheart.
We got to stay here until
they get your medicine right.
And then you can come home.
I miss the kids.
I hate it here.
Please, take me out of here.
I'll be okay.
I'm fine.
I feel better already.
But we got to wait until
the doctors say it's okay.
It shouldn't be more
than a couple days now.
Then things are going to
be so much better for you.
For all of us.
I just want you well.
♪♪♪
I told you, I want
out of here, damn it!
Listen to me, get me
out of this place!
I want to go to my
own fucking house!
I want to be with you
and my fucking kids!
Don't you understand?
[crying]
I'm sorry.
Oh, god, I'm sorry
I didn't mean that.
It's okay.
[gasping] I'm sorry.
God, I'm sorry.
It's okay, baby.
A couple more days and
everything's going to be fine.
[gasps]
What is it?
Do you see him again?
No.
Is he behind me?
No, he's not there.
I haven't seen him anymore
since I've been here.
Liar.
Okay.
Look, I'm going to let
you get some rest, okay?
I'm going to come
back this afternoon.
[crying] Take me home tonight.
Please, Frank.
Please, tonight?
We'll have to talk
to the doctors, okay?
I'll talk to them on my way out,
and I'll see what he has to say.
Okay.
Tell him I'm better, okay?
Tell him I'm fine now.
No more voices,
no more visions, okay?
I will.
Frank?
I'm not getting any better.
Aw, don't say that.
Sure you are.
Are you taking your meds?
I don't like the way
they make me feel.
My god, Claire...
Don't do that to me.
When I take them, it's
like I can't feel anymore.
It's like I have no emotions,
it's like I'm dead inside.
When you don't take them...
[crying] God...
I know, I hate it!
I hate it!
[crying] Oh, I hate it.
Come on now, you're
getting worked up again.
It's because you keep
telling me what to do.
Take your meds - you
act like I'm crazy!
Don't patronize me.
[crying]
[screams]
♪♪♪
[faucet turns back on]
What the hell?
[shower curtain opens]
I'm so cold.
[crying]
Please, help me.
No.
Please.
No, no.
No.
[crying] No, no.
[gasps]
♪♪♪
You're her!
[demonic screams] You're
the reason I'm dead!
Leave me alone!
Get awayfrom me!
[heavy breathing]
I didn't do it, I didn't do it.
It wasn't me.
[gasps]
It'll be over soon enough,
for the both of us.
I can't take it anymore.
I can't take it.
Not much longer.
[crying]
Make it all stop, please.
Make it stop.
[screams]
How many time, Tommy?
How many times do
I have to tell you
to keep this room
looking straight?
And look at it.
Claire?
Who are you talking to?
Tommy!
He made an absolute
mess all over the bed.
Hon, Tommy and Kristen
are outside playing.
He got crumbs all over the bed.
There aren't any
crumbs on the bed.
The kids are outside.
There were crumbs.
[sobbing] He's not here!
He's not here!
Claire, he's not here.
Look at me, look at me,
Look at me, who do you see?
Who do you see?
You.
Me. You see me -
I see you. I see you.
Yes, he's not here.
There's no one else...
No, damn it!
Look at me! [screams]
Look at me! Look at me!
[screams]
Damn it, look at me!
Look at me!
[sobbing]
It's just me.
There's no one else.
It's just me, Frank.
Just you and only you.
Do you understand?
Yeah.
Okay. I'm going to call -
I'm going to call
the doctor, okay?
But you need to sit here
while I go get my phone,
all right?
Okay.
I'll be back in 20 seconds.
[crying]
Okay?
Okay.
[panting]
[heavy breathing]
[screams]
Oh, god! No!
No!
Look at me!
Wait, don't leave me!
I don't want to.
[thud]
[sobbing]
You little whore.
Momma!
Please, help me!
[sobbing] Please, help me!
Your momma -
that whore lives in
the bottom of a bottle.
You...
you please me.
I can't!
Please.
Turn over.
[sobbing]
Or I'm going to beat you
until you can't move.
No, I can't,
I don't want to!
[heavy breathing]
I don't care what you want!
It's what I want.
[sobbing]
And you're going to
get what you need.
[crying] No!
Don't you lay a hand on her!
Don't you dare!
[heavy breathing]
[menacing laugh]
Look who it is.
I told you, you'd
never escape me.
She didn't do anything to you.
[laugh]
Oh, but she did...
she pleases me in so many ways.
Don't you touch her.
Or what?
What are you going to do?
Stop me?
You never could stop me.
Why don't you run to your momma?
You know where she is.
Maybe that bitch will help you.
[muffled Young Claire]
I don't want to!
I wondered when you were going
to come stumbling in here.
[Young Claire crying]
Momma?
You couldn't let the
dead rest in peace,
could you?
You're drunk.
And you're a wicked
slut of a daughter.
How can you say that?
How can you sit here,
while that's going
on in the next room?
You wanted it.
You wanted him all to yourself.
That's not true.
He forced himself on me.
Having him all to yourself
wasn't enough, huh?
You had to go and fuck him too.
He won't even look
at me anymore.
What kind of a mother are you?
He raped me.
He ripped my childhood
away from me.
Don't play me.
You were always
just a little whore.
Parading around
in those pajamas,
shaking that little
whore's ass of yours.
You never said anything.
You never did anything.
You never tried to stop him,
you did nothing!
You're just a dirty,
little whore.
[sobbing]
Why didn't you protect me?
I hated you.
You ruined my life.
You let him do
those things to me.
You and the others.
You took everything from me.
[sobbing] I was
nine years old.
I was innocent.
You...
were never innocent.
You were never sober enough
to noticed the difference.
Shut up.
You let my father rape me!
Shut up!
And you did nothing about it!
Shut that little trap of yours!
Or what?
You'll do what you did
while he was raping me?
I'm going to do what
I should have done
a long time ago.
♪♪♪
You hated me.
You hated me!
You let him rape me!
[heavy breathing]
♪♪♪
[menacing laugh]
Daddy's little girl.
[heavy breathing]
[gasp]
You didn't make the evil.
It's not your fault.
You just brought it here.
How?
How did I do that?
If I take your hand again,
is it going to help me
understand what's going on?
Yes.
Is it going to hurt
as bad this time?
Yes, worse.
Worse than before.
But not as bad as
it's going to be.
[sigh]
[gasp]
You stay here -
[yelling]
Claire, honey, you
need to tell us.
Ms. Dansbury here
says you've been
telling her all kinds of things.
Things about your dad?
Are these things you've
been saying about him, true?
Or are you just making them up?
You said you saw
bruises on her arms?
Yes, I did.
Are those bruises
from your daddy?
Claire, honey, look at me.
You know me, right?
And you know I'm
here to help, right?
Okay.
What you may not know,
as your principal, I'm
also here to protect you.
And if someone out
there is hurting you,
I can make them stop.
And they will never be able
to hurt you ever again, okay?
But I have to know if
these things are true,
you understand?
Yes, ma'am.
Okay.
Tell me now, is
someone hurting you?
[children laughing in distance]
You can tell me.
I will take care of you.
And I will make it
stop, I promise.
Is that a yes?
Okay, sweetie.
Your mother, does she know?
Does your mother know
anything about this?
No.
Only him.
Okay, listen, sweetie, this
is very, very important,
you have to tell me,
what does he do to you?
He...
Does he beat you on your bottom?
Or anywhere else?
Does he hit you anywhere?
On my bottom...
and other places.
Okay, what else
does he do to you?
Does he touch you
anywhere he shouldn't?
Do anything else to
you, he shouldn't?
[children laughing in distance]
Jill, get me Sheriff Moody
on the phone right now.
You just had to go and
open your fucking mouth,
didn't you?
You just had to tell somebody?
You've done it now.
You fucked it all up.
This is all your fault,
you little bitch.
He's going to come after us.
He's going to come
after us and kill us.
Or worse...
Was it so bad?
Huh, was it?
Just lay there and take it,
that's what I told you.
Just lay there and take it.
But no...
you had to run off and
open your fucking mouth
and tell someone.
He told you what he
would do, didn't he -
If you ever told anybody?
You think he won't?
No, he's going to come after us.
And he's going to kill us.
If he can find us.
Where is that little
bitch and her mother?
Monroe, please.
Tell me where they are, Michael.
Or I swear to God, I'm
going to snap your neck.
Ted's.
They're at Ted's.
Here, let's get you upstairs.
Ted, you got this down here?
Sure.
I'll be up to check
on you in a minute.
If he finds us
here, it'll be bad.
It's okay, Evelyn,
they won't let him go.
We'll sort out what
to do tomorrow.
[crying]
Claire?
Here,
have a seat for a minute.
You like jokes?
What's black and white,
and red all over?
Newspaper.
You heard this joke before?
Hmm.
You go.
What's black and white,
and red all over,
and it's not a newspaper?
Hmm, I don't know.
A sunburned penguin.
[laughs]
Good one.
[screams]
[heavy breathing]
Shh, it'll hear us and find us.
Quick, under here.
[heavy breathing]
Hurry, he'll find us.
What is It?
The evil.
It's coming for them.
What do you mean?
Shh, it'll hear us.
Don't let it get me.
[whimpering]
[door squeaks open]
♪♪♪
[inhaling soul]
I thought it had us.
[screams]
You're going nowhere.
[heavy breathing]
Go away!
No, no!
[screams]
♪♪♪
[panting]
[crying]
[sobbing] No! No!
[screams]
This is all your fault!
You can't get away with it!
It got her,
now It's going to get you!
[screams]
No! No!
[crying]
[hysterical crying]
♪♪♪
What?
[crying]
What is this?
Do you feel cold inside?
No.
Yes.
You took them.
[demonic laugh]
They belong to me now.
Oh, yes, their
souls belong to me.
My babies.
Not your babies
anymore, they're mine.
Their souls are mine.
Don't you hurt them,
don't you dare touch them.
Stop, stop it!
I'm going to collect her soul.
No, don't!
Or what?
Please, I'll do anything!
Anything you want!
Just don't hurt them.
Please.
I hardly think that's true.
What are you?
I'm you.
I'm your sadder side,
I'm the part that resides
in the darkest
recesses of your soul,
the part that you
pretend doesn't exist.
I am the great unwashed,
I am the savior of
those who suffer
the trappings of
deluded misdeeds,
you want to know who I am?
I am your pain.
[banging on door]
Claire?
Monroe, what... what
are you doing here?
Where is she?
I don't know, I
haven't seen Evelyn.
Not her, Claire.
Where is that little bitch?
Monroe, you need
to just calm down.
Calm down.
[menacing laugh]
[grunting in pain]
Dad, I was just...
[screams]
[thud]
♪♪♪
Monroe!
Where is Ted?
Where is Claire?
[menacing laugh]
Oh my God!
[crying]
[demonic growling]
[sobbing]
I hate you.
[demonic growling]
[sobbing]
Come here.
♪♪♪
[crying]
You're going to burn,
you little bitch.
I'm going to make sure of that.
I'm going to make sure
your life is a living hell.
I'm going to be there.
Every day, oh yeah, oh yeah.
[crying]
Because I ain't never
going back to jail!
[gunshot]
[crying]
Where are you going, Claire?
Where is she?
Where are my kids?
What have you done with them?
You can't escape me, Claire.
I've got them.
And now I'm here for you.
No place to run, Claire.
Besides, where ever you go,
there you are.
This is not real.
This not real! This
is not happening!
This is not real.
[clawing at door]
Little pig, little pig...
let me come in.
You!
You let the evil into our house.
I didn'tmean to.
And now, I'm cold.
So cold.
I'm sorry.
Sorry?
Do you know what
the pain is like?
It's like being
turned inside out
and your brain is on fire.
You deserve to be here,
burning with us, dying with us.
[crying]
[choking]
[gasping]
[demon yelling]
[screams]
Now you can see my true face.
[menacing laugh]
Claire.
♪♪♪
Leave her alone.
You're not real,
you're just in my mind.
Really?
Is that what you think?
Then what happens to her...
really won't
matter, now will it?
[neck snaps]
[screams]
And you were there
facing me last.
There it is.
Fuck you, you bastard.
[menacing laugh]
Look at your hand.
[gasps]
You can't escape.
You're not real.
Can you not smell the
stench of your past?
Get away from me.
Your soul is black and diseased.
Give into me.
I'll kill you.
You can't escape.
You know that!
[crying]
Embrace me now.
Stay away!
Put down the wrench.
Fuck you!
Claire!
Stay away!
Get away from me!
Stop swinging the
fucking wrench.
[crying]
You can't kill me, Claire.
[thud]
No!
[panting]
Where are you?
[menacing laugh]
Give into me, Claire.
Besides, I'm not
in front of you...
I'm behind you.
Boo!
[crying]
♪♪♪
[panting]
[crying]
♪♪♪
Mommy?
Kristen!
Tommy!
I can't move, Mommy.
Don't you hurt them.
They are such precious
children, aren't they?
Please, don't hurt them!
Then submit to me.
Get on your knees.
What?
Do it.
And see what happens.
♪♪♪
[demonic laugh]
Good.
Now take the knife...
and kill yourself.
What?
Kill yourself.
No!
[snaps necks]
No, you son of a bitch!
♪♪♪
[crying]
[choking]
Ah!
[demonic laugh]
[heavy breathing]
[thud]
[sobbing]
♪♪♪
Claire!
Claire Morris?
Claire Morris.
Who is it?
It's the Sheriff's Department.
Yes, just a minute.
Are you Miss Morris?
Yes, what is this?
Please, keep your hands
where I can see them
and come out of the tent.
Show your hands now!
Come out of the tent.
Wait, what's wrong?
What... no... hey,
what are you doing?
Hold still, ma'am.
Just hold still.
What's happening?
I haven't done anything.
I'm not... I'm not
going anywhere with you,
until you tell me
what's going on.
Just hold still.
I haven't done anything.
Stop!
No!
Hey, no, tell me
what we're doing.
No!
I haven't done anything.
Come on!
Wait a minute!
Where are we going?
Tell me what is going on.
No! No.
Stop!
Wait!
♪♪♪
[gasps]
What's going on?
What's wrong?
What's happening?
I have to show you.
♪♪♪
No.
I love you, Frank.
I love you too.
What's wrong?
[murmurs]
♪♪♪
I love you, too.
He'll never get you.
He'll never hurt you.
I'll never let that happen.
♪♪♪
[stabbing]
I love you.
I'll never let him get you.
Never.
[stabbing]
[screaming]
No, my babies!
No! No!
[screaming]
I love them, you
don't understand.
I saved them.
I love them, I love them.
I... I love them.
I saved them.
I love them.
I love them...
I saved them.
I love them.
Shh.
We love them too.
[demonic laughing]
We all love them.
[demonic laugh]
We love them.
We saved them.
♪♪♪