[Low humming music]
[Shutter clicks]
- That's right.
- You laugh now, right?
See, you laugh now. You wait.
I'm telling you, man,
it's a brand-new champion.
You better
take that picture, man.
You're looking
at a new champ, baby.
[Shutters click]
Back it up!
Back up, man.
- Can we get a picture of him?
- Back off, man.
- What do you think about
everything that's happened?
Do you feel you deserve to win?
- Back up!
Come on, man. Give him room.
Give him room!
Sonny...
Back it up! Back it up!
[Cheers and applause]
[Man shouts]
[People cheering]
[Dog barks]
[Door slams]
- Ah!
[Screaming]
Come here! Come here! Come here!
- Come on, get out.
It's all right. It's all right.
I got it. I got it.
What's on your mind here?
What's on your mind?
You have to talk about it.
You're gonna be all right.
- Hey, man. Give me a cigarette.
I said, give me a cigarette.
Big Lester.
- What's wrong with you, man?
You must be out of your
goddamn mind, man.
- We're fine. Okay, all right.
- What's wrong with you, man?
- You don't want to do this.
Just pick up big Lester.
It's okay.
- Man, this ain't over.
- Yeah, I know. It never is.
- Watch your back, man.
- Hey, take big Lester
to the infirmary; Come on.
It's all right.
He just slipped on the water.
You come on with me.
- No, I'm fine right where I am.
- Did you look over there?
Now, I know he's not
the brightest of all the guards,
but he's going to realize that
something's not right down here.
Why don't you just come on
with me and...
Come on.
Good.
Hey, Mason.
- One more. One more.
Come on, you got it.
- Why are we here?
- Well, not only
am I a chaplain.
I'm also athletic director.
- So what that got to do
with me?
- I figure with your strength
and your power
you might want to join
our boxing league here.
- Y'all got a boxing league?
- Oh, yes, sir.
Got some pretty
tough contenders too.
- Who the champ?
- Actually, you just
knocked him out.
It's big Lester.
[Dramatic orchestral music]
Sonny.
Sonny, come on. Get up.
First boxing lesson.
Come on, get up.
Let me see you punch me here.
You know what these are?
What these are?
- What?
- Come on. They're pads.
Punch 'em. Hit me.
What was that?
Do it again.
Come on.
Okay, come here.
Let's look at your legs.
Come on.
You're standing like a pencil.
Back foot back,
that about 45—that's it.
Let that, your back foot...
Just up on your toes a little.
That's where your power's
gonna come from, all right?
Let's try it again.
All right. That's it.
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven.
Keep it in circles.
Double up on the jab.
That's it. That's it.
That's right. That's good.
- That's girl stuff.
- It's not girl stuff.
It's working your legs.
What are you going to do,
stand there
and let them hit you?
Boxing's half about the feet.
You got back up there
and you jump rope.
We're going to start again
from the beginning.
Let's go. Boxing is dancing.
It's all—half is leg work.
Keep coming back. That's it.
Bob and weave.
Keep your eyes on him.
29, 30, 31, 32.
Keep going. 33...
He's got a long reach.
You're going to stay
away from him.
- Man, you got to be prepared.
- Okay?
- Don't forget about the feet.
All right?
Hey, catfish.
- Hey, you ready?
All right. Here we go.
Here we go. Here we go.
All right. All right.
Make some noise, y'all.
Make some noise.
Here we go, baby. Here we go.
Waiting a long time
for this match.
All right. Come on, now.
Come on, get up.
Let's do it. Let's do it.
Come on now.
Now, check this out.
I want a good, clean fight,
all right?
If you guys decide to get dirty,
I can't do nothing for you.
Ain't no such thing
as scorecards.
Y'all got to take that shit
out in the yard.
Match doesn't start
until I beat the bucket.
You dig? You dig?
Make it a clean fight.
Come on, man.
Kick his ass. Knock his ass out.
All right, let's go, baby.
Let's go.
Come on, now.
Here we go.
All right, go.
Big Lester, big Lester.
[Upbeat funky music]
Right, left, right.
That's right, left, right.
That's what
I'm talking about, baby.
- You forgot the footwork.
- Let's score while Sonny
has his breath.
He ain't got nothing on you,
baby.
- Hands up! Hands up!
- Big Lester!
- Big Lester! Big Lester!
Big Lester!
- Get up, Lester!
- Sonny Liston! Sonny Liston!
- Sonny Liston!
Hey, Sonny, man, look...
- All right. All right.
How's big Lester?
Come on.
11,12,13,14.
1,2, 3,4, 5.
Don't forget the legs.
Keep the legs loose.
Now, this guy's a different
kind of fighter.
He likes to dance around.
If he does,
just cut off the ring.
Stay in his eyes.
- Come on, we got Sonny Liston,
boxing state champ,
and over here we have...
What's your name, brother?
It don't even matter.
I'm just going to just
call you, uh,
evil negro turtle.
Evil negro turtle.
All right, evil negro turtle
versus Sonny Liston.
Here we go. All right.
- Look at that big guy's head,
man.
Last time I seen a head
that ugly,
I put a rubber on it.
- Away from him.
- Come on, Sonny.
Sonny. Come on, man.
[Men shouting]
- Oh! Oh, that's it.
Can you hear me down there?
Uno, dos...
Fuck. Man, you out.
You out.
Prison state boxing champion.
What's his name?
Sonny, Sonny, Sonny,
Sonny Liston.
That's what I'm talking about.
- [Grunting]
[Bucket clangs]
- Stop! Stop!
Sonny, enough!
Enough!
That's enough! That's enough!
- "Liston is...
UN...
"B—b—b...
B-e-a-t."
- Unbeatable.
- "UN-b—b—b..."
- Beatable.
Nd. "E-a" is a "e" sou
- no, man. To hell with this.
- You just got to be patient,
Sonny.
- Why? Why I got to be patient?
I'm going to be the heavyweight
champ of the world.
Why I got to be patient?
- You get out to here tomorrow.
Two years
on a five-year sentence,
that is because
you bettered yourself.
There are people that don't want
to see you get out of here,
but because
you bettered yourself,
they can't deny you.
- Getting out of here tomorrow
for doing the same stuff
I've been doing all my life:
Knocking motherfuckers out.
You know what's
gonna keep me out of here?
- What?
- Knocking motherfuckers out.
[Train whistle blowing]
[Upbeat jazzy music]
[Indistinct chatter]
- Can I help you?
- Sonny Liston.
- You can't be Sonny Liston,
because he was supposed
to be here yesterday.
- My first day out.
I had to get some pussy.
- [Chuckles]
You make that the last time
you show up here
without calling, you hear me?
- Well, who the hell are you?
- I'm the man that's gonna
change your life, pal.
I'm Caesar novak.
I got a lot of friends
in this town,
a little power, respect.
You got it?
- I got it.
- Father alios tells me
that you're gonna be
the next heavyweight champion
of the world.
-Mmhmm.
- He's sent me a lot of fighters
through the years.
He's never said that
about anyone.
Should we gamble on you?
- Bet the bank.
[Horn honks]
- Is there something wrong
with your eyes, mister?
- Well, I wouldn't be
much of a gentlemen
if I let a pretty lady
just walk in the cold.
- Well, thank god I'm pretty,
and I'll tell you what,
Mr. Gentleman,
you can just keep moving
right along,
seeing that I don't take rides
with strangers.
- Whoa. Whoa. Whoa.
Whoa.
I ain't no stranger.
Everybody around here know me.
Name's Sonny,
Sonny Liston.
- That mean boxer?
- Girl, I just can't win
with you, now, can I?
- Well, no.
You're not doing
a very good job so far.
- Well, I ain't going to let you
stand here in the cold.
This here my driver's license.
That'd be my address.
Take it.
I'm going to give you my keys.
You take my car,
you bring it to my house
tomorrow.
- And how are you
gonna get home?
- I'm gonna run.
- It says here you live
all the way out in Clark.
That's almost ten miles away.
- Well, then I better get going.
- Hey! Hey!
Mister!
♪ That's why they call it ♪
♪ falling in love ♪
♪ do you remember
when we first met? ♪
- Well, I guess I'm just
a little impressed,
Mr. Liston.
- I heard you were looking
for a cutman,
and I am looking for work.
[Laughs]
- Catfish.
[Upbeat funky music]
- All right, boxers.
Center of the ring.
All right, boxers.
You received your instructions
in the dressing room.
I want a good, clean fight.
Shake hands.
Ding!
[Men shouting]
[Crowd cheering]
Corner! Corner!
- One, two, three, four...
[Crowd cheering]
- One, two...
Ten. You're out!
[People cheering]
- Corner!
- Come on! Come on!
Come on!
- Four, five, six,
seven, eight, nine,
he's out!
[Crowd cheering]
[Cheers and applause]
- Six, seven,
eight, nine, ten.
[Crowd cheering]
[Church bell ringing]
- So you gave up prison life
for this?
- I ain't going to do that.
- Thank you.
- I've been here
for three months.
Why don't you have a seat?
Three months.
You just now—
you come to see me.
- Well, I met someone.
- Hey, O’Brien.
O’Brien, not now. Not now.
Last I heard,
you were meeting someone
just about every night, so...
- [Chuckles]
No, this one, she's special.
Her name Geraldine.
- Geraldine.
How long?
- About three, four months.
- That's really good, Sonny.
I know she must be
a wonderful lady.
Well, I wanted to come
see you fight,
but you don't have anything
scheduled, so...
- Everybody running from me.
They know they get
in that ring with me,
I'm going to act like the animal
they call me in the papers.
See, all that did
was make me stronger.
You taught me in prison,
no weapon formed against me
shall prosper,
so now I can't be beat.
- Maybe not by an opponent.
- What you mean?
- It means you don't
beat yourself, Sonny.
Pride—pride is
one of the deadly sins.
- In that ring,
I'm a deadly sin.
- All right.
Sonny,
can I buy you lunch?
You got time?
I'm going to take a step out.
You probably have to sign
an autograph
for father O’Brien there.
He's a big fan.
- I told you,
you ain't getting none
until you marry me.
- Okay.
- Okay?
- Let's go in house now.
[Knock on window]
- Hey, sport.
What are you doing
just sitting in the car?
It's time to go home.
- In a minute.
- I live right there.
- I said now, boy.
- Now, I know you ain't
talking to me,
'cause I don't see no boys
around here.
- Get out of the car.
Now.
- Wait, officer.
This is my woman,
and what kind of man I be,
I let you call me boy
in front of her?
- Oh, I see.
- Oh, you see what?
- I see you a smart-ass nigger.
Now get your black ass
out of the car now.
- Okay, baby. You wait here.
- Put your hands on your head!
- Please.
- And tell that hooker
to get out of the car too.
- Sonny!
Sonny!
Stop it, Sonny! Stop!
Sonny, stop!
- Freeze!
Let's go. That's it.
Come on. Move it.
- Sonny.
[Melancholy music]
- Hi.
I got us a new house.
My cousin's renting it to us.
And when we get there,
I'm going to make love to you
like you ain't never
had it before.
- Mmm.
- I been reading books.
- [Chuckles]
- And on the way,
we're going to stop
at the justice of the peace
and get married.
Did you say something?
- No.
- Good. Well, let's go.
- Congratulations, Mrs. Liston.
- Congratulations, Mr. Liston.
♪ You were meant for me ♪
♪ undeniably ♪
♪ you're all I need ♪
♪ it was written some place ♪
♪ long ago ♪
♪ I'd be smitten
by your first hello ♪
[Low humming music]
- Good day for hunting.
- Hey, hand me my bullets.
Where my bullets at?
You forget them again?
Dumbass.
You know why I hate your ass?
Because you're a foreign object
to life.
Put your hands on the truck.
Now, I don't want to hear
nothing from you.
- Ah!
Ah!
Ugh!
[Crying]
- Sonny.
Sonny.
Shh.
It's okay.
- [Gasping]
♪ My baby's gone ♪
♪ she don't know
what she's missing ♪
♪ ooh, my baby's gone ♪
♪ she don't know
what she's missing ♪
- Sonny, I got to run,
all right?
- What's going on?
- I got to talk to you later,
Sonny.
- Sonny, who is it?
- Huh. Oh, baby.
- Why don't you answer me,
and why did you leave
the front door open?
It's freezing out here.
- My, my, my.
- Whose car is that
in our driveway?
- Oh, look at them whitewalls.
And that grille.
That's that new one.
Holy...
- Sonny boy.
- What up, Caesar?
- You ready to get
the fight you deserve?
- I'm ready to be champ,
if that's what
you're talking about.
- All right.
I have to go to Vegas
this weekend.
I'm buying a house there.
I'm going to sit down
with some people,
people who could help you
get a shot at the title.
Know what I mean?
- Yeah, I know what you're
talking about.
- Good.
So I'm going out on a limb
for you.
Can you stay out of jail for me?
Good man.
- Sonny, let's go
do some shadow.
Come on.
- Go to work.
- That jelly roll move.
[Jet engine whirring]
- Ah, madon.
Yeah, look at that, huh?
Now, that's beautiful, huh?
What's that?
So what about my guy, huh?
- He's unmanageable.
Have you seen his arrest record?
- Nico, with all do respect,
who are we to judge
an arrest record?
Huh? Am I right?
- Yeah, when we get pinched,
it's for legitimate crimes,
right?
Not fucking small-time shit.
Come on.
- He's right.
He's nothing but trouble.
- This guy is going to be
the next heavyweight champion
of the world.
The heavyweight champion
We're going to let him walk
into someone else's camp?
Huh?
Come on. Let me handle this.
He's going to be
a fucking cash cow.
- I like you.
- Trust me. Let me handle it.
- It's against
my better judgment.
Don't let this guy
change my opinion of you.
- He won't.
We got a winner here.
It's going to be like
a gravy train.
All right?
- You listen to me,
one day, one of these
could be yours.
[Siren blares]
- New car.
- Yeah.
- I guess you can really take
the nigger out of the ghetto,
but you can't take the ghetto
out of the nigger.
- Sonny. Sonny. Sonny.
- Keep coming, boy.
You try that,
see what happens this time, hmm?
If you ever get a chance
to fight Patterson,
he's going to whup you
something good, boy.
Have a fantastic night, boy.
[Engine turns]
- Sonny, no.
Come on.
- Sonny.
- Any word
from the Patterson people?
- Patterson?
- Yeah, he can't
keep running from me.
I'm the number one contender,
and even the president said
he should fight me.
- You're right.
Well, the thing is, Sonny,
that the Patterson camp
called this morning,
and the fight is all set.
September 25:
Liston versus Patterson.
[Laughs]
How is that, huh?
Just get your ass home
and get packed.
I need you to get on a plane
with me tonight
and go to Vegas
and do some press.
We'll fool around a little bit,
check out my new house.
No wives allowed.
Right?
[Upbeat jazzy music]
♪ First time
I ever saw your face ♪
♪ takes me back
to our special place ♪
♪ everything was perfect,
time and space ♪
- There he is.
- Hey, how are you, Caesar?
- How are you?
- Good to see you.
- Bill Macky.
Sonny, from sports world boxing.
- How you be, Mr. Macky?
- Very well, thank you, Sonny.
- Thanks for asking.
- Have a seat.
- Yeah, let's just...
- Let's get started.
- Let's get going.
So, bill, what do you got
for Sonny?
- Well, Sonny, why do you think
Patterson's giving you
a shot at the title?
- Because it's the right thing
to do.
Sonny is a very talented,
gifted fighter.
He's the number one contender
in the world,
and he's earned it.
- Now, you've seen Patterson
fight, obviously.
What makes you think
you stand a chance?
- He wouldn't be here if he
didn't stand a chance, bill.
- So do you feel the pressure
of the negro race on you
to win this fight?
- They're both Negroes,
and I'm sure no matter
what the outcome is,
they're both going to represent
their race with dignity.
Right, Sonny?
- Right.
- No offense intended, Sonny,
but my money's on Patterson.
- Yeah, no offense, Mr. Macky,
but you're about to lose
your money.
I spent my whole life
knocking motherfuckers out.
- Well, then perhaps you care
to comment
on your extensive criminal past,
including assaulting
police officers
and your alleged ties
with organized crime.
- What did you say?
Get that fucking smile
off your face.
You fucking son of a bitch.
Get out!
- What the fuck!
- Motherfucker! Here!
You never insult my fighter
that way.
Ever!
Get the fuck out of here!
Fucking prick!
I guess that didn't go too well.
Let's go get a drink
at the pink dragon.
You can meet my new lady.
She's a singer there.
All right?
- That's a good right hand
you got.
- Learned from the best, man.
♪ Way beyond compare ♪
[Jazzy piano music]
♪ Do, do ♪
♪ do, do ♪
♪ if you want my love ♪
♪ just take all of me ♪
♪ just simply set me free ♪
♪ if you want me love ♪
- Gino!
How you doing, buddy?
How's your family?
♪ Just treat ♪
♪ treat, treat me right ♪
- Say hello to Sonny.
Sonny, Gino.
♪ My love ♪
♪ just take me there ♪
♪ if you want my love ♪
♪ just let me know you care ♪
- You all right?
- I want you to meet somebody,
Frankie.
- Hey, champ.
Nice to meet you.
- Next heavyweight champ
of the world.
♪ Just treat ♪
♪ treat, treat me right ♪
- There she is.
Put your tongue
back in your mouth.
- Please.
♪ It's a kind of love ♪
♪ that is rich and fair ♪
♪ love that I want ♪
♪ is not for everyone ♪
♪ but for that one man ♪
♪ that wants more than fun ♪
- No, no, no.
All right. All right.
[Applause]
♪ If you want my love ♪
♪just take all of me ♪
♪ if you want my love ♪
♪ just simply set me free ♪
♪ I will give to thee ♪
♪ just treat ♪
♪ treat, treat me right ♪
♪ just treat, treat,
treat, treat ♪
♪ Tre-e-e-eat ♪
♪ treat me right ♪
[Applause]
- Bravo!
- She's good.
- Whoo!
Thank you.
I'm going to take
a little break,
but I will back,
if you treat me right.
[Applause]
- There she is.
Why do you have to embarrass me
like that, huh?
- Because I love you.
- Sit down.
- I want you to meet somebody.
This is Sonny Liston,
the next heavyweight champ
of the world.
Hey, Gino.
Come on, I'm starving over here.
- Ah, ladies first.
- Oh, finally. A gentleman.
You're a gentleman, Sonny.
I'll have the escargot, please.
- And I'll have
what the lady's having.
- Really? You like escargot?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, it's one of my favorites.
Why?
- You just didn't strike me
as a kind of guy
who likes to eat snails.
- Yeah.
And a whiskey please.
A double.
- A seven and seven too,
hey, Gino.
- So tell me, Sonny,
when you're in that ring
by yourself
and everybody's cheering you,
how good does that feel?
- Well, I can't tell you,
'cause most of the time,
I don't be the one
they're cheering for.
- See, Sonny's more like
the bad guy, huh?
- Just the way I like it.
- Caesar.
- Hey, Bobby Zazo.
- Farah, can I talk to you?
- Hey, there's
someone else here.
- Where's your manners?
- No.
- I don't mean to be rude.
I know who you are, Sonny.
Actually, I'm a fan,
and my family and I
were very interested
in managing your career,
but it seems Caesar here took
the flight out to St. Louis
before we did.
- That's something else
I stole from him, right?
You know what, Bobby?
I'll give you another chance
to win her back.
Me and Sonny are gonna go
talk business in the back,
but after that, give it a rest.
Sit over here.
Here you go, Zazo.
- I'll be right back, all right?
- Okay.
- Wow. What a mouth.
- Caesar, go.
- Farah, look...
- No, Bobby.
You look.
We had our thing.
- Our thing?
Is that what you call it?
Me taking a hooker
off the street,
making something out of her,
making her respectable,
seeing something in her
that these dumb fucks
couldn't see
even if they had
a magnifying glass?
That's what you call
"our thing"?
Cat got your tongue,
you ungrateful bitch?
- This conversation is over.
- Fifth and main.
Fifth and main is where
I found you giving blow jobs
for ten bucks a pop.
But you know what
I just figured out?
You're still a hooker.
You just charge more
for your blowjobs.
- I said,
this conversation's over.
- So I'm out, huh?
- Nah, she's yours for now,
until something better
comes along.
- So you admit I'm better,
huh, Bobby?
- Hey, Caesar.
When you gave her
that last kiss,
I was just wondering,
how does my dick taste?
- Son of a bitch!
-Hew no, no!
You two stop!
I'll bust y'all right up!
- You're fucking dead.
You hear me?
- Fricking jerk-off.
There's gonna be all kinds
of ramifications
'cause of this asshole.
You got a fight
to worry about, Sonny.
Come on.
You got to get out of here.
- You sure?
- I'm sure.
All right, honey.
Let's go.
- What, are you fucking stupid
or something?
- No.
- What do you think
we said to his request?
- What request?
- To have you whacked.
- You said no.
- What makes you think that?
- Because you're
pissed off at me.
Usually, when you want
to whack somebody,
you're like,
"hey, Caesar, how you doing?
"Caesar, you hungry?
"Want some breakfast, Caesar?
"Hey, oh, ham and eggs, sausage.
"Come on, Caesar,
"I got a couple of broads
down the street.
"Come on, me and you,
we're going to get laid
tonight."
Come on.
- This time, you're right.
But if you're gonna give
a guy a beating,
it's nobody's business.
But you don't hit him
over the head with a bottle.
Now, you're going to have
to give him ten grand.
- Ten grand? Are you kidding me?
All right, I mean...
- It's his request.
That's what you're going to do.
- All right,
I'll give it to him.
But I don't have it on hand.
I mean...
- Don't make an asshole
out of me.
I don't need a war.
Capisce?
- Capisce.
- Nico will be over later
to talk about Sonny.
- You hear?
- I hear.
- [speaks Italian]
- I know.
- Okay?
- Okay.
[Doorbell rings]
[Soft jazz music]
- Hey, Nico.
- Hey, beautiful.
- Come on in.
- Thank you.
How are you?
- Good.
- Caesar's just down
by the pool.
- All right.
- Can I get you a drink?
- Ah, no thanks, sweetheart.
- I'm not staying.
- Okay.
- I love what you've done
to the house.
- Caesar. What are you doing?
- Nice to see you, Nico.
- You too, darling.
- Ooh.
- I'll be right there, hon.
- That is a sweet girl
you got there.
- Yeah, she is.
What's this?
What do I owe this to?
Holy shit.
- Yeah, take it to Chicago
and bet on the fight.
- All of it?
- No, I brought all of it
so I could bet half.
Yes, all of it.
- Wow, you know,
good choice, Nico,
because Sonny's gonna tear
this guy apart.
- On Patterson.
- No, no. Trust me.
There's no way Sonny's
gonna lose against this guy.
- Not if you tell him
to take a dive.
- What?
- Yeah.
- Take a dive?
No. Can't do that.
- Caesar, listen to me.
Don't fuck this up.
- All right,
let me see what I can do.
- Now go get me Savino's
ten grand
so I can get out of here.
- [Sighs] Be right there, babe.
[Brakes squeal]
[Knock on door]
Sonny boy?
- I said leave me be.
- Sonny, you got a minute? Huh?
I need to ask you a favor.
- What?
- I wouldn't ask if it wasn't
absolutely necessary,
but it's not just me here.
- And what is it?
My mind got to be right
for this fight,
so you say what you got to say.
- I really need you
to win this one.
- Done. What else?
- Just win, that's it.
- done.
- All right.
- Catfish.
[Knock on door]
Who the hell is it now?
What you doing here?
- Well, I would not miss this
for the world, Sonny.
I mean, I know it's five minutes
before the fight.
I did call, and Geraldine
wanted me to surprise you.
[Chuckles]
- I don't know what to say.
- Well, then you don't say
anything.
Just go out there
and you take what is yours.
- Good luck.
- All right.
[Dramatic orchestral music]
[Crowd cheering]
- Whoa!
[Cheers and applause]
- Focus!
- All right.
[Cheers and applause]
- [Whistles]
- Boxers. Boxers.
You received your instruction
in the dressing room.
I want a clean bout.
Hands up at all times.
Touch gloves, and let's box.
- Well, good evening,
ladies and gentlemen.
I'm Jack Wells.
It's now time
for the main event,
the fight that we've all
been waiting for.
The challenger, Sonny Liston,
versus the heavyweight champion
of the world,
Floyd Patterson.
A lot of controversy's swirling
around this one, folks.
- This fight
better be good, man.
- Alleged ties to the mob.
The NAACP has even said
themselves
they would prefer Patterson
remain the champ.
The fight is about to begin.
- Here we go, boys!
Ding!
- Box!
- All right, Sonny!
Don't forget the legs!
Don't forget the legs, Sonny!
- Break it up. Break it up!
- He's dancing! He's dancing!
Cut off the ring!
- Keep dancing. Come on, baby.
Come on.
- To the body! To the body!
- Give it to him!
- Guys, come on. Break it up.
- Stop running, you fuck!
Excuse my French.
- He ain't got nothing on you,
Sonny.
[Crowd cheering]
- Yeah, baby. Come on.
- Beauty.
- That's it.
- Yeah!
- Oh, yeah! Yeah!
- One, two, three,
four, five, six...
- Seven, eight...
- Nine...
- Ten. Down!
[Crowd cheering]
- Sonny Liston is
the new heavyweight champion
of the world.
- They all said
he couldn't do it.
Everybody was against him,
but he proved them all wrong.
- I love you, Geraldine.
I love you.
- We love you, Sonny.
- We love you.
We love you, man.
- What are the chances
of a rematch?
- We'll have a rematch any time,
any place, right?
- That little piece of shit.
- You know how much money
you lost tonight, huh?
Do you know how much
fucking money you lost?
- He's going to step
into a fucking world
he didn't know existed.
- Sonny Liston, baby!
They said America
didn't love him,
but they do love him.
- Ain't nobody ever give me
a chance,
so I thank you.
- You the champion...
- You ever want a rematch,
you got it.
- Can we get a picture, Sonny?
- Sonny?
I want to be a good champion...
Somebody that people
could look up to.
Lord, if you let bygones
be bygones,
I'd be a champion
you'd be proud of too.
Amen.
All right.
Time to talk to the press.
[Laughter]
Let them meet the new champion
of the world.
- I like the sound
of that, baby.
Let's go.
Nobody out here.
- What you talking about,
catfish?
- I'm telling you,
ain't nobody out here, man.
- I'm the heavyweight champion
of the world.
[Soft dramatic music]
[Upbeat jazzy music]
♪ Sparks just fly ♪
♪ right out of the blue ♪
♪ there's no way I can't deny ♪
- Hey, Caesar.
- Hey, Nico.
What are you doing here?
- Savino said to pick you up.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Listen, I got some great news.
- Hey, hey,
how's the flight, huh?
- It was fantastic.
- Oh, good.
- Hungry or something?
- Want something to eat?
- Yeah, I'm hungry.
Why are you being so nice to me?
- What?
- We should call savino.
- Hey, Caesar. Let's go.
- Excuse me.
- Come on, get out of the way.
Vamoose.
[Phone rings]
- This should be over here.
Think.
- It's ringing. Just hold on.
[Phone rings]
Come on, answer.
- You hear a phone?
- Hey, hey, stop! Stop!
- I got to do everything.
- Get out!
- Hey!
He's going to—wait a minute.
Wait a minute.
- Hello?
- Hello. Savino.
Hey, it's me, Caesar.
Yeah, I know.
I should be dead right now,
right?
But listen, I didn't do it.
I didn't tell Sonny to take
the dive.
- Yeah, I noticed.
- But I didn't bet
on Patterson either.
- So what does that mean?
We didn't lose $100,000?
- No, we didn't lose it.
- I bet it all on Sonny.
The odds were crazy.
We made $1.2 million.
- You have more lives
than a cat.
- Yeah, so do you mind
saving your bullets
and calling your dogs off of me?
Please?
- Put him on the phone.
- All right.
- He wants to talk to you.
- Oh, yeah?
- Yeah.
- Hey, what's up?
- [Speaks Italian]
Capisce?
- You sure?
- What do you mean "you sure"?
- All right.
Yeah, bye.
- You were going to really
kill me?
- What am I supposed to do, huh?
What do you want from me?
- What do I want from you?
Taxi!
- Do you want to ride with me?
- Huh?
- Yeah.
- [Laughing]
[Slow bluesy music]
- Sonny Liston, the champ.
Hey.
- Hey.
- You're in the newspaper today.
- Well, I'm the champ.
- Think I can get an autograph?
For my kids?
- Sure.
- Yeah, their names are Richard
and Sarah.
[Laughs]
See?
I told you he's a dumb nigger.
See, Sonny?
It says here that niggers
don't even like you.
- You know,
you're a goddamn disgrace
to the sport of boxing.
- You're a goddamn disgrace
to assholes.
- Put your hands
behind your back.
- Yeah, what for?
- Driving while intoxicated.
- Well, wouldn't I have to have
something to do with driving?
- You was about to.
- Well, your daddy was
about to sleep with a woman,
but instead he slept
with a female dog.
- That's it.
- Take one more step,
and I'll blow your face
clean off!
Don't!
Smack!
- That'll do.
You can take them cuffs off him
and the gag.
- Ah!
[Coughs]
- You enjoy beating up cops?
You'd already be dead
if not for your celebrity.
So this is your first
and last warning.
Get out of my town,
or I'm gonna kill you.
- [Coughs]
- Sonny.
Shit. You all right?
Those bastards fucked you up?
Come on.
I just gave them a ton of money.
Those pricks.
Get up, big guy.
- I ain't do nothing this time.
- I know.
You and Geraldine
go some place where
they're going to treat you
like a human being.
Come on, champ.
[Birds chirping]
- So how you like it?
- I like it,
but I'm not going
to get used to it.
Lord knows we don't stay
anywhere for very long.
- Oh, I guess
that's my fault, huh?
- No.
I'm the one who keeps on
beating up the police.
- Look, well, Gerry,
what the hell
was I supposed to do?
- I don't know, Sonny.
But you can't keep
beating up everybody.
Save it for the ring.
- Okay, well, next time,
I'll just make sure
to lay down and die.
- They are scared of you.
Now, that might be good
for the ring,
but in the real world,
you're just
a big, black, angry man,
and they're scared of you,
and if you don't control
that temper of yours,
one day, somebody who fears you
is gonna kill you.
[Jazzy piano music]
[Applause]
- Patterson's camp
keeps calling me.
They want a rematch,
but the money's got to be right.
How long do you think
it'll take you to get ready?
- About a hour.
- About an hour.
All right, tough guy.
- Ah, you have a phone call.
- All right, I got to take
this phone call.
Don't go anywhere.
- My usual.
-So...
How does it feel
to be the champ?
- It feel all right.
Ah, Caesar over there.
- I know. I see him.
So, Sonny, how's your wife?
- What?
- How's your wife?
- Why are you worried
about my wife?
- I'm not worried.
- I'm just asking; That's all.
- Yeah, well, my wife is fine.
Look, farah.
Caesar care a lot about you,
and a woman like you
could have any man she want.
- Are you making a pass at me?
- What?
- I'm just kidding.
- [Laughs]
Yeah.
- My set's up.
I have to go sing.
You going to be all right here
by yourself?
- Yeah.
Yeah, I'll be all right.
- Good.
- Excuse me, Mr. Liston.
- Good news, champ.
- Excuse me, Mr. Liston?
One picture.
- They want the rematch
in about eight months.
That work for you?
- Yeah, it works for me.
- Works for you. Works for me.
It works for everybody.
All right.
Sweet music.
Give me your best bottle
of bubbly, would you?
[Shutter clicks]
You think you're macho.
You think you're the man, right?
You ain't shit, man.
- You should have let me drive.
- Let you drive? No way.
- Because you can't hold
your liquor
- it's your first week in Vegas.
Come here!
Big, big fucking...
Get over there!
[Laughing]
- What do we have here?
- Take care of my boy.
- Who do you two think you are,
Davis and Sinatra?
- That's right. I'm Sammy Davis.
- Yeah, well, then I guess
I must be old blue eyes.
- [Laughs]
- Yeah. Would you look at her?
She's beautiful.
- Yeah, she is.
- If the champ thinks
you're beautiful,
then that's all she wrote.
I could have loved you
in another lifetime.
[Laughs]
You see, well, she been
around the block a few times.
She's beautiful, but, you know,
I mean, I ain't the first guy...
- He's drunk.
- That Bobby Zazo,
piece of shit,
I mean, come on, honey.
Ain't I good enough for you?
- Come on, man. You're drunk.
- Yeah, I know. Come on.
- I don't understand how you...
Blow jobs?
Bobby Zazo?
Piece of shit.
- Here you go, champ.
- Thank you.
- Farah.
- Yeah?
- You know he ain't mean
no harm.
- Yeah, not everyone
can be like you, champ,
but it's nice to know
that you think I'm beautiful.
- Come on, babe!
Hurry up!
- Have a good night.
- The heavyweight champion,
Sonny Liston,
is a man who won that title
last September
at Comiskey park, Chicago,
in two minutes and six seconds.
- What do you think's gonna
happen this time, Caesar?
- Same thing that happened
last time, pal.
- All right, gentlemen.
I want to have
a nice, clean fight,
watch below the belt.
You listen to my instructions
at all times.
Touch gloves.
[Dramatic music]
- Patterson trying
to get underneath
the champion's great punches.
Runs into a right uppercut,
which sets up the challenger.
- [Laughs]
- Come on! Come on!
- In your corner.
You all right?
- Yeah!
- Box!
- Ooh!
[Cheers]
- The challenger's long
right hand
grazes the champion's chin,
and Liston's countering
left hook is on target
and sets up the second
knockdown.
- In your corner, Sonny.
- Whoa!
- One, two, three, four,
five, six...
- Out!
- Eight!
Good to go?
- Come on! Come on!
Oh!
[People booing]
[People cheering]
- Okay. We'll see.
I'll talk to him.
- How you doing, farah?
Where's Caesar?
He left a message at the gym
for me to meet him here.
- I left that message for you.
- Oh, not that I mind,
but why'd you really
call me here?
- I don't know what I thought.
You're right.
♪ They say there's a time ♪
♪ when your heart will stop
singing the blues ♪
♪ but I think it's a lie ♪
♪ because I don't see the day ♪
♪ that I will stop missing you ♪
♪ they say there's a day ♪
♪ when your love begins
fading away ♪
♪ but the love that I feel ♪
♪ just turns into tears ♪
♪ 'cause I can't get over you ♪
♪ Oh, darling ♪
♪ I love you in the morning ♪
♪ I love you in the afternoon ♪
- Shh...
♪ Whoa-oh, whoa-oh, whoa ♪
♪ darling ♪
- Bunch of hos.
They're going to score
some shit.
Who are these bitches?
Who is this guy?
- Why are we sitting here?
- Bobby Zazo.
- What about him?
- He's been telling people
around town
the fights are fixed.
- Why would he do that?
- Fuck do I know?
It's just bad for business.
Farah's been acting strange.
I think he's fucking her again.
Something isn't right.
All I know is,
the family had a meeting,
and a decision was made.
- Look... whoaw. Whoaw.
A decision was made?
- Yeah.
- Well, what we about to do?
- Oh, calm down.
- If I kill somebody,
it got to be for my own reason.
- I don't want you
to kill anybody.
Just put a fucking scare
into him.
He's got a big mouth.
- What you need me for?
- Well, who's scarier than you,
Sonny?
That him?
Here we go. Come on.
Let's go.
Hey, douche bag!
- What the fuck do you want?
- Let's take a ride.
- I ain't got time
to go back and forth with you
over some dame.
- This ain't about a dame
this time, Bobby.
You got a big fucking mouth,
and I told you,
it was only a matter of time
before it caught up with you.
- Fuck you.
- I ain't going nowhere.
- You hear that? Fuck me?
You hear the way
he talks to me, Sonny,
this piece of shit?
- Do you mean to tell me
you cocksuckers
got the heavyweight champion
in the world
out here doing muscle work?
What a fucking lack of respect
for that man.
I don't know, champ.
Maybe getting with these guys
wasn't such a good idea.
My family would have never
done this to you.
The truth is,
I've been saying some things
I shouldn't have been saying,
but we all get a bit drunker
than we should sometimes,
but for them to send me
this fucking prick?
A slap in the face
is what that is.
- I got your prick right here.
It was nice seeing you
for the last time,
you big-headed fucking moose.
- Fuck you!
- Yeah!
- Cocksucking motherfucker.
- I heard it was about that big.
- Caesar, you something else.
- Come on, Sonny.
- No, no, no, no.
Come on, stop now. Stop.
Come on now. Stop.
Stop.
- Feed me a fry.
- [Chuckles]
Hey, baby, I don't know
what you think this is,
but I ain't the type of man
that's gonna be feeding you.
I ain't bringing you roses
or hugging you
under the full moon.
So why don't you just sit
on that bed,
watch some TV or something,
let me finish my sandwich?
Then we're going to do
what we came here to do.
That's all.
- You think I'm just here
because I want
some big black stud?
- [Chuckles]
Girl...
- Is that why you're here?
Is that is? What?
To take out on me
everything the white man
has ever done to you?
- Oh, yeah, the white man.
- Yeah, everything the reporters
say about you.
Is that it?
Because it's not because
you're not the type of man
that does those sweet things.
You just don't want to do them
with me.
Geraldine...
- I told you to keep my wife's
name out your mouth, didn't I?
- Okay—
- didn't I tell you that?
- Okay, great, Sonny. Why?
Now are you going to hit me?
Because that'll really be
sticking it to the white folk,
if you hit me and fuck me.
Wait.
No, no.
No, I’m...
I'm sorry.
- You better get out of my way.
- I didn't mean it, Sonny.
- I'm out of here.
- Please.
I get to see you once a week.
- Oh, that's it, huh?
You're going to miss
your once-a-week fuck, huh?
- No, that's not it.
That's not what I meant.
- That's all I'm good for, huh?
- Sonny.
- Your once-a-week fuck?
- Sonny, come on.
- Hmm?
- Sonny...
- Ah!
- Sonny. Ah!
- That's all I'm good for?
Go ahead and look me in the eye
and say I'm just good
for your once-a-week fuck.
- What I meant...
- What did you mean?
What did you mean?
- Don't be like this.
- No, you tell me.
Tell me.
What the fuck did you mean?
- Huh?
- Sonny.
Come on.
- What the fuck did you mean?
- Come on.
Come on.
[Cheers and applause]
- All set now.
World heavyweight boxing title
on the line.
31-year—old Sonny Liston,
22-year-old cassias Clay;
Sonny the champion,
cassias the challenger.
Sonny 218, cassias 210 1/2...
A 7 1/2 pound weight pool.
Referee:
The capable Barney Felix.
Brought to you by
theater network television.
- All right, Sonny, cassias,
you both know the rules,
so let's have
a good, clean fight.
Protect yourself at all times.
Good luck to the both of you.
Touch gloves.
Okay.
Let's do it.
- Sonny is feeling out
cassias Clay.
Clay is dancing and taunting
the powerful Liston,
pawing at him
with that strong left jab.
But this youngster
has his own style,
and it's confusing
for the champion to fathom
this early in the fight,
at least up to now.
Sonny Liston may have
his hands full tonight.
[Crowd cheering]
[Dramatic music]
- Cassius Clay on the move,
as we see,
looking to get Sonny to lunge,
with both hands high,
mocking the champion.
In close range,
if you look closely...
Although Barney Felix does
want them apart at this point,
because their hands were tied...
Sonny will be the guy
that will keep mauling away.
I'd like to point out
that the champion is strong,
durable, takes the good shot.
However, he is being
out-maneuvered at most points,
because this fellow has
that awkwardly fast style
of going side to side,
moving the upper part
of his body.
Ding!
- Sonny, you got this.
- Do it.
- What are you talking about,
man?
- Do it.
Ding!
- Time.
Let's go.
- Come on, Sonny! Come on!
- It looks like his eyes...
His eyes are bothering him.
Ladies and gentlemen,
something got in his right eye.
However he's blinking badly.
Sonny's gonna try
to take advantage of this,
but there's not enough time.
End of round.
- Come on, now.
- Big right hand to the body.
Clay, with a variety of punches...
Startling combinations.
Putting punches together,
that's his strong point.
Ladies and gentlemen,
what do you think is going on
in Liston's mind right now?
I'll tell you what
he's thinking.
He's thinking he's
underestimated this challenger.
He's quicker than he thought,
and more resilient
than he first believed.
There goes another one.
Sonny wobbles.
Cassius has him hurt.
Sonny is in trouble.
He's in trouble.
Clay is punishing him.
This young fighter
is showing a lot of heart.
- Look, we still got this, man.
You can't stand there.
You got to move, man.
You got to move.
Come on, man.
When you bring your head down,
you bring it to him.
You cannot stay in one place.
- Oh, shut up!
- Sonny...
- Shut up!
It's over.
- What are you talking about?
- That's it.
Tell 'em my shoulder.
- What's the matter?
- His shoulder.
- What?
- Right shoulder.
His shoulder, man.
- That's it. The fight's over.
- They might be stopping it.
That might be all.
Ladies and gentlemen,
it appears they're stopping
the fight.
They are stopping the fight.
Something about
Liston's shoulder.
Liston's shoulder went out.
He could not continue.
Winner by a TKO
in the seventh round:
Cassias Clay.
Cassius Clay celebrates
his victory,
goes into the record book
with corbett, Tunney,
and Braddock
as another who brought off
one of the great upsets
in heavyweight history.
- Why did you do it?
- "I am the greatest."
- Huh?
It's just us in here, Sonny.
Why did you do it, man?
- Because I'm ignorant.
That's what you want to do, huh?
You will my nature rise.
Mm-hmm.
-
- [Sighs]
- What are you going to do?
- Leave.
- Gerry,
put away the gun
before somebody get hurt.
- Before somebody get hurt?
It's too late.
Somebody already got hurt.
- She don't mean nothing to me.
- Well, you sure
mean something to her,
'cause she was ready
to stand here
and take a bullet with you.
Sonny, you know you famous now.
You can't just walk
into the same hotel
every week at the same time
and not be spotted.
Now, the papers don't know
who that white woman is,
but they know who you are,
and if you could read,
you'd probably know this.
Do you love her?
- Gerry, I told you...
- You think I give a shit
about what you done told me?
Do you love her?
- I love you.
- Well, you got a funny way
of showing it.
Well, here's what
you're gonna do.
You're gonna go find that lady
and you're going to tell her
that it's over,
and you are never, ever
going to see her again.
Um, you know what else?
You should have been training
instead of fucking.
I hope cassias Clay
whips your ass
again.
[Birds chirping]
- [Exhales]
- I just saw her leave.
How did she find out?
- It don't matter.
It's over.
- No.
We just have to be more careful.
- No, farah, we're over.
- Come on.
Sonny, please.
Sonny, look at me.
Look at me.
[Shutters clicking]
- All right, let's let him
get back to work now.
Thank you very much.
Okay, you got your picture.
Get back to work.
Sonny, I don't think
they're going to leave
unless you speak
to at least one of them.
- I don't give a fuck.
I tried answering
their damn questions anyway.
- Sonny, you got any comment
on the mobster
they found shot to death
in the desert, Bobby Zazo?
You and Caesar novak
knew this guy, right?
Was he with your family, Sonny?
- All right, that's enough.
- Come on.
- Did you know him well, Sonny?
How about I throw you a banana,
Sonny?
You talk to us then?
- What, motherfucker?
I'm gonna fucking...
- Oh-ho-ho-ho!
[Indistinct shouting]
- I'm gonna fuck you up,
motherfucker!
- You're an animal!
- Motherfuckers!
Everybody out!
- Sonny.
Sonny!
Sonny.
- I tried with these people.
- I know.
- But they just hate me.
From the day I was born,
even my daddy hate me.
What is it about me
that people hate so much?
Clay, with his big mouth
and people wanted me
to shut him up.
For the first time in my life,
people were on my side.
They looked at my different.
They looked at me like a man.
- Yeah.
- I liked it.
But then when it didn't turn out
the way they wanted,
then just straight back
to nigger-ville.
- I don't know why you listen
to them.
When they can't find goodness
in themselves,
I don't know how
they're gonna find it in you.
You can't look to them
for your validation.
for your love,
because they will let you down
every single time.
You're a remarkable man, Sonny.
I don't know how else you did
all those things.
You went from being
a prison inmate
to the heavyweight champion
of the world,
and I don't know why that
doesn't mean anything to you.
Don't let people tell you
who you are.
Don't let them make you
into something you are not.
- Good evening.
From the central Maine
youth center in lewiston, Maine,
tonight we have
the long-awaited rematch.
15 rounds of boxing
for the heavyweight championship
of the world.
- Sonny boy.
This is your night, baby.
Can you feel it?
- Yeah.
- Everybody we know
is out there,
from Hollywood to hoboken,
and the odds are in your favor.
Bust him up.
- Oh, I'm gonna do that.
- Huh!
[Crowd cheering]
- Here we go.
The world's heavyweight title.
The big fight. The big night.
Unusual locale: Lewiston, Maine.
Round number one.
Sonny Liston in the dark trunks
is chasing that man
straightaway.
Is that a mistake?
- Get out the box. Come on, now.
Come on.
You got to throw something now.
You got to throw something.
- Beautiful right-hand shot
that we saw.
It was the best punch thus far,
landed by the champion.
Halfway through
this first round,
and Sonny
has been shooting mostly...
Although he's going
to the head now...
Mostly toward that body.
You know the old story:
You kill the body,
and the head might follow.
Knockdown, ladies and gentlemen,
on a right-hand shot.
The right-hand shot on the chin.
[Low humming music]
- Come on, baby! Sonny, no!
- The right-hand shot
on the chin...
- You got to get up!
- Sonny, come on!
Come on!
- Come on.
- Three...
- He's good, man.
He's good.
- Ref!
Get down!
He's been down longer
than ten seconds.
Ref!
- That's it!
The time is over.
[People shouting]
- What, are you
out of your mind?
- What's going on?
- The question is,
did he even hit him?
If he did, it was too fast
for my eyes to see.
This is a sad day for boxing.
The crowd is yelling "fixed"
at the top of their lungs.
You can hear them
in the background.
Odds on Sonny tonight,
and now this.
This kind of thing is what
gives boxing a black eye,
but tonight Sonny Liston
went one step further.
He kicked dirt in the face
of the sport.
At one time,
a little over a year ago,
he was considered unbeatable,
unstoppable.
Now he has stopped himself
for the second time.
Was the fix in?
There's only one man
in this arena
who can answer that question,
and Sonny Liston
has a lot to answer for.
Who loses the most?
Tonight, Sonny Liston.
- Who did he
throw the fight for?
- I don't know.
I don't know.
I don't know
what the fuck happened.
I don't think Sonny
would do that.
- The blow barely tapped him.
I mean, I've watched this guy
take monstrous blows, Caesar.
- Somebody's gonna
have to talk to him.
[Soft piano music]
♪ The man that I love ♪
♪ nobody knew ♪
♪ the man that I love ♪
♪ friends would say ♪
♪ he's no good for you ♪
♪ he's no good ♪
♪ he'll only make you blue ♪
- How's it going?
- Bad.
- Did you throw the fight,
Sonny?
- [Scoffs]
Who's asking?
- I'm fucking asking.
What's the difference?
- If it's savino and Nico,
then it makes sense.
If it's you,
we got a problem.
- Why do we got a problem?
- Because you should know
better.
- Goddamn it, that punch
barely touched you, Sonny.
- Oh, you were in the ring, huh?
- Hi, Sonny.
- How you doing, farah?
- Caesar, would you mind
if we leave a little early?
I'm not feeling very well.
- Yeah, farah, I would mind.
You see, I'm sitting here
talking business with Sonny.
I didn't get you this gig so you
can go home early every night.
That's the third time this week,
for Christ's sakes.
We'll leave when I'm done.
All right?
- I ain't never thrown a fight
in my life.
Never
do you believe me?
Do you believe me?
- Yeah,
because I'm a fucking idiot
that'll believe
anything you say.
- So what now?
- You should go home.
Let me talk to these guys.
I'll be by later.
Or they will.
♪ Oh, the man ♪
♪ the man, the man ♪
♪ that I love ♪
♪ nobody knew ♪
[Applause]
- I told you to go out
till I call you
and tell you everything's okay.
[Knock on door]
Go to the room.
- No, Sonny...
- Go the room.
[Pounding on door]
- Hey, Sonny.
- So what happened?
- I put my ass on the line
for you.
I told them that you've never
thrown a fight in your life.
- Well, good. That's the truth.
- Yeah, but if they find out
something different happened,
it'd be bad for you and me.
- Well, they won't find out,
because that's the truth.
- I hope not.
I also said that
you would come up in the ranks
and be a champ again.
- I will..
- I know.
Listen, I got to go home.
Farah's waiting for me.
Just be careful.
[Upbeat blues music]
[Crowd cheering]
- Pasquale.
Over there, you see that?
What is that?
It looks loose to me.
- Hey.
There he is.
- [Laughs]
- Check that out.
- Oh.
- Look at him.
- Fantastic.
- Merry Christmas.
- Oh.
Buon Natale.
- Thanks.
You know, this is a good thing.
You know why?
- Why?
- Because it shows people,
even though they make a mistake,
they can get back on
the straight and narrow
and do the right thing
and can still work
themselves up.
- Thank you.
- Which brings us
to our next thing.
- What's that?
- We need Sonny
to take some dives.
- Are you sure there's...
There ain't another way?
- No.
- Well, what if he won't do it?
- He's got to do it.
- Okay.
All right.
See you later.
- Come on. Come on.
[Speaks Italian]
- Hey, Caesar.
Hey, Caesar.
- Yeah, what is it?
- One another thing.
Today me and the fellas,
we were doing my collections,
right?
While we were collecting
from that place
called hillcrest motel
over on fifth.
- Yeah?
- Anyway, we're sitting around,
we're talking about boxing,
all of a sudden this guy,
he says to me
that your boy Sonny used to come
there with some dame every week.
- So what?
- He says it was that singer
from the pink dragon.
- I knew about that.
- You did?
- Yeah, I knew all about it.
I passed her to Sonny.
Bobby Zazo gave her to me.
I gave her to Sonny.
- You did?
- That's right.
- Oh, good. Good.
No, I...
See, I...
I understand now. I understand.
- You understand?
- Yeah.
- It's all good.
- But a nigger? Huh? '
- hey, who gives a shit, right?
Who cares?
- All right.
[Dramatic music]
[Door opens]
Is that you?
- Yeah.
- I'm in here.
- What's going on?
What did you do to my clothes?
- I heard black
is your favorite color.
Is that true?
- I don't understand.
- Don't act surprised.
- What are you talking about,
Caesar?
- You're fucking Sonny.
Right?
You're fucking him, right?
Don't lie to me, bitch.
I trusted your ass.
Why'd you do that?
Huh?
Huh? Why'd you do it?
Get over here,
you fucking bitch.
How could you do this to me?
Why?
- Please stop it. Please.
- Doing what?
That fucking—
! Gave you everything.
- Caesar.
- Why did you humiliate me
like that?
- Stop it!
- You know, you're a whore;
I'll treat you like one.
I'll fucking treat you like one.
That's what this is about.
- Ah, Caesar!
Stop it!
- Come on. Come on, baby.
I can— I can do this!
I can do it.
You like that?
You like that, huh?
- Oh, yes.
- I don't ever want
to see you again.
Ever
get your shit.
Get the fuck out of here.
- [Cries]
Why?
- With your right.
Come on. There you go.
Hold on. Hold on, champ.
- Hey.
What's up?
- I've been calling you.
What's wrong?
- Nothing. How you doing?
- Good.
- How's Geraldine?
- She fine.
Sent her to see her mama
for the holiday.
- Oh, yeah? That's good.
Listen, the bosses, they wanted
me to ask you something.
- What's that?
- They wanted to know,
did you have a good Christmas?
- [Chuckles]
Yeah.
- I'll let 'em know
what you said.
- So you came all the way
down here to ask me that?
- Well, you know how they are.
When they want to know
something,
they want to know right away.
All right?
Finish your work.
Hey.
He said no.
[Soft music]
- Look, farah.
I don't know if it's a good idea
for you to come around here.
- Don't worry, then.
- I'm just passing through.
I just wanted to make sure
that you were okay
and to say thank you.
- Thank you?
For what?
For making your life crazy?
- You still don't get it,
do you?
Take care of yourself.
- Sonny, I'm home.
My flight was delayed.
Sonny, what are you doing
laying down here right now?
Sonny?
Sonny.
What...
What's been going on?
What is all this stuff?
Sonny?
[Low humming music]
[Crying]
Sonny.
[Shutter clicks]
[Somber jazz music]