Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
♪ Hey, tell me ♪
♪ Need did you turn out
to the girl of my dreams ♪
♪ My dreams ♪
♪ In my own little
world, own little world ♪
♪ Hey, baby ♪
♪ I hope that you learn
to love and feel me ♪
♪ Feel me ♪
♪ Hey, hey, you're sexy ♪
♪ Hey, hey, you're fancy ♪
♪ Hey, hey, you're classy
and I want everybody else ♪
♪ Settle down, settle down, baby ♪
♪ Sophisticated and I want you around me ♪
♪ So, girl don't be stalling ♪
♪ I want your loving now ♪
♪ Ain't no dine and dash over here ♪
♪ I got paper to spend on you ♪
♪ It don't matter what day ♪
♪ It don't matter the time ♪
♪ Trust me lady I got plans ♪
♪ Baby we gonna make it last ♪
♪ All in my, all in my ♪
[Tony] Yes, yes.
You're listening to
Atlanta station's, IYF 89.5
I got one at home that I know loves me.
[laughs]
You know that's right.
My time's almost up, folks.
And we'll be letting DJ Hershey take over.
He'll be waking you up
with everything you need
and a little bit more.
I'm gonna wrap this thing
out with my theme song,
"Last Night a D.J. Saved my Life".
Watch out for those energy vampires.
You know hurt people, hurt people.
It's your lover boy, Tony
Sinclair signing out.
You're listening to IYF 89.5.
[laughing]
I listened to you on the way in.
Hot.
Oh, thanks man.
Glad you liked it.
Liked it?
I loved it.
Tony, you really got a hang of this.
I wish my paycheck reflect that.
I want that stupid bread,
like G Smooth over at BBX 105.
Your time will come.
Just keep doin' what you're doin'.
He didn't get to where he was overnight.
I know.
Hell, been at this hole in
the wall station for 10 years,
and I still ain't got my big break.
10 years.
[chuckles]
Yeah.
Well, you have a good show, man.
[hands clap]
All right, got everything.
Stay up.
[birds chirping]
[smooth music]
[car alarm beeping]
♪ Niggers I can't trust ♪
♪ 'Cause they hoes ♪
♪ They be super sus ♪
♪ Hoppin' off the bus ♪
♪ To pull up just to get a nut ♪
♪ God, they give me hate ♪
♪ Fuck that hate ♪
♪ I need a new estate ♪
♪ Hoppin' off the porch ♪
♪ To a Porsche ♪
♪ Bitch, I moved away ♪
♪ I ain't got no patience ♪
♪ I can't wait ♪
♪ Bitch, I need a state ♪
♪ Fuckin' up the game ♪
♪ This free game ♪
♪ Bitch, you need to pay ♪
♪ Yeah, I'll make 'em pay ♪
♪ Bitch, you strange ♪
♪ Yeah, you went away ♪
♪ Fuckin' on her nigger 'cause she lame ♪
♪ And he got a raise ♪
Hey, baby.
You're late.
Late?
What are you talking about?
I came straight home after the station.
Can I get a kiss now that you got rid
of that morning breath?
[lips smack]
Apparently you didn't get
rid of that late night breath.
Look, I need to talk
to you about something.
What?
This shift of yours.
Like, the only time I
get a chance to see you
is when I'm leaving from work,
and when your ass is
getting home from work.
So you know what?
I don't think this is going to work.
Plus, I need you to
start bringing more money
into this crib.
Look, Christine don't start.
I just got in, damn.
Oh really?
Well, these didn't.
What?
What's this?
Let's see, we have the electric bill.
We have the cable bill.
And we have the gas bill.
Gas bill?
This is a totally electric apartment.
You get my point.
Look, I don't know why you tripping.
I'm out here hustling.
I got a job interview tomorrow.
Where?
BBX 105.
[Christine scoffs]
Yeah, that's right.
We gonna be trading that
hooptie for a Benz real soon.
So I don't know why, what's your problem?
If I have to tell you,
then don't worry about it.
What?
[door slams shut]
Really?
♪ Girl, you been actin' so different ♪
♪ You've been kinda distant ♪
♪ I don't really get it ♪
♪ One minute you love me
the next one you livid ♪
♪ I know you been ♪
♪ I know you been sippin' ♪
♪ Yeah you mixing emotions ♪
♪ Dipping up on it since
when do you roll it ♪
♪ Girl you can fly, but
lately you just floatin' ♪
♪ Don't know where you goin' ♪
♪ But I know, baby, I know ♪
♪ I know exactly how it feels to ♪
♪ Let somebody see the real you ♪
♪ Just so they can say they feel you ♪
♪ Knowing damn well you're
trying to find yourself ♪
♪ Girl I know you wouldn't
mind the help so ♪
♪ Been kinda rude ♪
♪ All that attitude ♪
♪ Got you thinking you run shit ♪
♪ I promise you I'm the kinda dude ♪
♪ That won't leave you for nothin' so ♪
♪ Girl if you stressin', just let it out ♪
♪ Don't wanna increase
it, just press it out ♪
♪ Everything you do is impressive ♪
♪ Just need you to get
it together now so ♪
♪ I know you been lost in the world but ♪
♪ Maybe we can find something different ♪
♪ Find something different yeah ♪
♪ Maybe we can find some ♪
[Homeless Man] Hey
hey, hey hey, hey hey.
How y'all doing ladies?
Hey, bro.
Hey man. How you doing, brother?
Good, man.
How you doing?
I'm great, man.
You look like one of
them DJs up there, man.
Nah, but I wish.
Hey man, listen.
Let me hold somethin'.
That's what I'm talkin' 'bout.
That's what I'm talkin' about.
Oh, 20 square!
Man, you want the rest of my orange?
Nah, man.
It's cool.
Man, listen, man.
You made my day, brother.
Listen.
I can tell right now you somebody.
You hear me?
You somebody.
Don't ever forget that.
All right.
Hey, man.
Get your damn head up.
[calm music]
Oh, damn.
Joe G. Smooth, much respect.
You a legend, brother.
Hey.
What's good, man?
How you doing?
Good, man.
I'm Tony Sinclair from 89.5.
Oh.
Okay, cool, cool.
That's what's up.
Yeah.
I just dropped off my air
check to your program director.
Good luck with that, man.
I would love it, if you
check it out, you know.
[elevator dings]
I'd love to work here.
You said you dropped it off to my PD?
[messenger dings]
Yeah, yeah yeah.
Greg Harris.
Okay, man.
Good luck with that.
[light hearted music]
[alarm ringing]
[kiss smacks]
What are you doing?
Come on, I'm about to go to work.
Man, get off me.
[Tony] Come on, baby.
Tony, I am trying to sleep.
Move.
Damn.
♪ Yeah yeah yeah yeah ♪
♪ Girl you giving me the blues ♪
[Christine] Turn that light out.
You're listening to the quiet storm.
I'm your main man, Tony Sinclair.
Let's take another call.
[Caller] Yo, finally I got through.
Tony, I'm trying to get
tickets to the concert, man.
What's up?
What's happening?
Not yet.
Try back later.
Next caller, you're on the air.
Talk to me.
[Caller] Hey, Tony. Yeah.
All them slow jams is cool.
But how about some Li'l Boostie, baby?
Yeah.
You heard me?
This ain't the trap hour, baby.
You're listening to the quiet storm.
You heard me?
[laughing]
Next caller.
What's on your mind?
Hi Tony.
Am I on the air?
Yes, love.
What's your question?
Well, I've been in a relationship
with this guy for quite some time.
And it just doesn't
seem to be working out.
What do you mean?
Well, it just doesn't seem
like we're on the same page.
Sometimes he really scares me.
Should I stay in this
relationship or move on?
When he touches me, I don't feel safe.
Love should make you feel safe.
If you feel that way, then
maybe it's time to move on.
[Robin] You think so?
I know so.
Thank you, Tony.
Just hang in there,
love. It'll be all right.
You're on the air with Tony Sinclair.
What can I do for you?
[Christine] Tony, it's Christine.
You mean my Christine?
[Christine] Yes.
Oh. Hey y'all, it's the love of my life.
My baby Christine, calling
to give me a shout out.
What's up, baby?
[Christine] Well you know,
you told that last caller
that she needs to move on?
[Tony] Yeah.
Well, I'm getting ready
to do the very same thing, boo boo.
It's done.
What?
Baby, stop playing.
Look, I'm gone.
[dog whining]
[dramatic music]
♪ Tell me the truth ♪
♪ Before I give my barbecue to you ♪
♪ Oh tell me the truth ♪
That's not how the song goes, pop.
You want some meat?
No, I'm good.
Man, it's your favorite.
You want any?
Nah.
I know you ain't all in your feelin' bad
with girl on the radio last night, huh?
All the barbecue in Atlanta,
and you in a love zone
about that little girl?
I ain't never like her, no.
Man, look here.
Don't you realize you Louis
Eugene Sinclair's grandson.
Huh?
Well then say it.
I'm Louis Eugene Sinclair's grandson.
Act like it, then, huh?
Okay?
[speaking in foreign language]
Y'all light skin people something else.
Man, cut that out.
Quit babying the boy.
James, please.
I knew I should've sent
your butt to Southern.
- You want some toast?
- Instead of Morehouse.
No.
You sure?
No. I'm good.
Let me get something for you.
[cell phone buzzing]
Wait a minute.
What's on the phone?
I know that isn't your little girl.
Nah, I just have stuff to do.
Look here, I need to talk to you.
I need-
- Okay, honey.
Love you.
Love you too.
Be good, okay?
I need to talk to you, man.
I need to talk to you, come on.
- What is it?
- I need to talk to you.
Look it, man.
Before you leave, let me talk to you.
Let me talk to you.
What's up, pop?
I need some gas money.
I got you.
That's all you got?
Come on, man.
[laughing]
What?
What are you doing?
You do this every time
I come over here, pop.
Don't worry about it, son.
That's all right.
Love you.
Man, you crazy.
Cool crazy.
I'll see you later, man.
All right.
Hey.
Don't call that girl.
- [Tony] I won't.
- What I say?
All right, man. [speaking
in foreign language]
You sure he my son?
Please, James. [speaking
in foreign language]
I'm just playing, girl.
Come on back, come on back.
I'm just playing.
You mad?
Come on, I'm just playing.
♪ This story about a young
and trying to get it ♪
♪ Trying to get it ♪
♪ My daddy told me boy ♪
You're Tony Sinclair?
Yeah.
I follow you on Instagram.
There's no charge.
Oh my God, it's Tony Sinclair.
What the heck?
Oh my God, oh my God!
[camera shutter clicking]
Oh my God, oh my God.
[Tony] Caller, you're on the air.
[Caller] Tony the Tiger.
Everybody's talking about this breakup.
You need some rebound sex.
My friend Champagne says she's down.
What's up?
[chuckles] I really
appreciate that, but,
right now is not the time.
Man, Tony.
Tell people to contact you directly.
Servers are crashing.
That's your job.
[cell phone buzzing]
Hello?
Greg Harris?
From BBX?
My man, Tony Sinclair.
What's good with you, man?
Good to see you again.
Oh, it's good to be seen.
Hey man, you blowing up.
You being seen by a lot.
What are you at, like five
million followers now?
Something like that.
Geez, man.
Hey, listen.
We need you.
Hey, G Smooth, I just
wanna say thank you.
Thanks for the opportunity.
I put in a lot of hard work to get here,
so I'm ready to rock.
That's what it takes, man.
No problem, man
Man.
This my crew?
Hey.
We fixing to make magic.
Let's get to it.
Thanks man.
I'm gonna look around, okay?
Hey, be my guest.
What's up, y'all?
- Hey.
- I'm Tony Sinclair.
- How you doing?
- Nice to meet.
[calm music]
[Bouncer] Whoa, whoa whoa.
What?
Just got to wait in line.
We'll get you in, okay?
- Line?
- Yeah.
We have to wait in this line?
Yeah.
Wait.
Hold on, I know you from somewhere.
[Bouncer] A lot of people
know me, sweetie. Okay?
Whoa.
All right, everybody clear this space.
Wait, no you ain't gotta
put your hands on me
like that though, right?
[Man] Hey, that's Tony Sinclair.
[Crowd] Tony! Tony!
[all talking at once]
Isn't that Tony Sinclair from BBX 105?
Yeah.
Didn't you used to go with him?
I mean, we hooked up a little, but.
Don't even be like that.
You know you messed that up.
Bad.
Whoa, whoa.
Hold up.
You're Tony Sinclair's ex?
The one that dumped him on the radio?
Oh no, you can't come in here.
- No, see.
- Hey, y'all are good.
No, that was a prank call.
I was just making sure he
got to work or whatever.
Like why?
You was listening?
Like, why are you up that late anyways?
Like, for real?
No, you know what?
You gonna what?
No, you're not gonna let me?
No, you about to let me in.
No, let me in.
- [Bouncer] Hey, sweetie.
- [Christine] What?
[Bouncer] Have a good night, okay?
[Christine] What?
[Bouncer] Have a good night.
[people cheering]
What's up, King?
Congratulations.
Hey, Cheryl.
Oh, you smell so good.
You always have the finest cologne.
Is that the new Talfor?
No, that's that classic Armani.
Ooh, nice.
Man, I remember when you
couldn't even afford Old Spice.
Now look at that.
You done came up, huh?
Yeah, I've been blessed.
You look great.
You look awesome.
- Look at him now.
- Oh my God!
[girls squealing]
[Fan] Tony, Tony, Tony!
[female vocalizing]
Wait I wanna get a picture with Tony.
Wait!
Boy, you like that, don't you?
[laughing]
I mean, it's cool, but,
I'd much rather have
what you and Cheryl have.
Oh, no he didn't.
- [Cheryl] Yes, he did.
- Yeah.
Last night.
You told me you we're gonna
do, but I didn't believe you.
Wow, congratulations.
Look like you spent a
few dollars on that too.
Yo, you.
What's up boy?
What up, D?
What's going on.
Man, your looking good, bro.
What up, darkie? [laughing]
Yes, yes.
You're looking good.
You smell good.
Oh, you jelly?
Skin is in, okay?
Looking good, man.
Anyway, anyway this is my friend
girl, girl friend, Keisha.
Keisha, this is Tony-
- Tony Sinclair, BBX.
Yeah, yeah put that up.
Yeah yeah.
She's hot as hell but
she's as dumb as hell, too.
[laughing]
Isn't that how you like them?
You already know, man.
Where'd you meet her?
On your route?
Yeah, man.
I've kept it rolled up.
[Robin] Excuse me.
Excuse you?
[Robin] Tony Sinclair?
Yeah.
Can I speak to you in private?
[smack thuds]
Yeah.
Yeah, of course.
Go do your thing.
Get that private lesson.
Get her done, boy.
Goddamn what an ass right there.
For real?
No, your ass better.
You're my little girl.
You know I love you, girl.
Like that don't you?
I know. [laughing]
Freaky freak.
Do I know you?
I mean, you trying to get with me?
You really don't know who I am, do you?
I wish I did.
About six months ago, you saved my life.
I did what?
I'm Robin.
Robin?
I don't know any Robins.
Okay, you remember the
night your girlfriend
dumped you live on the air
for the whole world to hear?
On the radio station, you remember that?
Yeah.
I'm the one who called
in right before her.
I was in an abusive relationship,
and I was really struggling
with getting out.
And you gave me the advice,
and courage, to leave.
[dramatic music]
[Robin sobs]
Damn.
I did that?
Yes, you did.
I don't know what to say.
Well, I want you to say you'll let me
take you out for dinner,
or lunch, or something.
I mean, like, I really have to show you
how much I appreciate what you did for me.
You don't have to do that.
Give me your phone.
Give me.
You just don't know.
Here.
Thank you.
Have a good night.
Neighbor.
What's going on?
Hey, Sade.
Look, I'm telling you and everybody.
I am not Sade.
She's the singer.
I'm from Alabama.
My name is Sadie.
Want something to drink?
No, I'm good.
Oh, well.
You want something else?
Girl, you better stop playing.
I'm not playing.
I'm good.
You sure are.
♪ Baby I promise I promise ♪
♪ I'm trying hard to
win my hardest hardest ♪
♪ Don't go acting like you
so heartless heartless ♪
♪ I know you wanna ride away ♪
♪ I know you wanna get away ♪
♪ I know you wanna ride today ♪
♪ Yeah I know you wanna ride away ♪
♪ I know you wanna ride away ♪
[cell phone ringing]
You liked that, Princess, don't you?
Yeah, girl.
[Darren] Yo, what's up player?
That's old girl with that
donkey booty, ain't it?
What?
Nah, man.
That's just the dog.
[Darren] Oh yeah.
I forgot that's the only
bitch you got in your life
since Christine left your ass.
Yo, what you want, D?
[phone beeps]
Oh, hey.
Let me hit you back.
[Darren] Hey, hey man.
I just dropped off Keisha, man.
I got them up to freeze.
About to come over your house.
That's cool man, right?
Why not your crib?
[Darren] Hell, nah.
My mama got her boyfriend over there, man.
You tripping.
Look, man.
I'll call you back.
[Darren] Call me back, man.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Hello?
[Robin] Hi Tony.
Are you asleep?
This is Robin from tonight.
I hope it's not a bad time.
Nah, nah.
Nah, I'm cool.
What's goin' on?
[Robin] I just wanted to tell you,
thank you once again for all you've done.
And I really do wanna
take you out for lunch.
I still don't feel
like I've done anything.
[Robin] Oh my gosh.
You just don't know.
Listen, do you like the Surf
Bar and Grill on Monroe?
Yeah.
Yeah, sure.
[Robin] Okay, well.
How about I meet you there Friday at noon?
You know what?
Let me check my schedule.
What do you think?
[calm music]
Yeah.
Yeah I'll see you there.
[Robin] Great.
Okay, I guess I will.
Bye.
Right.
I'm old school, brah.
Learn from your elders.
You missed me with that, man.
You're only one minute older than me.
You better chop with all
those blunts, though.
Smoking up more product than you sellin'.
Are you guys twins?
Yes.
How you doin'?
My name's 2P.
This is my brother, Ice.
That the hivs old girl right there?
Robin?
Yeah.
And that's the old boy
from the radio station.
Tony Sinclair?
Yep, yep.
That was hella funny when his girl
dumped him on air, though.
[both laughing]
Yeah.
But he came up since then.
So, what old girl now?
She looks like...
I love your polka dots.
Reminds me of Qualmaine.
[laughing]
I'm just playing.
You're gorgeous.
Oh, thank you.
Thank you.
[Christine clearing throat]
Mr. Sinclair.
Hey.
Well, am I interrupting something?
Not at all.
So, this must be your new...
Whatever.
Intern.
Robin, this is Christine.
Christine.
This is Robin.
Is nice meeting you.
Yes. I'm sure.
[Woman] Christine.
Christine.
It looks like your friends need you.
Get your ass over here.
Have a good evening.
Good night, Tony.
What was that?
I mean, was that real?
I mean, are we being punked?
I mean, like, what's goin' on?
She's just an old friend
from college, that's all.
[lip smacks]
So, what college did you go to?
Morehouse.
Really?
I went to Spellman.
[Tony] Really?
Yeah.
[laughs]
What did you major in?
Mass Comm.
Yeah, I can see that.
You're in radio.
Well, I used to have
other plans before that.
Like what?
You know, I wanted
to get into production,
film, make movies.
But.
I got stuck behind a mic.
Well, you know you can
still make that happen.
Nah, I'm good.
You know, I love what I do.
And, not to toot my own horn, but.
I'm pretty good at it.
Yes, you are.
You have no idea how you saved my life.
[scoffs]
You keep sayin' that,
but, I just don't get it.
I was about to take my
life that night I called in.
What?
I mean, I know you were in
a bad relationship, but,
there's nothin' worth suicide.
You never know what
you'll do until you're
in that situation.
Believe me.
Things got really crazy
in my relationship.
That night that I called in,
I was about to end it all.
But what you said to me, it
gave me the strength to leave.
Love should make you feel safe.
If you feel that way,
then maybe it's time to move on.
Maybe it's time to move on.
[Robin] I can never thank you enough.
Wow.
[laughing]
[Robin] Oh my goodness.
I can't believe that
was such a nice place.
[Tony] Yeah.
It was cool.
[Robin] Yes, really cool.
[sighs]
I had a really nice time with you tonight.
And thank you for dropping me off.
You saved me an Uber.
[laughs]
Well, come on, it wasn't a problem.
You know, we should do this again.
I'd like that.
You know, the station's
havin' a meet and greet
at Oceaner's.
Would you like to go?
I don't know.
I need to check my schedule
and then I'll get back to you,
okay?
Yeah.
Gotcha.
[both laughing]
What time we goin'?
I'll give you the details tomorrow.
[laughing]
Okay, sounds good.
[lips smack]
[sirens wailing]
Good night.
[Robin chuckles]
[crickets chirping]
[sultry music]
♪ Headlights in the driveway ♪
♪ I get butterflies ♪
♪ How you get me so excited ♪
♪ You gotta just sit tight ♪
♪ Now my temperature's risin' ♪
♪ It's gettin' hot ♪
♪ I undress myself ♪
[Tony] Hey, Atlanta.
You know, let me tell you people.
I am feelin' great today.
There's somethin' about
bein' around positive energy,
good vibes and just beautiful people
that makes the world look different.
[laughs]
You know what?
Let's keep this positive energy goin'
and fall way back to "Sweet
Thing" by Chaka Khan.
This goes out to all
my sweet things in ATL.
Especailly one.
She knows who she is.
[chuckles]
[phone buzzing]
How you doin'?
[Robin laughing]
[Robin] Was that shout out for me?
[laughs] You know that's right.
What's up?
[Robin] Nothin' much.
You know, just tryin'
to wrap up a few things
so I can leave a little early.
Mm.
We still on for tonight?
Yeah.
I got my nails done.
And now all I need to do
is get my pedicure, honey.
[laughing]
Oo.
You gettin' the hands and
feet ready for a brother?
[laughs]
You go ahead, Spellman
Jaguar, you might fool around
and get bit.
[Robin] [laughs] Is that right?
[laughing]
Oh.
Hey, I gotta get back to work.
[Robin] Okay.
Enjoy the rest of your day.
I look forward to seeing you later.
All right, baby.
[Robin] Bye.
[phone thuds]
[Tony sighs]
♪ You could be my new thing ♪
♪ My new thing ♪
♪ When you feelin' down ♪
♪ I could be your mood swing ♪
♪ Now I'm gonna put it down ♪
♪ That's the way I do things ♪
♪ Let me show you how I do things ♪
♪ I do things ♪
♪ You could be my new thing ♪
♪ My new thing ♪
♪ When you feelin' down ♪
♪ I could be your mood swing ♪
♪ Now I'm gonna put it down ♪
♪ That's the way I do thing ♪
♪ Do things ♪
♪ Girl, you know you amazin' ♪
♪ Everybody looking like you famous ♪
♪ Everybody wanna know your name ♪
♪ But they don't really know ♪
♪ How good your game is ♪
[dramatic music]
Robin.
How you doin', baby?
Damn, you look good.
What are you doing here?
I see you just had lunch.
Why don't you come inside and
have a couple drinks with me?
And then we can do dinner later.
I don't think so.
What?
Look, no disrespect, but I
don't think the young lady-
- Ain't nobody talkin' to you.
I said come on.
And I said no.
[chuckles]
Get her.
[taser buzzing]
[kick thuds]
[car engine starting]
[wheels squealing]
[dramatic music]
What was that all about?
That was my old boyfriend.
The guy I left.
What?
Do you know who that is?
That's disrespect.
Hendrix.
He's only the biggest
dope dealer in Atlanta.
That's your ex?
Man, what did I get myself into?
[Robin] It's going to be okay.
[Tony] Yeah, right.
[heels clicking]
[glasses clinking]
You want a drink?
I'm good.
[liquid pouring]
[bottles clinking]
Nice place.
You have a maid?
Nah, just a good mama.
[sighs]
Oh, you have a dog?
Yeah, that's-
That's Princess.
She's the lady of the house.
[heels clicking]
[Robin squealing]
So cute.
Hey, baby.
Aw.
Little different.
You know, most of you guys
have some big ass dogs.
[laughs]
It was for my ex-girlfriend.
Interesting.
Look, you can have my bed
and I'll just chill out here.
No, I don't.
I don't need to sleep in your bed.
I'm fine on the couch.
No.
It's not a problem at all.
No, it's fine.
You sure?
I'm positive.
I'll be just fine right
here on your couch.
You take your bed.
But thank you.
Okay.
Do you have a t-shirt I can borrow?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I gotchu.
[heels clicking]
I hope this works.
Yeah, that'll work.
[laughs]
I appreciate it.
You just go around the corner.
First door on the left.
Okay, thank you.
[heels clicking]
[phone buzzing]
What up?
Yo, what's up, freak?
Yo, D, what's goin' on?
I'm tryin' to get up under this brown.
You two following me faster.
For real?
Yeah, man.
Hey, man.
They really wild, man.
Suckin' titties all weekend.
You know what's up, man.
Hey, is that Tony Sinclair from BBX 105?
Hi, Tony.
Hey.
Yeah, that's enough.
Yeah, I told him I know you.
Trying to go through with somethin', boy.
Nah, nah, not tonight.
What you mean "nah, nah"?
They tryin' to get their booty ate.
Didn't you hear that?
Look, man, I've had a crazy night.
That's what we tryin' to have, man.
Come on, dog.
Hey, I'll call you back.
Hey, call me back, dog.
Call me back.
He gonna call me back.
Just had to go take care of some shit.
Make yourself comfortable.
Thanks.
Get some rest.
You too.
[soft music]
[sirens wailing]
[serene music]
I just wanted to give
you a kiss good night.
♪ Must be voodoo, babe ♪
♪ Some kinda magic ♪
[birds chirping]
[phone buzzing]
Hello?
Are you awake?
[Tony] Yeah.
What happened to you?
I caught a Uber.
I'm home now.
I could've taken you.
You were sleepin' so good,
I didn't wanna wake you.
I had a really nice time
with you last night.
I started thinkin' it was all a dream.
[laughs]
No, it wasn't a dream.
I am real.
In spite of the drama with hendrix.
You sure?
Yeah.
Look, I gotta get ready for work.
I really hope to see you again soon.
Yeah.
Bye.
[sighs]
[Tony sighs]
Hey, Atlanta, you're listenin'
to the midday craziness
of the Tony Sinclair Show.
Today, we're talkin' about
freaky relationships.
[laughing]
In studio today, I have
with me love specialist,
Dr. Jennifer Love.
How you doin', Dr. Love?
[laughing]
Hey, Tony.
We just got finished playin'
"Don't Fight That Feelin'."
What's the importance of being
freaky in a relationship?
Oh, it's super important, Tony.
You see, it's that spice
that keeps a relationship
fresh and new.
No matter how long a
couple's been together.
Oh really?
Oh yes.
See, the worst thing is for
someone to become, you know,
complacent.
Just get stuck in the same, dull, routine.
You think so?
[laughs]
I know so.
You see, what you wanna do, Tony.
You wanna add a little bit of spice.
And a little bit of freaky.
And just see how happy you'll be.
It looks like we got
a caller on the air.
Uh, caller.
[Heather] Hi, my name is Heather.
Hey, Heather, what's your question?
I'm white and my boyfriend is a black
and upcoming rapper.
Okay?
So what's your question?
[Heather] He likes me
to call him the N word
when we're making love.
Is that okay?
Well, listen.
As long as you keep it in the bedroom
and within reason,
and if he likes it, then
it's perfectly fine.
[Heather] See?
That's what's up.
I told you, my nigger.
Okay.
Movin' on to the next caller.
[Caller] Yeah, I wanna talk about dudes
that get in your relationship business.
Who's all up in your business, man?
[Caller] I mean.
Dude's that wanna tell a
lady what to do, you know?
Get in a relationship.
Mess things up for a real boss.
What would you do about that?
I guess I'd have to see about that dude.
[Caller] What about a
DJ that gives bad advice?
And makes a man's girl leave him?
What you think about that?
[dramatic music]
Well, I guess if he
was lovin' her right,
that woulda never happened.
[Caller] I guess that's
why your girl dumped your ass
live on air.
We're gonna go to the next caller.
[Caller] I bet you do, mother-
- You know what?
Why don't we take a break
and when we come back,
we'll get more from Dr. Jennifer Love.
On this Relationship Thursday
on the Tony Sinclair show.
Sorry about that.
Oh, it's no problem, Tony.
See, about that little
problem that you have.
You know, we can always
work some things out.
Let me take good care of you.
Thanks.
Remember.
A little spice.
[both chuckle]
[Instructor] Let's all go
down and stretch our arms.
All the way down.
And hold it.
And come back up.
And breathe.
Let's do it one more time.
All the way down.
Yo, T.
What's wrong with you man?
T.
Man, my mind is somewhere else.
Yo, what's up, Tony?
Man, these past few days
have been literally insane.
What happened?
Remember that pretty
young thing that came
to the club the other night?
Yeah.
You know that one I ran up to VIP?
Yeah, she was bad as hell.
Should've asked, dude.
What's up with her?
She's more than I want
and more than I need.
Remember that night me
and Christine broke up?
Yeah, she dumped your
ass over the radio man.
The whole city heard you got fried, man.
Yo, can you chill?
Anyway.
She was the girl that called
in right before Christine.
No shit.
Yeah.
Oh, man.
That's crazy.
Yeah, it gets even more crazy.
She was all over you
at the club, though.
Seemed like she wanted to get with you.
She does.
But the dude she broke
up with is Hendricks.
From the Ghetto Boys.
The Ghetto Boys?
Man, they sling all the
dope in Atlanta, man.
What's wrong with you, man?
Dude.
What're you tryin' to tell everybody?
You know, I still can't believe
that girl came the same night.
Christine fired your ass, man.
That shit crazy.
Look.
It gets worse.
One of his goons called the station today
talkin' reckless.
You know this is serious.
I think you need to call the Po Po.
Call the Po Po.
For real.
Nah.
Nah, it's cool.
No, it's not cool.
You're a public figure.
And you're verified on the 'gram.
The 'gram.
And you know everybody.
You know, anything could happen.
Seriously.
That's crazy, man.
So you're telling me
that all this happened
because she called the
station and you told her
to get rid of old boy?
You know what, man?
I think you need to protect yourself.
What you mean?
What do you mean what do you mean?
I think you should start packin'.
Pew pew, nigga.
Nah.
It's not like that.
It's Hendricks.
It's like that, bro.
For once, I agree with him.
What you talkin'
about you agree with me?
[phone dings]
Like a mermaid or some shit.
I don't damn know, but
just look at the booty.
The booty.
[groans]
Now what you gonna do?
Come on, I ain't got beef with y'all.
Wrong.
My mans, Hendricks, wanna see you.
About what?
Listen to him.
Sound like a little bitch.
Little bitch.
Hey ladies.
Oh my God, that's Tony Sinclair.
[women screaming]
Yeah.
[camera shutter clicking]
Can we get a picture?
Yeah, let's do it for the 'gram.
[blow thuds]
[rap music]
[car engine accelerating]
[cars driving by]
Man.
[phone ringing]
Hello?
[Robin] Hi, Tony.
You busy?
Ah, yeah, just a little bit.
Oh, you sound out of breath.
Yeah, well, you know,
two of Hendricks's goons
just tried to kill me.
Other than that, I'm fine.
Just great.
[Robin] Oh my gosh, are you okay?
Hell nah.
[Robin] Tony, I'm so sorry.
Robin, dealin' with you
has put my life in jeopardy.
[horn blares]
[Robin] I wanna see you.
Robin, I'm done with this situation.
[Robin] I wanna make this right.
You know what?
I just need to clear my mind
and I'm gonna go meet up with my boys.
If that's okay with you.
[Robin] Okay.
Well, yeah.
Go on and do your thing.
Yeah, I'll call you later.
[Robin] Be careful.
Bye.
[Tony] Yeah, bye.
Thanks.
This is.
This is crazy.
[door latch clatters]
Mm, mm, mm.
You smell so good.
And you look good, too.
Thanks, Sadie.
Ah, hey.
You wanna have a glass of
wine before you head out?
I'd love to, but I'm runnin' late.
Well go on.
[hand smacks]
With your bad ass.
Don't hurt nobody.
[both chuckles]
Bye, Sadie.
♪ It's your birthday ♪
♪ It's an earthquake ♪
Whoa, look at that ass, boy.
Workin' with a monster over there.
Yes, you can.
We're gonna be loch ness
monsters together, girl,
let's go.
Jesus.
She about to take off.
Lookin' like a cinnamon swirl.
Look at you.
[laughing]
Sup?
What's up, man?
Boy, you made it just
in time, my brother.
Have a seat, have a seat, man.
[Darren muttering indistinctly]
[chuckling]
Yo, why you sittin' in
the corner with your back
against the wall?
[slurps] This air lickin'.
[slurps]
Yo, T, what's goin on, dog?
You don't look too good.
Oh, I don't feel too good.
What's wrong?
Them boys are still on my nuts?
Who, Hendricks?
Is he here?
Come on, man.
Ouch.
You got one more time to be loud.
Damn.
What's you gonna do?
I'll knock your ass off that seat.
What's up?
Just sayin', man.
You need to call the
police like I told you to.
You're damn skippy.
See?
I gotta be right if
Darren actually agrees.
Oh you just called
me stupid, didn't you?
I'm just sayin'.
You need to get yourself some security.
Or a trap or somethin', man.
Yeah.
You're too important
to be walkin' around here
like somethin' happened to your dog, man.
For real.
You know what?
Hey.
Come here, you.
Bring your little self over here.
This will make you feel better, guy.
Go ahead and do your thing.
Do your thang.
Yeah, you like that, don't you?
[Tony] Yeah.
You like that don't ya?
Yeah, it's nice.
Look at that ass.
Jigglin' like a mother.
Go ahead.
Smell it.
[sniffs]
Oh, you banged before you came in.
Yes you did.
What kind of love are you?
What kind of love you using?
[cork pops]
[men scream]
What are you doin', man?
Get your dumb ass off.
You're in this club to get some ass.
You trippin'.
It's a dollar.
I was gettin' a dollar.
Give me that damn dollar, man.
I'm sorry.
He's retarded.
Didn't take his medicine.
Gonna eat some booty today, boy.
Woo.
[doorbell chimes]
[Tony] I take it you were in the area.
[Robin] Tony.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
I know I forgot to hit
you back, but I've had
a lot on my mind.
Tony.
I am so sorry about the
way things have been going.
Baby.
Why won't you let me help you
relieve some of this stress?
After the week I've had,
I'm one hundred percent down with that.
[sultry music]
♪ I don't wanna waste your time ♪
♪ I just wanna show you a good one ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ So baby lay down and free your mind ♪
♪ Oh no ♪
♪ Just enjoy the ride ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Let's explore all your fantasies, girl ♪
♪ 'Cause I wanna know your body ♪
♪ It feels like we're on ecstasy, girl ♪
♪ I get so high when I'm with you ♪
♪ Oh, oh, I ♪
♪ We don't need a drug ♪
♪ For me to beat it up ♪
♪ All we need is love ♪
♪ Isn't that enough ♪
This is so nice.
Yes.
Yes, it is.
I can't believe we're like this.
Can you?
What do you mean?
Why did you wanna go out with me?
Hm.
Your booty.
[both laugh]
No, I'm being serious.
[sighs]
Besides the fact that you're
the most gorgeous woman I've ever seen?
[lips smack]
[Robin laughs]
I just feel like the
universe brought us together.
It's like fate.
What made you pick me?
Are you kidding me?
What woman wouldn't wanna go out with you?
You're so sweet.
Yeah, right.
No, I mean it.
I knew the first time I talked to you.
Do we have to talk about that?
[Robin] Still a sore spot?
[Tony] Yeah, a little bit.
I was going through so much.
You mean with Hendricks?
What made you get with a dude like that?
You got down on this food.
He was so laid-back and sweet
when we first got together.
Oh.
To wash the palette.
Okay.
I like fruit.
You're beautiful.
Thank you.
[laughs]
I'm not normally shy, but
there's somethin' about you
that has me...
Just, I don't know what to
say when I'm around you.
[Robin] And then when I
moved in, everything changed.
He just got so controlling.
I mean, I couldn't even go to the bathroom
without him wanting to know where I was
and what I was doing.
I couldn't even drive
myself to work anymore.
He'd drop me off and pick me up.
Are you serious?
And then he started
putting his hands on me.
[Hendricks] What?
You think this is a fucking game?
[Robin yells]
[glass shatters]
He was pinning me down
and grabbing me mostly.
He used to say,
"It doesn't make any
sense to bruise up a peach
and then try to eat it."
You deserve so much better.
Yeah, I know.
I know.
But that's what I was
going through the night
that I called into the radio station.
That night I got the courage to leave.
And ever since that night,
I've really been able to
just live my life.
Enjoy my life.
I feel so safe when I'm with you.
Love should make you feel safe.
If you feel that way, then
maybe it's time to move on.
[doorbell chiming]
Christine, what are you doin' here?
Well, hello to you, too.
Darren told me about your new place,
so I figured I'd stop by.
I just came here to get my dog.
I know my Princess misses me.
[sighs]
I guess it's about that time.
Oh.
This is nice.
I guess our breakup really paid off.
And I see you haven't
changed a bit, Christine.
[chuckles]
Neither have you.
Princess.
[whistling]
So, am I interrupting something?
[Tony] Actually, you are.
[bed creaking]
Mm.
Damn, you been workin' out?
A little bit.
[Christine] I can tell.
[Tony] Oh yeah?
Yeah.
[lips smack]
Christine, what are you doin'?
I missed you, baby.
Hey, ba-
What the fuck?
Robin, for real.
It's not what you think.
Is this the girl from the restaurant?
Yeah, that's right.
I'm his lady.
Oh really?
[Tony] No.
That's my ex.
Christine.
[dog whines]
The girl that dumped
you on the air the night
that I called into the radio station?
You have got to be kidding me.
For re-
- Wait, wait, wait.
That was you?
Oh.
Come on.
Look, look.
Robin.
You've gotta let me explain.
No, it seems like you've
done enough explaingin.
[Christine sighs]
Robin.
Don't worry, baby.
It's gonna be okay.
You need to go.
[dog whining]
[Christine] Wait
Baby.
[dramatic music]
Robin.
[car passing by]
[Christine] Mm.
[Tony] Go.
Home.
[Christine] Tony.
[sad piano music]
What's up, stranger.
[liquid sloshing]
Come inside.
Jesus.
Next thing you know, Christine shows up
because bigmouth Darren
gave her my address.
Next thing you know,
she's kissin' all over me,
talkin' about,
"Oh I miss you."
And Robin walks in and
all Hell breaks loose.
You know what?
Tony, baby, you have got to just relax.
Now, look.
You need to take some
quality time by yourself
to think things through.
And the main thing is,
you've got to give it to God.
Pray on it.
Trust me, it works.
That's what I need to do?
You heard me.
God has never failed me, yet.
[chuckles]
Mm.
Love.
It's a powerful drug.
Get.
Get out.
Get your behind out.
Now.
Thanks, Sade.
I mean Sadie.
Boy, you heard me.
Get to steppin'.
I'll see you in the stairwell.
[scoffs] Bye.
[exhales loudly]
Thank you, Jesus.
Mm.
[exhales loudly]
Was close.
[Voicemail] You have reached
the voicemail box of...
♪ Like leaves fallin' from a tree ♪
♪ Or like injuries from
your favorite team ♪
♪ That's how I feel every
time you away from me ♪
♪ Competin' for your love ♪
♪ This new found fame
is like a drug to me ♪
♪ You keep me sane ♪
♪ That's why you're stuck with me ♪
♪ Missin' you feels incomplete ♪
[phone buzzing]
Robin?
Listen, here you little
rice and bean eatin'.
You little niglet.
We have some unfinished
business that we neeed to handle
face-to-face.
Yo, who the hell do you
thnik you are tellin' my girl
to leave me?
Don't nobody leave Hendricks.
Yo, look.
Look, man.
I don't want any trouble.
I don't care what you want.
Meet me at Wilson's Brothers
Lumberyard on Baycat
in a hour.
And you better be by yourself.
Or the next time you see
this pretty little face,
it's gonna be in some dog food.
You understand me?
[Tony] Yeah, man, I understand.
[phone slaps]
Shit.
[tense music]
[men speaking indistinctly]
How's your nuts?
It wasn't my nuts.
It was his nuts.
It looked like the same nuts to me.
Think you'll be able
to shoot both of us?
Before one of us shoots you.
You spin records.
You don't know nothin'
about this gangster life.
Oh, word?
[gun clicking]
Oh, shit.
[blows thudding]
[Tony grunting]
[Tony coughing]
Tony?
Oh my God, Tony, what did they do?
What did you do to him?
Tony.
[coughs]
It's not what you thought
about me and Christine.
Shut your cornball ass up.
[kick thuds]
[Robin] No, stop.
Tony.
And I felt it.
[Robin] Stop it.
[Hendricks laughing]
[Tony coughing]
Oh, that's so sweet.
So sweet it's killin' me.
But it's killin' you too.
Because of you, my woman left me.
I'm not your woman.
You know what they say.
Choke a bitch and she'll love you.
Let that hoe breathe, that
bitch will wanna leave.
[Robin choking]
I should have kept choking your ass.
You wouldn't be so damn disrespectful.
[Tony] You're a real
tough guy, Hendricks.
What you say?
You talkin' to me?
Huh?
You judgin' me?
[kick thuds]
[Tony cries out]
I'll beat your ass, too.
Up in my shit.
I will blow your FM radio
talkin' mouth out the back
of your neck.
No, no, no.
Baby, baby.
Baby.
Please don't hurt him.
Don't hurt him.
All right.
I'll let him live.
But you better straighten up, you hear me?
Yes.
I love you, baby.
And I wanna work this out.
I will do anything for you.
I'm gonna let you live.
Because my girl begged for your life.
I will never.
I will never leave you again.
Go get dressed.
We'll go get some ice cream
or some Lemon Lockey wings,
all right?
Just you and me, baby.
Like old times.
Hurry up.
Come on.
[blow thuds]
[Tony screams]
Get rid of him.
But make it look a suicide.
Got it?
[tense music]
[Tony groans]
[goons muttering]
Yeah.
You spend a lot of time
with your personal life
and not our business, Hendricks.
[Darren] Shit.
Damn.
Be cool.
We gonna follow him.
[Darren] Get your big
ass hand out of my face.
My bad.
[Darren] Hey.
It ain't worth this no more.
Aw, man.
They got guns.
We got guns, too.
[Darren] I forgot.
Just shut up and drive.
[Darren] What, you wanna follow 'em now?
Shit, let's follow 'em.
I ain't got time for this
man that you're talkin' about.
No, you work for me.
So, you have time for
anything I have to say.
[dramatic music]
[Hendricks] Man, fuck you.
Where's my money?
Look, I got your fuckin' money.
[speaking foreign language]
Very good.
[phone clatters]
Want a good time dish?
[loud snorting]
What we talkin' about?
He said he got my money.
And you believe him.
Only thing a man has
in this world is his word
and his book of deeds.
[tense music]
Oh, come on, Mellow man.
Come on, man.
Nah, don't do that.
[groans]
What should I do that?
You want another line?
Look at this piece of nothin'.
You saw somethin' that
didn't belong to you
and you took it anyway.
And now that goes into your book of deeds.
[Man] No, I didn't take nothin'.
[man screaming]
[body thuds]
[man crying]
Eye for an eye.
[man screaming]
Oh, he took my eye.
You still got one left.
You'll be all right.
[man crying indistinctly]
Yeah, that's them right there.
Oh, that's them.
Boy, I'm about to do
surgery with this one.
Darren, get back here.
What?
What are you doin'?
I wanna go take care of
my business for my nigga.
This ain't trainin' day.
All right, Lanzo?
So, be cool.
All right I'm cool.
- All right.
- I'm cool.
Don't be in a rush to get out there
and get your ass shot.
I don't wanna get shot.
- All right?
- Okay.
- Now, look.
- What?
I'm gonna go out here
and then we're gonna
handle this, all right?
All right, you go piss.
You sit in the car and
I want you to wait for me.
All right, I'm gonna wait for you.
All right.
Wait, wait.
How long?
I don't know.
Just give me five.
Five what?
Five, five, bro, what?
Five minutes?
Five seconds?
Five milliseconds?
Five, five-
- Dam nit, I don't know.
- Ultrasec-
- All right.
Just whenever you feel the time is right.
The time is right?
- Yeah.
- The time is right.
- Time is right.
Okay.
[suspenseful music]
[gunshot cracks]
[man screaming]
[gunshots firing]
[men yelling]
Didn't I tell you to give me five?
You ain't specify.
Point the gun that way.
Oh.
Yeah.
Pointin' the gun at you.
Stay right there.
That's the third damn time. [groans]
[Darren] Tony, you all right?
You good?
Boy, somebody fucked you up.
Boy, damn.
[soft music]
[glass clinks]
No, no, no.
I don't wanna get too fucked up.
Got a flight to catch in four hours.
Go upstairs and pack your shit, baby.
I'm not going anywhere with you.
Yes, you are.
What's up?
[gunshots firing]
[Robin screams]
I'll follow them.
You guys go get the police.
What?
Yeah, you heard what I said.
Go.
We're his kid niggas, bro.
[Robin] Let me out of this car.
I don't-
Stop this car.
Let me out.
I don't wanna go with you nowhere.
[Hendricks] You're never gonna leave me.
I said I'm not goin' with you nowhere.
I wanna get out of this car.
[Hendricks] Robin, you love me, right?
[Robin] I don't love you.
I don't wanna be with you.
Wow.
[Robin] I told you that.
Let me out of this car, please.
All right, I got somethin' for you.
[Robin] Please.
Shut up, I'm on the phone.
Yo, how y'all bring them
clowns up in my house?
Man, Hendricks, they
got the drop on us, man.
[Hendricks] Really?
Look, man.
You guys got the product?
We got it all.
All right, nevermind that other stuff.
We've got a flight to catch.
And I got Robin.
I said let me out of this car.
All right, peace.
Please.
- Jump out.
- Please.
Get out, then.
- Get out.
I'll get out this damn thing.
Well, go ahead. Go ahead.
- Hurt yourself.
- Unlock the door.
Let me out.
[both shouting]
After everything I done for you.
I always treat you good
I've always been there for you.
Is this how you treat me?
Please.
You said forever.
[Robin] Please, let me out.
I don't care about anything
else in this world,
but you and my money.
You know how much I love my money.
You should be honored.
[upbeat rap music]
[tense militant music]
Y'all ready to be some millionaires?
[Goon] [chuckles] You already know.
[metal scraping]
[tense music]
[Thug laughing]
So, you're tellin' me
you got a hundred pounds
of yaya and five hundred pounds of hydro?
We stand to make 10, 15 million dollars.
[chuckling]
Hell, we could buy our own island.
What?
You got somethin' you wanna say?
[tape ripping]
[Robin shouts]
What you lookin' at?
Nothin'.
Shoulda killed your ass a long time ago.
'Cause you're a liability.
I can't be out here in the
streets lackin' over no broad.
You coulda had everything.
The houses.
The cars.
The jewelry.
The money.
But you threw it all away because.
Because some dumbass DJ told you to.
And, on top of all that,
his girlfriend called in
after you.
And broke up with his punk ass on the air.
[thugs laughing]
You leave me for him?
Hurry and wrap that shit up.
We to a plane to catch.
I loved you.
I still love you.
But you a dumb bitch.
But you're my dumb bitch.
[Robin spits]
You call this love?
[chuckling]
Sometimes love hurts, bitch.
[Tony] Hold up.
Look who it, Captain Save A Hoe, huh?
Whose a dumb bitch now?
Drop it.
Right now.
Ain't no safety on now.
They're comin'.
You okay?
Robin, I'm so sorry.
[Robin] Me too.
I should have told you
about Christine that day
at the restaurant.
She means nothin' to me.
She's my past.
[Christine chuckling]
Oh, so I'm a part of your past, huh?
[Hendricks laughing]
[kiss smacks]
Good job, baby.
The worst thing you could ever do
is think somebody's dumber than you.
You up in the bar and grill
tryin' to put the move
on my girl.
And guess what?
I did the same thing with yours.
I knew that night you weren't shit.
You forget.
I stuck by you when you had nothing.
Nothing.
I paid your bills.
I made sure rent was met.
I was a damn good woman to you, baby.
And what do you do?
Work.
I worked, Christine.
How do you think I got
to where I am today?
I put in the work.
You couldn't wait for
a brother to come up.
You were too self-absorbed.
A good woman hangs around.
She does what it takes
to help her man make it.
It was all about you.
What you did was heartless.
There's no comin' back from that.
You dumped me on my own show.
Live on the air.
[gunshots cracking]
[hands clapping]
[speaking foreign language]
Very touching.
Almost cried.
[Spanish music]
Going somewhere?
Hey, Romelo.
Your stuff is right here.
I was just about to call you.
I was born at night.
But not last night.
[Officer] Police.
[gunshots cracking]
[Tony] Christine, don't.
No.
Christine.
[gunshot cracks]
[wind blowing]
[footsteps plodding]
[machine beeping]
Oh, God, Darren.
Hey, baby.
Is he okay?
No, he just.
He's not lookin' good.
Can we go in?
We can't.
Sit down.
How does he look?
I need to be straight.
He's in critical condition.
And, he has a bullet lodged
very close to his heart,
I'm afraid.
What does that mean?
[Doctor] It's too early
to say at this moment.
It's more touch and go, I'm afraid.
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
[melancholy music]
[door clicks shut]
Love should make you feel safe.
Can I speak to you in private?
If you feel that way, then
maybe it's time to move on.
I was about to take my
life that night I called in.
Just hang in there, love.
It'll be all right.
[tense music]
[gunshot cracks]
It's all your fault, man.
You knew you was mixed
up with that dope boy
when you called into that station.
You knew it when you brought
your ass over to that table
in the club, man.
Darren.
We've been friends
since high school, man.
We was little boys.
It's not the time.
I'm sorry.
[Darren clears throat]
You know what?
I can't.
I'm sorry.
[Darren] What you gonna
fuck her and leave her?
What's you mean?
You're gonna put a ring on it.
[Tony] She dope, man.
[laughing] Oh my God.
[machine beeping]
[oxygen pumping]
[tense music]
[Robin laughing]
[Robin crying]
Come on, Mattie.
Oh, touchdown.
Let's go, boy.
Woo!
Hey guys.
I know you guys are havin'
fun, but visitin' time
is almost over, so, once
again, tone it down.
Sorry.
_ Yes, nurse Jackie.
[men muttering]
Shut up.
Y'all don't keep down
that damn noise, man.
Oh.
What's goin' on, man?
Jesus.
Can't believe you're awake.
[Darren] Me either, man.
All right, if you don't
quit all that damn cryin'
and soundin' like a little bitch.
Ever since I got here.
[laughs]
I've been tryin' to wake
up just to slap your ass.
[scoffs] Wasn't cryin'.
He was cryin'.
I could hear it all.
Talkin' about,
"We've been friends since high school."
[Darren] High school.
[Tony laughs]
[Tony groans]
Relax now.
Man, it's good to see you awake.
Man, how you feel?
Yeah, man.
Man, I'm alive.
Wakin' up to you two knuckleheads.
But God is good.
[Both] Yeah He is, man.
It's just so good to see you awake, man.
Now, where you get off
scarin' Darren like that?
No, I wasn't.
I wasn't scared, man.
Last night was crazy, okay?
I wasn't scared.
Yeah.
You were scared.
But, other than that,
I don't remember much.
Wait, wait.
You don't remember how
we had your boy held up,
you know in the meat-packin' plant?
Yeah.
Remember that?
You know, he used it for his stash spot.
[Tony] Right.
[Darren] You know,
Chris rolled up on you.
You know, you find out
them two workin' together.
You don't remember none of that?
That's when everything became fuzzy.
Yeah, well that's when you got shot.
Yeah, Christine capped your ass, bro.
Christine shot- [groans]
Christine shot me?
Police came in, "Freeze."
You know, Hendricks disappeared and stuff.
And Christine is in there
fightin' for her virginity
in there right now.
Man, I guess hurt people,
they just hurt people.
Yeah, can't think about it.
Yeah, she tried to shoot Robin.
Yeah.
Where's Robin?
Oh, uh, we.
Lot has changed, man.
I don't know, she-
- She bounced, man.
Oh, uh.
Maybe.
I said some things I shouldn't
have and she, you know.
All right, gentleman.
I'm gonna have to have you leave.
Tony's parents are here
and they'd like to spend
a little time with him
My bad, bro.
See what you did, man?
[Doctor] Thank you.
[everyone chattering]
[upbeat music]
Hey, son.
You okay?
Hi.
Oh my baby.
[speaking foreign language]
♪ I've been travelin' this
boulevard of broken dreams ♪
♪ Boulevard of broken dreams ♪
♪ Everything and the way it seems ♪
♪ Everything and the way it seems to be ♪
♪ To be ♪
♪ Boulevard of broken dreams ♪
♪ Boulevard full of broken dreams ♪
♪ I had a whole lot of dreams before me ♪
♪ And I've seen them torn into pieces ♪
♪ Pieces ♪
♪ But these ♪
[Voicemail] The number
you dialed has been changed,
disconnected, or is no longer in service.
If you feel you have reached
this recording in error,
please check the number
and try your call again.
[upbeat music]
♪ I'm still in love with you ♪
[man chanting]
I Salaam-Alaikum, my brother.
Welcome to the religion of Islam.
Islam means peace.
And that's what we wished all the brothers
and the sisters and all
the human beings on earth.
Peace.
As-salamu alaykum.
Alaykum as-salam.
Thank you.
As-salaumu alaykum, my brother.
Alaykum as-salamu.
So good to see you.
Wow, look at you.
[men laughing]
You look amazing.
You too, my brother.
Hey, you want the rest of my orange?
Hey, this is my wife.
[speaking foreign language]
How are you?
[foreign language]
Good to meet you.
She's beautiful, ain't she?
Yes, she is.
Wow.
Keep goin' okay.
[foreign language]
My brother.
Let's go.
Wow.
[Homeless Man] You somebody, man.
I can see it.
Okay?
Don't you ever forget that.
Hey.
And get your damn head up.
[G Smooth] BBX 105 Radio.
You are live in the G Smooth Experience.
And that was the brand
new record from my man,
Malachi.
Yo, Malachi.
Thank you for comin' by
and droppin' that new music
on us, man.
You are welcome here anytime.
Preciate you.
'Ppreciate you havin' me too.
Awesome.
All right.
All right, Atlanta.
As you all know, my man, Tony Sinclair,
who is a integral part
of the BBX 105 family
was shot several months ago.
And, you know, we almost lost him.
But.
I am happy to say that my
man is back in the buildin'.
He's getting ready to take over.
Gettin' ready for the return.
Of my man.
Tony Sinclair.
It's all yours, man.
You're the man, G Smooth.
Let's get it.
[fingers snap]
Wow.
Right.
Get nice and comfortable up in here.
[sighs]
Hello, Atlanta.
You're on the air with Tony Sinclair.
And I just wanna say, from
the bottom of my heart,
I humbly am so happy to be back.
And I wanna hear from my callers.
I wanna hear from my people.
Atlanta.
You're on the air with Tony Sinclair.
What's on your mind?
[Carmen] Hi, Tony.
Hey, how you doin'?
[Carmen] This is Carmen.
I wanna let you know we missed you
and so glad to have you back.
It is so good to be back.
[Taurus] What's goin' on, brother?
It's DJ Taurus.
Hey, brother.
Good to hear from you.
[Taurus] Man, we thought we lost you.
Man.
I'm glad we didn't lose you, brother.
Welcome back.
Thanks, brother.
I appreciate that.
Next caller.
[Marcus] Hey, Tony, this is Marcus.
Hey, Marcus.
[Marcus] I just want
you to give a shout out
to all my friends in town for
the black gay pride weekend.
[Tony] That's what's up.
Next caller.
[Robin] Hi, Tony.
I'm so glad you're feeling better.
Oh, thank you, thank you.
[Robin] I wanna ask your advice.
Go ahead.
What should a woman
do when she's messed up
getting to know the best
man she's ever known
in her life?
[Tony] I don't know.
What do you mean?
I mean, what if she put
not only herself into danger,
but, him and his friends?
Why does your voice sound so familiar?
It should.
When I heard your voice on the radio,
I just had to call in.
Look, I was wrong for how I did things
and what I did to you.
I should have never got you
caught up in a situation
like that.
It could've cost you and
your friends your life.
I am so sorry.
I just want another chance.
No one has ever treated me as
good as you treated me, Tony.
[Tony] I don't know.
[Robin] Tony, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I don't know.
I just don't know.
[door clatters]
[heels clicking]
[door creaking]
If you can tell me no to my face,
I will never bother you again.
Go.
Robin.
[soft music]
[Darren sputtering]
Oh.
Oh. [laughs]
Uh.
Hey, Atlanta.
I don't know what to say.
[Robin laughs]
I was not expectin' a comeback like this.
The woman that got this
all started a while ago
and has my heart pumpin' every day,
is here in the station with me.
I just don't know what to say.
Shut up and kiss me.
[chuckles]
Go get it, boy.
I ain't about to sit your kids, though.
[upbeat pop music]
Oo, this is gonna be good.
What's up, pop?
I didn't know you was here.
What's up?
Nigger, that's gonna be good.
You happy, son?
Yeah.
I'm proud of you.
Thanks, pop.
I still need some gas money, though.
You know what?
I got you.
Come on.
What?
Just come on.
Watch my grill.
Is food ready?
Is it ready?
That's not done yet.
Try that one.
All right.
[car horn beeps]
You did good, boy.
I love it, man.
That's nice.
It's for you.
Man, quit playin'.
You bought me a car?
It's yours.
Oh man.
You bought me a car.
Okay, you gonna need to bounce.
Yes, ma'am.
You really are my son.
Marcia, the boy bought me a car.
Come see.
The boy bought us a car.
[all cheering]
[all laughing]
[upbeat music]
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull