[trance music]
[trance music continues]
[traffic]
Hey, how you doing beautiful?
[laughs]
[laughs] Oh damn!
Ohh! Turned down by a flamer.
Man! Fuck this!
[screeching tires]
What are you doing?
What are you going to say while
playing "Hide the Salami"?
[laughs]
[inaudible]
[screeching tires]
Shit!
Be careful...
His purse could be used
as a deadly weapon. [laughing]
[kissing sounds]
[laughing] Oh shit.
-[deep breath]
-Then what Stevie?
You aren't going to
wet yourself, are you?
[Mark laughs]
[huffs]
[loud rock music]
[fighting]
[rock music continues]
[siren]
Hey! Who's that? His lawyer?
His wife.
I've reached my decision.
[judge] Although only one of the
young men actually took part
in the assault,
I hold both responsible.
However, taking into
consideration that there
are no previous convictions,
I'm not going to give either
of you a prison sentence.
Steven Mendoza,
200 hours of community service.
Mark Gonzalez,
100 hours of community service.
In an AIDS facility!
[bangs gavel]
[sighs]
[upbeat music]
[upbeat music continues]
[music fades]
[sighs]
[deep breath] Hey how you doing?
I'm here for the um...
Um, I'm supposed to meet
a Mrs. Bernard or something.
-I don't know, I'm supposed to
help out or something.
-I'm Dr. Bernard.
You must be Stevie?
Alright, before we get things
started I think there's a few
things you need to know.
Firstly, we don't wear uniforms
because we are trying
to give the impression
of a home, not a hospital.
Also, we have
a very specialized clientele.
In order to be admitted
into this hospice,
a doctor has to determine
that a patient has...
six months or less to live.
So if a patient lives longer
than six months do you take him
out back and shoot him?
I'd appreciate it greatly
if you would supervise Stevie
during his short stay with us.
If it proves difficult,
all the staff
can pitch in and help.
Alright... thank you.
Well? What, if anything,
are you capable of doing
to help out or something?
I don't know? Um...
maybe clean both
your broomsticks?
If I had a guess
at your qualifications,
I'd say that there are
a couple of things you can do.
-OK.
-Bathrooms or bedpan?
[laughs] Yeah.
How about door number three?
-There isn't one Stevie.
-Well I'll make one. Look,
I'll refuse this shit
and have the judge
give me jail time instead.
OK, look. I think we got off
to a bad start.
Hi, I'm Stevie.
-I know that.
-And you are...
Supervising your community time.
OK Ma'am,
isn't there anything else
I can do for the next 30 days
besides cleaning toilets?
[floor creaks]
[knocks]
[coughs]
Um, to what do I owe this visit?
Uh, I was just stopping by...
the hospital.
Oh, where are my manners?
Please, have a seat.
-So, do you go to school?
-No.
Work then?
Ah, aren't we lucky.
All that can wait.
The important thing is to enjoy
yourself while you're young.
See the world.
Have you seen the world?
Actually... outside of the US
I've only been to Australia.
Some world-traveler, huh?
[frightened gasp]
[sighs]
-I didn't mean to startle you.
-No you didn't, it's just...
I only had time
to come in for a minute.
I got to go.
[piano music]
[sighs]
You know what I heard...
yeah, exactly.
[footsteps]
I gotta go.
Sorry, I don't think it...
[sighs] ...went too well.
[footsteps]
[sighs] Is Carlos OK?
I think we've gotten off
to a bad start.
My name is Sonya.
You don't have to clean bedpans
and I think it would be best
if you didn't visit
another patient.
What else can you do?
Well, I can clean up.
You know mop,
sweep, do the dishes.
That was pretty much
my last job.
And I think I can handle
just about any
maintenance thing.
You know, loose wiring,
patching up holes in the wall.
Stuff like that.
Just about anything
but painting.
I hate painting!
Should have told her
I hated getting laid!
[Will shouts]
Close my fucking door.
You trying to kill me
with those God-damn fumes?
-Sorry.
-Sorry? What are you?
Some kind of faggot?
[Stevie] Nope.
So what are you then?
Why are you painting walls
that don't need to be painted?
Are you dumb or just stupid?
Well this certainly
narrows it down.
You're obviously not a painter!
And you're not a talker.
And you say you're not a faggot.
So, what the hell are you then?
Are you good for anything
besides using up
the air on this planet?
I say, keep chopping down
the rainforest, we don't need
the air the trees provide.
We just need to kill off
the dead wood,
the people that are
a waste of space on this planet.
And we can start with you,
what do you think?
[laughs sarcastically]
[laughing]
Didn't mean to offend you boy.
In desperate times
such as these,
a fella's got to do
what he's got to do
to keep himself amused.
Yo? Yo Betty Boop?
Sorry...
Miss Boop, I was wondering
if I could borrow...
- What's your name boy?
- Stevie.
Can I borrow Stevie here?
Staring at the walls
of Cell Block 1-0-7 has made me
a little stir-crazy,
in case you couldn't tell,
and if I don't talk
to someone fairly quickly,
I'll surely pop.
So what do you say?
Can Stevie here
be the beneficiary
of hearing my life story?
-But what about the painting?
-I'm not talking all day Boopsy.
I could limit my life story
to the time I've spent
in this exciting establishment,
and then all I'd need
is three seconds.
I'll give you 15 minutes.
Your Highness is both
generous and compassionate.
Thou has put aside the rumors
that though hast no heart.
Come my Lordship,
time is of the essence.
[orchestral music]
[sighs]
[orchestral music continues]
Well, Stevie...
I said I'd be telling you
my life story but,
I've already heard it.
So, how about you tell me yours.
Actually,
I think I've heard yours too.
Grew up in a modest house
with your parents.
They fought some
but mostly got along
pretty darn good.
They tried to keep you
down on the ranch,
but you managed to sew
your wild oats anyway,
and that pretty much
takes up all your thoughts.
How you gonna sow more oats?
Well, now that we've finished
that story what else
can we talk about?
How about politics?
What do you think about Bosnia?
Affirmative action?
Nuclear weapons?
[sighs]
If your tongue's been cut out,
I could get a chalkboard
and some chalk.
Uh, well who says
you know how to write?
A snappy comeback.
Almost a witticism. I'm stunned.
I'm impressed. I see you
in a completely different light.
So, does this off-the-cuff
remark try to conceal the fact
that you have no opinion?
Or is it your opinion that we
should all be opinionless?
What is that?
A toy. That's what I do.
At least that's what I did.
Now, it's just a hobby.
That's what happens when you
continue to do things
that no longer make any money.
The career becomes a hobby.
So, with all that nuclear
testing going on in Nevada,
I've always been amazed that
anyone would want to live there.
Not that California's so great.
There's probably a nuclear sub,
from who knows what country,
passing by our great city
as we speak.
It could be from one of those
new Russian countries,
one of the ones like...
never could spell,
can't pronounce and have
no idea who the leader is.
But thank God
there's no nuclear threat!
And you know what happens
when the wind blows west?
Radiation is carried
all over California.
And when I realized this,
did I pack my bags
and get the hell out?
No. Actually... I think I went
to the deli and ordered
a pastrami sandwich.
Uh, anyway...
What kind of toy
is that going to be?
I'm trying to make a unicorn.
Hopefully one that will fly.
My father taught me
how to make toys
and I'm something of a prodigy,
if I do say so myself.
But there's always been
one thing that I could
never make...
a toy that would fly.
Even my paper aeroplanes
nose-dived straight
into the ground.
So before I leave this cruel,
gravitational world,
I'm going to make
something that will fly...
Hello William!
-I brought you a care package.
-[Will] Oh!
I'm sick of hearing him
whine, whine, whine
about the food here.
Am I interrupting something?
Well, I think our time
has expired for today.
If you keep
Herr Kommandant waiting,
you may not be able to come
and visit again tomorrow.
[soulful music]
[sighs]
[bottle breaks]
[laughs]
[soulful music continues]
[bottle breaks]
Hey, so um, how did it go today?
[sighs]
Alright, I guess.
You know, you got a car
and they gave you
the closest hospital.
Man, it takes me three buses
to get to my
fudge packers' clinic.
Nah.
Once I got there
it wasn't so bad though.
They all seemed kind of scared
of me so they didn't
boss me around so much.
What about you?
[sighs] I don't know.
I mean when I showed up,
the first thing I saw
was this fine-ass freak.
-You know what I'm saying?
-Hmm-mmm. [laughs]
And I thought
this prison sentence is
turning out to be pretty cool.
Yeah.
Then she opened her mouth
and ruined everything.
Man, I hate it
when girls do that shit.
You know, I was thinking
about digging a tunnel...
try to escape...
-but then I met this dude...
-And he asked if you wanted
to be the mommy or the daddy?
And you said
you wanted to be the daddy...
so he said "OK, get down
on your knees
and suck momma's dick."
[laughs]
Man, this guy's a trip.
I mean, I don't understand
half the shit he says...
You know, it's kinda like...
Remember when I had to go to
traffic school
and I got into that school
-that hired comedians
for teachers?
-Oh yeah!
They hired teachers
from our high school, right?
[laughs]
Anyway, the guy's a trip.
[soulful music]
You know if you keep enjoying
your work I'll have to give
you another assignment?
Don't worry I'm still hating it.
I just figured I might as well
try and get it done.
And give yourself
a little bit more time
to talk to Will?
-Yeah, I guess so.
If you don't mind?
-It's fine by me.
[sweeping]
We've caught one.
[somber music]
[plastic sheeting]
[plastic sheeting continues]
[zipper]
[somber music continues]
[Will] Have you ever considered
what you'd like done
with your body after you die?
[sighs] I'd like to be buried,
but I don't want a coffin.
A coffin is a waste of money
and a waste of a perfectly good
tree that is supposed to grow,
produce air, make treelings.
Not be chopped down,
nailed together
and stuck into the ground...
Just bury me as I came
into this world.
Hmm, in my birthday suit.
I've always like the idea
of being buried in my own land.
But, since the only land I own
is in this pot here...
I'd settle for being
buried in a park,
but not in some stuffy cemetery
surrounded by strangers who,
if I knew in life,
I probably wouldn't like.
You know,
I hate to tell you this Will,
but I think it's totally illegal
to be buried in a park.
There you go again
bringing realism into it.
The whole idea of a coffin
has always baffled me.
I think of it
as man's final attempt
to overcome nature,
be buried in a box
so that yucky dirt
doesn't get all over you.
I think I'd rather be eaten
by the bugs right away,
than have it prolonged
a few years while my coffin
starts to fall apart...
Do you think we can talk
about something else?
A little too morose
for such a sunny day?
Who the hell am I to take up
a six-foot plot of land
for the rest of eternity?
That would make me
more important in death
than I ever was in life.
And no-one ever goes
to cemeteries anyway.
Maybe my parents would visit
a few times, possibly a friend
or two might drop by,
but after they died
who would ever show up?
Nobody!
I say bury me then plant
some trees over me or...
build an ice-cream stand
on top of me for all I care.
[digging in pot plant]
You know Will,
to me you seem like you're
in great health.
Ha my boy, for that you can
help yourself to another soda.
[appreciative sigh]
-Hey, you want one?
-Ah, no... I have to
watch my figure.
[fridge closes]
[sighs]
[opens can]
[Will] Care for some
disinfectant?
Have you ever noticed
how people act when they drive?
The wimpiest guys
get in their cars and suddenly
turn into Super Cock!
The tattooed rebel...
itching for a good fight.
Flipping people off
without a moment's hesitation.
But the moment these people
step out of their cars
they turn into The Wimp again.
They fucking cower
as they walk down the street.
Yes, cower.
OK, maybe not cower.
But if somebody bumps into them
do you think they say,
"hey fuck you,
get out of my way".
No, they say "excuse me"
even if it's not their fault.
I bet you're one of those
drivers that flip people off
every chance you get.
Yeah but also in the street too.
Oh OK,
well then you're not as bad
as I thought.
[frustrated sigh]
Has anything I said penetrated
that virgin brain of yours?
You haven't given five minutes'
thought to why you're here,
or what'll happen to you
when you die.
Well God, or Jesus, or Allah,
or Mother Nature or whatever
you want to call him, her or it,
gave you something
called a brain.
Supposedly your brain
is superior to all the other
animals in this world.
It seems a shame
all you've learned to do with it
is discover two different ways
to crush a beer can
and ten different ways
to destroy your brain cells.
I'm giving you
a homework assignment.
I want you to go home tonight
and think about what you see
yourself doing in ten years.
And, if you think you'll be
doing anything other than
working a job you don't like,
drinking beer
and trying to get laid,
I want you to write down how
you plan to fulfill your goal.
Until tomorrow...
Too-da-loo!
Hey Sonya I was wondering,
you know I still got
a little time left...
is there anything else
you'd like me to do?
How about you do
some filing so I can
stare at you?
-Sure! [laughs] Not a problem.
-No really, you can go home
a little early tonight Stevie
and don't worry,
I won't tell the Judge.
OK but um, listen...
you get off soon too, right?
Well, how about we go
grab a bite to eat?
You know, nothing formal,
just a friendly meal?
Why are you asking me out now?
I don't know? I mean we seem to
be getting along pretty good...
No, no, no. But why now?
Because Stevie,
you saw me bend over
and that got your
little hormones all revving.
Relax man!
I'm not asking you
to marry me or anything.
Look Stevie...
we have to be together
for a certain amount of time...
and I told myself
I may as well try and be civil,
but it's nothing...
absolutely nothing
more than that.
Alright. Forget it. Later.
[rap music]
[sighs]
[rap music continues]
What's up?
[Stevie] Hey!
[guitar music]
How's jail time going man?
It's alright. How about you?
[shouts] It fucking sucks!
[laughs]
-What are you doing, man?
-Just some shit.
[sighs]
What kind of shit?
Uh, homework.
[strums guitar]
You maybe want to
do something later?
-Maybe.
-We can get
a couple of beers or something.
Uh, I don't think so.
I'm kind of busy with this.
Alright maybe tomorrow then huh?
Yeah... tomorrow...
[Mark] Alright then.
Later.
[Stevie] Later.
[phone rings]
-Hello?
-Hi Stevie, it's Will.
Now I know I'm crossing
the patient-volunteer boundary,
and you know I wouldn't call
if it weren't a dire necessity
and you can tell me to stop
apologizing any time now...
I don't mind you calling.
What's up?
Glue.
-Excuse me?
-I'm almost done with my project
but I've run out of glue
and no-one around here
will go and get me any.
-[sighs] Alright.
-Oh and there's one other thing,
you're not allowed
in the building at this hour
so you'll have to
take the side entrance.
-[Stevie] Side entrance?
[falling bag]
Shit!
[sighs]
[opening window]
Have you got
the letters of transit?
Here, I kinda dropped it
on the way up
but I'm sure it's alright.
I don't suppose you could
go back and get some more?
Oh well, uh... no matter.
[Stevie] Hey... what the...
It was the wrong kind anyway...
not strong enough.
I appreciate your effort though.
But, now that you're here
there is something I really
would like to talk about,
so... have a seat.
Well I'm sure that
you've noticed that I have
my share of opinions...
-No! You?
-But there is one thing that
I have virtually no opinion on.
-What? Whether you
have a conscience?
-Lighten up Stevie!
I'm talking about heaven...
I'm not sure if I believe
one exists or not.
Well, I wouldn't
worry about it.
I'm not worried
about getting in,
I'm worried about being
bored to death once I get in.
Well, maybe you can amuse
yourself by sending God
on useless errands.
For instance,
will there be movies and books?
Hopefully I've got nothing
to worry about
and it'll have the biggest
library in the whole galaxy.
I could read the latest
Hemingway novels,
the ones he wrote after he died.
Or, maybe go to the theater...
and see what
Shakespeare's written lately.
That's the spirit.
But, if there are movies
and plays and books,
can you imagine how badly
God would censor them.
More than likely I'd spend
the rest of eternity watching
Bob Hope flicks.
And then you'd realize
you were in hell.
Touché!
I should get you
upset more often,
it seems to have
stirred your senses.
And another thing,
do you think they allow
dating up there?
Or is heaven a place where
there is no longer any sex?
No longer any need for
entertainment such a movies...
just an endless flow
of spiritual harmony,
bliss and enlightenment.
Break time over!
You need to stop this
lazing around and get back to
your momma's house
and finish up that
little homework assignment.
[claps hands]
[moving bowl]
[vomiting]
[coughing]
[panting]
[moving sick bowl]
[still panting]
Yo! What's happening partner?
I've got my homework.
[Will still panting]
-You alright Will?
-Huh? Ahh...
I might look like I'm in hell,
but I feel... oh...
like I'm in purgatory.
Before our friendship goes
any further I need to know
what it is you've done.
-You mean about the homework?
-To get in here!
What crime against humanity
did you commit that forced you
to squander your time
with a person such as myself.
[sighs]
I kinda got in this fight...
Must have been
a pretty bad fight.
No, it weren't that bad.
[Will coughs]
And why did you kind of
get into a fight?
[clicks fingers]
Because he was gay... I thought.
You can go now.
[shouts] Go!
-[Sonya] What's going on?
-Nothing.
-Well, is Will OK?
-Uh, yeah. He just got
a little pissed off.
What did you do?
Nothing!
You know not everything
that happens around here
is my fault.
Oh, it's not?
[frustrated sigh]
[gentle music]
[classical music]
OK, look...
I don't know what it is
that I have against gays...
I mean, I used to never
even trip off them...
gays that is.
[classical music continues]
Um... a few years ago I had
this summer job where we went
around from store to store,
handing out
these free pamphlet things...
and one day I stupidly walked
into this crowded gay bar,
and I asked the bartender
if I could leave some pamphlets
on the counter...
and this bartender dude says
all sexually that no I can't
leave them on the counter,
but I can leave them
in the back room.
Now here I am,
some skinny little 15 year old,
and he wants me to go
in the back room with him.
And he had this strange look
in his eyes that...
scared me to death.
So I pushed my way
through the crowd and took off.
I think ever since that day,
I've always had some kind
of hatred towards gays.
[classical music continues]
These are for you to look at
when you get tired
of staring at the walls
here in Cell Block 1-0-7.
This is for you to wear
when the winds are blowing west.
-Radiation from the...
-Yeah, I get it.
Thank you.
Well... I guess I'll be going.
I got a lot of painting
to catch up on.
Actually...
maybe I can start
painting right here.
Shouldn't need more
than a few coats.
And I don't think the smell
will be that bad.
As a matter of fact,
in a few weeks there'll hardly
be any smell at all.
This... is me in my prime.
Mmm, very studly.
And this one was taken
many years back.
As you can see,
I hadn't quite mastered
the jungle gym.
[laughs]
Well I hope your parents
had insurance.
Speaking of which...
here are my illustrious parents.
I hadn't informed them
I was gay until I found out
I had AIDS.
I wasn't sure which piece of
news would be more devastating,
the fact that I was gay,
or the fact that I was dying.
But since they
have yet to visit I'm fairly
certain of the answer.
[turns page]
And these...
are some of my conquests.
[laughs]
They look like nice guys.
Girlfriend, is there something
you should be telling me?
Hey, who's she?
I had girlfriends too...
once upon a time.
I always had an advantage
when it came to getting women.
Huh, and what's that?
I'm scared to ask.
I was completely irresistible
to the feminine species,
because I was
so easy to talk to.
Just... one of the girls.
Here's another one
who finds me irresistible,
right Boopsy?
[Stevie laughs]
[turns page]
-Here's your meds.
-A nurse usually brings them.
Are you using this med-thing
as an excuse to come in here
to make sure we're not fighting?
Or couldn't you survive another
moment without sneaking a peak
at my incredible physique?
[instrumental ♪"yesterday" ♪
Will these steroids
really make me run faster coach?
Thirsty?
[Stevie mumbles]
How about you, Kommandant?
A pleasure as always.
[footsteps]
Deep down you've got
quite the crush, huh?
Huh? For her?
No way!
Uh-huh!
I think it's time
for lecture number 42...
"Sexual partners and the art
of obtaining one" or,
in your case...
"How to get a girl whose IQ
is larger than her breast size".
I've often thought about
writing a book on the subject,
but that just seems to be
one more thing
we never have time for.
Chapter One states,
"You must never approach
a potential partner... sorry...
an immature 16 year old
when you're with
a group of friends".
I'd never gotten anywhere
when I was with friends
and I'm sure you haven't either.
Once in 200 times doesn't count.
Sample question number one,
"when a young lady passes,
what do you do?"
I know your answer.
You eye her like a wolf and,
if she eyed you back which
she won't, you pounce on her.
Chapter One states
you must never, never, never
approach a young lady first.
Let her notice you.
Let her check you out.
Then, as she passes
you look at her and smile
and your smile
is not one of a wolf, but one
that shows that you are the
sweetest most loving human being
on the face of the planet.
And if she eyes you back,
you'd better have the cojones
to walk up and talk with her.
That's it?
No, that's Chapter One.
I don't if you've ever
seen a book, but there's usually
more than one chapter.
Chapter Two states
you must ask lots of questions,
get a woman
talking about herself
and you'll be
in her pants before dinner.
Yeah, but what if she doesn't
want to talk about herself?
Then she's probably
not worth talking to
unless you're into
unadulterated carnal sex
which I'm sure
you're much too mature for.
What else
does your book have in it?
Oh, there's infinitely more
but I can only cram
so much into your tiny skull
at one time.
[Stevie] Hello.
Yes?
I was just
stopping by to say hi.
So, how're you doing?
Fine.
Catching up with some paperwork?
Trying to...
Stevie, what is it
I can help you with?
Nothing.
Um, I was just seeing
how you're doing.
So, what else do you do
when you're not working?
I go to school,
three nights a week
at San Francisco State.
[quiet music]
What's your major?
Liberal Studies.
Liberal Studies...
What can you do with that?
I think I'd like to teach.
I'm not sure
if I'd like to teach children
or at the adult level
but I still
have a couple of years
to figure that out.
But right now, Stevie,
I really have to
get back to work.
-Okay.
[Stevie]
So what are you working on?
I really
have to get back to work.
Okay.
[Stevie]
What's in Chapter Three?
It is time
for the moment of truth.
My only fear
is this puppy will fly so far,
we'll never be able to find it.
[uneven mechanical sounds]
Well, let's see.
Back to things
of real importance.
Girl trouble.
Chapter Three states
that you must prove yourself
to be the sensitive kind.
How do I pull that off?
Open yourself up to her.
Reveal some hidden
part of yourself.
Let her in
on something personal.
- Like what?
- You tell me.
[sighs] I don't know.
Remember when
you told me about the incident
with the gay bartender?
I didn't necessarily agree
with your take on the event
but the fact that you tried
to understand your feelings
was beautiful.
Yes, uhuh.
I'll look up that information
and get back to you.
[Sonya] Okay, thank you.
Bye-bye.
I thought you went home already.
No, I was just reflecting.
[phone rings]
Excuse me.
[Sonya] Wilkes hospice?
Oh, that'd be great!
You can come visit him
any time you'd like.
Sure!
Okay, bye-bye.
I need to see
the files for Alex O'Neill.
[shuffling through files]
-What is it
I can help you with, Stevie?
-I can wait.
[shuffling through files]
Thank you very much.
I just wanted
to tell you something.
It's not
all that important or anything.
It's just that...
When I was a kid
I used to have this--
Hey Sonya. Any messages?
No, sorry.
I swear if his girlfriend
doesn't call every 10 minutes,
he thinks something's wrong.
OK, what were you saying?
Oh,
just that I had this neighbor
that nobody liked, all right?
She was this old lady
and everyone thought of her
as some kind of witch.
Hey!
Well, anyway,
my neighbor, she never talked
to anyone, right?
And one day
when me and a couple of buddies
were playing
football in the street,
the ball got thrown
into her front yard.
- I went to get it--
- Thanks, Sonya.
Good luck.
Well,
I didn't want
to go near the house.
It kinda gave me the creeps,
you know what I'm saying?
[sighs]
But I had to, so...
Just as I'm
reaching for the ball,
the old lady appears.
[gasps]
I thought she was
going to bite me or something
but she said,
"I hope one day I'll see you
playing for the 49ers."
And she said it
so sweetly, you know?
I realized all those rumors
about her being a witch
were just a bunch of bullsh--
Well, they weren't true.
She died a couple weeks later.
[sighs]
I think I was the only one
on my block to know
that she was actually
a very sweet old lady.
[soft music]
[sniff]
[soft music continues]
I'll make you a deal, Stevie.
If you stop telling me
these stories
and asking me questions
and allow me to work
maybe afterward
we can go get a bite to eat.
After work?
I know of a place we can go.
Just a friendly meal, right?
[exciting upbeat music]
[Billy] Here you are, gorgeous.
How's everything going, Billy?
Well, my work is killing me.
It takes them about two hours
to slice a bag of carrots.
So who's this?
Your little cousin?
[Sonya]
No, this is my friend Stevie.
Stevie, Billy.
A pleasure, I'm sure. Huh?
[Billy and Sonya laughing]
So, what else can I get you?
Um, how about a bran muffin
and a shot of your wheat-grass.
[Billy] You too, huh?
No, thanks.
[Billy] I'll tell you what,
I'll make you one on the house.
Ooh, great.
Great!
[upbeat music continues]
[Sonya] I used to feel
the same way as you,
but I got so tired of Billy
pestering me all the time
that I just gave in.
[upbeat music continues]
Hey, what is this?
Carrot and spinach
and I have them throw in
a little protein powder.
[upbeat music continues]
Here you go,
fresh from my garden.
[Sonya] Thanks, Billy.
[upbeat music continues]
[coughs]
Oh, hey,
it's kind of an acquired taste,
huh?
You have to drink
about five or six of them
to get used to it.
Hey, line them up!
You know what, Stevie?
I like you.
I think I'll kill you last!
[laughs]
Hey, come on
with a cappuccino already, huh?
I've shown them ten times
how to make a cup of coffee.
What could be so difficult?
So, now that you've had it,
do you feel any extra energy?
I feel an upset stomach.
Anyway,
so how come you work
at the hospice?
I mean,
it seems to me like
you get kind of depressed
in knowing
everyone you're working with
is going to die.
I'll be sure
to tell Will you said that.
You know what I mean.
So...
Well, why do you work there?
I mean, did you want to,
or was it the only job
you could get?
[quiet music]
My, uhh...
My older sister's gay.
She...
She came out of the closet
when I was 16.
When she told me
my mature response
was to just run
right out of the house.
I'm so stupid.
[soft sad music]
I didn't come home for two days.
And when I returned
I didn't apologize.
I only came home
because I had stayed out
in the cold the night before
and I couldn't bear
to do it a second night.
I didn't realize
how much I was hurting her
until...
One morning
I woke up and she was gone.
She just moved out.
[soft sad music continues]
She didn't tell anybody
where she was going. I...
I ended up later
finding out through a friend
where she was living.
And I begged her to forgive me
which she did immediately.
But, um...
I don't think...
You see...
I haven't forgiven myself.
[sad music continues]
How're you doing, beautiful?
[soft music]
Son,
we all have things in our past
that we're not too proud of.
Stevie?
Hey, what's going on, Mark?
How much?
Oh, Sonya, this is Mark.
What are you doing here, man?
Just having a juice.
And hey, it looks
kinda awful but you know
it's actually pretty good.
You want some?
So,
we're going to get together
tonight or what?
No. No, I mean, uh...
I don't know. Maybe.
So, hey,
how's your hospital time going?
Well, today was my last day!
And to celebrate they had me
scrub the garbage cans
down the back.
Most of the times
I was just fucking around
with the hose, you know?
Spraying the cars that went by.
Sounds exciting.
Yeah, well.
I'm gonna get going.
All right.
Um, I'll give you a buzz later.
Yeah.
Later.
Stevie,
we all have stuff in our past
that we're not too proud of.
I can...
contain my emotions
during the day
even hide them from myself
but night proves me a liar.
I can't remember the last time
I had a decent night of sleep.
I try reading
or distracting myself
with a movie
and sometimes
I'm lucky enough to fall asleep
while I'm watching.
But my mind
wakes me in a few hours
and gives me a reality check.
I lie awake for hours
oddly depressed.
[tender music]
It's not just my ailment
that keeps me awake, mind you.
What else?
Love, sex, flesh on flesh,
human contact.
Those goldfish
just don't cut it.
And knowing
that I'll never have sex again.
My memories,
and I have quite a few
have at times kept me content.
Especially when I remember
someone that I've completely
forgotten about.
It's like
reliving the experience.
Almost.
[tender music continues]
Mmm, I remember the night
like the Fruit Loop.
Club-hopping.
I used to walk into a nightclub
feeling like I own the place
the dim colored lights,
the pumping music
flirting my little ass off.
You went to clubs.
I thought you'd be
too mature to go looking
for unadulterated carnal sex.
That is a fringe benefit
of being on one's death bed.
I have suddenly
become a man of wisdom,
a man of great morals
one deserved of respect.
Even if I was
nothing but a tail-chaser.
On those occasions
when I'd meet someone
and we'd dance...
It's kind of
like your first kiss.
You never know how the person's
going to respond to you
on the dance floor.
Will they keep you
at a distance?
Will they
dance close
so they'd brush up against you?
Will they turn around
and stick their butt
in your groin?
I was almost always surprised
by my partner's responses
and that element of not knowing
was so fucking thrilling.
[tender music continues]
And if it weren't
for the nightclubs
I wouldn't be where I am today.
If it just weren't for
the damned night my loneliness
wouldn't be so bad.
[sighs] Sometimes
I dread the night so much
I turn on all the lights and try
to stay awake as long as I can.
I'd even beat the night
a couple of times,
but not sleeping
just turning myself
into a zombie of late-night TV.
But the night always wins
in the long run.
The night always wins.
[sighs]
[doorbell rings]
[door opens]
- Yes?
- How're you doing? Um...
My name's Stevie.
I work with, Will...
I'm a friend of your son, Will.
Will hasn't asked me
to come or anything.
It's just,
he's talked about
you guys sometimes.
I think he'd really like you
to come visit.
I appreciate your concern.
Wait, wait, wait,
Mr. Hawthorne,
he needs help with a toy.
Will's trying
to make this unicorn
and he can't get it to fly.
[door closing]
[Latin dance music]
[knocking on door]
Hey Stevie.
Are you going to church?
Well,
I figured there was one place
you never went.
[door closing]
And so it is.
[loud dance music]
So,
you want a beer or something?
No, I don't drink.
No?
Oh, I love this song.
♪ Oh baby, don't go away ♪
So, I don't dance.
So, then it's time you do.
[romantic music]
[romantic music continues]
Relax, Stevie.
♪ Please, don't go away ♪
Don't worry about the crowd.
[romantic music continues]
Remember me?
I'm sorry, Stevie.
I guess I kinda got lost
in the music.
That's cool. You know,
I never would have thought
the girl behind the desk
could dance like that.
And I'm just getting warmed up.
♪ Makes me stop, makes me think
How your love turns me on ♪
♪ Ooh, baby. Every time ♪
Two Cokes, please.
Oh, I left my money
in the coat check.
One Coke, please.
That's cool.
Don't worry, I'll get it.
[dance music continues]
That'll be three dollars,
please.
[dance music continues]
There you go.
Thank you.
Thanks.
[dance music continues]
I bet I can point out the guys
who came with their girlfriends
from the guys
who just met a girl here.
See, the guys who came
with their girlfriends
are much more laid back.
Just look at them.
They're not dancing,
they're just checking out
other girls.
And the guys
who just met a girl here
are all over them
hanging on the girl's every word
buying them drinks,
always trying
to make them laugh.
See how close
they can get to them
on the dance floor.
[music continues]
Oh God, what if this...
What if this is all
a metaphor of marriage?
Everything being roses at first.
But then the rose wilts.
And the petals fall off.
And all you're left with
is a stem.
And a few thorns
that you never even knew
were there.
[music continues]
I think I need a dance.
Well, I don't want to. That way,
if we ever go to a club again
and I don't want to dance
you won't be able to say
I'm turning into a thorny stem.
Because you already are one?
[music continues]
Thanks for a wonderful night,
Stevie.
[quiet music]
It's getting late,
I'd better be getting in.
We both have to be
at the hospice in a few hours.
[quiet music continues]
Well...
Goodnight.
Son, um...
See you in a few hours.
[quiet music continues]
When's the last time
you've done this?
Done what?
Been out on a date
and not made a move.
Not for a long time...
if ever.
[romantic music]
I'd get out of here
before I ruin the night
and get myself slapped.
[romantic music continues]
[Sonya]
Oh, and by the way...
You wouldn't
have gotten slapped.
[door closing]
[upbeat music]
[upbeat music continues]
Oh, my, my!
Look what the cat dragged in.
So,
I take it your date
went pretty well, then?
Who told you I had a date?
Don't play coy with me,
young man.
You should know by now
there are no secrets in here.
So tell me.
Did you kiss her?
Did you kiss her twice?
Did you see
what color panties she wore?
Details, Stevie!
I need details!
Gentlemen don't kiss and tell.
Gentlemen, are we now?
That means
you didn't get a kiss goodnight.
Not to worry.
Chapter Four states
it is usually better
in the long run
if you don't do anything
in the short run.
What is with the two of you?
Girlfriend,
wouldn't you like to know?
Well.
I see my flaming buoyancy
no longer embarrasses you
to the point
of having to leave the room.
So, the only thing left is
for us to be friends.
Hi, I'm James.
Stevie.
[Will]
Oh, now isn't that precious.
[chuckling]
Ohhh.
You are both in
for a special treat.
I've made
a few minor adjustments.
And it is now time
to demonstrate
the ultimate flying machine!
[uneven mechanical sounds]
[Will's father]
Let's have a look.
Good workmanship.
[uneven mechanical sound]
Mmm,
I think with a longer string
we should be able
to get this up and running.
That should about do it.
[uplifting music]
[whirring sound]
[inspirational music]
Hey girls.
[upbeat music]
[ominous dramatic music]
What happened to Carlos?
Did he move out of his room?
Carlos died Stevie. I'm sorry.
I thought you knew.
[door closing]
It's not your fault, Stevie.
Carlos was very sick.
It's Ok.
[sighing deeply and sobs]
You know...
The only thing I keep
thinking about is the look
on his face when I left.
I was probably
one of his last visitors.
And I treated him like shit.
[sobbing]
Well, goodbye, son.
The boy has become a man.
And I don't mean
in a sexual sense.
You have come of age.
No longer are you
some foul-mouthed
brain-dead teenager.
You have developed
into a caring, inquisitive
young man.
From this day forward,
you shall no longer
be called Stevie.
From now on,
you shall be known as Steven.
Steven.
You know,
I never liked
the sound of that before.
But from this day forth
I think I shall hear it
in a different light.
Don't get carried away
on me, Steven.
If I act grandiose,
it's fairly amusing.
If we both act grandiose,
we sound like babbling idiots.
Well, I guess this young man
has much to learn, huh?
Mmm, who doesn't?
Next.
Hi, I'd like to register
for next semester.
OK,
you need to
fill out these forms,
bring them back to me
and then you have to go upstairs
and take the placement tests.
Next.
The tests aren't pass or fail
they're just to determine
what level you should start at.
Thanks.
So how'd it go?
Put it this way.
I think all my classmates
will be foreign students
who don't speak any English.
[laughing together]
No, I'm kidding.
Come on, let's get out of here.
[exciting music]
Oh, oh, look at that.
Look at that.
Seeing something?
Hey!
Hey, how's it going?
[laughing] Man,
do you expect to get anywhere
with a line like that?
[door opening]
[door closing]
[quiet music]
I always thought
when death crept closer that
other things
would lose their importance
Prejudice
Poli-tricks...
World atrocities...
I thought I would see
that none of it
was of real significance.
That life was the only thing
of consequence.
But it seems so vivid.
It matters more than ever,
because
I've used up my chance
to do anything about them.
It might seem absurd,
but my goal when I died
was to have two lines
on my tombstone.
But not everyone
deserves a second line.
A line that tells
of their accomplishments.
One that proves,
after all, it's written in stone
that you served a purpose
on this planet.
But I haven't
eliminated nuclear weapons,
haven't brought about
world peace,
haven't organized a relief fund
to end world hunger,
I've made a couple of toys
that are not that original.
I always wanted
that second line.
Now I know I'll never have it.
You know, Will... sometimes
you can be so full of shit.
I mean you have a second line.
You made toys.
And you've also...
-You've made a difference
in my life.
-[Will] Wait.
Is there a soap opera on?
Well, you have. I mean...
Think I would have
enrolled in school?
You're killing me.
"Would have" enrolled in school,
not "would've" enrolled in.
You've mangled
the English language
time and time again.
I'd die happy if just once
you spoke correctly.
You think I would have Sonya
as my girlfriend?
Girlfriend, is she now?
And it's "do you think I would
have Sonya as my girlfriend?"
You never speak
in a complete sentence.
It's always
these choppy, unintelligible
improper sentences.
[quiet music continues]
Cat got your tongue?
Yes, I guess I am
partially responsible
for the upgrading
of your once-miserable life.
[coughs]
So, does this mean
you'll no longer participate
in another fag-bashing?
Well, what do you know?
In one fell swoop
I've managed to end prejudice
and create world peace.
I guess a "thank you"
is in order.
[quiet music continues]
[sighs]
Thank you, Will.
You've taught me a lot and
made me a much better person.
I think I can now live
a much fuller, enriching life.
Don't mention it.
And now leave me
so I can catch up
on my beauty rest.
[quiet music continues]
Mmm.
I think for the first time
in a long time I'm going to get
a good night's sleep.
It'll disprove
one of my theories.
But what the hell.
The night doesn't always win.
[sad saxophone music]
[Stevie] I was able
to convince his parents
to bury Will
next to a tree
in their back yard.
It's slightly against the law.
But so was Will's sexual
preference in 37 states.
I wasn't able
to persuade them into forgetting
about the coffin.
[sad music continues]
You see, Will would say
that his coffin was the waste
of a perfectly good tree.
Maybe I can plant a tree out
here to make up for it.
Or maybe I'll plant one
when I have my own back yard.
Who knows?
Maybe I'll never have a back
yard and forget all about Will.
But I prefer to think that I'll
remember to plant that tree.
And maybe, when the time comes
I'll ask to be buried
next to that tree.
[sad music continues]