[music playing]
[chanting in distance]
[crickets]
[horse neighing]
-Whoo!
(LAUGHING) Sweet!
-Mighty hunter.
[cackling]
-Did you see the rack?
-Your license is for
a cow elk, right?
-Yeah.
Yeah, it is.
-Looks like you got a
little over-anxious.
-(LAUGHING) That's a crying
shame is what that is.
-Well, let's just-- let's
just-- we'll back up the truck,
and we'll haul it out of here.
-Oh, you don't want to do that.
That's a $3,000 fine, at least.
-We-- we can't
just leave it here.
[animal grunts]
-(ALL) Whoa!
[elk sounds]
[laughing]
-Bravo, Saul!
It's a miracle!
[laughing]
-(LAUGHING) Whoa.
Hey.
Hey, what are you doing?
-He's gonna die sooner or later.
I'm not gonna let it suffer.
-Well, let it go!
(LAUGHING) We're not waiting!
[crow cawing]
[dark music]
[rumbling]
[eerie music]
[whispering]
-Bo?
Clacker?
[whispering intensifies]
[rustling]
[music intensifying]
[whispering]
[shouts]
[panting]
[screams]
[music playing]
-Look, I'm, eh, very, very
sorry about your mother.
-I don't see why we had to go
to this dumb funeral anyway.
--[sighs] Well, unfortunately,
without any known relatives,
we can't keep you together.
So after we pick up your things,
I'll be dropping Brock off
at, uh, Mr. and Mrs. Fliegal's.
And Kerra, I'm
afraid you're going
to have to spend the
night at the Center.
-We don't need anyone else.
I can take care of Brock.
I've been taking care of him.
-The law is clear, Kerra.
You're not old enough
to be his guardian.
And considering the
matter your mother died--
-I don't do drugs, Mr. Paulson.
That was my mother, not me.
-It's the environment.
And where Brock already
has a juvenile record--
-Then we'll move.
I'll get a job.
-I'm not sure you're
ready for any of that.
-We won't be separated.
Please, I'm begging you.
-And you really
have, eh, no idea
how to contact your father.
-Father left when I was five.
Brock doesn't even remember it.
-Well, I'm sorry, Kerra.
Maybe-- maybe in the
future we can arrange
for a-- a permanent
household together.
-Can you guarantee that?
[car door shuts]
[electronic music]
-Hey, Kerra!
[whistles] [laughing]
-We'll probably
be a little while,
so just meet us back here later.
-All right, I will
give you, uh, one hour.
Be ready.
[car door shuts]
-Let's go.
-Where are we going?
-Does it matter?
-I don't want to go.
-You're going.
-But all my friends are here.
-Don't you get it?
You're going to a foster home.
You're not going to see
them any way, or me.
Is that what you want,
for them to separate us?
Cause that's what'll
happen, maybe forever.
-I hate them.
-Fill it.
[strains]
-Mom's old Taurus-- just
pray it still isn't stolen.
We're gonna end up on
opposite sides of the map
where nobody cares, trust me.
Consider us wards
of the state now.
And mom doesn't have
much of anything.
I have a whopping
total of $87.40.
-What are you doing here, Spree?
My sister will freak.
-I got news, Brock.
I'm quitting the gang.
-Quitting?
-Yeah.
-You and I are brothers, right?
-Yeah, sure, Spree.
I--
-OK, because I need you to
take care of something for me.
-Oh-- OK, well, what's in it?
-Never mind.
And no peaking, got it?
-Sure, Spree.
But, I mean, we're--
we're leaving tonight.
-Where?
-I-- I don't know,
some place out of town.
-Perfect.
KERRA: Will you eat deviled ham?
-No.
-(UNDER HER BREATH)
Yes, you will.
-OK.
-You just call me when you
get to wherever you're going.
-Right, but I don't know when--
-Hey, that doesn't matter.
OK?
You just call me.
-OK, yeah.
-Hey, Kerra.
-How'd you get in here?
-Well, I just--
-You broke into my house?
-I was just saying
goodbye to the kid.
-Get out.
-All right, I'm going.
-Now!
-No goodbye kiss?
BROCK: Hey, I'll call ya.
-No, he won't.
NEIGHBOR: Hey!
Shut up down there!
-Don't ever talk to
my brother again.
-I told you she wasn't
making payments.
-What are we supposed to do now?
BROCK: Hide!
-(WHISPERING) We need to go.
-(WHISPERING) Wait a second.
(LAUGHING) Oh, this
is too hilarious.
-(WHISPERING) Where are you--
[door clicks]
-What are you doing?
-You want to get
out of here, right?
[car starts]
Now, get in.
-Move over.
-(LAUGHING) I don't
think that you'd-- I
didn't think you
had it in you, sis.
So proud.
Think I might start to cry.
-(WHISPERING) Quiet.
I'm not proud at all.
[squeeling tires]
-Oh no, not now.
-Well, look who's here.
Check it out, man.
[laughing]
That's a tight ride, Kerra.
Yours?
-Get out of our way, Hitch.
-What's your problem, honey?
What are you always
tripping for?
Yo, Brock.
What up, ese?
-Nothing, Hitch.
-Where's your flag, holmes?
-Wrapped away-- pack.
-[tsks] That's your symbol, ese.
Should be flashing it proud.
-Move your funeral
wagon, please.
-You rolling out, out Hm?
Going on a trip?
-As long as it's away from you.
-Hey, you seen Spree?
-No, Hitch.
-Mm, you sure?
We've been looking
all over for him.
I need to talk to him.
I really do.
-You get your hands off my car.
[laughs]
-Always tripping, mami.
That's no way to be
talking to your guardian
angel, such a pretty thing.
Sometime you may be needing
a little protection.
-Don't!
-Hey!
I touch what I want when I want.
You're in my
neighborhood now, mami.
OK?
Ah!
GANG MEMBER (COCKING
GUN): Lemme cap em!
-Oy!
Hey!
BROCK (LAUGHING): I can't
believe you did that.
[music playing]
Are you gonna tell me
where we're going now?
-Utah.
-Utah?
What's in Utah?
-Relatives.
-I thought you said we
didn't have any relatives.
-Yeah, well, these are
from-- from our dad's side
of the family.
-Our dad's side?
-I haven't seen em since
I was like five or six.
-You've got to be kidding.
Why in the--
-Don't use that
kind of language.
[sigh] It's just a visit.
It's not permanent.
Besides, they
might even help us.
-Help us how?
And besides, you use that
language all the time.
-Not anymore.
-Since when?
-Since I started
taking care of you.
-Don't say it.
-I wasn't.
-Don't say it!
-I wasn't!
-How can these people help us?
I've never even heard of them.
How come we've never met them?
-That's cause mom
didn't like them.
They're Mormons.
-Weird.
-Look, they're the only
relatives we've got,
and our only hope until I figure
out what we're going to do.
I don't want you
making fun of them.
-Me?
How could you think
I'd do such a thing?
[child giggling]
[flute music]
-So this is it?
-Yep, this is it.
-I've never seen a
town this small before.
You've got to be kidding me.
Are you sure you're not lost?
-I'm not lost.
BROCK: They grow on trees?
[car noises] What--
what was that?
-I don't know.
[brakes screeching]
BROCK: What's wrong?
-I thought I saw something.
BROCK: Saw what?
KERRA: I don't know.
-Bigfoot?
No, Sasquatch?
Oh, wait, I forgot,
Sasquatch is in California.
KID (SHOUTING): Someone's here!
Someone's here!
[door creeking]
[brakes screeching]
-Gracious.
Are you kids lost?
-Hello, Aunt Corrine.
I'm Kerra.
I'm your niece.
-Kerra?
Oh my word.
Oh my word, Kerra.
-Did she just say that
she was my cousin?
-Yeah, too bad for you.
[cat meowing]
-Um, our mom got a
new job in Florida,
so Brock and I are on our
way there to join her.
-You're traveling by yourselves?
-Sure, yeah.
I mean, we do it all the time.
-All the time.
-Well, that's just fine.
Looks like you'll
be a few days late.
I'll have Sklyar
look at your car.
If he can't fix it, we
may have to go into town.
-If I can't fix it,
nobody can fix it.
-When is your mother
expecting you?
-A few weeks.
-Weeks.
-A few weeks?
-Uh, days.
I meant days.
-Days.
-I see.
Well, tonight
you're staying here.
Skyler, why don't you help
bring in their luggage?
-Remember me, Natasha?
[laughs]
-I do remember you.
-How about me, Cherylynn?
-Cherylynn?
I think last time I saw
you, you were a baby.
-Why don't you girls show
Kerra where she'll be sleeping.
I'll go get your uncle
from the orchard.
Tessa, you watch
the banana bread.
Kolter, Soriah, get
the cats off the table.
Come on, baby girl.
Let's go get daddy.
[baby mumbling]
Yes, we get the cats
off the table, huh?
[meows]
-Where do you want it?
-Oh, here, she can have my bed.
-Oh, no, that's all right.
I'm fine over here.
[giggling] Sure
got bigger since I
saw you last, Skyler.
-Yeah, so have you.
Hey, I got a friend that
would really like to meet you.
In fact, I've got
a lot of friends
that would probably like to--
-Oh, not now.
--meet you.
But--
[laughing]
Oh, Kerra.
Mmm.
I can't believe you're here.
You're so beautiful.
-Oh, that is not true.
-Oh, don't even,
-Do you have a
lot of boyfriends?
-No, no boyfriends.
-Oh, you have to tell us
everything about California.
-Do you know any movie stars?
-Hey, I'm asking the questions.
Do you know any movie stars?
-Afraid not, heh.
-Hey, do you still talk
to that Donnie kid?
-Who?
-Kid Donnie, your
imaginary friend.
Oh, that's what I
remember most about you.
You used to spend
hours talking to him.
-No, I made all that up.
-Well, duh.
It's not like I thought
you believed he was real.
-Like Donnie the kid?
Was he a cowboy?
-Uh, no, he was a boy, a
magical boy, right Kerra?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Did I make you uncomfortable?
-No, it's fine.
It's just-- it's just
been such a long time
since I thought
about any of that.
It used to make people upset.
-(LAUGHING) No way.
I thought it was wonderful.
It made me want my own imaginary
friend, someone to play with me
and protect me like yours did.
Meh, didn't really matter.
I got frightened anyway.
-Frightened?
What frightened you?
The usual.
Dark closets,
bumps in the night.
-The whistlers.
-Whistlers?
-Cherylynn, you don't know
what you're talking about.
You haven't heard a
whistler in your life.
-I have so.
-She's lying.
No one's heard them in
practically forever.
-No, no.
I remember, the whistlers.
It's been so long.
You really don't
hear them anymore?
--[sighs] No, not since
I was really little.
Mom doesn't like us
to talk about it.
-She says it scares
the little kids.
-She says it's the wind
blowing through the hollow
just right, like
holes in a flute.
-Yeah, but why did it stop?
-No one knows.
-So you heard them?
What did they sound like?
-You just said you'd heard them.
-Well, I did.
I was just-- OK, so I
never heard them, heh.
-Yeah, that's what I thought.
-Sometimes at night or--
or in the early morning,
I'd hear, like,
whispers or a humming.
-Grandpa Lee says the
hollow is full of ghosts.
-Cherylynn-- great, five minutes
in this house and she already
thinks we're a bunch of wackos.
-I used to play
in those woods all
the time when I
was a little girl.
I remember it like
it was yesterday.
-Heh, that's amazing,
because none of us
will play in there for anything.
Are you sure you've never
seen any movie stars?
-You have a Slifer
the Sky Dragon?
-It came in the original pack.
My mom only bought me one.
-One pack?
And it had this?
-Is it a good one?
-Oh, well, uh, n--
not-- not really.
I mean-- I have better ones.
Maybe later we could,
uh-- make a trade?
SORIAH: Daddy!
Daddy!
-Well, hello--
-I am Soriah.
-Oh, yes.
Soriah, my little one.
Oh, I love you.
-I love you, I love
you, I love you, too.
-Oh-- [laughs]
-I'm Tessa.
-Tessa!
Hello!
-Honey, this is Brock.
-Brock, my boy!
How are ya?
-No, honey, Brock's your nephew.
He's, uh, Chris's boy.
Chris and Delia.
You remember Delia,
from California?
-Delia, of course.
[bell rings] Is that
banana bread I smell?
TESSA: I left the other loaf
in because this one came out
doughy.
-Kerra's here, dad!
-Oh, well, hello, Kerra.
-Hello, Uncle Drew.
-Kerra is Brock's sister.
She's your niece.
-Well, that's wonderful!
Welcome!
Are you staying for dinner?
-They're both
staying for dinner.
They're both staying
for a couple of days.
-Oh, fantastic.
Mi casa es su casa.
That's Spanish.
Do you know what that means?
-Yeah, actually.
-It means that my
house is your house.
Although, I'd
appreciate it if you--
-(DAUGHTER AND DAD)
left the family china.
[dad chuckles]
-(WHISPERING) What's
wrong with him?
-(WHISPERING) Later.
-(WHISPERING) It's
your turn, Soriah.
-Dear heavenly father,
thank you for this day,
for making my horsies
and my Barbies--
TESSA: Bless the food.
-Not yet.
And for Brock and--
what was her name?
TESSA (WHISPERING): Kerra.
-and for Kerra.
Hope they visit us again.
Hope that we can set a good
example like mommy says.
Hope their car gets better.
Hope that we don't
find out they're
in trouble with the law.
And bless the food by the
name of Jesus Christ, amen.
-(ALL) Amen.
-Pass the cucumbers, please.
Thank you.
-I can't take it, Kerra.
What's wrong with these people?
What's wrong with the Dad?
-Uncle Drew was injured, same
summer our parents split up.
It was an accident
in a machine shop.
A metal rod hit him, something--
-So is he like a zombie?
-(LAUGHING) Of course not.
He still runs a big farm.
Peaches, almonds, watermelon--
it just affected his memory.
-I think it's weird,
wigged-out, schizoid.
This whole family is schizoid.
-Don't sweat it.
We won't stay long.
-They know something's up.
They'll turn us in.
-I don't think so.
And besides, we've got
nowhere else to go.
-I'll steal another car.
-No.
No more of that, ever.
-I want to go home.
-To what, Brock?
There's nothing for us there.
-Ah, I guess we should
call their mother.
-Who?
Call whose mother?
-Kerra and Brock's.
They say she doesn't
have a phone yet.
Even if I could call her--
-What do you mean?
Why couldn't you?
-I don't know, I-- I don't
want to muddy the waters.
I want to enjoy my niece
and nephew while I can.
-You still blame her, don't you?
-I guess I do.
I do blame Delia.
My brother didn't
abandon his family.
You know that.
-Well, Corrine, we
never had any proof.
-She did it, Drew.
Or if not, she knows who did.
She got away with murder.
All these years--
[music playing]
[birds chirping]
[chimes]
[laughter]
-A lot has changed.
10 years ago a flash
flood washed through here.
That's when it stopped.
-You're Grandpa Lee.
-Yep.
And you must be, Sakura,
the little girl who
used to live in these woods
like a woodland fairy princess.
-You frightened me.
-(LAUGHIN) Oh, I do that a lot.
Your grandmother told me I did
that to her all of the time.
God rest her.
I was coming down the driveway.
I saw you enter the woods.
I figured this was
where you were headed.
-No one's called me
Sakura in forever.
-Ah, your father named you that.
Little cherry blossom,
Japanese, I think.
-So how did you know this
is where I'd be headed?
-'Cause I was
usually the one that
was sent out to search for you.
And I found you
here more than once.
-What did you mean,
that's when it stopped?
What stopped?
-Oh, the sound of the whistlers,
the shadows that flicked,
scurried through the woods,
voices and spirits of the dead.
Floods a few years
back must have
thrown things out
of kilter some how.
-I don't understand.
-That's cause I'm trying to make
it sound as spooky as I can.
How am I doing?
[shrieks]
[laughing]
-I remember sitting here for
hours when I was a little girl,
watching you carve your
violins or mixing up your,
uh, secret recipes
for amber varnish.
-I've got something to show you.
My master creation.
I did it!
The great ones would be so
proud, Veneri, Amati, even old
Stradivarius.
That's his varnish, lost
to the world for 300 years!
Want to know the secret?
-What?
-(WHISPERING) Look
right-- right here.
-"Holiness To The Lord."
-Heh, just giving credit
where credit is due.
[violin music]
-That's beautiful.
-Think so?
-One of the most beautiful
sounds I've ever heard.
-Most folks would say
it's just another violin.
But you, Kerra,
you have the gift.
You always did, even
when you were little.
You could hear things, feel
things few others could.
And it's that gift that
draws you into those woods.
-You think I'm drawn
there because of a gift?
-These woods are a very special
place, an ancient place.
The Indians knew it.
They were still coming here
to pray when I was a kid.
[sighs]
I can't explain it.
Maybe it's the fault line
that runs through here,
or a combination of things.
But it's all pulled
together right there,
everything that's ever
happened on this continent--
history, voices--
Prophets have said this land
was once home to a noble people.
[scoffs]
But you can feel it, too, right?
You can feel their presence
like echoes in time.
Ooh, sometimes I
can feel it, too.
-I'd better be going.
Thanks for the cocoa.
[door opens]
It is beautiful.
-Sometimes I can feel it, too.
Senile old buzzard--
[grunts]
-He's not in here.
Where you going, Spree!?
-(STRUGGLING) Come here!
-Where you going?
-Come on.
Stand up.
Hitch is here.
[chuckling]
-Hey.
-Where is it, holmes?
-Where's what?
What are you talking about?
-You must think I'm
pretty stupid, huh?
Hm?
Huh?
You think I'm stupid?
Huh!?
Well, you disappoint me.
You disappoint me.
[gun cocks]
[cackles]
-Hey, wait.
Wait, wait, Hitch, wait.
-You like that, vato?
-I gave it to the kid.
The kid's got it.
-Where's the kid?
-I don't know where the kid is!
-The kid is gone, huh!?
-He left town.
He's supposed to
call me any time.
I swear, he's
supposed to call me.
-When is he supposed
to call you?
-Any time, Hitch.
Hitch, Hitch, any time, Hitch.
-OK, you're going to
need a new alternator
and a new carburetor.
-Heh, maybe a respirator?
[laughs]
-What, is it expensive?
-(LAUGHING) Yeah.
[phone ringing]
-Hello?
PAULSON (ON PHONE):
Mrs. Whitman?
-Speaking.
PAULSON (ON PHONE): Uh,
my name is Carson Paulson.
I'm with the California
Welfare and Family Services.
We're looking for
your niece and nephew,
Kerra and Brock McConnell.
Your name wasn't
listed in their files,
but we did some digging and--
-Are they in trouble?
PAULSON (ON PHONE): Uh, yes.
I-- I'm afraid so.
They stole a car, Mrs.
Whitman, and, uh-- uh,
escaped our custody.
There's a-- there's
a warrant out.
Now, I know the
children are upset
since their mother's death.
But these are serious charges.
-Delia's dead?
PAULSON (ON PHONE): Y-- yes.
I-- oh, I'm sorry.
I thought sure you'd--
[sighs]
The children were in
the state's custody.
And I just hoped maybe you'd
seen or heard from them.
It-- it's possible that--
-I have to go.
PAULSON (ON PHONE):
Mrs. Whitman?
Mrs.--
[kids playing]
CORRINE: Hey.
-Thought he'd forgotten
how to be a kid.
-You probably haven't
had much of a chance
to be a kid yourself,
have you, Kerra?
-Just lucky, I guess, way things
work out, the way things are.
-But, you know,
with the way things
finally turnout-- we
all have a say in that.
We-- we do, God willing.
-I'm not very religious.
-Perhaps you just need
something worth believing in.
-My dad was a Mormon, right?
-Now, Kerra, you may have
been told a lot of things.
But your dad loved you.
He loved you so much.
-Aunt Corrine, I was
wondering if you, uh,
if you knew of any jobs,
for the summer I mean.
-Perhaps.
What about Florida?
-My mom's not quite settled in.
I'm sure it would be fine.
-Look, Kerra, I will help you.
Any-- any way I can, I'll be
there for you, I-- I will.
-Thanks.
[kids laughing]
-Where's Brock?
-Upstairs.
-I thought you two were playing?
-We were.
He won all my cards.
-He what?
-All my Yu-Gi-Oh!, all my
Pokemon, he won em all.
[sighs]
[snickering]
-Give them back.
-Give what back?
-You know very well
what I'm talking about.
I can't believe you took
advantage of your cousin.
-Oh, I was going to
give em back any way.
Here.
-Is this all?
-Yeah, practically.
-Don't lie to me.
Is this all or not?
-I'll-- I'll even throw
in one or two of mine.
-Is this all or isn't it?
-Hey, I won his cards,
fair and square.
I deserve to keep at least one.
-Give it-- Brock.
-Oof!
-Here--
[ripping]
-Look what you did!
-Now, give him one
of yours to replace
it, whichever one he chooses.
-I hate you!
I hate you!
[door slams]
[rumbling]
[glass breaking]
[screaming]
[gasps]
NATASHA: What was that?
CORRINE: Is everybody OK?
KERRA: Brock!
CORRINE: Skyler, Natasha,
check on all the kids.
I'll be right up there.
[match ignites]
[cranking sound]
NEWSCASTER (ON
RADIO): The epicenter,
as far as reports
seem to suggest,
was just northeast
of Leeds, Utah--
[whirring]
--15 miles north of St. George.
No damage has yet been reported.
This is the first time
we've had a quake in--
-No damage that I can see.
-We'll check it
again at first light.
NEWSCASTER (ON RADIO):
--once again, the earthquake
measured 4.9 on
the Richter scale.
-4.9?
Pff, that's nothing.
CHERYLYNN: Didn't
feel like nothing.
NATASHA: Northeast of Leeds,
that's almost right under us.
-A real earthquake?
That is so cool, heh.
NEWSCASTER (ON RADIO):
--the St. George area.
Power is reportedly
knocked out in Leeds, and--
[electricity buzzing]
[eerie whistling]
[unintelligble whispering]
KERRA: Whistlers.
[music playing]
[gasps]
[eerie whistling]
[panting]
-(WHISPERING) Ghost.
Not a ghost.
Kerra, get a hold of yourself.
Just a jerk, trespasser.
[scrambled voice]
-What are you doing here?
It's dangerous.
-You don't belong here.
This is private property.
-It's no one's property.
Who are you!?
-Corrine and Drew's niece.
-Who!?
-The McConnells, they
live right through there.
And if they knew
you were here, you'd
get a rear end full of buckshot.
-Right through where?
-(PANICKED) Look,
I won't ask again.
I'll just go back and
have them call the cops.
Come any closer and
I'll take your head off.
I'm warning you!
-Why are you dressed
so strangely?
-(SCOFFING) Have
you seen a mirror?
-What is your name?
What is your tribe?
-Look, look, I'm just
gonna go home now, OK?
I'll leave you here to
play your Aztec-- Apache--
-You're one of them, aren't you?
-One of them?
-A Gadianton!
Just like them to
send a woman spy.
-Look, I swear I don't know
what you're talking about.
-Then what is your tribe?
What is your name!?
-Sakura!
-Sakura?
It's me.
It's Kiddoni.
[waverly gasp]
Sakura!
[weeping]
[child laughing]
[crying]
-Never mind, Dad.
She just showed up.
Kerra?
Kerra, are you all right?
-(SNIFFLING) Yes, Aunt Corrine.
I'll be out in a minute.
-All right.
Breakfast is ready, eggs.
The quake didn't
crack a single one.
KERRA: I'll be right down.
[panting]
(WHISPERING) Kid Donnie.
Kiddoni.
NEWSCASTER (ON RADIO):
was in Silver Reef,
where one home
reported a new crack
in the driveway.
There are also reports of
broken glass shattered--
-I heard them when I woke up.
Why am I always the only one?
Did you hear them, Kerra?
Did you hear the whistlers?
-That's enough.
NEWSCASTER (ON RADIO): --a lot
of shaken-up people here in St.
George--
-After last night,
everybody's frightened enough
without stirring
up that nonsense.
-Where were you?
-I went for a walk.
-You weren't here when
Uncle Drew left for work.
I was worried.
-Sorry.
-Did you see any
cracks in the driveway?
-I didn't notice.
-But in the woods
there was this sort
of long crevice in the ground--
-Hey!
KIDS: It's Grandpa!
Grandpa!
-Look who's here.
-(LAUGHING) How is
my little Soriah?
Oh.
Just wanted to make sure
everyone is all right.
-We're fine.
Have you had breakfast, Dad?
-Oh, I don't mind if I do.
-Sit, here.
-Hey Grandpa, some geology
guys are coming today.
They think the epicenter
was right in the middle
of our hollow.
SKYLER: Yeah, they're
coming to survey the area.
-Wait, how do you know?
-They called 30 minutes ago.
-I have to go.
-W-- you haven't eaten.
-I'm sorry.
I'm-- I'm not hungry.
I'll be back.
[door closes]
[harp music playing]
-You're back.
It is you, isn't it, Sakura?
You've grown up.
I visited here 1,000 times
after you stopped coming.
Why?
Why did you stop coming?
-I moved away.
I-- I couldn't come.
-I chose this as my post,
this place in the wilderness,
hoping that someday you might--
that I might see you again.
-You're real.
(LAUGHING) I can't believe it.
I had decided that you didn't--
I stopped believing in you.
-My father used to say
that you were a demon.
But I told him only an angel
could be so kind and beautiful.
-Don't call me that.
I'm not an angel.
And you-- I still can't
believe you're here.
You meant everything
to me once, my friend,
my-- my secret friend in
the woods, my only friend.
I missed you so much.
When we were kids, I
never asked or even cared,
but now-- what are you, Kiddoni?
-I'm a Nephite, a warrior in
the army of Captain Gidgiddoni.
This is my outpost.
I watch for enemy spies.
-Enemy spies?
-Robbers of Gadianton.
They infest these mountains
and forests like vermin.
They are vermin.
My people have gathered
all their possessions
to Zarahemla in self-defence--
-To Zarahem--?
-Our capital.
You cannot mean you do not
know the great city of Z--
if not an angel, what are you?
-A girl.
Just a girl.
This is America, Utah.
Over there is a little
town called Leeds.
-There are no cities
that way, just
jungles and
mountains to the sea.
-There's no jungles here.
-Here?
-Here, where I am.
I don't understand.
I mean, we occupy
the same place.
But right here, this
spot of ground, it's
not the same for you and me.
It's like we're in two
different-- it's like--
-This is the wilderness of
Zarahemla, named for Zarahemla,
a descendant of Mulek, son of
Kind Zedekiah of Old Jerusalem,
who crossed the great
waters like Father Lehi,
to escape the great--
-Wait, what did you say?
-Which part?
-Old Jerusalem, your people
came here from Israel?
-Yes.
-You're from the past.
-From what?
-From the past, from a time and
place that hasn't existed for--
I don't know,
thousands of years.
-This is nonsense.
Why am I from the past?
Maybe you're from the past.
-No, sorry.
Why are you so sure?
-The things you said,
Old Jerusalem, Zarahemla.
How long ago did your
people cross the ocean?
-600 years.
-Wow.
Then that would make it--
-The six month of the
19th year since the sign
was given of the
birth of the messiah.
-What?
-You've never heard
of the messiah?
-No, I've heard of it.
It's just that I never
thought that it was actually--
-Kerra!
-It's all right!
It's my brother.
-He must keep his voice
down, or these entire woods
will be swarming
with Gadiantons.
-I'll go to him.
Actually, I just
came here to warn
you there's people coming here.
-Gadiantons?
-Heh, geologists.
People from my world.
They're-- Never mind.
Just stay away from here for
a little while, a day or two.
-I can't desert my post.
I will be reprimanded
or flogged.
-Then hide, please.
If they found you here,
there's no telling--
BROCK: Kerra!
-I have to go.
-Wait.
-You can't get through that way.
Go back.
-I'm stuck And who
were you talking to?
-No one.
Stay there.
I'm coming around.
-I know what I heard.
-No, you don't.
-Did you really
see someone, Kerra?
One of Grandpa's ghosts?
-No, th-- there's nobody.
All right?
Everybody just chill out.
-Grandpa, what's a Nephite?
-A descendant of Nephi.
Their tribe once lived
in ancient America.
Where did you hear that word?
-I don't remember exactly,
on TV or something.
-Well, Nephites were
a powerful nation.
They built cities
and ships, temples.
Their civilization
lasted 1,000 years.
-What happened to them?
-They were destroyed.
KERRA: By who?
-Lamanites,
descendants of Laman.
Nephi and Laman were brothers.
But they became bitter enemies.
The feud was carried
on by their children
and their children's children.
-But they lived.
-We're not sure.
Somewhere in this
hemisphere, but most
think Central or South America.
-But not here.
-You mean Utah?
Maybe some of them did.
We don't know for sure.
-Were there ever jungles here?
-(LAUGHING) Maybe 65
million years ago.
-Why haven't I ever
heard of these tribes?
-General Authority
Edition, 1888, first one
they ever broke down
into chapters and verses.
And if you're careful,
you're welcome to read it.
[music playing]
-I'm sorry, I shouldn't
have frightened you.
-I can feel you.
I don't understand.
-It's like before.
Sometimes I could touch you,
and sometimes I-- I couldn't.
-The rift must be widening.
It's getting stronger.
-So it appears, for now.
But if the earth rumbles
again, it may not remain.
What is that?
-A book about you, I think.
-Me?
-Your people.
-I can't read this.
What language is this?
-The same one you're speaking.
-I speak the same
language of my fathers.
-You speak English.
Or at least that's what I hear.
(LAUGHING) This is intense.
I have no i--
-Shh.
Come with me.
Now, tell me, what
is that place?
-(WHISPERING) Get down.
They might see you.
-It wasn't there yesterday.
-It's my aunt and
uncle's farmhouse.
Like I said, the rift
must be widening.
-I've been debating
whether I should attack it.
-Please don't.
-But it's right in the
path of the invasion.
-Excuse me?
-Oh, never mind.
No one believes me, anyway.
-Wait, is that all you see?
Don't you see any other houses?
My uncle's orchards?
-I see the hills of Gideon,
the wilderness of Hermounts.
-And over there?
-Forests and jungles.
Beyond is the great
city of Zarahemla.
-Stop!
You're there.
You're at the edge of the rift.
Ah!
It must take in most
of the valley now.
Let's go back.
-Before, when you were little,
you were always so sad.
Why?
-It was a sad time.
My parents divorced.
And then my father went away.
-Went away?
-It's not important.
-I understand.
My own parents were killed,
murdered by the same demons
that seek to destroy my people.
But I will fight
them, I will do all
I can to drive them from
the face of this earth.
-Wow.
That sounds heavy.
-You don't approve?
-I just don't think it
could be good for anyone
to feel so much hate.
-Hate?
No, this is a
struggle for survival.
-You know, no matter how
many of them you kill,
it won't bring them back.
It won't change anything.
-To do nothing is weakness.
I will change things.
I will defend my people.
-Look, that's not what I meant.
I'm-- wow, I'm sorry.
It's just-- nothing lasts,
especially things you love.
You can count on it.
-That sounds so lonely.
Do you believe in nothing?
-Not really.
Not much.
(LAUGHING) This is all so crazy.
It's not real.
You're not real.
It could all go
away in an instant.
-But it's here now.
We're here.
-I can't trust that.
I have to go.
They'll come looking.
-But you'll be back, yes?
-Maybe.
Yes.
-You see?
You still have some faith, then.
BROCK: This?
It's a cartoon.
-But it's cool!
-Eh.
Oh, man!
Yes, yes, I love this guy.
-It's rated R.
-So what?
We buy a ticket
for something else.
Then we do the old switcheroo.
-Nah.
If my mom caught
me, I'd be toast.
-All right, fine.
Let's just see this one.
-It's PG-13.
-So?
-I'm not 13.
-You've got to be kidding.
-My mom says for some movies
like that, I'll never be 13.
-That's child abuse.
Man, just forget it.
[mysterious music]
[crickets]
[dialing numbers]
-"And after the
messiah shall come,
there shall be signs given
unto my people of his birth,
and also of his death
and resurrection.
And great and terrible shall
that day be unto the wicked."
HITCH (ON PHONE): Hello?
-Uh, I need to talk to Spree.
HITCH (ON PHONE): He's not here.
He asked me to
take his messages.
[ratchet cranking]
-It's Brock.
He'll know who I am.
Just tell him to come
get me, right away.
HITCH (ON PHONE): Where are you?
-I'll give you directions.
Ready?
-"Behold I prophesy unto you
concerning the last days."
[stick breaks]
[low voice]
-Hello?
[door opens]
CORRINE: Skyler?
Do you have my good
dish towels out there?
-The rooster ones?
CORRINE: Yes.
-These are your good ones?
CORRINE: I want
them in here now.
In the wash, with bleach.
(UNDER HER BREATH)
Dangit, Skyler.
[sighs]
[door closes]
[corrine talking inside]
CORRINE: --his car in the mud.
-"And there are also
secret combinations,
even as in times
of old, according
to the combinations
of the devil.
For he is the foundation
of all these things."
-(LAUGHING) What a day.
KERRA: "Yea, the foundation of
murder and works of darkness."
CORRINE (INSIDE):
--and into next week
until I've decided that maybe
you will remember not to do
this to every dish
towel that I own.
KERRA: "And he leadeth them by
the neck with a flaxen cord."
SKYLER (INSIDE): I left
the one in the car.
CORRINE (INSIDE): You finish.
And then let's watch the movie
like the rest of the family
and take my shoes off
and enjoy myself--
-"Until he bindeth them with
these strong cords forever."
[screaming]
-Mom!
Mom!
Oh my god!
[screaming] Oh my god!
-Go see what is going on!
Honey, tell me
what's the matter.
What did you see?
[whimpering]
Honey, what happened?
-Don't see nothing there.
-They're gonna check it out.
Everything's OK.
[whimpering]
-She said his face was
painted red, like blood.
And he wore a helmet in
the shape of a skull.
-A Gadianton spy.
-Gadians?
I thought your
enemies were Lamanites
-Not in my lifetime.
Although, many
Gadiantons are Lamanites.
Nephites, too.
They're a secret society,
sorcerer's and murderers.
They swear bloody oaths,
hide their crimes,
and destroy anything
that threatens them.
Your people may not
understand such things.
-No, we understand,
unfortunately.
-Their numbers
increased in our lands
until they became too numerous.
Those who would
not join them were
forced to gather into one body.
Now, the armies
of the Gadiantons
are prepared to attack.
-The invasion?
-Yes.
Our generals say the attack
will come from the mountains,
just as Lamanite
armies of long ago.
But if you've seen a
spy, it's further proof
that I've been right all along.
They have to believe me now.
-And you're the only one
guarding this entire area?
-Of course not.
There are others I can
signal them with this.
But I'm the only one stationed
in this particular valley.
No one thinks it's
important, too
congested, and full of briers.
But that's exactly
it, it's an advantage.
If I were old
Giddianhi, I'd send my--
-Who?
-Their leader.
If I were Giddianhi,
I'd send my army
creeping right through here
under the cover of these trees.
-When would this happen?
-Some say next Spring.
I say sooner.
We burned our crops before
gathering to Zarahemla.
The Gadiantons are too
lazy to do honest work,
so they're starving.
They could attack at any moment.
I must tell my captain.
Sakura, you must
warn your family.
If there's trouble,
blow this with all
your wind and strength.
The lookout on the
next ridge will
hear it and sound
another warning.
Then another will sound
until the entire Nephite
army is alerted.
I won't be long.
-Grandpa Lee.
[mysterious music]
[animal sounds]
-Cool.
[crow cawing]
-Not a sound.
Not one.
-What is he?
-Unknown.
TRIBESMAN: A Nephite?
-Does he look like a Nephite?
-One of the children
of the fortress,
the one with the
lights and the music.
-Hold your tongue.
-What are you?
-What am I?
-Are you a spectre?
A devil child?
-Not the last time I looked.
-What are you
doing in the woods?
-Walking.
Who is-- Who's that?
-He's not important, a
slave awaiting death.
-What have you done to him?
-Same as we'll do to you.
-We're wasting time here.
Giddianhi will be coming
through here in the next--
-Silence, Makan!
Are you a complete idiot?
Speak in the tongue
of the Nehors!
-Forgive me, Lord Kush.
I will use the secret tongue.
Our army will pass through
here in a few hours.
The escaped slave
has been recaptured.
But the Nephite watchman lives.
We have to kill anyone
who might sound a warning.
-But the Nephite
is not at his post!
-This warrior has seen us!
Execute him!
And the slave, right now!
-I won't tell anybody
about the-- about the army.
I swear.
I--
-You understood us?
-How did he understand?
-A demon!
-Where did you learn the
tongue of the Nehors?
-I-- I can't say, really, I--
-Slay him.
Cut his throat.
-Can't kill a phantom.
-Watch me.
-Don't be a fool.
His body will be found here.
The Nephites will investigate.
The invasion will be revealed.
-He knows the secret language!
He's like the bearded slave!
A sorcerer of tongues.
-He's a child of the underworld.
-Giddianhi will decide.
-It's his, isn't it?
It belonged to my father.
Grandpa says you were with
him the day he disappeared.
-That's right.
[laughing] He shot a bull
elk without the proper license.
[sighs] I knew his life was a
mess, I-- like everybody else,
I just figured he'd had
enough of it all and took off.
-Didn't anybody search?
-We all searched, Kerra.
There was no sign
of him or the elk.
-But, Grandpa, you
said those woods
are a special place,
and ancient place.
What if my father didn't
leave Brock and me?
What if he crossed over
and couldn't get back?
What if he's been
there for 12 years?
-Kerra, listen to
what you're saying.
I know those woods are strange.
Unusual things happen, but--
-More unusual than you know.
-You guys are from that
green jungle place, right?
What-- what's your name?
-I-- I am Chris.
-Don't speak to him.
-This isn't right.
-Of course it's right,
same way we came.
Keep walking.
By all the gods,
what is happening!?
-I told you it was wrong.
BROCK (LAUGHING):
Are you guys lost?
-Silence!
The demon boy!
He did this!
He changed it!
-Where are we?
What have you done to us!?
-No!
Nothing!
Don't you get it?
You, like, passed
through a new dimension.
TRIBESMAN: We must find
Giddianhi and his army!
-Leeds.
-What'd you say?
-Utah.
TRIBESMAN: What are these words?
What is down there!?
-Nothing.
People, houses.
BROCK: Have you been there?
TRIBESMAN: Is there food?
-Yes!
Yes!
There's lots of it!
-Then you will take us.
-I know it sounds insane.
But it's like a-- like a
double, over the entire hollow.
The energy field runs
several hundred feet
on either side of
the fault line.
-Unbelievable.
-You don't believe me.
-Well, that's just it, I do.
When was it this Nephite, uh--
-Kiddoni.
What year did he say
it was in his century?
-He said it was the sixth
month of the 19th year
since the birth of the messiah.
-Interesting.
-Grandpa, do you think my
father could still be alive?
-I don't know.
I'm gonna read a little.
-But what if Kiddoni is right?
What if an invasion
is really headed
this way, right to
Corrine and Drew's house?
-Calm down.
I'm sure no one's in
any immediate danger.
[rock & roll music playing]
[shouts]
[screaming]
[dog barks and whimpers]
[woman guffawing]
[car horn]
DRIVER: Get out of
the road, you morons!
-This one is dead.
-You will find us
food and take us
back to where we were
this morning, understand?
-Where's Brock?
-I thought he was with you.
-Kerra, we need to talk.
-What do you mean, with me?
-Well, he saw you
leave this morning.
And he said he was
gonna follow you.
-Kerra-- Kerra.
-There goes our payday.
-Oh, yeah.
-Hey, bro, do you
need any company?
-No, this might, um,
require a little privacy.
-Hora le.
-Secure the house.
Find that gym bag.
PASSENGER: Let's
go, man, let's go!
[tires squealing]
Go!
[screaming] Hey, hey, stop!
Hey, come here!
All right, everybody,
gather around.
We're gonna play a little game.
It's called sit
down and shut up.
-(LAUGHING) Nice.
[giggling]
-Can I help you?
CUSTOMER: You all with
the Manti Pageant?
[sniffs]
-I already took a bite of that.
-Take the food!
All you can carry.
-Hey!
[screaming]
-We go!
[tires squealing]
-You know these things?
How do they work?
You will take us
back in one of these.
-Wait.
Cut me loose.
He's a kid, he can't drive.
-Yes I c-- No, no, he--
he's right, I can't drive,
-No!
Or I won't drive it.
I won't help you.
-No, no!
-You try anything, and
I will not hesitate.
-Move!
OK, come on, let's go.
[car starts]
[tires squealing]
-Where are you taking us!?
-Back to where we came from.
-Don't trust him.
He's defied us.
He must die!
[shouting]
[grunting]
-Are you all right?
-Uh, yeah.
Yeah, I'm fine.
[panting]
-Come on, let's go.
-What happened?
-This isn't their world.
They can't pass through here.
-I don't get It.
-Some places are
entrances, some are exits.
And some, like this--
[grunts] are just windows.
But you can't predict it,
how powerful it will grow,
how it will change, or
when it will disappear.
Come on.
We've got to cross the hollow.
BROCK: So it is true.
You are from up here.
I mean from today, from my time.
-What's your name, boy?
-Brock McConnell.
-(WHISPERING) What did you say?
My uncle's house is about
a mile through there.
-How old are you?
-11.
-Y-- you have a sister?
-Yeah, Kerra.
-Sakura?
-Yeah, how'd you know?
[loud whistling]
-We have to keep moving.
Come on.
-"And it was in the sixth month.
And behold, great and
terrible was the day
that they did come up to battle.
And they were girded about
after the manner of robbers.
And they had a lamb-skin
about their loins.
And they were dyed in blood.
Great and terrible
was the appearance
of the armies of Giddianhi."
[shouting]
Sixth month, 19th year.
CHRIS: Run, Brock!
-Brock!
-Yo, Kerra.
What's the matter?
You're not all
tickled to see me.
-What are you doing here, Hitch?
How did you find us?
-Your brother invited us.
He has something for me.
-He has nothing for you.
Leave!
-Brown canvas bag?
Huh?
About yea big.
You've seen it?
Oh, so you have.
(LAUGHING) Oh,
you're so unfriendly.
A little stick, huh?
No Jackie Chan?
No Bruce Lee?
No Tae Kwon Do?
-What's in the bag?
-Nothing much.
Just a quarter million
dollars, street value.
-Stay back.
-Come back with us, OK?
We have some fun.
We stop in Vegas, roll some
dice, take in some shows.
[struggling]
[grunting]
Nice outfit, holmes.
-(SOBBING) Kiddoni!
-Who is he?
-Never mind.
I'm so glad you're here.
[weeping]
-I couldn't convince
them, Sakura.
I told them about
the Gadianton spy.
They're still convinced
that Giddianhi
will invade from the mountains.
-Kiddoni, Brock is missing.
-Your brother?
[cocks gun]
-Hitch, no!
[screams]
[weeping]
-(CRYING) No!
No.
No!
Kiddoni!
[weeping]
-Come on.
Ay!
Come here, mami.
Come on!
Come here.
-Hey, what's wrong?
-I killed someone.
Something, an
Indian, I don't know.
You got the bag?
Huh?
-Still haven't found it yet.
-Where's your brother, Kerra?
Hm?
Where's my bag?
[baby crying]
Kerra, where's your brother, OK?
-Please let me go back!
Please.
-[gasps] No.
Look at me.
You're not going anywhere, mami.
OK?
Now, tell me where
your brother is, OK?
I want my bag.
-Lobo!
[shrieking]
-Hey, no, mom.
Calm down.
[gunfire]
-Hey, ese, come on in
and join the party, man.
[breathing heavily]
-Brock?
-Are-- are you the man
who talked to my sister?
-Unbelievable Unbelievable!
Are you hit?
-Grandpa Lee, we
have to get help.
We have to go back there.
There's a man with a long
beard and long hair--
-One emergency at
a time, grandson.
-Ah, what hit me?
-Bullet, I'm afraid,
but-- [laughs]
you've got yourself a
guardian angel, my friend.
There's your bullet.
Never seen one of
those before, have ya?
You really are a Nephite.
-We're secure.
-Look, those people
who've got Sakura
have got guns, or bullets.
Stop, wait!
Wait.
-I have to rescue her.
[struggling]
-All right.
Then let us help you.
-How long are we
gonna wait, Hitch?
-As long as it takes.
-What if he saw us coming?
What if he saw us
coming and ditched?
[baby crying]
-Then I'm gonna start shooting
someone every ten minutes.
[car horn]
Check it out.
Come on!
Hora le!
-Hello.
Are you sure you
want to use those?
Might mess up this
fine upholstery.
-Riz!
Lobo!
What's going on, eh!?
Huh?
Adder, don't let anybody move.
Let's go for a walk, mami.
Come on.
Stay.
Get out.
Get out!
[brock struggling]
Where is it?
-Huh?
KERRA: Don't!
-Spree's bag, don't lie to me.
-I-- I hid it in the woods.
[gunshots]
KERRA: Kiddoni!
-Move it!
Come on!
Let's go, move it!
[baby crying]
Better be there, kid.
Huh?
Or else you're gonna be
at a barbecue with Spree,
with the man upstairs, huh?
-You killed Spree?
-Ah, just hand it over, ese!
-Ah.
-No!
[gunfire]
-Hasta la vista, mami.
[cocks gun]
Ah!
Ah, don't!
Stop!
Ah!
[weeping]
-Kerra.
Kerra, we-- Kerra, we
have to go back there.
I met this guy.
He saved my life.
He knows you.
-What-- what did he look like?
-Uh, gray beard, long hair.
They-- they said he was a slave.
He was attacked by
men with painted
faces, painted in blood.
-Giddianhi's army.
-There's more of them.
They're coming this way.
-The warning
trumpet, where is it?
-This man could be my father.
-You must tell me.
The trumpet?
[car horn]
-You all right, boss?
-No.
That's all right, I'll walk.
-You-- you sure?
I mean, you know the
way, Mr. Whitman?
-To my own house?
[laughs] I should think so.
[baby crying]
-Shut up!
Shut her up.
-Natasha, give the baby to me.
I'll take her.
-No!
Sit down.
[glass breaks]
-Who's up there?
[cocks gun]
Who's up there?
[metal pieces jingling]
[grunting]
-I'd stop right
there if I were you.
-Hey, I found it!
[screaming]
[grunts]
[shouting]
[struggling]
KERRA: Brock!
[shouting]
-The horn, where did it fall?
-Uh, in there, I think.
[shouting]
[piercing sound]
-Kiddoni!
I can't reach it.
Kiddoni!
[grunts]
[yells]
[horn sound]
[multiple horns sound]
-No!!
[piercing sound]
[exhales]
-Daddy?
-Sakura?
(WHISPERING) Y-- you are Sakura.
My god.
-Oof!
[gasps]
-It's the invasion.
-Children, go to the van.
[shouting]
DRIVER: Hurry up!
Go!
Come on, come on!
-Go, go!
[shouts]
-Hey!
Wait!
Whoo!
Hey!
Hey, stupidos!
Ah!
GRANDPA LEE: Into the van.
Hurry, go!
Go, go, go!
Hurry!
-Where's Bernadette?
-I'll get her.
I'll get her!
I will get her.
-Into the van!
-There's juice.
[growls]
[growls back]
MAN: Bernadette!
[baby moaning]
-Get them!
[baby crying]
[ignition sputtering]
-Oh, God Come on, baby.
OK.
[ignition sputtering]
[screams]
[shouting]
-How'd you get away?
-Long story.
Suffice it to say, don't
stand around arguing
about who slays the captive.
He might escape,
even steal a weapon.
[arrow snaps]
[shouts]
-You OK?
-I'm all right.
-They're coming.
Come on.
KIDDONI: Go!
All of you, leave here.
-But you're hurt!
-I can still run.
Our army is also coming.
-Sakura, we have to go.
-Go!
[horns sounding]
[gasps]
-This way, this way.
[shouting]
In here, in here.
Come on, come on, come on.
[shouting]
[gasping]
[birds chirping]
[whining]
[fighting]
-He's out there, dad, in that.
Kiddoni, he's out there.
-I know.
Don't worry.
Everything will be all right.
It will be all right.
-I have so much to tell you.
Everything is not all right.
Brock and I, we're in trouble.
-(WHISPERING) It's OK.
We'll work it out.
We're together.
That's what matters.
I won't leave you again, ever.
I promise.
[bird singing]
[rumbling]
Aftershock.
-W-- what is it!?
-It's gone, the whistlers.
They're gone.
Kerra!
Brock?
[soft music playing]
-Hello, dad.
-Chris?
[gasping] Oh, Chris.
Oh, my son!
Oh.
-Kerra!
Kerra, wait!
[crying]
-It's gone.
The rift, it's gone.
[soft music playing]
-Hey, look.
Nothing broken, nothing lost.
-Yeah.
Nothing lost.
[warping sounds]
-Gadianton.
-Eh?
[soft music playing]
-Come on.
Sakura let's go.
[crying]
KIDDONI (VOICEOVER): Sakura?
[whirring sounds]
-You're all right.
-The battle was won.
Giddianhi is dead.
It's because of you.
-No, you knew all along.
-Your father and brother?
-They're all right.
Th-- they're here.
Don't y-- don't you see them?
-No.
The rift is fading.
-But not forever.
I won't fade forever.
-You can't leave me again.
I love you.
Please don't go away.
-I won't, not for long.
Do you trust me?
-Of course.
Yes.
-Then you must have faith.
You must believe.
I love you, too, Sakura.
-What am I supposed to do?
-Learn of me, the book.
Learn of my people,
of the messiah.
We'll meet again.
We will meet again.
-I believe it.
I know it.
-Goodbye, my little angel.
[music playing]