Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
(SIRENS WAILING)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
(GUN CLICKS)
(IMITATING AIRPLANE)
Dad is very silly. (LAUGHS)
Good morning, Daddy.
Good morning, baby.
You look nice, Daddy.
You look beautiful, too.
Look at your hair. Good job.
Thank you.
Did my thing.
Yeah.
You look...
amazing.
How cute am I?
Very cute.
Be safe.
You do the same.
You gonna eat this food.
We gotta figure
something out, okay?
Ah.
Eat your food.
Wait. Wait.
Chris.
Hey.
What's wrong?
I don't want to say this
in front of Sabrina,
but I had one of
those dreams again.
Ah.
Come on, Chris.
I- I know I have
a lot of dreams...
but this one was different.
I'm serious.
Listen.
CHRIS: Talk to me.
Despite all of
the racial tension
between the police
station, the communities,
or whatever other kind
of bullshit is happening,
I need you to make
it your business
to come back home
to your family.
No matter what.
Hey, hey.
My family is my first priority.
You hear me?
And you, Officer Jones,
you make it your business
to come home to your family.
Try to go be a good cop.
It's not many of us left.
(ENGINE STARTING)
WOMAN: Why is it so hard
for you to just move on?
MAN: Bitch, I been moved on.
I just stopped by
to see my daughter.
You are very disrespectful.
Just chill out.
Yo, don't be calling
her no bitch, man.
- What, nigga?
- Yo chill, yo chill.
- Nah, fuck that nigga.
- Yo, yo, yo, it's not right.
I'm not looking for
any problems, man,
but that's my girl.
MAN: I just stopped
by to see my daughter.
Fuck that nigga.
Bitch ass nigga.
Don't call her no bitch, man.
MAN: Man, fuck
that new nigga.
Man, get your
motherfucking hands off me.
I ain't looking for
no problems, man.
Easy, easy, easy.
- But that's my girl.
- Hey you, you, come here.
Let me see some ID.
Okay. You come here.
Let me see your ID.
I got him.
He's with me, Officer.
What's good, nigga?
What's up?
- You doing too fucking much.
- Back the fuck up.
- I got him.
- Bitch ass nigga.
Come on, it's not that serious.
(GUN FIRING)
(WOMAN SCREAMING)
No!
Why did you do that?
(BABY CRYING)
Yo, yo Sonny, he hit this nigga.
Yo, yo, yo, yo.
Yo, what the fuck?
OFFICER: Get back.
Don't cuff him, man.
He's dying, man.
What the fuck did you do?
(BABY CRYING)
(SIRENS WAILING)
RIVERA: Just do me a favor.
Put your hands against the wall.
Spread your legs.
CHRIS: Spread your legs.
RIVERA: Spread 'em more.
You guys have anything on
you sharp in your pockets?
SUSPECT: Nah, yo.
You got any weapons?
Any illegal drugs on you?
- SUSPECT: Nah. Nah. Nah.
- You're positive?
Turn around.
- What's your name?
- Sebastian.
- CHRIS: What grade you in?
- Senior.
This one's on me.
Next one's on you.
- Yeah, he's good.
- RIVERA: He's good, too.
Aight, beat it.
RIVERA: Yeah.
(BOAT HORN)
- Sup?
- Hey.
Seen this?
Another young black
male dead in his 20s
due to the lack of training
and accountability.
Well it's incidents like this
that make me scared to
give my kid a cellphone.
Mmm-hmm.
- What's up, Rivera?
- Hey.
- Susan.
Chris.
Who you got in the Eastern
conference this weekend?
Oh, come on now.
You didn't have to ask me that.
I'm going with
Kyrie all the way.
(LAUGHS)
Counting your
blessings too fast.
Toronto is hungry.
Yeah, yeah.
RIVERA: You might be
onto something there.
I'm for the Warriors.
I love me some Stephen Curry.
Ohhh.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, hold up.
Am I feeling some bets coming on
or am I just feeling pure hate?
Put up or shut up.
I'm just saying you
want some of this?
Yeah.
Let me run.
Hey, did you hear about that
mistaken cellphone shooting?
- Yeah.
- RIVERA: Yeah.
- It was bullshit.
Yeah, hey.
You just have my money ready.
You hear?
Let me get up outta
here before Sabrina
and Jackie put an APB out on me.
SUSAN: You got that right.
See you later.
- RIVERA: Later, partner.
- Bye.
(PHONE RINGING)
- Are you gonna go with Curry?
- SUSAN: Yeah.
(PHONE RINGING)
(SIGNAL BLINKING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Take it to the body, B.
- I used to hit like this.
- PETER: Excuse me.
- Like ah, like.
- Used to hit that.
- Police.
- I need to see some ID.
- Hey.
Yo Chris, what's up
with your peoples, man?
What you trying to
be fucking funny?
Calm down.
Does it look like I'm
trying to be funny?
We are calm.
Calm down, I'm a cop, aight.
So what you stopping
us for then?
Call come in from central.
Wait a minute, wait a
minute, wait a minute.
I'm asking the fucking
questions here.
Do you have ID?
Whoa.
Okay.
Oh, I see.
I see what this is.
- You're one of them, huh?
- PETER: Yeah, I'm one of them.
- Give me the fucking ID.
- Aye, look, aye.
Yo Chris, just show these
motherfuckers your ID,
so we can get out of here.
Alright, everybody just...
calm down.
You better shut
your fucking mouth.
You know you think just
because you got a badge
let's you talk to
people like that?
Gives you the merit to
speak to people like that?
- Yes, it does.
- I got ID in my car.
I'll get it right now.
Just calm down.
- Got a gun!
- Hey, hey, no, no.
I'm a cop!
Don't shoot me!
- (GUN FIRING)
- (CHRIS SCREAMING)
Hey, step back.
Step the fuck back!
(GUN FIRING)
Shit.
Oh God. Oh, oh God.
Motherfucker shot me.
Yo, you stupid.
He's a cop!
- What are you doing?
- Man, he shot me.
Oh God.
Shoot him.
Shoot that motherfucker.
Call an ambulance!
Call an ambulance.
(CHRIS SCREAMING)
Hey Chris, Chris,
please calm down.
Calm down.
CHRIS: Okay. Okay.
(SIRENS WAILING)
Sir, hold for me one second.
Excuse me.
My husband, Detective
Chris Jones was shot.
Yes.
- JACKIE: Do you know?
- He's on the second floor ICU.
JACKIE: Okay.
Okay, um...
RECEPTIONIST: Okay.
You go right through
the doors, please.
Do you know if he
was wearing his vest?
He's an officer.
He should've had on his vest.
You can't tell.
You can't call anybody and ask?
RECEPTIONIST: No, we
don't have the report yet.
What information
did they give you?
RECEPTIONIST: They
didn't give me anything.
How long do I have
to wait again?
How long?
(MACHINE BEEPING)
How are you feeling, Mr. Jones?
All right.
Yeah, you've been through a
lot the last couple of days.
Your body needs some rest.
You do need some time off.
That's for sure.
(MACHINE BEEPING)
I think you're
getting a lot better.
Just need some rest.
(MACHINE BEEPING)
What are you gonna do
about this motherfucking
nigger cop that shot my son?
Okay, you need...
you need to keep
your voice down.
We don't address our
officers by color,
but by last name or rank.
I can see that you're angry,
but so are the Jones family.
They are both cops and
they're both in our prayers.
You need to go to the hospital.
Be by your family's side.
They need you more
than ever now.
I'm sorry.
We tried to resuscitate him,
but his wounds were fatal.
No!
JOHN: We can fix this.
(DOG BARKING)
I hope these motherfuckers.
It ain't no set up or no shit.
My niggas know the whereabouts.
The where to be.
The where to be the fuck at.
Homie, I'm trying
to fix this shit.
You feel me?
A little something.
Well check this out.
If united both flags
is the new suicide,
then let it ring 'cause I'm
not gon' keep standing by.
Keep letting these
happy crackers
keep having open season on us.
I rather die standin' on my feet
then live on my knees any day.
You follow me?
Why don't we do this right?
Then we both is all shooters
together and everything else.
You feel what I'm saying?
Let's do the negotiations
on that part, B.
- BLUE: Got you.
- Aight, Blue.
(KNOCKING)
This motherfucker, man.
Aye yo Blue, man.
Why you bringing this red
ghost slop up in here, man?
BLUE: Aye yo chill, man.
You house trained little poodle?
Yo chill, Du.
You gotta understand it's
the color you're wearing
that incites the bull.
Y'all already know what this is.
It's only right we sit down
and put our flags to the side
and create a truce,
especially with all this shit.
Got all these police
keep killing us out
in these streets like this.
All right, Crip.
'Cause you got to know
we wouldn't be here
if it was any other option.
I wouldn't want to have to.
I got people all over, man.
OG's know, man.
He know me, hey.
That part.
So what you said is now
we got a temporary truce?
I mean I know we on y'all
side, y'all say cool.
You know, when this side over
here translation I say boom.
Du, tell the rest of the set.
Aye yo, man, you
trust this nigga?
Yo, you ain't gotta trust me.
I'm Mr. Word Out 'cause the
word out is like word out.
- Boom.
- That part right there.
- Dun, dun, dun.
- Aight, cuz.
I'm like God on whoop gang.
These is bloody shoes.
CROFT: Fuck that nigga.
Yo cuz, I don't trust
that nigga, man.
Fuck that.
That nigga crazy.
A source tells us
this could have been
a case of mistaken
identity, but either way,
this entire
community is on edge.
Joining me live now
is Regina Clark.
Regina, you witnessed this all.
What can you tell us?
He deserved what he got.
They come in our community.
They kill our young black men
and they walk out without
a scratch, but not today.
Everybody was yelling and
telling him not to shoot
and that the other guy was
a cop, too, just like him,
but because he was black,
he didn't wanna believe it.
It was self defense
if you ask me.
Well thank you for that.
As you can see raw emotion
spilling out here
to the streets.
Daddy, do white cops
hate black people?
REPORTER: Back to you.
Baby.
Baby, come here.
Careful.
Now, where'd you hear that?
What would make you
say that, Sabrina?
My teacher asked how's
your father coming along
and then my friend Peter said
that white cops don't
like black people.
Oh, baby.
Your friend Peter.
He's wrong.
Now mommy and daddy would not
be cops if that were true.
- Yeah.
- Okay?
Yeah, you know what Sabrina?
Sometimes, um, when
people are afraid,
sometimes they act out in anger
and it affects how they,
um, deal with other people.
Right?
And then, um, it
doesn't necessarily mean
that they hate the person,
but just sometimes
people act out of fear.
Do you understand?
Okay.
Well, go brush your teeth.
Get ready for bed, okay?
- SABRINA: Okay.
- Night, night.
Love you, Daddy.
- Love you too, Mommy.
- Love you, baby.
Oh God.
Did you hear that?
This is crazy.
Do you see how this is
affecting our child?
How are we supposed
to raise a child
in this climate when
we're the boogeyman?
This is ridiculous.
Or some. Like we're some
kind of racial group
that doesn't like people
for their differences
and beliefs and cultures.
I tell you what though.
I swear to God,
I'll quit this force
before I let it
dilute our child.
Social media don't
make it no better.
Let me go get her situated.
(MUSIC FROM NIGHTLY NEWS)
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
I'm sorry for your loss.
You've come to the
right place for support.
I wanna show you something and
you give me your take on it.
What do you see?
And what comes to mind
when you look at this?
All I see are niggers and spics.
We see the same vision.
Yo, you know where that
come from? (LAUGHS)
Knowing the creator.
But yo on some real shit.
That shit happened so fast,
I thought I was a dead man.
Yeah, I heard.
My mans and 'em
out of Jamaica fam
was killed by one
of them devils.
He said they tried to say
homie went for their weapon.
That's the reason
they killed him.
Some bullshit.
I'll tell you that.
Yo, I'm getting sick
and tired of this shit.
And you know what?
I'd rather be judged by 12
then to be carried by six.
- You feel me?
- Feel you.
MAN: Real talk.
Real talk.
Nigga, what you mean real talk?
Your dusty ass
ain't about nothing
but stealing the coldest
beer out the Arab store.
Come on, nigga.
Yo, chill out, man.
Yo, this is some serious shit.
What other options
we have left for us?
You said yourself you'd
rather be judged by 12
than carried by six.
- Yeah, man.
- That's a fact.
What else y'all
getting into though?
Got some hos on mind.
I got a lot of shit on the mind.
Nah, seriously though.
I'm getting sick and
tired of these pigs, man.
Yo look, I ain't no
killer or nothing.
You know I'm a working
man, but I'm a man first.
That's what's up.
Ain't nobody gonna
save us but us.
Yo, this shit got to
stop, man, for real.
And I think we got to
do something about it.
I'm ready to do it with you.
(SNIFFLING)
Hey.
I still can't believe he's gone.
Don't do this.
I can't either.
But we gotta hold on for Mom.
Can you do that?
Yeah.
Okay.
Where's Mom?
Upstairs.
And Josh?
He's up there too acting weird.
All right.
This is what I'm gonna do.
I'm gonna go talk to Josh.
I'll be right back.
No more liquor.
Glad you're here.
KEVIN: Okay.
Hey. What did I say?
No more liquor.
Okay?
Got it.
I promise.
KEVIN: Okay.
I love you so much.
I love you.
KEVIN: Okay.
What's up?
(TV PROGRAM CLICKS OFF)
What are you doing?
I was watching that.
KEVIN: What were you and John
whispering about
at the hospital?
I don't know what
you're talking about.
You don't know what
I'm talking about?
You fucking selfish prick.
Let me tell you something.
Mom had to bury one son
'cause of his fucking ego.
Don't make it two in
the same fucking week.
You don't think I don't
know what John's up to?
He's mind fucking you.
You done?
I got more to say to you.
You bring any fucking
pain into her house
any more than
she's been through.
You bring any trouble
in here and guess what?
I'm gonna be the one who
fucking turns your ass in.
Oh, you want revenge?
You're a fucking man.
It wasn't about me.
It's about him.
Yeah, what are you gonna do?
You gonna bring him back?
This is the stupidity that
fucking got him killed
in the fucking first place.
What are you gonna do?
Get yourself fucking killed.
Is everything all right in here?
Yeah, it's okay, Mom.
Yeah, Mom, we're, uh...
we were just getting stirred up.
We're talking about
the good old days.
(HORN BEEPING)
(DOOR THUDDING)
Morning.
Hey, gentlemen.
How you feeling?
I've felt better.
Let's get this started.
My name is Jerry Rifkin
from Internal Affairs.
This is Lieutenant
Michael Rullan.
Please state your name, rank,
and precinct you're assigned to.
My name is Detective Chris
Jones, 115th precinct.
All right, Chris,
can you tell us
what happened on the
night of June 16th?
Yes.
A friend and I were
coming out of a bodega
where we were approached by
two plain clothes officers.
How'd you know they were
plain clothes officers?
One was wearing badge
beads around his neck.
All right, go on.
Detective McKenzie, rest
in peace, approached me.
Though they were
both asking for ID,
Detective McKenzie
seemed overly aggressive
for it to be
identification check.
Then I spoke in
code to his partner
and I asked him if a call
had come in from central.
He glanced over at me as
if he knew the language.
That's when Detective
McKenzie remained stoic
and things got confrontational.
You said confrontational.
What are you referring to?
The friend that I was
with stated to me verbatim
talk to your fucking people.
Detective Mackenzie must've felt
that he was directing his
frustration towards him.
That's when he stated
back to my friend,
watch your fucking mouth
before I crack you in it.
I stated to him, you think
that badge grants you the merit
to talk to people that way?
Detective McKenzie's
face remained aloof
as if he had already
made his future decision.
While all of this is happening,
I'm still looking for my ID.
I tell him that it must be in
the truck across the street.
He glances over
it, but to no avail
did any of them
take the initiative
to validate my reasoning for
the identification delay.
At that time his partner...
he notices my backup weapon
and he yells out gun.
And I said to him, I'm a cop.
Don't shoot. I'm a cop.
That's what I said.
Detective McKenzie
takes out his firearm
and he fires two shots at me.
One hitting me in my body armor
and the second one
penetrating in my hip.
I then returned fire
striking Detective McKenzie
while I'm on the ground.
Two shots.
All right.
Is there anything
else you'd like to say
before we close
out this interview?
I just wanna send my
condolences out to his family.
All right.
We bring this
interview to a close.
Time is now 11:14 a.m.
CHRIS: You think just
because you got a badge
let's you talk to
people like that?
Gives you the merit to
speak to people like that?
PETER: Yes, it does.
CHRIS: Don't
shoot, I'm a cop.
That's what I said.
I'm a cop.
CHRIS: Don't
shoot, I'm a cop.
(GUN FIRING)
(CHRIS SCREAMING)
SUSAN: Has anyone got
word back from Chris?
Today he went for
his I.A.D. interview.
Oh, that's right.
Yeah, not today.
We spoke yesterday.
I said we'd all come
by to cheer him up.
You gotta see how they're
rioting in different cities
'cause unarmed black
men are being killed.
Fucking crazy.
It's scary because
there's so many good cops
out here honoring the badge.
Yeah, it's true.
It may sound crazy but
the good ones are looked
at even worse than the
ones abusing the badge
and that's because
we turn an open eye
instead of doing
something about it.
Look, don't get me wrong.
Some of these perps
that we arrest,
you wanna turn an open eye
and put your hands
and feet on them.
Yeah I would if I was
into that type of force.
Those would be the ones that
are your rapist and molesters.
You don't kill them.
That's true.
You know, it's a
gift and a curse.
Hey, what time we
headed over to Chris'?
I need to get home
to prepare dinner.
Oh, let's meet up like seven
being that it's Friday.
- Okay, great.
- Sound good?
- See you guys later?
- RIVERA: All right.
SUSAN: Get home safe.
COP: Yeah.
Oh my God, I still can't
believe what happened.
Yeah, it's bullshit.
That it is. That it is.
Them shits gon' get
you too high, my nigga.
You know what I'm saying?
I don't fuck with that shit.
Them niggas better
not violate though.
I'm telling you, man.
- Straight up.
- Yo, man.
I don't think we even gotta
fucking wear this shit, man.
You know what I'm saying?
Yo, man, who gives a fuck
what you think, my nigga?
You know what I'm saying?
Listen, I don't agree with
half of this shit out here.
But I listen.
You know what I'm saying?
Yo.
DU: What up, cuz?
- What's going on with you?
- What's popping, man?
Just trying to stay sucker free.
That's all, you know.
- That's all you can do.
- Aight, aight.
- What's up?
- What's good, man?
When your brother
Suave come home?
He still got about three to do.
- Damn.
- Short.
- Three?
- That's what it is.
Shit, he'll be home soon.
I know your ass was shook when
them shots ran out though.
It take you to say
something like that, right?
But to answer your question,
you damn right I was.
I'm a working man.
I ain't used to having guns
and shit pulled in my face,
especially by the motherfuckers
that's supposed to
protect and serve me.
You feel me?
Nigga, I don't feel you.
You know I'm only fucking
with you, my nigga.
I know, nigga.
I know.
You already know, nigga.
(WHISTLE BLOWING)
Good morning, sir.
I have something for you.
You can't be serious.
First degree murder.
Do you love your job?
You know what?
Ponder that before you answer
and bring me a real case.
You know they're talking about
trying to bring charges
up against you, right?
Yeah, tell me about it.
My lawyer told me
something like that.
Also told me not
to worry about it.
I don't get it.
If this were vice versa,
it would have been
considered a friendly fire.
JACKIE: Yeah.
Give a fuck, cops, come on.
All I can say is that
today is a new day.
Is it?
As long as you address
your deepest sympathy
to the McKenzie family
and made peace with God,
everything else is a feeling
that will eventually go away.
- Amen.
- Yeah, that's true.
So how did the
I.A.D. briefing go?
Better than I anticipated.
Yeah, you know the
drill, you know.
What happened before
the fatal shot?
What they really
wanted to know was
at what point in time did
I state that I was a cop?
DETECTIVE: That's exactly
what they wanted to hear.
Everything else was
circumstantial to the ears.
CHRIS: You know it.
Yeah, I'm just happy you
wore your body armor.
Yeah, well you're gonna have
to thank Jackie for that
because she makes me wear it,
ugh, everywhere besides bed.
Damn right 'cause
you never know.
Well, I'd say she just
proved a point, huh?
Enough said.
It's just ridiculous
because you know,
we take this job with the
notion to protect people.
Then we, as cops
have to come home
and hear our child ask us do
white cops hate black people.
CHRIS: It's crazy.
JACKIE: That's what she
said to us the other day.
- Are you serious?
- Man, now that hurts.
And what's sad is that
not every white cops
have those hateful feelings.
The moral of it all is that
we have a job to uphold,
and before we go out there
and perform our duties,
get down on our knees and
you thank God for waking up.
JACKIE: That's right.
We kiss our loved ones.
And we tell ourselves
at the end of the day
that we are gonna make it
home one way or another.
Yeah.
Well, it's getting late.
Yeah, I agree.
Jackie, it's always
good to see you.
Help me up.
When's the next time I
see you to the range?
JACKIE: You might see.
I need to be on this morning.
I'll let you know.
SUSAN: Yeah, okay.
Careful.
RIVERA: I hope you see us
back out there
sooner than later.
You know that.
RIVERA: Jacks.
Continue getting that
work comp disability
or whatever you've
been getting there.
CHRIS: You crazy.
Get out of my house.
Have a good night.
Y'all get home safe.
(BAGPIPE FUNERAL MUSIC)
(SIRENS WHOOPING)
We are gathered
here to praise God
to witness to our faith
and to give thanks
for the life of our
dear brother Peter.
Blessed are the dead who die
in the Lord says the spirit
for they rest from their labors
and their works follow them
all the days of their life.
Are there members of the family
who would like to offer
any last words for Peter?
He wanted to make a difference.
How proud he was to
serve as an officer
in the New York City
police department.
You will be missed, my son.
Now people of God is to
go forth upon this day
and upon this hour.
We live into the
blessing and the service
and the life of Peter
that as he helped
and blessed this world, we
go forth with the same spirit
within our hearts
and upon our souls.
From this day forward
and forevermore.
Amen.
(INTENSE EMOTIONAL MUSIC)
How you coming along?
I'm okay, Captain.
Just one day at a time.
It's a sad day for us all.
(SOFT TENSE MUSIC)
Why are you here?
Why?
You're not one of us.
(TENSE MUSIC)
Detective Jones, is there
anything you'd like to say?
How do you feel about the loss
of Detective Peter McKenzie?
Do you feel this whole
incident was racially motivated
due to all the unarmed
African American men
who are being gunned down
in this country
by police officers?
Please.
You as an African
American detective,
what do you think
needs to be done
to address this senseless
violence against Latino
and African American
men by police?
Accountability.
Well, there you have it.
Truly solemn day for
one of New York's finest
as both the mayor
and the chief of police
briefly spoke about
the emotional toll
this has taken on the community.
I'm Jim Hannigan reporting live.
Back to you in the studio.
(RAIN PATTERING)
You nervous?
A little.
Daddy, what is this place?
It's a place where
cops like daddy
come to be interviewed, buddy.
Interviewed about what?
About how good we work...
or how bad.
Justin, that's enough
with the questions, okay?
So Daddy's gonna go
and talk to these men
and then afterwards we can
go get your favorite food.
Would you like that?
McDonald's.
That's it, but no
more questions.
(CLOCK TICKING)
Good morning.
You nervous?
No.
The time is 10:30 a.m.
The day June 30th, 2018.
My name is Internal Affairs
Detective Jerry Rifkin.
This is Lieutenant
Michael Rullan.
Can you state for the
record your name, rank,
and the precinct
you're assigned to?
My name is Officer
David Mitchell
and I'm assigned to
the 12th precinct.
Can you tell us to the
best of your knowledge
what happened on the
day of June 16th?
My partner
Officer Peter McKenzie
and myself were performing a
routine identification stop
when we observed two
African American males
coming out of the bodega
on ninth and 40th Avenue,
who appeared to be
loud and disturbing.
At that point, we jumped
out of our unmarked cruiser
and approached the two men.
When you say
appeared to be loud,
can you amplify a little
more on what appeared means?
Sure.
They were talking loud.
At that point I started
performing a warrant check
on one of the men while
Officer McKenzie tried
to contain Chris Jones,
but within five minutes,
Chris John started
acting belligerent
and crazy and refused to
surrender his identification.
And at that point I happened
to notice his firearm.
I alerted Peter and
we both drew our guns
and ordered Chris Jones
to lie on the ground.
At that point, it
looked like Chris Jones
was going for his
gun and that's when
Officer McKenzie
fired striking Jones.
At any point in time,
did Officer Jones state
that he was an officer?
No.
Are you sure that
at no point in time,
did Officer Jones
state to the best
of your knowledge
that he was a cop?
Not that I can recall.
You stated when you both
observed Officer Chris Jones
and Jason Johnson you were
performing a routine stop.
Correct?
That is correct.
MICHAEL: On who?
I'm sorry I don't
understand your question.
On who were you performing a
routine identification stop
when you noticed
Officer Chris Jones
and Jason Johnson
appearing to be loud?
On no one. That was our
assigned patrol duty.
I have two more
questions and I'm done.
Do you acknowledge
Officer Chris Jones
as your fellow officer?
Of course.
Why would you ask that?
Why didn't you fire your
weapon, Officer Mitchell?
DAVID: Excuse me?
Well, in this report it states,
you didn't discharge
your weapon.
Why?
My partner had already
fired striking Jones.
I'm sorry.
Are you saying I
didn't do my job?
Officer Mitchell, is there
anything else you'd like
to state before we
close on this inquiry?
No, thank you.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
MICHAEL: The time is 10:40.
This inquiry has
come to a close.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
Look at all the stolen
bikes in the pile over here.
Motherfucker.
They put police
tape on 'em, too.
Look at that. They put
fucking, they use our tape.
That's from where the guy
got shot the other day.
They took the tape
out to put it over it.
Well, he had it coming.
- These fucking kids, man.
- He had it fucking coming.
- COP: Nothing over here either.
- No, I don't see nothing.
COP: Where the
fuck are these guys?
OFFICER: Ah, they're
off to a meeting.
We get no luck.
We're better off
getting something to eat.
COP: You're hungry already?
I'm hungry.
Ah, fuck.
We'll get something
in a little while.
Hold on.
(SOFT MUSIC)
What's over there?
BLUE: All right, that's
what up? Are you gripped up?
MAN: Hell yeah.
Aight, just make
sure you be mindful.
They gonna be on
that bullshit today
being at the funeral for
that cop Chris hit is today.
MAN: Aight, I'm
definitely am up on it.
Aight, that's what's up.
(SOFT MUSIC)
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
Eh, yo, like I was saying, make
sure you stay on point, man,
'cause them crackers
is out here.
Yeah, yeah.
No shit.
Hey, come on.
Right there.
(SOFT MUSIC)
These motherfuckers right here.
What are you doing, brother?
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
Yo, get the fuck off me.
Blue, you good?
Calm down.
DU: Bullshit, man.
It's over.
Fuck off.
- Mind your own business.
- Back up.
Fuck you.
MAN: Take that vest off.
Take that vest off.
No fucking way.
You motherfuckers is crazy.
Fuck you gonna do?
That's what I thought.
It's coming.
Oh, it is, huh?
I'll be fucking waiting.
You gonna get what's
coming to you.
Back the fuck up, all right.
Yeah, real soon.
Finally got your ass.
Yeah, we got you now, huh.
Where you been hiding, huh?
After you.
Watch your head.
(GENTLE MUSIC)
Fuck him.
Go 'head.
(TENSE MUSIC)
We're looking for those
guys from the other night.
Last night and two nights ago.
Same group.
They get up around this time.
OFFICER: Look at these animals.
Look at 'em.
Do they think they're getting
away with anything here?
Look at this.
- (UPBEAT HIP HOP MUSIC)
- (GROUP CHATTERING)
Fuck you guys doing?
What we got, what we got?
What is this?
What do you have,
what do you have?
TRIGGER: The only
reason y'all around
this motherfucker
harassing motherfuckers is
because of that dead
ass, lying, racist, cop.
What the fuck did you say?
MAN: You heard what he said.
- I'm not talking to you.
- The only reason y'all around
this motherfucker is 'cause
of that damn racist cop.
Oh shit.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
Come get this nigga.
- (DRAMATIC MUSIC)
- (GUN FIRING)
Oh shit.
That's enough.
Fucking move this motherfucker.
Yo, yo, yo.
I need backup on 41st Avenue.
Right between your fucking eyes
and nobody here will
know the better.
He ain't do nothing.
(GROUP YELLING)
We need equal standards
around here, man.
Calm him down, man.
Yo, he ain't do nothing.
Come on.
Fucking finish your life
right now, motherfucker.
I'm sick of this shit.
Don't shoot.
You don't want this.
Excuse me.
Hey.
They about to shoot me.
Fuck over here on the hood.
Piece of shit.
(TENSE MUSIC)
CHRIS: I gotta wrap her hair?
No, she wants her hair down.
This is what she wants.
Sabrina, go brush your
teeth before you go to bed.
I already did.
Excuse me.
Mommy thinks that
you don't know her.
(DARKENS VOICE) All of a
sudden out of nowhere...
SABRINA: Don't
treat me like a boy.
I don't care.
Tell him again.
Chris, get up.
You're gonna hurt her.
She's a girl.
That's my baby.
Yeah.
You know what time it is, right?
Yes.
Bedtime.
Give mommy a kiss.
Fun, fun, fun.
Goodnight, sweetie.
Goodnight.
She's getting so big.
I know.
That's your child.
I'm not ready for teenage years.
JOHN: This is it.
You ready?
(TENSE MUSIC)
JOSH: Not today.
JOHN: What?
Dude, I went on a
fucking limb for you
to get this information.
I said I'm not ready!
JOHN: What are you scared of?
I mean...
JOSH: Sh, sh, sh, sh.
(TENSE MUSIC)
JOHN: There's nothing there.
JOSH: Come on, man.
Come on.
JOHN: All right, fuck it.
You don't wanna fucking do it?
Let's go. Let's go.
JOSH: Come on, man.
JOHN: Fucking pussy.
Let's go, go.
(TENSE MUSIC)
Lights going over
that manhole cover.
Oh man.
He did say he was a cop
before we opened fire on him.
(OVER PA) Pull
over to the right.
(SIREN WAILING)
What did you just say?
(GENTLE MUSIC)
License and registration.
Yeah. Can you tell me why
you pulled me over?
What?
Can you tell me why
you pulled me over?
(TENSE MUSIC)
Excuse me. You're free to go.
Drive safe.
Okay.
COP: Did you tell internal
affairs the same story?
No, because we had
a beer that night.
It was game night.
Peter was having
trouble at home and...
we pulled over to perform a
routine identification stop,
but this guy was hitting Peter
with questions
only a cop would know.
I kept looking over at Peter,
but Peter was off in his
own world being Peter.
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC)
He even said that his fucking ID
was in the truck
across the street.
Did you validate
that information?
Did you go across the
street to the truck?
No, because I was holding
a perp I'd attained.
Plus I thought maybe he
just knew those questions.
You know?
Hey look, I would've never
expected to go the way it did.
But by then it was
too late anyways.
I saw his gun and
I alerted Peter.
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC)
He was a cop for
crying out loud.
You both ignored him
and a life was taken.
Two families are broken
because of you both.
(TENSE EMOTIONAL MUSIC)
(POLICE CLAPPING)
COP: Yeah, Chris.
- Hey.
- Welcome back.
Good to see you, man.
Thanks.
Feels good to be back.
Hey.
RIVERA: Welcome back, partner.
Thanks for all the
love to all y'all.
SUSAN: Good to see
you back on your feet.
I wouldn't be able
to do it alone.
- It's always love.
- Yeah, yeah.
If I'm not mistaken, I
think you owe me some money.
This guy and his money.
The game.
I almost forgot.
Yeah, I knew I was gonna have
to pay the reaper
one way or another.
Nah, it's cool.
Glad to have you back.
Thanks.
RIVERA: You ready to
hit the bricks or what?
Yeah, let's get it.
- Let's do it.
- All right.
See you guys later.
- SUSAN: Be safe out there.
- CHRIS: Yeah, you too.
Detective.
Hey, Cap.
It's good to have you back.
It's good to be back, Captain.
Keep your eyes open.
Not everybody's in
favor of the turnout.
Feel me?
I understand.
Good.
You watch out for each other.
RIVERA: Of course, Cap.
Get out of here.
CHRIS: You driving?
RIVERA: Of course.
(HORN BEEPING)
KEVIN: Unbelievable.
For six months I heard about
how I missed the barbecue.
'Cause I'm working.
It's like God forbid.
Yeah, so you better be there.
If I'm not there, I'm gonna
have somebody kicking my ass.
That's right. You know
the Korean temper. (LAUGHS)
It's good to have you back here.
I appreciate that.
You been watching the news?
What are you gonna tell me?
Yeah, I watched the news, but
not that much, I don't know.
You know what the
news will do to you?
It'll make you quit this job.
We don't get enough bad news.
Go 'head.
What bad news you wanna tell me?
It's all over the
news that the cop
that shot your brother
is back on the beat.
Yeah. Well that's good
'cause he's a cop.
He's got mouths to feed.
He's got a home to go home to.
It's honorable to
hear you say that.
Don't get me wrong.
I love my brother.
As much as I honor this badge.
But only the people
that were there
and God truly know what
happened that night.
It's not honor. It's accepting
the fate of our decisions.
And I gotta trust in God's will.
Surrender, right?
Surrender.
You know all about surrender.
I would hope, right?
Surrender.
I'm trying my best
to fucking surrender.
And the rest of your family?
They're surrendering?
Irish Catholic families
don't know
what the fuck surrender means.
They're surrendering
to the liquor stores
is what they're
surrendering to these days.
No, they're doing
the best they can.
I love them.
I mean, I'm trying.
They're getting there.
It's Josh that I worry about.
What's going on with Josh?
It's nothing. I just...
I worry about him.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
(JOSH WHISPERING)
All right, all right.
(JOHN WHISPERING) Fucking move.
JOSH: All right.
What is that?
What the fuck are we doing?
JOHN: Come on.
JOSH: Oh shit.
Look man, I'm not ready.
I think we should go.
Fuck up and give me
the crowbar, dickhead.
Give me the crowbar.
(GLASS SHATTERING)
JOSH: Ah fuck.
Fuck.
Fuck is wrong with you?
Come over here.
JOSH: Fucking hand.
- JOHN: Fucking baby.
- JOSH: Fuck.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
Fuck.
Come on, dick.
What are we doing?
JOHN: Get the fuck over here.
Come on.
Do you hear that?
JOHN: Shut the fuck up.
Look, I think we should go.
JOHN: Give me the flag.
So what are you a fucking child?
Give me the fucking flag.
Fuck out of here.
Come on. Hurry. Fuck.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
(GENTLE MUSIC)
I'm just so fucking glad that
Sabrina wasn't here. Fuck!
SUSAN: Where's Sabrina?
She's at her
grandmother's house.
Can you imagine if she
would've been in there?
Can you imagine if Sabrina
would have been in the house?
OFFICER: Got him.
JACKIE: Oh, my God.
Whoever did this,
left something behind.
Thank God.
That's good.
You take that down
to the lab right now
and you get that checked out.
Yeah, ASAP.
Look, we're gonna get
this motherfucker, okay.
Yeah.
RIVERA: They're gonna start
to get some looks, okay.
This is just pure hate.
It's okay.
Nah, that's hate, man.
RIVERA: I'm gonna
see you guys tomorrow.
(EMOTIONAL MUSIC)
SUSAN: Bye, guys.
(CHRIS SOBBING) What
the fuck is going on?
It's okay.
(EMOTIONAL MUSIC)
A very emotional day for
Anthony Williamson's family.
We just received word that
NYPD Officer Michael Garrett
will not face any
criminal charges
in the shooting
death of Williamson.
He was unarmed at the
time when the officer
allegedly mistook his
cell phone for a handgun.
The family members just
left court here minutes ago
devastated over these
latest developments.
For now we're live
outside Queens criminal court.
Nicole Johnson.
Back to you.
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
Hey, Garrett.
(GUN FIRING)
Get down, get down.
Get on the ground.
Garrett, Garrett!
Anybody else hit?
WOMAN: Garrett!
COP: Medic!
WOMAN: Stay with me.
Secure the area.
Secure the area!
(GENTLE MUSIC)
REPORTER: Detectives
in this neighborhood
are still very upset
that there has been
10 consecutive days
of no running water.
REPORTER: Breaking news.
Officer Michael
Garrett was just killed
inside his district precinct.
Oh, shit.
REPORTER: No idea to what
connection the shooter...
There is a God.
Ma!
Lord Jesus, why?
Why would my son go and do that?
Oh, God, all this shooting.
It's got to stop.
There must be a path to justice
with all this
senseless shooting.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
CONGRESSMAN: Mr. Mayor,
did you see the news today?
'Course I did.
Well, obviously you realize
that we have a broken system.
And people are starting to take
justice into their own hands.
Now I get it.
It has to go
through legislation.
It has to go through Congress.
It has to go through the
house and so on and so on.
But accountability must
be a moral obligation
to the people and it
must start somewhere
and somewhere has to be right
here and right now, Mr. Mayor.
Mr. Mayor, you're on in 15.
Thank you.
Congressman, I agree with you.
Accountability starts here
and I accept that challenge
and the people will know
I accept that challenge
when I start to
implement change.
My moral obligation is to
the people of this city,
but the fight can't
just be by myself,
legislature and Congress.
The very people that object
to the way these laws
are being enforced and
governed are the same people
that voted for them
in the first place.
Yes I mean, I'm the first one
to take responsibility
for my people.
You know, I am them
and they are me.
But the reality is,
leadership begins at the top.
It starts at the top.
And you and I both know
attitude reflects leadership.
It's time, Mr. Mayor.
Congressmen, know that I
hear the cries for justice.
Mr. Mayor, you hear
my cries for justice,
but the reality is we
feel the pain just us.
If you'll excuse me, gentlemen.
JACKIE: Chris! Come down here
before your food gets cold.
I'm so proud of you that
you ate your food today.
Thank you, Mommy.
Did you pack my money
in my bag for my trip?
Yes, I have.
You have badgered me about it
morning, noon
and night, little girl.
SABRINA: You're
the best, Mommy.
Okay, and you're the
best seven year old.
Chris!
CHRIS: Hey baby, did
you see what I saw?
Who the hell is knocking
at the door like?
JACKIE: Officers.
OFFICER: Hello.
JACKIE: Wait, hey.
Chris.
CHRIS: Whoa, whoa, whoa,
hold up. Come here, baby.
What's the problem?
Good morning.
My name is Detective Jack Mullen
and this is my partner
Detective Keith Edwards.
No, I didn't ask you your names.
I asked you why you're here.
I'm sorry, but we
don't make the rules.
We have a warrant
for your arrest.
Respect you as one of us.
With that being said.
We won't treat you any
less than your rank
and we won't handcuff you.
What is Detective Chris
Jones being charged for?
We don't know. Our orders were
only to bring him in.
That's all we know, Sargent.
That's all you know?
(SCOFFS) This is some bullshit.
This... this is ridiculous.
Hey, hey, shh.
It's okay.
Don't you worry.
Look.
Hey, don't you worry.
You know what to do.
Don't touch me, man.
Yo, how you feel about
that situation, Jay?
What they trying to give
you some stupid ass payout
for some mental
anguish or something?
Yeah, I wish.
Look, all he worried about is
me never missing a day's work.
Yo, you know what my boss
had the nerve to say to me
the other day?
Watch the people
you keep around you
because if you miss
another day at work,
I'ma have to find
somebody to replace you.
Typical plantation talk, see.
I hate that cracker.
Word to my mother.
It ain't all what it seems.
Read the newspaper.
What the fuck he talking
about read the newspaper?
Everybody know that
they lock Chris up
for killing that devil.
Could they even do that?
Ain't he a police officer?
JUSTICE: Easy.
Just do it.
Exactly.
Shit ain't gonna be real to them
until we start murdering
these motherfucking
crackers, man.
Start shooting them
unarmed white kids.
Yeah, you ain't never lie.
Them some wicked folks.
Yeah, I was looking at this
Farrakhan video last night.
Like basically he went on to say
how if the legal justice
system fucked up,
the next step is to
result in violence.
Listen.
I don't never agree
with nothing he say,
but I can honestly say
I definitely agree
with this one right here.
I fucks with Farrakhan, man.
- Fuck that.
- Yeah word.
Before I got my flag, I
had knowledge of self.
He was always dropping bombs
about racism and them devils,
but then when his man
Khalid Muhammad got smoked
and he didn't respond, that's
when I fell back on him.
Yeah, I heard about
that with Khalid.
I fucked with Khalid,
but that's like me
not riding out for
the peoples, man.
Never would I do that.
JUSTICE: All right,
cuz, you see?
(MAN WHISTLING)
What up, cuz?
JUSTICE: What up, OG?
BLUE: What's happening?
- DU: Cuz, what's up?
- What's happening?
Justice, let me holla
at you right quick.
Come on, let's talk about it.
Oh, boy.
KIMBERLY: Daddy.
Hey, princess.
Woo, how was your day?
Good.
Mommy made a surprise for you.
She did?
Yup, but you have to promise me
you won't tell her I told you.
Oh, I don't know.
You know, we don't keep
secrets around here.
You know that.
Aw.
Okay, you can tell me.
What is it?
KIMBERLY: Red velvet cake.
What?
My favorite.
Kimberly, where are you?
I should have known
when she disappeared.
- Hey baby. How was your day?
- Hi.
Interesting.
All right, well get cleaned up.
Dinner is ready.
Okay, I'm hungry.
Papa's hungry.
Oh, and another thing.
Yeah?
I'll just tell you at the table.
Oh, okay.
Kimberly, come.
Help me set the table, okay?
KIMBERLY: Okay.
WIFE: Okay.
Oh, man.
You didn't tell your father
what we made for him, did you?
Huh?
Kimberly?
I tried to keep it a
secret, but it's hard.
Daddy gets everything out of me.
Your father is your
kryptonite to Superman.
What's that?
(SING SONG) That's I love you!
All right, before we can eat,
it's your turn to say grace.
Okay.
Thank you, God, for this
good food Mommy cooked.
Oh, and the red
velvet cake for Daddy.
Yaaay!
Oh boy, this looks delicious.
Papa is hungry.
WIFE: Thank you.
KIMBERLY: Can you
cut my chicken?
WIFE: Sure, just
pass your plate.
I'm not the cupcake.
You're the cupcake.
You're my two favorite
women in the whole world.
(GENTLE MUSIC)
Oh, wow.
Let's eat.
(GENTLE MUSIC)
MICHAEL: What'd
you wanna tell me?
I have nothing to say.
I just wanna ask you
how you're feeling.
It seems like you have
a lot on your mind.
Yeah.
I can tell this guy
thinks I'm against him.
Try not to let it worry you.
Like you always say to me.
You have your strategy.
Mm-hm. But I think in this case,
it flares up some
extenuating circumstances.
(GENTLE MUSIC)
Do you got this, babe?
You know, at no point
in the interview
did Officer Mitchell refer to
Detective Jones as an officer.
And two he never
discharged his weapon.
Why wouldn't he
discharge his weapon?
I don't know what to tell
you when it comes to that.
Yeah, selective memory.
A lot of these young
cops are never screened
for mental evaluation.
They've been bullied as kids
or they're just
fucking closet racist.
Well.
That's good that you're
the one on the job.
And you know I don't
like closet racists.
Really?
I did not know that.
Really? (LAUGHS)
Thank you for that velvet cake.
You're so welcome.
CAPTAIN: How you feeling?
Let me tell you, Cap.
I'm not gonna be taking that.
Cap.
No.
Look Captain, it's protocol.
It's protocol.
Conversation is
totally off the record.
Yes it is.
I can't sit around
and feel like I'm participating
in this whole ordeal.
It has to stop.
You are a great detective.
Your safety is my concern.
Now don't get me wrong.
My pain goes out to the
McKenzie family as well,
but there's too
much at stake here.
So.
From this point on...
you are officially relieved
from your duty as detective.
Starting effectively today you
will be assigned desk duty.
(EMOTIONAL MUSIC)
Something tells me you're
gonna be needing this.
(EMOTIONAL MUSIC)
I was thinking about having
dinner for the holidays
at my place this year.
Okay, good.
MOTHER: Thank you.
(GENTLE MUSIC)
KEVIN: What happened
to your hand?
Huh?
What happened to your hand?
I cut it.
It's no big deal.
(GENTLE MUSIC)
We good?
Yeah, we're good.
JOSH: All right.
(GENTLE MUSIC)
Is everything all
right here with him?
MOTHER: Yes.
Why do you ask?
How you doing, Pop?
Morning to you, son.
It's not so good to me.
(GENTLE MUSIC)
Let me get out of here.
Love you, Mom.
(GENTLE MUSIC)
See you later, Pop.
Ease up on the sugar.
Hey.
- Good morning.
- Morning.
KEVIN: Mom and Pop are
pretty blank this morning.
You know, Peter could do
no wrong in their eyes.
You know that.
He just keeps playing
it over and over.
It's hard to move on.
They're getting better.
And you?
How you doing?
Different days,
different feelings.
So tell me, did Josh tell you
what happened to his hand?
Oh, he said something about
cutting it on something,
but I don't really
get into it with him.
I got it.
Let me get out of here.
I love you.
Okay.
(GENTLE MUSIC)
How are you?
What's the word on Chris?
I know, I know.
Me and my husband was
talking last night about how
easy it can be swept
under the rug
when they the ones
behind the gun.
And I love my job.
I really do, Lisa, but when
it comes to my family...
my baby...
I'm treading.
LISA: Girl, you
ain't gotta tell me.
- Really treading.
- I know.
It's crazy out here.
Sometimes I feel...
You ready to get this work?
JACKIE: Get this work.
You crazy.
- Get out of here.
- Hey, Sergeant, what's up?
How you doing?
JACKIE: What's up?
Let's go, come on.
Ain't he though?
And he sexy, too.
You just gotta
love him. (LAUGHS)
Look, for real though.
You need something, you call me.
JACKIE: Watch
yourselves out there.
Safety first.
Love you.
JACKIE: Love you back.
Sarge, you have a good day.
JACKIE: I will, at home.
(ON TV) That's great, Buddy.
As you know, Buddy has won $17.
Yo man. You know, they giving
Little Chris Chris 25 years
for defending himself, man.
Self fucking defense.
Quarter fucking century, nigga.
See, that's the
bullshit right there.
You know what I mean?
I find it real funny
how they can kill us.
Shoot black cops
and shit like they did
ole' boy. The cop from Queens.
That part.
And never even see the
entrance of a courtroom.
Like what part of
the game is that?
Yo bro, pass the blunt, man.
I hate how they do us,
but we have to blame
ourselves too sometimes.
Fuck you talking about, Deb?
TRIGGER: Why don't you listen?
It's like I said.
Them white cops are scared, too.
Okay, imagine some of them
growing up in a white school,
surrounded by all
white students,
dreaming of becoming a cop.
Never really coming
into contact with blacks
except through the
social media and news. Right?
Then they pass the cop test.
Get dropped into areas like ours
where people are killing
each other like a sport.
First person they come into
contact with
happens to be a flag leader
with tattoos all over his face
tripping off of this sour.
TRIGGER: Why are
you looking at me?
You know what I'm saying.
Yeah, I know.
You blowing mine.
Listen.
No, listen, she blowing y'all
'cause the fucking
smartphone dumbed you down.
Look.
This ain't fucking
Utah and shit.
Some old hick ass shit
where it's only two niggas
in the whole goddamn state, man.
It's the fucking
Mecca in the culture.
All this shit that's out
here worldwide, nigga.
This motherfucking
New York, blood.
That's a fucking
excuse for them niggas
to just be fucking stupid, yo.
They wanna hold something.
Hold these nuts, nigga.
I need something
to get on my feet.
The best way to get on your feet
is to get the fuck off your ass.
Blood on that.
If you don't fight
for something,
you gon' fall for
everything, blood.
That's what this truce's for.
I already beat up that
motherfucking truce.
I don't know.
Anybody got a motherfucker
question about it?
Anything?
I already beat that truth
is popping like that.
Nana, you finished them
taters back there and shit?
This shit ain't even lit.
TRIGGER: Y'all niggas hungry?
Trigger, you ain't stupid
like some people, all right.
One thing I can say that
speaks volumes to young people
and cops is that we
can come together.
That truce slash
unity that you have
with Croft and them
crips supports that.
That shit speaks volumes
to people like me,
but they're scared of that shit.
And you wanna know why?
Why?
Because they don't like
blacks coming together
because we're too influential.
You know it.
I know it.
Look at how hip hop
affected their children
with listening to hip
hop, dealing with racism.
They're not so much scared
of the guns that we bust off.
They're scared of us uniting.
My bitch deep.
See that?
You go, girl.
Boy, please, you're my bitch.
Don't try to impress
Trigger because you know.
(GENTLE MUSIC)
Shit.
Blood sample that was submitted
last week
came back inconclusive.
So the blood sample
is from a human,
not an animal, corrrect?
That is correct.
The only problem is
that person's name
isn't in our system.
TECHNICIAN:
That is correct.
Do me a favor.
Have it run through
an NCIC check.
Something might come up.
Got it.
You didn't think I fucking had
it like that you cocksucker.
You got this one, partner.
I'll see you outside.
I'll see you later.
(DISTANT INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(INAUDIBLE)
Yeah, don't worry.
Appreciate it.
We good?
All right.
Got you now, fuck boy.
Fuck you.
JOSH: I can't wait.
JOHN: You're like
a fucking child.
- Get the fuck out.
- JOSH: Goddamn.
JOHN: Fucking take
a piss every five minutes.
Yeah, just leave
my door open.
Fucking jerk off.
JOSH: Fuck man, I'm
pissing all over myself.
JOHN: Let's go, dick.
Oh.
Oh, fuck.
- JOHN: Let's go.
- All right, man.
JOHN: Fucking jerk.
JOSH: Maybe if we
didn't fucking day drink,
I wouldn't have to piss so bad.
JOHN: Ah, look at this.
Look at this, you
fucking jerk off.
JOSH: Just relax.
Look, I'm just gonna tell
him my brother's a cop
to get out of this.
- Relax.
- JOHN: Let's see if that works.
JOSH: Be cool, man.
Relax.
JOHN: You had to go to
the fucking... (INDISTINCT)
- Can't be a normal human being.
- JOSH: Relax.
'Cause you know what we
got in the fucking back.
What you got?
It looks like we're having
a little party here.
JOHN: I was telling him
that we gotta get back
to the house
for my mother's dinner.
That you do.
Let me see some ID,
license, registration.
You, you pissing
on the sidewalk.
You see a sign that says fucking
bathroom on the wall?
Oh no, Officer,
I'm so sorry, man.
My brother.
My brother's a police officer.
OFFICER: Oh yeah?
What's your brother's name?
Kevin McKenzie.
As in Detective McKenzie,
brother to Peter?
Yes, sir.
I'm sorry for your loss.
Peter was a friend.
- That was hard news.
- JOSH: Yeah.
All right, so,
so can we go now?
OFFICER: All right,
here's what we can do.
If there's nothing
in the car
and your identifications
come back clear,
this never happened,
okay?
Okay, cool.
No, no, why can't
we just go now?
We're already
running late.
It's still procedure.
OFFICER:
Step out of the car.
We at the 110 all
sympathize with your loss.
Oh, watch out.
OFFICER: Against the car.
Hands behind your back.
I need back up on 86th Street
and 25th Avenue
across Story Boulevard.
White male wearing black
tee shirt, blue jeans.
Possibly armed.
JOSH: (GRUNTS)
Come on, man.
DETECTIVE: It's being printed.
All right, do me a favor.
Take Detective McKenzie
over to see Officer Fuller.
All right.
Detective, sorry for your loss.
Your brother and I
were good friends.
Thank you.
Appreciate that.
What's Josh
being charged with?
Right now we didn't
put him through.
All in good faith
because you're his brother.
They found two guns
in the back of a car
owned by a guy named
John Macintosh.
The car isn't under
your brother's name.
You see where I'm
going with this?
I see. Where's John
being held now?
John took a run
for it at the scene.
He got away.
Okay.
Thank you.
Can I get a minute
with him?
Sure. Take your time.
I appreciate that.
(DOOR BUZZING)
Sit down!
Sit the fuck down now!
What were you and John planning
on doing with those guns?
JOSH: What guns?
KEVIN: The guns in the trunk
of that fucking car
that you both were in.
That's what guns.
I told you before.
You come in here, you bring
any problems to the family,
and I bust your ass myself.
Do you think I was
joking with you?
I really didn't know there were
any guns in the car.
Nothing. I didn't know.
I'm gonna get you
out of this one,
but if I find out you knew...
(DOOR BUZZING)
Sit.
- We have a problem.
- What's the problem?
Your brother has an
outstanding warrant.
An outstanding warrant
for what?
You're not gonna
believe this.
Josh's fingerprints
were found at the scene
of the detective that's accused
of killing your brother.
Are you fucking kidding me?
The media's gonna have
a fucking field day with this.
I just found out
how you cut your hand.
What?
Notify the district precinct
who put the warrant out.
You gotta be
kidding me, man.
OFFICER: What do you wanna
do about this situation?
- Charge him.
- What?
Hey.
Come on, man.
Come on. Kevin.
Kevin.
Come on, man,
I'm your brother.
Get me out of here.
Kevin!
DU: Hold your head, my nigga.
I'm trying.
Yo, Du, you good?
Why, what's up?
Don't worry 'bout them.
They ain't gonna do shit.
Fuck 'em.
What's up?
You guys got some ID on you?
I look like a kid to you?
Come on now, boys.
You heard what he said.
Yeah, what's happening?
Fuck you gonna do?
You don't have nothing
better to do
than harass these kids out here?
Yo, you see my man
grandmom's out here, right?
- Damn.
- That's somebody's grandmother.
Y'all being real disrespectful.
OFFICER: And she needs
to watch her mouth
Yo watch how you talk to my
motherfucking grandmother.
Yo, yo, get my grandmother
out of here.
- Fuck you gonna do?
- What you mean what I'mma do?
What the fuck you gonna do?
Move so I can shoot
this motherfucking cop.
(GUN FIRING)
I'm on 40th Avenue
and 10th street.
I need backup.
Be advised, my radio is stolen.
Yo, who the fuck this nigga
coming in here
with his strap out?
Is that that nigga Du breaking
the truce, my nigga?
What's up?
Yo, yo, I'm hit, my nigga.
Yo. Yo!
- Ah.
- TRIGGER: Get him out of here.
Get him out of here.
(OVERLAPPING CHATTER)
Oh, oh, oh.
Put that fucking gun down.
Put that gun down.
♪ Heart racing
♪ Want some more
♪ Why so was she
♪ Ah
♪ To say hi
♪ I don't believe ♪
You wanna tell me something?
No.
I think you're a lying scumbag.
The fuck you talking about?
You can tell me now or you
can tell the judge later.
All right listen, I already
fucking told you everything.
- Okay?
- You don't fucking tell me now,
you'll never see your
wife and son again.
You know, fuck you
and fuck that nigger cop.
Listen.
Listen, Mitchell.
You tell me what
the fuck happened
on the night of June 16th.
Tell me.
I already fucking
told you everything.
I said tell me.
Weak, man.
Yo, take care of
yourself out there today.
CAPTAIN: Detective, can
I talk to you for a sec?
Hey, Cap.
Of course.
I'm sure you already know
about the big commotion
that took place in
your old neighborhood
between 110th precinct
and the two rebel gangs.
The bloods and the crips.
Yeah, I see where
this is going, Cap.
To make a long story short.
I just got off the
phone with the 110th
and they're asking for your help
in retrieving the
radio that was taken
during that big incident
between them and the two gangs.
Cap, what makes them think
that I could get it back?
That's not what they're saying.
It's only a request
with a strong hope
that you'll be able to make
that radio materialize for them.
You puttin' me at
great risk, Cap,
but if that's what you're
asking me to do then...
I mean, technically I've
been relieved of my duties.
I'm supposed to be on
desk duty right now.
I explained that to them.
That's one.
And two I would never compromise
nor negotiate your safety.
You know that.
This is again, it's a
request all in good faith.
All right, Cap.
If that's what you
want me to do then...
I'm good.
- Can I go now?
- Yes.
No.
Never let the sickness
like race or religion
of another man's mind be
your crutch for deviating
from the moral obligation
you still hold to that badge.
We all took an oath.
We all share.
Now I don't agree
with a lot of politics
or policies that
our badge protects,
but I don't make the rules.
I just follow them.
You got it, Cap.
You got it.
ASH: How you holding up?
Good, Ash.
I'm okay.
Seen better days.
How's mom?
I miss you so much.
KENNY: Come on, Ash.
Don't cry.
You gon' make me cry.
I'm sorry.
Ma's fine.
Cries a lot.
We saw you on the news
and she just broke down.
Had to do what I did.
Couldn't keep coming home
looking Ma in the face
and just not doing
anything about it.
Then on top of that them
cops is sitting there
laughing at us like
they making fun of us.
I'm not mad at all.
I just wish it could've happened
where you didn't get caught.
Honestly, once I
made peace with God,
getting caught was the
least of my worries.
I'm okay.
I miss Michael, but I ain't
want him to die in vain.
You know?
Hey, remember when
we was younger
and we would go to Nana's house?
She'll make that chocolate cake
and let us mix the
icing off the blender.
You remember that?
I remember.
You and Michael
used to fight over
who would get the bowl
and Nana would give it to me
to be fair by not giving
it to neither of you.
Only if you knew
that I used to start
with Michael on purpose
'cause you was the little one
so you would never
beat us to the punch.
For real?
Yeah, for real.
OFFICER: Visit's over.
- Don't go. Not yet.
- KENNY: I have to.
I have to, Ash, all right,
but kiss Mommy for me.
Tell her I love her, okay.
- They can't break me.
- ASH: I love you.
All right, I'mma be all right.
ASH: Please don't
hurt my brother.
I love you.
I love you, Ashley.
Remember that.
I'm only doing this
'cause of you, Blue.
This better not be no bullshit.
I got you, C.
Check this out, my nigga.
I don't talk to police.
I don't fuck with police.
Only reason I'm doing this
is 'cause you from the hood.
Niggas say you 100
so speak on it.
Now Croft, I appreciate
you taking out
the time to meet with me.
Now there was an incident
that allegedly occurred
between the crips
and two detectives
from the 12th precinct,
which led to a man being shot
and a police radio being taken.
What this shit's about a radio?
A motherfucking radio?
What, somebody told you
I was there or some shit?
Hey.
Is this a set up
or some bullshit?
- What's going on?
- Hold up, I'm alone.
- I'm alone.
- Yeah cuz, what I don't get
is why the fuck you worried
about them cracker's
radio so much?
Aren't they trying to
send you to prison?
You know, I asked myself
the same question.
Why the fuck am I standing with
these people in the battle,
but I'm alone in the war?
And you're right.
You're fucking right.
It's 'cause I took an
oath as you both did.
Now we may not agree
with all the things
that happened under that color,
but we still find a
way to protect it,
which means having a truce
with them red ghost bloods.
That's to help
things along the way.
We do what we gotta.
I need your help.
Either I come and get it or
they gonna come and get it
and you and I both
know only two things
are gonna happen if they come.
That's injustice and injustice.
Neither's good for business
or for the community.
Check this out, my nigga.
I believe you give
respect, you get respect.
You had a lot of balls coming
here just fucking with me.
So I'm gonna do what I can do.
I put that on the set.
Like I said.
Thank you for taking the
time out to meet with me.
Yeah.
I think we done.
Keep moving.
What you think, Croft?
Fuck the police, man.
Fuck 'em.
I want you to listen to this.
Check this out.
DAVID: I had an idea
that he was a cop
once he asked us
why did you stop us
and did a call come
in from central.
He said he was a
cop the whole time.
Wanted to go get his wallet
from a jeep across the street.
Mind fucker, huh?
Got that scumbag.
LAWYER: You heard it.
I'm demanding a dismissal
and for my client
to be placed on full, active
duty effective immediately.
LAWYER: All charges
are hereby dropped
and you are placed back
on full active duty
as a detective
effective immediately.
CHRIS: Hey, thank you
for being there for me.
I'm trying.
Detective Jones, are you
planning on filing a defamation
of character lawsuit
against the city?
No comment at this time.
Thank you.
What, if anything, did you
learn from all of this?
Say something.
I can't.
You know, I really
enjoy being a detective
and despite all of
our differences, okay,
most of all our legal
justice system works
once we held them accountable
for their actions.
Thank you.
Anything else you
wanna share with us?
CHRIS: No, thank you.
Excuse us, please.
Thank you.
REPORTER: Detective,
one more question.
And the world will never rise
to its full moral,
or political, or
even social maturity,
until racism is
totally eradicated.
Well, it may be true that
morality cannot be legislated,
but behavior can be regulated.
It may be true that the law
cannot change the heart,
but it can restrain
the heartless.
It may be true that the law
can't make a man love me,
but it can restrain
him from lynching me
and I think that is
pretty important also.
And so while the law may not
change the hearts of men,
it does change the habits of men
if it's vigorously enforced.
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
(LOVE MYSELF PLAYING)
♪ It's a difficult
idea to comprehend
♪ We try to act so perfect
but it's all pretend
♪ We feel alone in this world
to realize we've got friends
♪ But in the moment we latch
onto what we're feeling
♪ It's so bad that people are
scared to travel through
♪ Why are we so scared
to just be true
♪ You gotta find the
strength to just be you
♪ I know it's hard but it
is something you gotta do
♪ So I'm just
gonna love myself
♪ No, I don't need nobody else
♪ 'Cause I realize
who I am is enough
♪ So I'm just
gonna love myself
♪ I just wanna say
you're the good in me
♪ Make it come alive,
feel my heartbeat
♪ I don't wanna be so perfect
♪ I don't wanna
feel so desperate
♪ Don't have time for that
♪ I just wanna see
where my mind will go
♪ Where this goes from
here only time will show
♪ Where it is my life is going
♪ 'Cause I'm focused
on my own thing
♪ Moving on my track
♪ I'm not scared
of some setbacks
♪ 'Cause I know that
I can clap back
♪ I don't need approval
to feel beautiful
♪ I don't need to change
myself to fit a mold
♪ I'm not caught up
with them boutiques
♪ 'Cause I am special
'cause I'm unique
♪ I don't need to
feel accepted
♪ I hope you get the message
♪ So I'm just
gonna love myself
♪ Hey
♪ No I don't need nobody else
♪ Need nobody else
♪ 'Cause I realize
who I am is enough
♪ Enough
♪ So I'm just
gonna love myself
♪ No I don't need nobody else
♪ 'Cause I realize
who I am is enough
♪ I'm just gonna love myself
♪ So I'm just
gonna love myself
♪ No, I don't need nobody else
♪ 'Cause I realize
who I am is enough
♪ So I'm just
gonna love myself
♪ Yeah, yeah
♪ No, I don't need nobody else
♪ Don't need nobody else
♪ 'Cause I realize
who I am is enough
♪ Enough
♪ So I'm just
gonna love myself
♪ Self
♪ So I'm just
gonna love myself
♪ No, I don't need nobody else
♪ Myself
♪ 'Cause I realize
who I am is enough
♪ So I'm just
gonna love myself ♪