Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
[film projector whirring]
[ominous music playing]
[indistinct transmissions
overlapping]
[sharp notes play]
[faint yells]
[hip-hop playing on speakers]
[party chatter]
[girl] All right,
all right, all right.
- [whooping]
- [chatter continues]
[Luke chuckles]
"Boyfriend, girlfriend."
Man, I know that's
so weird to hear.
but I guess I can tell you.
Just tell me.
Why didn't you tell me
sophomore year?
I don't know. I was scared.
Thought you weren't
gonna talk to me again.
Aww.
That's so cute.
[both laugh]
Yeah, well, I guess you're
not the only one with a secret.
I've kind of
been into you, too.
What?
Uh-huh. [laughs]
And you weren't gonna tell me?
I don't know. [laughs]
Guess I was scared.
Thought you'd never
talk to me again. [laughs]
[hip-hop and chatter
continue nearby]
[tense music playing]
Um, excuse me. Do you mind?
[chuckles] We don't have
any drinks for you guys,
so can you, like,
leave us alone?
[echoing] Will you let us in?
I'm sorry. What?
You know you guys are,
like, five months premature
with the whole
Halloween costumes, right?
Ugh. What is that smell?
I don't know.
Let's get out of here.
Well, ladies and gents,
it's been a pleasure,
but we're gonna skirt.
[chuckles] Okay, I don't know
what kind of weird stuff
you guys are pulling here,
but we're just gonna go, okay?
Oh, my God.
Okay, seriously, guys,
get the hell out of our way!
[echoing] Will you let us in?
Is that all you guys want?
You want us to let you in?
'Cause I don't know
what the hell that means,
but okay, sure.
We'll play along.
[gasps]
- [joint pops]
- Agh! My arm! Ahh!
Oh, my God! Let him go!
[gasping]
Damn it.
- [rustling]
- [gasps]
- [wings flutter]
- [bat squeaks]
[ringtone plays]
[static crackles]
- Dad?
- [crackling] Honey, you okay?
Dad, oh, my God.
There's crazy people after me,
and I'm in the middle
of the woods,
- and I don't...
- [breaking up] Carly...
- [static crackling]
- Carly...
Dad?
Dad!
- [static stops]
- Dad, my...
Dad, can you hear me? Please.
- Dad...
- [on phone] Will you let us in?
[squeals]
[Luke] Carly!
Carly, where are you?!
- Luke?
- Carly, please!
Luke?
Oh, my God. Luke, are you okay?
Yeah, I think so.
[winces]
[gasps] Agh!
[moaning]
All right! Fine. [sobs]
I'll let you in.
[gasping]
[birds chirping]
[alarm beeping]
That trick never
gets old, Nana.
[laughs] Unlike my boobs.
By next year, these bloody
things'll be hitting the floor.
TMI, my lady.
Emmy, both your dad and I
are working late tonight,
and it's bridge night for Nana,
so can you Postmate dinner?
They literally just moved
my Aronson meeting up to 9:00.
Honey, is my gray suit
still at the cleaner?
Oh, God, I forgot. I'm sorry.
I'll pick it up
on my way back from my 7:00.
Great. Love you. Thanks. Bye.
So who's taking me to school?
- Uh, your father.
- [door closes]
Could have told me that before.
- [groans]
- Sweetheart, your lunch.
Thank you, Nana.
Dad!
Oh, my God.
You could have waited for me.
I'm so sorry.
[school bell rings]
[overlapping chatter]
19 days and counting, huh?
[chuckles] I know.
Hopefully we
figure it out by then.
It's in the bag, young lady.
It's in the bag.
Uh, sorry, babe.
Seat's taken.
- Oh, sorry.
- No worries.
Honestly, it's so annoying.
There's, like,
a million other seats here,
and she has to sit
right next to me.
- Hey.
- Hey, guys.
[cell phone chirps]
[girls laughing]
Oh, God. [groans]
I messed up.
[girls laugh]
Oh, sorry, sweetie.
I accidentally
sent that to you.
You can just delete it. 'Kay?
Oh, my God. This is so awkward.
[girls laugh]
It's not like
you want to go anyway.
It's not a rooftop party.
But just in case,
think we're gonna need
a no-murderers policy
at the door.
[girls laugh]
[girls moan]
What?
Too soon?
Bye, Felicia.
Mommy, I didn't tie it.
[soft rock music
playing over speakers]
'Ey, what's up, Shark Tank?
What's happening, Bisquick?
Your convertors came in today.
Finally.
Come on, girl.
I sell records and things,
and sometimes the things
take a little longer
to get than the records.
There you go.
I get it. How much is it?
Ah, you consider it
a donation, okay?
Just go win the damn thing.
Hmph. You know, they're wrong
about you, Bisquick.
Yeah, well, you know,
they're all a bunch of idiots.
[chuckles] Yeah. See you later!
Go get 'em.
[ominous music playing]
Where have you been?
Well, guess what came in today?
Yes.
We're gonna win this thing, Em.
You need to start thinking
about if you're
gonna use the prize money
to buy the Ford Challenger
or the Silverado,
not to mention
what you'll be packing
for our luxurious trip
to Cape Canaveral.
[reel squeaking]
[static crackling]
This is where we make history.
[chuckles] Dramatic much?
[frequencies warble]
[tone squeals]
[transmission chattering]
I think it's gonna happen.
I think it's about
to frickin' happen.
[transmission chattering]
Holy crap.
[rumbling]
[tone beeping]
[clatter]
Jeez.
[tires squeal]
Oh, shoot.
I'm so sorry.
Am I interrupting
something huge here?
I've told my sister
at least half a dozen times
to park on the driveway
between the hours
of 3:00 and 6:00.
It's fine.
It was exciting,
though, wasn't it, Em?
Can you imagine
what it's gonna be like
when it finally happens?
It's gonna be lit.
See you tomorrow?
I'll be here.
- Bye.
The young teenagers were
last seen in this very area
enjoying a social outing
on Saturday night
and have yet to be
heard from since.
She always answers her phone.
And if she doesn't
have reception, she texts us.
She's very responsible.
I just want my baby back.
[crying] I just want her back.
Authorities have been
unable to uncover any clues,
as there were
no eyewitnesses on the scene.
Both Luke and Carly's parents
have initiated search parties.
[doorbell rings]
- [broadcast continues]
- [sighs]
Postmates.
[panting] Coming!
[echoing] Will you let us in?
Uh, sorry.
Thought you were Postmates.
I think you have
the wrong house.
[tense music playing]
Wh-where's my phone?
Where's...
[panting]
[Operator] 911.
What is your emergency?
Hi. Uh, there's people
trying to break in
and... [gasps]
Will you let us in?
- Hello? Hello?
- [Operator] Yes, ma'am.
I'm here.
Are these people in your house?
No, but they're
trying to break in.
Please send the police.
I'm all alone.
Young lady,
the police are on their way.
I'll stay on the phone
with you 'til they arrive.
Thank you. Thank you.
Ma'am, what's your name?
Emily. My name's Emily.
How old are you, Emily?
- 12.
- Okay, Emily.
Everything's going to be okay.
Just take some deep breaths.
Police will be there
before you know it.
[breathing deeply]
Will you let us in?
[screams]
[siren approaching]
[Emily screams]
[police radio chatter]
So, uh, how many of these guys
were there again?
Like, around five,
but only one of them
broke through the skylight.
So other than the, uh...
black eyes, uh,
any other distinct
or recognizable features
about them?
Uh, isn't that enough?
Yeah.
That's good for now.
I'm gonna be straight up
with you, Mark.
I feel like we're still dealing
with the lingering effects
of the incident.
Uh, kids find her
an easy target,
and I'm not condoning
that behavior,
but I want to be clear about
what we're dealing with here.
Aw, come on.
It's not exactly like they
were toilet-papering the house
or leaving a burning bag
of crap on the front step.
These jerks
broke through our skylight.
I mean, I think this is
a little more advanced.
Well, that's just it.
We checked the bathroom.
Skylight's perfectly intact.
No shards of glass
or trace of blood anywhere.
[scoffs]
[tense music playing]
Yuck! That is disgusting.
Just the way I like it.
Listen, Christopher.
I don't know if I'm up
for hanging out tonight.
We got popcorn,
your favorite movie.
I'll even let you
dress me up like a girl.
Can't even tell you how much
I've been looking forward
to this evening,
just me, Cherry Garcia,
and Netflix.
At this rate, Mom,
you'll meet a man in no time.
Appreciate it.
Em, you doing okay, honey?
I'm good. Thanks.
They'll find those jerks.
I hope so.
You need anything,
you let me know,
anything at all, 'kay?
Thank you.
Hey. Ooh, that smells good.
Ugh. [spits] I don't think
you put enough butter on it.
The king of excess.
[laughs] So true.
What?
I love your shoes, Jess.
Thanks, Em.
Mm, any way I can bribe you
to do my makeup tonight?
Depends on the bribe.
Mm, how 'bout one day
of being driven
wherever you want to go?
I'll be like
your personal Uber driver.
Without the charges, of course.
[sighs]
[sighs] I'll sweeten the deal
and throw in the Air Force 1s
for one day of wearing.
[chuckles] Deal.
Sweet. Let's go.
Hold on a sec.
Thought we were watching
Flying Saucer Rock 'N' Roll.
Ugh!
Might have overdid it.
[gasps]
[rock ballad playing on stereo]
My God. That's really scary.
I'm so sorry you had to go
through something like that.
I-I can't even imagine.
One thing you are is tough.
Eh, not to mention talented.
You know,
you should do tutorials.
You'd have, like, way more
followers than Jeffree Star.
[scoffs] I wish.
No, seriously.
You'd be doing a public service,
considering how
most of the girls in my school
walk around
looking like the Joker.
That sounds familiar.
How are they treating you?
- Who?
- Girls at school.
Oh, like crap.
That good, huh?
Yep.
It won't last long.
Trust me.
Things chance in high school.
Hope so.
Hey, why don't you come
to the party with me tonight?
Huh?
I mean, I heard
Tobey's little sister
is bringing some
middle schoolers anyway.
Oh, no. Scarlett is like
the mob leader of the pack.
They all hate me.
Okay, who cares?
I'm inviting you.
Besides,
it's my boyfriend's party.
Listen, Jess, I love that you're
inviting me and everything,
but I don't think
it's the right move for me.
Oh, of course it is.
You'll be hanging out
with all the cool kids
from high school,
instant street cred.
[laughs] Come on.
I've nothing to wear.
Well...
now you do.
[TV program playing]
Come on.
Hey, Christopher.
- Christopher.
- Hey, Christopher.
Are you okay with me missing
Flying Saucer and going out?
You know what?
I think he's Gucci with it.
Yeah.
[kiss]
[hip-hop music playing]
♪ All eyes on me in the club
♪ See 'em all lookin' at me
Fiendin' to touch ♪
♪ Top-dollar lady baby T
Is what's up ♪
♪ Money, money, money
I can't even get enough ♪
♪ And you know
I got my nails done ♪
♪ Hair done
Everything did... ♪
Finally we can start the party.
My queen has arrived.
[squeals, laughs]
Oh, you're wearing
the cologne I got you.
- Is it too much?
- No, perfect.
Um, Tobey, this is Emily.
She's basically
my little sister,
so please make sure
everyone's nice to her tonight.
Of course.
Nice to meet you, Emily.
- Nice to meet you.
- Mi casa es su casa.
Are you in, uh,
seventh or eighth?
Uh, seventh.
Then you must know my sister.
Scarlett...
you know Emily?
♪ Two for the show
♪ Three of us girls
Four, let's go ♪
♪ One for the money...
Of course.
TBH, wasn't really
expecting you to come.
[Jess] Oh, well, I invited her.
That all right with you?
Of course, Jess.
No need to get salty.
Scarlett, just make sure
Emily has fun, okay?
Absolutely.
What type of host
would I be if I didn't?
Come on.
Everyone's in the other room.
♪ I'm a naughty little girl
♪ And I give 'em
what they need... ♪
Those pants are straight fire.
Thanks. I couldn't
really take credit for it.
You could take credit
on how snatch they look on you.
[laughs]
[chuckles]
Truth.
You make out
with Brandon at homecoming?
That would be a yes.
- Yuck. I...
- Eww. Eww.
What? He's cute.
What?
It wasn't really
a make-out, make-out.
He kissed me for,
like, a second on the lips.
Well, actually,
it was on the cheek,
but it was an air kiss,
so he didn't really kiss me,
so the answer would be no.
I didn't make out with him.
Emily, this one's for you.
Uh, no.
I-I'm just a spectator.
Don't be such a wimp, Sparks.
Bam! Truth or dare?
Uh, I'll have to pass.
Oh, come on.
You can't just go through life
sitting on the sidelines.
Get in the game, thotty.
All right. Leave her alone.
If she wants to be
a little bee-yotch about it...
then let her be
a little bee-yotch.
Really? That's your game,
a reverse-psychology insult?
We're not insulting you, babe.
We're just calling you out.
Seriously, Em.
I mean, there's a reason
why you're not the most...
liked girl at school.
[girls laugh]
You'd think you want to make
a little more
of an effort here, right?
We can be your new besties,
just as long
as you don't try to,
you know, kill us, too.
- [laughing]
- Oh, my God!
[gasps]
You witch!
My brand-new top.
Oops.
[ominous music playing]
[hip-hop music playing]
[scoffs]
I hate her.
- [ominous music playing]
- What the...
Turn on the freakin' light!
Not funny, thotties.
Ivy?
Scarlett?
Hello. I can see you
standing right by the door.
[echoing] Will you let us in?
Brandon? That you?
Honestly, you're so annoying.
[scoffs]
You guys are such jerks.
[toilet flushing]
What the...
[gasps] What the hell?
Will you let us in?
Okay. You guys are super creepy.
You're Peter's friends, right?
Didn't know you were into
the whole
ratchet goth emo thing.
Yeah, my friends aren't
really into that stuff.
You know where Peter is?
Okay, special needs.
How 'bout you get
the hell out of my way?
What are you doing?
[blow echoes]
[woman] Never discuss it
with your parents?
Not really.
Why not?
I don't know.
I mean, they've been through
so much already.
I don't really want
to bug them with it.
That's very selfless of you.
But you can't continue
to carry the weight of this
on your own, Emily.
It's not your fault.
According to everyone else,
it is.
It doesn't matter
what everyone else thinks.
You know what the truth is,
an unfortunate accident.
It could have been you.
Should have never told her to...
Listen to me.
It is not your fault.
I know it may be
hard to accept it...
but you can let it go.
[overlapping chatter]
Bye, Dad!
[sentimental music playing]
They filed
a missing persons report.
She's been gone
since Saturday night.
[Emily] I was with her
on Saturday night.
Really?
So you were at the party?
Yeah, but I left early.
It's awful. I just...
hope she's okay.
So tell me, what's going on
with the project?
It's going, but I don't know
if it's ever
gonna actually happen,
but I just don't want
to crush Christopher's dreams
of communicating with aliens.
Emily, do you know how many
times Thomas Edison failed
before finally inventing
the light bulb?
Is this another one
of your dumb science jokes?
Thousands.
He failed thousands of times
before finally
getting it right.
You guys are
nowhere near that.
Keep it going.
You're gonna succeed.
Not to mention the winner
gets a brand-new truck.
And don't you want
a trip to Cape Canaveral?
Yeah, I know. It'll be so cool.
["Shave and a haircut" ringtone]
Keep on course, Em.
You never know.
You guys could be
the next Thomas Edison.
It's been over five days
and counting
as the hunt for Carly Hudson
and Luke Freitag continues.
The community
has banded together in...
[Emily] I think these are
the best ones we've made.
I mean, they're so on fleek.
Ugh. Well, I imagine
that's a good thing.
I think in your day, it would
be referred to as groovy.
[laughs] Oh, yeah. Okay.
Yes, all right.
Well, that is
definitely a good thing.
Come on.
Don't cheap out on me, queen.
[reporter] Manson says
he wants to thank all...
[doorbell rings]
[broadcast continues]
Who is it?
Uh, hi there.
My name's Harold Lutz.
I'm with the Times.
Oh. [laughs]
Oh, we're not interested.
We already receive
the Daily News, but thank you.
- Thank you very much.
- Yeah, no, no, no.
Um, I'm sorry. I'm not
selling subscriptions, ma'am.
I'm a journalist with the Times.
I'm writing a story
about the kidnappings.
To date, there have been...
three missing persons,
all in the course
of just one week,
all of whom are teenagers.
And there's been no trace
of any evidence.
Except for
a single eyewitness
who saw a group of kids
wearing black hoodies.
It was brought to my attention
that you were the victim
of an attempted robbery
involving a group of young kids
wearing black hoodies.
Yet you managed to escape.
Is that true?
I think we ought
to wrap this up now, Mr. Lutz.
Emily has to study
for an exam tomorrow, and she...
[Emily] Yes, it is true.
They kept asking me
to let them in.
Sorry. Uh, do you mind
if I record this?
[recorder clicks]
All of them were teenagers?
Yeah. I...
Well, not all
the same age and gender,
but they had black eyes,
like the entire eye was black.
And they had
extremely pale skin.
They smelled really bad,
like a mixture
of really old cheese and butt.
That's, uh, vividly descriptive.
Yeah, I'm just trying
to paint a picture for you.
It's very helpful.
You said that they asked you
to let them in?
Did they mean into your home?
Yeah, I guess.
I don't know.
The thing is,
this is a really small town,
and I've never seen
kids like this before ever.
Besties pact.
We do everything together,
no matter what.
[Emily] No matter what.
Okay, here we go.
But you go first.
I'm still nervous.
It'll be fine. Trust me.
You ready?
- Yeah.
- Here we go.
[deep breath] One...
two...
three!
- [thud]
- [gasps]
[panting]
[machinery whirring]
All I did was tweak
the frequency a fraction,
and then, boom,
it was real quick,
literally like three seconds,
and then all the power
just shut down.
[Emily] No offense, Christopher,
but I don't think
a tiny movement of needles
is proof of communication.
Trust me, it was
nothing we've heard before.
[transmission crackling]
This shihizzle's for real.
[frequencies warbling]
[transmission chattering]
[distorted] Jungspars.
[transmission crackles]
[transmission fades]
What?!
[blows lips]
Christopher, my dear friend,
I think that we need
to finally come to terms
that this is probably
never gonna happen.
What are you saying?
I'm saying that we've put in
a great effort here,
but I think we should try
something more realistic.
So you're just going to quit?
No, I'm not saying quit.
I'm just saying we should
figure out something else.
Emily, persistence is
science's middle name.
You know how many times
it took Edison
to finally invent
the light bulb?
- Thousands.
- Yes! How'd you know?
'Cause I know everything.
If you did, you'd realize
that we are so close
to communicating
with whatever is out there.
Well, what if there's
nothing out there?
You and I both know that
there's something out there,
and we are destined
to communicate with them.
I stan your passion,
Christopher,
but I think
I'm gonna cut my losses.
Emily, come on.
You can't do this.
[transmission crackles]
[distorted] Jungspars.
[crackles]
Jungspars.
- [transmission warbles]
- [chatter]
Go ahead.
[speaker squeals]
Hello.
Uh, it's me, Emily Sparks,
coming to you from Earth.
Uh, you probably
don't understand
a word I'm saying
right now, but, uh,
me and my friend Christopher
created this
communication device
to try to talk to aliens,
and I guess it works.
- [speaker squeals]
- Give 'em the Cliffnotes,
not the novel.
Okay. Oh, you're right.
Keep it tight. Okay.
So, uh, tell us
a little bit about you.
- [warbles]
- [distorted] Emily.
Did it just say my name?!
- It just said your name!
- Oh, my God!
- It just said my name!
- It said your name!
Said my name. Oh, my God.
[gasps]
[distorted] Christopher.
What?!
- They just said your name?
- They just said my name!
- They said your name!
- Oh, my God!
[distorted] Jungspars.
Jungspar.
Jungspar? Who's Jungspar?
[crackling]
[electricity surges]
[Chris sighs]
And you wanted to quit.
[knock at the door]
Can I help you?
[echoing] Will you let us in?
Oh, I-I'm sorry.
We're actually closed.
We open up again
tomorrow morning at 11:00.
Our friend is quite dehydrated.
We're just looking
for something cold to drink.
Uh, sorry. I already
closed the register,
so I can't really
sell you anything.
Um, there's a Smart and Zip
around the corner.
They're open 24 hours.
Okay. Have a nice night.
Creepy much?
[gasps]
Will you let us in?
[pounding on the door]
[slow pounding continues]
- [blow thumps]
- [metal clatters]
- [objects clatter]
- [yelps]
[panting]
Come on. Come on. Come on.
Come on.
Come on!
[knock at the door]
[Tobey] Jessie, it's me.
Open up.
- Tobey?
- Open up, babe.
Everything's okay.
[yelps]
Will you let us in?
Screw you.
Ouch.
- [bone cracks]
- [screams]
[groaning]
Okay, I'll let you in!
I'll let you in.
I mean,
just the fact that you guys
worked so hard
putting this together
and got something or somebody
to communicate back
is absolutely incredible.
I am so proud of both of you.
Emily, honey,
are you staying for dinner?
Sure. I guess.
Sweetie, we have to wash those
before you eat them. Remember?
You had that horrible bout
of diarrhea last time.
Jesus, Mom. Have a little couth.
Oh, I'm sorry. You're right.
Well, will you please
tell your sister
to come downstairs?
And if you
have to use the bathroom,
please use wet wipes.
Hysterical, Mom,
but Jessie's not home.
Where is she?
I don't know.
Her shift ended an hour ago.
Is her car here?
I told her no Tobey's
until the weekend.
Oh, you are
in serious trouble, Missy,
sending me
straight to voicemail.
Christopher, please
set up the table, sweetie.
- I got it.
- Thank you.
[Emily] Wait.
So has she not responded?
No, and she usually does
right away.
I'll solve this
once and for all.
She's still at work.
What?
How could she still be there?
[sighs] It's locked.
[pounding]
Jessie! Jessie, you in there?!
Let me go check the back door.
[Christopher] Jessie?
Mom. Mom.
- Huh?
- Give me a minute.
- What?
- I think I just sharted.
Honey, I told you
not to eat those grapes.
I know, Mom. I was just hungry.
I'm a growing boy, you know.
[clatter]
[metal creaks]
[Emily breathing heavily]
- [metal objects clatter]
- [gasps]
[metal objects clatter]
[door slams open]
- [footsteps shuffling]
- [guns cocking]
[man] Freeze!
[police dispatch chatter]
[Michelle] Um, I-I think
it was around 5:00.
- It was a text from her.
- [sirens approaching]
My God, I can't believe
this is happening.
You need to find her.
You need to find her now.
There are so many kids missing.
Something bad is happening.
[police dispatch chatter]
I'm scared, Em.
I'm really scared.
[chatter fades]
[doorbell rings]
[rain pattering]
Hello there, Emily.
Hi, Mr. Lutz.
This is my friend Christopher.
Nice to meet you, Christopher.
Uh, please come in.
Including your sister,
Christopher,
there's been seven missing
persons reports this week alone.
So do you know who these kids
are or where they're from?
No. No one does.
That's what makes it
so frustrating.
Some say it's a bunch
of meth kids from Canopy Falls.
Others think
it's a type of zombie.
But in all the research
I've done,
there's only been
one other account
of these black-eyed kids.
It happened in this town
over 50 years ago.
Over 25 missing persons,
and there was
only one eyewitness.
And his name is Frederick Munch.
He and his fiancée were taken
five days before their wedding.
Apparently they let him go.
Why?
[chuckles]
You'd have to ask him.
Is he still alive?
He is.
He lives over on Elm.
Wait, Munch.
You mean Mean Mr. Munch?
You know him?
Yeah.
All the kids know him.
His house is totally haunted.
Yeah, the kids created
the Munch challenge.
It's where you gotta walk up
to his creepy doorsteps
and ring his creepy doorbell
and try to make it out alive,
and one kid tried it, and...
He made it...
but then broke into a seizure
the minute he got home.
Well, I've been trying to talk
to him for the last six months.
Threatened to kill me
if I stepped on his property.
I'll talk to him.
You're kidding.
No, and you're coming.
That's not a good idea, Emily.
You have a better one?
[thunder rumbling]
[bird squawking]
[dog barking]
- Emily...
- Yeah?
I'm quaking.
Yeah, me, too.
- [dog barking]
- What if he cuts our heads off
and uses our bodies
as flotation devices?
I don't think that's possible.
Bodies don't float.
[Christopher]
We can literally run now,
and the least we'll suffer
is a seizure.
[doorbell buzzes]
[bird squawking]
[ominous music playing]
[sighs]
Okay, obviously
he's not home, so...
[Munch] Leave it by the door.
Uh, hi, Mr. Munch. I'm Emily,
and this is
my friend Christopher.
We live down the street.
Uh-huh.
[intercom clicks off]
Uh, Mr. Munch?
Mr. Munch!
[bird squawking]
Oh, well. We tried.
[doorbell buzzes]
Emily, come on. He obviously
doesn't want us here.
We're finding your sister.
[sighs]
Get off my property.
Mr. Munch, please help us.
Christopher's sister has been
taken by the black-eyed kids.
- [groans]
- Please just let us...
We should go.
[hinges creak]
Holy crap.
[hinges creaking]
Creepy A.F.
[clock chimes]
Jesus Christ.
[exhales]
[mournful piano music playing]
[Christopher] Could this house
be any creepier?
[Emily] Shh.
[Christopher] I didn't
know someone so creepy
could be so talented.
Christopher, shut up.
I think I just urinated myself.
Emily...
[Emily] Come on. Get a grip.
[piano music continues]
[piano music stops]
I haven't had one lesson.
[clock ticking]
I appreciate you letting us in.
That supposed to be a joke?
I'm sorry.
I-I didn't mean it that way.
We're just trying to get
all the information we can get.
The black-eyed kids.
Yes, exactly.
I haven't talked about this
in more than 50 years.
I was too scared to.
But with all
the kidnappings going on,
I feel I need to.
Thank you.
I saw 'em first
in the winter of '59.
They took me and my fiancée...
all of 'em...
with their alabaster skin...
and that jet-black hair...
black eyes.
Black as briquettes.
They had this awful odor.
Awful.
Smelled like...
rotten molasses and, uh...
pig droppings.
I can still smell it today.
They ended up taking
my sweet Juniper.
My fiancée.
And they let me go.
There's not a day that I
don't wish it was the opposite.
So where did they take her?
Some sort of portal.
A portal?
To where?
Space.
Space?
Outer space.
Like outer outer space?
Like rocket ship outer space?
This kid on the spectrum?
[laughs] Yeah, of course.
Outer space.
So are these
black-eyed kids aliens?
Yeah, that's what I'm saying.
They don't refer to themselves
as black-eyed kids.
They call themselves Jungspars.
Jungspars?
Every 20 years,
they come to Earth...
to abduct
adolescent girls and boys.
It's their harvesting time...
a way for them
to propagate the human race
on their planet for slavery.
I was there. I've seen it.
And believe me,
you don't want to see
the things that I've seen.
You've seen them, too,
haven't you?
So why do they ask you
that question,
to let them in?
Because they have to.
They need permission.
They don't like
being said no to.
So they will terrorize you...
until you say yes.
But whatever you do,
never say yes.
Trust me when I tell you
the pain that you will suffer.
Saying no will be nothing
compared to the pain that
you'll suffer if you say yes.
So how long
do they stay here for?
After researching,
I discovered that the duration
of each stay
was ten nights
from the first abduction,
not a minute later.
Holy crap.
I'm sorry, Mr. Munch,
but I have to go.
Hold on just one second,
young lady.
Take that.
In case you need
to summon them...
or cause severe pain.
Thanks.
I gotta skirt, too,
but nice meeting you.
I get it.
I'm a germophobe, too.
Fist bump club?
All good.
[Emily] Hurry up.
We only have 'til midnight.
I'm doing it as fast as I can!
Jesus!
[tense music playing]
[distorted] Jungspars.
[transmission chattering]
Jungspars.
[chattering]
[electricity crackles]
Damn it!
Bisquick! Let us in!
Thanks, Bisquick!
Go get 'em, Shark Tank.
[transmission chattering]
[frequencies warble]
[distorted] Jungspars.
No, no, no, no, no!
[pulling cord]
[engine grinding]
Yes, yes, yes, yes!
- [chatters]
- Jungspars.
[chatters]
Hello.
It's us, Emily and Christopher.
Uh, last time
we talked on here,
you mentioned
the word "Jungspars."
Could... could you please
tells us more about that?
- [static crackles]
- Hello?
Can you hear me?
[tone warbles]
Uh, it's us,
Emily and Christopher,
and we wanted to know some
more information on Jungspars.
[tone warbling]
[static crackles]
[distorted] Emily.
Christopher.
- Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
- Okay, okay.
Okay. Uh, it's us,
Yeah, Emily and Christopher.
Um, what do we call you?
Kluuk.
Okay, Kluuk.
Nice to officially meet you.
So, uh, can you tell us
more about Jungspars?
[static crackles]
Jungspars.
Emily...
beat them.
How do we beat them?
H-how do we do that?
Shine.
Shine? Shine what?
Hello?
[static crackles]
Light.
Shine.
Shine light?
Shine...
the...
light.
[music playing]
[insects chirping]
[owl hoots]
[scoffs] This is insane.
I told you no one would show up.
Give it a minute.
Not to mention
you made it so convenient
for them to chop our parts
into a hundred pieces
and bury us in the forest.
Christopher, they don't murder.
They abduct.
Oh, well, that makes me
feel so much better.
[Christopher sighs]
They're not coming, Em.
Think we need to reassess.
They'll show up.
[owl hoots]
[brush rustling]
- [wings flap]
- Oh, Jesus. The things I do
because I have a crush on you.
What?
Uh, I-I didn't say anything.
[footsteps crunching]
Hey.
Appreciate you showing up.
Of course.
So how do we get them back?
[blowing high-pitched tone]
- [boy] This is stupid.
- [girl] This isn't gonna work.
- [kids muttering]
- [scoffs]
[girl] I mean, seriously?
[tone continues]
[girl 2] Good plan, Emily.
Well, guess the old dude
gave us a defect.
[blows high-pitched tone]
Uh, Emily.
[footsteps shuffling]
[echoing] Will you let us in?
No chance...
witch.
Now!
[shrieking]
Oh, snap. This worked.
This frickin' worked.
Come on, Christopher.
Now!
[screaming]
Just tell us where our friends
are, and we'll let you go.
- [screaming]
- Where are our friends?
Tell us where our friends are,
and we'll let you go.
[screaming]
High beams!
Christopher.
Christopher!
Christopher! Christopher!
Emily, have you seen Scarlett?
No. Have you seen Christopher?
Christopher! Christopher.
Christopher!
[police dispatch chatter]
[Wilton] Well,
you seem to have a knack
for getting caught in the eye
of the storm, young lady.
They took Christopher!
I need to find him!
And we will find him.
In the meantime,
I want you to stay put
and focus on being here,
where you're safe.
You guys don't understand.
They're not human!
You don't know how they think!
Emily, let me
make myself clear.
If you leave this house,
I'm gonna have you arrested.
Are you comprehending me?
You gotta be kidding me.
Serious as a tornado.
You guys don't understand
that the people who are
still missing are still alive,
are we're running out of time!
[sighs]
Get some sleep.
We'll be right back, honey.
[police dispatch chatter]
[crying]
And this is
the exact same location
where both Carly Hudson and
Luke Freitag were taken from.
Authorities still have no clue
as to who's involved
in these snatchings,
but eyewitnesses
believe they're not human.
They're not human.
I don't know what they are.
- [girl] Where's Scarlett?
- [Emily] Christopher!
Christopher!
Where's Christopher?!
[insects chirping]
[gasps]
[police dispatch chatter]
Oh, damn it.
Oh, what am I...
[police dispatch chatter]
[knock at the door]
Come in.
They've got you
in isolation, huh?
Ah, Nana, please,
you gotta get me out of here.
They've taken Christopher.
Ohh. Sweetheart...
the police will take care of it.
No, they don't even
know where he is! But I do.
Well, you tell them then.
No, they think I'm crazy, Nana.
They don't believe me
when I try to tell them!
Look, you know
my friend Cindy's dad's
a policeman, right?
So all I want to do
is just tell him,
and he'll take care
of everything.
So please just let me
get out of here
so I can do that.
Sweetheart.
Please, Nana.
I don't want to lose
another best friend.
[sighs]
[Carol] I think we need to take
a lot more responsibility
for what's going on here.
I mean, when do you actually
spend quality time with her,
- just the two of you?
- Oh, okay. Okay,
so all this going on
right now is 'cause of me?
- Is that right?
- Well, possibly.
- [thump]
- [Nana moans]
[Mark] Mom!
I've fallen...
and I can't get up.
- God. Okay, what happened?
- Oh, my God.
Can I help you up? Come on.
- I don't know.
- Here we go. Here we go.
- [grunting]
- Okay. Okay?
[Nana] Yeah. I don't know.
[music playing]
Shoot.
[ominous music playing]
[car approaching]
Need a hand?
Maybe this isn't the safest
place to be right now, you know?
We're really close.
It says
he's literally right here.
May I?
Sure.
You're right. He's right here,
or at least
his phone's right here.
We need to hurry up.
It's almost midnight!
- [brush rustles]
- [whispering] This way.
Come on.
[brush rustling]
What is this?
I think we found their Airbnb.
[distant humming]
I'm starting to think
this wasn't such a good idea.
[distant fluttering]
[fluttering]
What do we do now?
Seriously?
You got a better idea?
[fluttering]
[pad beeping]
[energy humming]
[footsteps crunching]
Hey there, buddy.
Just gonna take
some of our friends back home.
You cool with that?
[screaming]
Oh, my God. Are you guys okay?
Thank goodness you're here.
Oh, my God. Yeah.
How did you...
We're trying to get
you guys out of here.
- [boy] Please help.
- Oh, my God.
[girl] Get us out.
[pad beeping]
Move.
You really think
that's gonna work?
[laughs]
Jessie!
Oh, my God.
[Mr. Jayo] Oh. Wow.
- [chains rattle]
- Emily.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah. Are you?
Yeah, I'm okay. I'm okay.
Um, you need
to go get Christopher.
They took him
and some other kids.
They're gonna send 'em
away somewhere.
- Where are they?
- Down the corridor.
Okay. Take care of these guys.
Emily, wait!
Proceed forward.
No.
No. No.
No. No. No.
[screams]
- Proceed forward.
- Here's the thing.
I'm not really ready for this,
so if you could just me go?
Please just let me go? No.
No, no, no, no, no, no!
- No, no, no, no, no!
- Let him go!
I know it's hard to see
with those black eyes of yours,
but my finger is literally
on the light switch.
You think you'll get out alive?
Let him go.
- [grunts]
- [chain clinks]
We're gonna get out of here.
[wailing]
[girl] Emily.
Rachel?
It wasn't your fault.
Emily, you didn't
do anything wrong.
I slipped off the roof.
It was an accident.
But I'm okay.
I'm alive.
Take my hand, Emily,
so we can play together
just like we used to.
[panting]
[ominous music playing]
[gasping]
So we meet again.
Had a feeling we would.
I have the suspicion you know
what I am going to ask you.
So will you?
Will you let us in?
I suggest you make this
simple for both of us.
Will you let us in?
Hell no.
[screams]
- [girl] Run, Emily!
- [yells]
Em, back of you!
[wailing]
Get out!
[wailing continues]
[screams]
[cheering]
Thought I lost you.
It's okay. I'm right here.
I'm right here.
[music playing]
[Carol] Oh, did you
bring your retainers?
[Emily] Yes, Mom.
[Mark] Okay, I think we
double-checked everything
at least four times.
[Christopher]
May I take your bag, ma'am?
- Thank you, sir.
- You're right. Sorry.
How 'bout the slippers?
- Got those?
- [Emily] Yep.
[Christopher] I don't think
I slept a minute last night.
- Me, too.
- Listen...
about the crush thing...
Drop it.
But for the record,
if I was ten,
- I'd totally date you.
- Really?
So there's hope.
I mean, "if you were able
to go back in time" type hope.
[chuckles] How dopey.
Next project, time machine.
[laughs]
Em.
I love you.
I'm so proud of you.
Cape Canaveral,
that's pretty rad.
Wow, Dad.
Didn't know you were so hip.
Nah, your dad's still got
some teenager left in him.
Oh, God, Dad. That's so creepy.
[gasps] Jessie!
[laughs]
What's this?
They're yours now.
They're brand-new.
Aww. Thank you so much.
Have so much fun.
And if he annoys,
you just flick his nose.
Not funny.
[laughs]
All right, you two.
NASA's waiting.
[Emily sighs]
All right, here we go.
[mouthing words]
God, are they having, like,
a marathon today or something?
[crowd cheering]
[Christopher] Holy sweetness.
This is for us!
Oh, my God, this is insane!
I'm so shook right now.
There's Principal Malinsky.
Guess this is what happens
when you're local heroes.
[crowd cheering]
[Christopher] Look!
There's Mrs. Barnett!
And Dr. Bauer!
Did she just blow you a kiss?
[cheering continues]
[footsteps shuffling]
[ominous music playing]
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
[instrumental playing]