(MultiCom Jingle)
(dramatic music)
(blasting)
- My name is Josh Kirby.
I was just your average ninth grader.
My biggest problem was
getting good grades.
And my idea of excitement
was racing my bicycle.
Yes!
I never thought time
would catch up with me.
But I couldn't have imagined
that hundreds of years from now,
mankind would invent the Nullifier,
a device capable of controlling
or destroying the universe.
A scientist named Irwin 1138
tried to disassemble
and hide the Nullifier,
but even he couldn't stop it.
- [Irwin] Dr. Zoetrope!
- Give me the Nullifier.
- You're too late!
- It's not too late.
- Irwin and Zoetrope have
been chasing each other
across the galaxy, trying to be the first
to find the Nullifier's pieces.
This time, they're gonna land in 1995.
The place?
My front yard.
Now, I'm going along for
the ride of all time!
What's going on?
Where are we?
- [Irwin] I hope you're prepared
to do battle, young man.
This will be a war time
and Dr. Zoetrope will take no prisoners.
- [Josh] We've got help from a warrior.
- My name is Azabeth Siege.
- She's amazing!
And a magical creature called Prism,
to show us the way.
Together, we're on a quest through time,
visiting different worlds
to fight for the Nullifier's pieces.
- I'm obviously in the right
place, and the right time.
- Because if Zoetrope ever
assembles the Nullifier,
he'll conquer time itself.
I've gotta try and save the universe.
(heroic music)
I was just a 14-year-old kid
before my adventure began.
But now, I'm Josh Kirby, Time Warrior.
- [Narrator] On the last chapter
of Josh Kirby, Time Warrior.
- I'm obviously in the right
place, and the right time.
(screaming)
(buzzing)
- These things sting like
bees back home, only worse!
- On the other side of
that bridge is a nightmare.
- Josh Kirby, run!
- Oh no!
- Come on, jump!
(screaming)
Don't look at its eyes!
She's slipping rather quickly, Josh.
Josh?
- Five minutes.
- Great jumping hounds!
You're summoning your own time storm.
Josh, be careful!
- What are you trying to do, poison me?
- I was somehow able to turn back time.
- [Irwin] You did it! It worked!
(buzzing)
- Zoetrope!
- Toss me the Nullifier
component so I can pull you up.
- No, I'd rather see it lost
forever than in your hands.
- Pull the past from out of my mind.
You can do it.
You're a time warrior.
- Thank heavens I was able to recalibrate
Colonel Damon's blaster to
match my own palm print.
Are you all right, Josh?
- Yeah I'm fine, but you
didn't have to shoot him!
- Ah, forget his evil lies.
Trying to turn you
against me is child's play
for an evil genius like him.
- Irwin?
Let me probe your time memories.
- Never!
(dramatic music)
Hand over the final Nullifier
component now, Josh!
- No.
No, not until I know the truth.
- Please, Josh.
After all we've been through together,
don't force me to blast
you to smithereens!
- Irwin, I don't understand!
I thought we were friends.
I thought we were out to
save the world together.
- We are friends, Josh.
You're just too young
to be able to understand
all the subtle nuances of the situation.
- Yeah.
Yeah, but I'm not too young to understand
that friends don't point plasma blasters
set for disintegrate at each other.
- He's no one's friend, Josh.
Except for the evil tyrants
who rule the 25th century without mercy.
- Quiet, you!
- Dr. Zoetrope!
Irwin, I can't believe you did that.
- Don't make this any harder for me
than it already is, Josh.
Now hand me the final Nullifier component.
- No.
- I'll count to three.
One,
two.
- Josh Kirby!
Irwin, what's going on?
(muttering)
- Oh, put a sock in it, Prism.
You excuse for a pet.
- Irwin's gone rogue.
- I beg to differ, young miss.
I am no rogue.
I'm a loyal servant of
the utopian dynasty.
I'm Minister of Science for all of Earth.
If I abandon my mission to
keep the reassembled Nullifier
out of the hands of
enemies of the state, then,
then you could call me rogue.
- Irwin, what the heck
are you talking about?
- I've said too much already.
Hand the final Nullifier
component over to me now, Josh.
Before I disintegrate Azabeth!
Finally.
Just one last step.
- What are you doing?
- Oh don't worry Josh.
My staff is too low on
energy to be a lethal weapon.
But its micro-computer
is still working in tip-top condition.
I didn't lay a finger
on that young hooligan
thanks to Prism, who is so
adept at transporting his matter
from one location to
another on a mere whim.
- Irwin, if you're trying to impress me
with your scientific
know-how, it won't work!
- That's where you're
wrong, my young friend.
It will work.
I've just entered Prism's
bio-codes into my micro-computer,
transforming him into
a matter transmitter.
Like so!
(dramatic music)
- Irwin!
Irwin!
Come back!
- I'm truly sorry, Josh Kirby.
It would appear that Irwin 1138
is not the friend he claimed to be.
I too trusted him completely.
And I should have been more careful.
It is the very first code of Kang.
Things are not always as they appear.
- But Azabeth, I don't understand!
Why would Irwin do that, why?
- [Zoetrope] I can tell you why, Josh.
- Are you okay?
- Just a bit shaken up.
My time armor protected me from the brunt
of Irwin's disintegrator blast.
- Well for goodness sakes,
tell us what's going on!
And what is Irwin really after?
- I can do better than tell you Josh.
I can show you.
That is, you can reach inside
my mind and see for yourself.
It's time to trust me now, Josh.
You can access images from the past
as easily as rewinding a
primitive 20th century videotape.
You're a time warrior.
Concentrate, Josh.
Concentrate.
- [Josh] I can see it.
It's gotta be the 25th century.
Some sort of big city.
But it's, it's nothing like I pictured.
It's nothing like I
pictured the future at all.
It's dark, and sort of creepy.
It's you, Dr. Zoetrope!
And Irwin.
It looks like the two of you
are arguing over something,
but I can't quite hear what you're saying.
- Concentrate harder, Josh.
Pull the sounds of the
future from out of my past.
Don't you realize what
you have done, Irwin?
By turning over this ancient
piece of hyper-advanced
alien technology which
you happened to find.
- That is a Decimator, and
I did not happen to find it.
It was my ingenious Klaatu formula
for locating interstellar refuse.
- Klaatu formula, don't make me laugh!
A radon storm happened
to deposit that thing
a half a mile away from this
very laboratory of yours.
You practically stumbled onto it.
- I'd have you know, it was a
carefully calculated stumble.
- Don't you realize
that by turning the Decimator
over to the Supreme Prefect,
you have doomed all of humanity to suffer
under a yoke of brutal tyranny forever?
- Wild exaggerations.
As Minister of Science,
I would never permit such things to occur.
If I could help it, that is.
- That's it, isn't it?
All you really care about
is that ridiculous job
and that foolish title.
I had it from age seven to 12,
and turned it down eight years running,
and would never have accepted
it from a totalitarian moron
like the Supreme Prefect.
- Maybe my ambition is unquenchable.
But on the scale of character defense,
your unbounded egotistical arrogance
beats my ambition 10 to one.
Do you hear me, Zoetrope?
10 to one!
- Arrogance?
Well, that's quite refreshing
coming from the Minister of Science.
- [Josh] Where are we now?
- [Zoetrope] It's my secret laboratory,
mere moments before
the beginning of chaos.
- Seize him!
- Blast you Irwin, how did you find me?
- You did yourself in this time, Zoetrope.
Only you would be so supercilious
as to dub your secret laboratory,
The Fortress of Brilliance,
and to have it listed among the top 10
scientific attractions of the universe.
Amazing.
So the rumors were true.
It is another alien device,
similar to the Decimator.
- Not quite, you jealous old windbag.
This device is the counterpart
to that hideous doomsday weapon
you've handed over to the Supreme Prefect.
The Decimator is the only
thing that keeps the Prefect
and his utopian dynasty in power,
and this device will nullify
the Decimator completely.
Once that has occurred,
the Supreme Prefect's evil
reign will be finished.
- Silence!
You, Dr. Emile Zoetrope 366.
Youngest Nobel Science Laureate
in all of Earth's history.
Winner of the Colonial prize
for the advancement of
quantum physics, at age four!
Simultaneous graduate of
16 post-doctoral studies
while still a pre-teenager.
And arrogant user of a first
name as well as a number.
You are under arrest.
And as for this Nullifier.
As of this moment, I decree possession
of such an alien device
to be scientific heresy,
punishable by 20 years on a mining colony.
- You'll never get away with this, Irwin.
It'll be child's play foiling
your pathetic schemes.
I'm still more intelligent
than you and you know it.
- What is the point of intelligence
if you are denied the power to use it?
And it's remarks like that
that will get you yourself
nullified, for good.
As an example of nullifying
something for good.
- Some example, old man.
The Nullifier is completely impervious
to attack of any kind.
Nothing you or anyone
else can do can harm it.
- I've just thought of an ingenious way
of ensuring that this alien
device is never activated.
Rest assured that your days
as numero uno scientist
are finished for good.
Take him away!
- You'll never win, Irwin!
- Oh yes I will!
Try to ruin my plans, will you?
There's only room for one
all-powerful alien device in this time.
(cackling)
- [Zoetrope] So, Irwin 1138
inaugurated his ingenious plan
for maintaining control
over the Nullifier.
He accessed the time stream
and scattered each of
the Nullifier components
to the far corners of time and space.
(dramatic music)
- Prepare for the storm.
Next.
We need another 93 seconds.
Seal the door.
Quick, load the final component.
- Let's go.
(shouting)
- Dr. Zoetrope!
(gun firing)
(beeping)
- Give me the Nullifier, you lunatic.
- You're too late, Zoetrope.
- It's never too late for me.
In the name of all creation,
twisted old man, what have you done?
- Are you all right?
Josh Kirby, what did you see?
- The truth.
Azabeth, I saw the truth!
I can't believe it.
Irwin has been deceiving us all along.
He's the villain, not Dr. Zoetrope!
- Perhaps villain is too harsh, Josh.
Irwin is merely a jealous old man,
desperate to be seen as the
smartest being of his era.
Unfortunately, the need
to prove himself better
than everyone else instead of
being the person he truly is
may very well doom the universe.
- You mean, the Nullifier was really meant
to save the future, not destroy it?
- That's about the size of it, yeah.
I saw this with my own eyes!
- All of this means nothing now.
Irwin has escaped, and
without a time travel device
we're stuck here in the
center of the Earth,
powerless to stop him.
- But there must be something we can do.
A warrior can't just give up.
Besides, we are all partly responsible
for the success of Irwin
1138's nefarious plan.
We've been helping him all this time.
- Of course!
All this time.
The last thing Irwin
said before he took off
was something about putting
my theory to the test.
- You had a theory?
- Yeah sure, the Kirby theory
of temporal replacement.
- Don't you mean, temporal displacement?
- No, I mean temporal replacement.
As in retracing your steps through time
in order to restore
the overall time stream
to its original state.
- Crude, but interesting.
If proven correctly,
this would totally debunk
Irwin 1138's own time
displacement postulate.
I can't believe he would throw
his own theory out the window
just to test yours.
- That old man may be
an aging megalomaniac
with delusions of grandeur,
but he is no fool.
If he thought Josh
Kirby's theory would work,
he's try it in an instant.
- Even presuming that we
have correctly deciphered
Irwin's own plan, so what?
Our only chance to stop him
would be to intercept him before
he reached your time, Josh.
That was my first stop
on my trek through time,
so that would be Irwin's last
before heading home to the 25th century.
- Yeah, but my time
doesn't exist any more.
Does it?
- Not at the moment.
But, assuming that your theory
has any validity whatsoever,
by the time Irwin gets there,
he will have repaired enough of the damage
to the time stream that your world
will be almost completely
restored to normal.
- You know, Dr. Zoetrope,
my time powers have been getting easier
and easier for me to use.
Just maybe.
- Wait a minute, Josh.
You're not thinking what
I think you're thinking.
- I've been able to turn back
time a few minutes or so.
Just maybe I can use myself
as a time travel device.
- Absolutely impossible.
No one can travel through time
without temporal displacement
technology of some sort.
- Yeah, well I'm not no one.
You said it yourself.
I'm a time warrior.
- I've won.
I've won!
(cackling)
- All right, everybody.
Hold on tight.
If this works, it'll be
like swimming underwater
without an oxygen tank,
or flying through the air
without a plane, or--
- Crossing the poison river of Andor
without a purification craft.
- Yeah, that sounds about right.
- If this does work Josh Kirby,
I will personally see to it
that you become a legend
in the annals of time.
- A legend, huh?
Well even my dad will
be impressed with that.
Okay, here goes something.
I hope.
(electric buzzing)
- It's working!
(triumphant music)
- I did it!
- (laughing) I knew you
could do it, Josh Kirby!
- Let's save our congratulations
until we have achieved our goal.
We still must stop Irwin 1138.
- What a party pooper.
All right, next stop, Green Oaks, USA.
September 12th, 1994.
20th century, here we come!
- And now, to put young
Josh's theory into action.
Excellent!
Let the experiment continue.
- Stingers!
- (cackling) You're a genius, Josh!
You're almost as smart as me.
(blasting)
(screaming)
Whew, that was close.
- Nice try!
Strike two!
(shouting)
(laughing)
(screaming)
- Oh, it's those fleshy-headed morons!
They're trying to make
me into a human pet.
Enjoy your bizarre existence
while you can, mutants!
When I've returned time to normal,
your era might not even exist! (cackling)
- This isn't good, Josh.
- What's happening?
- Irwin Must be successfully retracing
our journey through the ages.
Hypertime is beginning to
return to its natural state,
freeing itself of a displaced time stream.
- You mean time is being
returned to normal?
- Precisely.
- That's good, isn't it?
- If we were to return
time to normal, yes.
But Irwin is restoring
the natural time stream
for one reason and one reason only,
so he can put the Nullifier
alien device out of commission,
this time, for good.
- What in the name of Kang is that?
- No, not now!
- It's an energy distortion
in the time stream.
A time wave.
- And it's headed straight for us!
- Josh, you've gotta bring
us out of hypertime, now!
- Well sure, but I'm not sure
I've locked on the right time yet.
- Look out!
(screaming)
My head.
- Yeah, I just feel like
I ate some moldy cheese.
- That was definitely the
worst experience of my life.
- Yeah, me too.
And I'm only 14.
Hey, we did it!
This is it!
- This is where you live, Josh Kirby?
- Yeah, it's all back to normal.
This is my house.
Where I live with my dad.
Oh boy is he gonna be glad to see me.
But it looks different somehow.
- Remember Joshua, we arrived
here before encountered Irwin.
Before any of our adventures took place.
More likely your father will wonder
why you're not still in school.
- Josh Kirby, this Green
Oaks, USA is remarkable.
- Really?
I always thought it was
kind of dull myself.
- Oh, you should be very proud,
and very thankful for your home.
Josh Kirby, a place like this Green Oaks,
this is what I and my people
have been fighting for
for generations!
- Gee Azabeth, I've never
really thought of it
like that before.
- No slave pens.
No pain centers to herd
people into like cattle.
No acid pools, no guard to make sure
you do not cross into the restricted zone.
- Yeah, I guess I do have
a lot to be thankful for.
Holy moly, that was my dad!
Why didn't he stop, why
didn't he recognize me?
Dad!
Hey Dad.
Dad, don't you see, it's me, Josh!
Dad!
He doesn't see me.
I don't get it.
Hey Dad, it's me Josh.
Why don't you recognize me?
- Is that really your father, Josh Kirby?
He doesn't seem to want to
acknowledge your presence.
- Of course, it must
have been the time wave.
- What, the time wave made my
dad deaf and blind to his son?
- Quite the opposite, Josh.
It made us invisible.
- Wait, come again?
- When you traveled through time,
you also traveled through space.
Now it's obvious the time wave must have
thrown off your concentration just enough
so that even though our chono-journey
was completed successfully,
our spacial journey to
this area was disrupted.
- Holy invisible cow!
It's true.
- Of course it's true.
The most brilliant man of the 25th century
does not state conjecture.
You see, although we are close
enough to this time plane
to view its occurrences,
our spacial fields
remain displaced, perhaps by mere seconds.
- So, even though we
can see and hear events
in this time period, they
can't see and hear us?
- Precisely.
A more experienced time warrior
could have navigated that time wave.
But, you are still learning the ropes.
- Well, Zoetrope may have
turned out to be the good guy,
but he's still an egotistical know-it-all.
- It is the 19th code of Kang.
Large ideas often spring from large heads.
- There's something
different about all this.
I can't quite put my finger on it.
- That's not surprising.
It's not every day you return home
and no one bothers to notice.
- No, but it's more than that.
My dad looks different somehow.
And my house too.
It looks like someone repainted it.
We've been wanting to
do that for a long time,
but we never really had the money.
And even our truck looks weird.
It's usually covered with mud and rust,
but now it's shiny.
(muttering)
What is it, Prism?
It's just a newspaper,
Prism, I don't see...
Oh no.
- [Azabeth] Josh Kirby,
is something wrong?
- The date.
That's why everything looks so weird.
My house is freshly painted.
The truck is brand new, and
my dad almost looks young.
And that thing he's building?
That Genghis Khan's doghouse.
We got here before Irwin all right.
14 years before.
- Who is this Genghis Khan?
- Why, a 13th century
Mongol warlord, of course.
But why Josh's dad would
be building him a doghouse
is beyond me.
- You think you are so smart, Zoetrope.
But it makes perfect sense.
Where else would a mongrel
warlord live except a doghouse?
- That's Mongol, you ignorant Amazon!
Mongol.
- Ignorant, I will show
you who is ignorant.
You can say it, fathead!
- Okay, now stop it.
Break it up, you guys.
Genghis Khan's my pet dog.
- I think I liked you better
when you were a villain, Zoetrope.
At least then I could have broken your arm
in 13 different places and
not felt guilty about it.
- Try it, you alien freak.
Come on.
I am master of 52
interstellar combat styles.
Come on.
- Well now you've done it.
You pompous, insensitive jerk.
Just because Azabeth looks different
doesn't mean you can call her alien freak
and get away with it.
- I didn't mean it.
I just got a little
full of myself, I guess.
- You owe her an apology, Dr. Zoetrope.
You're not the only one around here
who's trying to save
the universe, you know.
Azabeth is the best partner
anybody could have and you know it.
And another thing.
Just because you're smarter than everybody
doesn't mean you're always right.
- Please forgive me, Miss Siege.
I was wrong to call you anything
than what you really are.
Which is, the bravest female
tech warrior I've ever met.
- I am the only female tech
warrior you have ever met.
You self-centered, patronizing egghead.
But I accept your apology anyway.
(dog barks)
What is that little monster?
- That's no monster, it's a puppy.
In fact, that's my puppy.
That's Genghis Khan!
How did he see me?
- See may not be quite correct, Josh.
Animals have more highly-developed
faculties than humans.
Perhaps he merely senses us, or...
- What now?
- The solution is simple enough.
Josh will simply have to concentrate,
use his time warrior powers,
and zap us forward 14 years
to the year when Irwin is due to show up.
- Uh, there's just one
problem, Dr. Zoetrope.
I can't always use my time warrior powers.
- What?
Why didn't you tell me?
- Well I thought you knew.
You seem to know everything
else about being a time warrior.
- You mean we're marooned here
until you've regained your warrior powers?
- That's about the size of it, yeah.
- That could be an eternity.
Every minute we're stuck here
is another minute Irwin has
to dispose of the life-saving
Nullifier, forever.
We have got to do something
before it's too late.
- I did it!
I'm back!
- Irwin 1138?
- Irwin 1138, esteemed Minister of Science
and most brilliant man of
the 25th century speaking,
who is this?
- It is I, Irwin 1138.
Report to me immediately
on your whereabouts
for the last several days.
- Ah, Supreme Prefect.
Yes, excuse me, I only
just got in a minute ago.
I was preparing my report
and was about to call you
immediately, Supreme One.
- There have been rumors, Irwin 1138.
Rumors of Zoetrope plotting against me.
Roumors of an indestructible
device called the Nullifier.
A device some say
capable of eradicating the
effects of my Decimator
and bringing me down in ruins.
- The Nullifier does
exist, oh munificent one.
- What?
- But not to worry.
I have the situation under control
and have completely eradicated any threat
to you or your Decimator.
- You realize, Irwin 1138,
if I were to fall,
you too would immediately be nullified.
From Minister of Science,
to public enemy number two.
Number two, after me of course.
- Take is from me, oh splendiferous one.
The Nullifier's threat to
you is completely eradicated.
- That's what I like to hear.
- I'm getting too old
for this sort of thing.
Summon my technicians
and secure the facility.
- This,
will serve our purpose.
- What are you gonna
do, mow the time stream?
- Your sarcasm is not appreciated.
This, however, is.
The metal blades could serve
as a transtemporal heating device.
- Well I don't know, Doc.
If you can make a time machine
out of my dad's Lawnmaster,
you must be the most
brilliant guy in any century.
- [Woman] John, have you seen my homework?
- [Azabeth] Is something
wrong, Josh Kirby?
- That voice.
- [Woman] John?
- [Zoetrope] It's female, obviously.
Probably your mother, right?
- No, that's impossible.
She passed away almost 14 years ago.
- [John] It's down here
honey, in the kitchen!
(sentimental music)
- Three more weeks until finals, pal.
Can't afford to waste any time.
- [John] Well gee honey,
with all you've been through,
don't you think you oughta
give yourself a rest?
- I wish I could.
But honey, you know we can't stay
at my mom and dad's house forever.
- Well I can do some
overtime down at the plant.
- We talked about this.
The only way we're gonna
get a place of our own
is if I get my Master's degree
and then that engineering job.
- But I'm supposed to be the man.
- Yes dear.
- Mom, Dad, it's me, Josh!
- They can't hear us, Josh.
Our voices suffer from the
same spacial displacement
that plagues the rest of our bodies.
- But she's alive.
My mom's alive.
- Well would you at least stop wearing
that stopwatch around your neck?
You're starting to look
like a gym teacher.
- Honey, they only give you 45 minutes
for the quantum physics final.
I gotta go over sample
questions, pace myself.
You know the routine.
- Oh yeah, believe me, I know it.
- Besides, I got this little gem
for Mrs. Crabtree for two dollars.
I fixed it, it's good as new.
- Well I don't know honey,
it looks more like just
one more clock to me.
- That's what you say every time
I add a new time piece to my collection.
- Hey Mom.
It's me, I'm right here!
- What's the matter, honey?
- Nothing.
I must be working too hard or something.
(baby crying)
- That sounds like a baby crying.
- Duty calls.
- I can't believe it.
- Come on Josh.
Oh, come on little man, it's lunch time.
Yes.
Here you go.
Come on Josh, come on
little man, it's lunch time.
- I don't believe it.
- You're my little hero, aren't you Josh.
You're gonna grow up to be
big and strong like your dad,
and smart like your mom.
You're gonna be somebody important, Josh.
Somebody who's gonna make a
difference in this crazy world.
You just wait and see.
- What?
What is it, what are you trying to say?
- Its incredible.
He's in two places at once.
Two beings composed of
exactly the same DNA,
exact same molecular structure.
The fact that two Joshes can co-exist
in the same space time
continuum is, astonishing.
- Well.
You are quite an adorable
child, Josh Kirby.
Your parents seem like very
hardworking people, Josh Kirby.
- Yeah.
I can't believe I'm seeing them together.
Especially my mom.
- You never knew your mother?
- No.
I was too young when she...
Well, you know.
- This is a great day for you, Josh Kirby.
It's not every child that gets
to see his long-lost parent.
Even if she can't see him.
- Hey, where's Dr. Zoetrope?
- Outside in the garage,
working on the time mower.
- I'm almost done.
Even though it's not easy
working under these primitive,
impoverished conditions, all
I need is one last component
to make my time mower complete.
A three-pronged adapter.
- Not again.
- That child must not be harmed.
If anything happens to baby Josh,
teenage Josh could cease to exist.
(baby gurgles)
- I didn't know I was
such a problem child.
- I'm just happy I don't have to babysit
for you every day, Josh Kirby.
(groaning)
- Quick, he's coming.
- The time mower!
- Josh!
Josh, what are you doing
out of your playpen.
That's the last time I
let you out of my sight.
I gotta watch you extra
careful from now on.
If anything ever happened to you,
I don't know what I'd do.
(baby cries)
Uh oh.
Someone needs a new diaper.
- This is humiliating.
I just messed myself
in front of everybody.
- Well, you said your
father was overprotective.
At least now you know how he got that way.
It was your own fault to
begin with, Josh Kirby.
- This is more embarrassing
than baby pictures.
- Well I think it's cute.
And I think you're cute,
no matter what age you happen to be.
All this excitement has made me hungry.
Josh Kirby, do I have your
permission to search the contents
of your family's cryogenic
food preservation unit?
- You wanna raid my fridge?
Yeah, go ahead.
You're the most brilliant man
of the 25th century, right?
- Yeah.
- Do you understand girls?
- Sometimes.
- Well, do you think
that when she said cute,
she meant, you're so cute
I'd like to pinch your cheeks
and accidentally break all the
blood vessels in your face,
or, you're so cute I'd let
you take me out on a date,
and maybe let you give
me a kiss on my doorstep
when we say goodnight?
- How old did you say you were?
- 14.
- But I'll be 16 in 23 months.
- Josh.
Women,
girls, are a mystery.
And every man must attempt
to unravel that mystery
on his own.
- But I hate mysteries.
- And another thing.
It's best not to drive
yourself crazy about this.
But Azabeth Siege is from the future.
A future far beyond the 25th century.
A future that may no longer exist
if our mission is successful.
It's best I take your
relationship with her
one moment at a time.
- Should we prepare for
the storm, Minister?
- Not yet.
I'm going to try something new.
- Come on, Genghis.
There you go.
- Yay, Daddy.
Nice job honey, you did good.
- It's time, Josh.
Hold on tight.
Next stop, the year 2494.
- Well Dr. Zoetrope.
Not only are we still in the 20th century,
but we're six inches tall!
- Perhaps I miscalculated a bit.
- Do I hear an admission of fault?
- Keep back!
- It's gone, Minister.
You actually managed
to destroy one of your
millennium steel tool dies.
- Not quite.
I've merely rendered it
invisible. (laughing)
(sentimental music)
- Well, Azabeth was right, Mom.
This is a great day for me.
I mean, I never thought I'd
get the chance to see you.
Not in this life, at least.
And if I did see you, I never thought
you'd be the size of the
Jolly Green Giant, either.
(sighs) But no matter how big you are,
you're still beautiful, Mom.
I kept this picture of
us, at home, on my table,
just like you.
I used to have dreams sometimes.
What you'd be like, the fun
things we'd do together.
All kinds of stuff.
But then I'd wake up, and...
Well I just wanted to say,
this is reality Mom,
and it's better than any
dream I could ever have.
- Josh Kirby?
Dr. Zoetrope sent me.
12 hours is almost up.
It's time for you to use your powers
to take us to the 25th century,
and bring the battle back to Irwin 1138.
- Well maybe we could stay somehow.
I don't know, wait another 12 hours, or...
- I am sorry, Josh Kirby.
I know that you missed
your mother very much.
And it's important that
you spend as much time
with her as possible.
But you...
You are the only chance
for the future of mankind.
You know which is more important.
- But Azabeth.
It's just, I missed her so much.
I didn't realize how much
until I finally got the chance to see her.
Well maybe with more time,
I can figure out a way
to communicate with her,
just let her know I'm here.
- I know it is difficult
when you are faced with
a personal decision.
And at the same time, a bigger duty calls.
It is a hard life we
humans, and half-humans,
must sometimes lead.
- Isn't there a code of Kang
that sums it all up for me
and tells me what I should do?
- I'm all out of codes
of Kang, Josh Kirby.
This one you have to decide for yourself.
- Well, I've gotta go.
I've gotta try and save the universe.
It's nothing really.
Well, it's been great seeing you.
Or, meeting you, that is.
Oh, good luck on your final.
I'm sure you'll do great.
Hey, don't just take it, ace it.
Goodbye, Mom.
I love you.
- Don, Don.
Don, wake up.
- What is it?
- There are these little people.
- Whoa whoa, slow down, little
people, what do you mean?
- Honey, they were right there.
- I don't see any little people, sweetie.
- You must think I'm nuts.
- No, no.
What I think is that between
your schoolwork and the baby,
you're spreading yourself a little thin.
- But Don.
- Listen.
Too much stress can cause bad dreams.
Nightmares.
- Okay.
- Besides, the only little person
we have to worry about
in this house is Josh.
Goodnight.
- Goodnight.
- Dr. Zoetrope!
They can see us!
- It's nothing.
Apparently a side effect to
our miniaturized stature.
I'm fairly certain we'll be returned
to our rightful dimensions
once we're back in hypertime,
which won't be long now.
12 hours are up, Josh.
Your time warrior powers
must have regenerated by now.
Let's head for the 25th
century immediately.
The future must be saved.
- All right, hang on tight.
Look out Irwin, here we come.
(dramatic music)
- What's happening?
Why isn't is working?
- I don't know.
I am doing everything the same.
- Yeah, well concentrate, Josh.
It must work, or the world will be lost
and the future will be doomed.
Concentrate.
- Look, Dr. Zoetrope, I'm trying, honest.
Maybe I need more time.
- That is not it!
It ha been more than 12 hours!
Now why aren't your time
warrior powers working?
Why?
(baby crying)
- Hang on Josh honey, hang on.
It's okay, it's okay, Josh.
Mom loves you.
- That's it.
Of course.
- What's it?
And why can't I summon the time lining?
- It makes perfect sense.
- Oh goodness gracious,
it's all right, it's okay.
- I knew there had to be
some anomaly when two beings
of the exact same molecular structure
occupy the same time and space.
Well, this is it.
The infant Josh Kirby
is a natural inhabitant
of this time period.
Therefore, the time space continuum
is rejecting our Josh
Kirby's metahuman abilities.
- Could you try that again
Zoetrope, in English?
- Basically it boils down to this.
There's only room for one time
warrior in this time period,
and he's it.
Good luck asking him to
transport us through time.
- Look, Dr. Zoetrope,
this is a setback, I know.
But we can't give up.
We've got to find a way
to get to the future.
- With what, hmm?
My good looks?
This is the late 20th century.
That was my mistake with the time mower.
There's no technology here
even remotely advanced enough
to jerry-rig a time travel device.
It's 1980.
They barely have VCRS.
- So what are you saying?
In order to whip up some sort
of time machine that works,
we need some technology from the future?
- Yes.
- Well you're wearing it!
And so are you, and so are you!
- [Zoetrope] Josh, what do you mean?
- The CDLs!
- Josh, you're a genius.
With the sophisticated machinery
from our chrono-displacement locks,
I may, just may, be able
to rig something up.
With these various
doohickeys we've gathered up,
and with these electrodes
as a primary power source,
we might just be in business.
I just have to make a
few more adjustments,
and we'll be ready to try it out.
- The steel mesh from the
screen door will come in handy.
You'll need some sort of
battle garb of your own
if you're going to encounter
Irwin's time armor.
- You know what?
This helmet actually looks pretty cool,
for a thimble.
- Thanks.
It reminded me of the battle helmet
worn by the Daconian guards of my time.
They were most honored
heroes of my people.
Until the slavers wiped them out.
- That's it!
It's not time armor, but it'll have to do.
- So let's go!
Time's a-wasting.
- Unfortunately this
machine's only powerful enough
to take one person through time.
But it will require the
use of all the CDL units.
- Wait a minute, without the CDLs,
we can't remain in this time continuum.
We'll be whisked away to limbo.
Lost in hypertime forever.
Well forget it.
I obviously didn't think it through.
It's crazy.
It's insane.
It's--
- The only way, Josh.
- The only way?
You know something?
Irwin was right about you.
You are an arrogant, selfish maniac.
What gives you the right to risk us
so that you can reach Irwin's chrono-lab,
grab the Nullifier back from
him and save the future?
- Not me.
I'm not going. You are.
- Me?
But why me?
- It's obvious.
Josh Kirby, you're the time warrior.
- Wait, even if I'm okay
zipping through the time stream,
the rest of you won't be, you'll all be...
You'll all be gone forever.
- It's a sacrifice I'm willing to make.
- Well good for you.
But you're not the only one involved.
- I too am willing to
sacrifice, Josh Kirby.
Just as you must be willing
to shoulder the burden
which only you can carry,
by going to stop Irwin without us.
- No, I can't.
- But you must!
You heard what Dr. Zoetrope said
about the Supreme Prefect
and his Decimator device.
You even saw it with your own eyes.
If you do not go on, 25th
century Earth is doomed.
Doomed to continue under
the Decimator's yoke
of suffering and enslavement forever.
- But why should you sacrifice yourself
for a planet full of strangers?
What do you owe the 25th century Earth?
- You do not understand.
Josh Kirby, I am not doing it
because I owe 25th century Earth.
I'm doing this because I owe it to myself.
As one who has personally
suffered the pains of slavery,
do you think I could go
on living with myself
knowing I had the chance
to free another world
and didn't take it, because
I didn't have the courage?
- But Azabeth, you'd be sacrificing
yourself to save humans!
The same race that turned your people
into slaves to begin with!
- What are you saying, Josh Kirby?
Are you saying that
because the slaver warlords
that terrorized my home were humans,
that I should se each and
every human as my enemy?
Even you?
- All right.
Now listen to me Prism.
It's all up to you.
It's possible your people
invented the Nullifier.
Maybe even possible your
people invented time itself.
But I need an answer from you.
Not the answer you think I want.
Or the answer you think Zoetrope wants.
Or even the answer you
think Azabeth wants.
Now look, I know you understand me,
so just shake your head yes or no.
Do you want to be a part of this?
Is this the right thing to do?
- Of course, Josh Kirby.
That's why I'm here.
Go ahead Josh, take it.
Go on.
- Your little friend has done his part
for the future of mankind.
Now come and see what you must do.
All you have to do is snap
my CDL, then Azabeth's,
into place right alongside Prism's.
I calibrated your stopwatch
as a time trigger,
so when you're ready to
go, just push the button.
It's already programmed
to take you straight back
to Irwin 1138's 25th century chrono-lab,
so you don't have to worry
about navigating your way
through the time stream.
Unfortunately, I can't say
as much for the ride itself.
With the primitive materials
I had to employ for construction,
I'm afraid it's going
to be a very bumpy ride.
- And then what?
I mean, even if I do get
back to Irwin's chrono-lab
before he starts launching
Nullifier components
all across time, what do I do to stop him?
- I'm sure you'll think of something.
You're the time warrior.
Be seeing you.
- I can't believe this!
No Azabeth, don't.
- Stop it, Josh.
Stop being so selfish!
- Selfish?
- Yes, selfish!
Quit thinking only of yourself!
Yes it will be difficult
for you to go on alone.
But you have a responsibility.
And the future of your
world hangs in the balance.
- Azabeth,
you just called me Josh.
- I'm sorry I yelled at you, Josh.
I guess I'm just a little scared.
- No, no, it's okay.
- Full-blooded human or not,
Josh Kirby, you are the finest
being I have ever known.
And it is said that, in a
single day with one such as you,
is worth a lifetime with any other.
- Well I thought you said
there weren't any more codes of Kang.
- There aren't.
That one's a code of Azabeth.
- Goodbye, Azabeth Siege,
leader of 10, follower
of the 21 codes of Kang.
I'll never forget you.
And don't worry.
There's no way I'll let
your sacrifice be in vain!
(uplifting music)
Here goes.
- (laughing) Who would have thought it?
The most beautiful sight I've ever seen,
and it's impossible to see it.
Disassemble the Nullifier components,
and prepare for the storm.
It's a primary law of physics,
that what you can't see,
you can't reassemble.
Now no one will ever be able
to track the six of you down
and put you together again,
no matter how bright he is.
(beeping)
- Hand over the Nullifier, Irwin, now!
- Never!
You should have stayed
back in the magic cabin,
Joshua, with your friends!
- My friends are all gone thanks to you!
- Good riddance.
Prepare to join them!
Ah, you little pest!
Look what you made me do.
- Minister, if you keep firing
you'll destroy the laboratory.
- [Computer] Intruder alert.
- Ah, warning, schwarning.
What's the use of an alert if
the intruder's already here?
Well at least, if I can't
blast you to smithereens,
but I can send these Nullifier components
out of your reach forever.
Get that toy off that clock!
- No!
I'm getting sick and tired
of this invisibility!
- Load number two.
- Okay.
See Dad?
I told you I could play football.
- Blast you, Josh Kirby!
Get him!
- Now I know what an end zone feels like.
Four, two, hut!
- No!
- Now it's just you and
me, Minister of Science.
- Do you realize what you've done?
- Gee, I'm sorry Irwin,
but you almost destroyed the universe.
You've gotta pay for your crimes
and that's all there is to it.
- You, you, have ruined my plans.
You've destroyed my lab!
You've sent my highly trained technicians
into the limbo of hypertime,
and you're not getting away with it.
Give it up, Josh.
I've got the height and the reach.
- Maybe so, Irwin, but I've got the right,
and that's all that matters in the end!
I hope.
- Stop it.
Stop it!
I tell you, stop it!
- Let's see how your armor holds up
if it's 10,000 years old.
- Stop it!
Prepare for the storm.
Prepare for the storm!
- No, I'm sorry Irwin,
but the storm's over.
No, you're too late, Dr. Zoetrope.
I've taken care of it already.
- Who are you?
- What, you mean you don't remember?
- I'll have you know, I haven't forgotten
a single pertinent piece
of acquired knowledge
since reaching the age of
seven and a half months.
- Well Dr. Zoetrope, I hope you remember
how to activate an
invisible Nullifier device,
so that you can nullify
all the evil effects
of the Supreme Prefect's Decimator.
- Sure, no problem.
After all.
- Please, don't tell me, I know.
You're the single most brilliant
man of the 25th century.
- How did you defeat Irwin 1138,
and what's that refuse lying at his feet?
- That's what your time
armor's gonna look like
in about 10,000 years.
- That's ridiculous.
My time armor was built
to last a million years!
- Go back to the drawing boards.
Irwin, don't worry.
I'm sure you'll be the most brilliant man
in whatever intergalactic
prison they put you in.
- Do you really think so?
- Sure.
- It's true.
The cerebral weight of
the average criminal brain
is infinitesimal compared to my own.
- Irwin's cloaking formulation
is simple enough to deactivate.
- So I guess I'm stuck here
until my time warrior powers regenerate
and I can get myself back home.
- How long is that?
- About 12 hours.
- Well sit back and enjoy
the show, young man.
A lot can happen in 12 hours.
- Irwin, what's going on over there?
I've got reports coming in
from all over the planet,
of people rising up,
thinking for themselves,
throwing off the yoke of my Decimator
as if it didn't even exist.
I demand an explanation.
- Ah, well, it's just a glitch, sir.
It's just a mere setback.
- I'm sorry to be the one
who has to tell you this,
but you're everlasting dynasty
is about to be nullified.
(dog barks)
(alarm ringing)
- Dr Zoetrope?
Azabeth? Prism?
- [Josh] Get up, Josh!
Another day, another dollar!
- Dad?
- Whoa, what's all this for?
- Nothing, I'm just glad to be home.
You know, you look better with grey hair.
You look more distinguished.
Genghis!
How you doing?
- Crazy kid, you're acting like
you haven't seen that dog in years.
- How you doing?
How you doing?
- And, after studying the many artifacts,
we can determine that the
ancient Cardaginian people
practiced the somewhat tasteless
act of human sacrifice.
They also rode elephants.
- Okay, so wait a minute,
Josh man Kirby man,
you're saying that in
this crazy dream of yours,
my great-great-great-great-great-grandson
was the second-most brilliant
man in the 25th century,
and because of that he was
going to destroy the universe?
And had to travel through all
kinds of crazy mixed-up times
in order to stop it?
Man, why can't I have
cool dreams like that?
You know what I always
dream about, Josh man?
Shrimp!
Live shrimp, baby shrimp,
boiled shrimp, fried
shrimp, shrimp scampi!
I don't even like shrimp.
- You know what?
Your ancestor had a theory,
that once time was altered,
it couldn't be put back to normal.
But I could find he was wrong.
You know, you're just
as crazy as ever, Irwin.
- Hey Josh, where's my homework?
- Homework?
- Don't tell me you didn't do my homework?
- Yeah!
Don't tell him that.
- Hey, Beth, how's it going?
- Do I know you?
- Hey.
Hurry up and meet me for lunch.
- You got it, babe.
- Okay Duke.
You can punch my lights out.
But it's not gonna change the fact
that I'm smarter than you.
And I'll always be smarter than you
until you decide to study and
do your homework for a change.
- Well Kirby, this is gonna hurt your face
a lot more than it hurts my fist.
- Hey.
Pick on somebody your own size, creep.
- What do you have a death wish, chick?
Don't you know who I am?
- Ah sure, you're a jerk with muscles,
no brain and a broken hand.
- There's nothing wrong with my hand.
(groans)
- Now there is.
- You're dead, chick!
Get her!
- That was real.
- I hate bullies.
You okay?
- Azabeth?
- No, but pretty close, Elizabeth.
Elizabeth Kang, and you are?
- Josh, Josh Kirby.
And this is my best friend, Irwin Lee.
- Pleased to make your
acquaintance, ma'am.
Say, you're new around here, aren't you?
- Yeah, transfer student.
- You look a little
old for the 12th grade.
- Well, things aren't
always as they appear.
- You're a transfer student?
Where from?
- It's kind of far from here,
you wouldn't have heard of it.
- That was one awesome
display of babe fu, lady.
Think you could teach me some of that?
- Guess Irwin 1138's
theory was right after all.
You can't get time exactly back to normal.
So, I guess since you saved me,
we're finally even now, huh?
Don't you remember?
The 12th code.
- I have no idea what
you are taking about.
- What's that?
- Oh, it's a prism.
You hold it up to a light source
and it glows with every
color in the spectrum.
- Let's hit it guys, it's lunch time.
- Oh, the cafeteria can be
a pretty confusing place
without a guide to show you the ropes.
There's long lines, old
ladies with hair nets,
and there's always a
controversy with the milk money.
- I've heard interesting stories
about the meatloaf at this school.
- I'm sorry ma'am, I can
neither confirm nor deny
any of the meatloaf rumors.
So I guess you're just gonna
have to try the meatloaf
firsthand, if you have the courage.
- Well, I'll try anything once.
Lead the way, Josh Kirby.
(triumphant music)
(electric buzzing)
(MultiCom Jingle)