- [Man] The endless city,
one get tired of living
and two deserve it.
(upbeat music)
- You better you prick.
I want my million fucking dollars Paris
I'm sitting up here with my
ass hanging out while this
mother fucker's trying to kill me.
(upbeat music)
- [Man] I pity the poor
bastard who killed her.
- Where's the money?
- In a safe place.
- How can I let you live?
- [Man] Why didn't he just run?
- I don't think he want's to live.
(upbeat music)
- [Woman] Somebody's been following me.
- I'm already a dead man and
I'm taking everybody with me.
- [Man] I just want my fuckin' money.
- [Man] Is a million worth dying for?
- Give me your gun I'm
gonna kill this prick.
(upbeat music)
- Don't say I didn't warn you.
(dramatic music)
- I'm sorry Tonio but I'm
taking Anna and the money
far away from you and the family.
So please just hand it over.
- Wherever you go, however long
it takes Blake I'll find you
and I'll kill you, then
I'll take Anna back.
- Yeah, yeah I know, that's
why I have to kill you.
- [Woman] Blake don't!
- No Anna.
(gun firing)
(screaming)
(crying)
- Anna.
(screams)
Anna please, Anna please stop
you saw it he shot himself.
Listen Anna listen to me.
You're the only one for
me Anna I won't let anyone
take you away from me.
(screaming)
Anna, Anna.
- Anna, Anna.
- Anna you're mine listen Anna.
- [Blake] Anna I love you.
- Blake, I love.
(crunches)
(coughing)
- Anna, Anna I didn't mean to.
Anna, Anna I didn't mean to.
- I'll see you in hell Tonio.
(dramatic music)
(phone ringing)
- Joe Average.
Morning captain.
When?
Browning on his way?
Okay I'll meet him there.
(clicks)
Shit.
I got two stiffs waiting for me.
Can we talk about this later?
Maybe take in a ball game?
- I'll think about it Joe.
- I wanna work this out.
- Oh go to work Joe.
(crying out)
(splashes)
- [Man] Tell him I said hello.
- [Man] Yeah.
- What do we got Browning?
- What else Joe?
Murder.
- Who is he?
- Passport says Blake Johnson.
- Her?
- Car down the hill had her purse in it,
passport, license Anna Martel, 22,
two sets of luggage in the car.
- Martel as in Paris Martel?
- I'm afraid so.
One of her old man's cars.
I pity the poor bastard who killed her.
- Well maybe she pulled the trigger.
- No, no it wasn't fired.
There's some foot prints though.
One set went running off that way.
Male about 180 size 11's.
- Whose the fourth?
- Might possibly be our anonymous caller.
Female, found the bodies,
robbed 'em and phoned it in.
No cards or money in the wallet.
- I love this town.
- I'll get back with ya
after we put 'em on the slab.
Oh and I'll let you break
the news to Paris Martel.
- Thank you ever so much.
(dramatic music)
What the hell are you doing?
- I'm moving out.
- What are you talking about?
- Which part of the sentence
didn't you understand Joe?
- I thought we were talking this out
and going to a ball game?
- It was never we, you don't
love me, I'm outta here.
- Melissa.
- Anything you never do.
- Melissa we're cops you
know what that does to us.
- Yeah it makes some of us assholes.
- You had the affair not me.
- Well if you would have
fucked me once in a while
maybe I wouldn't a.
- Is this what it's all about?
Sex?
- It's about being a human being.
It's about being partners.
It's about being a husband
something that you know nothing about.
- Well no one's perfect.
(banging)
- That you do know about.
- God damn it you're still my wife.
- You'll hear from my lawyer.
- Where will you stay?
- Maybe Skeeze's maybe my dad's.
In any case don't bother calling.
- Why are you doing this to me?
- I'm not doing anything you haven't
already done to yourself.
- You can't stay at Skeeze's he's a punk.
- Well at least he's man enough
to hold me when I need it.
- You can't go from one cop to another.
How would that look?
- I don't give a rats ass.
Maybe you should go back to your partner,
better yet maybe you
should go back to the bar.
- I invested in that bar so we'd have
something to retire on.
- You're not gonna live that long Joe.
- Take that back.
Take that back.
- Go fuck yourself.
- What is this seat taken?
- Yeah there's a gorgeous
pigeon sitting right there.
- Speaking of pigeons, take a look.
- Oh, not bad, you casting a movie?
- Yeah it's all about two dead
lovers in a field of dreams.
- So how does it end?
- I don't know but it's got
some colorful characters.
- Give me a hint.
- Well for starters that
is Mrs. Blake Johnson aka
Theresa Fields.
- So?
- So, the Theresa Fields, Miss Wholesome,
Miss Million Dollar Huckster.
- Okay?
- Johnson slapped a
restraining order on her
just to keep her away from his place.
- Now that's a twist.
- Yeah I thought you might like
to ask her a few questions.
- I do.
And not just about dead husbands.
(laughing)
- Both her and Johnson
are from outside Huston,
been separated five years,
he's a freelance trucker
who doesn't own a rig.
- So who does he freelance for?
- So ask his wife.
Oh this'll make your day.
Miss Martel was engaged
to a one Tonio Mandio.
Paris Martel's dock foreman.
- Shit.
I'm not in the mood for this today.
(gentle music)
(dramatic music)
I'm looking for Tonio
(mumbling)
Come on.
Where's he at?
Do you know where he's at.
- No.
- I got five bucks you
can tell me where he's at.
(mumbling)
Nope.
Where's he at man?
I need to know.
- You got to go down here,
to the left, then go up
there he is.
(mumbles)
- Take care, thank you.
(dramatic music)
(marching band music)
(crying out)
- [Man] That's enough!
(thudding)
(crying out)
That's enough!
Where's the money?
- It's in a safe place.
- Don't kill him until he talks.
- Let me get him once for Anna.
(thudding)
(crying out)
- I came to you for forgiveness
tell Walter my life for the money.
- You killed my daughter.
How am I gonna let you live?
- Then we all die.
(tinging)
- Put a price on him.
Alive!
Yeah he got away.
You'll get your money Walter.
Don't make threats you can't keep.
- Still beating your employees Paris?
Where is he?
- I don't know what you're talking about.
- You know what I'm talking about.
- Why don't you get off my ass Joe.
- I'm gonna be on your ass
so close you're gonna never
be able to smell again.
- How much you want buddy?
Why don't you keep your
fucking cops outta here,
keep your badge clean.
- Hey are you offering me money for this?
Is that's what's going on.
- Is that what I said?
- Yeah you asked me how much I want.
- I want you off my property
unless you got a warrant.
You clear out of this, this is a family.
- Listen you see him you give me a call.
You hear me?
(train clattering)
(dramatic music)
You know looking for your
connection he's not here.
I need a favor.
- Yeah you always do.
- Tonio alive.
(laughs)
I say something funny?
- Everybody wants Tonio alive.
(gun firing)
(crying out)
(dramatic music)
(tires squealing)
- We have an uncomfortable situation here.
- What's your name cop?
- Joe, Joe Average.
(dramatic music)
- Hey cop.
(thudding)
(crying out)
Don't make me a cop killer.
(dramatic music)
(thudding)
(crying out)
You're not very good at
this game are you Joe?
- Fuck you.
- (laughs) Is that anyway to
talk to a lovesick killer?
- Get it over with.
- Would you shoot me if
I was lying in the street
with no gun?
- Maybe.
- Promise me one thing Joe.
- Okay.
- When this is all over
with, make sure I'm dead.
- One way or the other.
(dramatic music)
(rustling)
- Hey mother fucker what
you got in that bag?
- Ah a million dollars.
- Yeah and my mother's rockdefeller.
- No really man take it it's yours.
- Yeah right.
Guess what asshole we're
picking door number two.
Your ass is worth 10 grand.
(crying out)
(thudding)
(squishing)
(crying out)
(gun firing)
(dramatic music)
- Anyone we know Browning?
- Local boys, shot while lying here,
stabbed and beat up the rest.
- Anybody see anything?
- No one's come forward.
- Tonio's on the run.
Word on the street Paris posted 10 grand
to bring him in alive.
- Alive?
- Yeah that's what I said.
These guys probably tried to collect.
- I'll run ballistics and
see if I can match these up
with the two this morning.
- There's another one waiting
for you when you get back.
One of my snitches.
- Sorry.
Any word on Theresa Fields?
- I made an appointment with her agent.
Now if you don't mind
I'd like to go clean up.
- Joe watch your step.
- I'm not worried about Martel.
- I meant with the actress.
- I'll carry my gun.
(dramatic music)
Detective Joe Average.
Homicide.
I called your agent he
told me where to find you.
- Now look if this is about
Blake I have nothing to say.
- When was the last
time you spoke with him?
- Months ago.
- Why did he have a
restraining order on you?
- Because there was a
time in our relationship
I would've killed him myself.
- Did you?
Do you have any idea who he worked for?
- Drove trucks outta
Mexico that's all I know.
He had vegetables on his brain.
- Look it's hot do you mind stopping?
- I don't wanna cool down.
- You either cool down
here or in a holding pen
take your pick.
- Look cop don't get tough with me.
- Who was Blake driving for?
- He mentioned a Walter Dunning once.
- That's better.
- Look Blake was a son
of a bitch and a loser
now if you don't mind I'd really--
- He was about to run
off with another woman.
- He was always running off with something
and usually it was his mouth.
- Look if you're hiding something
your life could be in danger.
- I don't scare easily cop.
(dramatic music)
- That's far enough right there Average
and don't get tough.
- What, ruin a good shirt?
- What do you want?
- Talk with Walter.
- What about?
- About how I had to push my
way through some smart ass
punks so I could talk with him.
- You know one of these days
we're gonna meet in a dark
alley Average and we'll
see who is the punk.
- What's the matter Billy?
Your ass still sore from the pen?
- Fuck you.
(thudding)
(crying out)
- Nice chatting with you Billy.
(dramatic music)
(laughing)
(knocking)
- Wait a minute.
I got a dick at my doorstep.
What?
- Hang up the phone.
- I'll call you back Fred.
So talk.
- Blake Johnson.
- Listen if you've come here
to pin anything on my boys
again Average forget it,
Johnson was a sweetheart of
a driver and I'm sorry as
hell the fucker's gone.
- When did he work for you last?
- Shit I don't know.
Night before last he
delivered a truckload of kale.
- To?
- I'd have to look it up.
Look I got over 20 fuckin' trucks here.
Maybe you'd prefer we
bring in a few good men
and go over your shipping reports.
- Course what was I thinking of?
Tuesday night, Martel produce.
- Do you have any idea
where Tonio Mandio is?
- No but don't worry if I do
a cop will be the first thing I call.
- I ran across Billy Reese outside.
When'd you start hanging
out with convicts?
- When you started arresting my employees.
I trust you didn't hurt him?
(dramatic music)
Yeah it's me Joe Average
just paid us a visit.
It won't take him long to
put two and two together
and turn Tonio against us.
You better you prick.
Settle down this cocksucker
I want my million fuckin'
dollars Paris, I'm sitting up
here with my ass hanging out
while this mother fucker
tryin' to kill me.
Jesus not here what if Tonio
decides to smoke us both out?
Yeah, yeah I know where that is.
I'll change I'll meet
you there in 20 minutes.
(dramatic music)
- Hey Tonio, how's it hanging?
- Right where you left it.
- Hey chill homeboy it's time for a drive.
- So you guys got guns?
- Hey Tonio we don't need
no guns we just wanna talk.
- Okay.
(thudding)
(crying out)
Come on, come on.
(thudding)
(crying out)
You guys should have brought guns.
Where's Martel and Dunning hiding out?
- King warehouse, waiting for you.
(screams)
You son of a bitch.
You son of a (crying out).
- Give this to Martel and Dunning
tell 'em I got the
money and I'm on my way.
- My finger.
- You won't need it.
- No!
(gun firing)
(dramatic music)
- Patch me into 4023.
Joe, Browning get this
Blake made two calls
to Theresa's number yesterday.
- I talked to Walter Dunning.
Blake delivered a load of
kale to Martel's last night.
- Things are getting interesting.
What about Eddie and Billy?
- I know where to find them.
How about lunch?
- Yeah I know where that's
at, I'll see ya in 10.
(dramatic music)
And that's not all.
What? What?
- Hm? Nothing go on.
- Blake's got two tickets
to Maui waiting for him
under the name of Mr. and Mrs. Smith.
- How original.
So first she called and left
a message on her machine
and then he called Theresa
back and talked to someone
for almost 10 minutes.
- Could have been the maid.
- Yeah it could have been
Santa Claus but I doubt it.
So Miss Fields did talk to
her husband the night before
he was murdered, about what?
- I don't know?
What do husbands and
wives always talk about?
- Money and restraining orders?
- I'll buy that.
- But why are they still married?
- She's rich and famous.
- She is now.
- Meaning?
- Meaning who and what was she before?
- Are you saying maybe
Blake has something on her?
- Had.
- What?
- I don't know but if the
world finds out I bet the
advertisers won't be so
willing to pay Miss Fields
so much money to hock their wares.
- Mrs. Fields, no.
She's as refreshing as a blueberry muffin.
- Trust me.
- Television won't ever seem the same.
- Look do me a favor get a court order
and pull Johnson's banking records.
See who's been paying him
what on a monthly basis.
- You mean alimony?
- Something like that.
If we're right I think Theresa
may wanna cut us a deal
or for whatever Blake had
on her, books, photos.
- Oh, do you mind if I finish my lunch?
- By all means.
- You gonna eat that pizza.
- Nah take it.
(dramatic music)
(intercom beeping)
- [Man] Who is it?
- Joe Average homicide I'd
like to take a look at Blake
Johnson's apartment please?
(mumbles)
- Just buzz the door.
(dramatic music)
- [TV] Today on the channel
four news, she was a typical
teenager who turned into one of Holly--
(cheesy music)
(moaning)
- Actually no the lighting
was a little dark.
- I was only 18 I didn't know any better.
- Just a horny little girl
who had no idea you were ever
gonna be famous.
- Hey fuck you alright?
We needed the money.
Then an agent found me and
I destroyed what I thought
was the only copy.
- Only Blake duped it in case
you got smart and dumped him.
- That's right give it to me.
- Have you got a permit for that?
- What, I walked into my
murdered husband's apartment,
I found an intruder how was I supposed
to know you were a cop?
- Better think it over.
- I have thought it over for 10 years.
Now give me the tape.
- We know you've been paying
Blake money every month.
- So?
- We also know he called you
twice the night before he died.
- Big deal, I forgot.
- Look I'll destroy this tape
right here if you tell me
what you talked about.
- Look I had nothing to do with this.
He said he was ripping him
off for a million dollars.
- Well whose money was it?
- Walter's.
Blake was running coke across
the border in Walter's trucks
and he was delivering it to a Paris Martel
and Blake would then deliver
the money back to Walter,
that's all he told me I...
- What about Anna Martel?
- I don't know maybe he loved her.
He always had a thing
for those young girls.
- So he called you last night
to let you off the hook.
- Yeah.
And Blake was always
braggin', Mr. Bigshot.
- Why didn't you just come right
over here and get the tape?
- Somebody's been following me.
- Who?
- Me, on your knees cop.
- Don't try anything stupid.
- It's to late for that.
I'm already a dead man and
I'm taking everybody with me.
Stop looking for me or
she goes first got it?
- I got it.
- Joe (crying out).
- Hey what about the rent?
- I've got your rent right here.
(gun firing)
(laughing)
(whimpering)
(dramatic music)
- Shit.
Shit.
- Hey look if it ain't
detective Joe blow Average.
What's the matter ocifer
poor baby got a flat.
(laughing)
- You punks having a good time?
- Oh we're just out taking a
stroll looking for new digs
and a little action.
- Yeah now that we're outta the joint,
no thanks to you.
- So here we are in a
lonesome alley after all.
- Yeah just me and you--
- And monkey face.
- Hey I just come by to give you a hand.
- Yeah a couple of 'em.
(thudding)
(crying out)
- Come here, come here.
(thudding)
(crying out)
Oh he's gonna change
my fuckin' tire eh now?
- I ain't changin' your fuckin' tire.
- Oh yeah?
(thudding)
(crying out)
How about you?
Come on.
Change the tire.
(engine running)
- Why didn't you fucking shoot?
- He may not be alone.
- Oh Jesus.
- Come on finish up.
- Fuck you asshole.
(thudding)
- Ah shit.
- What about him?
- Let him go.
- Hey, hey man my life's in danger here.
Hey you gotta take me in.
Okay?
I'll tell you anything you want to know.
- He tried to kill you Joe.
- I'm not wasting the public's
money on this punk again.
- Get the cuffs.
- Okay I know where Martel
and Dunning are hiding out
they're waiting for Tonio.
- Where?
- No I want protection.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
King's warehouse off Figaroa and the five.
- Thank you, now hit the road.
- Hey arrest me mother fucker.
- Joe you can't do this.
- I'm an endangered species man.
Hey you can't let him
put me out on the street
without protection.
Are you fuckin' nuts?
- Always wear your raincoat now beat it.
(dramatic music)
- Where the fuck did he go?
What the hell did you do that for?
- B, come on get in here.
- So if Tonio's got the money
why doesn't he just run?
- I don't think he wants to live.
- Then why grab Theresa?
- Buying time from us, getting
even with Blake I don't know.
- You think he's gonna kill her?
- What's he got to lose?
- What'd you find up at Blake's?
- Nothin'.
- Nothin', so you destroyed
whatever it wasn't.
- I don't know what you're talking about.
- That good huh?
- Good enough to explain
the restraining order.
- Just drive.
- I don't like this.
Where are those guys?
- Shut up!
God your whining's driving me nuts.
- Listen if your daughter
wasn't such a slut
we wouldn't be in this mess to begin--
(thudding)
(crying out)
- Someone's up there.
- Give him back his gun.
- Hello ladies.
- Shit Tonio.
Hey man I'm unarmed.
- Keep climbing.
- Hey thanks Tonio, hey
for a minute there man.
I thought you'd waste me.
- I am
(gun firing)
(crying out)
(banging)
- Open up, come on it's me!
- We gotta let him in.
- Oh Jesus!
- If you open that door the
next scream will be yours.
Anybody see Tonio?
- Nothin'.
(gun firing)
- Shit.
(crying out)
(gun firing)
God damn.
- No!
- Unless you're ordering
a pizza Bob don't.
- We've gotta call in for backup Joe.
- I wanna go in quietly.
- Are you crazy?
You can't go in by yourself.
- I'm not.
- Whoa wait a minute, I'm a
desk man these days remember?
- You're here and I need your help.
- I don't have a gun.
- There's one in the glove box.
- I can't Joe.
- He had a gun on you Bob.
- He was just a kid.
- It was either you or him
and you made your decision
now live with it.
- I have, I do the leg
work, I push the pencils.
- If we call in backup the
captain's gonna call Mitch
and Skeeze, Theresa won't stand a chance.
Tonio doesn't know we're
coming and that's the way
we gotta play it.
- God damn me for having a
partner with suicidal tendencies.
- You damned yourself now live with it.
- Fuck you, stop the God
damn car, let me outta here.
- Get out.
- Why do you always have to
be a prick about everything?
- It's the bright part of my personality.
Shut the door.
(muttering)
Take the gun.
- No and I'm calling backup
just as soon as we get there.
- Well I'm goin' in.
If you get a shot at Tonio take him down.
- Maybe we should wait for backup.
- Theresa could be dead by then.
- It's been a long time Joe.
- Bob, just aim and pull the trigger.
- He just tossed out the briefcase.
(rattling)
- Is a million worth dying for?
- I just want my money
and the fuck outta here.
- Why would he let you go?
- I don't have anything to
do with this shit Tonio.
You know that.
I just want my fuckin' money.
I'm comin' out.
(rattling)
There it is.
I'm in, I'm vader I fucking made it.
One cool fuckin' million come
to papa my little million.
Jesus.
- Does anybody see him?
- Check it out.
(ominous music)
- Jack, do you see anything over there?
Jack?
(ominous music)
- I see you Tonio.
- I saw you first.
(ominous music)
Hello boss.
(thudding)
(crying out)
I'm a bandit you know.
- You better kill me
while you can you bastard.
- Oh no.
- Oh my God.
It's Jack.
The mother fucker cut his throat.
(whimpering)
(ominous music)
- Rock and roll Tonio.
(crying out)
- Bob for apples babe.
(ominous music)
(banging)
(crying out)
- It's me come here.
- Give me your gun I'm
gonna kill this prick.
- I don't have one.
- What you're gonna save me
but you didn't bring a gun?
- Shh.
(ominous music)
(crying out)
- Tonio.
It's me Steve.
Yeah I know we messed you
up at the warehouse but
you killed the boss's daughter.
Hey I got a wife and a kid.
(crying out)
You psycho fuck.
(ominous music)
- All I wanted was my life back.
- Please don't kill me Tonio.
- Don't worry Rick I'm
saving you for later.
(ominous music)
(crying out)
Don't say I didn't warn ya.
(thudding)
(crying out)
- Okay.
(thudding)
(crying out)
- I forgive you Tonio.
(ominous music)
- If life could be that easy.
- Hey butt head!
(ominous music)
- Thanks.
- I'll take her home.
- Just get me outta here.
- Rick!
Answer me boy.
- He's dead.
It's over Paris.
Put down your gun put
your hands on your head.
(gun firing)
(ominous music)
- Hey Joe.
- Hey Browning how'd it go?
- Oh they didn't find a thing.
- No money, no coke?
- Nada.
So where are you off to?
- A certain gorgeous
pigeon gave me a call.
- Well you better be careful.
- Yeah don't worry.
(laughs)
- Oh by the way I can't
make the game tonight.
- Oh come on.
- I'm sorry Joe no can do, my
kids would like to know who
their father is.
- Okay.
(gentle music)
- Hi.
- Thanks for comin'.
- No problem.
- I just um, I wanted to
well yesterday I just didn't
get the chance to say thank you.
- It's just part of the job.
- And I wanted to apologize
for the way I spoke to you
and to give you something.
- What?
- This.
(romantic music)
(light hearted music)
- We're rich yay!
Whee!
Come on let's go.
(gentle music)
- Joe Average.
Morning captain.
When?
Browning on his way?
Still beating your employees Paris?
(thudding)
(crying out)
There's another one waiting
for you when you get back,
one of my snitches.
(thudding)
(crying out)
Nice chatting with you Billy.
- I'll run ballistics and
see if I can match these up
with the two this morning.
Mrs. Fields?
No, she's as refreshing
as a blueberry muffin.
Trust me, television
won't ever seem the same.
- Oh don't worry.
- Oh by the way I can't
make the game tonight.
- Oh come on.
- I'm sorry Joe no can do my kids.
Johnson slapped a restraining order on her
just to keep her away from his place.
- Now that's a twist.
- Thought you might like that.
Oh and I'll let you break
the news to Paris Martel.
- Thank you ever so much.
- Anna I didn't mean to.
Anna.
Anna I didn't mean to.
Don't make me a cop killer.
- Why did he have a
restraining order on you?
- Because there was a
time in our relationship
when I woulda killed him myself.
A son of bitch and a loser
and if you don't mind I'd really--
- He was about to run
off with another woman.
- He was always runnin' off with something
and usually it was his mouth.
Fuck you alright we needed the money.
An agent found me and I
destroyed what I thought
was the only copy.
- Give him back his gun.
- Being partners.
Being a husband something
that you know nothing about.
- Well no one's perfect.
- That you do know about.
Rat's ass maybe you should
go back to your partner.
Better yet maybe you
should go back to the bar.
- And one of these days we're
gonna meet in a dark alley
Average and we'll see who is the punk.
- We were just out taking a
stroll looking for new digs
and a little action.
- Yeah it's me Joe Average
just paid us a visit.
Won't take him long to
put two and two together
and turn Tonio against us.
You better you prick.
I didn't have anything to
do with this shit Tonio.
You know that, I just
want my fucking money.
I'm coming out.
(rattling)
I made it, I fucking made it.
One cool fucking million come
to papa my little million.
- Hey thanks Tonio.
Hey for a minute there man
I thought you'd waste me.
Hey, hey man my life's in danger here.
Hey you gotta take me in.
Why didn't you fucking shoot?
- He may not be alone.
- Oh geez.
- Come on finish up.
- Fuck you asshole.
- Mess you up at the warehouse.
But you killed the boss's daughter.
Hey I got a wife and a kid.
(ominous music)
- What?
- This.
(gentle music)