State your name
for the record, pleas.
Jack Lucas.
For the record, I'm detectie
sergeant Joseph Dexter,
internal affairs.
This interview is beig
conducted
with regards to
case number 65-a456.
[ Lighter clicks ]
[ Lighter clicks shut ]
Would you mind?
Sorry.
[ Ashes sizzling ]
[ Inhales, exhales ]
[ Heartbeat pounding ]
Okay, detective Lucas,
let's talk about the evens
of April 23, 200.
Uh...
[ Glass shattering ]
My partner, al voss, and I were
set to pick up an informant.
Uh, he had some information
on some drive-by shootings
that we thought the red dragons
were responsible for.
[ Machine-gun fire ]
This one pretty much
sealed it.
[ Bullets clanking ]
Police! Drop your --
[ bullets clanking ]
Uh!
[ Engine revving ]
[ Tires screeching ]
So, uh, detective,
uh, voss and I immediately
went off in pursuit.
[ Tires screeching ]
Were you aware,
detective Lucas,
that the month prir
to this incident,
your partner's cellphone lg
showed over 25 calls
to one of the red dragon's
top lieutenants?
No, I was not.
[ Gunshot ]
[ Tires screeching ]
[ Gunfire ]
And that the last
of these calls was placd
less than an hour before you
and detective voss staked out
the Hong luck --
huang luck.
Huang --
huang luck market?
He, uh...
[ Gunshot ]
[ Gunfire ]
He did step out of the car
at one point for some privacy.
I assumed
he was calling his wife.
You just assumed?
Yes.
He was my partner.
I trusted him.
[ Tires screeching ]
So what you're telling m,
detective Lucas...
Al?
...is that you had absolutely
no knowledge...
[ Tires screeching ]
...of your partner's
extracurricular contacs
with the red dragon?
[ Shell casings clinking ]
No, none whatsoever.
[ Sirens wailing ]
You expect me
to believe that?
[ Gun clicks ]
You can believe what you want.
It's the truth.
[ Gunshot, tires screeching ]
[ Glass shattering,
metal squealing ]
[ Dog barking ]
[ Horn honking,
indistinct shouting ]
Hey!
Whoo!
[ Man laughing ]
Wait, wait, wait!
[ Laughs ]
Whoo!
Whatever happened to
trick-or-fucking-treat, huh?
[ Ice clinking ]
Man: That's what he said
anyway.
[ Laughs ]
Hi, Jack.
[ Indistinct conversation,
cash register dings ]
[ Irish accent ] Ah, you're
a lovely man, Eddie,
and you always will be.
You're not gonna get
into my pants
no matter how much you try
to sweet-talk me, Jack.
[ Normal voice ] Oh, yeah.
You get those flowers I sent?
Ah, fuck you, huh?
Hey, cut it out or else I'll --
I'll have to start advertising
that the great Jack Lucas
is a regular here.
Maybe sell some tickets.
Nobody gives a shit
about that, Eddie, all right?
Innkeeper!
[ Laughter ]
Straw for my men,
wine for my horses.
I'm a little short on straw,
Mr. Lucifer.
What else is your preference?
Martini up, olives.
Right.
Thank you.
And get this man another
whatever he's having.
Make it a double --
the least I can do
for having nearly run him down
with my carriage.
My humblest apologies,
my good sir.
That's all right, okay?
And the drink's not...
[ Indistinct conversations,
laughter continue ]
...necessary.
Well, it would seem to b,
as they say in Paris,
a fait accompli.
I suggest you enjoy it.
[ Billiard balls clacking ]
I'm Ollie.
Jack.
Good to meet you, Jack.
You look familiar.
You an actor?
[ Laughs ]
No, but I bet you are.
Oh. How could you tell?
[ Laughs ]
[ Sniffs ]
So, what do you do?
I work for the city.
Can't get it.
I know I know you.
I just -- it'll hit me.
I'll be driving home --
bang!
It'll hit me.
Hmm. Long as you don't hit
anybody else.
Touché.
Lovely. Thank you.
[ Indistinct conversations,
cash register dings ]
[ Coins clinking ]
[ Billiard balls clacking ]
Great ass, huh?
Yeah, museum quality.
[ Laughs ]
My ex had an ass like that.
Walked in on her screwing
another guy -- broke my heart.
It's kind of stupid, though,
you know?
She didn't love me.
Now the bitch wants half
of everything I own.
Yeah.
What are you gonna do?
You can't live with 'em...
You can't kill 'em.
[ Laughs ]
But I'll tell you
something, man-to-man --
if I wasn't
such a fucking pussy,
I would strangle
that gold-digging slut
with my bare hands.
[ Sniffs ] You want to see
a picture of her?
Sure. Why not?
Works downtown --
a place called the plaype.
You know it?
I've been in there
once or twice.
Yeah, sure you have --
[ Laughs ]
You got kids?
No.
If you had kids, would you let
a slut like that teach 'em?
The reason I ask is
this particular slut goes
to the valley every morning,
teaches little girls
how to plié,
then at night,
fucks onstage for money.
Two shows a night,
seven days a week,
she'll fuck anything
that moves.
Men, women, donkeys --
doesn't matter.
Obviously, the place
has changed since
the last time I was in.
[ Pager ringing ]
Ahh.
Duty calls.
Yeah.
Eddie, ring me up,
will you?
I got to make
a phone call.
Thanks.
It was nice talking
to you, Jack.
[ Indistinct conversation ]
[ Printer clicking ]
[ Paper tearing ]
[ Dialing ]
Excuse me.
Yeah.
Is that, uh...
Real-life hero, my friend.
[ Sighs ]
The mobile customer
you are trying to reach -
[ receiver clicks ]
It was hit and run all the wa,
and here comes the throw,
and he is safe!
Yeah, safe.
Leets made a nice throw,
but just a little late...
This one's all yours,
pal, okay?
It was surely
a double play...
Listen, do me a favor.
Get one of your buddies
to drive you home.
Oh, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Come on.
This guy just told me
who you are.
I knew I knew you.
It was that article.
I read that.
What was that --
three, four months ago?
Yeah, something like that.
Look, let me show
a little gratitude, all right?
You guys
work your asses off.
A toast.
A toast!
To the heroes!
The real kind.
Oh, god!
[ Inhales sharply ]
Oh, god, I am sorry.
I am so sorry.
Don't worry about it, okay?
It's -- it's fine.
For Christ's sakes.
Are you all right, Jack?
Yeah, it's -- it's --
it's nothing, Eddie.
Don't worry.
God, I feel terrible.
Let me --
let me take care of this.
Fine. Thank you.
It is --
it is an accident.
I'll --
I'll take care of it.
Eddie: You come in, busting te
joint up, for Christ's sakes.
Let me get a broom
in the back.
[ Breathing heavily ]
[ Door hinges squeaking ]
Uh.
[ Breathing heavily ]
Are you all right?
[ Clears throat ]
[ Distorted ] Are you okay?
[ Water running ]
[ Water gurgling in drain ]
Jack!
Jack! Hey!
Jack! Hey, come on! Wake up!
You all right?
Jack!
Hey. Easy.
Hey, look, I know
I pour a hell of a drink,
but this is ridiculous.
You're half Irish,
for Christ's sakes.
One drink and you're facedown
in the toilet?
You should be ashamed
of yourself.
That hand --
you need to get it looked at.
[ Water running ]
I'll get your cigarettes.
[ Breathing heavily ]
Here.
Thanks.
What the hell...
What?
What are you looking for?
Nothing.
[ Horn honking ]
That guy -- the guy with
the devil mask --
is he still here?
No, him and his friends left
about 10 or 15 minutes ago.
[ Echoing ] Let me --
let me take care of this.
You got his
credit-card imprint, right?
No, they -- they paid cash.
What?
All right, listen --
uh...uh, Eddie,
you got to do me a favor.
Yeah, sure. Anything, Jack.
What?
That guy or anybody
he was with --
they come back in here,
you got to call me, all right?
Yeah, sure.
You want me to call you
a cab?
[ Exhales deeply ] No.
No, the, uh, fresh air
might do me good.
[ Door closes ]
[ Beeps ]
Hey, neighbor, it's Caitlin.
Listen, am I stupid or what?
I just realized
I forgot to tell you
to give Rudy one of the pills
along with his food,
which, sorry,
I left in the truck.
The keys are on the counter.
If you need to reach me,
my brother's number in
San Francisco is 415-555-672.
See you next week!
[ Receiver clicks ]
[ Beeps ]
Jack, it's your dad.
I didn't hear from you.
I'm assuming we're still on
for tomorrow.
See you then.
[ Receiver clicks,
answering machine beeps ]
[ Birds chirping ]
[ Lawn mower whirring ]
Hey, pop.
Sorry I'm late.
That car was supposed
to get you through graduatio,
not retirement.
Yeah. Well, you know me.
I have a hard time
letting go of things.
I was just reminiscing
with your mother
about something that happened
when you were a boy.
Pop...
It's been two years.
What is it you used to tell
your patients?
There's a time
to stop grieving
and a time
to start living again.
And I always used
to tell you...
Don't shrink the shrink.
Don't shrink --
that's right.
Help me up, will you?
Oh, no.
You look like crap.
Oh, hey, thanks.
You're still not sleeping,
are you?
It's getting better.
I'm up to, like,
three hours a night.
Three hours?
Here I was worried.
Why don't you let me prescribe
something for you, huh?
No, no, all right?
I don't want to argue
about this, dad.
I'm gonna lick this
on my own.
Well, you always were
a stubborn little son
of a bitch, weren't you?
Yeah, well, the apple doesn't
fall far from the tree, does it?
I'm gonna have to plead
no contest to that one.
I'll let you off
with a warning...This time.
[ Sighs ] Come on.
There's a plate
of bacon and eggs out there
with your name on 'em.
[ Indistinct conversation ]
I sure hope you got
the tag number...
Of the truck that hit you.
Yeah, it was a rough one.
You look like shit.
What -- you been talking
to my old man?
He just told me
the exact same thing.
Hey, great minds.
How's he doing anyway?
Ahh.
Good. He's good.
Thanks for asking.
Lucas.
3:00 tomorrow afternoon.
You know, Joe, you should
try using complete sentences
once in a while.
It really helps.
As in my office,
3:00 tomorrow afternoon.
Yeah? What for?
Well, you'll find out
when you get there, won't you?
Oh, fuck you.
Excuse me.
I didn't catch that.
Nothing.
Tomorrow.
You got to watch
your mouth, partner.
Talking shit won't help
your case any.
Look, I heard him talking
to pruitt --
he's submitting your report
day after tomorrow.
Good.
It's about fucking time.
What do you mean, good?
You're not worried?
We all got a job to do.
Dexter's just doing his,
you know?
Yeah, right.
Yeah, the report will say
what it says,
and then whatever happens
will happen.
What are you,
a Buddhist now?
Why don't you
just shave your head,
put on your little orange robe,
and go hang out at the airport?
No, I shaved my head
in college once on a dare.
I looked like a dope.
Yeah, well, you're sure acting
like one.
Might as well
go the distance.
Ooh.
Look, I'm going
to the bathroom.
I'm gonna get the shaving cream
and the razor, hear?
[ Birds chirping ]
[ Engine shuts off,
keys jingling ]
[ Gunshot ]
Noisy bugger, aren't you?
Did you gargle with salt watr
like I told you?
Yeah, well, I know
it doesn't taste goo.
Hey, don't you use that word
with me, young man,
or you'll be gargling
down soap when i'm
through with you, hear?
Okay, look, I know --
I know you're sick, okay?
I'm sorry.
But mama can't come home
right now.
Your daddy will be home
in a couple hours and --
[ snapping ]
What?
You got to go, go.
You sure?
Yeah, no problem.
I got plenty to do here.
Thank you.
I'll be home in 20 minute.
Get the salt water ready.
I'll check in
with you later.
[ Telephone ringing ]
Works at a place downtown -
the playpen.
You know it?
[ Dialing ]
Playpen. This is mik.
Yeah, hi, this is detective
Jack Lucas, l.A.P.D. Homicide.
I need the last name
of one of your dancers.
[ Vehicle door opens ]
Hey, Judy!
Hey, Jess.
[ Keys jingling ]
See you, girls.
Pepper spray. Back off!
Okay, take it easy!
Take it easy!
I-I'm -- I'm a detective,
all right?
I'm Jack Lucas,
l.A.P.D. Homicide, okay?
Are you Jessica tarrant?
Yeah, what do you want?
First, I want you to put
the pepper spray away.
Can we do that?
I-I just need to ask you
a few questions.
What can I help you with?
I'm gonna be late for work.
Uh, it's, uh, it's about
your ex-husband.
Oh, my god.
What did he do?
I-I can't really comment
on anything that he may
or may not have done.
I just need some information
like a-a phone number
or an address.
From me?
I haven't seen him in...
Two years.
Last I heard,
he was back in england.
England.
Yeah, so, sorry.
I can't help you.
But good luck.
Hope you find him.
And if you do, please don't let
him know where he can find me.
[ Engine clicking ]
Oh, shit, shit!
Not again!
[ Exhales sharply ]
You got AAA?
Expired.
Oh.
Jumper cables?
[ Sighs ]
Think it's just the batter?
I can't be late
for work tonight.
You're asking
the wrong guy.
Great.
So you're saying that you
hadn't seen your ex
in a couple of years?
Yeah.
My battery's all corrode.
Brand-new.
Yeah.
Was he prone to violence
at all?
[ Scoffs ]
I guess that's a "yes"?
Yeah. Angry punk rocker
who liked to hit women.
We were married
for three months.
Rick the dick.
Should I start it?
W-W-Wait a second.
What did you say
his name was?
Rick.
Last name Oliver
by any chance?
Because the guy who says
he's your ex-husband
introduced himself to me
as Ollie.
Could he be using
an assumed name --
I mean, living
in the country illegally?
It's not Rick.
Yeah, how do you know?
Because I know!
But you do know
this Ollie character?
Yeah.
Why do you think I have
the pepper spray?
Well, do you know his last name
or -- or maybe where he lives?
No, I don't know
his last name.
I don't want to know
where he lives.
I just don't want to see
the guy anymore.
Should I start the car?
Uh, yeah, yeah.
Give it a try.
[ Engine clicking ]
Oh.
Shit!
He was a regular
at the club.
He was there
almost every night.
Really big tipper.
He used to stuff $100 bills
in my bra.
He told me that I-I reminded
him of some old movie actres,
somebody I never even
heard of.
It was no big DEA,
you know?
I didn't think twice
about him.
Till one night,
I'm backstage changing,
and he's -- he's back there,
and he starts groping me,
and he wouldn't take no
for an answer.
Really creepy.
I yelled out
for Mike, the bounce.
He comes,
he throws the guy ou,
and he tells him not to come
back to the club.
When was this?
Two months ago.
That's when all the weird shit
started happening.
Oh, yeah? Like?
Late-night hang-ups, filthy
messages on my machine --
stuff like that.
All right, slow down.
It's right up here on the right.
So, uh...Listen,
if you -- if you need anything,
you just give me a call, okay?
Because dance lessons
don't pay the rent.
Excuse me?
That's the answer.
What's the question?
Why would I want to work
in a place like this?
I've seen that look before.
Listen, I, uh, I already have
one shrink in my life.
I think that's my limit.
[ Footsteps approaching ]
Jess?
Hey, girl.
Hi.
Jack, this is
my friend, Sandy.
Be careful --
he's a cop.
Oh.
You better get in there.
Sal's pissed.
Okay, I'll be right in.
Well, thanks for the ride.
Yeah, listen, did you happen
to keep any of those tapes
of the, uh, messages he sen?
Yeah.
Can you get 'em to me?
Why? So they can collect dust
on your desk?
Sorry.
No, that's all right.
People have their issues
with cops.
What are you gonna do?
Have a better day.
[ Dance music plays ]
Man: Good afternoon, gentleme,
and welcome to the playpen,
where every hour is happy hou.
So take your hands
out of your pockets
and put 'em together for sand.
Isn't she lovely?
How'd you like to get
into those boots,
ladies and gentlemen?
And on stage two,
the lovely Jessica!
Put your hands together
for Jessica.
Do the collars and cuffs matc?
You'll find out
in a minute, gentlemen.
[ Music continues ]
♪ For you ♪
♪ for you ♪
[ Sighs ]
Hey, Josh,
how's the throat?
Mama didn't make you gargle
with soap, did she?
[ Laughs ]
Yeah, yeah.
Put her on.
Hi, how are you?
Yeah. No, no.
You didn't miss anything.
No, I just followed up
on a couple of loose ends.
I came up empty. Yeah.
All right, I'll see you
tomorrow, then.
No, I'm going straight home,
mother.
[ Laughs ]
Good night.
Yo, Jack!
I'm glad I caught you, man.
Yo, man, we're going out
to O'Malley's, man.
You coming?
Oh, come on, man.
All right. Why not?
Yeah. Let's roll.
Oh, oh, oh.
[ Laughs ]
[ Wheels squeaking ]
[ Keys jingling ]
[ Squeaking resumes ]
[ Switch clicks ]
[ Lock clicks, drawer opens ]
[ Drawer closes ]
[ Laughter ]
So, check it out --
this Indian dude
goes into a whorehouse
to get laid
for the first time.
Ohh.
[ Laughs ] They tell him, "you
know, you need to go outside
"and practice on a knot
in a tree for a while
and come back in."
So he goes out
a couple of hours,
comes back,
and says, "I'm ready now."
They get their best hoe.
They send him
in the back room, right?
So, they get in there.
He starts poking her arm
with a stick.
Bitch says, "what the fuck
are you doing?"
Indian dude says,
"me be smart this time.
Me check for bees."
[ Laughter ]
Ohhh!
Come on, Jesus!
Didn't you tell that one
last week?
Oh, no. Fuck no, man.
That was brand-new, man.
[ Laughs ]
All right. Okay.
That's it for me, boys.
Oh, no, no, no.
Where you going, man?
Yeah. No,
I'll see you tomorrow, man.
Come on, man.
The night's still fresh.
Come on, Jack.
Come on, now.
I got plenty more jokes, man.
One more drink.
Come on, man.
All right, I'll get US
another round.
Ah, there you go.
Martinez, move, move.
Yeah, make 'em cold, Jack.
Excuse me, excuse me.
[ Laughs ]
[ Indistinct conversations ]
[ Engine revving ]
Jack, good to see you.
Enough with the games, asshole.
Where's my fucking gun?
Well, I'm sure it will turn up
someplace.
All right, out of
the fucking car right now.
Have you seen your I.A. File?
You should be concerned
with that.
It's not exactly a rave.
How the hell do you know
about that?
You're off duty, Jack.
You should learn to relax.
All right, stop it.
All right, stop this car.
You are under arrest!
You're under arrest, goddamn it!
[ Tires screeching ]
Don't touch that glas.
Excuse me.
Here. Thank you.
Do me a favor.
Get me a baggie
or something, okay?
Mm-hmm.
[ Indistinct conversations ]
[ Snoring ]
[ Crickets chirping ]
[ Clattering ]
[ Dog barking ]
[ Sniffs ]
[ Billiard ball thumping ]
[ Footsteps approaching ]
Ohh! Uhh!
Joe...so sorry.
[ Coughing ]
Is that your nose?
Ohh! Uhh! Uhh!
Whoo!
Uhh!
[ Gasping ]
Uhh! Ohh!
[ Crying ]
Please, stop!
Whoo!
[ Sobbing ]
This is a nice place
you got here, Joe.
[ Sobbing ]
I'm a big fan of
divorce modern myself.
Thinking of having some
work done at my place.
[ Laughs ] This!
Wow, right in the middle
of the fucking living room.
Bet the missus would never let
you get away with this, huh?
[ Gasping ]
Why are you doing this?
We live in a
fucked-up society, Joe.
Cops get criticized,
criminals run free...
But, when assholes like you
from within the force itsef
make other cops' lives
even more difficult,
that's where
I draw the line.
[ Sobbing ] Why are you doing
this? What do you want?
Joe, I need you
to sign this.
I made a few changes.
I hope you don't min.
I didn't write this.
It's false. It's dirty.
Lucas is not involved.
Sign the fucking paper!
[ Sobs ]
Thank you, Joe.
You've been very cooperative
[ gun cocks ]
In what I know are
trying circumstances.
[ Gunshot ]
[ Shell casing clinks ]
[ Telephone beeping ]
Homicide. Lucas.
Ollie: Hey, Jack. What a
kick, talking to you right
there in the department.
I bet you're tracking down
the bad guys right now, huh?
All right, look -- whoever you
are, the joke's over, okay?
[ Playing slow music ]
I don't know if I like
that tone of voice, Jack.
This is your pal,
Ollie, you're talking to.
Bressler: You gave me
the wrong file yesterday.
I asked
for the mcfarland file.
You got something that
belongs to me, you little
shit, and I want it back.
I'm sorry, what's that?
You're gonna have to speak up.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh!
That's right, you can't.
Not with all
those other cops around.
[ Music continues ]
Must be embarrassing,
Jack,
to have your gun lifted
by some dirtbag,
and then not to report it,
well...[Tsks]
All right.
Listen to me.
So far,
nobody's been hurt.
If you want things to go
easier for you, you'll
stop this right now.
Actually, things have been
very easy as it is.
You've been very cooperative,
surprisingly so,
and don't think for a minute
that I don't appreciate it,
because...i do.
And it's really not
accurate to say nobody's
been hurt, Jack.
That's right.
The bad news is
you lost your gun.
The good news is
I got him.
Got who? What the hell
are you talking about?
[ Trilling notes ]
Well, I'll give you
a little hint.
Have you seen Dexter
this morning?
He's not there,
is he?
Perhaps it's because
his brains are splattered
all over his living room.
Is that too big
of a hint?
Jack?
Are you there?
Hello?
Oh, come on. You've got
to admit you're pleased.
Is this some kind
of sick joke?
God, no, Jack.
No, no, no, no, no.
I would never
joke about death.
Death's too frightening,
don't you think?
[ Beeps ]
Yeah, this is gifford
in homicide.
I need a trace on Lucas' phone.
15. Go, go!
By the way, have you had
a chance to see his report?
There's only so much
I can do to save you, Jack.
I'm afraid the report's
your problem.
All right, buddy.
Let's, uh...Let's just --
let's just slow down for
a second, all right?
Let's talk about thi.
You know what, Jack?
I feel strong.
Strong enough to deal with
that bitch ex-wife of mine.
All right, this, uh --
this thing about Dexter --
can, uh -- can we talk
ab-- can we talk
some more about this?
Sure. Sure thing.
Let me just go get some quarters
so I can spend a little more
time on the phone with you.
Gotta go.
[ Telephone beeps ]
[ Dial tone ]
[ Inhales sharply ]
Who was it?
Anonymous tip.
About what?
[ Camera shutter clicks ]
[ Man talking indistinctly
on police radio ]
[ Talking indistinctly ]
[ Gifford
talking indistinctly ]
...and this is
all you have?
[ Talking indistinctly]
Okay, but...
Nobody touched it
but you, right?
All right, all righ.
I know this is --
this is close to hom.
Man, oh, man.
I mean, Dexter wasnt
anybody's favorite..
Here.
Sorry,
I don't do autographs.
Cute.
Well, I'll tell you
one thing.
This killer -- he's one
careless individual.
Either that, or he's trying
to set somebody up.
It's too damn easy.
Look what bressler just found.
Yeah, I got this
out at the curb.
It's got blood
all over it.
He must've dropped it
on the way to his ca.
[ Scoffs ] Let me go
lock this in the truck.
[ Indistinct conversations ]
Well, well, well.
Look who's here.
I guess all five local
channels must be outside no.
Oh, my god.
He's wearing makeup.
Lucas. Gifford.
Sir.
Looks like everybody's managed
to control their grieving.
Well, Dexter was
never a candidate for
Mr. Congeniality, sir.
I'll give you that.
So, you guys were
on the scene first?
Yeah. Lucas got
an anonymous tip.
I see.
O.i.s. Briefed me.
What do you guys go?
[ Exhales slowly ]
Time of death between
3:00 and 6:00 A.M.
We got the slug.
It's, uh, a 9-mil.
Execution-style killing.
Okay. We're talking
professional hit.
Or somebody with a grudge.
The way I hear it,
ex-wife number one was after him
for back alimony.
Ex-wife number two caught him
doing ex-wife number one,
apparently right here
on the pool table.
All right, giffor.
That's more information
than I need right now.
Well, I know it ain't pretty,
sir,
but she did say she'd kill him
if she ever saw him again.
Maybe she saw him again.
Lucas,
what do you think?
I don't think we can rule
anybody out at this point.
Okay.
Well, there's about a dozen
good cops that are out on
unemployment right now
because Dexter got 'em
bumped off the job,
plus 15 ongoing
investigations
in our precinct alone.
You happen to be
one of those.
Everybody knows Dexter
was looking at me.
That's right.
Well, the media's gonna try
to make a meal out of this,
understand?
Can't afford
any more missteps,
so I'm gonna put bresslr
and Martinez on this on.
Nothing personal.
Sorry, guys.
[ Radio news theme plays ]
Man on radio:
It's 11:58 in the southland.
Coming up next on kzby,
we go to the newsroom
and sky copter --
[ clicks radio off ]
[ Birds chirping ]
You got any aspirin?
Whatever my son's got,
it seems like i'm
coming down with it.
Hey, Jack!
How was your lunch, man?
Fine. Why?
'Cause your dessert just showed
up about an hour ago, man.
Your honey here,
I was trying to talk to
her, but she wouldn't have
nothing to do with me, man.
All she wanted
was you.
Hey, Jack, man,
you backing that, ain't you?
No, no. She's just a fr--
no!
Aw, come on, man.
You could --
I'll be right back.
Ha ha ha! Yeah, yeah.
That's my man.
Jack's backing that!
Whoo! Whoo!
You're a damn pig,
bressler.
Ain't no two ways
about it.
Hi. Did you bring me
those tapes?
Are you all righ?
He was at my place,
in my apartment.
When?
Last night.
All right.
How did he get in?
I don't know.
I checked everything.
I looked.
[ Voice breaking ]
The windows weren't jimmied,
and my door was still locked.
Did you see him?
No, no! I was sleeping!
Jesus!
All right, all right.
Just try to calm down,
okay?
I can't calm down, okay?!
I want this guy
arrested now.
All right, look, look --
I -- I want this guy
as bad as you do.
Really. I --
I'm on your side, all right?
[ Sobs ]
But...but I have
to -- I have to follow
procedure here, okay?
That's how it works.
He was in my apartment.
Next time,
he could kill me in my bed.
That's how it works.
I wanna talk to a female cop.
A female will understand.
I understand, all right?
But a female cop is
gonna have to follow
procedure just like me.
"Procedure"?
If your procedure means
that I have to go home
and wait for this psycho
to slit my throat
before you do something...
You can take your procedure,
you can shove it up your ass.
All right, hold on,
hold on a second, okay?
Hold on. All right?
All right, l-let me -- let
me put it to you this way.
You have to look at it
like a judge would.
All right, there was no
evidence of a break-in,
nothing was stolen,
you didn't even see the guy,
so if I want to pull a warrant,
I have to have
probable cause.
You want probable cause?
Here.
A little present
he left me last night.
I'll give you three guesses
what he did all over them.
Show that to a judge.
[ Exhales deeply ]
Shh.
[ Telephone ringing,
indistinct conversations ]
Jack: Jessica?
Jessica, please.
Mm-hmm.
She wouldn't be the reason
you have bags under your eyes
every morning, would she?
Pruitt: Jack!
[ Sighs ]
Jack, uh,
did Dexter give you a copy
of your I.A. Investigation
before he got whacked?
What do you mean,
did he give me a copy?
It's a simple question,
Jack.
No, of course he didn't.
Why?
Well, there were
15 ongoing investigations,
but only 14 files
in Dexter's cabinet.
Yours is missing.
Forget it.
Let's hope it turns up.
[ Telephone beeping ]
Lucas.
Yeah, yeah. Hey, George.
Uh, yeah, thanks for
getting back to me.
I was calling about
that glass from O'Malley's.
You get
any prints on that?
Yeah, well, you know,
it was worth a try.
Thanks.
[ Beeps ]
Hi, it's Jess.
Please leave me a message.
If this is work-related,
page me at --
[ Vehicle door closes ]
Jessica?
Oh, great.
You're getting as bad as him.
Would you just
wait a second?
I can't be late
for work again.
Could you just wait
a second, please?
[ Buzzes ]
Mike, it's Jess.
What?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry
I was insensitive,
but this thing is a lot
more involved than it would
appear with this Ollie guy,
[ footsteps approaching ]
And I couldn't really
talk about it --
is there a problem here?
No, Mike, he's cool.
Thanks.
I get off at 11:00.
I'll pick you up.
[ Gate hinges squeaking ]
How you doing, Mike?
[ Mid-tempo music plays ]
[ Mid-tempo music continues ]
Unh-unh.
No touchies.
Yes, yes, yes!
I'm so out of here!
What?
This really freaky creep
just made my rent! Plus!
Don't worry, it's not him.
This guy has, like,
long, stringy hair,
and his teeth are gross!
You don't mind taking care
of yourself tonight, do you?
No, I have a ride,
actually.
Oh, no.
Let me guess.
"Freeze! Police!"
Cut it out.
"I'm sorry, ma'am.
[ Sniffs ]
"But I think I'm gonna
have to frisk you --"
stop it!
[ Laughs ]
It's not like that.
Yeah, uh-huh. Right.
[ Laughs ]
[ Door opens ]
Mike, call me a cab.
Okay. You're a cab.
Ha ha.
You gotta admit,
it's a little funny.
Yeah, but keep the day job,
big guy, okay?
Wait a minute.
[ Vehicle door closes ]
Hey!
Hey.
You're early.
Oh, really?
She said 11:00.
Yeah, well, since she
was late last time...
[ Lighter clicks ]
Wonder why?
[ Exhales ]
Sal's making her stay.
Hmm.
[ Lighter clicks shut ]
You should go in.
Her act's hot.
I'll get Mike to
let you in for free.
[ Ringing ]
Um...
No, I don't know.
How long did you say? An hour?
You're not gay or anything,
are you?
'Cause most guys
wouldn't mind --
I'm kidding.
Well, if you're not
in the mood to watch a bunch
of beautiful women dance
and wearing almost nothing,
yeah, can I get a cab over
at the playpen, please?
You could save me
some cab fare.
Deal.
Thanks!
Mike, cancel the cab!
See you tomorrow!
All right, never mind.
Scratch that.
[ Engine turns over,
cellphone beeps ]
Always the blondes.
♪ I'll never
go to sleep again ♪
♪ till the night rushes at yu
on leathery wings ♪
Man: Hey, and that's the lovey
Jessica, gentlemen.
Please put your hands togethr
for Jessica!
Why not let her put a feather
in your cap
in one of our private booths
or, better yet,
the v.I.P. Lounge,
where, for a c-note,
you can see it all.
♪ ...and your hope is
almost gone ♪
♪ pray for dawn ♪
♪ yeah ♪
[ Brakes squeaking ]
All right, here you go.
Yep.
I'll wait until you
get inside.
Listen, uh, do me
a little favor.
Turn on the light and
give me a wave so I know
you're okay, all right?
[ Laughs ] Okay.
Well, I won't wait up
for you two.
♪ Black sabbath,
somebody screams ♪
♪ something warm runs
down your face ♪
♪ all that matters
in this haunted dream ♪
♪ is how to get out
of this place ♪
♪ pray for dawn ♪
♪ the devil's at your door ♪
♪ pray for dawn,
pray for dawn ♪
[ Exhales deeply ]
♪ When all your hope is gone♪
♪ yeah, you know ♪
Hey!
♪ Pray for dawn ♪
I'm okay.
♪ The devil's at your door ♪
♪ pray for dawn,
pray for dawn ♪
♪ when all your hope is gone♪
♪ gonna pray for dawn ♪
♪ you better pray for dawn ♪
♪ pray for dawn ♪
♪ you better just
pray for dawn ♪
♪ the devil's at your door,
[ Door unlocks ]
Lucas: So, what are you
gonna do tonight?
I don't know. Sandy
said I could stay here
as long as I want,
which is great, 'cause I
have nowhere else to go.
Aaaaaah! No!!
No!! Oh, my god!!
Sandy!!
[ Sobbing ]
No!! No! No!
[ Crying ]
[ Indistinct conversations ]
[ Police radio beeping ]
[ Helicopter blades whirring ]
[ Dog barking ]
[ Police radio beeps,
indistinct conversation ]
You need to start leveling
with me right now...
Partner.
What the hell's going on
between you and her?
I met her at the club.
Oh. I didn't know you were
into titty bars, Jack.
But, hey -- we've only been
working together three months.
Guess I wasn't gonna find out
everything all at once.
Why was she down at
the station today?
She said somebody was
threatening her.
I told her i'd
look into it.
Oh, well, we sure as
hell are doing that
right now, aren't we?
[ Indistinct conversations ]
Look, Jack...
I'm not boss.
You're gonna have to trust me
once in a while, okay?
This girl might be dead
'cause you didn't.
You don't think
I don't know that, Carla?
[ Conversations continue ]
All right.
[ Plastic rustling ]
Look, I found this
in the dead girl's hand.
All we gotta do now is find
some asshole walking around
with no pocket
on his shirt.
You see this?
Right here, along the bottom,
along the seam.
It's tobacco.
[ Ashes sizzling ]
Yeah.
Just a few grains, but it
makes our killer a smoker.
Maybe the lab can tell US
what brand the fucker smokes.
[ Sighs ]
Well...
Shall we go
talk to your friend?
Yeah.
[ Woman talking indistinctly
on police radio ]
I'm afraid
you're not gonna be able
to stay here tonigh.
Do you have any friend,
family you can get wit?
No.
Then I will give you the names
of a few women's shelters.
They'll be able
to help you out.
There's a decent oe
over on Wilshire.
I'll have a patrolmn
take you there.
Listen, Carla...
I don't want to pass her off
to a stranger, okay?
She trusts me.
I'll take her.
Take me a half hour,
45 minutes.
It's no big deal.
Detective Lucas
will take you.
Thank you.
[ Clattering ]
Jack, I don't have to
stay here. I -- I could --
no, you're safer here
for now.
I just don't want to
cause you any more trouble.
I'm already in trouble.
[ Metal jingling ]
[ Crackling ]
The DNA results on my
handkerchief should be
in by tomorrow night.
If I don't have anything
on him by then...
[ Flushes ]
All right, I gotta get back
to the crime scene.
Try to get some rest.
[ Shuffling footsteps approach ]
[ Doorknob rattling ]
[ Lock rattles, clicks ]
[ Door hinges squeaking ]
[ Exhales ]
[ Hinges squeaking ]
It's okay.
I'm awake.
I told you to take the bed.
I'd hit the couch.
No, I didn't feel comfortable
with that.
Um, I did borrow this,
though.
I hope it's okay.
It was just kind of cold
in here.
Oh, some woman called,
looking for you.
I -- I wasn't snooping
or anything,
but the -- the volume
was up on your machine.
She had
a really sexy voice.
That was Caitlin,
probably checking up on me.
Oh.
S-She's my neighbor.
I -- I feed her cat
when she's out of town.
She's kind of, you know,
neurotic about that.
Uh,
you want some coffee?
Sure.
I -- I got instant.
Great.
Hey, how did it go?
When you got back.
[ Pot clangs ]
[ Clattering ]
Fine.
[ Faucet turns on,
pot fills ]
And your partner?
Did you tell her
that I was staying here?
[ Faucet turns off ]
[ Pot clattering ]
I thought it best not to
mention that for now.
[ Lighter clicking,
flame igniting ]
It's amazing, isn't it?
How one person can fuck up
your life completely.
But when
it happens twice --
well,
that's not really fair.
What was the first time?
[ Cigarette package
rustling ]
September 16, 1997.
I'd just gotten back from
the royal ballet summer
workshop in London.
I had an audition for the
hottest new show on Broadway,
and I was in love.
Well, you know
what happened there.
Yeah, well, you wouldn't be the
first person to blame the ex
for fucking up your life.
Oh, no, no.
He was small potatoes.
I'm talking about
Peter kirmyer.
Who's he?
Bicycle messenger.
He bring you
some bad news or something?
No.
He hit me.
The day before my audition,
as I was crossing
57th street.
I broke my ankle.
And that, as they say,
was that.
When a horse breaks
its leg, you shoot it.
When a dancer breaks her leg,
well, it's time to start
looking into shoe sales.
I think you're doing all right,
you know? You're...
You're working.
Doing what you do.
It's not exactly
what I dreamed of, growing up.
[ Scoffs ]
I know what he wants
from me.
What does he want
from you?
Wish I could figure that out.
I never busted him.
I remember the face of everybody
I ever booked.
Well, maybe he picked you
because...He hates cops.
Maybe it's rando.
No.
Nothing about this guy
is random.
Nothing that's happened between
him and me is an accident,
I know that.
There's a connection
there somewhere. I just --
I saw that befor.
What the hell is it?
[ Chuckles ]
Talk about somebody fucking up
your entire life.
Detective Lucas,
I'd like to talk to you
about something of a
more personal nature.
[ Clock ticking ]
That's fine. Go ahead.
December 5, 1999.
Your mother was found murderd
on that date.
That's correct.
[ Rustling ]
[ Crunching,
smacking lips ]
Who wrote it?
The person
who killed my mother.
It was left
at the crime scene.
The case was never solved.
Can you talk about how
that murder --
how that affects
your job?
Well, I think, if anything,
it's made me a better cop.
And why is that?
Well, when I go to see
somebody whose entire word
has been taken away
by some asshole...
Who doesn't give a shit
whether he's killing
somebody's mother...
Or father, or daughter -
whatever, you know --
maybe they just looked at them
the wrong way, you know?
And he pulls the trigger.
He snuffs out that light
forever.
Well...
I know what those peope
are feeling, you know?
I know what they'e
going through.
Does that make sense?
Yeah.
Makes a lot of sense
to me, Jack.
[ Smacks lips ]
[ Telephone beeps, dialing ]
[ Telephone ringing ]
Lucas.
[ Telephone beeps ]
[ Dial tone ]
Oh, my god.
[ Clock chiming, ticking ]
[ Telephone rings ]
What do you want,
you fucker?
Hey.
Jeez, Jack, do you always
answer the phone that way?
You're gonna
drive your callers off.
Eddie?
Yeah. Well, you told me
to give you a call
if those knuckleheads
came in again.
You know, the, uh, French maid,
the one with the great ass?
Uh, yeah.
Well, uh, she stopped in
and I carded her.
Now, do you want
her address,
or you want to go on
talking nasty to me?
[ Water spraying ]
What was that last name
again, please?
I think it's chadwicke,
with an "e."
You know, when you
first pulled up,
I thought you were gonna ask me
to wash your car.
Yeah.
Uh, you say you were
in his acting class?
Yeah. He's a great actor,
but he's a little weird,
if you ask me.
We did this scene
in class once,
and I went to his house
to rehearse.
You say you went
to his house?
[ Vehicle approaching ]
[ Gate clanking ]
[ Engine turns over ]
[ Tires screech ]
My, my, my.
Aren't we clever?
Hello, there,
Ollie, old pal.
Nice to see you, too, Jack.
Would you move your car, please?
Get out of the car.
You're under arrest.
[ Chuckles ]
You're arresting me?
For what? Murdering Dexter?
Hardly worth it.
He died sniveling --
get out of
the fucking car!
Jack! Easy!
Jack, please!
I have neighbors.
You gonna fuck me now,
Jack?
Is that it?
Shut the fuck up.
[ Leash jingling ]
I haven't done anything!
Call the police!
[ Dog barking ]
Ma'am, I am the police.
This is under control here.
Thank you.
Oh, god, he's killing me!
[ Barking continues ]
You have the right
to remain silent.
[ Handcuffs ratcheting ]
Anything you say can ad
will be used against yu
in a court of law.
You have the right
to an attorney.
If you
cannot afford an attorne,
the state will provide you one
at no cost to you.
These are your rights.
Do you understand them,
you piece of shit?
[ Exhales ]
Yes, I do.
Gifford: Let me just understad
what you're saying...
You're waiving your
constitutional right
to counsel,
is that correct?
I'm an innocent man.
I don't need a lawyer
to tell you that.
[ Sighs ]
Why'd you kill Joe Dexter?
I have no acquaintance
with any Joe Dexter,
much less
a reason to kill him.
Yo, Jack.
Man, I did -- I did the rundown
on this guy like you asked.
This is it?
Okay.
Jack's gone now.
Feel free
to open up a little, okay?
We checked everything, man.
He's clean.
Man, I even ran
the plates on his caddy --
not even
a fucking parking ticket.
Transfer of ownership
from previous owner
Franklin billow four years ago.
That's it.
Doesn't make any sense.
He gave it up already?
No, this motherfucker's
a character.
Now, I got to admit --
he's creative --
that's for sure.
[ Inhales sharply ]
Have dorland come down here
with his machine.
Dorland?
He waived counsel
and agreed to a polygraph?
How'd you pull that one off?
No, he requested it.
[ Jack scoffs ]
[ Machinery scratching ]
Mr. Chadwicke,
do you own a Cadillac?
I do.
Call me old-fashioned,
but I like to buy American.
Yes or no, please.
Yes.
Did you know Joe Dexter?
No.
[ Scratching continues ]
Did you ever meet
Joe Dexter?
Never.
Did you telephone
detective Lucas
here at the station
yesterday evening?
Yes.
Why?
Detective Lucas
and his girlfriend,
Jessica tarrant,
are engaged in a plan
to blackmail me.
Ms. Tarrant is a..
Well,
there are ladies present,
so I'll just say
she's an exotic dancer,
but that should tell you
enough right there.
Anyway, after their failed
and clumsy attempt
at extortion,
I assume they are now
trying to frame me
for the murder
of this Joe Dexter perso.
Oh, give me a -- oh.
See, I told you --
it's rich, ain't it?
What was the nature
of the conversation
between you
and detective Lucas?
Well,
I...admittedly have,
on one or two occasions...
Visited Ms. Tarrant's club.
And I tend to tip
rather heavily.
It's a weakness of mine.
Anyway,
Ms. Tarrant became...
Fixated on me,
for lack of a better wor.
I think she smelled mone.
My family's quite wealthy.
It makes me something
of a target.
Let's stick with the
conversation between you
and detective Lucas, please.
Yes, of course.
I simply told detective Lucas
that I knew very well
what he and Ms. Tarrant
were up to,
and that if he thought
he was gonna get away with it,
he was sorely mistake.
It's not the first tie
that somebody's tried
something like this.
You cannot imagine
the kind of scum
that comes out of the woodwork.
Stick with the conversation,
please.
Detective Lucas
became abusive,
and I was forced
to hang up.
I'm not believing this.
I mean, this fucker is lying
through his teeth.
Oh, come on, cap, you're not
buying this piece-of-shit story.
I mean, this -- this
is all just a -- a
fucking smoke screen.
Ask him where he was
the night Dexter got kille.
Mr. Chadwicke...
Where were you the night
Dexter was killed?
At home.
I was...Watching
one of my mother's old films.
I have them all
on videotape.
It reminds me
of what she was like.
I still feel her loss
as if it were yesterday.
You know,
I read the papers.
I've heard about this
department's questionable
ethics and tactics --
rogue cops and whatnot,
but this...
This is unacceptable.
Once again, Mr. Chadwicke...
Did you murder Joe Dexter?
Why would I murder
a man that I have never met?
Yes or no?
No.
[ Scratching continues ]
Absolutely not.
Jack...
[ Footsteps retreat ]
[ Clicks, scratching stops ]
Well, you may not want
to hear this.
Bridges, let's have it.
In my opinion,
he's telling the truth.
I don't see how.
Jack said he admitted
to killing Dexter,
and I believe him.
Look, there's something off
about this guy.
I think he knows
how to beat your machine.
It's impossible.
Unless he's so crazy he believes
everything he's saying,
he's telling the truth --
bottom line.
Sorry.
Cut him loose.
Mr. Chadwicke...
Hmm?
You're free to go.
Hmm.
Catch me if you can.
The fuck did you just say?!
Ugh!
You murdering fuck!
Jack!
Jack, come on!
Bressler, can you get him?!
Jack! Jack!
Get off me!
All right, get off me!
Hey, get him out of here!
Get him out of here, bressler!
All right, I got him, man.
Now I know -- now I know!
Do you hear me?!
Get him out!
All right, come o.
[ Sniffles, sighs ]
My hands are tied.
That's the city's
official position.
[ Sniffling ]
Okay. Thank you.
Mr. Chadwicke...
Uh-huh.
Okay, here's
what we're willing to do.
Uh, the department will pay
for all hospital expenses,
um, any other restitution
you may need.
As for pressing charges,
I hope you'll reconsider.
This man injured me.
He humiliated me
in front of my neighbors.
I know.
I am -- I'm -- I'm very sorry.
And -- and he's sorry, too.
And his temper --
um, that aside,
I think that we do better
to handle things
within the department.
The department?
The department's a disgrace.
I'm filing charges.
Well, you don't --
I'll tell you
something else, sir.
I have many friends in
the media as well as on the
county board of supervisors.
And it is well-known
that you have your eye on
the chief's job when he
steps down next year.
I'll thank you to wipe
that smirk off your face.
I want this man placed
under arrest immediately,
or I will make some
phone calls,
make your life
a living hell!
Okay.
All right.
You have my word.
Good.
[ Footsteps retreating ]
[ Telephone beeping,
door closes ]
[ Door opens ]
[ Clears throat ]
Door.
Yeah, pruitt.
What?
[ Latch clicks ]
Uh-huh.
Yeah.
[ Ashes sizzling ]
I see.
What about the DNA?
The -- the second it comes in,
you let me know.
All right. Bye.
[ Receiver clicks ]
There's a security guad
at the playpen,
says he saw
the murdered girl
get into your car last nigh.
That makes you, jac,
the last person
to see her alive.
Greg, how long
have you known me, huh?
You can't really believe
I killed this girl.
That's not the issue.
Let's put that aside.
This guy --
this character --
chadwicke...
You should have seen
what you did to his nose.
He wants your ass real bad.
All right?
Real bad.
Yeah, so,
what are you saying to me?
What I'm saying, Jack,
is we've been getting
the shit kicked out of US
in the press recently.
If I don't stop
the bleeding now,
it's gonna turn into
a media circus.
Look...
I know you've been going
through hell recently.
I feel for you.
But...
I got to ask for your gun.
Come on.
That's the way we do it.
[ Exhales heavily ]
[ Sighs ]
And the other one --
the beretta -- where is it?
[ Vehicles passing ]
It's at home.
Why?
I took it to the range
the other night.
I noticed a, uh, a crak
in the slide.
I was gonna take t
to the armorer.
Look, I can go and get it,
all right?
It'll only take me an hour.
If you're worried,
you send gifford with me.
One hour. Go.
Don't leave me hanging,
Jack.
[ Door closes ]
[ Vehicle approaches ]
[ Brakes squeaking ]
[ Keys jingling,
engine turns off ]
Be right back.
She's there, isn't she?
The girl?
You didn't take her
to no damn shelter.
No.
[ Sighs ]
I knew it.
He would have found her there,
Carla, all right?
He could have gotten to her
like that, easy.
You are not helping
yourself any.
Damn, Jack, sometimes
I wonder if you want to go down.
Look, let me explain
something to you.
I'm gonna help you out
as much as I can, okay?
But I won't go down
with you.
I can't do that to my family.
I wouldn't want you to.
All right, as long as
we understand each other.
This will just take
a few minutes.
Damn, if that's all it takes,
I feel sorry for her.
[ Laughing ]
Just trying to lighten things
up a little, okay?
[ Car door closes ]
Ahh.
[ Door opens ]
I don't have a lot of time,
so grab your things and
come with me, okay?
Why?
Just do it, please.
Jack,
tell me what's going on.
He killed my mother,
Jess --
my mother, Dexter, Sandy.
He's the one who wrote this.
Oh, my god.
Now, there's no question
in my mind that you're next.
This fucker knows
everything about me.
He knows where I live,
and I'm pretty sure
he's figured out
that you're here by now,
so can we, please?
But I'm allergic to cats.
I promise you you'll never see
the fucking thing.
It hides under the bed
all day.
Listen, once you're in here,
don't come back out.
Don't let anybody in
but me.
What if your neighbor
comes back? What do I say?
She won't.
She's gone all week.
[ Engine grinds ]
[ Sighs ]
[ Engine turns over ]
[ Tires screeching ]
[ Frédéric chopin's "etude
in e major op. 10 no. 3" plays ]
[ Latch clicks ]
[ Exhales sharply ]
[ Clock chimes ]
[ Paper rustling ]
[ Drawer opens ]
[ Whistling ]
[ Drawer closes ]
[ Whistling continues ]
[ Ice rattling ]
[ Paper rustling ]
I got you, you little fuck.
[ Telephone rings,
whistling continues ]
[ Beeps, static ]
[ Sighs ]
[ Static continues ]
[ Whistling ]
[ Floorboard creaks ]
[ Doorbell rings ]
Yes?
Man: Fedex.
Can you just leave it,
please?
I need a signature.
Sorry.
Of course you do.
Coming!
[ Music ends ]
[ Whistling ]
[ Horn honking ]
[ Engine revving,
tires screech ]
Jack?
Dad, I'm in trouble.
I need your help.
What kind of trouble?
Just get in, please.
I'll tell you on the way.
Where are we going?
Your place.
I need to borrow something.
Jack, what in the hell's
going on?
The kid in this picture --
was he ever a patient of yours
at shackleton?
Jesus Christ.
Where in the hell
did you get this?
So you do know him.
Richard Bigelow...
Brilliant, brilliant kid...
Deeply disturbed...
Dark, violent nature.
That's his mother,
Shannon cane.
She was an actress, right?
B-movies.
More of a pinup girl,
really.
There were rumors she had
an incestuous relationship
with her father,
and she, uh, carried on
the family tradition
with her son.
Anyway, Bigelow walks in
on them one afternoon --
mother and son
in all their glory.
He tries to separate them,
and Richard beats him
within an inch of his life.
So the old man
has the kid committed.
Three years later,
both parents are dead --
murder/suicide.
The father did it.
He strangled her,
then he shot himself.
Richard is named
sole beneficiary
of the family's fortune --
over $100 million.
And he can't touch it.
He's enraged.
He tried everything --
tried to pretend
he had been rehabilitated,
but I knew better.
What did you do then?
I made damn sure
he stayed locked up
as long as humanly possible.
I got the review board
to Grant
a 10-year stay
on any further reviews.
Oh, my god.
His next review date
would have been...
A little over two years ago.
Oh, god.
It's him, dad.
"Catch me if you can" --
he said it straight to my face.
[ Brakes squeaking ]
[ Engine turns off ]
[ Police radio beeps ]
Man: Perry -- 33 negative.
[ Vehicles passing ]
[ Rattling ]
[ Clicking ]
Be careful, son.
[ Keys jingling ]
[ Engine revving ]
[ Footsteps approach ]
[ Water running ]
[ Police radio beeps ]
[ Man talking indistinctly
on police radio ]
[ Woman talking indistinctly
[ Tires screeching ]
[ Creaking,
water stops running ]
[ Telephone rings ]
[ Answering machine clicks ]
[ Beeps ]
Hey, neighbor, it's Caitlin.
So, I call in for messages
a few minutes ago,
and some chick
answers the phone.
What's up with that?
Call me.
[ Answering machine beeps ]
Oh, fuck this.
[ Door closes ]
[ Floorboards creaking,
man talking indistinctly ]
Oh, hell, no.
[ Door hinges squeaking ]
[ Inhales sharply ]
Jack, show me your hands.
[ Panting ]
Is this how you reward
people who trust you?
[ Gasps ]
Carla...
Ugh!
Shh.
You'll scare the kitty.
Carla, listen to me.
He's in there right now.
He's in there somewhere,
and if he finds Jessica,
he's gonna kill her.
Do you hear me?
Ahh!
Where's Jack?
[ Gasping ]
Where's your hero?
Carla, please, listen to me.
Do you remember what you
said to me last night
about trusting yo?
Come on, sweetie.
Tell me.
If I was guilty,
would I come back here, huh?!
[ Gasping ] No!
[ Muffled ] No! No!
No!
Carla, please.
I'm begging you.
[ Gun uncocks ]
I swear to god, Jack,
I lose my job over this,
I'm taking it out on your ass!
Call for backup
and watch that back exit.
[ Muffled ] No! Ugh! Ugh!
[ Door hinges squeak ]
[ Door closes ]
Officer needs assistance --
possible homicide suspect --
1307 palmetto.
[ Exhales deeply ]
How the hell
do I get myself into this shit?
Jess?
Jessica?
[ Gasping ] Jack! Oh!
It's okay. It's okay.
It's okay.
I got you.
Jack!
I'm here.
[ Crying ]
It's okay. I'm here.
I got you.
[ Coughing ]
It's gonna be okay.
You're okay.
[ Panting ]
Oh, how sweet.
Would you get your hands
in the air, please?
Up!
[ Breathing rapidly ]
Quite the rogue cop,
aren't you, Jack?
Hell of a killing spree
you've been on.
Too bad it has to end.
But...all things must pass.
[ Gun cocks ]
Would you get on your knees,
please?
I promise you,
you won't feel a thin.
Like my mother?
Oh, I wish that were true,
Jack,
but unfortunately,
there was quite a bit of pain.
If only your father had
cooperated, none of this
would have been necessary,
but...stubborn to the end,
I suppose.
Mine was the same way.
We have that in common.
What are you talking about?
Oh, Jack, don't you know?
It's amazing what you can
accomplish in a single night
with a lazy orderly
and a broken window latch.
You won't get away with it
this time.
My partner's downstairs
right now calling for backup.
Well,
I'll add her to the list.
Just think, Jack...
When all is said and done,
you may go down
as one of the city's
great serial killers.
[ Gun cocks ]
Say a little prayer.
Gifford: Drop it.
[ Gun cocks ]
Drop it.
No.
[ Panting ]
[ Woman talking indistinctly
on police radio ]
You take care of her.
I'm gonna secure that gun.
Thanks.
You're gonna be okay,
honey.
[ Crying ]
I need an ambulance --
1307 palmetto.
Ugh.
[ Groaning ]
[ Gun cocks ]
[ Vehicle approaching ]
Out of the car,
and nobody gets hurt.
Cool, cool.
[ Gunshot ]
[ Gunshot echoes ]
[ Tires screeching ]
[ Gunshots ]
[ Glass shattering ]
[ Tires screeching ]
[ Engine grinding ]
Come on!
[ Tires screeching ]
God damn it!
[ Engine revving ]
[ Grinding continues ]
And I thought my car
was a piece of shit!
[ Engine revving,
tires screeching ]
[ Gun cocks ]
[ Gunshots, glass shattering ]
[ Tires screeching ]
[ Clicks ]
[ Engine revving ]
[ Horns honking ]
[ Tires screeching ]
[ Tires screeching,
horns honking ]
[ Glass shattering ]
[ Engine revving ]
[ Gunshots ]
[ Tires screeching,
indistinct shouting ]
[ Horns honking ]
Whoa!
Oh!
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
Whoa! Whoa!
[ Tires screeching ]
Oh!
Aah!
[ Indistinct shouting ]
[ Gunshots ]
[ Tires screeching ]
[ Engines revving,
tires screeching ]
Oh! Oh! Oh!
Aah!
Whoa! I don't know!
I don't know!
Aah! Aah!
[ Indistinct shouting ]
[ Sirens approaching ]
Man, look, don't shoot!
Get out of here!
Move! Move!
[ Indistinct shouting ]
Shall we add her
to the tally, Jack?
After all,
this is your gun.
Why do you want
to shoot her, huh?
You won.
I'm already fucked.
You saw to that.
You walk away right now,
and I'm still going down,
just like you planned it.
I know what you're trying to do,
Jack -- very admirable --
pathetic, but admirable.
You really want to talk
about pathetic?
My father told me
all about you,
about how your mother used you
to get back at daddy.
[ Laughing ]
That's not true.
He's lying.
Did it hurt?
Did it hurt knowing
she was just fucking you
to feed her own fucked-up,
twisted psyche?
I mean, no wonder you're such
a little motherfucker, huh?
[ Chuckles ]
Well, here.
Now, come on.
Let her go. You win.
I told you, Jack,
it won't work.
[ Shell casing clinking ]
[ Thud ]
Just did.
[ Sirens approaching ]