Tensions are
high as a result of the US
not signing the Kyoto
agreement, the global treaty
aimed at reducing the world's
pollution and emittance levels.
The State Department is declaring
the Brazilian rainforest
to be of national interest
to the US since May 1998.
Unidentified tribesmen of
Brazil's Amazon River region,
protesting what they
call death pollution,
have taken over and
shut down two dozen
American oil installations.
To date, these sieges
have cost the petroleum
industry almost $14 billion.
In response, the US and
Brazilian governments
broke ground on a new program
they hope will end this turmoil
and bring these two sides together.
Scott Turner from the US State Department
is here to oversee the program.
It's a win-win, Ann.
Under SBP, the area
businesses will receive
this paved superhighway
and a unilateral peace
keeping force to prevent
further hostilities.
Now, the tribesmen will receive
our word that this highway will
extend no further than 100 miles
into the country, a moratorium
on any new drilling,
and restrictions
on pollution and emissions that
will be stricter than ever before.
Hopes hang high here
that separate, but protected,
may finally bring an
end to this unrest.
From the town of Brazil,
I'm Ann Bauer, ICN News.
And clear.
Good.
Man it's hot.
Quadrant 10 all clear.
Follow up check at 1300 hours.
Hopes hang high here.
That's a large lump of alliteration,
wouldn't you say?
Bite me, Raka.
I am tired.
Tired, I wouldn't guess.
Horny for a certain State
Department suit, maybe, but not tired.
What?
Yes, Mr. Turner, please tell us what you
are doing to save the indigenous peoples.
He's not that bad.
Well, the perfect hair does
hide the pointy little horns.
Boy toy at six o'clock.
Scotty.
Hello again.
Hi.
Listen, I was...
I was wondering if you
had any plans for dinner.
You mean, something
other than black beans
and rice for the
fifth consecutive day?
Exactly.
How would you like to come to
Brasilia with me for a real dinner?
Steak, french fries...
You serious?
I never joke about dinner.
That sounds like a plan.
Great, excellent.
Just give me 15 minutes, OK?
All right.
OK.
My god.
Scotty, look.
Hit it.
Attack!
Attack, attack!
Fire.
Get your guns.
Come on, guys.
Get some coverage.
Get down!
Where is it coming from?
Get your gun.
Come on, guys.
Get behind here, now.
There they are.
Shit.
Jesus Christ.
What?
I don't like this, Ann.
We were told not to leave camp.
We're breaking curfew.
They took my tapes.
They took my camera.
Do you mind telling me
what we are looking for?
No idea.
Well, how are we going
to know when we find it?
No clue.
This has been fun.
I'm going back now.
- No.
Raka, no.
Wait.
They are hiding something.
I can feel it.
Ann, what are they hiding?
I don't know yet.
We haven't found it.
Tell me exactly what
the tribesman said.
He said he was a shadow people.
Shadow people?
The hell is shadow people?
Supposedly, the ultimate
warriors of the Amazon.
And until today, I just
thought, just a legend, but.
Well, why would they be here?
Well, that's what freaked me out.
When I asked him that, he said..
My Portuguese is a little rusty.
What?
Ann, that's demons from the sky.
Demons from the sky?
Shadow people?
I wonder if they're looking
for an anchor in Wichita Falls.
Run.
What the...
This is a restricted area.
Do not move.
Passaporte.
Ann Bauer.
I'm a journalist.
Come on, guy.
I'm just doing my job.
No.
Shit.
Vamos.
Let's go.
Get out of here.
Blood pressure stable, no infection,
rapid tissue regeneration
due to unknown toxin.
Unknown toxin?
What the... Looks like
some kind of insect.
My god.
Get well soon, sexy.
Got to go.
Doctor?
Well, yes and no.
Let me be specific.
Are you my wife's doctor?
Wife?
Martin Bauer.
I'm Ann's husband.
North.
Dr. Stephen North.
How did you...
Ann's emergency contact card.
Are you my wife's doctor?
No.
Actually we're more like associates.
Associates?
Yes, associates.
Well, Mr. Associate,
you want to tell
me why you're playing tonsil
hockey with my comatose wife?
I think you've got the wrong idea.
Yeah?
Well, maybe.
But I think you better
get your ass out of here
before I introduce
my foot to your ass.
Lovely.
Excuse me.
I can't imagine why she'd be
divorcing someone as charming
as you.
These babies really
are the perfect killers.
Our bioengineered beauties
cleared six towns.
No wonder they call
them demons from the sky.
Sir, census shows 37 villagers.
We have 37 confirmed kills.
37 out of 37, that's not bad.
We're moving to the next town.
Yes, sir.
I'm trying to make up my
mind if I should let you live.
You should've killed
that reporter last night.
Yes, sir.
I'm very disappointed.
Can I trust you?
Yes, sir.
You don't like me?
No, sir, I don't.
Good, let's keep it that way.
I'm going to give
you one more chance.
Sir?
What are you...
Better be quick.
Goodbye.
Shit.
Merda.
Show me exactly where
you were on the base.
Why are you so interested?
Raka, this could save Ann's life.
You want to help or not?
All right.
Somewhere around here.
Dr. North, what is it today?
An outbreak of trench
foot or jock itch?
Just some research, thank you.
Come on, guys.
Come on, let's get moving.
OK, clear this out.
Yeah, right here.
Right in here.
That's good.
Go back.
Contusions of the
face and chest, insect toxins
appear to have sped
up tissue regrowth.
Rule out ants.
OK, where are you guys?
Come on.
I know you're here somewhere.
What the...
My god.
What are you doing here?
Let's see.
In case of emergency, call
Martin Bauer, husband.
That's me.
So you want to tell
me what happened?
I'm pretty sure that I got shot.
After that, I don't know.
Those welts are nasty looking.
That's attractive.
It didn't seem to
bother your boyfriend.
Boyfriend?
Dr. North.
Gross.
He's a medical researcher.
Well, he had you in a lip
lock when I came in the room.
It just makes me wonder what
kind of research he's doing.
What the hell are you saying?
Look, why don't you just
come back to New York with me?
Here it comes.
Ann, I need you.
Yeah, Martin's needs first, right?
Come on.
Don't start with that again.
Yes, this again.
Do you even remember why I left?
See if this rings a bell.
Let's have a baby,
Martin, start a family.
Look, I want those
things too, but I just...
When?
Some day, I don't know.
You know, these last few months,
I have realized that you will
never be ready to be a dad.
Because you will
never be ready to put
anyone else's needs before your
own, not a child, not mine.
Ann?
Scotty.
Hi.
Martin, this is Scotty Turner.
He works for the State Department.
Scotty, this is my...
Martin Bauer.
Martin, it's a pleasure to meet you.
I came as soon as I heard.
Ann, I am so sorry you got
caught in the crossfire again.
Maybe we should just
get you out of here.
Scotty?
Would you mind giving us a second
to finish our business?
Yeah, sure.
I'm sorry.
I understand.
Here, I got these for you, Ann.
Thank you.
I'll just be down the hall.
Is there any guy
in this country who's
not trying to sleep with you?
Get out.
Look, I'm sorry, just...
OK.
When did you become such an asshole?
At the exact moment you packed
your last bag and you left.
Take care of yourself.
The bites have faded.
It's amazing.
No, that's a miracle.
Happy bar mitzvah?
Well, they were all out of
sorry you got shot while I
was running my ass off, so.
Well, it works.
Thanks for coming.
Least I could do for
the one who got shot.
And how do I look?
Not bad.
Have you seen North?
I have a backhand
with his name on it.
No, he's gone.
He flies to New York today.
What?
Why?
Yesterday, he goes out
to where we got jacked
and he comes back
with a sealed crate.
Today, he fly.
Did you see what was in the crate?
No, he wouldn't let anyone near it.
Why?
Let's take a ride, Raka.
Sure appreciate this, sir.
A lot.
Perfect.
You know we're putting ourselves
in danger by going back there.
Raka, I'm a reporter.
I've got to do my job.
Just drive.
Ann?
Yeah?
You don't remember much about
the night you got shot, do you?
No, not much.
Why?
You do remember getting
chased though, right?
Yeah.
They're back.
Get us the hell out of here.
Come on.
Just whose cornflakes
did you piss in?
Why do you think it's me?
Because everybody love Raka.
I got an idea.
When I yell \ "now, \"
brace yourself.
Anytime you're ready.
Don't rush.
In 3, 2, 1, now.
And your story is
going to get us killed.
They are not going
to let you carry it on.
Don't worry.
It will fit under my seat.
Yeah, and about seven others.
I'm not hearing you.
She's right, you know.
Excuse me?
This airline allows for a
maximum carry-on girth of 62
inches, which is the total length,
width, and height of the bag.
Your surfboard's too long.
Told ya.
This is a Dewey Weber.
It does not travel with baggage.
Your fly is down.
United Flight 777 to Los Angeles
is now boarding at gate 53.
This is the final boarding call
for Interamerica's flight 71
to New York City.
But it's a Dewey Weber.
I don't care if it's
a Denzel Washington.
It rides downstairs.
Hello.
Thank you.
All I can tell you
is we gave our best.
OK, you gave it your best.
That's all a man can do.
Stay put.
I'll pick you up.
- Yes, sir.
Roger that.
Thank you.
No problem.
10-4.
Yeah, Buzzard?
This is E.
- Yes, sir.
Go for Buzzard.
Over.
I think we've located
our problem tribe.
There's no time to get
our project to site.
I need fire power in the air.
Right away, sir.
Requesting coordinates.
Over.
OK, Ann.
Before I go back to the Jeep,
what are we looking for?
We're looking for what North found.
And that is?
You're a leper.
Come on, Raka.
Be serious.
I'm seriously not following.
Look, if I know North, he thinks
that whatever gave me
these delightful hickies
also caused my rapid recovery.
And that could be worth a
pretty penny in New York.
And I think it might be what
our friends in the dune buggy
were trying to protect.
Ezekial, you son of a bitch.
Run!
Welcome on board to Interamerica's
flight 71 to New York City.
We'll try to make the
next 10 hours of flight
as pleasant as possible.
I've been informed we
have some turbulence
for about the first 100 miles,
but we should be able to get
through that pretty quick.
Please, if you would, keep
your seatbelts fastened.
Refrain from using any personal
electronics here until we
get out of the rough stuff.
Thanks for flying Interamerica.
Sir?
Yes?
Your laptop?
Yes, it is.
Thanks for asking.
The hell was that?
Shit.
Is that what I think it is?
Ideas?
No.
This has not been my week.
Demons from the sky.
Let's get the hell out of here.
You know, three years traveling
to this backward-ass
continent, I've yet
to finish a complete drink.
Jesus Christ.
You guys try to hit
every bump or what?
Shit.
Have... have Bonnie and Michelle
check on the passengers.
Yes, sir.
Interamerica passengers
flight 71, this is
your captain speaking.
Sorry for the bumpy ride.
We'll try to avoid any more
turbulence in the future.
In the meantime, please
keep your seatbelts fastened
and refrain from moving
around the cabin.
Thank you.
Have you ever seen
anything like that?
Yeah.
I just forgot to tell you.
Wonder if there's any
openings for cameramen
in the Middle East.
Pick up the phone, lunatic.
You don't mind if I
answer this, do you?
I think we're out
of the rough stuff.
Be my guest.
Thanks.
Hello?
Maniac.
You didn't do what I think you did?
Ann?
Hi, how are you?
You didn't do it, did you?
You haven't read about the
honey shortage in New York,
have you?
It's a terrible thing.
Are you out of your mind?
Do you have any idea
what those bees can do?
Do I know what they can do?
Sweetheart, you were covered
with stings from them
and your tissue healed
at a remarkable rate.
You know, by all rights,
you should be dead now.
More times than you'll know.
Do you have any
idea what this little
find will be worth to the
pharmaceutical community?
And I'm sure you understand this
couldn't possibly be trusted
to some third-world facility.
No.
Only the best for my
little bee-auties.
You sick monkey.
You've got to...
Ann, we're breaking up.
I think we're going into a tunnel.
Look, when I get to New
York, I'll give you a buzz.
Asshole.
Women.
Scott Turner.
Scotty, big problem.
Ann, what's wrong?
Something very dangerous is on
a plane to New York right now.
Hold on.
Slow down now.
What plane and what's dangerous?
Bees, Scotty, killer bees.
No, he's coming this way.
We weren't properly introduced.
I'm Adam.
What did you say your name was?
I didn't.
She's Sandy.
Quit it.
So Sandy, maybe when
we get back to New York,
we could get together, you
know, for dinner maybe.
Dinner?
Breakfast too,
depending on how it goes.
Alex?
Adam.
Can I be blunt with you?
I prefer it.
Good.
Because I'd rather run my towel
over a midget wrestler's hair
butt than spend one more second
this close to a geek like you.
OK, Alex?
You just lost your chance at dinner.
Deep regret.
Sir.
I'll be out in a snap, OK?
Hey.
Well, that's the
third one we've passed.
What's that?
A deserted town.
Where are all the people?
You know, it's a
reasonable question.
This whole thing gets
weirder and weirder.
Turn on your
phone, you bloody idiot.
Mister?
Yeah?
Can I ask you a question?
Well, you can't jump in front.
No.
It's more like advice.
Advice?
Not exactly the father knows
best type, if you know what I mean.
That's all right.
Do you understand women?
I mean, like, how to treat
them so that they'll like you?
I'll tell you what.
You give me your number.
And when I figure women
out, I'll call you.
Great.
Yeah.
So expect a call in, like, never.
Thanks.
No problem.
Maybe I'll just
stick to my computers.
What is that guy doing in there?
What's that?
Probably hemorrhoids.
You ready for this, Casper?
What did he say?
Well, you did get your hickies from the
demons from the sky, which makes you highly
unpopular with the townspeople
because you should be six feet under.
Right.
Rumor has it that
after you were stung,
you were taken away
by shadow people.
Wonderful.
Are you OK?
Shit.
Get the captain.
You want to look
for the shadow people?
Absolutely.
Why?
Well, it's obvious.
They must have a serum.
They saved my life with something.
That's great.
They can open a drugstore,
call it Spook and Save.
Raka.
- Ann, they could be cannibals.
Raka, if those bees get out on
that plane, hundreds could die.
And if they breed in New
York, it could be millions.
That's not fair.
All right, but I'm driving.
Well, just, you know,
heard this really loud bang
and then he came out like that.
Did you hear anything else?
Just the electric shaver, that's it.
Have you seen my headphones?
Yes.
There they are, my dear, down there.
Now what the hell's going on?
You have to warn the pilot.
Ann, my people have been trying.
Interamerica hasn't heard of
any problems with that flight.
They're inclined to let
them complete the trip
and handle the
situation in New York.
Scotty, if they don't
bring that plane back soon,
it's going to be out over the water.
And if anything does
happen, they're screwed.
I know.
And we are working on it, OK?
Now, shouldn't you be resting?
Yeah, well I have to
meet some people first.
What people?
Shadow people.
What?
What, are you kidding me?
No, I wish I were.
You know where they are?
Well, I think so.
The shaman told Raka.
Why?
I don't know.
I just heard they were
hard to find, that's all.
Why are you looking for them?
Well, I think they
must have an antidote.
If anything does happen,
we have to be ready.
Got to let us know what's going on.
In a minute, sir.
Are you sure?
This is the third time I've
been over the passenger list.
If there's a doctor on this flight,
he doesn't want to be known.
Captain, we got to land this thing.
You're in my chopper.
I'll have a beer or two.
Buzzard?
Si?
Yes, sir.
Go for Buzzard.
Over.
- Yeah.
We've got a problem.
A little bit of our
project has flown the coop.
Sao Paolo, this is Interamerica 71.
We have a medical emergency
on board, two passengers down.
Need medical assistance,
authorization return.
Over.
Flight 71, maintain current course.
The hell is going on down there?
Well, sir, let me give you
three reasons why you hired me.
I know how to improvise.
I'm quick on my feet.
And I'm a natural born asshole.
Why don't you guys
go back to your seats?
I can look after him for a while.
What now?
Somebody help me.
He's choking.
Come on.
Get it out.
There you go.
Get him a glass of water, would you?
All right.
Just breathe, OK?
Deep breaths, you're going to be OK.
Breathe.
Mr. Bauer?
Yeah, kid?
I think you need to see this.
What is it, chicken wing?
No.
It's a bee.
Bee?
A bee?
My god.
You.
Yes, me.
Molested anybody else's wife lately?
Stay back.
How about if I just wipe that smirk
off your face right here in first class?
You don't know what
you're dealing with.
No.
You don't know what you're dealing...
This isn't helping, morons.
Fellas?
What?
Look.
Got a bee on your neck, pal.
Get it off!
You OK?
Here, take this.
You're going to get a call.
What?
This is Interamerica's flight 71.
Come in, Sao Paolo tower.
Any ideas?
Well, all the attacks
have occurred in coach.
So maybe if we move
everybody up to first class
and try to find some way to seal
it off, maybe that will work.
Might buy us some time.
All right.
You're in charge out there.
OK.
OK, executive decision.
Let's turn this
around and head back.
I'm not going over water like this.
Something that shaman told me back
in town kind of freaked me out.
What's that?
Legend has it that the shadow people
are led by a white demon named Savior.
Yeah?
And the shaman told me that Savior
carried you in his arms.
Now, you're possessed by him.
So I've got that going for me.
My god, it's ringing.
This will never work.
Yeah, got any better ideas?
Duct tape.
Look, maybe if you
just stop bitching.
Mr. Bauer?
Yeah?
Continue this later.
Yeah, hello?
You stupid asshole.
Call me an asshole, bitch.
Martin?
Ann?
You know that person?
It's my wife.
Great, his wife.
Maybe my mommy will call next.
She'll let us land.
You want to shut up so I can hear?
Marty?
Ann, calling to talk
to your boyfriend?
That pompous ass
is not my boyfriend.
What are you doing?
Here?
Well I just figured
our reconciliation
went so well that I should probably
go back home and clean the pizza
boxes off your side of the bed.
You are such a jerk.
Look, Ann.
I'm kind of busy here right now, so.
Martin, it's really important
that I speak to Dr. North.
Well, I don't think
you're going to have a very
enlightening conversation.
You see, Dr. North is doing his
best not to swallow his own tongue.
My god, the bees got out?
How in the hell do
you know about that?
It's too long to explain.
Is anybody else hurt?
Yeah.
We got four down so far.
And from the looks of
them, I don't even think
they're going to make the meal.
Listen, I don't think we can
keep the bees out of the cabin
much longer.
We got to land this thing.
Well, I'm working on that.
And I think I found a serum.
We'll meet you wherever you land.
Deal.
It will be good to see you again.
Yeah?
You too.
Bye.
Scott Turner.
Scotty, how come that plane
is not on the ground yet?
I told you.
We are trying.
We are trying very hard.
For Christ's sake, what was that?
I'm going to have
to get back to you.
Ann?
- So now what?
Walk, I guess.
I was afraid you
were going to say that.
Raka?
- Ann?
We're more than 100 miles from
the eastern border, aren't we?
Probably two.
And the new
superhighway is only supposed
to run 100 miles, right?
That's what I heard in the news.
So why is there all this
road construction equipment way
out here?
- That's a good question.
Let's go.
All right.
How's it going?
Done?
Well, as done as I could do
with duct tape and blankets.
Let's take a look.
Your controls.
OK.
Thanks for the info.
Out.
I know why they won't let us land.
I just talked to a friend of mine
over at Ecuadorian Internationals.
Rumor is we're carrying
a type of virus,
like the Ebola or something.
- What?
Somebody got a call from the US.
State Department confirming.
US State Department?
No one's ever going
to let us land if they
think we have a virus on board.
Looks like we're on our own up here.
Can help you, sir?
I'm sure you can.
I'm positive there's a passenger
that needs a barf bag or a pillow.
Why don't you go find...
I think everyone is OK, sir.
Why don't you return to your seat?
No can do, sky waitress.
I'm here to see the captain.
Well, he's very busy now, sir.
Look, Kristi, love.
You either move out of my way or I'm
going to be forced to put you
on the low rent section of this bus.
Do you know what I mean?
Of course I do, sir.
Now, let me tell you what I need.
First, the name is
Michelle, not Kristi, love.
Second, this is Interamerica's
flight number 71, not
some rickety, old southern bus.
Third, when I tell
you to take your seat,
it is for your safety, as well as
the safety of others around you.
Sir, we're going to be landing soon.
Let me put your tray in it's...
locked position.
Thank you for flying Interamericas.
Have a nice day.
Now what?
Let's go check the blankets.
Tell him we're not
going to hurt him.
I understand he's a shaman.
He must be a proud man.
Is he wise too?
Do you know who I am?
I'm the asshole.
Ask him about the shadow people.
Where are they?
Por favor.
Por favor my ass.
I know you know where they are.
Point it out on the map.
Do you know what this is?
It shoots people.
Sir, you're wasting our time here.
He doesn't know.
Now, this kid, he's
got a three-year-old daughter.
I know him and I
don't even know you.
Once upon a time.
Eenie, meenie, miney, mo.
Shadow people.
Hey, Mr. Ezekial, take
a look at this place.
These aren't the
coordinates the shaman gave me.
Looks like someone screwed up.
Buzzard?
It's E.
- Yes, sir.
I'm in the air.
Go ahead.
I have another assignment for you.
Burn them down.
- Yes, sir.
Requesting coordinates.
Over.
I thought you could
use a pick me up.
Great.
Thanks, Bonnie.
No problem.
So far we've got, you know,
everything sealed off from here
on down, but I don't know how
we're going to get behind this...
Get him off the control.
Shit.
Holy shit.
Rick?
My god.
How the...
Look.
Get... get it.
Mr. Bauer?
What is that?
I don't think our friends liked
that last bump in the road.
God.
Shit.
Going to need some help here.
My god.
Naomi.
Eat this and that.
Come on.
You want a piece of this?
And that, you want some of this?
You don't want none of this.
Come and get some of this.
Take that and that.
Buzzard, it's E.
Go for Buzzard.
The ocean is out.
Our vitamin bee project has
made an unscheduled U-turn.
Can you drop them somewhere else?
Recommendation, sir?
Somewhere nice and quiet.
How about Negro?
Over.
- Sounds good to me.
Right, sir.
- 10-4.
This is Buzzard out.
I love this job.
That could be them.
Do you ever get the
feeling that we're...
Ann?
I do not like this.
I'm with you.
Come on.
Ideas?
Just got to think.
I have an idea.
Yeah?
Run.
Go, go, go.
Think we lost him.
I think we lost him.
What?
Game over.
This is not good.
Any other bright ideas?
None right now.
I'll let you know.
Hi, fellas.
Is there an Ann Bauer with us?
What the hell was that?
So you're breaking hearts
way out here too?
I'm Ann Bauer.
Ann Bauer, nice to see you when
you're not bleeding to death.
I'm Savior.
Meet the shadow people.
How's everybody doing?
Well, the bathroom
guy's just about gone.
What about you?
I can't even get anybody
to answer me anymore.
It's like we're the
pariah of the sky.
The natives are getting
restless back there.
What do you want me to tell them?
Tell them to screw it.
I can't set her down now because
there's mountains all over.
An hour south of here is farm land.
It should be bumpy, but safe.
I'm setting her down.
OK.
Careful.
You think those are
there to freak me out?
Because if they are, it's working.
Those are Okupis, poison dart frogs.
Poison dart frogs, great.
Their bile is dipped on the tips of
darts, strongest poison in the jungle.
Ann, if that's the strongest
poison in the jungle,
why is she putting
it in drinking jugs?
7165 west, 0079 north.
Got that?
Is it clear?
You'll see us half a click
away from the village.
10-4.
But you're a doctor.
A small and exclusive practice.
This is ridiculous.
I wish you had not come, Ann Bauer.
Well, I didn't have a choice.
You have the serum.
If you don't help us, everyone
on that plane will be dead.
I have greater concerns than that.
Greater concerns?
Much.
I'm trying to save a region
that is being systematically
destroyed by your kind.
Pollution from your factories
is killing our people,
poisoning our river,
driving us from our land.
You're killing us for
your precious oil.
This is one small example
of your government's
policy of sacrificing the
environment for corporate greed.
Savior, I'm on your side.
These are ordinary people.
This isn't about politics.
Blank people,
they're not my concern.
Blank people?
Blank people... blank
in color, blank in honor,
blank in soul, blank.
Savior, please.
My... someone very close
to me is on that plane.
Blank.
No.
He's OK, right?
Come here.
We're going to get out of here.
I promise.
It's OK.
One potato, two
potato, three potato.
All right, boys, make some noise.
Now I must ask you
to go and never return.
Savior, give us the serum.
We'll leave and I swear
we'll never return.
You idiot, you were followed.
Yeah, boss?
We're getting no resistance here.
I think five minutes should do it.
Nothing like
a few well-placed rounds.
Ann Bauer.
Ann, read about you in the paper.
You hurt?
Ann?
Son of a...
Sorry, you were saying?
You're the guy who does the videos?
Who do you think you are?
Are you like a genius or a fool?
This is my business.
Nobody gets to shoot anything or
anybody without my permission.
Kiss my ass.
You know what this is?
It's a gun that can
kill you very quickly.
Raka!
Nice shooting, Pedro.
The hell is going on here, Ezekial?
Thank god.
This man is crazy.
Sorry, we're just
cleaning up the mess.
Scotty.
Just give me a second, Ann.
So this is Savior.
God, I have been looking
forward to meeting you, sir.
All right.
All of them, outside, now.
Why, Scotty?
Reasonable request.
I'll indulge.
Buddy Savior's been a
huge pain in the poo-poo
with these raids on
our oil interests.
Now, with the cross-country
highway going in,
we couldn't have any
more of his shenanigans.
What?
Cross country?
- Ann?
What happened to 100 miles,
separate but protected?
Well, we really couldn't call it
Operation Manifest Destiny now, could we?
Think of the PR.
No, no, no.
That road's going cross country,
sweetheart, all along the Amazon.
Ann, what's going on?
But why?
Ann, do you have any idea the
amount of oil in that region?
More than Texas and Alaska.
We need a protected shipping lane.
We can't have these savages
taking over any time they want.
No, no.
That costs money.
So all this is about
a little bit of money?
No, Ann.
This is about a great deal of money.
$14 billion these low lifes
have cost American businesses.
I think that quite
frankly, enough's enough.
How do the bees come in?
Well, we needed a clean way to
clear the people from our jungle.
So you went au natural?
Right.
We genetically engineered these babies,
breeding only the meanest, the toughest.
And we engineered in a very short
lifespan, only about a week and a half.
They're better than chemical weapons
because they leave no fingerprints.
In fact, they're the
perfect soldiers.
They... they kill
fast, then they die.
You sound like a proud father.
I am.
And I am also very proud of you too.
Really?
Yes, really.
We've been looking for old pale
face and his posse here for some time.
Who'd have thought the chick I was trying
to bang would lead me right to him?
I'd get that foot out
of my head if I were you.
Pity.
Anyway, the only thing
we didn't count on
was your Doctor Daffy taking
home bit of our project as a souvenir.
Which reminds me, what is
the status of that plane?
They're waiting for your word, sir.
Good.
Shoot it down.
Martin, you have to land the plane.
Bitch.
Ann?
Damn it.
Captain, we got a major problem.
Buzzard?
Go for Buzzard.
Shoot that puppy down.
You got to put it down.
And where do you suggest I do that?
How should I know?
I'm not the pilot.
You are.
- We're over mountains.
There's nowhere.
Yeah, well, I don't know about you,
but I'd rather take my chances
with mountains than missile.
Well, maybe you should
fly the goddamn plane.
All right, well, maybe I should.
Hey, guys?
I've been listening.
I got an idea.
Hey.
Am I going to die?
Yes, you are, just not today.
I'm sorry, just tell me again.
Well, it's actually quite simple.
Every plane has an
onboard computer, right?
So?
So the onboard computer
generates a signal so that air
traffic knows where we are.
And this is probably locked
on to that right now.
So you're going to
turn off that signal?
No, I don't think I want to do that.
I'm going to duplicate it, you know,
screw with the missile's mind.
This thing won't let me in.
I got the missile,
100 miles in closing.
Check your gloves, check your boots,
make sure that absolutely
no skin is showing.
Ezekial?
Sir, bees are allergic to me.
Whatever.
Let's do this.
Looking over my shoulder
is definitely not helping.
Goodbye, Ann.
Goodbye, Savior.
Scotty?
There's a little
problem with your plan.
You do know I found an antidote?
Did you now?
Yeah, I did.
It's all around you.
Give me a little hint.
Poison from the Okapi
frog, dart poison.
Bees hate it, won't come near it.
70 miles.
OK, and then...
Now what?
Now we screw with its mind.
Come on, duplicate.
Duplicate.
See, Okapi poison not
only acts as a repellent,
it breaks down the bees' venom
before it can shut down major organs.
Amazing thing is, I found out later,
it also speeds up tissue regrowth.
Gave some to Ann the night
these bastards shot her.
Really helped with her healing.
55 miles.
Keep doing it.
Going as fast as I can.
Now, I want you...
Get the hell off my land.
Look.
It's working.
How far?
40 miles.
30 miles.
Seven miles.
It's going to be close.
Boy, you're ugly.
One mile.
Hang on.
No, no, no, no, no.
Pull it back.
I'm trying.
You got it.
I got it.
- You got it.
Yeah!
Yeah.
It's Ann.
Hey.
Martin?
I don't think I've ever been this
thrilled to hear your voice.
Yeah, well, same here.
We literally dodged a bullet
on that one, thanks to you.
No charge.
Actually, you can pay me back later.
I'll be the one with the serum.
I can't wait.
I love y...
Ann?
Yeah.
How are we supposed to
get this stuff to the plane?
We will walk if we have to.
We're going to try.
Ann.
This is going to save lives, doctor,
human lives, flesh and blood.
You know, a real doctor still
gives a shit about human lives,
blank or not.
You know, flew medivacs
in 'Nam, '68 through '71.
Got over 500 kids out.
If there's a helicopter I can't
fly, I ain't found it yet.
Let's go.
I'm afraid I got some
bad news on my end.
What's happened?
Explosion cracked a line.
We're losing fuel.
Great.
I'm open to ideas, but I think we
have to land, take our chances.
These can't get everybody.
I have an idea.
There you go, just
like riding a bike.
I hope not.
Why?
I always crash my bikes.
You're talking about opening
a door of a plane in flight.
We'll start to drop,
possibly even crash.
Well, not before the
bees are sucked out.
OK.
Who's the idiot who's going
to open the back door?
If he doesn't get stung to death,
he's probably going to get
sucked out with the bees.
Mr. Idiot, at your service.
Shit.
Flight 71.
This is Savior on route
with serum and med supplies.
Say heading and altitude, please.
Over.
- Hello, Savior.
This is flight 71 heading
300 and flight level 125,
approximately three miles
southwest of Lago Dos Pedros.
Over.
Roger that, flight 71.
Should be in position to rendezvous
in approximately seven minutes.
Copy that, Savior.
See you soon.
Why did you and
your husband break up?
Martin always cared more
about himself than anyone else.
And that doesn't make
for a good father.
I never looked at him and
thought, you're my hero.
I need that.
There they are.
Yeah?
Guess what I'm looking at right now.
I got no clue.
The rear end of a plane.
Yeah?
Listen, Ann, I've been thinking.
Now listen to me, OK?
I'm serious.
I think I'm ready.
Ready for what?
You know, you, me, baby makes three,
you know, Sundays at the park,
you know, the whole thing.
Martin.
You know...
You know, weekends at Coney Island.
Martin?
Or you know, sports.
I mean, you don't have any problems with pee wee football, do you?
- Martin?
What?
How about dinner?
No commitments
further than that, OK?
OK.
See you on the ground.
Yeah.
Bye.
We got to do this now.
Make sure you tie yourself
down with anything that you have.
We will be opening the rear door
and it will become very windy.
OK, Rick, I'm all
set and ready to go.
Are you ready?
OK, let's do this thing.
All right.
On three.
One, two, three.
Shit.
Look.
Martin?
Shit.
Mr. Bauer!
Mr. Bauer, grab my hand.
Climb, Martin.
Come on.
Climb, climb.
You're almost there.
Grab my hand.
All right.
Mr. Bauer?
Yeah.
Adam, you are beautiful.
All passengers, take your seats now.
Interlace your fingers behind your neck
and put your head between your knees.
This is going to be
a very bumpy landing.
You did it, you son of a bitch.
Rick?
Please take your seat.
My god.
OK, if you're going to sit
up here, you got to work.
No problem.
Just got to tell me what to do.
What's our altitude?
Where?
Dial in the center.
Just under 2,000 feet.
Now, lower the landing gear.
Where?
Lever by your left knee.
Yeah.
That's it.
Done.
They're landing, Savior.
They're landing.
Rick?
Rick!
Pull back on the throttle,
lever in the center.
Easy, easy.
OK, sorry.
It's my first time.
OK.
- How's that?
That's great.
When we hit the ground, you push
that lever by your left foot
down with all your might.
You got it.
Hold on.
Get ready.
It's going to be a rough one.
My god, we're alive.
We made it.
My god, we made it.
Yeah!
There we go, little one.
Yeah.
Feels pretty good, doc?
Yeah, blank or not.
Hey.
Raka, this is Martin Bauer.
This is my husband.
The hero.
All right, bee stings.
Sure, yeah.
What do you say we get out of here?
Fabulous idea.
Was that it?
Is what it?
Is that how you treat a woman?
That's it.
So that's how you treat a woman.
Thanks, Mr. B.