Vinnie, you promised.
Just trying to make it
through the day, baby.
Where did you get that?
Don't worry about it.
Don't worry about it?
That's all I do
is worry about it.
I mean, do you think
they're just going to keep
fronting you without payment?
It's cool.
My credit's good.
Oh, oh, and that's supposed
to make me feel better, huh?
I mean this shit will kill you!
You crazy?
That's $200 worth you
just threw on the floor.
Why should I
worry about it, huh?
Your credit's good.
Yeah, go on.
Get up there.
Stay outa my face!
How you doing?
I missed you yesterday.
Yeah.
I'm real sorry about that
but I was just getting
ready to come by and see you.
I guess I saved you a trip.
According to my
calculations, we seem to be
missing a kilo of cocaine.
Now, how do you suppose
that bag got away?
Huh?
Any ideas?
I don't know, But.
I swear to God.
Perhaps I can
refresh your memory.
Wait.
Don't.
I took it.
I'm sorry, man.
I swear on my father.
I was just going to come
by and pay you for it.
So where's my money?
Well, that's what I was going
to come and talk to you about.
Oh, Vinnie, Vinnie, Vinnie.
No, no, no.
I can get it.
I just got to make some
collections, you know?
It's like singing the
same old song on the charts.
Going all the way up to
number one with a bullet.
No, Blade. please.
Go ahead.
Take it.
It's worth way more
than I owe you.
A lucky horseshoe, Ray.
Please.
Vinnie, I'm touched.
Chico, am I a pawnbroker?
No.
Do I look like a pawnbroker?
I am not a pawnbroker.
And you know what?
It's only lucky, if you
were on the right side.
You had it upside down
and that's bad luck.
Get her.
Now, you see, Vinnie?
That's the way you're
supposed to wear it.
That's good luck.
See it?
Ah, perfect fit.
I'm not interested.
Yeah.
I know what I said.
But I changed my mind.
Look, I don't want it.
All right?
And do me a favor, huh?
Why don't you just stop
calling me, all Right
Hey, Mario, you having
ex-girlfriend problems?
No, no.
Long distance carrier.
Shit.
Got some new
talent, hey, Mario?
Business must be good.
Look I told your boy.
I can't be paying you
protection money no more.
You get my message?
Yeah.
I got the message.
That's what I'm doing here.
Show you what might
happen in case
you don't make my payments.
Boys.
Hey, what are you doing?
Get outa here.
Guys go.
Cut it out.
Tell them to cut it out.
Maybe this will
show you the value
of a good protection agency.
Hey, cut it out.
Ho.
What say you come
down here, cowgirl?
Ride my fucking bronco?
Oh.
Hey, Mario, what's happening?
Wow.
Nobody move.
What took you so long?
You know me, I have
to have my coffee.
Officer Palermo, I
got one thing to say,
thank you very much.
Oh, no, don't mention it.
You think later
on you and I could
catch a cup of coffee, huh?
You know, I still
have a few bullets left.
Coffee?
I wasn't needed.
I wasn't needed here.
Woo, hoo!
Well, if it isn't
the queen of the rodeo.
Oh, back off, Fredericks.
Well, how would you like
to come back to my office
and let me shoot you
with my love gun, honey.
Thanks, but you know what?
I heard that you
might be low on ammo.
That's pretty funny.
All right.
OK, look.
The captain wants to see you.
Great.
Do you mind covering
while I go change?
Sure.
But you might want to
keep that outfit on,
especially if he brings up that
raise you've been asking for.
That's not even funny.
It's not funny.
It's just a thought.
Listen, you're gonna go
and you're gonna wear this.
What the hell's going on?
Sir.
Palermo, what is
with that get up?
It's the undercover
bust at Wiggles, sir.
Oh, yeah, congratulations.
Thanks.
Need to see you in my office.
Yes, sir.
May I please go change first?
Yeah, go ahead.
Oh, and Palermo.
Yes, sir?
Y'all hurry back to
my office now, pardner.
Hey, Stace.
Got the word you
had a tough day.
You kidding me?
I danced for less
than 30 minutes.
Made over $100.
You're joking.
What's the name of this dive?
Maybe I should do a
little moonlighting.
Now you would make a fortune.
Unfortunately, it's
all in very sweaty ones.
Ick.
Got the picture.
You splitting that with Zig?
No way.
It was my butt on the line.
He didn't even show up until
after everything went down.
Zig knew you could
handle it, that's all.
Besides, I heard
he told Dietrich
that he was going to stand
by outside to cover you.
Really?
He didn't want to
embarrass you, that's all.
How long you
guys been partners?
A little over two years.
And in all that
time he never...
No, no, no, no.
Not that he didn't
try anything, but no.
So what's the problem?
He's kind of cute, earns a
decent pay, and he's straight.
What could possibly go wrong?
Plenty.
If it doesn't
work out, you just
get the captain to
reassign him to Vice
and I'll take good care of him.
Jody.
You are something else.
Believe me, I know
what I'm talking about.
I had nothing to do with that.
Yeah, right.
Come on, I'm your partner.
All right.
I'll make it up to you.
Dinner on me tonight at Zord's.
You're on.
I am?
Yeah, you are.
Hey, Stace.
You really do have
a nice pair of legs.
What's that?
About the size of yours.
Real nice.
That'll be all.
Right, Captain.
Detective Palermo,
this is Lisa Wilkes.
Stacey, call me Stacey.
Ms. Wilkes arrived
home from work
this afternoon to find out her
boyfriend had been murdered.
Oh, I'm sorry.
She walked all the way
here because her phone
has been disconnected.
Look, I think
homicide;s about done.
I was hoping maybe you
could take her home.
Sure, sure.
That's not a problem.
Do you want to go?
OK, yeah.
OK, I'll be out
in a minute then.
Thanks.
Why do you want me
to do the babysitting?
I've got a ton of
paperwork to do.
Cause I think you
can get her to open up.
She knows more than
she's letting on,
and I hate to admit
it, you're probably
the best damn detective
this precinct has.
I do believe that was
a compliment, Captain.
Yeah.
You know, if it wasn't
for that god awful tie,
you wouldn't be half bad.
I love this tie.
Lisa, let's get going.
Stace, what's up?
Ziggy.
Oh, god, could you
book those boys for me?
I have to run an errand.
Sure.
What about dinner?
Oh, god.
I'll call you.
Sorry.
They're here.
No sweat.
Norris and Bach
are on their way.
Don't you have a
sheet or something
you can cover him up with?
They took his ring.
The bastard shot him and
they took his ring anyway.
It's only thing that ever
meant anything to him.
Oh, my god.
- Oh, no.
- What?
What is it?
It's a death notice for me.
No, it's not for you.
Look, they do that
to scare people.
I got to get out of here.
I can't stay here.
OK.
Do you have anybody
you can stay with?
No.
I don't know.
Can't we just get out of here?
Lisa.
That's them.
Take them out.
You all right?
You want to go somewhere,
stop somewhere?
No.
Look, it's OK.
Nobody's going to hurt you.
Get real.
Give you my word on that.
That's supposed to
make me feel better.
I know what you're
going through.
You don't know shit.
You're just a damn cop.
There is a huge difference
between your world and mine.
You only write the reports.
I live them.
But you wouldn't know
anything about that.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
See that?
I wouldn't know
anything about that.
That was because I didn't
have dinner ready on time.
I've been there, Lisa.
I'm sorry.
Isn't there anywhere
I can take you?
No, not really.
A relative?
My folks live in Pennsylvania
and I haven't spoken to them
in years.
So you don't have any friends?
No.
My friends won't
even talk to me.
Vinny was real trouble.
It wasn't his fault. It
was just his habit and all.
It must've been tough.
I stood by his side and you
gotta give me credit for that.
I loved him.
God.
God dammit!
And those bastards just killed
him like he was some animal.
It's all right.
Just let it out.
Oh, god.
Lisa, get down.
Get down!
Stay down!
Stacy!
You all right?
No, I'm not all right.
They just tried to kill me and
you know they'll try again.
Come on.
Where are we going?
Someplace where
you'll be safe.
Come on, let's go!
This better to be good.
Captain?
Nichols, I told you
never to use his phone
unless it's an emergency.
Sorry, Captain, I
tried normal channels,
but I couldn't get through.
I thought you'd like
to know what happened.
Oh, let me guess.
You're putting in
for early retirement.
No, but Palermo might be.
Why so?
Two punks took a dry dive
off the Fifth Street Bridge.
Seems they were chased
through downtown by Palermo,
shots were fired.
Let me speak to her.
No can do.
According to
witnesses, she took off
in that clunker of hers
right after the accident.
Classic.
Nothing, she calls that
old heap of junk a classic.
Belonged to her old man
before he left the force.
Listen, where the
hell is she at?
Probably in hiding.
Word on the street is
there's a big payday waiting
for anybody who
can put the finger
on Vinnie Mateo's girlfriend.
All right, Nichols,
stay on it, will you?
- You bet.
- Thanks.
Food here is pretty bad.
But you'll feel a lot
safer, believe me.
Yes, Rita.
Well, I hate to
bring everyone down,
but I talked to my psychic
pal last night and...
Oh, brother, here we go.
Quiet, Tony.
Hey, hey, hey, that's enough.
Just let her talk.
Go ahead, Rita.
Anyway, she said something
bad was going to happen
in the next couple of days.
Yeah, you're going
to get your phone bill.
I can't believe you
actually fall for that shit.
You're so gullible.
Don't even go there.
At least I'm not sitting around
waiting for collect calls
from my jailed boyfriend.
Are you due for
a tranquilizer?
Oh, cat fight, cat fight.
Uh, oh.
Anybody home?
Stacey.
Hey, sis.
So good to see you.
It's about time you
came out for a visit.
Hey everybody this
is my sister, Stacey.
Or should I say
Detective Palermo.
Stacey, the gang.
Hi, everybody.
Could I please talk
to you for a second?
Oh, yes, sure OK.
Smoke them if you got them.
I'll be a few minutes.
Come on this way.
You know you missed our
fundraiser the other day.
Oh god, I know.
I'm sorry.
Put me down for a C note.
I'm good for it.
You bet I will.
So, what can I do for you.
Cindy this is Lisa.
Hi.
Lisa needs a safe place
to stay for a while.
Well, we're just getting
the place in order,
but I'm sure we
can make some room.
- Thanks.
- Sure.
Can I use your phone?
Yeah, go ahead.
I'll just go wrap up
the meeting and then
we'll get Lisa settled.
And you are staying for dinner.
I won't take no for an answer.
Make yourself at home.
Thanks.
She's really nice.
That's my sister.
Uh, Were you baptized Bambi?
Is that the name on
your birth certificate?
No, I was named
after the movie.
I see.
Ziggy, it's me.
Palermo, where
the hell are you?
I'm over at my
sister's shelter.
We got caught in a drive by.
- Are you OK?
- Yeah, we're fine.
Lisa just needs a safe
place to stay for a while.
Yeah, the captain
filled me in.
You think she knows anything?
I'd say so.
All right.
Listen, I got it.
What about dinner?
I'll have to
take a rain check.
No problem.
Something's come up here anyway.
Anything important?
- Nothing I can't handle.
- OK.
Then I'll call you
before I leave here.
I'll see you.
Miss Bambi, would you like to
join me in a culinary delight?
Lieutenant, I'm not
that kind of girl.
I meant dinner.
Oh super.
Yeah.
OK.
Put the word
out on the street.
I want this bitch found
and I want her dead.
And I don't care what it takes.
If she fingers us, they're going
to lock our asses up in jail
and throw away the key.
Get your fucking
feet off my desk.
Hold on.
Yeah.
Boss.
They got Paco and Torrez.
Shit.
But I followed them to an
old house on Route Seven.
It's easy to get into.
We'll take them down.
- Just get the hell out here.
- All right.
Good work, Chico.
Be right over.
Saddle up, boys.
Pay back time.
Look, I can't help you
if you don't help me.
If you saw somebody or
someone, you've got to tell me.
Hey, why don't you two
come out meet the girls.
All right, let's go
get you settled in.
We all pitch in and work
as a team around here.
Makes everybody feel
needed and important.
This is Sammy Jo.
She comes to us all
the way from Quebec.
Hi, Sammy Jo.
What's with her?
Don't take offense.
She's been through a lot.
About two months
ago, they found her
in an alley completely naked,
gagged, beaten left for dead.
She hasn't spoken a word since.
Jesus, that's so sad.
Yeah.
And of course, they never
found the guy who did it.
Oh, and here's Charisse with
some of her famous biscuits.
Hey, looks like I'm going to
have to fix two more plates.
You look like you could
use a good meal, huh girl?
I am kind of hungry.
Well, sit on down girl.
Eat as much as you want.
We're going to put some meat
on that little ass of yours.
Charisse.
Are you the cook?
No, I'm not the cook.
I'm just the same as
anyone else here, homeless.
OK?
How did you wind up here?
Let's see, a broken
collarbone, fractured skull,
dislocated shoulder.
God, he did that to you?
To me?
No, honey, it's
what I did to him.
See, I got tired of him
putting his hands on me.
So I wanted till
we went to bed one
night and beat his mother
fucking ass with a frying pan.
Hey, you got to look
out for number one.
Rita, come on in.
Rita, this is Lisa
and my sister, Stacey.
Hi.
Thanks, honey.
She can be very emotionally
unstable at times.
She spent the last
three years in prison
for murdering her
abusive husband.
But we're trying
to find some way
to ease her back into some
kind of normal existence.
Oh, and here's Helen.
Hello.
Hi.
Watch what you say.
The place is bugged.
She's a paranoid
schizophrenic.
What?
She thinks that government
agents are out to kill her.
Oh, and last but
not least, Toni.
Toni, this is Lisa
and my sister, Stacey.
We've met.
I was going to say you look
familiar, but I can't remember.
You busted my boyfriend.
Johnny Cotello.
And thanks to you, I'm
stuck living in this shithole.
Toni.
Well, it ain't the Waldorf.
Look, one day you're
going to thank me for doing
you a really big favor.
A favor?
My boyfriend is in
jail because of you.
Well, jail is exactly
where he belongs.
Stacey.
You know, I swear
to God if I could
put a bullet through your
fucking skull I would.
Hey, that's
enough, both of you.
I don't care if she's
your sister or not, OK.?
Don't expect me to lay
out the welcome mat.
I'm not hungry.
I'm sorry.
It's OK.
What kind of place
did you get me into?
Would you rather go
back to your apartment?
Listen, you guys make
yourselves at home.
I'm going to go
get Dan and Mike.
Dan and Mike?
The maintenance guys.
This place would fall
apart without them.
Hey, guys.
Dinner's on the table.
All right.
Coming in.
Well, hurry.
It'll get cold.
Come on, Dan.
Charisse made biscuits.
Dan?
Dan!
Oh my god.
He's shot!
Mike!
Dan!
Get him inside.
Get him inside!
Get down!
Stay on the floor!
Stacey.
Stay down.
Where's she going?
Shoot the motherfuckers.
Shoot, girl.
What the hell is going on here?
This is worse than
my old neighborhood.
Just stay down.
Did you call for help?
The phone's dead.
Great.
What are we supposed to do now?
Well, they stopped.
Maybe they're gone.
Cindy, I don't think there's
a chance that they're gone.
Everybody just stay calm.
Oh, shit, guys.
They're back.
Stay where you are.
That's him!
Everybody OK?
Sammy Jo?
Sammy Jo, it's me.
It's Cindy.
It's OK.
Sammy Jo!
It's OK!
That's a good girl.
Is she all right?
I hope so.
Say one for me too, honey.
So, supercop, what
do these guys want?
How the hell should I know?
None of this shit
started till you got here.
You think it's my fault?
Well, it ain't mine.
It's the government.
It's them.
They found me.
Helen, we've been
through this before.
The government is not after you.
How do you know that?
Who are they then?
What do they want?
Maybe they want the money.
I have over $5,000 in cash
upstairs from the fundraiser.
I never made it to the bank.
No, if it was money, they
would have asked for it.
It's my fault.
What they want with you, girl?
What difference does it make?
She put us all in danger.
Helen.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
What do you got
that they all want?
They want me.
That's ridiculous.
My boyfriend.
They killed him and I
saw the whole thing.
Oh, great.
She has to leave.
You've got to go.
They'll kill her.
They're going to kill us.
No one is going anywhere.
She's going to
get us all killed.
Look, maybe somebody heard
the gunshots and called it in.
I don't know, Stacey.
The nearest place is
two miles down the road.
It's not that far.
They could have still
heard the shots.
Yeah, did she mention
it's a firing range?
Great.
Well, the nearest
police station...
Is 10 miles away.
Shit.
Cindy, maybe you were right.
I don't see anybody.
OK.
Let's not do anything rash.
Let's just sit tight and wait.
Wait for what?
For them to come back
here and blow us all away?
I agree with her.
She's putting us
all in jeopardy.
We don't even know this girl.
...please
take a chill pill.
You know what I think?
I think you should take your
little friend over there
and you both should get
the hell out of here.
We're not running a
witness protection program.
And do you know what I say?
No one is going anywhere.
This girl came to us for
shelter and she's going to get
it, just like I gave it to you.
You got that?
I didn't bring the
Wild Bunch with me.
Look, she's right.
I'm going to go.
I'm putting you all in danger.
See, even she agrees.
Lisa, I promise
you I'd protect you.
I'm not going to
go back on my word.
That's right, honey.
You're under our roof now and
we take care of each other here.
See, that's right
we're all a team.
Las mujeres.
- Isn't that right, Cindy?
- Yes, Rita.
That's right.
We are a team.
How you doing on ammo?
Six shots.
That is not a lot.
OK, listen up.
I've got an idea.
I've got two shotguns in the
back of my car in the trunk.
If you can distract them
somehow, I can run out there
get the shotguns,
radio in for help.
All right, that's good.
Give me the keys.
I'll go get them.
Forget it.
I can't ask you to do that.
You're not asking me.
OK, I'm telling you.
I'm not risking any civilians.
Palermo.
Palermo!
She's still on the road, boss.
But I'm sure she heard you.
Don't be a wise ass.
Sagowski just spoke
to a vagrant who
said Lisa Wilkes
was already home
when her boyfriend got hit.
You think she saw anything?
That's what I'm
trying to find out.
See if you can track
her down, will you?
Oh yeah sure, boss.
Good.
Stace, don't you
think if someone
would have called
the police, they
would have been here by now?
Definitely.
I don't know what's going on.
You say you've got a
radio in that car, right?
Forget it.
No, I'm not
going to forget it.
Look, don't even
think about it.
It's my responsibility.
I'm trained for
dangerous situations.
Besides, you're
working here as a...
As a what?
As a maintenance man, is that
what you were going to say?
Look let me explain
something to you.
All right guys, this
is not helping any.
And Mike, as much as I hate
the idea, she is right.
No, Cindy, she's not right.
It's suicide and you know it.
What do you suggest?
We have to create a diversion.
We've got to try to
drama away from the car.
You got any ideas?
Well, I got some
bottles downstairs
and I got some turpentine.
Let's make some
Molotov cocktails.
I've got rags in the kitchen.
Let's go.
All right, guys,
I'll be right back.
Stacey.
I don't know how you do this.
God, I just really wish
I had your strength.
Where do you
think I got it from?
Love you.
What do you mean
the lines are down?
Will you just try it again?
All right, all right.
Thank you.
Freddy.
Yeah.
Keep trying to get
Stacey on the radio.
I'm going to try
to find her now.
You got it.
We could use a couple more.
Great.
Just throw them when
you hear me yell.
Oh, yes, ma'am.
This isn't the
time for sarcasm.
All I'm saying is I
should be the one going.
OK?
I'm not discussing it.
Hey.
Be careful.
I will.
Still no sign of them.
All right.
Just yell as loud as
you can to see if you
see any kind of movement.
All right.
Stacey, please
don't do this for me.
I'm doing this for all of us.
Hey, good luck, Sis.
Vaya con Dios.
Now!
Go!
Dispatch.
Shit!
Where'd you get that?
Sometimes it just
pays to break the rules.
They're never
going to make it.
I don't know why you said...
She's going to make it.
What are you looking at?
Nothing.
Thanks.
Jesus.
God, Helen.
She OK?
Helen?
She's dead.
Cindy, I'm so sorry.
Lisa.
Where's Lisa?
Lisa!
In here!
Everybody stay down.
- Somebody get some bandages.
- Yeah, I'm on it.
I'll cover the door.
Did you get through?
I got the guns
and ammo, no radio.
- Let's get you out of here.
- Let's go.
Make some room.
Wait a minute.
No.
How can anybody live out here?
Got coyotes up your
ass, everything.
Where the hell are you, Stace?
Come on.
How's that feeling?
Oh, it's, it's fine.
Don't think I'll be playing
softball for a while.
What position do you play?
What position do I play?
After all it's happened, you
still manage to muster up
some small talk, huh?
Helps pass the time, I guess.
Shortstop.
First base, that's what I
play, female officers league.
Really?
Yeah.
I like first base.
It's an important position.
Should come by the
ball park some time.
I'd like that but, you know
I'm just a uh maintenance man.
Hey, I'm sorry about that.
I apologize.
Thank God.
Someone's coming.
It's a cop.
Well, never thought I'd be
glad to see one of those guys.
It's my partner.
Ziggy, look out!
You bastards!
Fuck you!
Sorry, Stacey.
No!
Sorry.
This is war, gentlemen.
They killed Juan.
I want them dead.
Screw the cops.
Chico, you call in
for extra troops.
They mess with us, we'll give
them a goddamn bloodbath.
Looks like they're getting
ready for another attack.
How many do you think?
It's hard to tell.
I'd say a few dozen though.
Gotta do something.
I say we barricade
ourselves in.
Look, we don't have
much of a choice.
OK.
Let's do it.
All right, guys, listen up.
We're going to do our best
to barricade ourselves in.
Downstairs I've got
lumber and tools.
Let's go down there and
start bringing it up.
Also grab anything that
can be used as a weapon.
They may be making a charge.
OK.
Now one last thing.
I can handle that pistol if
you're going to use a shotgun.
OK.
Here.
Any units in the vicinity
of Park and Lincoln,
reports of gun fire.
Please respond.
Unit nine to base.
We're on our way.
Ten-four unit nine.
Come on, Sammy.
Here, take that.
Move.
OK.
Come on, Sammy Jo, this way.
Got some more for you.
That should hold.
Any more downstairs?
Yeah, do you want
me to go get it?
Yeah, hurry.
Thanks.
Don't shoot.
Scared the shit out of me.
Just thought I'd
come down and help.
It's OK.
I got it.
So why did you do it?
Do what?
Risk your life to save mine.
It was no big deal.
No big deal.
You could have gotten
yourself killed.
But I didn't.
You didn't, so let's
just leave it at that.
OK.
Look, I'm really
sorry about Johnny.
Never meant to hurt you.
I was only doing my job.
I wish there some way we
could bury the hatchet.
OK.
Well, I guess I can't blame
you for hating me then.
I don't hate you.
I knew what was going on all
along and I let it happen.
You know, I kept asking
myself over and over
again, what's your limit?
I mean when is it
really enough, you know?
But the truth of the
matter is, I didn't
have the strength to walk away.
Toni, don't blame yourself.
I blamed everyone
else for the past year.
I think it's time
I face the facts.
You made a mistake.
You're only human.
We've all got our
war stories to tell.
Now, it's just time to let
it go, start over again.
It's easier said than done.
I did it.
So can you.
If you only let your guard
down for a split second,
you realize there are people
around who care about you.
I'm one of them.
I'd love to help, if
you'd only let me.
This is getting heavy.
So what do you say?
OK.
What do you want us to do
with the rest of this wood?
Arm yourselves.
Just in case.
They some near me, I'll
slice their conjones.
I don't have any 357 ammo.
Already got it covered.
I had some stashed in the back.
Toni, hey.
Bet you're glad I
got it now, aren't you?
All right, guys, listen up.
Here's what we're going to do.
Hey, who put you in charge?
You think just because
you're the hombre,
that makes you the boss?
Rita, we are a team here.
Let's hear what he has to say.
If you say so, OK, Cindy.
Yes, Rita, I say so.
Go ahead, Mike.
Thanks.
Everybody's got a weapon, right?
Good.
Because I think you're
going to need it.
Guys, from what I can
tell, it looks to me
like they're planning a charge.
So I say we break into pairs,
each of us take a room.
If they start to break through,
do your best to hold them off.
If you have trouble,
yell it out.
Any objections?
No.
All right.
Let's do it.
Sounds like you know
what you're doing.
Had a little experience.
What kind of experience?
Marines.
Why didn't you
tell me that before?
I sort of tried to,
but you wouldn't let me.
Sorry.
So what brought you
here from the Marines?
My little sister
used to be here.
She used to live here
while I was overseas.
But she got into
a lot of trouble
and sort of fell in
with the wrong crowd,
if you know what I mean.
Your sister Cindy was the only
one that would help her out.
She's terrific, your sister.
Yeah, I know.
Well, when I got
back from overseas,
I came back here
looking for her.
We were going to
move up to Oregon.
Figured it would be
good for her and figured
it would be good for me.
She's the only
family I have left.
When I got back here Cindy
told me that she had run off.
I went looking for her but
I didn't have much luck.
I came back here.
I stayed, hoping that
she would come back too.
She knew you were
here, she'd be back.
Listen, everybody's set.
It's been quiet.
Do you think they left?
I don't think so.
I think they're
just waiting us out.
Oh, shit.
I can't believe no one
has called the police.
Unit nine to base.
Go ahead, Unit nine.
No sign of any activity.
Everything's pretty quiet.
10-4.
Give it the once
around one more time.
10-4.
One more time.
Hey, I just want to say
that I'm sorry about all this.
I feel like this
is all my fault.
It's not your fault.
But it is my fault.
I mean, if I had just
been honest with the police
from the start none of this
would have never happened.
I was just so scared.
Lisa, everybody gets scared.
Yeah well I've
caused so much trouble
and I feel so responsible.
I know but you
are not to blame.
Look, you just have to
accept that what's done is done
and move on.
I know it isn't easy
but we're here for you,
and when all this is over.
You mean if we make
it out of here alive.
No.
I mean when all this is over.
I hope you decide
to stay on with us.
You really mean that?
Yeah, Lisa, I really mean it.
I see great things in you.
That's the first time anyone
has ever said that to me.
Captain.
You find them?
Line is dead.
Disconnected?
No, the phone
company says they're
having a problem in the area.
Send over a squad car.
Sure thing, Captain.
Got one right near there,
checking on a report of...
Now!
Right, Captain.
Just pray, Sammy Jo.
God will see us through this.
Pray for me too.
Quiet as a graveyard.
Yeah, pretty dead.
Let's get something to eat.
Gurdy, you're always eating.
Take a left at the next corner,
the best coffee shop in town
is about a mile down.
Hey, wait a minute.
Looks like we got some activity.
I don't like the looks of this.
Call the Sarge.
Get him to contact
the phone company.
Penny.
Come here and check this out.
Base to Unit nine.
Come in.
Come in, Unit nine.
Man, are you as
hungry as I am?
Was kind of looking
forward to those biscuits.
Yeah, well if these guys don't
kill us, those biscuits will.
Come in, Unit nine.
Damn.
Unit 12?
Come in, Unit 12.
This wait is going
to drive me nuts.
Girl, you already nuts.
You should talk.
You're the craziest
bitch I know.
Honey, I spent
my whole life going
in and out of bad situations.
If I didn't laugh
it off, I think
I'd just shrivel up and die.
I hear you.
Yeah, my mama always told
me, things are looking bad,
just be thankful
they ain't worse.
Yeah, well.
they can't get much
worse than this.
You got that right.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Got something funny going on.
I am not in a laughing mood.
Did you find them?
That's just it.
I've already sent
tow cars to the area
and I can't get either
one on the radio.
Damn it.
If that is pulling
another practical joke,
I swear I...
I don't think so.
I've checked with
the phone company.
They can't find their
repair team either.
- What are you telling me?
- I don't know.
It's like the whole neighborhood
just turned into the Bermuda
Triangle or something.
Fredericks, do I have
to go down there myself?
I'll send another unit.
And send them
straight to the shelter.
And make sure they stay
in constant radio contact.
Right.
I just wanted you to know.
Bermuda freaking triangle.
What are you thinking?
I think your hunch was right.
They're just waiting us out.
Look.
Cindy, it's the police!
Oh, my god.
Thank God you're here.
No, get down!
Oh, my god, no!
Everybody, back
to their posts.
Hey, Chico, we got company.
Oh, shit, stay back.
Stay back.
Cover the windows.
Here, take this.
Go!
Get down!
We did it!
We kicked their ass.
Thank god.
They just gave up.
Yeah, right.
They're not going to stop
till they get what they want.
We're not going
to die in here.
Rita, back off.
No.
She's the one that they want.
Why don't you just
let them have her?
We're not all going to suffer.
You never cease to amaze me.
Don't pay her no mind.
She's just tripping as usual.
Guys, come on.
We're not out of this yet.
We're got to get these
windows boarded back up.
Forget the windows.
We got to make
some kind of move.
How much longer do you think
we can all hold them off?
As long as it takes.
There's no way we're getting out
of here without being detected.
Why don't we just
blow the place up then?
Girl, have you lost your mind?
You got a better idea?
Wait a minute.
Toni, what are you thinking?
OK, look, if we can
lure them in somehow,
we could trap them inside and
blow the place up with gas.
How?
Turn on all the gas
jets in the kitchen,
throw a can in the microwave.
And how do we get out?
Once they're inside,
we go downstairs, and get
out the doors to the basement.
Stace, what do you think?
Well...
I got to tell you, this is not
the best idea I've ever heard.
Well, unless someone's
got a better one,
I really don't see we
have much of a choice.
Anybody?
All right, that settles it.
Let's just do it.
Captain.
What is it now, Fredericks?
Alien abduction?
Worse.
I got a couple reports from the
47th precinct about gangbangers
cruising around,
gunfire in the area.
Still no word from
any of our units.
Sagowski or Palermo.
Shit.
Wait a minute.
This graffiti.
It's gang death notice.
They found out where
Lisa Wilkes is.
Alert the SWAT team.
Get every available
unit down there now.
Call the neighboring precincts.
We need backup.
Go!
Lisa, get the tape.
Come on, Trace, you're
making a meal out of it.
One more and
we'll call it a day.
Got it.
All right, listen up.
Guys come back here licking
your wounds like you went
up against some major people.
They're just a bunch
of bitches, man.
Here, take this.
You think this
is going to work?
It better.
- Body's in the roof.
- The house is all set.
We need to get
into the basement.
Let's go.
Let me finish up.
I'll be right there.
All right.
Girls, move.
All right, you listen to me.
You make this quick.
This place is ready to go.
Go, go go.
Move, Move, move.
Come on!
Where's Stacey?
I don't know!
Now what we're
going to do is we're
going to storm this place.
And we're going to do it
before the god damn cops
get here with their army.
Where's Stacey?
She's coming.
Move.
All right.
Everybody all right?
- Yeah.
- All right.
Sit tight.
And you ought to be
ashamed of yourselves.
Because I know I am.
So do it right this time.
Shit.
They've got Chico.
I want everybody
in that house dead.
When Stacey gets here,
we'll blow this hole
and get out of here.
Shit.
Where's she going?
I gotta get something.
No, forget it.
It's too late.
I can't wait.
Cindy.
Cindy!
There's Stacey.
What is she waiting for?
Come on!
Let's go.
Shit!
It's locked.
Locked?
What do you mean locked?
I never locked it
from the outside.
Come on!
Come on, follow me.
Come on, come on, let's go.
Rita, come on, you first.
Good girl.
Come on, come on, come on!
Come on, you're next.
You get your tired ass up
there before..
Come on!
How you doing?
That's enough.
Come on, let's go.
Move, Move.
Sammy Jo, please.
We gotta go.
Come on.
Leave them alone!
Where are they?
I'm not telling you shit.
Ah.
Come on, come on.
Where's Stacey?
There's no time.
Get down, everybody.
Get down now.
This could be next.
Oh, god, there's
not enough time.
Get the door.
Mike?
Stacey?
Stacey!
Come on!
Move!
Come on.
Cindy!
Get out the door.
Out the door.
Stacey.
Stacey, what...
Drop all your
weapons, or I'm going
to blow her fucking brains out.
And I'm going to
do it in such a way
that I won't even get a
speck of blood on my clothes.
What was that?
Jesus.
my
God.
Oh.
You OK?
Yeah.
Palermo, what the
hell is going on?
We've got everything
under control, sir.
All right?
Yeah, thanks.
Good.
Let's clean this mess up.
Sweet Jesus.
What are we going to do now?
Well, I suggest we start
looking for a new place.
You know what?
Might be a little crowded,
but until you guys find a place,
why don't you guys
just stay with me?
OK.
Even me?
Especially you, Toni.
That's right.
It's time to start over.
Hey.
What?
What on earth was so important
for you to go all the way
back upstairs like you did?
Fundraiser money.
I worked too hard for this.
And hey, it certainly came
in handy, don't you think?
Maybe.
Oh, just leave me
out of it, girls.
How you doing?
I'm good.
how you doing?
Everybody is coming over to
stay at my place for a while
until they get resettled.
I was thinking I could make some
room for you, if you'd like.
Aren't you afraid
I might get on base.
Come here.