[mysterious music]
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
[Dee] Well, at
first, his letters
and phone calls were adoring,
but when I didn't
return the affection,
the letters and the calls
became threatening, violent.
Long before he
started stalking me,
he went after my best
friend, Deborah Voorhees
from "Friday the
13th" franchise.
Deborah and I met when [laughs]
we were both starting
out in Hollywood.
You know, once you get
well-known in Hollywood,
the friends you knew
before you made it
are the only ones
you really trust.
To my shame, I didn't
believe Deborah.
I thought she was just paranoid.
Fans can say creepy things.
It doesn't mean they
really want to hurt you.
I was sure that the stalker
was just an obsessed fan.
No one dangerous.
[tense music]
Karma's a bitch.
[engine roaring]
Can you make sure to
give them extra hay?
[horn honking]
How are you guys doing?
[Woman] We're
doing pretty good.
Grandma!
Oh, hey, sweetie!
How are you?
Good.
All right guys, have fun.
Keep Grandma out of trouble.
Hey, Kelsie.
- Wanna go for a ride?
- Yes.
You have to help me
get some kindling first
- for tonight, okay?
- Okay.
I love you more than
chocolate chip cookies, Grandma.
I love you more than peach
pie and homemade ice cream.
Sounds delicious.
Come on.
Help me carry this in.
We might've packed
this one too heavy.
Try.
All right.
Here we go.
[Kelsie] Birdie, come on.
All right.
I'm gonna go get
the water bottle.
- I'll be right back.
- Okay.
I'll race ya.
Birdie!
Birdie?
Probably found a rabbit.
Oh, I bet she did.
She'll catch up to us, though.
She will.
When's Grandpa gonna be home?
Not until tomorrow morning.
- You wanna talk to him?
- Yeah.
[tense music]
[camera shutter clicks]
[text message dings]
[suspenseful music]
[Deborah mumbling]
Come on, come on.
- Let's go.
- What about Grandpa?
[Deborah mumbling]
[water splashing]
Hey sweetie.
[dramatic music]
[tense music]
Come on, we need to hurry.
Stay right here with me.
Do not leave my side.
No, no flashlight.
We don't want any lights.
Come on.
Come on, stay right with me.
Come on, hurry.
[dramatic music]
[horse neighing]
[suspenseful music]
[Man] Tina!
I promise you I'll be back.
I don't want to.
I'm scared.
Get inside.
Come on.
[tense music]
Be very, very quiet.
Do not come out
until I come for you.
[suspenseful music]
Gran, no!
[Man] Tina!
Where are you,
you son of a bitch!
Where are you!
[Man] Tina!
I'm gonna kill you,
you motherfucker!
[suspenseful music]
[Man] Tina!
[gunshot bangs]
Tina.
[Deborah shouting]
[Deborah crying]
You were always my favorite.
Why did you ignore me?
[dramatic music]
[girl screaming]
[siren wailing]
All right, do it
a couple of times.
Okay, all right.
Looks good, guys.
All right, so just
in a few moves,
you can defend yourself
from a much bigger attacker.
My much bigger
attacker, right here.
You ready?
All right, guys, we're gonna
work on that next week.
[class applauding]
Bye.
Bye, Wesley, I'll
see you tomorrow?
[text messages dinging]
Hi, baby.
Just wanted to call and tell
you I'm thinking about you.
Kind of a hard day
for both of us.
Still wake up and remember
that she's not here.
Expect her to call me
for lunch or a drink
or to brag on you.
13 years, you think
I'd be over it by now.
Anyway.
Just wanted to call
and tell you I love you
and I'm thinking about you.
Take care of yourself, okay?
You're my best friend, Dash.
[solemn music]
[tense music]
[water running]
[suspenseful music]
Oh, sh...
Babe, it's me.
Chris.
What were you thinking?
I was thinking I
need to rethink having
an MMA fighter as a girlfriend.
[tense music]
[ominous music]
♪ 13 ♪
Just because your father...
Oh.
Owns half of...
Half of Malibu doesn't
make you a princess.
You're just the
same lowlife bitch
that crawled out of the gutters
of the south side.
And then our villain hits
me with a roundhouse kick.
Knocks the gun out
of my hand, grabs it.
Stabs me, and I'm
rushed to the hospital,
but we don't know if
I live or if I die.
Until contract negotiations.
Exactly.
♪ 13 ♪
♪ Watching you tonight ♪
♪ You are ♪
♪ You are my ♪
♪ Little girl, yeah,
I'm cool tonight ♪
♪ 13 ♪
♪ Waitin' on you tonight ♪
♪ It's Friday night ♪
[intense rock music]
Hey, everybody,
James A. Janisse here
at a three-day horror convention
held every year in
Pasadena, California.
They are celebrating
their 10 year anniversary.
So let's see what
they got inside.
[man shouting]
Everyone here is just so
into the horror genre,
and everyone here
is so friendly.
They're the nicest people.
That's so cool.
- Fan of the movie?
- Oh yeah.
Thanks for being a fan.
Have fun.
I've had a crush on you
since I was a kid.
Not a little nervous, are you?
Come on, let's get this.
[intense rock music]
[man singing indistinctly]
Nice to meet you.
Give me one second.
[phone line ringing]
[phone ringing]
Hey, Kelsie.
Hey, Lar.
You coming?
I'm gonna be a little late,
I had a family emergency.
My son was in an electrical
accident at work.
I don't know the
details, but he's okay.
He's good, thinks he's
bulletproof like his mama.
Okay, good.
I saw your table, I just didn't
see you, so I was worried.
Okay. All right.
[Kelsie] All right,
I'll see you soon.
Thanks.
Okay, sorry.
[Lar] Where the
hell's my photo album?
[tense music]
- Thank you.
- You have a great weekend.
Excuse me, sorry.
Big Hollywood producer
coming through.
Mike Merryman, hi, how are you?
Oh, excuse me, sorry,
don't mean to interrupt,
but I gotta interrupt.
Mike Merryman, how are you?
Caitlin Price.
I love your work.
Oh my God, I've
been following you.
You're amazing.
You are my favorite new
up and coming actress.
By the way, can we get a photo?
Let's get a photo.
Let's get this. There you go.
Hey, that's 35 bucks.
Yeah, yeah, I'll get it, okay.
All right, look
good, there we go.
Cute.
Hey, listen.
You know what, I want to
put you in my new movie.
I'm working on "Bloodlust III."
So I think we
should have dinner.
- Yeah, okay.
- You're so cute, look at you.
Oh, I'm so sorry you had to die.
Junior,
you're a fuckin' asswipe.
[man chuckles]
Thanks for the compliment, Ma.
[tense music]
[people chattering]
Hmm, get security.
Does it look real?
Can you check it?
Thank you, sorry.
Let me see that machete.
[tense music]
Damn, good job.
Thanks, guys.
Thank you.
Sorry about that.
- What's your name?
- Rose.
Rose.
[people chattering]
- Oh, hey, baby!
- Hey, guys!
Hey!
Is there anything else I can
get you ladies of horror?
Yes, a big hug!
Oh, beautiful.
How are you? Good to see you.
- Thank you.
- Hi.
Always a pleasure,
hi, how are you?
- Can I get in there?
- Have a seat!
- Of course!
- Yes!
Let's take a selfie.
This is it.
- Hey!
- Four Musketeers!
Woo!
Hey, hey, hey, guys,
you gotta see this.
You gotta see this.
[intense rock music]
What's up guys? Drumdums here.
What's you're about
to see is horrifying.
Lar Park Lincoln,
the horror icon,
has been brutally murdered.
- What?
- This went live 30 minutes ago.
Lar's live broadcast has been
captured over the dark net.
[suspenseful music]
Can you hear me?
Can you ping me, can
someone locate me?
I don't know where I am.
Check this out, guys.
Horror producer Vincente Disanti
is calling for an investigation.
Best known for producing the
fan film "Never Hike Alone,"
where he played the iconic
killer, Jason Voorhees.
Disanti is producing a
found footage slasher
called "Snuffed Out."
Lar was supposed
to star in that film.
You know, I just
can't help but think
that history is
repeating itself here.
I mean, what's to say
the person behind this
isn't the same person
who's behind the death
of Deb Voorhees?
And how are we ever gonna know?
Wait, has Lar Park Lincoln
been brutally murdered?
Or is this just a publicity
stunt for her new movie?
Please tell me
this isn't happening.
I'm so... He's here.
[tense music]
No, no, no, no, no!
[Drumdums] Brutally murdered.
[dissonant music]
It's just a publicity stunt.
[people talking drowned
out by tense music]
I'm sorry, I'm so
sorry, I didn't mean...
- Jeez.
- I didn't, I'm sorry!
[phone ringing]
Just...
Can you walk her to her room?
Yeah, I got it.
[solemn rock music]
- Kelsie, hey.
- Just leave me alone.
Are you okay?
[solemn rock music]
♪ You couldn't feel it
turning in your bones ♪
♪ All rising, it's
the devil you know ♪
♪ And all that
fear that you own ♪
♪ Vagrant heart turns you cold ♪
♪ And that humming in your ear ♪
♪ Something we all know ♪
♪ And that humming that you
fear, it's the devil you know ♪
[tense music]
[Man] Dash!
Come out and play!
[tense music]
Dash!
This is Kelsie Voorhees.
I need security at
room 215 immediately.
[Man On Phone] On our way.
[door rattles]
Dash!
Did you get my picture?
I think you would
have been nice.
[phone ringing]
I need security up here now.
Hotel security checked
the hall and stairwell,
no one is there.
Then no one is
knocking at my door.
Then he has to have a
room close by to hide in,
like come on!
[Man On Phone] Maybe your
sweet Dee will want to play.
[knocking on door]
Come on, babe.
I know, I'm sorry.
Somebody was banging on the door
- and they were trying to get me.
- Hey, hey, hey.
You're okay.
Kels, when I'm with you,
no one can hurt you.
You're safe.
Okay?
- Okay.
- All right.
Come here.
I got you.
[tense music]
♪ Magazine ♪
♪ Every night you're
in my dreams ♪
♪ Friends tell me
to tell you so ♪
♪ But I'm still
waiting for your call ♪
♪ And I'm haunted
by your reverie ♪
♪ Haunted, please
come back to me ♪
[muffled music on radio]
[solemn music]
Private property, buddy.
Time to go home.
Lar!
[tense music]
Lar.
Lar, are you here?
[cat meows]
Freeze.
Keep moving, let's go.
You don't understand.
That way.
You need to listen to me!
Be quiet!
- She's yours.
- Okay.
Get those people out
of the back yard, please.
I'm telling you
something is wrong.
Kelsie, what the hell
are you doing here?
- Listen to me.
- No body, there's no weapon,
there's no murder.
Have you seen the video?
There was some kind
of a found footage
slasher horror thing.
It's a publicity stunt.
Okay, well she wouldn't
have left her cat, okay?
- There's no food.
- Kelsie-
- There's no water, I'm
telling you something...
- Listen, to me lady!
- Is wrong.
So we're all getting
off the property
or I'm gonna put
the cuffs on you.
That is up to you, that's
up to all of you people,
but we are off the property.
[Kelsie sighs]
[tense music]
Cuffs are coming out if
you're still on this property
in five minutes.
[tense music]
[camera shutter clicking]
Hey Kelsie, look over here.
[suspenseful music]
Oh my God.
No.
Oh.
[tense music]
Hello?
Oh my God, what is this?
Anybody!
[suspenseful music]
[Lar gasps]
[door unlocking]
[suspenseful music]
[man breathing heavily]
[Lar groaning]
[Man] Naughty girl.
Just when I was bringing
you some dinner,
and some chocolate.
Your favorite, right?
Cold water?
It's been three days.
I'm sure you would've
really enjoyed that.
[man chuckling]
There's no escape.
Why are you doing this?
[Man] I don't
wanna hurt you, Tina.
I wanna take care of you.
I'm not Tina.
[Man] You shouldn't
post your worst fears
for the world to see.
Welcome to your hell.
[tense music]
[door slams]
Please come back.
I've been really naughty.
But I've learned my lesson.
Let me out for a
little bit, please?
[Man] When I was a kid, my dad
used to lock me in the
basement when I was bad.
The only thing I had
to keep me company
was a stack of VHS tapes.
"Friday the 13th" and
"Halloween," the entire sagas.
You all became my family.
You're all I had.
So I wrote, and I wrote.
But you never wrote back!
I would have written.
If I had gotten your letters.
You sound so nice.
I didn't get any of the letters.
If I got the letters,
I would have written.
I'm so sorry that
everybody hurt you.
You just let me out a
minute, just for a minute.
Just hold my hand.
Sir.
[Man] You're weak!
Pathetic.
No one will ever
find you but the rats
that will feast on your corpse.
[suspenseful music]
[banging on door]
[Lar shouting]
[phone ringing]
Ah.
Hey, Judie.
Oh my God.
Been way too long.
You had a stalker, right?
Yeah.
Why is, somebody bothering you?
Yeah, it started out as
normal kinda creepy stuff,
like "You're my best friend,"
or "Wouldn't it be cool
if you died in real life like
you did in 'Friday the 13th'?"
But then, he's
sending photos now.
Hard copies started
showing up in my mailbox,
in a menu at a restaurant,
in my gym bag, my home.
Even at my mother's home.
[tense music]
Sausalito murders.
I've covered higher profile
murder cases in my day,
The OJ Simpson trial.
But this one still haunts me.
Dale.
Is it true that you
were in "Friday the 13th?"
Yes.
A blue bikini.
That is so cool.
All right, guys, your
assignment for the weekend.
I want you to go out
and produce a news story
about something exciting
you do over the weekend.
All right, got it?
Not sure I can film that.
[class laughing]
[bell ringing]
Grow up, jerk.
[text message dings]
Please.
Hmm.
[tense music]
What is this?
What the fuck?
What?
[tense music]
What the...
[Tracie gasping]
Okay, okay.
[phone ringing]
Answer.
[suspenseful music]
[horn honking]
Come on.
[text message dings]
James.
[phone buzzing]
Someone's out there, John.
[tense music]
John!
[phone buzzing]
[glass breaks]
[woman screams]
[Man] Basement.
Go.
[tense music]
[suspenseful music]
[frenetic rock music]
[tense music]
Oh my God.
[keys jingling]
University of Los Angeles.
Room 131.
Building nine.
[tense music]
There's a man.
He's trying to get
into my classroom.
Oh fuck, he's here now..
Help, please hurry.
[tense music]
Hello, Debbie.
I'm one of your biggest fans.
[Tracie panting]
[suspenseful music]
Get out of here, now!
[man grunts]
Oh God.
[Man] Bitch!
[Tracie gasps]
[suspenseful music]
[tense music]
[Jennifer] So, are you
gonna leave me in suspense?
Did you get it?
Well, the director
went on and on
about how big a fan he is,
had me sign a couple things,
and then turned me down.
What?
Seriously?
Kane, his fucking loss.
He said he couldn't
see the legendary
Kane Hodder in a role like this.
Run into this all the time.
Everybody thinks I'm
just a silent killer.
I'm sick of it.
I believe in you.
Kane, who cares if some
fucking asshole producer does?
Look, Kane.
This has always been your dream.
Let's green-light
this ourselves.
We'll produce the play.
I'll be your Stella,
you'll be my Stanley.
Maybe you're right.
So is that crazy stalker
still bothering you?
Kane, I'm worried.
A lot of actresses are worried.
I've seen a lot of
fanboys in my day.
There's just something
about this one.
[tense music]
[kettle whistling]
[text messages dinging]
[tense music]
[Jennifer crying]
[phone ringing]
- Jen?
- Kane?
It's happening again.
Okay, have you
called the police?
I've called them before,
it doesn't do any good.
They come, they take
a report, they leave.
[Kane] Have they traced
the phone number at least?
They've tried.
He uses burner phones.
I block one number, by the
next day, he has another.
Please tell me
you're almost here.
Do you trust me?
Of course.
I'm close by.
Go up to your room,
turn off your light
- like you're going to bed.
- Why?
Just do it.
I'm on my way.
Be there soon.
[tense music]
[text messages dinging]
[Jennifer whimpering]
[clock chiming]
[suspenseful music]
[tense music]
[Jennifer gasping]
[suspenseful music]
Kane!
[Jennifer screams]
[tense music]
[Man] The one thing
the franchise taught me
is that death is an art.
I take great pride
designing each and every
one of my kills for my loves.
Jen.
[Man] You used to
take my breath away.
Now I'm gonna take yours.
[Jennifer choking]
Jen!
[Kane groans]
[Jennifer choking]
Jen, Jen, Jen, Jen!
[suspenseful music]
[Jennifer crying]
[solemn music]
Nearly lost you.
Kane!
Don't you dare die on me!
You don't have to yell,
I'm right in front of you.
[Jennifer crying]
You can't die.
[siren wailing]
You're Kane Hodder.
I'm Kane Hodder, yep.
Flesh and blood, I bleed
like everyone else.
No.
That Kane on the screen,
yeah, he can never die.
But that's not reality.
I'm a husband to
a beautiful woman,
And father to two amazing sons.
[Jennifer crying]
I was there when my dad
was at the end of his life,
and I never said, "I love you."
Please, tell my wife and
sons that I love them.
[Jennifer crying]
[Jennifer mumbling]
No stunt coordinator.
[Jennifer crying]
[dramatic music]
Hang in there, buddy.
EMT is on the way.
[tense music]
Hey, come on, sleepyhead.
Dear God, what
time did you get up?
Six.
I love you for not
waking me up then.
[Ron] Love you too.
I can do this.
Hey Ronnie, you know where
my gold earrings are?
Yeah, I saw you put
them in the jewelry box
- last night.
- Yeah, but they're not there.
Well, that's weird.
You must've dropped them.
No, not on the floor.
[door closes]
I guess we're both
losing our minds.
[Dee gasping]
[tense music]
[knocking on door]
Dee.
Get it together, Dee.
Hey Dee, I'm heading
out to the grocery store
to pick up a few things.
You need anything?
[knocking on door]
Dee?
No, nothing, sorry.
You okay?
Yeah, just an upset stomach.
[Dee crying]
I won't be long, honey.
Call me if you need anything.
[Dee crying]
[suspenseful music]
[phone buzzes]
Come on.
Past time to leave.
Little short, don't you think?
Hey Dee, it's Judie.
So the producer
of "Snuffed Out,"
that thing that I showed
you guys the other day,
Vincente Disanti, he
wants you to star in it.
Yeah, he's a little
bit of an ass,
but he's a really good
producer, and I'm in it, so.
So expect a call and
would love to work
with the great Dee
Wallace, finally.
All right, let me
know how it goes.
Bye.
Bit of an ass, huh?
[Judie] She'll be
expecting your call.
Well, thank you.
- Kelsie.
- Mm-hmm.
Hey, Kelsie.
You know, I don't
know if you know this,
but first of all, great
work out there today.
- Amazing stuff.
- Thank you!
But also, I don't
know if you know,
but I actually collect
all of your cage fights.
- I've got all of them.
- That's nice.
Yeah.
Why are you putting
the robe on, though?
Gotta keep wardrobe clean.
You know this, Mike.
Yeah, I know, but
then you ruin the view
for the rest of us.
'Cause, well...
Great scene, Kels.
Kelsie, are you doing
the shower scene later?
Uh-huh.
That's good.
'Cause I'm really looking
forward to the nude scene.
Aren't we all.
Yeah, I think
everybody here is.
Chris!
- Hey baby.
- Ah, lips, lips, lips!
Cute.
So, you're the lucky guy, huh?
You get to...
Out my index finger
in the okay sign?
With her.
- With her.
- All the time.
[Chris] All the time.
You're a lucky guy.
- Where'd you get that?
- What?
I've never seen that before.
[tense music]
Jesus Christ, who
the fuck is that guy?
Mike Merryman.
Put like a hundred
grand into the film
so now he gets to be
a pain in the ass.
Grabs my ass one more
time, there's about to be
an accident with
the curling iron.
He grabbed my ass yesterday.
What?
He can grab my ass any time.
Honey, that's just
Mike being Mike.
You put that much
money into a movie,
you have carte blanche
to handle all the goods.
Can't do anything about it.
Nor would I want to.
- I can do something about it.
- Chris.
I like my job.
What are you doing here?
100K, that's not
even that much money.
This is like a
$2.5 million film.
It's enough they
let him hang on set
and be as creepy
as he wants to be.
Kelsie, we have one more scene
and you are released
for the day.
Part your lips a little bit?
As per your agent, you
have the next three days off.
Second AD will send you a
call sheet Wednesday night
- with-
- Part your lips a little bit?
[tense music]
- Uh-huh.
- Grabbed my ass yesterday.
You put that much money...
I'm looking forward
to the nude scene.
Kelsie. You with me?
Yeah.
Great.
Okay people, back
in five, back in five.
- Yeah, I'm gonna grab food.
- Okay.
Kels.
Some producer guy
wants to meet you.
[tense music]
- Oh, hey, Kelsie Voorhees?
- Hi.
Vincente Disanti, I'm the
producer on "Snuffed Out."
We're currently casting
for the film, and I-
- "Snuffed Out?"
- Yeah.
You're the creep exploiting
the death of Lar Park Lincoln,
and my grandmother.
You're advertising everywhere.
The same man who killed Deborah
Voorhees also killed Lar?
Really? That's tasteless.
What happened to your
grandmother was unfortunate.
Unfortunate?
Kelsie, I understand-
- Were you in the
woods that night?
Did you watch your
grandmother die?
You don't understand shit.
[Woman] Kelsie,
we're ready for you.
All right, let's be honest.
You only got cast in
this role because you're
a cute little cage
fighter with the last name
of a famous slasher
movie villain.
We're both opportunists, so
come on, what do you say?
Fuck you.
All right, let's do this.
All right. Quiet on the set.
- Sound? Camera?
- Audio speeds. Rolling
Scene 44, Victor,
take one, mark.
Action.
[suspenseful music]
Somebody help me, please!
[dramatic music]
Babe, it's not your fault.
I didn't double,
triple check it.
Kels, it's not your job.
A woman is dead!
And she died in my hands.
Do you think it matters
whose fucking job it was?!
Dammit!
I didn't fucking
check the knife.
[Kelsie crying]
Babe.
Just stay home tonight.
I don't want you
driving in this state
and I can't make
the plane either.
I haven't slept in 24 hours.
I'm exhausted.
I just need her, Chris.
I know, I know.
I'll drive you anywhere you
want to go in the morning.
[tense music]
[Dee sighs]
[girl laughing]
- Birdie.
- What's wrong?
If anything happens to me...
Nothing's gonna happen to you.
Deborah.
You cannot live
your life in fear.
I feel it in my gut.
This fanboy is dangerous.
Sweetheart.
Who's gonna be my grandma now?
I will be your
grandma, sweetheart.
[solemn music]
I will be your grandma forever.
[knocking on door]
Hey.
God, honey, please
don't do that.
Sorry, babe.
You need to eat.
Not hungry.
You know grieving
won't bring her back.
Every anniversary of her
death, it's the same thing.
When's this gonna finally end?
I don't know, honey,
maybe when my friend
isn't dead anymore.
You gotta stop
blaming yourself.
You couldn't have known.
Okay look, we've been
over this a million times.
I should have believed her and
I should have done something.
[gulls cawing]
[waves crashing]
[camera shutter clicking]
You make such a
beautiful murdered woman.
Who likes looking at
photos of naked dead women?
Horror fans.
[camera shutter clicks]
Beautiful.
That's a wrap, guys.
There's my girls!
Hi, sweetheart.
I wanna pet him,
I wanna pet him!
Okay, okay.
Everybody's gonna get a
chance with the doggy.
Hey, thanks.
The kids always cheer her up.
Love you, Mom.
Have a good day, Abby.
Bye guys.
We'll pick them up
Monday morning, okay?
- Okay.
- Hey.
Let me take that for you.
[groans]
What do you got in here, rocks?
[tense music]
There we go.
- Hold up.
- Okay.
Is it refrigerator-ready,
Grandma?
Oh!
I don't know, let's go see.
Come on, walk this way.
[camera shutter clicks]
Love it.
Thank you.
[phone ringing]
Oh.
Janey.
Yeah.
How are you?
[camera shutter clicks]
Can we look at
the stars, Grandma?
Well, hey, I hope
you have good news.
Grandma, can we
set up the telescope?
Stars, stars,
let's go, Grandma!
I already set it up.
Come on, you guys.
We're gonna look at Pluto.
[camera shutter clicking]
They won't even read it?
- What are you seeing?
- Stars!
That's called the Milky Way.
[camera shutter clicks]
It's like a billion stars.
No, I understand.
Okay, thank you, thanks
for letting me know.
[Man] Don't worry, Cynthia.
I'll put you back
in the spotlight.
[suspenseful music]
[tense music]
[dramatic music]
[Dee screams]
What's the matter?
There's somebody out there.
I saw him.
Don't you look at me like that.
Is it the bad guy, Grandma?
Oh, no, it's not.
There's no bad guy.
I'm not crazy.
Grandma, are you okay?
Yes, sweetie.
Hey, no, one's there.
It's just a shadow.
Come on, it's time to go to bed.
I've got a great story
for you guys.
If this doesn't stop,
our son isn't gonna
let us see our
grandkids anymore.
Is that what you want?
Nope.
Dee.
[tense music]
[suspenseful music]
Anybody can locate me.
Please tell my son...
That I love him so much.
[tense music]
Locate me.
I don't know where I am.
Please, please.
No!
[keyboard clacking]
[tense music]
Now we have some really
sad news to report.
"Friday the 13th"
actress Tiffany Helm
was found stabbed to
death late last night
outside of her
Hollywood Hills home.
She was stabbed nine times
in the neck and abdomen,
and some reports are
even saying her head
was completely severed.
Police haven't made any arrests
yet, but they are saying,
it looks like she was
the victim of a stalker
in which she was referred
to as her character's name,
Violet.
Yeah, pretty creepy.
Now of course, thoughts
and prayers go out
to Tiffany's family.
And you know guys, we
all love the films,
the kills, the blood, the gore,
but when it's
happening in real life,
it can be pretty scary.
So stay safe out there and
let's hope that they can catch
whoever is responsible
for this very soon.
[text message dings]
Hey, babe.
You need to wake up.
Chris.
Chris!
Come on.
Seriously?
[tense music]
Pick up, pick up,
pick up, pick up.
[phone buzzing]
[Operator] What
is your emergency?
Hi, I need to report
a possible murder.
[Operator] What
is your address?
No, it's my
friend, Dee Wallace.
I'm afraid something's
gonna happen to her.
Kelsie Voorhees?
Is there an immediate threat
at Ms. Wallace's house?
Well, no, not that I know of,
but some really weird
things are happening and-
- Okay, if there is
an immediate threat,
call back, we will
send a unit out there.
Otherwise, you're welcome to
call the non-emergency number.
I'm sure Detective
Evans will be happy
to hear from you again.
Shit.
[tense music]
Grandma, I had a bad dream.
Uh-oh.
Come on.
Dreams aren't real, you know.
It feels real.
Hey, you know where
I got this doll?
This was my mommy's doll.
And she gave it to me
when I was about your age.
She's really pretty.
Isn't she?
Just like you.
Would you like to have her?
- Mm-hmm.
- Uh-huh.
Okay.
Can we watch a funny movie?
Ah-ha.
I think this was all a ruse
to get to stay up later
and watch a movie.
Maybe!
Maybe.
All right, let's see
what we can find.
[phone ringing]
Hold on.
Hey, Kelsie.
It's a little late.
Got the kids this weekend.
Okay, hi.
Lock your doors, hide the
kids in the hiding place
and get your gun and
point it at the door.
If anyone comes through, fire.
Oh my gosh.
[Kelsie] What, what happened?
All the electricity
just went out.
Okay.
Someone cut the
electrical lines.
I am on my way.
Kelsie, I saw him.
Go, get your gun, now.
- Okay, I'll see you soon.
- Okay.
Okay.
- All right, sweetheart.
- Grandma, what's going on?
You and I are gonna go find
the safe place, remember?
- Mm-hmm.
- Yeah?
Shh, it's okay.
- Come on, honey.
- What's going on?
We're gonna go down
to the safe place.
It's all right,
everything's fine.
Hold on, wait!
What's going on?
Somebody cut the
electrical line.
- Cut?
- Yes.
Dee, it's probably
just a fuse.
[tense music]
I want Scout.
I'm gonna keep him for
right now, sweetheart.
Go in and be very,
very quiet, right?
No matter what,
you don't come out.
Okay.
[Girl] What if I need
to go to the bathroom?
[Dee sighs]
[tense music]
Oh, Dee, are you crazy?
[dog whines]
Maybe.
But I'm not taking any chances.
Get behind me.
That's it, I'm
taking the kids out.
No you're not.
Just leave them where they are.
You take 'em out of
there and you're wrong,
we all could get killed.
You're gonna shoot me?
If I have to.
Just stay, get behind me.
You're on your own.
[door closes]
Ron!
[tense music]
Ron.
Ron?
[suspenseful music]
[gunshot bangs]
- It's me.
- Oh.
- God, I coulda killed you.
Actually you shot a bird's
nest 30 feet above my head
and 20 feet to the
right, I'm good.
[suspenseful music]
[tense music]
[Dee gasping]
What the hell are you doing?
What's wrong with you?
You called Scott?!
I had to!
Sorry, Mom, you gave
Dad and I no other choice.
We don't wanna leave Grandma!
They were fine!
Jesus Christ!
We've lost our daughter, now
we've lost our grandkids.
You, because of you!
It's not me, it's you!
God dammit, Dee!
[tense music]
[Dee shouts]
- It's just me, I'm sorry.
- Don't do that!
- Sorry.
- Oh, you know better.
What is this?
I don't know.
Can you get it?
Oh, you're kidding.
Cynthia Strode?
Open it.
"Roses are red for
a beautiful lady.
You're my favorite scream queen.
I first saw you when I was 12.
I had a huge crush on you.
Could you sign my photo?
I've included $50 plus a
self-addressed stamped envelope.
You're the coolest.
Sincerely your number
one fan, Kenneth Casper."
- I love real fans.
- Right?
Kinda creepy 'cause
it came to your house.
Yeah, you think?
Oh, but pretty roses.
[Kelsie] You want some tea?
[tense music]
I'm so sorry.
Unfortunately, we don't
have a lot to go on.
There was a piece
of my hair cut out
in the middle of the night.
I didn't cut it out.
That means this fanboy,
he's not just watching me.
He's coming into my home.
Why didn't he just kill me?
If the guy is a
killer, he may get off
on terrorizing his
victims before the kill.
The way a cat
toys with a mouse.
There's no signs
of forced entry
on this floor or downstairs.
You did keep
your doors locked?
Of course.
Dee, we wish that there was
more that we could do, but-
- He broke into my home.
We're gonna send a squad
car around periodically,
keep an eye on the place.
In the meantime, you
keep your doors locked
and your gun loaded.
[suspenseful music]
Dee, I won't doubt
you again, okay?
It's fine, really.
[knocking on door]
- Hey babe.
- Hello.
- How's it going?
- Good.
Missed you.
What happened to your hand?
Oh.
Nothing, just burned on the
stove while I was cooking.
Hey.
- You must be Chris.
- Yeah.
- Hi Dee.
- Hi, good to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
You're my first crush
when I was younger.
[laughs] Okay.
Oh, shit, sorry, I didn't
mean to go all fanboy on you.
That's okay, honey.
Everybody's grown up on me.
- Want a glass of wine?
- Yeah.
- You?
- Of course.
Yeah, of course.
- Dee Wallace.
- What?
You're such a nerd.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Not a chance.
Okay.
So you have to understand that
even though Kelsie's grandma
was a girly girl, she didn't
take shit from nobody.
Oh, sounds familiar.
Like this one time, we
stopped at this dance hall,
and this dude comes
over and he whispers
something in her ear.
Swear to God, she wouldn't
ever tell me what it was,
but she said it was so bad
it would make a sailor blush.
By this time, a whole bunch
of people are coming through.
She maneuvered around
to let them through
and she took her big
old stiletto heel,
buries it in this guy's arm.
And that's what he did.
Exactly.
And she just dug that heel
right in until he yelped.
She turned and said [gasps],
oh my god, I am so sorry.
Oh, it was an accident.
I didn't mean to do that.
Nobody, nobody in
the whole place
knew that she meant to do it,
that it wasn't an accident.
She was something.
- One more.
- Oh no, no, no, no,
- Come on.
- No more.
I'm going to bed.
Boo.
- Oh.
[tense music]
Oh, sorry.
I was hoping that you
would sign this for me.
Sure, yeah.
Let me get my pen.
Oh no, I got one right here.
Here you go.
- There you go.
- Thank you.
Awesome.
Thank you so much, Dee.
You remember to lock up.
- Night.
- Love you.
- Love you
Really?
Sorry.
Last time, I promise.
[tense music]
[clock ticking]
[water dripping]
[door creaking]
[tense music]
Chris?
[computer beeping]
[tense music]
[woman screaming]
[suspenseful music]
Ronnie.
Ronnie, wake up.
Wake up.
[suspenseful music]
Help me.
Help me!
Somebody help me!
Kelsie, help me!
Help me!
Oh! Kelsie!
[Dee crying]
[suspenseful music]
Help me!
It's okay.
[Dee crying]
[tense music]
[suspenseful music]
[Deborah shouting]
[Deborah crying]
What?
I don't understand.
I wasn't there, I
swear, I wasn't there.
How can that be?
I wasn't there.
- You killed her.
- What?
- No, Kelsie.
- Why?
She loved you.
No, Kelsie, no, I would never
hurt her, you know that.
I'm sorry, come on.
I don't understand.
I wasn't there.
Don't do this, you
know I can't do this.
You have the right
to remain silent.
Lori, you know I
couldn't do this to Ronnie.
Oh, don't do this.
Please don't do this.
Can and will be held
against you in a court of law.
No!
You have the right
to representation.
If you cannot afford
it, one will be...
[dramatic music]
Whoever killed
Deborah killed Ronnie.
And the video on my computer.
Please, I'm begging you.
[horn honking]
The right side of her
face has light on it,
but there's no light
coming from the right side.
Only from the left.
Now watch this.
- See it?
- See what?
Okay.
Look again.
All I see is a slight glitch.
It's not a glitch.
There.
- That a hand?
- And a part of a forearm.
Someone not only superimposed
Dee in the video,
but they've covered
up the second killer.
Look.
This is what Dee was
wearing on Saturday.
Look.
[Man On Radio] Dispatch,
four-one-two, we got a wild one.
You gotta see this guy.
Found him in the woods
outside Miss Wallace's house.
Kelsie, Kelsie, baby, it's me.
Let them know I'm a
producer on "Bloodlust III."
I'm her producer.
I was just trying
to say hi to Kelsie
and meet Dee for the first time.
No big deal.
He had these in
his possession.
Guy swears he paid a buddy
250 bucks for a pint of blood.
I did!
I did, I just wanted it
to be authentic looking.
You know, we're making a low
budget horror movie here.
You know, you gotta
do what you gotta do.
Spare no expense, but
keep it within the budget.
That's what I was taught.
We just tested it
in the onsite lab.
It's human.
Now we're gonna test it
to see whether or not
it matches Miss
Wallace's husband.
[tense music]
Thanks for bringing
me a change of clothes.
I'm sorry I doubted you.
That's okay.
I was beginning
to suspect me too.
Come on, let's go.
[solemn music]
We don't wanna be in here.
Why, what's wrong?
The house is bad.
No, sweetheart.
The house isn't bad.
Just something bad
happened in the house.
Will the bad man come back?
Nope, they arrested
him and he's in jail.
[Girl] For good?
For good.
Do we have to stay in?
No, you go play.
Maybe the kids have a point.
Maybe you should move.
What?
Not a chance.
You know how many memories
there are of Ronnie
and you kids in this house?
I'm not gonna let some psychopath
run me out of my own home.
[door closes]
Oh my gosh.
You both came.
I am so sorry, Dee.
Ronnie.
Ronnie was amazing.
What can we do for you?
We're here for you.
We'll be in town to help,
anything you need done.
Where are you staying?
We have rooms in the town.
Oh, please stay here.
I really need my
friends around me.
Yes, yes, yes.
I'm so sorry.
I hope they string
the bastard up.
[clock ticking]
So have the cops
arrested anybody yet?
Yeah, he hasn't
been charged yet.
He was caught outside
though, with human blood
and a machete, so, I'm sure.
Hey.
Oh guys, come on.
Don't have to walk on pins
and needles around me.
Sorry.
You know...
Could I ask you guys to just
gather Ron's clothes
and the pictures,
put 'em up in the
attic for me tomorrow.
I just really don't want
to see anything right now.
Can you do that for me?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Thank you for
everything today.
- Of course.
- Love you.
Sleep well.
[suspenseful music]
Ronnie, wake up!
Ronnie?
Ron.
[text message dings]
[Kelsie] What's going on?
Sorry.
Tracie Savage is in
town and she wants me
to meet her for
dinner tomorrow night.
She doesn't know?
I didn't think to call her.
Well, you have to eat.
[tense music]
[mysterious music]
Do you know this number?
No.
Weird, they're telling
me to check your phone?
Well, I've always
got it on silent.
Oh, Detective Evans.
[Lori] Dee, I've been trying
to get ahold of you all day.
Unfortunately we had to
let Mike Merryman go.
- We held him for as long as we could.
- What?
- But there wasn't any DNA-
- Come on.
For the blood, it was
human, but it really
belonged to his
very alive buddy.
Listen, I'm gonna send
a couple of my guys over
to check on your place.
Let me know you
got this message.
[tense music]
Flank right,
I'm gonna go left.
[Officer] Got it.
[suspenseful music]
[Man] Cynthia.
Cynthia.
[phone ringing]
Who is this and
what do you want?
[Man On Phone]
Off to see Tracie?
Aww, she might not
make the best company.
We gotta go.
[suspenseful music]
[Dee shouts]
[Dee groans]
Come on, we gotta go.
- Oh, God!
- You gotta get up.
I'm sorry, we have to.
- I can't.
- Let's go. Come on.
[tense music]
[suspenseful music]
I can't, I can't, go, go.
I'm not leaving you!
[Dee] Get help!
Police, send somebody to help,
someone's trying to kill us.
[Man On Phone] A
unit is on the way.
They will be at
least 15 minutes.
We don't have 15 minutes.
- [suspenseful music]
- Cynthia, tell Dash to leave.
I only want you.
[suspenseful music]
No!
[tense music]
[Dee shouting]
[suspenseful music]
You leave her alone!
[Dee shouting]
[Dee crying]
I spared you once, remember?
Not this time.
Get away from her, you fucker!
This is all your
fault, Cynthia.
You should have sent her away.
No!
[suspenseful music]
[Dee crying]
I have been waiting my whole
life to fight you, Jason.
So what do you say, kid?
You want a shot at the title?!
[thunder crashing]
Don't mind if I do.
[men shouting]
[men grunting]
[thunder crashing]
[suspenseful music]
No!
[man shouting]
Dirty bastard!
[man growls]
Get up, old man!
[thunder crashing]
[tense music]
No.
They say the best and
worst day in a boy's life
is when he finds out that
he's stronger than his father.
I loved you, Jason.
No.
Wait.
[tense music]
[flesh squelching]
[C.J. groaning]
Killing you will be
the greatest honor...
Of my life.
[gunshot bangs]
[thunder crashing]
[Dee crying]
[suspenseful music]
[siren wailing]
You just suck it up.
[Dee laughs]
[siren wailing]
[solemn music]
Oh.
- I love you.
Sure you don't
want me to stay?
Well, I need you,
but you can go.
Okay.
All right, I love you.
Oh, I love you, honey.
Take care of Dee for me, okay?
- Buh-bye.
- Bye.
Love you.
Drive safe.
[engine rumbling]
[solemn music]
Thank you again for staying.
I swear I'm gonna be a
basket case for two months.
Let's go drink.
I have a movie I
want to show you.
[Dee] Okay.
My directorial debut.
Oh goody.
It's not quite finished.
In fact, I want you
to play a role in it.
Oh, well, I'd be honored.
Yeah.
Boy, this wine.
It's really hitting
me fast tonight.
Yeah?
Oopsie.
Yeah, you had
quite a rough week.
Let me give you a
little back rub.
I won't argue with that.
[Judie] Yeah,
right, who doesn't?
Oh.
[tense music]
Ow.
What was that?
Nothing, it's just
the succinylcholine.
You're gonna be
totally incapacitated
in about 20 seconds.
And then...
It should last, oh...
About 12 minutes,
What?
Don't worry, you
won't miss a thing.
Your mind will stay hyper alert
and your nerves hyper sensitive.
Come on.
Let's watch.
[suspenseful music]
Please.
Come on.
[Judie] 10 simple questions
about "Friday the 13th."
You get six right,
it's a D minus.
Passing grade.
Let you walk out of
here with your life.
Please.
- But Tracie, if you fail-
- Oh, come on.
[drill whirring]
[Judie] All right, we'll
start with an easy one.
What is the name of the location
of "Friday the 13th Part V?"
I don't know.
I played one role in part three.
I didn't even see
the other movies.
That's a wrong answer,
because it's Pinehurst.
What? No.
What is the name
of the cemetery
that the killer is
buried in in Part Six?
That wasn't my answer.
- Wrong.
- Oh God.
It's the Eternal
Peace Cemetery.
Please.
Stop.
I got one.
All right.
Who did the producers
get to play the killer
in "Friday the 13th Part II?"
Steve Dash.
Whoa.
You didn't let me finish.
Oh, come on.
Before they hired Steve Dash.
I don't know.
- Oh, you don't?
- No.
Well, then that's wrong again.
Oh God.
That's three wrong
and zero right.
Whoa, you really
suck at this game.
- Please stop.
- You know?
I mean, if you continue
like this, he's...
[drill whirring]
[tense music]
Tell me, what kind of power tool
was used as a
weapon by the killer
in "Friday the 13th Part VII."
My favorite part.
Tree saw.
Oh.
She got one.
- Ha ha, wow.
- That's impressive.
So that's three
wrong, one right?
See if you can keep this up.
Oh, please.
Okay.
In "Jason Goes to Hell,"
who dragged that mask
all the way back to hell?
Freddy Krueger?
Is that a question?
That's a guess.
- I'll give it to you.
- Fuck.
- Again, more.
- Okay.
What's the name
of the cruise ship
the students of Crystal Lake
High get on to go to Manhattan?
[Tracie] I have no idea.
- That'd be The Lazarus.
- Come on.
[mumbling on video]
You think you're better
than us, don't you?
I'm just, you know, some
victim from the fourth film.
What is so special about you?
Why do you get the long
lines at the conventions?
You and your precious Kelsie.
Did I mention that I'm
gonna kill her next?
[suspenseful music]
[people chattering]
Oh God no.
No, no, no.
[drill whirring]
Oh my God, no.
[Tracie screaming]
Just like the movies.
[video beeps]
Because we're friends,
I'm gonna give you a choice.
Drill to the brain...
[drill whirring]
Ah, the dagger.
Goes to the left of the
stomach and across and up.
Disembowel.
Tracie's husband loved this.
The bleed out was rather slow.
Okay.
This one's my favorite.
It's just so long.
[door opens]
[suspenseful music]
[glass breaking]
[Judie screaming]
[Kelsie grunts]
[suspenseful music]
That's the sweetest
thing I've ever seen.
[suspenseful music]
[solemn music]
♪ 13 ♪
♪ Waitin' on you tonight ♪
♪ What gives you the right ♪
♪ Wanted your head,
want it a while ♪
♪ Pretty girl, yeah,
I wanted your smile ♪
♪ 13 ♪
♪ And it's all right ♪
♪ Watching you tonight ♪
♪ You won't run ♪
♪ You won't hide ♪
♪ Little girl, yeah,
I'm coming tonight ♪
♪ 13 ♪
♪ Waitin' on you tonight ♪
♪ It's Friday night ♪
...I've ever seen
[kiss sound]
[laughing]
Sorry.
Scared me.
[laughing]
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull