(bright soft music)
(glass shatters)
(car engine rumbling)
(bright upbeat music)
- Yo, Floyd, your man gonna
be here tonight or what, man?
- Man, who you talking to, dog?
My man is working the door,
I ain't no standing in line,
no cover charge,
VIP all the way.
Yo Jay, is that the
good shit right there?
- Yeah.
- Well, then puff puff
give motherfucker.
- There you go.
- Why don't you puff
puff get your own shit?
- For once nigga, damn,
what the fuck do you do?
Run outta that $40
bag of dirt shit
you've been smoking, Floyd?
(phone rings)
- Man, you've been smoking what?
Clarence, what's up
with your cousin?
What, you ain't smoke weed?
- Nah man, Damon don't
need that shit, man,
he already think
on a higher level.
Now me, I need that shit.
- Yo, problem.
- What's wrong man.
- Caesar said the Nevins ass
niggas ain't
paying up.
- Word?
- Word.
- Motherfuckers, man.
- Hey, hold on, hey, hold on,
this ain't even the
way to the club.
Blacks on my
hoods and ghetto
Hot projects and metals
Put your guns up
North, south, east to west
- Hey, come on, man, why are
you pulling over here, man?
We gotta get to the
club by midnight
else we gonna miss the
drink, stuff and shit,
we gonna miss the whole...
- Shut the fuck up, Floyd,
all right?
Damn!
Come on, man.
- Now?
- No Ice Cube, next
fucking Friday, yeah, now,
what the fuck is wrong with you?
- Fuck man, yo, what
about your cousin?
- Nah, nah, he can
stay here, man,
I'm just gonna run in here and
put a scare in him, a warning
or some shit,
all right?
Come on, quit acting
like a bitch and come on.
Fuck it, slide your punk ass
over here and drive me, man.
The fuck.
- This shit means stuff.
- Yo, Damon, I'll be
right back, all right,
you wait right here.
- All right,
do your thing.
Calm down, Floyd, chill.
- Now, every time-
- Man, Floyd, Floyd!
Smoke this and calm
your motherfucking ass.
- I mean, these
fools like to go out
shooting motherfuckers ass,
I don't understand that.
- All right, man,
we going there, man,
chill.
(gun bangs)
Oh, shit!
(tense music)
(gun bangs)
- Go!
- Oh, shit,
come on, come on, come on.
Get in, get in, get in.
(tires screeching)
(guns banging)
(glass shatters)
- Damn!
- Yeah, go. - We'll kill
you motherfucker.
(man laughs)
- Oh, shit!
- The fuck!
(tense music)
(men laughing)
- What the fuck was that?
What kind of warning
was that, Clarence?
- Your (indistinct) is wild.
- He probably piss
his pants, I know it,
yo, Damon, you ain’t gonna tell
your mom about
this, huh?
Damon.
(soft somber music)
- What?
- Oh, fuck, Damon!
- [Sway] So, what's the
deal, Philadelphia's WBST,
it's your man, Sway,
spread that brotherly love.
Next up, we got some
homegrown flavor
straight outta Kingsbridge,
number one record in the street,
Philadelphia's finest, Prolifik
with that "Mind Games,"
he's doing it really
big right now,
you got it first
right here, WBST.
This life about
guns, money and hoes
This life about cars,
jewelry and clothes
This life about
sex, lies and oh
This life about sell
weed and clothes
This life about
guns, money and hoes
This life about cars,
jewelry and clothes
This life about
sex, lies and oh
This life about what
This life about
My life is more than me
and the clothes on my back
Ice burg, Gucci
shit, keep all that
I'ma lay it down flat,
I'm not here to floss
A lot of my men paying with
their lives to be the boss
We all brand the streets,
carry the brown heat
Went through the worst parts
to get to Brand
suite
Deep in the game that
ain't got no love
And many that lost their
minds all to the throne
I know thugs who used to
push bricks, smoke nicks
Floss the fliers
with damn nigga shit
Step on the block thinking
back how they had it locked
Dem days is over now and they
see him through
the rock
These streets don't play,
I know that he's a killer
It's not a good sight to see
if nigga getting to the grip
Sit out here rip,
seeing it all happen
He's just pumped
up drugs and stuff
And that the size
that describes
This life about
guns, money and hoes
This life about cars,
jewelry and clothes
This life about
sex, lies and oh
This life about sell
weed and clothes
This life about
guns, money and hoes
This life about cars,
jewelry and clothes
This life about
sex, lies and oh
This life about what
This life about
I love life more
than Jerry dough
than burnt out hoes
I fell for the streets,
staying low with the heat
I'd been through the war
nigga, ain't shit sweet
Seen the good times and
went through the worst
One point in time I
thought I was a curse
Couldn't flow so that I
suppose that felt dead
It's cold as fuck
and I'm in a cell
That's why I smoke Ls
and live life day to day
Love is love, feel it feels,
then you pay
the price
Niggas pay the latter,
me I ain't quit it
Some dudes like to floss
me I just come and get it
Play strip poker,
without no cards
One gun pulls clear,
get ready to meet
(car door slams)
(TV chattering)
(door clicks)
(remote clatters)
(footsteps clumping)
- [Machine] You have one
new message, first message.
- [Officer] Hi, this is
the attendance officer
at Overbrook High School,
I'm calling in regards
to Erik Triggs.
Erik...
(machine beeps)
- [Machine] Message erased.
(uptempo music)
- Malik, don't you ever knock?
- Front door was unlocked,
do you wanna hit this?
Yeah, you bet, let me play
my new joint, all right?
(bright soft music)
Say my name niggas
Yeah, dope baby
Say my name
Is my shit the bomb or what?
(bright upbeat music)
- It's the bomb, Malik.
- Nino Brown
- What?
- Look, I keep telling
you, all right,
from now on, it's Nino Brown.
you know, like that
dude in New Jack City.
- Right.
- All right, you know things
is a little lean right now,
do you know what my
rhyme this skill,
I'm gonna get paid real soon,
and you ought to think
about managing me.
- Maybe, let's see what
you do with your demo tape,
you finish it?
- Close, man, I'm close.
Still got a few
things to finish.
The problem is I need
more studio time.
- I thought Ricky B
was hooking you up.
- Me and Ricky B ain't
really vibing right now.
- [Erik] And why's that?
- Kind of gotta do
with his sister.
- (laughs) Oh, no, you didn't.
Please, tell me you didn't.
- Hey yo, I can't help
these magnetic charms,
shawtys be up on me
like bees on honey.
Yeah, though, all I need is a
few more hours in the studio.
If only I have some dough though
- Why don't you get a job.
- Man, Hip hop is my profession,
I ain't got time to be
supersizing no fries.
E, you were a player at Ill Wax.
- So?
- So then, don't they got
that recording studio,
the Hit Palace?
- Mm hmm.
- So, then hook me up.
Then we can roll in
there, turn the hit out
it's me and you, all right?
- I don't know.
Look, I gotta break out.
- Whoa, whoa, where
are you off to?
Ain't tell me you
skipping school again.
- Nah, I gotta go hook up with
Cheryl over the
Ill Wax.
- All right, while
you down there,
you know, start
spreading the word,
you can be like, ah, that kid's
shit amazing,
you know?
- (chuckles) Cool, hey
check you later, Malik.
- I told you, it's Nino.
(bright upbeat music)
(car engine roars)
- You tell that
ignorant asshole,
he can kiss my ass
if he ever thinks
he's gonna see another
dime on my fucking money.
(footsteps clumping)
(faint soft music)
- Hey sugar.
- Hi Bobby.
- How you doing, what
do you got for me?
- Johnnie Marandino
called twice.
- Ah, twice.
- Midas is in your office.
- Yes, how you doing?
- Good.
- Morning, everybody,
morning, what's
that smell (sniffs)?
I smell money, money.
Ooh, Ms. Cheryl Bennett.
- Bobby.
- You know, sometimes
I think you're too fine
to be a marketing director,
what do you say I make
you the next big R&B diva?
- So, what's the word on
the new Prolifik album?
- How about I give you three,
guaranteed smash fucking hit.
I'm expecting half a
million pre-orders today.
You know, you play
your cards right,
and I see something
very big in your future.
- They'll be pepper
spray in your future
if you don't take
your hand off my ass.
- Oh, oh.
(footsteps clumping)
(upbeat hip hop music)
(remote clatters)
I heard these beats last week,
when am I gonna hear
the completed album?
- Oh, hopefully by Christmas.
- You're telling me two months?
- At least.
- No, uh-uh,
totally fucking unacceptable.
This goddamn record
was supposed to be
mixed a week ago, Midas.
- Bobby, I'm trying man,
but all I get is one or
two takes out of him,
then he's all getting
blunted with his boys, man,
yesterday, he
didn't even show up.
Look, Bobby, man, I know
you think this Prolifik had
something special, man,
but if you asked me.
- Hey, I didn't ask you.
He's got the number
one rap single
in the fuckin' country, man,
it's obvious this
guy's got the goods.
- Oh man, I'm trying
everything I can, dude.
- Try harder!
This guy, he's a little rough
around the edges, you know,
he's like an uncut diamond,
you need to take him and
shape him and polish him.
You wanna coax the
talent outta him.
- (laughs) You know, man,
Prolifik ain't down
to being coaxed.
Man, the other day asked
him to retake a verse over,
then he threw a 40 at me.
(phone beeps)
- [Jessica] Bobby,
call on line two.
- I'm fucking busy!
- [Jessica] It's
Johnnie Marandino.
- Oh, fuck me.
(Bobby exhales)
Hey, Dino, what's up.
- [Dino] Bobby, what the
fuck is going on here?
So, I know I've been calling you
and you haven't
returned my call.
(upbeat hip hop music)
(zipper grinds)
(footsteps clumping)
(upbeat hip hop music)
- Erik, what are you
doing at my desk?
- Just downloading my latest
work for your approval,
check this one out.
- Erik, you're insane,
no one told you to
snipe the art museum.
- City of Philadelphia
may call it vandalism,
I like to call it
artist promotion.
- Yeah, well, I don't wanna be
getting any more fines, okay,
so, just stick to
telephone poles.
(computer beeps)
(faint upbeat music)
Damn, Erik, you covered
a lot of ground.
- Took me most of the night but
for Prolifik, it's
worth it.
Now, you think you
could hook me up
on an advanced copy
of his new album?
- It's not done yet,
but when it is, you'll
be the first to get one.
Oh, that reminds me,
we printed up some posters
for the show Prolifik
is doing at Club Mecca,
do you think you can
throw some up tonight?
- No problem,
I'll just do the other
side of the art museum.
- That's not funny, Erik.
(Erik laughs)
Just stay here, I'll
see if they came in.
- All right.
(footsteps clumping)
(Erik sighs)
- [Receptionist] Ill Wax
Records, please hold.
- Hey yo, I'm gonna
talk to Starr.
- [Receptionist] Do you
have an appointment?
- Fuck an appointment,
tell him I wanna talk now.
- You're late boo,
they got your picture all up
on the motherfucking wall.
- Bobby.
Clarence Ubanks.
(Prolific scoffs)
I mean, Prolifik.
He's here.
- [Bobby] I'm fucking busy.
- Okay, Bobby.
He's in a meeting right now,
you could try back after lunch.
(footsteps clumping)
(faint upbeat music)
- Look, I'm telling you,
we're sitting on a
fucking gold mine here.
Yeah, look, I know it's taking
a little bit longer
than I said it would,
but I just saw Midas this
morning and he assured
me that
the record will be
done in a few days.
Yeah, okay, great.
Hey look, let me go,
you tell that beautiful
wife of yours I said, Hey.
Speaking of the man, Prolifik,
I'm glad you're here,
we gotta discuss a few things.
- You damn right, we do,
it's time for you
to cut me another
motherfucking check, Starr,
I ain't have no cash since
I signed this fucking deal.
Fuck you looking at, man?
- Whoa, Prolifik,
chill out, man.
We paid you a nice
healthy advance
with the second payment
due upon delivery of an
album, remember?
Album, yeah.
- That shit should have been
done a long time ago, man,
I did that track over like 50
times for this
nigga here.
- Whoa, whoa,
whoa, man, we'll record that
shit over a hundred times
if that's what it
takes to get it right,
and I don't know,
maybe you can remember
your own damn lyrics.
- Lyrics?
Lyrics ain't the problem,
you're just a whack
ass bitch,
like garbage.
- Okay, man.
Fuck this, man, I can't
work with this hoodlum.
- Hoodlum?
Who the fuck do you think
you're talking to, man?
- What, what?
- Whoa, whoa, whoa,
hey, break that
up, break that up.
- I'm a professional, man.
(all speaking)
- That's enough! - Get your
hands off
me, man!
- Back up.
- Shut the fuck up.
- Hey, Prolifik, you got a
beef about your payments,
then I suggest you take another
look at the contract,
that is, if you ever
bothered to read it
in the first fucking place.
I swear to Christ every time
one of these hood rats
gets a record deal,
you'd think they'd
won the lotto.
You have no understanding
of the intricate process.
- Intricate process?
The fuck is you talking about?
That's some intricate bullshit,
Starr, you know
it, man.
Fuck that, man, maybe it's true
what they said
about you,
maybe you're some type of
fancy talking con artist
or some bullshit.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa,
hey, Clarence,
I was creating hits
back when you were hustling
rocks on the corner.
(footsteps clumping)
You know, it's time
for you, Clarence,
to step up and deliver,
so, if I were you,
I would just do
the Harlem shuffle
right out this fucking office
and right over to the Hit
Palace, move in if
you have to,
because if I don't have
the completed album
on this desk but in
one fucking week,
you're history, are
we clear, Clarence?
Hmm?
- Fuck you, man, come on.
(upbeat hip hop music)
Made this damn label,
man, fuck you looking at?
Speech, man.
- [JD] I told you to do
this shit the old way,
now, this nigga telling
you to move into studio,
what kind of shit is that?
Meet public enemy number one
Five-O said freeze
(paper rustling)
(faint hip hop music)
- (sighs) Here you go.
- Cool, cool, cool.
Check you later, Cheryl.
- All right, stay outta trouble.
- Can't make any promises.
(Cheryl chuckles)
- [Prolifik] This nigga, Starr,
was a sheisty motherfucker,
man, I knew it.
- [JD] That nigga would have
been talking to me like that.
- [Prolifik] I should have
got more money upfront, man.
- [JD] Told you that,
man, told you that.
- You'd be talking a
lot of shit, you know.
Fuck is you looking at?
- Nothing.
It's just I'm your number
one fan, that's all.
- Word.
Man, a year ago I was taping
your tracks off
the BSTs
up and coming show,"
now, here I am throwing up
snipes for your new album.
- Fuck, for sure?
That's your work?
- No doubt.
- You've be doing
all right, man.
I've been seeing my shit
up like all over the place.
- Know, you think you
could sign one of these?
- Yeah, no doubt, no doubt.
Yo, light this shit, man.
- Please, man.
- The fuck is this?
- You know you're the
realest MC out here.
- Thanks man.
Yo, call that nigga
or something, man.
So, from Prolifik
to Snipes, (laughs)
word, man, thanks.
- Take it easy.
- All right,
I can't wait for your
new album to drop.
- Thanks, neither can
I dude, neither can I.
- Where did you go?
- Fuck!
Fuck took you so long, man?
Fuck was you doing?
(soft serene music)
- [Sway] Yeah, yeah, let's
do this Philadelphia,
it's your man, Sway, on WBST,
keeping you locked and loaded.
We gonna keep it
really dirty right now,
send this special request
out to the thugs hanging
out at the power plant,
it's Ram Squad, "Ruff, Rugged
& Raw" like we
do, WBST.
How many niggas living
ruff rugged and raw
- Yeah, yeah.
Triggs, I've been
looking for you.
- What's up, Bugsy.
- I've been seeing that
Prolifik shit everywhere
I go,
been busy, huh?
- No doubt.
In fact, Prolifik and I
were kicking in it today,
just tell me what a good
job I've been doing.
- What's Prolifik doing hanging
out with a punk
like you?
- What?
We hang out all the time, we're
tight, calls
me Snipes.
(laughs)
I know you've been ripping
down my snipes, Triggs.
- Yo, Malik.
Sorry.
I mean, Nino.
- Never interrupt me in the
middle of a freestyle,
you know,
it's kind of like
going up to AI,
and you're slapping
the ball out his hand.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, Mac daddy,
you need studio time, right?
- Yeah, why?
(keys chinking)
- Hit Palace, kid.
- Oh,
yeah.
(bright upbeat music)
(car engine roars)
- Now, I hope you have skills.
- I got skills.
- (laughs) We'll see.
(car doors slamming)
- You know, E,
when I get my deal,
I'm gonna buy my
grand mom a house,
I'm gonna hook up
a Lexus for myself,
and I was thinking
a black drink.
- Uh-uh?
- Oh, and I ain't
forgetting about you, dog,
you about do for a
nice whip as well now,
you know what I mean?
- All right, cool.
Yo, hold on a second,
this one's for my pops.
- Yo, get me in a
shot real quick.
- All right, go ahead.
Bend down a little bit.
- You got it?
- Yeah.
- Get another one.
- All right.
- (laughs) Yeah, you crazy, man.
- All right, cool, got it.
(tires screeching)
Damn, they out (laughs),
crazy, straight up.
- Come on.
When are you gonna
start puffing?
- When are you gonna get a job?
(faint upbeat music)
- Hold on, I gotta do this.
It's not locked.
(faint upbeat music)
- Hello?
(door squeaks)
(faint upbeat music)
- Whoa, somebody been
smoking the good shit.
(footsteps clumping)
Yo, turn the lights up,
and check if they got
any sodas up in here.
- Find your own damn sodas.
- Here's the reason why
the room is so stinky
and it's still lit.
- Come on, Malik, we're
here to work, man, damn.
(chair creaking)
(suspenseful upbeat music)
- I wonder what
kind of sampler...
(suspenseful upbeat music)
Oh, shit.
Is he dead?
(suspenseful upbeat music)
This is a joke, right?
- Shit, this ain't
no fucking joke.
- [Man] Are you
fucking kidding me?
(footsteps clumping)
(bell rings)
(bright upbeat music)
(footsteps clumping)
(bell rings)
(bright upbeat music)
It's going down,
here we ride
Take your time,
make it right
Here we fly, make it five
We can reunite
Day on the way
Spin blue blades...One on one...
- Fuck!
(car engine ignites)
- What's wrong?
- Shit, I don't know.
- Man, let's go.
- I think it's flooded.
- Come on, let's go.
- Come on.
- Shit!
- Fuck out of here.
(bright upbeat music)
(siren wailing)
- [Cartoon] You
keep out of this,
he does not have
to shoot you now.
- [Larry] I'm Larry
Minty, our top story.
a stubborn fire in
West Philadelphia
lights up the night sky.
Two vacant warehouses were
destroyed by the flames,
if it wasn't for the quick work
of Philadelphia firefighters,
it could have been
much, much worse.
Let's get the latest
now from the scene.
(footsteps clumping)
- What's up, pops?
(paper rustling)
- You up awfully
early on a Saturday,
what's the occasion?
(paper rustling)
- What's up?
- School called yesterday,
wanted to know if you were sick,
said you missed
three days this week.
- Look, pops, I have
business to take care of.
- Business?
You're 17 years old, Erik,
what kind of business would
you need to take care of?
- You know, I've been working
for the record company.
- What?
That littering they
have you doing,
you've been missing
school for that nonsense?
- It's not nonsense.
Look, this isn't a
really good time.
- Erik, this is
the perfect time.
I bought home the application.
- What application?
- You know what application?
I want you to fill it out.
I've already spoken
to my supervisor,
he said he'll see
you for an interview
as soon as you graduate.
- But I already have a job.
- What you do is not a job,
it's called screwing around.
- Forget it, I'm not
working at a post office
stooped over a desk,
sorting mail all day.
- Oh, you got it
all figured out.
You'd rather run
around the streets
with that dope fiend
buddy of yours.
- I gotta go.
- I'm going fishing this
weekend at the shore,
I'll be back Monday morning,
at which time, one of two
things is gonna happen,
either that application
is filled out
or you can pack your shit and
find another place to live.
(door clicks)
(door slams)
(bright upbeat music)
- Hey kid, where's building A?
- Over there.
- You sure?
- Yes.
- All right.
All right, come on,
come on, come on.
(footsteps clumping)
(bright upbeat music)
(car engine roars)
(Malik slurps)
(bright upbeat music)
- If you have seen
this show before,
you know how accurate and
intensive reading
with me
can be
(door knocks)
Let me tell you a
little about myself.
(door thuds)
I was born as shaman,
this is part of African, Haitian
and Jamaican culture
and spirituality.
My grandmother,
a shaman herself,
recognized the mark of
a shaman at my birth.
- Malik.
- [Woman] Traditionally
you are trained by...
- You're smoking that
reefer in the house?
- [Woman] Passed away
when I was very young,
so, I was trained by another,
my mentor, a shango priestess,
this is the life I was born.
(Malik inhales)
(door thuds)
- Malik Davis.
(Malik coughs)
Some shit weed, man (laughs).
I came across this demo
tape of yours this morning,
I thought I'd drop by.
- Are you from a record
company or something?
- Or something, yeah (chuckles).
- Okay, so, you
heard the demo tape,
it's dope, isn't it?
- Yeah.
You wanna tell me why you were
in my studio
last night?
- Your studio?
- Yeah, my studio, dog,
the Hit Palace,
you were up there last
night, weren't you?
(phone rings)
(Erik exhales)
(voicemail beeps)
- Yo, Malik, what's
up, it's me, Erik.
Listen, something really
strange is going
on around here,
it's like last night
never even happened,
you'd think it'd be
all over the place.
Right now I'm down
at the Hit Palace
and this sure as hell don't
look like no crime scene.
Look, remember what I said,
don't say nothing to nobody,
all right?
Check you later.
(voicemail beeps)
- Whoa, whoa, whoa.
- And Malik, I want those
tapes and I want them now.
- Tapes?
- Malik?
You smoking them
reefers in the house?
- Let's blow this
fucking bitch now.
- Oh, shit, Tony,
don't shoot him, I
need those tapes.
(ladder glides)
(bright upbeat music)
Get the fuck out of here, go.
- What the devil's going on?
(bright upbeat music)
(ladder glides)
(footsteps clumping)
(bright upbeat music)
(car honks)
(Malik thuds)
(tires screeching)
(car engine roars)
- Call 911.
(footsteps clumping)
- Come on, come on.
- Yo, is he dead?
- Yo, come on, come on.
- Is he dead.
- Come on, go, go.
(footsteps clumping)
(radio chatter)
- Oh, shit!
(woman sobs)
- Oh, Malik.
Oh, Malik.
- What happened?
- Hit and run, some
kid got killed.
- Oh, no, Malik.
Malik, oh, no, oh no, Malik!
(train engine roars)
(Erik sobs)
- This one's for my pops.
Get me in a shot
with it, all right.
(bright upbeat music)
- Hey, bend down a little bit.
A little bit more.
- You got it?
- Yeah.
- Take another one.
- All right.
(Erik laughs)
Hey, you crazy, man.
(tires screeching)
- Damn, they out (laughs).
(faint hip hop music)
(zipper purrs)
I ain't shitting you
You and your crew
will get done
Cut up in chunks right now
but that hits like love
Coz not everybody can
bring the war like a pun
I mean to brag,
now bring it back
I usually
But I'ma keep it
For them niggas
in the back screw
the slick talk end up a
boardwalk of the fool
Uh-uh, it ain't
goin' down like this
The you the income, they
do the N with the L shape
Uh-uh, it ain't
goin' down like this
Don't you ever forget
Uh-uh, it ain't
goin' down like this
Come on
(door bell rings)
(footsteps clumping)
(floor creaks)
- Yes.
- [Erik] Hey, Cheryl,
it's me, Erik.
- Erik?
- What are you doing here?
- I need to talk
to you, could I,
can you please open the door?
- [Cheryl] What's going on Erik?
- Cheryl, Cheryl so,
it's important, can you
please just open the door?
(door buzzing)
Hit and run my ass.
I'm telling you Cheryl,
it was no accident.
Whoever killed those people
in the studio last night
know that we saw those bodies
and now they're
covering their tracks.
They got Malik and now
they're coming for me.
- This doesn't make
any sense, Erik.
I think I would've
heard something
if there was a double homicide
at the studio
last night.
- Cheryl, I know what I saw.
- All right, I believe
you, calm down.
- No, you don't believe me,
I'm going to the police.
- And tell them what?
That some bodies disappeared?
That your friend got
hit by a car, huh?
And that someone's after you?
Erik, do you have any
idea who is after you?
- This dude right here,
can you zoom in on him?
- Okay.
(computer beeps)
- What's the matter?
- Nothing.
- Well, can you blow
him up, zoom in.
- All right.
(computer beeps)
- Oh, man,
now, he looks like a killer.
(bright upbeat music)
Cheryl, where are you going?
(footsteps clumping)
(bright upbeat music)
What's going on?
(car engine roars)
(car door slams)
(bright upbeat music)
(footsteps clumping)
(door bell rings)
(bright upbeat music)
- What's that?
- It's a 38.
- No kidding, what's it for?
- Just let me do all
the talking, okay?
(door bangs)
- Baby, who's at the door? -
I dunno, who the
hell is it?
(bright upbeat music)
(door bangs)
- Can I help you?
(bright upbeat music)
Where do you think you're going?
(footsteps clumping)
(bright upbeat music)
- Well, who is it, Lucinda?
(footsteps clumping)
Come on, girl, shit!
Cheryl, what the
fuck you doing here?
Who the fuck is he?
- Look at this.
- Oh, bitch, you better
turn your ass back around
and march out that door.
- I wanna know what happened
at the Hit Palace last night.
- Look, I don't know what
the fuck you talking about.
Lucinda, get your
ass in here woman.
Hey baby, uncuff me.
- I told you, Midas, I
ain't doing no group shit.
- Oh, that's it,
that's it, bitch,
get in the fucking bathroom,
get in the fucking bathroom.
- Hey, hey, come on.
- Get in.
- Cheryl, what
the fuck, come on,
that's not cool, Cheryl.
Dude.
- [Lucinda] Midas,
they'll force you.
(footsteps clumping)
- (stutters) Who you calling?
Cheryl, who you calling?
- Shut up!
(phone ringing)
- Cheryl, come on now.
- 911?
Yeah, I got an
emergency over here,
my boyfriend, he's
on them drugs again
and he's acting be really crazy.
- Cheryl.
- Y'all,
you better send somebody quick,
he's tearing up the place.
- Girl, come on.
- My address?
Hold on.
- Okay, okay.
God damning, hang up the phone.
(phone clicks)
Fuck!
- I'm listening.
- Somebody kidnapped Prolifik.
- What?
- You heard me,
I mean, somebody kidnapped that
little talented
nigga, why?
I have no idea.
I ain't feeling this, man.
Last night was a closed session
with strict orders from Starr,
he didn't want no posse allowed
He even posted one of
his boys in the studio
just to make sure.
About midnight, you know, we
started wrapping things up,
then outta nowhere...
- Motherfuckers.
All right motherfuckers get
your shit up, get it up!
What you looking at?
What the fuck are
you looking at?
- Now, I tried to stop it but
I got jacked from behind.
Then he takes
every fucking tape,
the whole entire
Prolifik album project,
and he even grabbed the
one off of the deck.
Now, Starr's guy
tries to be a hero
and that's when some real
wild West shit plays out.
The fuck!
No, no, stop.
(gun bangs)
(bright upbeat music)
- Get your ass up, come on.
Walk gangsta.
- I was this close
from grabbing my nine
and capped all them niggas,
but you know, I didn't
wanna endanger Prolifik.
And I called Starr, you
know, I woke his ass up
and let him know what happened.
He was like, look, don't call
the cops, I'm
on my way.
- So, then what happened?
- It's not locked.
- So, I go to the
men's room to wash up,
well, you know, I had to wash
the blood outta my Versace.
You know, about
20 minutes later,
Starr shows up with
some more of his boys,
they start dragging bodies out
and scrubbing down the wall
and patching up
holes, the whole bit,
and Starr tells me, if
I say a word to anybody,
I'm gonna be the next
body dumped in the river.
- You say a word
about this to anybody,
you're in that fucking
river, you got that?
You fucked up, get that
bullet outta the wall,
get these bodies outta
here, clean that shit up.
- Why cover it up like that?
- Are you kidding?
They'll didn't do anything
to keep Johnnie Marandino
from finding out.
- Who's Johnnie Marandino?
- [Midas] The devil incarnate.
- What the hell does
Johnnie Marandino
gotta do with all this?
- They're business partners.
I mean, he's practically
Starr's fucking uncle.
Last year when Starr was
trying to float Ill Wax,
he heard through some friends
that Marandino was looking for
a way to clean up some cash,
so, Bobby made his old uncle
Johnnie a little proposition.
- Rap music, huh?
- [Johnnie] Rap music?
- Yeah, rap.
- [Johnnie] You know
anything about rap music?
- The fuck is he gonna
know about rap music?
It's like, it's
urban, it's ghetto,
it's like, it's where
the money's at, man,
I'm telling you
there's so much money.
- Yeah and he's gone
through a ton of it,
close to a million dollars.
I mean, he was banking
on this Prolifik album
to set shit straight.
- [Lucinda] Midas, get
me the fuck out of here.
- Shut the fuck up, bitch!
- I guess you could see why
Starr don't want
the cops involved.
I mean, he's gotta find
Prolifik and them tapes
before Marandino finds out that
his investment
was jacked
by a couple of street punks.
- So, does Starr have
any idea who it was that
kidnapped Prolifik?
- Yeah, man, some dude
named Malik, something.
- What?
- Man, this stupid motherfucker
left his bag behind.
- What's that bag?
- Huh?
Had a tape with his
name and his address
printed right on it.
- That's it?
- Well, isn't that enough?
Yeah, it's everything
you wanna know.
Would you wanna
uncuff me, please?
- Let's go, Erik.
- Cheryl, why you
gotta be a punk?
Cheryl, that's not cool,
man, what are you doing?
Hey, come on, brother, help me.
Come on, help me out, man.
Cheryl!
Fuck you.
(bright upbeat music)
- We gotta go to
the cops, Cheryl.
- I don't know, Erik,
I mean, we should think
this thing through.
- What's there to think through?
- Well, first of all, you still
have no proof
of anything.
- [Erik] What about Midas?
- Oh, Midas isn't going to
repeat that story
to no cops.
(phone rings)
- Who's that?
- Oh, it's Starr.
- What's he want?
- [Cheryl] I don't know,
it's strange timing though.
- Maybe Midas got loose.
- Maybe,
we still have to finding
a place to stay tonight.
(bright upbeat music)
(footsteps clumping)
Hi, I would like a room
for the night, please.
- Okay, I'ma need a
credit card or something.
- I'm gonna go use the phone.
- Okay.
(coins glide)
(buttons chiming)
(phone ringing)
- [Voicemail] Yo, what's up,
you've reach
the Triggs,
we're not here right
now, leave us a message.
(beep)
- Pops, it's me.
I'm in some sort of...
(phone clatters)
(door lock clicks)
(Erik sighs)
Cheryl,
what are you thinking?
- Erik, there's some
people I have to go see.
- Who?
- I can't tell you,
and I have to go alone.
They don't know you, Erik, and
they don't like strangers.
- Cheryl, listen,
stay here.
(Erik sighs)
- Do you trust me?
- What do you think?
- Then let me go,
no questions asked.
If my idea doesn't work, I'll
come back and
I promise
that we'll go to the cops first
thing tomorrow morning.
Okay?
(Cheryl pecks)
I'll see you in a
couple of hours.
- Be safe.
- Yeah.
(Erik sighs)
(door slams)
- She'll be back.
(phone rings)
- Clone Motel.
Hello?
(footsteps clumping)
(upbeat suspenseful music)
(door clicks)
- Yo, wrong room, you're
in the wrong room.
(Erik grunts)
(Erik groans)
(furniture clatters)
(bright upbeat music)
(Erik grunts)
(footsteps clumping)
(Bobby whistles)
(tape tapping)
- Hmm.
Nice.
Listen closely, fucko,
we're gonna have a little
Q&A session here, all right?
Where are my tapes?
- I don't have your tapes.
Yo, you're talking
to the wrong guy.
Look, I think I saw
the guys who did it,
I had a digital camera with me.
Inside are the
pictures of the guys
you really should
be looking for.
- Did you find a camera?
- Nah, just his beeper.
- Yeah.
(fist thuds)
(Erik groans)
Now, let's try this
again, where are my tapes?
- I don't have your tapes,
me and Malik weren't
the kidnappers, you
have to believe me.
All we wanted was
some free studio time.
- Studio time?
(men laughing)
I don't believe you, cut him.
- No, no, wait, wait,
wait, wait, stop, stop.
- Oh, whoa, wait, you
got something to say now?
- I talked to Midas,
told me all about you
and Johnnie Marandino.
- What?
- Yeah, Marandino finds
out, you're dead, right?
That's why you're trying
to cover it up like this?
If he cuts me, my boy's gonna
tell Johnnie Marandino
and you gonna get fucked up.
- Get Midas on the phone, now.
You think you can threaten me?
(phone rings)
- [Lucinda] Get me
the fuck outta here.
- Shut the fuck up, woman.
(phone rings)
- He ain't home.
- Oh, that sucks.
You know, I've seen this
exact scene in a movie
like a hundred times, right?
There's always some poor
bastard's being leaned on,
that would be you,
and he's always trying
to turn the tables
on the guy who's doing the
leaning, that would be me.
So, he comes up with some bluff,
some bullshit story in hopes
of saving his
own ass,
that's what's happening
here, right, kid?
It's a bluff.
Yeah, I thought so.
(fingers snap)
- What (stutters)
get off me.
- You know, I love
movies, Triggs,
I mean, it's like my favorite
thing in the world.
I'm like a, I'm a film
buff, I'm a fanatic.
You can learn all sorts
of fucked up wrong things
by watching a movie,
remember that one?
(Erik screams)
(Bobby laughs)
- (screams) Now, I really
enjoyed your little
home movie,
the one over there
on the fucking table.
- What are you talking about?
- What am I fucking
talking about?
I'm talking about that tape
you sick fuck sent to my
office a little while ago,
that's what I'm talking about.
I mean, you can't buy publicity
like that,
you know.
I mean, we're thinking like
2 million extra in sales,
this record's gonna
be fucking huge,
so, that's why I need
those goddamn tapes.
I'm asking you one more fucking
time, where
are they?
- I told you, I swear,
I swear on my mom's
grave, I swear.
(Erik screams)
(Erik crying)
- Clean his ass up.
Shut up, you think that
was bad, that was nothing.
Now, I know you and
that genius, Malik,
didn't pull this
off by yourselves,
there was a third
person and I'm betting
he was the one
calling the shots.
So, unless you give me
a name in three seconds,
I swear to Christ, you're
gonna be pissing into a bag
for the rest of
your fucking life.
One, two...
- All right, I'll tell you.
- Give me a goddamn name!
- Nino.
(bright upbeat music)
(Erik sniffles)
Nino.
- Nino, who?
- Nino Brown.
- Nino Brown, who the
fuck is Nino Brown?
- He's the guy who put
this whole thing together,
he's got the tapes.
- Where's he at?
- I don't know.
- Wrong answer.
- I dunno where he is right now.
We always meet in
different locations, look,
he's due to call me
the next few hours.
You got my beeper, you gotta
believe me, he's gonna call.
- Kid,
I'm telling right now, if
you're bullshitting me,
I swear to Christ,
I will kill you,
and then just for the
fucking fun of it,
you know your old man,
I'm gonna chop him up into
little, itty, bitty pieces
and I'm gonna feed
him to my fucking dog.
Tie this bitch up.
- Don't touch me.
Don't touch me, get off of me.
(Erik panting)
(chair glides)
Oh, fuck.
Fucking Starr.
- Ah, Nino Brown, Nino Brown,
I fucking know that
name, Nino Brown.
- Yo, Bobby man, what
you want us to do?
- I'm thinking.
Okay, Tony, I want you to
call your peeps at Crayford,
all right, I want you to see
if you can get any information
on this criminal mastermind,
Nino fucking Brown.
Donnie, I want you
to grab a phone book,
you go online if you have to,
I want some fucking 411
on this cat, got me?
(table clatters)
(faint upbeat music)
(knife clatters)
(bright upbeat music)
- Okay.
Yo, Bobby man, we got a problem.
(bright upbeat music)
He says the only Nino
Brown he ever heard of
was this cat in a movie and
he doubts that's the
same cat you looking for.
- (chuckles) Go get that kid,
now!
(bright upbeat music)
(footsteps clumping)
- Oh, mother shit!
(bright upbeat music)
(car engine roars)
(train engine roars)
(bright upbeat music)
(Erik shivers)
(dogs barking)
(bright upbeat music)
- [Cheryl] This is Cheryl,
I'm tied up right now,
but I'll call you right
back as soon as I can,
okay, bye bye.
- Look who it is, Mr. Snipes.
Goddamn, Triggs, you're a mess.
Looks like someone tried
to chew your face off.
- Yo, who that?
- Just some punk who
thinks he's the shit.
- Yo, he looks fucked up.
- Ain't that right Mr. Snipes?
(Erik thuds)
- Yo, dog.
Oh, he's twisted, come on.
Come on.
- Come on, get up, get up.
(faint upbeat music)
(Erik sniffles)
Snipes!
Hey, you're alive.
- Where am I?
- You don't remember?
You're in my crib,
you crashed out
about 10 hours ago,
Trix wanted to take you to the
hospital but you wouldn't go.
- How's the nose?
- It hurts.
- Looks nasty, I used
super glue to close it up.
I'm saying I do piercings,
that's what we use in
case of an emergency.
- So, what happened, Triggs?
You stick that nose
somewhere it didn't belong?
- The tape, where is it?
(tape clatters)
(static glitching)
- Starr,
I want you to meet somebody,
Clarence Ubanks,
AKA Prolifik.
This punk used to be one of us,
said if he made it
in the rap game,
he'd take us out the projects
on some bling shit.
He lied, left us
the fuck behind,
don't act like you don't
remember who the fuck we are,
but the bitch won't be
able to forget us now.
So, I'm afraid he gotta go.
- Let's do it.
- What the...!
(gun bangs)
- Shit, yo, that's fucked up.
- The fuck, say something first.
See this, it's the master reel
from Prolifik's long
awaited debut album.
You can't walk 10
steps in the city
without seeing one of
those fucking posters.
Everybody's waiting
on this record,
and there no back ups.
This here reel is one of a kind.
It's hard to, you know,
put a price for
things like this, but
guaranteed platinum tracks,
they don't come cheap,
so, we figured half
a mill is fair.
This is a one time exclusive
offer from us
to you.
We'll call you later
with the details
when and where to
make the transaction
so you just gather up
the cake and sit tight.
No cops, we smell fucking Jake
and this shit goes up in flames.
- Bobby Starr thinks
you're part of this?
Look, I wouldn't normally
suggest this, Triggs,
but maybe you ought to
go talk to the cops.
- Cops can't do nothing for me.
I can't prove Starr's
done a fucking thing.
Shit.
He's got guys watching my house,
he said he's gonna chop my
pops up into little pieces
and feed him to his dog.
- Goddamn!
- And he means it.
I gotta get his
tapes back to him.
- How the hell are
you gonna do that?
(tape rewinding)
(bright upbeat music)
- I've seen this ink before.
Looks like a white guy.
This dude right here,
can you zoom in on him?
- Okay, Erik.
- You got the
"MindGames" single?
Kingsbridge crew,
fucking killed him.
- Triggs, what are you thinking?
(footsteps clumping)
Look out
Yo, I told you not to shoot
that thing
in here.
- My bad.
(faint upbeat music)
- Triggs, I'm starting to think
you might have
bad luck.
Okay, maybe you should go find
your pops before Starr does
and get the fuck away from here.
- I'm gonna go find that
dude with the tattoo.
- Triggs, you're not thinking
of going over to Kingsbridge,
are you?
You're crazy.
- I need a favor.
(suspenseful upbeat music)
- Okay, Triggs,
did some checking and I
found out a few things
about this big white
killer of yours,
you were right, he's
from Kingsbridge.
Everybody knows the guy,
he stands out like a
sore thumb over there,
he's part of the crew, hangs
out over on Ridge Avenue.
You want some advice?
Do not go looking
for this guy, Triggs,
he's bad news, man,
a complete psycho.
(bright upbeat music)
- [Sway] WBST, this is Sway,
coming up at the
top of the hour,
we got some brand
new Lela James,
Voice of Choice into shock
waves through your radio,
and speaking of big, we're
still trying to
get our hands
on some tracks from
that new Prolifik album,
"Revenge of the Intellect,"
everybody's waiting
for that one,
we'll be sure to
keep you posted.
Anyway, we're headed
for a really long day,
so, let's buckle up and
do this thing right,
send it off with
Street Nine on WBST.
(bright upbeat music)
Oh oh oh
Oh, where my tribe at,
oh, where my tribe at
Oh, where my tribe at
(car engine roars)
(footsteps clumping)
- They think they're tough.
- Well, let's show them.
(men grunting)
(karate kicks thud)
(lighter ignites)
(men grunting)
(karate kicks thud)
- [Captain] Oh, hey,
I'm the captain,
what do you want?
- [Man] Oh, I've come a
long way, just to see you.
(men grunting)
(karate kicks thud)
(soft serene music)
(dispenser glides)
(footsteps clumping)
(door creaks)
(phone ringing)
- Fuck!
What?
I'm on my way, I had to stop.
What are you doing?
You call that
motherfucker, Starr, yet?
For real?
Where's he at?
Oh, why is he talking
to her, fuck that bitch.
Yeah, you're damn right we
gotta figure something out,
but not at her house, I don't
want her all
up in this.
Right, let's hook up
at the Love Lounge.
All right,
peace.
Oh, fuck.
(tin clatters)
(sole squishing)
(soft serene music)
(gun thuds)
- Fuck, oh.
(bright upbeat music)
(men groaning)
(cover thuds)
(ceramic shutters)
Can't get fresher than this
(sings in foreign language)
(bag rustles)
(zipper purrs)
(paper rustling)
(soft serene music)
All right, let's hook
up at the Love Lounge.
(car engine roars)
(car door slams)
(bright upbeat music)
Ah
This one's for all those
Hey, if you got
a mother, sisters
You got a father, your
grandparents, your kids
Some of them died,
feel them and move on
They say this life is
only what you make it so
If they hand it down I'm only
gonna take it in the ghetto
Promises is only made to
break and never understood
Niggas only love
me when I'm naked so
Take a look into this
life I live and learn
Never judge a book by the
cover, gotta turn the page
14 turn the age
I was already learning
ways to earn this change
Playing on my bag for
a couple of stacks
Was the way for me,
mama, please pray for me
It was daily, she ain't
even know where I stay
The making through my
day was the only way
I was the only one out
of my four siblings
That gave her problems
And make her life
more different now
Everything around
me did a 360
Ride and feel good
just to sleep in now
'Cause sometimes, you
gotta right the wrong
When the nights get long
and the days are gone
- Floyd, man, why
you look so frail?
- Chill.
- Shit is ill right now.
- I know, man, Floyd, relax.
Relax, cuz, all right?
- [Floyd] Yeah,
I'm chilling, but I'm saying,
shit ain't going right
and I ain't gonna relax.
- [JD] Why ain't going
right, we got everything?
- [Floyd] Trying to
pay you money back,
but dude said he ain't
taking the money.
- Look, he gonna pay, chill.
- I'm fucking going worry.
Man, I told you a half a mil
was too much to be asking.
Yo, maybe if you
drop that shit down
like a quarter of a mil.
- You don't huggle with
no ransom, you idiot,
this ain't no auction.
- Yo, but the man
says he ain't paying.
- He gonna pay, he just
stalling, yo, damn.
- Oh, you fucking know the
whole, I guess you know.
- Where Ceaser at, man?
- You know, JD knows
what the fuck is going on.
- You know what JD know? - Know
what the fuck
going on.
- JD know Bobby Starrs
a reject gangster.
- All right, maybe Starr's
- Relax, chill, all right,
Look at shawty up there, she
got the fatty fatty
banger ass.
- [Floyd] Right, right.
- Go tip or something, dog.
- [Floyd] No, I'm just,
just fucking calling.
Shit ain't going right,
I ain't gonna relax.
- He ain't picking up the phone.
- [Floyd] You using
the words, don't worry,
and I'm saying,
nigga I'm a worry
about the shit, you
know what I mean?
I mean.
- Stop bitching, man,
now you bitching, man.
- It's just stressful man.
Look, man, I'm gonna wait yet.
- Shit is stressful, man,
this shit, all right?
- Stop smoking so
much fucking weed.
- [Floyd] Man, it ain't
that, man, it ain't.
Bad habits will
hold you back
Pick up a book instead
of holding crack
(phone rings)
Oh, boy, thank God, yo.
- What up?
- JD?
- Who this?
- I got your tapes.
- What you mean you got,
who the fuck is this?
- I said I got your tapes
and I'm onto you assholes,
you, Caesar and
Floyd, you going down.
- Yo, what the fuck you mean
you got tapes, who is this?
- Hello, hello?
Some dudes talking
about, he got the tapes.
-Hey, they got the fucking riffs
What do you mean
he got the tapes?
(bright upbeat music)
(footsteps clumping)
(door slams)
(car engine roars)
(tires screeching)
(bright upbeat music)
(car engine roars)
- [Sway] All right,
Philadelphia, it's
your boy Sway,
man, it's been a long day,
coming to the end of
a double shift, woo,
but let's do the damn thing.
This next one is a
BFT up and comer.
(car engine roars)
(bright upbeat music)
(doors slamming)
(door creaks)
(door slamming)
(dog barks)
(footsteps clumping)
- Yo, are the tapes still there?
- Yeah, the tapes
are still there.
Look, man, lower
your voice, damn.
Don't tell nobody about that
phone call either, all right,
shit is tense enough
around here as it is.
- Who you think it
was that called us?
- I don't know man, but
he knew all our names,
me, you and Caesar.
- My name?
No shit, if Bobby
Starr know who you are,
he gonna kill us all.
- Shut the fuck up, Floyd,
we got the tapes, all right,
homes, we hold the tapes,
we hold the cards.
(door creaks)
(soft suspenseful music)
(door slams)
(footsteps clumping)
(indistinct chatter)
What, yeah.
Ceaser, where you been, dog?
What happened to your head?
- I got jumped.
- [JD] By who?
- I don't know, he robbed me.
- Oh, he robbed you, huh?
Who the hell would
wanna rob your fat ass?
Yo, back up, back up.
- Chill, damn, big man.
- All I'm saying is that the
shit ain't made
no sense
and neither does
that phone call, man,
yo, you're not feeling me, dog,
somebody is fucking after
us. - What phone call?
What the fuck is
he talking about?
- [JD] Man, you're just being
paranoid and shit, Floyd,
calm your ass down, man.
(indistinct chatter)
(soft suspenseful music)
(gun clatters)
(zipper purrs)
(bag rustles)
(footsteps clumping)
(soft suspenseful music)
- Why you got her ass
locked upstairs,
what kind of stupid
shit is that?
- [JD] Yo, so she don't
go  to Starr
and talk
and she ain't going nowhere
till we have it, this bitch.
- No shit, why don't we
just smoke the bitch?
- [Floyd] Look, hold on, man,
ain't nobody laying
a finger on Cheryl,
she ain't got nothing
to do with this.
- She got everything
to do with this, man.
She was down from
the door, right,
then she wanna come in here
screaming and yelling and,
hell no.
- Bitch is just jealous
'cause she ain't getting
a cut of the ransom.
- Mm-hmm, Floyd, dog, she know
everything, she
gotta go.
- Once we get our loot,
we gonna have to
silence her permanently.
- I mean, come on, Jay, I
mean, I know this nigga
but come on, man, how
long we known this girl?
What, you gonna take her life?
No, no, Jay, what, you gonna
take her life, I'm saying.
- Floyd, it ain't
nothing personal,
strictly business.
- Yeah, man, strictly business.
(glasses chinking)
- No Kingsbridge nigga.
put that fucking gun away.
- Kingsbridge nigga.
- [Ceaser] Put your
gun down, Floyd.
(soft suspenseful music)
(floor creaks)
(epic suspenseful music)
(bright upbeat music)
(footsteps clumping)
(urine burbles)
(man groans)
(toilet flushing)
- [Man] Yo, Clarence?
- Yo.
(footsteps clumping)
(soft suspenseful music)
(Cheryl grunts)
(bright upbeat music)
(footsteps clumping)
- Yo, Starr should have
called by now, man,
that's what I'm saying.
He fronting like he
don't want these tapes
when you know he do.
(footsteps clumping)
(bright upbeat music)
- Fuck, yo.
- Where's the gun?
- Yeah, right there.
- What do we do with this guy?
- He's coming with us.
- Let's go.
- What the fuck?
(bright upbeat music)
- Let's go, come on, come on.
- What, y'all gonna
kidnap me now?
- Get moving.
- Damn.
- Open the door, Cheryl,
get in the middle.
- All right, yo,
you ain't gotta poke, you
ain't gotta fucking poke,
you ain't gotta poke.
- Get the fuck in.
- Fuck!
Come on, man.
(car engine roars)
- Cheryl, where are we going?
Come on, y'all, what's going on,
y'all not gonna
kill me, are you?
'Cause yo, I swear to God,
that was JD and Ceaser,
they was the ones that
was gonna kill you, yo,
but I wasn't gonna
let 'em, I was like.
- Shut your mouth, Floyd!
- Don't fucking talk, man.
- He's annoying but harmless.
Erik, what happened
to your nose?
- Present from Bobby Starr.
- Yo, listen, y'all
can let me off
right at this block right here,
I swear to God, I
swear to God, I'm cool.
Because kidnap ransom shit show,
yo, I ain't cut out for this.
(tires screeching)
- Shut the fuck up, Floyd.
- I saw Prolifik
back at the hideout.
I saw a tape of
him being killed,
but he was alive,
what's up with that?
- Yo, yo, it's Clarence that
came up with the whole plan,
all right, kidnap himself,
fake his own death
and bail out on a whole
fucked up situation.
He was gonna get Bobby Starr
for half a mil and disappear.
-Not without these,
he ain't..
- Yo, kid, I'm telling you, you
better take them
tapes back,
you don't wanna get
mixed up in all this.
- I'm already mixed up in it,
these tapes are my
fucking way out.
I don't get it,
this record was gonna
make Prolifik a superstar,
why would he pull
something like this?
Why would he pull
(door creaks)
(door slams)
Cheryl, I need some answers.
- You sure you wanna the
truth about your hero?
- He ain't no hero
to me, not anymore.
- "Mindgames," "Mindgames"
what an appropriate
title for his album.
His whole bullshit career was
one big fucking
mind game.
- What are you talking about?
(twigs snapping)
- Yo, listen, if y'all
got shit to discuss,
I could be on my way.
- (sighs) This is
very complicated.
I grew up in the Cambridge
project, it's all
right, Erik,
(bright upbeat music)
right next door to Clarence.
There was this thing between us,
but my family moved
out when I was 15
and he and I, we lost touch,
and about a year ago, fate just
started messing
with me.
(bright upbeat music)
I couldn't believe it was him.
We started catching up and I
wanted so much to impress him.
I'm in the record
business, okay?
Told him I just need to
make my first big discovery
and then I'd be on my way.
Clarence laughed, said
he was managing this MC,
his cousin, Damon, who was
going by the name
of Prolifik
and that he had had a
demo that was the bomb.
He played it for me
that night in his car.
The tracks were incredible.
This kid just had
this flow, this style,
that was just totally unique.
The next day I brought
the tape to Bobby Starr,
well, he flipped out.
- This kid's fucking
amazing, okay.
- He tells me to set up the
meeting as soon as possible
to do the deal and
if it goes well,
I'll get points on the project,
a bonus, a promotion,
everything.
- Oh, fuck, yo!
- Damon!
- [Cheryl] Well, Damon never
made it to that meeting.
- Oh, shit, Damon. - He's
kill the night before.
Clarence called me at home
sounding all broken up.
Hello, hey Clarence,
and I was about to call  Bobby
Starr with the
bad news
when he hit me with
this crazy idea.
You see, Starr had never seen
so much as a
photograph of Damon,
so, he had no idea what
Prolifik looked like.
- I know all his rhymes,
I know all his rhymes,
I was there in the
studio when he did,
I know the whole
album, I can do this.
- Clarence said he
could play the part,
he could be Prolifik.
He couldn't rhyme or write
lyrics as well as Damon but
he could imitate his style.
I thought this is insane,
I mean, how could we
possibly get away with it?
But of course, Clarence had
another way of looking at it,
how could we turn our
backs on a six figure deal?
He gave me a long
speech about family
and how he was gonna take
care of Damon's sick mother,
Clarence could always turn
on the charm when he had to.
- And now I even get to
take care of you still.
- Oh, yeah?
- Sure.
(bright upbeat music)
- So, I agreed to the plan.
He signed the deal, we
split the advance money,
Bobby Starr put out the EP
and the "Mindgames"
single blew up,
and just like that,
Clarence was a rap star.
In no time at all, he was
believing his own hype,
as far as he was
concerned, he was a star.
Of course, Clarence pissed away
his half of the advance money,
the studio sessions
kept dragging on
and everyone was
wondering, you know,
what was wrong with Prolifik?
How come he couldn't
get it done?
- Man, that's it, man, fuck
you man, that is it, man.
- So, he and his boys came
up with this kidnap plot,
ransom the master reels back
to Starr for half a million
and fake his own death.
He could disappear with the loot
and get Bobby
Starr off his back.
They never told me, I would've
never allowed it to happen.
Once I found out about
Johnnie Marandino,
I knew this whole ransom scheme
was headed for disaster.
They're gonna get
themselves killed
and my involvement in this
whole thing is gonna
come out.
(bright upbeat music)
(car engine roars)
(doors slam)
(bright upbeat music)
- Don't kidnap me.
- What the fuck is this?
- I didn't put this shit on.
- Fuck is it remote at, man?
- Yo, the fuck you doing,
hid the remote too?
- Shouldn't we check on Cheryl?
- She'll be all right,
fucking leave her up there.
- You think Starr
gonna call soon?
- He should be
calling any minute.
It's about that time
any fucking way.
(phone rings)
- All right.
- Told you.
- Yo, who this?
- Yo, yo, JD, it's me, Floyd.
- Floyd, where the fuck you at?
- Yo, listen to me, dog,
Cheryl and some kid, they
snatched the tapes,
all right,
and ain't no prank this time,
they grabbed them out the
house about an hour ago
and they got my ass hostage.
- What?
What the, what?
- [Floyd] Yo, yo, just
go check, just go check,
they took them, JD.
- What the fuck is
Floyd talking about?
- He talking about
the reels ain't here.
- The fuck he mean
the tapes ain't here.
- Yo, what the fuck are you
talking about, Floyd, man?
- Go down there and see if
the tapes down there, man.
- You listen to me, yo,
they had me tied up y'all
but you know me,
dog, I busted loose.
- [JD] Busted loose?
- Yo, yo, I think
I hear them coming,
hold up, hold up, hold up.
- Floyd.
Floyd, what is you
talking about, man,
what's going on?
- They're not in there.
- What?
- The fuck you mean
they ain't there?
- Not fucking there.
- Man, come on, I don't
think it's gonna work.
- Oh, it's gonna work 'cause
you're gonna convince them.
- Walk your ass back down them
steps and check again, man.
- Yo, just listen to me, dog.
- Hurry the
fuck up,
what the fuck is
you talking about?
Get the fuck out of here.
- Jay, are you there, Jay,
listen to me, dog, listen to me.
Cheryl, some kid, they cut
their own deal with
Bobby Starr,
they're meeting
three hours from now
to sell the shit back to him.
- Where, where?
- It's over at the
old power plant
on the corner of
Delaware and Belgrave.
- Yo man, this
better be no joke.
- Oh, shit, yo yo,
I gotta go, peace.
- Yeah.
- They're still
not fucking there.
Yo, we got business to handle,
we got business
to handle.
- Fuck man.
- This nigga telling...
(all speaking)
- Was that your,
y'all like that?
- That wasn't bad.
You think they'll show up?
- Oh, hell, yeah.
- All right.
I just hope this works.
Floyd, give me a
mic check right now.
It's all right.
- Mic check, one,
mic check two,
pimp daddy Floyd and
his Kingsbridge crew.
- All right, that's
enough, Floyd.
(equipment clatters)
(phone beeping)
(phone rings)
(glass clatters)
- What?
- Hey Bobby, you
ready to do this?
- Who's this?
- It's the kid with
the bloody nose.
- Whoa, where are
you little fucker.
- Oh, Bobby, I got
your precious tapes.
- What?
- I wanna give you back the
masters to the Prolifik album.
- Oh, okay, now we're
thinking, that's smart.
- For the super discount
price of $200,000.
- What, you little fucking shit.
- We'll make the transaction
three hours
from now,
there's an old power plant on
a corner Delaware and Belgrave
meet me there at 7:00 AM, sharp.
- Power plant Delaware and
Belgrave in three hours.
Okay, got it.
Kid, you better fucking pray
I never find your old man.
- Oh, aren't you forgetting
about Johnnie Marandino?
He's not gonna be too happy
if I tell him that
Prolifik's dead.
- Well, kid, I told you before,
right, don't threaten me,
I ain't afraid of Marandino,
that Guinea cock sucker has
got nothing to do with this,
Bobby Starr don't answer no one,
this matter's
between you and me.
- But what about the way
you've been spending
Marandino's dough?
Like the $20,000 you dropped
taking those two
strippers to Hawaii,
or what about that new Mercedes
you just bought on
the company dime?
- Oh, did Midas tell you that
because he's full
of shit.
- But I gotta say you topped
yourself with that little
19 year old girl daughter
of Johnnie Marandino,
you know, the one he wanted
you to demo as a singer,
must have been hard for her
to get more singing done
with your dick in her
mouth the whole time.
- Well, motherfucker, you
ever repeat that, I swear.
- Meet me at seven,
don't be late.
- That was nice, Erik.
- That was good.
Hey kid, that was good.
- Real nice.
- Hello?
Hello.
Fuck, just a little fucking kid.
Where's my gun, you got my gun?
- [Man] There you go, did
you do hit the number?
- Yeah.
(indistinct chatter)
(chips chinking)
- Take three.
(paper rustling)
- Jesus Christ!
- [Bobby] I ain't
afraid of Marandino,
that Guinea cock suckers got
nothing to do
with this,
all right, Bobby Starr
don't answer to no one.
(bright upbeat music)
- Nothing yet.
- [Cheryl] Keep
an eye out, Erik,
I just saw Starr's car go by.
- Hold on.
He's here.
(bright upbeat music)
When we enter up on the
dance everybody bang
Bitches shaking their glass
fast, everybody
bang
Niggas getting their money
all when you put
it bang
Baby how you get
paid, bang, bang, bang
- Where the fuck are they?
(bright upbeat music)
(car engine roars)
Smell like I had a few beers
Every time we
- Here comes to
Kingsbridge crew.
(bright upbeat music)
- Nobody shoots til I see
these tape, you got it, huh?
- Hand over the fucking money.
- Where the fuck's Triggs?
- Hey dude, who
the fuck's Triggs?
- I don't know no
fucking Triggs.
- Look, man, just give
us the goddamn bag
with the money in it,
you get your tapes and we
get the fuck outta here.
- Tony, grab the money.
- Yo Bobby, you might wanna
check over there first.
- What the fuck?
(bright upbeat music)
(Erik laughs)
- They see him.
- What's he saying?
- Whoa, whoa, whoa,
it looks like my tapes
are right over here
you little pieces
of shit (laughs).
- What the fuck?
- How the fuck did
they get over there?
- Donnie, grab
those fucking tapes.
Grab those fucking tapes now!
(bright upbeat music)
Go, move it, come on, hurry up.
Niggas scream my M16's got
- Yo, big man, you better
freeze your ass right there.
- That's a bad idea, Starr.
- Watch my back.
- I got your back,
just pick up the
fucking tapes, hurry up.
- I'm warning you, Bobby.
- Fuck you,
pick up those fucking tapes.
- Don't touch them
fucking tapes.
- Fuck you.
- Come on,
you fat piece of shit,
pick up the fucking tapes.
- Back the fuck up! - Put
down the fucking tapes.
- Shut the fuck up,
pick them up, now.
- Starr, I'm not fucking
telling you again.
(bright upbeat music)
(gun bangs)
- Shit!
- Fuck!
- You see that?
I told you this ain’t
no game.
- Erik?
Erik, are you okay?
- [Erik] Hold on.
- Fuck did that come from?
- You wanna fuck with
Ceaser, motherfucker?
- Donnie, you hit?
- I don't think so, there's
a fucking sniper up there.
- You know, I see him, I see
him, we got you covered.
- Erik, are you okay?
- It's Prolifik,
he on a building
shooting at Starr.
(bright upbeat music)
- There's your
last chance, Starr,
give us the goddamn money.
- The last chance for
you to go fuck yourself.
- Fuck you, Starr, look, I'm
telling you, I'm warning you.
- Pick up the
fucking tapes, now.
(bright upbeat music)
(gun bangs)
- Donnie!
(tapes clattering)
- Oh, shit!
- What?
(gun bangs)
(bright upbeat music)
- Erik?
Erik (sobs).
- Oh, shit.
- Erik, are you okay?
(bright upbeat music)
(gun bangs)
- Fuck you, punk.
(man grunts)
(bright upbeat music)
(gun bangs)
- Oh, shit, motherfucker.
(bright upbeat music)
(gun bangs)
What the fuck, little bitch.
What, what, what.
(bright upbeat music)
(gun bangs)
(metal clangs)
- [Cheryl] Erik?
(gun bangs)
(bright upbeat music)
(Ceaser groans)
(gun bangs)
(bright upbeat music)
- Fuck, Cheryl.
He's heading out, Cheryl.
Cheryl, Prolifik's heading out.
(bright upbeat music)
- Erik, Erik,
you're breaking up.
(bright upbeat music)
- Tony, grab those tapes.
- What?
- Go.
(bright upbeat music)
(gun bangs)
(Tony grunts)
Ah, fuck!
(gun bangs)
- Cheryl,
Cheryl, can you hear me?
Cheryl?
- Erik?
Erik?
- Cheryl?
- Oh, fuck, it's him.
Marandino just rolled up.
- Get the fuck.
(birds cawing)
Oh,
fuck!
The fuck is he doing here, shit?
Hey Dino.
I mean Mr. Marandino,
what are you doing here?
- What are you doing there?
Get up.
- Yeah.
- What's with all
the dead people?
- That's rather
complicated, actually.
- It's rather complicated?
- Yeah.
(palm slaps)
Fuck.
- Where's my investment, Bobby?
Oh, is it over there
lying on the ground?
- Erik, Erik, Erik,
the phone's dead,
the phone's dead.
(footsteps clumping)
- You lied to me, you
pissed away my money
and now you let some
fucking street punks
kill your big rap star.
- What? Who told you that?
- Oh, a little fucking
birdie told me that.
- Erik, Erik?
Something ain't right.
(gun bangs)
Oh, my God, oh my God.
- [Prolifik] You miss me?
(bright upbeat music)
- Oh, my God.
Someone help me, oh, my God.
- Shut the fuck up
and drive, bitch.
(Cheryl crying)
(bright upbeat music)
(car engine roars)
- Stop, stop, stop it.
Get out.
(bright upbeat music)
Sorry.
(car engine roars)
(bright upbeat music)
(tires screeching)
- Okay, look,
Dino, it's all good.
- Oh, it's all good?
- Yeah.
- Oh, terrific. - Yeah,
no, it's good because
you gotta understand
this rap game, you know,
and this cat Prolifik, he's
worth more to us now dead
than he was alive,
I mean, and now,
the record's gonna
get like a great buzz
and we can hype
this motherfucker.
- Yeah, you're fucking
stuttering, Bobby.
You know, you let me down.
- Yeah, but Dino,
we're family, right?
- You shouldn't have fucked
my sweet little Gina, Bobby.
That's not what I meant
when I asked you to teach her
something about the business.
Let's go for a little ride.
- Oh yeah?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- Jump in the front there, Bob.
(bright upbeat music)
(Prolifik mumbles)
- No, no, no. - Get your
hands off
of that.
- No, come on, please.
(bright upbeat music)
(door slams)
(Cheryl sobs)
No (crying)!
- Walk.
(bright upbeat music)
- Can we just please
think about this?
- Fuck your ass.
- I can help you, all right?
I can talk to Marandino,
all right, please.
- No need, he already think
I'm dead anyway, so fuck it.
- Please, Clarence, just...
- (striking) Shut up, man.
Get your motherfucking
ass down them steps.
You gonna pay for
selling me out.
(Cheryl groans)
(Prolific mumbles)
(Prolific thuds)
(gun clatters)
(car engine roars)
- Come on, come on, move, move.
(bright upbeat music)
(Prolifik groans)
(groaning)
(bright upbeat music)
(car engine roars)
(tires screeching)
(door slams)
(footsteps clumping)
(gun bangs)
(Erik screams)
- Cheryl.
(footsteps clumping)
Cheryl.
- Erik.
- Cheryl, are you okay?
- I'm so sorry (sobs),
I didn't want you to get hurt.
- Don't worry,
Cheryl, I'm not hurt,
everything's okay.
- It's okay.
- Listen, we gotta get
you outta here.
Oh, shit, Cheryl,
you're bleeding.
Fuck!
Cheryl?
I get money, say the bitch don't
wake up.
Oh, shit.
If it ain't my number
one fan, Mr. Snipes.
Can't say I'm not
happy to see you, though.
I'ma need your help
getting out this shit hole.
What?
What you think about shooting?
Get the fuck out of here nigga,
you not no fucking gangster.
You ain't gonna be Snipes,
that's what you do.
You're worse than a
motherfucking groupie.
Groupie, slide that
motherfucking gun
over here before I
fuck you up like I did that
two timing bitch over there.
Slide it over, nigga.
- Fuck you!
(gun cocks)
Stop!
Don't, don't, stop,
stop, stop, stop,
stop, stop!
(gun bangs)
(gun taps)
- More now on the kidnapping
and brutal murder
of a popular
Philadelphia musician.
25 year old Clarence Ubanks
known in the world of
hiphop music as Prolifik
was found shot to death
in a north
Philadelphia basement.
Police now say they have a
videotape of the killing.
The tape was
delivered anonymously
and is said to show the
gruesome details of
Ubanks's murder
- Hey Erik, did you hear
about the hero rap star?
It sounds like he
got himself shot.
- [Anchor] Saying it is
a key piece of evidence.
- Yeah, I heard about that.
How's that application
coming along?
- [Anchor] To finding
Ubank's killer.
- I'm working on it.
- [Mr. Triggs] By the
end of today, Erik.
(soft serene music)
(bright upbeat music)
- What's up, Snipes?
(footsteps clumping)
- Hey Bugsy.
Hey, call me Triggs, all right?
- Okay, Triggs,
I see you made it out that
situation in one piece
and I heard what
happen to Bobby Starr.
I guess he ain't gonna be
messing with you
no more, huh?
- Guess not.
- And those masters
are still missing, huh?
- Yeah, I don't think
they'll ever find those.
- It's a real shame
to be with a fortune,
that album will go mega
platinum, everyone
will buy it.
- You don't think so?
- Hell, yeah,
everyone wants to hear
what Prolifik had to say,
those tapes could
be his legacy, man.
Out with the old
and in with the new.
(paper rustling)
That's the thing about Snipes,
Triggs, they're temporary.
- Guess I never
saw it like that.
- You know, Fish just quit,
you think you can
give us a hand?
- Nah, man, I got
something to do.
- Okay, you should be good.
- You too.
- You know you still the
second best to Philly.
- Thanks man see you.
(bright upbeat music)
(water splashing)
- [Sway] WBST, this
is your man, Sway,
and like all of you,
Philadelphia, still
in mourning,
hoping to keep the memory
of our man Prolifik alive,
may he rest in peace,
but let's pour out a
little liquor for Prolifik
and all our lost loved ones,
here's some new music that
might help uplift
your spirits.
Remember, hold your head
up and keep it righteous,
it's WBST.
I done done a lot of fast
shit and I got to
live with
it
I ain't got nothing but
love no, I'm give with it
Life is strange, the
fact he saw tight bug
Remember Mike, he was hands
Til he got touched
by them slugs
Playing with them thugs
gotta learn like a brother
It's not a good sight to see
a cat catching in his mom
Profiles open,
Cs before chain
Both eyes closed, we met
death felt the flames
We all feel the pain
I'm seeing a lot
of cats can't bear
And they catching buckets of
noise across the face where
To the grave scar for life
For running his lips instead
of busting his
clips
He'd rather talk shit
and got sprayed out
For them chips and
bricks, it got laid out
Beat taught today, didn't
know she was played out
Young and naive, blind to
these streets that we walk
This kindness and weakness
that got 'em outline to talk
It's the destiny,
destiny, destiny
Better be ready for
the fight of your life
Destiny, destiny, destiny
Y'all know the answer
We're leveling down
I ain't seen none
of the rainy days
And when pat got
shot, it killed me
Like the slugs he got
hit with filled me
With nothing but stress
Eating holes
through the brain
Love life but can't live
another day in this game
Calling it quits, packed
my bags, gotta run
Kiss my honey
and rode around
And explained
my story to son
Daddy wasn't a good guy when
he was on these
streets
Ran with thugs, sold drugs
and carried around heat
I was young living fast,
it was all about the cash
And who could finish first
I wasn't trying to be the
last but the past caught up
And it went in for the kill
When I thought it was all good
things started getting hell
We made a turn for the worst,
I'm I blessed with
a curse
My destiny to be young
laying in the hearse
Face that and I
dwelled in the sorrow
I was the type to
chase that never dealt
with the tomorrow
It's your destiny,
destiny, destiny
You better be ready for
the fight of your life
It's your destiny,
destiny, destiny
No one knows the answer,
we live or we die
I wish that most my peeps
in jail could post bail
Wish that most
of my brothers
Didn't walk
through this hell
Wish on the started rising
the east sets in the west
To my friends,
I wish them love
To my foes wish
them the best
Life's a test, I'ma pass this
class with a straight
Leaving earth on two feet
ascending to heaven straight
I see that must suffer
in order for you to learn
Whether God or the devil,
good or bad, we all
gonna burn
I got one life to give and
I'm running chasing death
Gunning, I get to heaven when
I catch my last
breath
Seen where all my faith
went, my love, my glory
When my father opened a book
My life was written
in the story
Stated you gonna go
through the good times
Along with the bad
You gonna see
the great times
When you're confused
and you're sad
The one that turned
your frown to a smile
And makes you glad
Physically man with your
father's spirit,
I'm your
dad
It's your destiny,
destiny, destiny
You better be ready for
the fight of your life
Destiny, destiny, destiny
No one knows the answer,
we live or we die
Your destiny, you determine
what you want
it to
be
It's your destiny,
your destiny
You determine what
you want it to be
(music fades)