Good morning!
Anyone else here yet?
It's 7:00 am.
I thought the Christmas luncheon
didn't start until lunch.
Well, the early bird
gets the fresh coffee.
Can we help you
with anything?
Oh no. It's ok,
I got it.
Good morning.
mm. Cold coffee,
my favorite.
Do you also have lumpy biscuits
or some very stale crisps?
You will take the caffeine
and you will like it.
Are you going home
for Christmas?
So my mum can badger me
about settling down
whilst my cousins play dodgeball
with minced pies?
No thanks.
I'm headed for Barbados.
What about you?
Back to coyote creek.
My parents run the local inn and
every year they host a big event
the day before Christmas eve.
Last year it was the festival
of lights,
the year before that it was
a Christy Christmas.
Agatha Christy!
A murder mystery party.
Sounds like the type of thing
that'd look killer
in your portfolio.
You're going to submit for the
senior planner promotion, right?
Oh, yeah, I guess I should.
That's the logical next step,
right?
Right.
But you don't exactly seem
thrilled about it.
I am.
Andrea.
Are we prepared?
Tell me we are and if we're not,
tell me we are anyway.
Hi, Andrea. Yes, of course,
we are.
Good luck, ladies.
Oh, Andrea?
Yes, what?
Since it's a luncheon
for the historical society,
I thought we could do
a Christmas through the ages
kind of thing
so I went to the library
and I dug up these antique
Christmas cards.
I had them enlarged and printed
on these vinyl placemats
for the table.
Fine. Fine, fine.
She really doesn't need to pile
on the praise like that,
it's, it's embarrassing.
what are we doing here again?
We have to get uncle jack
a Christmas present
before we go into the office.
Isn't that what malls
are for?
yeah, but we're going
to get him a hotel room
with a king-size bed
and a coffee machine
and Mediterranean omelettes
on demand.
It's called a staycation,
and grownups love 'em.
Well, I don't get it.
There are way too many places
out there to see.
Like the grand canyon.
I'm so excited for our trip.
Me too.
I'm gonna shout into the abyss
and count how many seconds
it takes for my voice
to get back to me.
The abyss?
It's my word of the day.
come on.
I know it's a little bit
last minute
but merry Christmas.
It's a hotel stay.
Sweet.
Bluetooth noise cancelling
headphones.
Mm nice, thanks.
You didn't think I'd forget
about my favorite nephew,
did you?
I'm your only nephew.
True.
No way! A new camera?
I really wanted one of these.
Thank you, uncle jack.
No problem.
Merry Christmas.
So, when are you two heading off
for Arizona?
Play it by ear.
Think you could add a stop
along the way?
What kind of stop?
You sit tight for a minute
while I go talk with uncle jack
in his office?
Oh, ok.
-See you later, kiddo.
-Bye.
A stop in the Rockies?
I got a call today from Meyer's
national property group.
They're looking to invest in us.
But they want to see us
diversify our assets.
And this, this is our ticket.
Mom and pop outfit, they've had
great success in the past,
but for some reason
they're thinking of selling.
Now, if we can get our hands
on this,
Meyer's national is going
to come on
with extra funding for
future developments.
You want me to scope it out?
Yeah, a quick eval'.
Do we really need this?
To be honest, I'm still
suffering a little jet lag
from the last quick eval' in
Alaska and Maine, before that.
Was kind of looking forward
to taking a break
and spending some real time
with Noah.
This would be for Noah.
With the investment
from Meyer's national,
you could pare back
on field work.
Look, if we don't land
this investment,
we're just going to have
to make up for it
with more acquisitions,
more traveling.
Which means even less time
with Noah.
All right, all right, all right.
Let me check with him, ok?
Sure.
-thanks for the picture!
Curve ball.
I'm listening.
-Detour.
-Where?
-Mountains.
-How long?
A week.
-Five days.
-Grand canyon?
-After.
-Promise?
-Promise.
-Deal.
Want to go pocket some
peppermint macaroons for later?
Sure.
All right.
hey, mom, what's up?
How did the luncheon go?
Did Andrea like the placemats?
Um, yeah, yeah.
It went well.
So, anyway, Christmas is less
than two weeks away
and you still haven't told me
the theme for the party.
The suspense is killing me.
Actually, that's what we wanted
to talk to you about.
We were thinking of scaling back
this year.
Scaling back?
Your dad and I,
well, you know, we've been
road tripping a lot lately.
Telluride, durango, and did
we tell you about Wyoming?
Geysers, hot springs and gallons
of chokecherry jam.
Mom.
All right, well we sort of
fell behind on Christmas.
Fell behind?
This isn't like spring cleaning
or paying the cable bills
or a summer reading list.
This is Christmas
we're talking about here.
And Christmas will
still be Christmas,
just a little understated
this year.
No, no, understated is not
in the family vocabulary.
Ok, us Parkers we are
all or nothing.
Emphasis on the all.
Ok, how about you let me take
the reins on this one.
I've been wanting
to spruce up
my work portfolio
for a while now
and this could be a great
opportunity for me to show
that I can do something
on my own for once.
For once? Is there something
wrong at work?
No, no, work is great.
Don't change the subject.
To go all out or to go all out,
that is the question.
Let's talk about it
when you get here, ok?
Fine.
And by the way,
I hope you're ready to drink
your weight in eggnog.
Your father's been experimenting
with home brews.
Pumpkin pie's the best flavor
by far.
I like the gingerbread batch.
Sounds delicious. I can't wait.
Love you.
-Love you.
-Love you. Bye.
♪ Christmas is near ♪
♪ Christmas is just round
the corner ♪
♪ he's almost here ♪
♪ Santa, he won't be
much longer ♪
♪ so bring on the cheer ♪
♪ 'cause Christmas is just
round the corner ♪
♪ counting each day ♪
♪ Santa, he just
takes forever ♪
♪ watch for his sleigh ♪
♪ his reindeers will
all be together ♪
hi!
The Parkers? Back together
again in the same zip code?
It's a miracle.
Oh, mom.
Oh, let me get your bags.
I am so happy to be home.
I'm so glad you're here.
where is our tree?
Dad?
Quinn! I missed you.
We video chatted yesterday.
I still missed you.
Julie!
Welcome home, Paige.
I hear you're trying
to talk your parents
out of this ridiculous notion
of scaling back Christmas.
Mmmhmm.
Hi, Paige. Good to have
you back.
Where are we on the whole
knocking some Christmas sense
into your parents thing?
We are getting there.
Mmmm.
this is so cool.
Yeah. Can see almost the whole
world from up here, right?
Actually, not the whole world,
but as far as the eye can see.
Which is still pretty far.
Whoever thought I'd be raising
the next Andy Warhol?
I'm more of an Ansel Adams.
He does landscapes.
They'll come around, right?
Let's just put it this way,
when everyone else is
bulk-buying hot chocolate
and holiday cards,
your parents are buying
hiking boots
and taking notes off
the travel channel.
Yeah.
I think they just want
to put their energy
into a different direction
for a change.
No, and I get that, I do.
That's why I said I would
do all the work.
You know, last year I convinced
jimmy fleet
to come out of retirement for
a Christmas concert in Denver.
The hall of famer?
Yeah. And do you know
how hard it is
to get an ex-rock star
to sing jingle bells.
So if I can do that,
I can do anything.
Hey, Paige, Quinn.
Hey, Mia. Did you just
have a gig?
Yeah. It was awesome.
Although somebody put a cheese
danish in my tip jar.
I think they took the whole
starving artist thing literally.
well, I better get going.
My mom has a holiday itinerary
and if I am late for Christmas
cocktail hour,
I'll never hear the end of it.
Mistletoe martinis
wait for no one.
Exactly.
Well, I'll see you guys later.
-Bye!
-Bye.
Ok, I know you're doing
the whole play it cool thing,
but that was just
straight-up cold.
You didn't say one word
to her?
Oh yeah, like I woke up
this morning and was like,
you know what would be great?
Running into Mia
and forgetting every word
in the English language.
You know, in fact,
that was so much fun,
let's do it again tomorrow.
Quinn...
Mia's been coming to the inn
since the dawn of time
and do you know
who she raves about
in her yelp review every year?
You.
I mean, it's actually,
it's physically painful to watch
two smart people be so dumb.
Well, I mean, between the inn
and volunteering at the library
and plowing my way through
the last year of grad school,
I don't really have time
for dating anyway.
Yeah, but it's such a romantic
time of year, isn't it?
Cozying up by a fire
with some hot cocoa, mistletoe?
Are you kidding?
When was the last time
you welcomed
even an ounce of romance
into your life?
Right now, when I fell in love
with my coffee all over again.
we'll send that up right away.
The Andersons would like
more shampoo.
Mrs. Alvarez has requested
an 8:00 wakeup call
and Mr. Tenaka was wondering
if we could extend breakfast
until 11:00 tomorrow.
-Not a problem.
-Great.
-Hi there.
-Hi.
What can we do for you?
I'm Dylan bailey, bailey
brothers development company.
This is my son, Noah.
Uh, are you rick
and Linda Parker?
That's us.
Excellent. I believe you spoke
with my brother, jack.
Ah.
Well, yes, but we weren't
expecting you until next month.
The email said January 17th.
I'm sorry, but jack told me
it was this month.
Do you want me
to come back?
No, no, no. You've already made
the drive up.
I'll be in and out
before Christmas, I promise.
Great. Let's just get you
checked in, Mr. Bailey.
Just call me Dylan.
Dylan, um, our daughter
just came up from the city
and she doesn't know
we're planning on selling,
because we were going to wait
until after Christmas,
but since you're here now.
I was wondering if you wouldn't
mind doing your evaluations,
maybe, under the radar?
You know, just until we can find
a moment to tell her?
Uh, sure.
Thank you. Thank you.
Yeah.
Hey, Noah.
Come on, bud.
So, what's first
on the agenda?
-A structural-
-swashbuckling!
let me guess,
word of the day?
Yes, sir.
What exactly does
swashbuckling entail?
I don't know exactly, but
I do know we'll need fuel.
Sounds like you could use some
famous coyote creek hot cocoa.
Point the way, and let
the swashbuckling begin.
Brace yourselves.
Ok, so I know it's way late
in the game
and I know you have other things
you're focusing on,
I totally get it, but I just,
I really think that we need this
Christmas party.
Ok.
What?
Really?
'cause I mean I had a whole
speech prepared.
I didn't even get to
the chronological breakdown
of every Parker Christmas
since the '90s.
Well, I hope you weren't going
to mention '99, when you...
ahem. Moving on.
Right.
So, what's the theme?
Huh.
All right. Now, before we begin,
Julie, George...
It'll be easier for you two
to listen in here.
Are you implying that
we're eavesdropping?
'cause we most certainly...
Were.
come on.
All right. Now, who has an idea
for the theme?
How about valentine's day?
Because at this rate that's
when we'll be ready.
Hey, you are not helping.
Anyone else?
How about the cast of Christmas,
where each guest dresses up
as their favorite
Christmas character?
Do we really want an
over-confident risk taker
showing up as krampus?
Actually, I would love that.
Christmas carol-oke.
Also known as how many times
can you hear
your favorite Christmas song
before you hate it?
Hey! What did I say to you
about not helping?
Fine.
Uh, Christmas pajama party?
Ooh.
Hm. Linda just got me
a new deep v flannel set
that I've been itching
to wear.
You guys don't mind a little
bit of chest hair, do you?
Dad!
Oh, la, la.
Ugh, mom!
that's it!
We're gonna host a how
to learn Swedish seminar?
Icelandic, but no.
Mom, dad, every year people
come here from all over, right?
Mm-hm.
So many customs and cultures
right under our nose and
we don't celebrate any of it.
So, what about Christmas eve
around the world?
A giant feast that combines
recipes and traditions
from all over.
I love it.
You had me at giant feast.
We're in.
Why not.
That's the spirit.
Great, ok!
Now, speaking of tradition,
I'm off to find myself a marmot.
Check the gazebo.
Well, are you ready for this?
The last Christmas
at coyote creek?
Shh. We don't have to think
about that right now.
hm.
-Look at all these presents!
-Yeah.
-Lose something?
-No.
So, what are you doing?
I'm looking for... Charlotte!
Urgh!
A giant squirrel?
No, not a squirrel.
You must not be
from around here.
Everyone knows
Charlotte the marmot.
Why is she dressed up?
It's Christmas tradition.
Our town mascot is the marmot.
I know it's a pretty silly thing
for a town called
coyote creek, huh?
But every December we take turns
hiding her all around town
and every time we find her,
you have to add another piece
of Christmas clothing and then
hide her somewhere new.
That sounds like fun.
Maybe if you stick around long
enough you'll find her yourself.
We're only in town for
a few days on business.
I thought it might be a nice
holiday getaway from the city.
Oh, you're from Denver?
I live there too.
I come home every year
for Christmas.
My parents run the local inn
and I grew up there.
The coyote creek inn?
Yep, that's the one.
We're staying there.
So you must be one of
the Parkers?
Yeah, I'm Paige.
Their daughter?
Yeah, yeah, they run the inn.
Didn't we just do this?
Yeah, sorry. I'm Dylan
and this is my son, Noah.
Well, it's nice to meet
you both.
I guess I'll see you
around then.
Yeah, yeah, I guess so.
Ok.
Ok, so first things first,
and I can't believe I even
have to say this,
but we need a Christmas tree
for the lobby,
so I will head down to
Pete's pines this morning.
Mm-hm.
Next comes the menu,
the decorations, the music.
For this part we should probably
do some research
on Christmas traditions
around the world.
Mm-hm.
Lastly, flyers, evites,
social media, the whole shebang.
Get the word out to as many
people as possible.
Wow, ok.
Good morning, Paige.
Well, good morning, Noah.
What are you up to today?
Actually, I was just on my way
to get a Christmas tree.
But not just any Christmas tree,
the perfect Christmas tree.
What makes the perfect
Christmas tree?
Seven and a half feet tall,
fifty inches in base diameter,
one-inch needles, extra full,
freshly cut.
-Oh, wow.
-I know.
And here I thought you were
gonna set unrealistic standards.
Can we come?
Oh, well-
I don't think we have time, bud.
Please? Please?
Ok.
no, no.
I know what you're thinking.
Do you?
Yeah, your expression
wasn't exactly subtle.
You're thinking that
I'm too rigid or critical
or high maintenance
or whatever other word
gets slapped onto women
who believe in setting
high standards
and making plans
to achieve them.
I was thinking that this just
seems like a lot of trouble
for just a Christmas tree.
Oh.
No. There's no "just"
when it comes to Christmas.
Every little thing,
every ornament,
every cinnamon stick,
every bouquet and wreath.
Every cranberry scented candle
contributes to the magic.
It all matters.
Agree to disagree...
Strongly disagree.
Do you lack social
graces entirely
or just when it comes
to strangers?
Oh, entirely.
Noah's the only one
that can stand me.
Just you two?
Yeah.
Yeah, his mom's not around.
Hey, Paige.
What about this one?
Oh, let's see.
Hm.
It's not the perfect tree?
You know what,
I forgot to tell you the most
important thing
about picking out
a Christmas tree.
What?
You want the ornament
to hang straight, right?
Sheered trees or long needles
set the ornament at an angle
and no one wants a blown glass
keepsake ornament
sliding off and shattering
into a millions pieces.
Believe me, I have
been there.
So, let's see.
see? It is perfect.
Yeah.
well, thanks for letting us
tag along today.
Sure.
Hey, Noah, you wouldn't
be interested
in helping us decorate the tree,
would you?
I definitely would!
I mean, yeah, if you want,
I could do that.
That ok?
Yeah, yeah. I actually have
some work to do,
so if you don't mind.
No, not at all.
He is kind of handsome,
don't you think?
I mean, he's not my type,
but...
Is he?
I... I hadn't noticed.
let's get decorating!
I definitely like
that one.
And that one in the box
is pretty good too.
I had glitter stuck in
my eyebrows for weeks.
-Yikes.
-I know.
Do you have a favorite
Christmas ornament back home?
Actually, we don't normally have
a Christmas tree.
Oh.
We're usually traveling.
Lake Tahoe, mount Rushmore,
San Diego.
I've been to 23 states.
Wow, that's impressive.
Does your dad travel
a lot for work?
Sometimes.
But, a lot of the time we're
just doing it for fun.
Huh.
Christmas in hotels
and hammocks, huh?
Well, sort of.
We're men of simple tastes.
Just give us the open road and
gas stations with good snacks.
-Good snacks are essential.
-Uh-huh.
Ready?
Ready.
Woah!
You can say that again.
Woah.
you know what they say,
all work and no play
makes jack a lifeless cog
in the capitalist machine.
Thank you.
It does sound familiar.
All this land yours?
Yep.
Nearly 30 acres.
Seem like you could do a lot
with that much land.
Yeah, Linda and I had a few
plans for additions,
but this place is hard enough
to keep up as it is.
We don't want to bite off
more than we could chew.
Well, I'm just about done
out here.
You mind pulling
the finances together
for me to take a look at?
Mortgage details,
rental income, gross yield.
Sure.
Now, what do you say
we rejoin the others?
Truthfully, I've never really
been any good
at that sort of thing.
More of a Halloween guy, huh?
Ah, I just never really
liked anything
that was too... Well, that.
well, unfortunately we got
a lot of "that" up here.
You'd be surprised the effect
this place has on people.
Thankfully I think I'll be
long gone
by the time it can get me.
-I'll see you in there.
-Yeah.
Ok, what do you think?
A boa or suspenders?
-Suspenders.
-Yeah.
These things
come in handy
if you need a last-minute
costume for a Christmas party.
Yeah.
Dad, look. Isn't it
totally awesome?
Yeah. Totally.
Paige was just telling me about
all the cool Christmas things
they do around here.
A Christmas card-a-thon,
homemade cookies and eggnog,
and a huge Christmas party.
Christmas eve eve party.
Ah, that sounds pretty great.
Maybe we can stay a little
longer in coyote creek
than we planned?
Yeah, maybe.
-oh, it's you.
-It is me.
Why is it you?
I mean, what... What are you
doing here?
Same as you.
You're looking for information
on long-standing global
Christmas traditions
and unique cultural
culinary delights?
Yeah. Crazy, right?
where's Noah?
Oh, I lost him to
the photography section.
Those all for
the Christmas party?
Yeah.
Yeah, it's a Christmas around
the world kind of thing.
A big feast meant
to celebrate all the different
Christmas traditions,
but honestly it's a little
overwhelming.
I don't even know how to choose
between some of these.
Um, do I go with Italy's octopus
salad or pierogi from Poland?
Well, what about
pfeffernusse cookies?
Feffer the what now?
Pfeffernusse, they're German.
They're made with spices
and molasses
and covered in confectioner's
sugar.
Mm.
Noah and I spent Christmas
in Munich three years ago
and, let me tell you,
I must have eaten 20 of those
in under an hour.
And by 20 I mean 30.
Yeah, well they do
sound delicious.
Hm. Maybe I'll stop by
the bakery.
Woah, Woah, Woah there
cookie thief.
Excuse me?
Well, you don't get to steal
my cookie idea
and then also not take me.
Fine, fine. We'll both go
to the bakery then.
-Fine.
We're going to the bakery?
Dibs on the biggest cookie!
All right, I gotta know,
what's with the marmots?
The town of coyote creek
began in the winter of 1858
with just a single log cabin
built by hank Odell.
There's actually a really great
stone monument
in a pavilion dedicated to him
and every year the town hosts
a Santa's workshop
at the pavilion every Christmas.
Anyway, when hank was setting up
his first Christmas tree,
he realized he didn't have
any lights or decorations.
Over the course
of the next few days
all these random objects
started appearing on his porch.
Flower petals, twigs,
pine cones, you name it.
And it was these marmots
who were bringing him
like tokens of gratitude because
he'd unknowingly scared away
all the coyotes who'd never seen
a human before.
But, on Christmas eve,
he received the biggest
surprise of all.
A 12-ounce gold nugget
on his porch
that the marmots found by
burrowing into the river bed.
-Wow.
-I know.
Sort of became tradition
for the townspeople to leave
small gifts at Christmas time on
the porches of their neighbors.
I mean, most of us aren't
carrying around
12-ounce gold nuggets,
but you get the idea.
here we are.
-Ah! Merry Christmas, Paige.
-Merry Christmas.
Do you want the usual?
Actually yes, I do, but
that's not why I'm here.
Oh.
-Peppermint fudge.
-Thank you.
And we'll take two more
for these gentlemen
whose lives have yet to be
forever changed
by your edible excellence.
here you go.
-Thank you.
-You're welcome.
-Hm.
-Thank you.
Well?
Mmm. This is...
Delectable!
man, you are killing it
with these word of the days.
I know, right?
-I know.
-Yeah.
So what's up, hon?
Well, this year I'm taking
the reins
on the inn's Christmas party
and I thought maybe
you could help me
with some of the desserts.
The menu is gonna consist of
dishes from all over the world
and Dylan here recommended
fa.. Fifenu..
Pfeffernusse cookies.
Yes, of course.
German, right?
Yeah, that's right.
Great choice.
The key ingredient
is anise seeds or extract
to get that licorice flavor.
And black pepper.
It's that hint of the spice
that's what makes it distinct.
A man who knows
his seasoning.
Anyway, you know I'd love
to help out hon,
but I'm pretty backed up
on holiday orders.
Christmas pageants,
office parties.
Thirty-six hours to make nearly
300 Christmas cookies.
Ahh!
Well, what if I were to help you
with the orders?
I'm no pastry chef but I am
a decorating dynamo.
I don't know.
I can help too.
Can I?
Well...
All right then.
operation Christmas cookies
enlists another soldier.
Come back tomorrow, 8:00.
-Deal!
-Deal.
Enjoy.
See you tomorrow morning,
Paige.
See you tomorrow.
-You got a good one.
-Yeah, yeah I did.
Not sure what I did
to deserve him.
Are you always this hard
on yourself?
Yeah, one of my defining
characteristics actually.
That and being really,
really, charming.
Oh, don't forget your
incredible modesty.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Really?
Well, yeah.
You didn't think I was going
to let Noah have all the fun,
did you?
Well, I just didn't peg you
as someone
who wants to bake 300 Christmas
cookies on a tight deadline
and at the risk of early
onset arthritis.
That's not why I'll show up.
Hey dad, are you coming
or what?
We're almost at
the Annie Leibovitz
chapter of this podcast
and I don't really want
to keep explaining to you
what you missed.
okay, okay.
cinnamon sugar, butter,
fresh dough.
You're cheating on me.
with Sarah's sweets!
Oh, George, you have
to forgive me.
The fudge, the fudge.
Oh.
So, I have a culinary mission
for you,
should you choose to accept.
-Let's hear it.
-Ok.
I've compiled a list of popular
Christmas dishes
from around the world
for the feast.
We have puerto rican
roast pig,
french guinea fowl roasted
and stuffed with chestnuts,
Venezuelan hallacas,
danish boiled potatoes.
And Sara's gonna try to help
with some of the desserts.
German cookies,
Slovakian honey cake,
pavlova, Filipino bibingka
and I have to stop
because my mouth is
literally watering.
Ok. Well, that sounds great...
But?
But, and just hear me out
on this,
it just feels like if the goal
is to celebrate
the many Christmas traditions
of our guests,
you might want to talk
to our guests.
Oh. Thank you.
There you go.
Ok, I'm gonna go back to work.
mm. Genius. I'm a genius.
Well, the property's
in good shape
and they're sitting
on a lot of land,
but their finances are
a bit confusing.
Confusing how?
Profits have been increasing
year after year.
Why sell if business
is booming?
Hm. That is odd.
But the why doesn't
matter to us.
They are selling
and that's that.
Any more word from
Meyer's national?
Yeah, about that,
before they come on board
with an investment
they want to see plans
for a redesign.
Of the inn? Why?
We need to show them
what we can do
on the development side,
not just on the
acquisition side.
Show what sets us apart
from the other firms.
So go ahead and draw up
the blueprints for the future.
The future bailey brothers
luxury resort and ski lodge.
Hm. So when you said redesigning
you really meant
bulldozing it to the ground
and rebuilding it entirely?
I'm sure the Parkers
will love that.
♪ ho, ho, ho,
who wouldn't go, ♪
♪ up on the house top,
click, click, click ♪
♪ down through the chimney
with good saint nick ♪
that sounds great!
Oh, sorry.
What did you say?
Nothing, it's...
I, I just didn't,
I didn't hear you.
You sound great.
Thanks.
Ok.
-like that.
-Ok.
Am I doing this right?
I don't think I'm doing
this right.
it's Christmas cookies,
not cubism.
Just be creative,
but don't draw like
a treasure map
or write Morse code.
Ok. No Morse code,
got it.
What about Italian?
Hm.
Dov'è la paninoteca?
Did you just ask me where
the sandwich shop is?
You speak Italian?
Si, ho imparato un poco.
I learned a little when
my company hosted a dinner
for Denver university's
foreign exchange students.
Sorry.
I didn't know you had
a company.
Oh, no, not my company.
Just the company I work for.
I'm an event planner.
Oh, that sounds exciting.
Hm.
So is it like, masquerade balls
and galas or,
or luncheons for tech moguls
and antique dealers?
Oh, a little bit of everything,
but honestly, it's not
as exciting as all that.
It's mostly painting
by numbers,
coloring inside the lines,
paying attention to detail.
Which I'm good at.
I can see that.
Thanks.
Come on, go crazy.
It's therapeutic.
Ok, fine.
Oh, like you mean it.
and, for the record?
I like it better that way.
Whew! That was record time.
I'll get started on that list
of desserts
just as soon as I get done
with these deliveries.
Thank you so much, Sara.
I appreciate it.
I know. See ya later!
-Bye!
-Bye.
Do you think there's a bakery
at the grand canyon?
Not like, in the canyon,
but near it.
Probably.
There must be something
near the hotel. Why?
Sara was telling me about
all the different types
of Christmas cookies.
Drop cookies, blossom cookies,
rolled cookies,
pressed cookies, bar cookies,
and snowballs.
I want to try them all.
Sounds like a man
on a mission.
so grand canyon, huh?
Yeah, it's a national park
with geologic strata
from the Proterozoic
and Paleozoic eras.
You should check it
out sometime.
I know what it is,
what I don't know is
why you seem to want
to spend Christmas anywhere
but home?
Noah told me about the whole
jack Kerouac on the road thing.
Ah.
What is home anyways?
A place where you feel safe
and loved that welcomes you back
no matter how long
you've been gone.
Ok.
Why does home have
to be somewhere,
why can't it be someone?
For me, home is simple.
It's not a bad thing, you know.
What?
Having actual emotions.
Ok, so I know two things
about you.
You are not great
at cookie decorating
and you don't like to talk
about anything serious,
which I had to infer
from your brooding silence.
-I'm not brooding.
-Mmm.
I'm maintaining an air
of mystery.
People like mysteries,
don't they?
All right, fine.
I really hate olives.
Now you know three things.
Come on, seriously?
No, seriously.
I really hate em'.
-Bye, Paige!
-Bye.
-See ya.
-Yeah.
What?
Oh, nothing, nothing.
I was just wondering if all the
guests get a private tour guide
or just the handsome
single dads.
We were helping Sara
with a huge Christmas order
so she could help me
with the feast.
A strictly selfish motive
on my part.
Mm-hm.
Ok, can I please see
the guestbook?
I want to talk to some
of the guests
about their Christmas
traditions.
Mmm.
Thank you.
The Christmas holidays last from
December 12 through January 6th.
We have nightly posadas,
celebrations that take place
in different family homes.
We always have lots of food,
games and piñatas that we fill
with fruits and candy.
And fireworks,
lots of fireworks.
That sounds amazing.
the Christmas cat
is a huge beast
that comes down the mountainside
at Christmas
and eats all the children
that do not get new clothes
for Christmas.
Oh.
we also like shortbread cookies.
in Italy it's tradition to play
the bagpipes at Christmas.
Oh.
Fried chicken.
Fried chicken?
The most popular Christmas meal
in japan.
We love the party buckets.
-hey.
-Anything good?
Yeah, I think so.
Although, I'm not sure why
a carnivorous cat
with a taste for human flesh
gets people in the Christmas
spirit, but, you know.
I mean, the Christmas spirit
works in mysterious ways.
That it does.
Oh, by the way, do you have
any ideas for Christmas music
for the party?
I mean, I'm down for
a good bagpipe ballad,
but I'm not sure that should be
our only source of music.
Um, actually, I've heard Mia
play around the inn.
She's really good.
Maybe we should ask her
to perform?
Hm. That sounds like
a great idea.
I'll let you get
right on that.
You want me to ask her?
Yeah. Obviously.
Ok.
All right. Well, I'm gonna
head up.
I gotta polish my portfolio,
catalogue my client
testimonials,
review my references
and reorganize the budget
and design templates.
Wow. And I thought indexing
all the poetry works
from the Elizabethan and
Victorian eras was tedious.
All right, I'll see you tomorrow
at the Christmas card-a-thon.
-All right.
-Good night.
This is the year that we
accidentally double-booked
Mrs. Thompson and Mr. Clark
in the same room.
Ten years of marriage later I'd
say it worked out well for them.
I love being a chapter
in someone else's story.
Even a short one.
I'm gonna miss that.
We're still gonna be a part of
people's stories.
We're just moving
into a new genre.
The adventure genre.
What do you say to Christmas
in Paris next year?
Crème brûlée on the seine,
lights along the gondolas.
Carolers singing noel blanc
in the city square.
Sold.
you two have a minute?
Noah's asleep.
Sure.
So, I've been going over
the numbers you gave me.
Um, I gotta say,
I don't understand.
Don't understand what?
Well your profits are increasing
and judging from the pattern
they're likely to continue
to increase.
Usually when we get the word
on a place like this
it's because the business
is struggling,
but this place is
a huge success.
so, why give it up?
Well, it's less about
giving it up.
It's more about letting it go.
Moving on doesn't have to be
a bad thing.
We might be old,
but we're not that old.
Still got a lot of years left
in us.
Years that we want to spend
sipping on mai tais
in the Maldives.
Is that so wrong?
No, no it's not.
We've run this place
for many years.
Rick's mother ran it before us
and his grandmother
ran it before her.
It's just time for someone else
to have a turn.
Paige didn't want
to take it over?
Well, of course part of us
hoped for that,
but she's got her own life
in Denver
separate from all of this.
She's happy with her
own career.
Is she?
What does that mean?
Well, I got the impression
that...
I just think you need to tell
her the truth, 'cause I can't.
I just think that she deserves
to know.
-You're right.
-I agree.
We'll tell her tomorrow.
♪ deck the halls
with boughs of holly, ♪
♪ fa la la la la,
la la la la ♪
♪ 'tis the season
to be jolly ♪
♪ fa la la la,
la la la la ♪
♪ don we now
our gay apparel ♪
♪ fa la la la
la la la la la ♪
-Paige?
-Yeah?
There's something we wanted
to talk to you about.
What's up?
It's about the inn.
Your mom and I...
Wait...
I think I know what
you're gonna say.
And, as much as
I'd want you to,
I know that it's unreasonable
to think you guys would run
this place forever.
And I know that traveling
is something you've wanted to do
for a while now
and it makes me happy
to see you guys seizing life
in that way.
Carpe Diem and all that jazz.
Anyway, I've been thinking
about it a lot,
about what this place
means to me,
what it means to everyone.
There's so much potential here
and I would hate to see it
go to waste.
But, I would also hate to see
you guys continue on
with something just because
you felt like you had to.
Ok.
And I've felt more fulfilled
planning this party
in coyote creek
over the past week
than I have in my company
in Denver
over the past year.
So, basically, my answer is,
I will consider it.
I will consider taking over
the inn.
That's what you guys wanted
to talk to me about, right?
-Uh...
-Not exactly.
Hi, Paige.
Uh, we'll talk about this later,
ok?
so, this is the Christmas
card-a-thon?
The one and only.
We have a huge list of names and
army bases of overseas soldiers
who'd really love a good
Christmas card.
So, am I gonna be able
to wrangle you in
for some Christmas
card signing?
Duh, I have excellent
penmanship.
what's wrong?
Nothing. I, I just don't know
what to write.
Well, merry Christmas is usually
a good place to start.
so, how did all this get
started anyways?
Well, both Quinn's parents
are in the military
and they missed
a few Christmases
when she was growing up.
So this place and my family
became like a second home
to her,
but she never missed a year
writing them for Christmas.
-Where are they now?
-Belgium.
But they'll be here
in the new year.
That's gotta be tough.
Christmas is supposed to be
something you spend
with the people you love.
I think it's great, though,
that this one small practice
grew into this huge tradition.
Yeah, yeah a few of the guests
had loved ones overseas
and kind of snowballed into
the event that it is today.
It's really cool to see
everybody working together
for the common good.
At least that's what someone
with actual emotions would say.
When I said that I didn't
mean it like that.
It's ok.
I haven't exactly been
transparent about everything.
It's hard for me to...
-Open up?
-Yeah.
Why is that?
See, to explain to you why it
would be hard for me to open up
would actually require me
to open up.
Catch 22.
Noah's mom left
when he was four.
I guess she just realized
one day
she wasn't ready
to be a mom.
I'm so sorry.
I can't even imagine what that
must have been like for Noah.
-Or for you.
-It's ok.
But that's why I try to make
our life one big adventure.
Especially around
the holidays.
Yeah.
I figure if we have enough good
memories someplace new,
then the old ones won't...
-Hurt as much?
-Yeah.
Long time since I've seen him
this happy... Or excited.
Paige, there's something
I want to tell you.
What's that?
Hey, Paige, look at all these
photos I took.
Wow, that's amazing, Noah.
These look like they should be
in a Christmas catalogue.
I don't know. My work's
more editorial.
Uh, lean in.
Us?
Who else would I be
talking to?
sorry.
so, we definitely need to start
rearranging in here.
I want to decorate each
of the main rooms
after a different
country's Christmas.
Uh, Quinn, do you think you're
ok to close up without me?
Oh, sure, stick around
for the fun,
dip out on the clean-up
duty.
yeah, ok. Ok, yeah.
Yeah.
Good night, Paige.
-Hey.
-Hi.
So, uh, there is something
I wanted to ask you.
Yeah?
Um... I was wondering,
I was wondering if you would
want to perform
at the inn's Christmas party.
Oh, uh, yeah.
Yeah sure, I'd love to.
-Great.
Well, good night.
'night.
Hey kiddo, I'm just gonna
step out for a minute, ok,
but I'll be right back.
Ok.
hello, coyote creek inn.
Hi. Is Mr. And Mrs. Parker
there?
Uh, no, sorry.
They've actually turned in
for the night.
Um, what about Dylan,
Dylan bailey?
I'm trying to reach him
but he hasn't returned my calls.
Oh, may I ask who's calling?
I'm his brother,
jack bailey.
Oh, hi.
Well, actually I think he also
turned in for the night,
but can I take a message?
Uh, yeah, sure.
Can you tell him
I'm forwarding
some final estimates on the inn
ahead of the sale?
Hello?
Yeah, I'll tell him.
Thank you.
Yeah, but...
To you.
Yeah.
How could you have not
told me?
How could they not have
Well, they wanted to tell you,
they did.
The right moment
just never came up and,
and I didn't think it was
my place to...
You didn't think it was
your place to tell me the truth?
No, you were just hoping
that they would do it for you
and then your part
would be overlooked.
When your parents
first contacted my firm
it was just another property,
another sale, another client.
How was I supposed to know
that I would get here and...
I just didn't think that
I would get to know you
the way that I have and the more
time we spent together,
the harder it was to tell you.
Ok, but how can you
not see
that now all that time we spent
together feels like a lie?
Look, I never meant
to hurt you, Paige.
I'm sorry.
morning.
Paige?
Hey, sorry.
Good morning.
Oh, how'd it go with Mia?
Uh, she said she'd play
at the party.
That's it?
yeah, that's it.
I chickened out.
I'm just mad at myself,
that's all.
I'm sorry it didn't go the way
you wanted it to.
But you'll get another chance.
-You think?
-Yeah, I do.
Just don't fumble it
a second time.
I won't.
What's wrong?
My parents are selling
the inn.
-Wait, what?
-To Dylan.
-Wait, what?!
-Yeah.
You didn't know anything
about this, right?
I honestly didn't.
But business has been
so good.
They haven't said anything
to me.
They didn't say anything
to anyone.
I'm sorry, Paige.
I don't even know
what to say.
Me neither.
Thanks for the walk,
I needed that.
-That was nice.
-Yeah.
I'll give you guys some space.
So, I got a call last night
from Dylan's brother.
Yeah, I know about the sale.
Paige...
Why didn't you guys
just tell me?
We tried to.
Not hard enough.
Yesterday at the card-a-thon
when you brought up
taking over this place.
You've never said anything
about that before.
We had no idea it was something
you were considering.
We thought you were happy
in Denver.
I mean, we didn't know.
You still should have told me.
And to think you guys let me
go on and on,
planning this Christmas party
as if it's just another
Christmas, but it's not.
It's the last Christmas here.
That's why we waited
to tell you.
We didn't want to ruin it
for you.
But I'm an adult and I can
handle the truth.
I need you guys to trust me
with the truth.
We just wanted
to protect you.
We're so sorry.
It's time to see what someone
else can do with this place.
Yeah, but that someone
could have been me.
Would you be taking over the inn
because you really wanted to
or because it's what you thought
you should do?
I don't know.
But now I won't even get
a chance to find out.
I'm gonna go into town.
I can't even think about this
right now
and the party is
in three days
and I still have to transform
this place
into a culturally inspired
Christmas haven.
Paige.
Try to take it easy on Dylan,
if you can.
Why should I?
-you've got a lot-
-no, no, it's ok.
-Paige, come on.
-I said I got it.
Where's Noah?
Back at the inn, brainstorming
new eggnog flavors with rick.
Look, I wanted to find you
and tell you how sorry I am.
I don't want your apology
and I don't need some speech
or some explanation
that just makes you feel better
about what you've done.
Ok, ok.
There's more.
Ok, what?
My firm, my brother and I,
there's gonna be a redesign
of the inn.
And I'm telling you
all this now
because I wanted to be
upfront, okay?
We have an investor
that's interested in us
but they're mainly focused
on larger commercial projects
and jack and I, we owe them
new blueprints.
Do my parents know?
Yeah, I told them right before
I went looking for you.
So that's it?
Yeah, we have nothing else
to talk about.
I'm glad it's been a successful
business trip.
hey.
What is all this?
I told Julie about the sale.
-And I told George.
-And I told Sara.
-And Sara must have told...
-Everyone.
Ok, take a look at this.
Christmas is just days away.
And you'd think people
would have their own
massively overcrowded
family gatherings to attend to.
Yeah, but I guess this is
a family too, right?
The coyote creek family.
Ok, everyone huddle in.
Right this way.
ok.
What do you think
you're doing?
Helping.
No, not a chance. I think
you've done quite enough.
Not even going to give me
a chance
to try to make it up
to you?
Are we really gonna do
this here?
I don't think we're
in a position
to be turning away
extra help.
Ok, fine.
All right. First rule here,
keep the client happy.
We need to do something
to keep people's minds off
this check-in circus.
Provide some type
of distraction.
Uh, second rule,
think outside the box.
We have a lot of people here
and not a lot of space,
so we need to find some other
type of accommodations.
How are we gonna do that?
No idea.
Well, aren't you sitting
on like 30 acres?
Yeah.
I'm not sure people will take
to the idea of sleeping outside.
This isn't man vs. Wild.
Who said anything about outside?
It just, leave the
accommodations to me.
You really expect us
to trust you?
Yeah. Yeah, I do.
Ok, well it seems we have
no choice,
so Dylan will do whatever
he's gonna do
and the rest of us should focus
on keeping people happy.
In the meantime,
dad, you wanted taste testers
for you eggnog?
Well, you got 'em.
Quinn, see if Mia can do
an early soundcheck.
Ok. Everyone good?
Mmmhmm.
Ok. Break.
Thanks for doing this
on such short notice.
If anyone can lull an angry mob
into a spellbound silence
it's probably you.
Like pan's pipe or lyre
of Hermes or the sirens?
Didn't the last one end
in shipwreck and disaster?
Yep.
Speaking of disaster,
about last night.
What about it?
So, listen, um...
I might just be
reading things wrong
and if I am we can just pretend
that this never happened.
What the heck, it's Christmas,
I'm just gonna say it.
I like you.
I've always liked you.
Finally.
great.
It'll be here in an hour.
What will be?
I don't like not being a part
of the plan.
I know.
What are we going to do
for a full hour?
Um, well, I think there's a cool
place to take some more photos
just around the bend.
Cool.
♪ deck the halls with boughs
of holly ♪
♪ fa la la la la,
la la la la ♪
♪ tis the season to be... ♪
-wow!
-Yeah, wow.
Told ya.
♪ don we now
our gay apparel... ♪
smile!
thank you.
♪ troll the ancient
yule-tide carol ♪
♪ fa, la, la, la, la,
la, la, la, la. ♪
♪ see the blazing yule... ♪
Paige, I'm really sorry.
It wasn't fair of me
to hide that from you.
I was just trying to do
right by your parents
and I was trying
to remind myself
that it was just business,
but it's not.
This place is so much more
than that,
and I see that now.
You helped me see that.
Just makes you think,
you know, if it wasn't
like this.
Like what?
If I was just a normal guest
and you were just you,
none of this got
in the way.
No way!
I found Charlotte the marmot!
But I don't have anything
to put on her.
Oh, um, here.
You can use my scarf.
Come here Charlotte.
There, now you're officially
a part of our tradition.
This is the best
Christmas ever!
Here we are.
Right on time.
What is this?
Glamping.
It's like camping,
but with a little more...
Pizzazz?
What does that mean?
Something with style
and glamour.
A little extra oomph.
Then yeah. Dad called
in the pizzazz.
I'm a loyal customer of
a lot of rental companies.
Perks of the rambling
man lifestyle.
-Thank you.
-Yeah.
I owed you one.
so what's with
all the cobwebs?
It's Ukrainian folklore.
There was once an old widow
who lived with her children
in this tiny shack.
And they had no gifts
or decorations
and on Christmas morning
they woke up
to find their Christmas tree
completely covered in cobwebs,
but when sunlight entered
the shack,
all the cobwebs turned
to gold.
Oh.
I love stories about the
importance of material wealth.
Well, I like it because it shows
that anything is possible
during the Christmas season.
No matter who you are
of where you come from.
There's always a little hope
for some Christmas magic.
You never know what could be
waiting for you in the morning.
-Here you go.
-Thanks.
Hey!
Julie, are you ok?
Well... It's just... I've worked
here nearly half my life.
I've spent most birthdays,
most Christmases,
even most world cups
with you all.
What am I supposed
to do next?
And Paige, I think this is
going to be
the best Christmas party yet.
I love seeing all these
different traditions
come to life,
but, well, you've been
so focused
on including the rest
of the world
you've overlooked our corner
of it.
Where's coyote creek
in all of this?
you ok?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Except for the colossal
oversight on my part.
I can't believe for
the very last Christmas
at coyote creek inn
I overlooked coyote creek.
I mean, how could I be so...
Hey, hey, hey,
don't do that.
Do what?
Undermine yourself.
I don't want to leave tomorrow.
Then don't.
It's not that simple.
all right.
Oooh!
Hey, so, Sara will be
dropping by
with the first batch of desserts
later today
and I am on fire
with these recipes.
Ok. Well, please be careful or
that will literally be the case.
oh!
Thanks.
What's up?
Well, Julie's right.
Party's tomorrow,
what am I gonna do?
Well, you'll think of something.
You always do.
Good morning, Paige.
We've got a little something
for you.
People usually save the gifts
for Christmas day.
Well, we thought you needed
a little inspiration.
We've been putting this together
over the last year.
Oh, wow.
I'm really gonna miss
this place.
It's ok to miss it, but keep
in mind that the memories
that people have made here,
those will never go away.
That's it.
What?
Let's have the guests write down
their favorite Christmas memory
at coyote creek inn.
It could be a story or a single
sentence or an old photograph.
Anything that shows the part
this inn played
in people's lives.
And it'll be like one last trip
down memory lane.
Well, then I'm gonna write
out Christmas of '99
when your mom...
When are you gonna stop
bringing that up?
When it stops bothering you.
I think it's a great idea.
I'd love to look back on a few
of the good times.
-hey, Noah.
-Hey.
What memory are you
gonna pick?
I don't know
which to choose?
Decorating the Christmas tree,
baking cookies with Sara,
the Christmas card-a-thon,
hank's pavilion or the
gingerbread eggnog batch.
Gingerbread, huh?
I thought vanilla bean
was the best.
Agree to disagree.
so, where's your dad?
He's on the phone
with uncle jack.
He'll be down in a minute.
So, you're taking off then,
huh?
Yeah.
Christmas at the grand
canyon awaits.
I sent the appraisal
report to Meyer's national
and they're looking over
the preliminary redesign.
The Parkers have signed
on the dotted line,
I've signed, but this is
the bailey brothers firm
and both bailey brothers
need to sign.
What are you waiting for?
I just... I thought maybe
there was some way
we could compromise.
Maybe we could involve
the Parkers in the redesign
or, or bring 'em on
as some sort of...
What? No, I'm... I'm sorry
but no.
This is business. It's nothing
personal against the Parkers.
When we found the firm,
we had a mission, right?
To find, preserve and cultivate
unique properties.
Don't quote the mission at me,
I know it.
I'm just saying, I don't think
anybody's gonna rush to,
to check into a new hotel
just 'cause it's got
a jacuzzi and wi-fi.
I certainly would.
Jack.
Please.
I spoke with jack.
I told him I wouldn't sign
until I'm completely satisfied
with the redesign.
Oh, well that's good,
I guess.
I'll try and keep you involved,
as long as I can.
If you have any ideas
or suggestions,
I want you to reach out
to me, ok?
A business card? Really?
-I'm, I'm not used to this.
-Used to what?
Feeling like this.
I mean, the past few years,
it's just been Noah and I
versus the world.
He's the only constant
in my life.
The thought of bringing somebody
new into that is terrifying.
I have to think of Noah,
I gotta protect him.
Maybe in a year or two, or...
You don't have to do that,
you know?
Do what?
I get what you're saying,
I do.
It's just, I've finally realized
what I want.
And I want a partner
that I can build a life with
and I want someone
who wants that too.
I can't just wait around
until you're ready.
Um, is it ok if I say bye?
Yeah, of course, bud.
Come here.
Thanks, Paige. I've had
a great time here.
No, not great...
Stupendous.
Me too.
I hope you have fun
in the grand canyon.
-Merry Christmas.
Merry Christmas, Paige.
-Come on, bud.
-Ok.
hey, what's up?
Nothing.
It's not nothing.
Come on, tell me.
It's just, you are a complete
and utter buffoon.
word of the day?
Yeah, but I mean it.
Hm. I did kind of mess up,
didn't I?
It's not too late.
We can turn around.
Yeah, but don't you want
to see the grand canyon?
It's just a big hole
in the ground, right?
Yeah, but you could have
told me that sooner.
I thought you wanted to go.
You wanted to go,
that's why we drove 350 miles.
If we turn around right now,
we can still make it in time
for the party.
Ah, decorating in
complete silence.
Happiest time of year.
I'm sorry.
Just have a lot
on my mind.
Is this the kind of thing
where I should ask about it,
so you can unburden
your thoughts,
or the kind of thing where
I should just shut my mouth
and stick to
the snow globes?
The snow globes.
Got it.
What about work?
Is that off limits?
How are you feeling about
the promotion?
Honestly, I don't know how
I feel about that anymore.
I'm gonna submit
my portfolio materials
the first of the new year
and I know that senior planner
is the next step.
But?
But, when does it end?
Senior planner, event manager,
event director.
There's always another rung
on the corporate ladder
and to be honest, not really
sure I want to climb it anymore.
♪ we wish you
a merry Christmas, ♪
♪ and a happy new year ♪
♪ good tidings
we bring to you... ♪
feliz navidad
Mr. And Mrs. Alvarez.
♪ good tidings
for Christmas ♪
♪ and a happy new year ♪
♪ now bring us some
Figgy pudding ♪
♪ and a cup of good cheer ♪
♪ we wish you a
merry Christmas, ♪
♪ we wish you
a merry Christmas, ♪
♪ and a happy new year ♪
♪ good tidings we bring ♪
♪ to you and your kin ♪
♪ good tidings for Christmas
and a happy new year ♪
♪ we wish you
a merry Christmas, ♪
♪ and a happy new year... ♪
sorry, it's not a 12-ounce
gold nugget.
What is it?
The redesign.
Expansion, really.
Coyote creek inn, 2.0.
Owned by the bailey brother's
development firm,
operated by Paige Parker,
if she accepts.
Oh, and approved by
your parents, if that helps.
What happened to
the luxury resort?
I told jack and Meyer's national
that destroying this property
would wipe out decades
of historical charm
and eradicate an entire town's
social and civil bonds.
And then when that didn't work
I just showed him the numbers.
I may not be very convincing,
but dollar signs usually are.
I think the old saying is, don't
fix what isn't broken, right?
Business men are usually
pretty practical that way.
Thank you.
It means so much to all of us.
But, how do I know that
I can trust you?
I mean, how do I know
that you're not just gonna
leave again?
Because letting you down
felt awful.
I never want to do that again.
I was just trying to do
the right thing yesterday.
I was trying to be
a responsible,
realistic, level-headed adult,
which by the way is really
difficult to do
any time I look at you.
It's never really about Noah,
protecting him, it's about me.
Oh, yeah, no.
I, I know.
so, I'm gonna stay,
'cause a week with you
wasn't enough time
and I want to know everything
about you
and I want to know
how you like your eggs
and the name of your first dog
and where you were
when you heard the Beatles
for the first time.
I'm gonna stick around.
And not just for the weekend,
or for Christmas,
but for, at least until
you get tired of me.
Which you won't,
because as we've established,
I am incredibly charming.
Hmm.
Some might even
say irresistible.
Oh, would they?
Well, I'd be lying if I said
I wasn't happy to see you,
because the truth is,
with you and Noah,
this was starting to feel like
the best Christmas yet.
come on, bud.
♪ hey ♪
up we go.
♪
♪ Oooh ♪
♪ Christmas ♪
♪ it's Christmas ♪
♪ and I want to share
this Christmas with you ♪
♪ it's Christmas ♪
♪ and I want to share
this moment with you ♪