[bell tolls]
[breathes heavily]
[announcer on radio]
South Texas Radio.
[radio host] Welcome back.
I have to tell
all of you listeners,
in case you haven"t
already heard about this,
and this one"s a doozy.
The State of Texas is releasing
a convicted murderer
by the name of Neto Niente,
straight off of death row
and back onto our streets.
It seems that an overzealous state
trooper by the name of Robert Cuaron
planted a key piece of evidence
that led to Niente"s conviction.
Well, shortly before his death,
the trooper confessed
to planting this evidence.
Now, let me tell you folks,
this Niente is the kind of guy
who should be locked away
for good.
His gangster associates
called him The Jesuit
in some sick reference
to the fact that certain Jesuits
performed torture during
the Spanish Inquisition.
It is only a matter of time
before something
truly awful happens.
Callers, I want to know
what you think.
Crystal in Laredo.
[Crystal] This fella
does sound pretty bad,
but one sin
does not justify another,
especially by the authorities.
In the end, it will be God who
will pass judgment on this guy.
[host]
I hope you"re right.
Jose in Corpus Christi.
[Jose] I don"t care
if he rots in prison.
This guy, he just makes
my people look bad.
[fading] I really have
no sympathy for him.
[prisoners chattering
in distance]
[door lock buzzes]
[guard] These boots.
A bag of clothes.
I "m sure I" ll see you again.
[car approaching]
[Neto] Counselor.
Neto.
Brought you a hat.
Where do you want to go?[Neto]
Let"s get out of here.
So, your stuff"s
in the back there.
Well, you"ve got
about 30 grand-ish.
Plus your passport.
Speaking of which,
I"ve got something for you.
There you are.
That"s got all the
latest shit on it, that has.
You won"t believe
that fucking thing.
How"d you get Cuaron
to change his testimony?
Well, as you know,
six months ago,
he discovered he"s got
cancer of the asshole.
He says, "God, what have
I done to deserve this?"
He can"t sit.
He can"t take a shit.
So his wife says,
"Roberto, my love,"
she says, "You must
confess your sins."
She says, "When you" re
standing at the pearly gates,
God is gonna look directly
into your soul, right?
He"s going to see
all your secrets,
and he"s gonna
judge you."
So he says,
"Cecilia, you" re right.
Tomorrow, I will go down to the
police and I will confess all my sins."
And I said, "Hold on a minute."
I said, "Hold on a minute."
Tomorrow, when I come by
with his medicine,
I"ll bring along a judge to take down
his statement, which is what I done.
And now,
Robbie"s soul is at rest.
A week later, he was in the arms
of St. Peter, thank you very much.
You know you got no
restrictions on you, right?
No parole, no supervision.
You can go wherever
you fucking want,
but in Texas,
they don"t forget
the fucking Jesuit.
Not the police. As far as they"re
concerned, you took one of their own.
And certainly not the fucking
cholos. You"re fucked there.
You was an enforcer.
You made enemies.
They fucking remember you.
If I was you,
I"d fuck right off.
There"s just one thing
I got to do first.
What"s that? I have to see my son.
[breathing heavily]
[exhaling forcefully]
[car alarm blaring]
[blaring continues]
[alarm chirps]
[grunts]
[siren blares][officer] Police!
[Neto grunts]
[grunts][officer] Well, well, well.
Wall hasn"t changed you.
[grunts]Haven"t changed you at all,
have they?
[groans]
Mama always said,
"Never kick a fresh turd
when it"s hot out."
But it"s been raining.
[grunts, groans]
Your ball-sucking lawyer
may have manipulated Cuaron
into changing his testimony.
Lord knows you"ve sinned.
You"ve sinned plenty.
We"re gonna be watching you
closely, boy, that"s for goddamn sure.
[grunts]
[groaning]
[person gasps]
[breathing heavily]
[grunts]
[groans]
[person] Yes?
[footsteps approaching]
Hi.
You should have called.
May I come in?
Look at you.
You are nothing but trouble.
What do you want?
I"d like to see my son.
[in Spanish]
No. He"s not here.
[in English]
You need to leave.
It"s been four years.
Please let me in.
Five minutes.
Thank you.
Julio.
So, what was prison like?
People in there, they
ain"t very smart, you know?
I mean, not like you.
I knew they"d let you go,
see their mistake.
I never stopped praying.
What happened here?
Vincent happened.
Did he lay a hand on you?
No, he just doesn"t
believe in God.
Neto. You have to go.
Vincent will be home soon. But, Mom...
Neto, please.
Here. Smile.
[camera shutter clicks]
[person]
No! No! No!
[grunts]
[in Spanish]
Who are you?
[in English]
What do you want?
I need to send
your husband a message.
I have no husband.
[grunts]
[Neto speaking Latin]
That"s Latin for,
"Let the lying lips
be put to silence."
No! No! No! [screams]
[groans]
He"s going to kill you.
He"s going to fucking
rip you apart.
You know, I haven"t had the
pleasure of meeting your husband...
but I"m sure as hell dying to.
No! No! No! No!
No!
[children chattering
in distance]
[choir vocalizing]
[priest sighs]
When did you get out, Neto?
A few days ago.
Good to see you again
in God"s house.
How long has it been
since your last confession?
Oh, it"s been a long time.
Would you like to confess?
Have you seen Julio?
Yeah, I saw him yesterday.
He really looks up to you
and helps you during
the Sunday services and all.
He does.
Julio"s a good boy.
Kindhearted.
But you"re the one
he really admires.
Maybe I should
keep my distance then.
Perhaps.
Self-sacrifice is the way
to lead a just life.
[people chattering]
[Latin pop music
playing over speakers]
♪ Yeah ♪
[in Spanish]
The Jesuit.
[chuckles]
[in English]
You want to talk to me?
Just checking in.
[in Spanish] You haven"t
changed at all, bastard.
[in English]
Do you need something?
Do you need to be set up?
Well, actually,
I was thinking of
going the other way.
Stepping back.
That"s not possible, ese.
Blood in, blood out.
[in Spanish]
For life, remember?
[in English]
Yeah, I remember.
That"s why
I"m telling you first.
See, I"ve made up my mind.
Now you"ve got to decide
which side you want
to be on this.
See those vatos?
They"d love to take you on.
Cut down The Jesuit.
Get his rep.
Oh, I"d love to see them try.
Me too! [laughing]
[in Spanish]
Okay, asshole.
[in English]
I"ll give you a pass,
but you can"t stay around here.
Can"t have people
knowing you"re back
and not taking orders.
[in Spanish] Don"t take too
long to leave, understood?
[in English] I hear
you join another group...
[in Spanish]
You"re dead.
[in English] And my wife,
she has a new boyfriend, uh,
Vincent Rice.
She says he sells condos.
You know him?
La Cara del Norte.
[in English] He has weight
down south, not with us.
[Vincent] Migalito![cell phone ringing]
First, you promise me
payment on delivery.
That"s one strike.
Then you make me come here.
That"s another.
Ah-ah.
That"s enough.
It "s a shame I can" t deal
with a better race of customers.
We got two strikes
on the batter,
so unless you want
to eat a baseball,
I would suggest you tell me
where my money is right now.
Hey, Vince.
It"s her.
Ah, shit.[ringing continues]
Game"s over.
[grunts][groans]
[in Spanish]
Pick up the damn phone.
[in English] Finally. Hey, pretty.
I told you not to come here. You
forgot to leave me the money again.
The money?[Riley laughing]
Riley, the bag.
[police siren wailing
in distance]
[Vincent] I"m sorry.
You want cash?
Here"s your cash,
you gold-digging whore.[gasps]
Now fuck off.
Remember, bitch eyes,
you"re just part of the act.
[laughing]
[in Spanish]
Bye now.
Is everything all right?
I just wanted to see you.
You know your mama"s
going to kill me.
She doesn"t need to know.
All right.
Come on in.
I brought you a gift.
[speaks Spanish]
[in English]
Where"d you get that?
Well, Mom told me
it was your favorite,
so I decided to keep it.
You know, my granddaddy used to sing
this all the time when we went out riding.
Really? Yeah.
I"ll tell you what.
Why don"t you, um,
keep this for me?
Are you hungry?
Do you like pizza? Of course I like pizza.
Everybody likes pizza. Let"s get pizza.
Pizza it is then.
[cell phone ringing]
Counselor. I hope you"re
long gone by now.
No, I"m still here. I surprised a bunch
of your relatives
trashing my office today.
No offense.
Fabulous-looking people.
Seemed very keen
to find your ass.
What "d you tell" em? What do you think?
I grabbed Jeffrey"s .45
and told "em to fuck off.
Are you okay?
Yeah, yeah.
Listen, don"t be dumb.
Leave town before the shit
really hits the fan.
See you, mate.
Wake up, son.
Come on, wake up.
[groans]Wake up.
What?
I have to take you home, okay?
But I want to stay here.
You can"t stay with me.
Come on, get your stuff.
[Julio] Thanks.[Neto in Spanish]
Take care, son.
[door closes]
Julio,
I told you you can"t see him.
He"s my dad.
I don"t care!
[in Spanish] You don"t understand,
son.[Julio in English] Whatever.
[shouting in Spanish]
Julio, come here! Julio!
[phone chimes]
[Latin hip-hop playing
over speakers]
[rapping in Spanish]
There"s nowhere to run.
[in Spanish]
Fucking Jesuit.
[grunts]
[screaming, groaning]
Puta!
[groaning continues]
[gunshot]
[screaming]
[shouting]
[car engine starts]
[cell phone ringing]
Who is this?
[Bailarin in Spanish on phone]
Fucking Jesuit.
[in English]
You still got it. Where are you?
You know me.
I got eyes everywhere.
Everyone is after you.
[in Spanish] You have more
fucking enemies than you think.
[in English] This is
why I told you to leave.
Yeah, I know.
You know what to do.
[bowling ball
rolling][bowling pins crashing]
All this time gone.
I never wrote.
I never came. I...
I thought
you would never be free.
It"s okay.
I don"t blame you.
I thought my life was over too.
I was afraid of what I
would feel when I saw you.
Julio always said
you were innocent,
and now he can"t stop
talking about you,
like some kind of saint.
Just tell him I"m not.
[Nadia and Neto moaning]
[both breathing heavily]
[moaning]
[moaning continues]
[belt buckle clinking]
Get out.
What do you think this is, huh?
This is the end.
I"m not going back
to the streets.
You thought I was gonna
give up everything, huh?
I have to think about me,
about what"s best for Julio.
Hey, he"s my son too.
If there is one thing
I hope for Julio,
it"s that he never
turns out to be like you.
[Neto] Oh, you want him
to be like Vincent then?
[Nadia] Fuck you! I know who he is, Nadia.
[Nadia]
Get the fuck out.
[car engine starts]
[in Spanish]
Tell him.
[keypad beeping]
[line ringing]
[cell phone rings]
Yeah? You were right, boss.
They are going different ways.
Right.
[in Spanish]
The Jesuit, guys.
Get the boy.
[cell phone ringing]
Hey, son.[Julio] Dad!
Dad! Can you hear me?[Nadia screaming]
They got Mom, and they"re
trying to get me. Dad? Dad?
[Nadia] No![gunshots]
[Julio] Dad!
[thunder rumbling]
This is Bobby, over.
[dispatcher over radio]
Hey, Bobby.
[Bobby] I think we found our
boy with his hand in the cookie jar.
So you might want
to send me some backup.
All right, honey?
Julio?
Julio!
[vase shatters][Julio] No!
Shut up,
you little shit! Shut up! Let me go! No!
Stop right there,
asshole.[panting] Dad. Dad.
Julio.Dad.
[screams]Julio, calm down.
[shouts]Everything"s gonna be okay.
Motherfucker. Hey!
You so much as twitch, I"m gonna blow
your goddamn brains out, you hear me?
You see, actions
have consequences.
Or didn"t they teach you
that in prison?
What, you think
you can come into my home,
fuck my woman,
and get away with it?
You let go of my son right now.
You see, that"s not gonna happen,
because he"s coming with me.
Riley, bury him.
[Julio screams][grunts]
[Vincent] Fuck!
Fuck!
[grunts]
[Bobby] Drop it! [grunts]
[Julio gasps]
Come on![grunts] Get off!
Where is he?
Where the fuck is he? Dad!
Find him and kill him![Julio grunts]
I"m going to find you!
You broke my fucking arm!
You fucking wetback,
skinny little shit motherfucker!
Where are you, man?
Where are you?
I"m gonna fucking kill you. You got
to say your fucking prayers, buddy!
Say your fucking prayers!
[gunshot]
Get in! Dad!
[Vincent grunts][Neto] Julio!
Shut up, or I"ll
shoot you in the face.
[Neto] Julio![tires screech]
[police siren wailing]
[siren stops]
Freeze!
Stop!
Now, I picked up your stuff.
Got your money and
your clothes from the motel.
Did the cops find Vincent?
No. No, nothing yet.
To tell you the truth, I don "t
think they" re particularly bothered.
What are you talking about?
I told "em about Vincent,
but all they really wanna do
is find The Jesuit.
The whole force seems to
have a bit of a hard-on for you.
Can"t say I blame them, really.
A vicious little fucker like you, a
murderer, gets released from prison.
Four days later, his wife and a
police sergeant are found shot to death,
and they see you running
from the scene of the crime.
Fuck. Fuck is right.
You gave them the needle
on the golden platter, mate.
I need to find Julio fast.
Well, bastard"s probably
gotten across the border by now.
Did you find out
anything about him?
Well, I made a few phone calls.
Um, Feds definitely
had him on their radar.
He"s supposed to be smuggling
a truckload of guns down south.
To tell you the truth,
Vincent makes people
a little bit nervous.
You know what I mean?
"La Cara del Norte," right?
Um, that"s his nickname,
"The Face of the North."
Why do you fucking people
always have to have nicknames?
[sighs] So?
Well, he was supposed
to have hooked up with, um,
a local gunrunner
by the name of Jet Rink.
That"s his real name, by the
way. That"s not a fucking nickname.
He"s a Catholic cunt, like you.
I think you should look him up.
Do you know where
I can find him?
Yeah, he owns a place
called Lady Birds.
What, the titty bar?
Yeah, that"s the one, yeah.
[car engine starts]
[Neto]
I need one more thing from you.
You got a full tank. I owe you big-time.
In that case,
do me a favor? Yeah?
Big-time. Yeah?
Forget my fucking number
before these psychos
kill me too.
[people cheering, whistling]
[upbeat dance music
playing in club]
playing over speakers]
[customer whistles]
[customer 2] Yeah!
Hi there.[dancer]
No, I did. I swear.
Yes, I said that
the next weekend after...
You"re up, sweetie.
There"s a man at the bar.
Not today.
I just can"t take it today.
[dancer]
Why? He looks nice. I"m going upstairs.
Howdy. Hi, I"d like a coffee,
please.
Uh, black? Yeah, black"s fine.
All right, there"s
a two-drink minimum.
I guess I"ll have two then.
Can I get
a black coffee, please?
How you doing? I"m fine, thanks.
Good.
All right, thank you.
All right, follow me.
[customer whistles]
There you are,
best seat in the house.
That"ll be $20.
Nice! Do you want company? Sure.
What"s your name? Inez.
That"s interesting.
Interesting for a stripper,
you mean?
Like it"s not
a regular stripper name?
What"s yours?
You know what Inez means?
It"s from Agnes.
It means "holy" or "chaste."
I bet I know
what you "re think in".
[chuckles] You "re think in",
"Oh, I bet you"ve been
"chased,"" or something like that.
Listen, honey.
I"m looking for Jet.
Who? Jet Rink.
I"m sorry.
I don"t know the guy.
You have a good time.
I"ll see ya.
[upbeat music continues playing]
[customers whistle, cheer]
[giggles] Baby, stop it.
What you making?
Lobster?
I like lobster.
[phone ringing]Mm-hmm. Butter?
Wait a second.
What?
[Inez] That cute Mexican"s
looking for Jet.
Tell Waylon to get his piece.
[customer whistling]
I"m looking for Jet.
He"s out sick today.
Called in.
You take a wrong turn?
A friend of mine, Vincent Rice,
suggested I contact Jet.
Said he"d help me out.
[customer whistles]
Lots of gun dealers in town,
they can do the same.
I understand that.
The thing is, Vincent
owes him some money.
[snaps fingers]
Here"s a down payment.
[Waylon] Hey, Collie. Is this
the spic I"ve gotta get rid of?
Everything"s fine, Waylon.
You want some rice and beans?
So, you got a number for him?
What"s your name?
Just tell him, um,
I want to establish a
long-term relationship, okay?
Really? How nice.
Hey, baby.
I got a fricking spic here.
He says he wants to...
Yeah, from Vincent.
I don"t...
Name?
John.
[chuckles]
Yeah.
John.
No, he"s a fricking beaner,
that"s what he...
All right, babe, I don"t
think it"s a good idea.
Fine. No, I...
Fine.
You can go out by his house,
out by Beeville.
Armadillo 67.
Don"t be there before midnight.
Call before you ring the bell.
[scoffs]
[in Spanish]
You"re welcome, John.
[reporter 1 on radio] An
Amber Alert has been declared
following the abduction
of Julio Niente,
allegedly by his father,
the notorious released killer,
Neto Niente.
A statewide manhunt
from Dallas-Fort Worth
to the Mexican border
is currently under way.
[reporter 2] This was preceded
by the grisly discovery
of the bodies of his ex-wife,
a state trooper
and an unknown male
at his wife"s residence.
[dog barking]
[blues playing over speakers]
Pretty clean for a spic.
Attaboy.
Hold up.
This way, friendo.
He"s clean.
John.
You like lobster?
You know these little fuckers,
they"ll amputate
their legs and their claws
if they feel
any sense of danger.
Is that right?
My little Collie,
she just loves them.
I do.
Careful, baby. You be careful, baby.
[chuckles]
In you go, you little fucker.
[laughs]
Ow!
Of course, you already
met my beautiful wife.
She said you were sick.
I am...
In the fucking head.
But she makes me
feel so much better.
Do I? Yeah, baby.
Come on. I want
to show you something.
Can we have a drink first?
Of course we can.
Get up there.
Follow me, John.
[gun cocks]
[blues playing]
Ah, here we are.
Guns, guns, guns!
Guns!
[Collie]
Welcome to our humble home!
Well, this here,
this is my pride and joy.
This belonged to Sam Houston.
It was made by, uh...
What "s that fucker" s name?
Henry Gross. Henry Gross, Ohio.
Actually used this
in the Mexican War.
But this one"s not for sale.
You mind if I take a look?
Honey, go get the
fucking drinks, would ya?
Straight Jack? Please.
Coming up.
Help yourself.
That "s what they" re there for.
[Jet] Now... [sighs]
...what can we do for ya?
I got cash.
I got customers.
And I got an in-place
transportation system.
I"d like to purchase
a hundred automatic rifles,
the latest design...
XM8s, FN-F2000s.
As many as you can get.
Fill out the order with M4s.
[Collie]
That "s one big fuck in" order.
Would you shut your mouth,
darlin", please?
So, uh,
what did you do before?
Work with Vincent.
And now you want
to work against him?
It"s called capitalism.
[Jet] Now, I take it
you have good-faith money?
I do.
How much you got?
10,000.
Let"s see it.
This beaner don"t look
like no John to me, Jet.
He looks like one of those
drug cartel guys from the news.
Shut the fuck up.
Waylon, count it.
The thing is,
I don"t do business
with people I don"t know.
[whispers] So what
the fuck are you doing?
Asking you to shut up.
So I called
me old amigo, Vincent,
seeing as you"ve been
spreading his name all over town,
and he told me
all about ya, Mr. Juan...
[grunts]
[Collie]
Shit! Fuck!
[Collie gasping]
You have no fucking idea
what you"re dealing with
here, mister...
Ah! You fuck![Collie screams] No!
[screams]
Ya fucking bastard! You son of a bitch!
Collie, get down now!
Get the fuck
off my property! [grunts]
You filthy, dirty bastard!
Fuck.
My baby.
You greasy little beaner! Collie, wait! No!
[gunshots]
[screams]
Collie?
Collie!
[sobbing]
You killed the only thing
I ever fucking loved.
Where"s Vincent?
Fuck you!
[screams]
Fucking motherfucker!
[groaning]
Where"s Vincent?
[breathes heavily]
I"ll tell you what I know.
If he "s not in Texas... He ain" t.
Then he"s down south,
buying up some shit condos.
There"s a leaflet
on the table up there.
So?
So that"s where
he keeps everything!
But if he"s running,
that"s where he"ll run.
You"re full of shit.
Call him.
Fuck you! [cries][grunts]
[grunts]
Give him a fucking call.
You fuck...
[cries] Baby.
Fuck my hole, motherfucker!
[barking]
[barking continues]
[barking stops]
[car engine starts]
[dog barking]
Come on, carnal, chase him!
[upbeat dance music
playing on speakers]
[people chattering]
You want a dance?
You like those?
Jake, can I...
Hi there.Hey.
Two coffees? Whiskey, please.
Whiskey? Yeah.
All right.
Two whiskeys, coming up.
There you are.
$40.
Listen, um...
Can you watch my seat?
I"d like to have a chat
with you when I come back.
Sure.
[customers cheering]
[Inez]
Can you get that tray?
[music volume increases]
[door creaking]
[snaps fingers]
[gun cocks]
[customers cheering]
[grunts]
Fuck!
[both grunt]
Who sent you?[in Spanish]
Motherfucker!
[screams][grunts]
[grunting]
[in Spanish]
Stay still, motherfucker.
[grunts]
[in English]
You"re working for Vincent?
[in Spanish] We"re not going to
tell you anything, fucking Jesuit.
[Neto in English] You"ve got five
seconds to tell me where my son is.
[grunting]
[gunshots]
[music continues]
Are you okay? Yeah.
What about the boys back there?[Neto] Yeah.
[music volume decreases]
Um, what time
do you get off work?
I"d like to hire you.
Yeah? Yeah.
I"d like you to be my wife.
Well, shit.
That"s some job.
Well, not the conjugal part,
just the pretending to be my
wife part to cross the border.
You mean not to care about
each other, just to pretend,
like... like a real wife?
Yeah.
You got a passport?
How much you paying
for this job, mister?
Well...
It"s only a day, so...
How about 500?
How about a thousand?
It gets really busy here
on the weekends.
And do I get
to keep my clothes on?
Yes, ma"am.
And then what happens?
Well, we cross the border.
The next day,
you take a bus back.
A thousand.
Just a ride. Across the border.
Do you mind?
Put it away.
You"ve been in prison, huh?
You"ve got that look.
So, I didn"t see those boys
come out of the bathroom.
The owners are used
to cleaning up
those kinds of messes
all the time anyway.
Do you want me to wear this wig?
Do you prefer blondes
or brunettes?
It"s driving me crazy.
It really itches.
I think this is going to be fun.
I"ve never been to Mexico, if
you can actually believe that.
[in Spanish]
Speak Spanish.
[Neto]
When the officer comes,
I want you to smile
and look pretty.
You understand?[Inez] Sure thing.
[border agents chattering]
[agent] Can you open
the trunk, please?
So, I"m thinking that $1,500
sounds like a more
appropriate amount.
Yeah, I ain"t paying you
to think.
[clears throat]
You know what?
Let"s make it 2,000.
It"s a more even number,
don"t you think?
It sounds nicer.
Okay, sweetheart?
[agents chattering]
All the way down.
Yes.
[both speaking Spanish]
[Neto]
We will spend the night here.
Tomorrow I"ll take you to the
bus station so you can go back.
[Latin music playing
in distance]
[service bell dings]
So, what are you looking for?
I know you"re looking
for something.
I"m looking for my son.
My wife"s boyfriend
took him, went south.
[in Spanish]
Good night.
Two rooms.
We only have one.
How much? Forty.
[Inez in English]
So, uh, this boyfriend...
You met him? Yeah.
And he"s met you? Mm-hmm.
[Inez] So he knows
you"re looking for him,
and you"re
just going to show up?
Yeah.
I mean, don"t you need
some help, maybe,
if you don"t mind my asking?
I mean, I can arrange
the contact for you.
He doesn"t know who I am.
Well, how much
is that going to cost?
I don"t know.
It sounds pretty dangerous.
Name your price.
Five grand, at least.
Goddamn, you"re just gonna
clean me out, aren"t you?
It"s a win-win, if you ask me.
Were those in the truck
the whole time?
Yep.
What was your plan gonna
be if the border man
asked to look through it?
Well, I wasn"t
too worried about him.
He was too busy
looking at your tits.
[gun clicks]
[Inez] Well, he wouldn"t
have been the first.
[sighs]Do you mind if I borrow
a shirt to sleep in?
I packed really fast
and I forgot one.
My sign is a Pisces. I am such
a Pisces. What sign are you?
I was kind of discovered
like Anna Nicole Smith.
I dream about going to Hawaii,
"cause I really wanna open
my own flower shop.
"Cause I do like making people
feel good, and I like having fun.
You would love my grandmother.
You know why?
Because she doesn"t ever talk.
I learned how to knit a little bit
by myself, which I like. I like it.
Yeah, I"m not so good at it,
but I"m not sure why,
but it"s just never
really stuck with me.
Oh, wow, are we here?
Are these them?
Ooh, they look like
pretty nice-looking condos.
[Inez] Houston.
Well, I"m originally from Waco.
Yeah. [chuckles]
That"s right.
So, yeah.
So, I have a friend, um,
who lives in Tampico,
and she was saying
that there was a...
You know, I saw your sign.
That"s what it was.
I saw your sign,
and I remember her saying
something about this guy,
Vincent Rice,
who is developing
a community of houses somewhere,
and it"s really
going to be great,
and that she wanted me
to look into it.
You know what?
I think I can do that. Uh-huh.
Yeah. Great.
I"ll see you in an hour.
And Vincent"s going
to be there, right?
Oh, great! That"s great.
He can!
Okay, good.
Good. Okay, thank you.
I appreciate it.
Thank you very much.
I"ll see you soon. Bye.
[Vincent]
I"m not gonna kid you, Inez.
You seem like
a real smart cookie.
The market"s going down,
the peso"s going down.
This is the time of opportunity.
It"s all upside.
Literally no downside.
"You buy low,
you watch it grow."
You know
who said that? No.
Somebody rich.
[chuckles] I bet.
So, you have children?
Oh, not yet.
I"ve been thinking about it, but I gotta
convince my boyfriend first, of course.
Boyfriend? Mm-hmm.
Aw.
Uh, you live here? No.
No, I live in a small mansion
on the other side of town.
Mmm.
Oh, my goodness.
They follow you
everywhere you go?
That"s
my sales team.Mmm.
Do you mind if I take
a couple pictures?
Feel free.
Just to show my boyfriend.
I think he would really...
Give me this... really like this place.
[in Spanish]
Felipe, bag.
[in English] So...
Yeah, I guess you can just
show me the facilities, you know.
Playground, clubhouse.
Clubhouse? Yeah.
Follow me.Okay.
[camera shutter clicking]
[breathing rapidly]
[Vincent] Up over there
is gonna be the greens.
Up top there will be
the new football field.
Of course, over here
will be the casino.
Right next to that,
the clubhouse
with, of course,
another pool, a sauna,
etcetera,
etcetera, etcetera.[Inez laughs]
Oh, I"m sorry.
Did you want one of these?
Oh. I never had
one of these before.
You"re
kidding me.Yeah.
How do you do it? Oh, it"s easy.
Just suck.
That"s it.
Mmm? [chuckles]Like a chimney.
[Vincent smacks lips]
That"s him, right? Yeah.
Okay, so...
[sighs]
...those are the condo
offices right behind him,
and let"s see...
There were workers all over.
They don"t look like workers
to me, but they were all leaving.
Um, and then here I am,
Miss Motormouth, of course.
"Can you show me this?"
and "Can I see that?"
"Take me here,"
and blah, blah, blah, blah,
running my mouth,
blah, blah, blah.
There were no sign of any kids.
There were no candy wrappers,
no sports stuff or footprints.
No clothing, nothin...
Any drawings? No.
He"s got him somewhere.
Well, I said
I"d see him at 10:00.
I didn"t ask you to do that.
Well, I did it on my own.
I"m a big girl.
And I"ve handled a lot worse
than him, that"s for sure.
[grunts]
[chattering in Spanish]
[guard speaking Spanish]
[buzzer sounds]
[in Spanish]
Let her in.
[guard speaking Spanish]
[Vincent in Spanish]
Ah, beautiful.
[Inez in English] Hey.
Whoo!
[in Spanish]
Very pretty.
[Inez laughs]
[in English]
This is romantic.
Thank you.
[chuckles]
Thank you
for coming.Oh.
[kisses][giggles]
Yeah.
So, you got something
to eat or...
I"ve got something much
more interesting than that.
Oh.
[in Spanish]
It"s fine.
[in English] Wow,
you look unbelievable!
[Latin music playing
over speakers]
[snorts]
Oh, damn, that"s good.
Mmm.Good. One more.
No. You.
No, I don"t partake.
[gasps]
What?
That"s not fair. One more.
[snorts]
Mmm.
That"s enough.
I was wondering something. What"s that?
Now, why is it that a
good-looking guy like yourself...
[laughs] ...doesn"t have a
regular woman? I don"t get it.
Oh, I just never had much luck
with the women. In fact, no luck at all.
I find that hard to imagine.
Well, aren"t you sweet.[giggles]
Can I have
some of this? Mmm.
Oh!
Whoo!
I need to use
the bathroom. No, no, no. Sit.
Okay.
[laughing]
Well, you sure like
that thing, don"t you?
[chuckles]
[humming]
[scoffs]
I really need
to use the bathroom... Sit! Sit!
[grunts][screams]
What "s wrong? What" s wrong with me?
No! No!
[grunts]
What, you don"t think
I knew you were playing me?
Who sent you? No one. Just don"t...
Who sent you? I don"t know what
you"re talking...
[grunts][groans]
[Vincent]
Such a pretty face.
What a shame.
[chattering in Spanish]
[silenced gunshot]
Get up![screams]
Get up! [grunts][yelps]
Get up!
Come here! Hey![screams]
Shut the fuck up. No!
[silenced gunshot]
[guard speaks Spanish]
I just want to know who to thank
for sending you! Who was it?
[screaming]
No! No!
No? Come here.
Open that mouth.
Eat that wood!
[grunts]
Before I carve up
that pretty face of yours,
you"re gonna tell me
exactly who it was!
Who was it?[blow lands]
[Inez gasps, breathes heavily]
Go to the motel.
I"ll call you if I need a ride.
What are you gonna do?
Go, please.
Where"s my son?
You"ll never find him.
You know that
during the Inquisition,
the Jesuits would place
the instruments of interrogation
right in front of the accused?
Often, that was enough.
They knew that everyone talks.
Every single one.
"Grief has limits.
Apprehension has none."
That"s a quote
from Pliny the Younger.
[grunting]
Now we begin.
[Vincent]
Wait, wait, wait.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Wait, wait. What are you
doing? What? What now?
Don"t, don"t, don"t.
Fuck! Fuck!
No! [screams]
Oh, my God!
Oh, you motherfucker!
Motherfucker!
[groaning]
[grunting]
They"re gonna kill you.
Oh, they"re gonna kill you.
[grunting]
They had time back then.
The accused were put in cages,
left to starve
for everyone to see.
Braided to wheels on high poles
for the heat
and the crows to pick at...
Your boy"s gone! You say his fucking name!
Julio! Julio!
They got him! He"s gone!
No, no, no!
[grunting]
[screaming]
Fuck.
[whimpering]
Okay, okay, oh...
Okay, okay. Okay.
Oh. Okay.
I"ll give you his name.
His name is...
Suck my dick.
[laughing]
Wait, wait. What are
you doing with that?
Don"t you fucking do that.
Don"t you...
[slices flesh][screams]
Señor Sans!
[sobbing]
Oh, God.
Who the fuck is Sans?
He"s a lunatic who lives
out in the jungle.
He used to be ATF.
[groans] He kidnaps
high-profile people...
Rich Mexicans, foreigners.
He"s got people all over the country,
and he"s got a shitload of guns.
You know why?
Because I sold it to him.
And that"s the truth.
Oh, fuck.
I just told you the truth.
What are you doing?
[breathing heavily]
No, no, no. I just told
you the fucking truth.
I just told you the truth.
No! No! No!
[screaming]
[sobbing]
Oh, God.
I told you the truth.
You want the real truth?
Huh?
I"ll give it to you. I"ll give
it to you. I"ll give it to you.
I owed Sans. I owed him.
What, you owed him?
You used my son
to pay off a debt?
Yeah.
Señor Sans. He likes...
He likes little boys.
[chuckles]
Right now, he"s got
a belly full of leche
and an ass full of cream cheese.
[laughing]
He"s had more cock in him
than a Tijuana
whorehouse. [laughing]
[dog barking in distance]
[dialing on phone]
[line ringing]
Bailarin, it"s me.
I really need your help.
[speaking Spanish]
Weren"t you going to lay low?
Walk the straight line?
[speaking Spanish]
[Neto] I know. Listen.
You know a guy named Señor Sans?
Quién? Señor Sans.
Some fucked-up ex-ATF agent.
He has Julio.
[in Spanish]
I don"t know that asshole...
[Neto in English] Fuck.
[in Spanish]
...but...
[in English]
I"ll make some calls.
Thanks.
I owe you for life.
You already do, carnal.
[in Spanish]
Take care.
[beeps]
[groans]
[sighs]
Would you mind?
No.
Thank you for saving my life.
Well, I was the one that
threw you in the lion"s den.
I volunteered.
For a price.
All those good old boys
down at the Lady Bird
probably miss
the hell out of you.
I want to stay.
I can"t afford you anymore.
I"m running low on cash.
[on phone] It"s Bailarin.
I know where
you can find Señor Sans.
[in Spanish]
Go to Tepito in Mexico City.
[in English]
Look for a boxing gym.
It"s called
Del Toros Boxing Gym.
It"s the only one.
[dogs barking in distance]
[Latin music playing inside]
[Inez] Is this it?
Oh, my God.
Are those guns?
[speaking Spanish]
[Inez] I just want you to tell
me what kind of boxing gym
has guys with machine guns
out in the front.
[Inez scoffs]
[clears throat]
So this Señor Sans guy
is not just a kidnapper, is he?
So, what"s your plan?
Are you just gonna
waltz in there
and ask for Señor Sans?
Pretty much.
I need to draw his people out.
You got enough money to catch
the first flight in the morning, right?
Who says I want to go?
[Inez moaning]
[both moaning]
[people chattering in Spanish]
This is it, Inez.
Come on.
Come on, please.
[whistles]
Hey, taxi!
Taxi, taxi!
[Inez]
Please don"t die.
Let"s go. Please.
Let"s go. Come on.
[chattering in Spanish]
[grunting]
[speaking Spanish]
Señor Sans?
[no audible dialogue]
[boxers grunting]
[in Spanish] He"s here.
Yes, he"s already here.
[wolf whistles]
[boxers grunting]
I told you to leave.
I"m just not the kind of girl
who leaves her man.
[Neto grunting][Inez screams]
[Latin music playing on radio]
[in Spanish] How much longer?
This crap still says five hours.
[car horn honks]
[grunting]
[grunts]
[tires screeching]
[gunshot]
[shouting in Spanish]
[grunts]
[tires screeching]
[screams]
[birds chirping]
[grunts]
[insects chirping]
[chattering over radio]
[Inez screaming in distance]
[Inez sobbing in distance]
[Inez speaking indistinctly]
[sobbing continues]
[gang member]
Want to live, bitch?
[in Spanish] I"m asking
you a question, bitch.
Are you ready for close-ups?
[blow lands][Inez groans]
Are you ready for the...
[gang member speaking Spanish]
[Inez screaming][gun cocks]
[in Spanish]
Move your hands, bastard.
Arriba!
[blow lands]
[prisoners whispering]
[flies buzzing]
[groans]
[whimpers]
[Neto groaning]
[metal gate creaking]
I thought you retired,
my friend.
New life and all that.
[grunts]
[screams]
[screaming, groaning]
Like my work?
[Inez screams]
Unfortunately,
it"s not original.
I"m just a copycat.
"Good artists borrow.
Great artists steal."
Where"s my son?
In time, my friend.
All things in time.
But I"m sure you learned that,
having spent all
that time in lock-up.
[in Spanish]
Take out the knives...
[in English]
and bring her.
[Inez screaming]
That was nice work you did
back at Vincent"s house.
Your son is this way.
You have a good-looking boy.[whimpering]
Sensitive soul.
[grunting]
[grunts]
He reminds me of my own son,
don"t you think?
I used to go by a
different name back then.
[Julio grunting]
Hey!
Don "t tell me you don" t
remember that face.
He"s the boy that walked in
while you were
cutting up his mother.
[child] Mommy?
[mother speaking Spanish]
Leave him alone.
[gunshot]
But I am the father of that boy.
Now it"s time
for some retribution.
[Julio grunting][Neto grunting]
Bailarin must"ve thought
it was time for you to pay.
They say time heals us.
Bullshit.
Dad! Dad!
[Sans] I guess this was
meant to be, amigo.
[Julio] Wait, no![grunts]
Blood in...
[Julio]
No! Dad! No! Dad!
Julio!...blood out.
[Inez screams]No! No!
Dad! Dad, please!
Dad! Please! Dad!
No! No! Dad...
[Sans speaking Spanish][screams]
[muffled screaming]
[Neto grunting]
[screams]
[gunshots][screams]
[gun clicks]
[grunts]
Yado! Leave him.
[grunts][screams]
[Neto grunting]
[Inez screaming][Neto] Julio!
[screams]
[Neto groaning]
[grunting]
[Inez screaming]
[gunshot][henchman screams]
[Neto] Julio! No!
Julio...
Yado!
I said leave him!
Goddamn it.
[Neto groaning]
You see?
This is what justice looks like.
Let"s see how your boy is doing.
[grunts]
[groaning]
[groaning continues]
[sniffling]
[prisoners chattering
in distance]
[Neto] Julio,
I was never the man
you thought I was.
I killed an innocent boy,
and for that,
you paid the price.
For all the things I"ve done,
for all the things
I"m about to do,
may God have mercy on my soul.
[groaning]
And now, Judas,
it"s time for you to pay.
[muffled shouting]