[FOOTSTEPS]
ERIC GELBER: This
journey is relentless.
This is a grueling endeavor.
To run this far,
you know, it hurts.
[POLICE SIREN]
I failed twice before.
It's entirely possible
that I could fail again.
[RETCHING]
I wish I could say that
Anita was here with me,
but she is not.
I think of her all
the time when I run.
All I want now is to finish.
It means everything.
[ICE FALLING]
Do you have the list?
Headlamps and handhelds.
So we can cross that off.
Four chairs.
1, 2, 3, 4.
I just want to make sure, you
know, every time I come around,
we should have one bottle of
water, one bottle of Tailwind.
Yeah.
I need someone out there
ready to give me the lube.
The lube.
Chapstick.
Sunblock.
I got it.
I've done this before.
OK.
I used to smoke two packs a day.
There's nothing I do
that's sort of half assed.
You know, my relationships
with friends,
you know, my family, I
mean, I'm in it 100%.
When I'm working,
I'm in it 100%.
And I'm just-- I'm very
passionate in my life
and everything.
And when I run, I think
it is an addiction.
This is important stuff.
These are our new
shirts this year.
These are all the names
of either people I know
or people who have just
asked me to run for somebody
that they care about.
The Central Park Run, which
we call the Journey Towards
a Cure, is still the hardest
thing I've attempted,
and I'm yet to finish.
No throwing lanterns.
The first time we did
this run was in 2013.
We covered 164 miles that year.
And we went back and
did it again in 2014.
Covered 176 that year.
And so this year,
I'm going to attempt
to finish 200 miles, which is
33 loops around Central Park,
over the course of one weekend.
Yeah, I mean, it takes its
physical toll, obviously.
So I had foot surgery.
I had hernia surgery.
And then I just had
labrum repair on my hip.
You know, it hurts,
and it takes a lot.
So, yeah, this will be my
third and final attempt.
Always pack with water bottle.
I saw that.
That's in here.
So I worry about the pain.
I worry about what's
going on in his head.
And I worry about
the hip because we're
less than a year
from the surgery
and I know he's just
going to keep going.
And I need to be there and
make sure you can keep going,
but I worry too.
But I've got to put my
crew chief hat on, set my--
ERIC GELBER: She's acting
all nice and sweet right now.
--set my wifey emotions
aside, and just kind of--
ERIC GELBER: As soon
as you get out there,
she tells me to get off my ass.
She doesn't let me sleep.
TANI GELBER: Right.
Come on, bear.
[LAUGHTER]
TANI GELBER: I'm definitely
nervous and anxious because I
know if he doesn't
complete that 200 miles,
he sees it as failure.
So I've got to help him because
it's his last opportunity.
[CAR ENGINE STARTING]
Good morning.
We are just leaving the
house, so we're on our way
to Central Park.
And today is the day.
I mean, I'm so motivated.
You know, failing twice
before, all I want
now is to make this happen.
My personal goal is
to finish 200 miles,
but really the big goal here
is to raise a total of $250,000
for the Multiple Myeloma
Research Foundation,
which will bring our all time
fundraising to over $1 million.
KAREN KARL: Hey.
How are you?
Everyone's a little
too happy to see me.
It's because I have cancer.
[LAUGHTER]
My name is on the shirt.
That's right.
I'm so excited
to get my shirt.
What size are you?
I would like the
biggest size you have.
I was diagnosed at
50, seven years ago,
with multiple myeloma.
I had never heard of the
disease, no less understand it.
And I was given
five years to live.
Multiple myeloma is a
disease of the blood
marrow inside your bones.
It has no cure.
It's not the most
common disease.
Hi.
KAREN KARL: This is an
unbelievable not only
fundraiser, but just a
great rise of awareness
so we can do research and make
this a manageable disease.
I started looking
into this disease
called multiple myeloma,
and I was scared to death.
Without the MMRF, I
would feel very isolated.
We support each other so much.
How are you doing?
CARMEN PHANEUF: And
we pray for a cure.
Thank you so much.
BILL MCHUGH: What he's
doing to fight this disease
and to find a cure for me
and everybody else that's
on this shirt is just amazing.
There's somebody
special to him that lost
the fight with this disease.
His friend, Anita, is gone,
but her legacy will live on,
and he's going to
be part of that.
ERIC GELBER: Anita's
diagnosis was
the beginning of our journey.
Anita was actually a very
close friend with my parents.
I would say she was family.
She was the first
person that I ever
knew that was sick and dying.
So in 2007, I decided to run
the New York City Marathon,
you know, to honor Anita.
She called me.
Eric, honey, you don't
know what this means to me.
Then I gave her my
medal from that run,
and she used to wear
it in chemo treatments.
She used to say that when I
ran, she could feel the medicine
going right into her veins.
To have him do this for us,
to raise this money for research
and hopefully a cure someday,
gives me great hope being
a multiple myeloma fighter.
KAREN KARL: This man is giving
a piece of himself to help me.
There's nothing more
heartfelt in your life.
There is a person
who wants to do this.
He's challenged himself three
times to try to get this done.
I know they say this is
the last time he'll try this.
I'm just hoping we hit that 200.
I really wanted to hit that 200.
WOMAN: OK, everybody.
Time to go to the start.
I'll see you in an hour or so.
All right.
WOMAN: Hey, everybody.
Everybody get a shaker.
Allen, who is
Anita's husband, is
going to start the race for us.
WOMAN: Yay, Allen.
You ready, Eric?
Yeah.
Let's do it.
Here we go.
[AIRHORN BLASTING]
[APPLAUSE]
ERIC GELBER
(VOICEOVER): 200 miles.
7 and 1/2 marathons.
33 laps around Central Park.
[BELLS RINGING]
[CHEERING]
Breakfast of champions.
I love it.
Who's got the bottles?
Love you, Eric.
ERIC GELBER (VOICEOVER):
I'm not running a 5K here,
so I just want to get in a
rhythm that I can maintain.
It's almost like a
beat in your head.
It's the perfect beat.
I can hear my feet.
I can hear my
heart, my breathing.
And then just cruise.
You know, when I first started
running, it was just me.
I was running it for one person.
There's a lot of names,
you know, on my shirt
at this point.
It's really this whole journey
that we're all on together.
This is way bigger than me.
He just started at 8:00 AM.
He's going to run
200 miles to raise
awareness and funds
for multiple myeloma,
which is a blood cancer.
Oh, wow.
ERIC GELBER: I feel like
there's a lot of people
depending on me, you know.
He's ready for the ice?
OK.
Where are you guys?
They're about 15 minutes away,
but he wants now full ice
in both cups and cantaloupe.
It's getting hot now.
[BELLS RINGING]
[CHEERING]
WOMAN: Eric.
We got you, Eric.
Eric, thank you
for all you do.
You're a wonderful human being.
It's just so awesome
what's going on here.
You know, you get a
disease that you think
you're just going to die from.
You don't realize--
you don't realize
the help that's out there.
How are you feeling?
I'm feeling good.
Yeah.
We're doing well, right?
We're waiting on a phone
call, so I'm hoping--
I said, what better
place to be than here?
So we'll see.
And the phone call's coming
today, or you don't know?
Hopefully.
I had a biopsy of a lung.
ERIC GELBER (VOICEOVER):
You're dealing
with an incurable disease, and
the five year survival rate
right now is only about 43%.
Even though, you
know, there's hope
and there's more drugs and
all of that, in the end,
I keep getting bad news
about all of my friends.
So, you know, I'm
like, well, all right.
I'm just going to
keep running then.
[BELLS RINGING]
[CHEERING]
You're going to do awesome.
Love you too.
Wish we could be here.
We'll be here in spirit.
You know that.
- All right.
I'll talk to you later.
- Love you.
You got this.
MAN: Hang in there.
You're doing great.
OK.
Shoe change and we're out.
Did he go to the bathroom?
Yes.
So it's 7:15.
We're almost 12 hours in.
And we start worrying
at this time of day
because now the sun is going
down and he's obviously tired.
And he starts to
get a little low.
So this is where it's really
important for me and our crew
to kind of motivate
him and push him along.
If he can just get
through the night,
that would be a huge thing.
All right.
CARMEN PHANEUF: Hi.
How are you?
How you doing?
Good.
I'm going to go with
you to the next one.
OK.
Awesome.
CARMEN PHANEUF: Almost
all cancer patients
go through pain and
suffering and loneliness
and fear that they're
not going to make it.
You know, for a lot of us, it is
one foot in front of the other,
one day at a time.
In 2002, we had
decided it was time
to try to have a baby, so I did
some pre-pregnancy blood work.
And the doctor said, you know,
something's really wrong.
We were, like, in
disbelief because I
was in the prime of my life.
I was in great
shape, working out.
We were so excited.
We had lived on a
sailboat for three years,
had taken a year off from
work, and we're coming back
and we want to settle.
And then you hear this.
It was just unbelievable.
Being pregnant and going
to the cancer center
and sitting in the
waiting room, you
know, being five months pregnant
when everybody has masks on
and is bald, for me, that
was one of the hardest parts.
And finally, at six months,
I said, I'm not coming back.
It was very difficult
to start chemo.
I physically-- I couldn't
walk into the infusion center.
I had a huge breakdown right
outside the doors with Michael
because this was
like the beginning,
you know, of this, you
know, journey so far.
And it was one of the hardest
things to do, is walk in
and, like, start.
Of course there was
fear and uncertainty.
But I think part
of my personality
was that I am going to
live as long as I can,
and I'm also going to
live under my terms
because you don't know how
many days or moments you
have really left.
Things could, like,
switch in a month for me.
That's the truth.
You know, what he's doing
is incredibly difficult,
and there is pain and
suffering involved in it.
And I'm sure at points,
he's questioning himself.
Can I do it?
He has fears that he's
not going to succeed.
--trying to make history
this weekend by running
around Central Park 33 times.
Describe to someone
what your 24 hours, what
these 2 and 1/2 days, are like.
It's a roller coaster.
I'm up here right now.
At 3:00 in the morning,
I'll probably be down there.
So in the past, he'll
start getting tired and sore
and just keep moving and pushing
through and not stopping.
This time, we tried
something new.
He actually stopped for 20
minutes and closed his eyes
and put his feet up.
This is going to
be the strategy.
Let's see.
$259,018.
WOMAN: Awesome.
WOMAN: Wow.
That's exciting.
Wow.
TANI GELBER: The donations
are still coming in.
We're well past $1 million
now, so the stress of getting
the money raised, it's done.
The 200 miles, that's--
that's what he's thinking about.
That was 14, right?
That was 14.
Sorry.
What?
Are you sure?
No, I'm serious.
You just finished 13.
MAN: Go get them.
TANI GELBER: Be strong, baby.
Eric just went out
for his 14th loop.
He's a little frustrated because
he thought he came in and had
just completed his 14th floor.
Now, the mental
challenge is upon him.
[POLICE SIREN WAILING]
ERIC GELBER (VOICEOVER):
The early morning
always is tough for me.
I just get really tired.
It's just hard to--
hard to motivate.
I'm so tired.
My feet are killing me.
It's typical, you know.
It just came on a
little sooner today.
I'm running, and
I'm fighting really
hard to get through something.
And then I'll think
about my friend, Anita.
I don't remember when
I first found out,
and I had never heard of it.
I didn't know what it was.
It didn't even strike me as
being all that bad, frankly.
I'm like, OK, she's got cancer.
She'll go through chemo.
She's going to be fine.
And then when I saw her
going through her stem cell
transplant, that's
when it really hit me.
She's got a fatal cancer.
I mean, she's dying.
It just changed my
perspective about everything.
I think about that
when I'm struggling.
Is something really so hard,
or is it really so bad?
I mean, I can certainly,
you know, keep running.
553.
Just don't trip on your son.
What is that, 85.4?
5.4.
TANI GELBER: Can you still
do math right now, babe?
I would like to just take off
my socks and put my feet up.
Now, or--
Well, do you want
to talk about that?
Because-- do we want
to talk about reality?
Yes.
OK.
Do you think I'm
actually going to finish?
You're doing really well.
I know, but--
I don't want you to think
like that at this point.
I know.
I'm trying not to.
It hurts.
You're doing good.
I know.
TANI GELBER: It's tough because
am I a crew chief first,
or am I his wife first?
Do I look at him like, OK,
he's the father of my children?
Is he going to be able to run
around with kids and grandkids?
Or as crew chief,
do I keep pushing
him to get through this run?
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Does he need to sit?
Does he--
No.
He's good.
Give him-- let's do
water, ginger ale, salami,
potatoes, and cantaloupe.
Here he comes.
I'm coming.
I don't know if I
should sit for a minute.
Why?
What's wrong?
Just I've been sore and tired.
OK.
Is that OK?
I don't think you
need to right now.
Can you walk?
Yeah.
The sun's up.
I don't want to lose momentum.
I'm pretty strong, and I can
handle seeing him in pain.
My feet every step
feel like someone's
hitting them with a hammer.
Every step is just a
pounding in the quads.
It just hurts just all the time.
TANI GELBER (VOICEOVER): But
I have to think of what's
best for him in the future.
And I'm always having
this battle with myself.
ERIC GELBER: I know she
knows that I'm going
to go through these things.
It's like putting out a fire.
Still, when you see someone
you care about going through,
it's got to be--
you know, it's got to be tough.
Are you mad at me?
No.
OK.
You going to tell
me I'm mean again?
She wants him to finish.
She knows the disappointment
the last few times
he's attempted this.
She's the one that
ultimately with him
has to make the call of
whether to keep going or stop.
And I think that
pains her a lot.
Do you have any requirements?
ERIC GELBER: I don't know
what I want to do right now.
OK.
I'm so fucking tired.
[BELLS RINGING]
KAREN KARL: Running
the damn 200 miles.
I can't even run
one lap with him.
But I ring a good cow bell.
MAN: Yes, you do.
I ring a nice cow bell.
I should have been
a cheerleader.
It's too hot.
Don't push it right now.
There's no need.
You're doing great.
You're going nice and steady,
and I feel like you're
feeling pretty good.
KAREN KARL: The change
cancer does to all
of us is more than physical.
It brings you closer to
people on another level.
I went into a depression
after my stem cell transplant.
And had you asked me then, I
would say, I'm not depressed.
I have cancer.
That was my low point,
when I just had to say,
is this all worth it?
My mother sat there and babied
me like I was six years old,
literally fed the
oatmeal like, come on.
Open up.
The train is coming.
She'd follow me into the shower.
It was just dehumanizing.
But she saved my
life, literally.
And my dad--
I never watched
baseball in my life.
My father came over every Yankee
game for that entire season.
I'm bald, broken hipped, stem
cell transplanted, and on oxy.
We're sitting on the couch, and
I'm passing out on his shoulder
and he's talking.
That's Derek Jeter.
That's Mariano Rivera.
This is what a closer does.
This is what this--
and he took me to the
playoffs that fall.
Emotionally healing
from cancer is huge.
And I've come to realize
everybody needs a team.
Everybody needs a team.
Actually, can you
hold it behind me?
ERIC GELBER: It's huge.
All right.
Let me go take care of that.
Can you spread your toes?
Cut it.
Oh.
ERIC GELBER: There we go.
Feels better now.
The question is, what's
going to happen to it later?
That's bad.
MAN: Things like the blisters
and for Eric, anything that's
going to throw off
your gait, that
is something kind of serious.
And, you know, he's
been going 120 odd miles.
So it's starting to break down.
He's starting to get tough.
He's tearing apart his body.
It's the pain that he'll
deal with to help fight
the disease that I'm fighting.
So yes, I can run
five more steps,
but he's running five more
steps, which is resulting
in 500,000 more dollars,
which is resulting in three
drugs being released last year.
These are action and rewards.
And they're occurring.
And it's making a difference.
TANI GELBER: He's
starting to feel all
of the pressure of finishing.
Look at everyone that
is here to support me
and I can't let anybody down.
The crew, we're working really
hard to just keep him motivated
and keep him moving.
Want to stretch,
bend over and stretch
a little bit, your back.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
TANI GELBER: These
last two attempts
at Central Park, because
he didn't get to 200 miles,
that was a huge disappointment.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
You know, he was barely moving.
And everything hurt.
I thought to myself,
you can't even walk.
There's no way he can run.
He's in so much pain.
Every single step
he took was painful.
We just looked at each other and
we knew, like there was really
nothing needed to be said.
And he just apologized.
And I told him there was
nothing to apologize for.
And I called the crew over and
just said, we're going to stop.
It was the right decision.
And I personally was relieved.
But I felt like
I had failed him.
Because I couldn't
get him through.
I'm getting really sharp
pains along outside and across,
and in this toe.
But it's like it's
putting me to tears.
It's so fucking painful.
TANI GELBER: He recognized all
that he did in those first two
years, but he was
focused on falling
short of that 200 miles.
So in his eyes, he wasn't done.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[SIREN]
I want to be
able to suck it up,
but I just don't
know how long I can.
OK, one step at a time, right?
[MUSIC PLAYING]
TANI GELBER: I'm definitely
worried Eric's not going
to be able to get this done.
[COUGHING]
As crew chief, as
his wife, I don't
know if I would be able to
pick up the pieces for him
if he doesn't finish.
You're the best dad
and best husband.
I don't want-- so
many look up to you.
You've already done so much.
Don't forget that.
All right.
OK?
Yep.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
WOMAN: Good morning,
how are you?
The red, white and
blue in the house.
TANI GELBER: There's a lot
of activity in the park
already, because the
New York Road Runner
18 mile tune up is starting.
That means 7,000 people
will be joining Eric.
It's going to be a
shit show out there.
You know what, I
bet you anything--
I don't know I'm
going to deal with that.
--you're going to
feed off that energy.
It's a new day.
He's gotten through the night.
MAN: How's that feel?
OK?
TANI GELBER: I think we
can really just push him.
And I know he's going
to want to be pushed
to get to that 200 mile mark.
WOMAN: Excuse me,
your father is here.
How are you?
Good, how are you?
When I see him, his feet
bleeding, and the pain
that he's gone through,
he just is an inspiration.
As a kid, you know,
Eric had his share
of issues getting in trouble.
I was very happy
Eric took up running
instead of going to jail.
I mean, when he was about 16,
we called it the black years.
Everything he bought was black.
Anita's the kind of person
that would buy him black
because it made him happy.
She always stuck by him.
She always was
supportive of him.
And when she got ill, she
made a conscious decision
that she was not going
to be a victim of life.
And she did the best that she
possibly could to hold her own.
I think all of that
rubbed off on Eric.
And I think that was
the change in his life.
She's a loss.
Anita is a loss.
But not only does
her memory live on,
her behavior lives on in
the people that loved her.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
ERIC GELBER: I've never
ever had this much pain.
I keep thinking about stopping.
MAN: I'm from here, but I
grew up in Pennsylvania.
Yeah.
Yeah, that was fun--
fun times.
[CHATTER]
ERIC GELBER: People keep coming
up to me and saying thank you.
Telling me how much it means.
So basically, I got
myself into my own mess.
I don't see any other
way to get out of it.
MAN: I was diagnosed in 2008.
So January, 2013, I
did my transplant.
I had a big
fundraiser beforehand
for the Myeloma Foundation.
And that next year, I
met this gentleman here.
And I had a biopsy in May.
And I'm all clear.
I have no trace of disease.
Wow.
Amazing.
And I swore that this guy
is going to make his 200,
and I will never
lose my hair again.
We're done.
MAN: Yeah.
MAN: When I first lost my
hair it was very awkward,
and I didn't know what to do.
And I remember getting
into the shower,
and hair is just
pouring out of my head.
And I called my wife in,
and I said, is it bad?
She goes, uh, yeah.
I said give me the clippers.
It was tougher going into work,
because only a couple of people
knew what was going on.
And so to walk into work
that day with a baseball cap,
and take the baseball cap off,
and the room just gets silent.
And nobody knows what to say.
And it's that awkward moment
that you don't want to be in.
It's the big
elephant in the room.
How do you talk about
it and how do you get
people to know what's going on?
Eric puts on a shirt, this one's
for Bill, this one's for Trish,
this one's for Anita.
I'm one of those people.
And I see what he
does as a way for us
to gather together
and bring awareness
for what this disease is.
Yeah, Eric.
MAN: He's not a
professional runner.
He's just Eric.
And to that point, he and
I are in the same boat.
It gives everybody that
superhuman kind of hope.
We are making a
poster to celebrate
this next lap,
because Eric is going
to surpass his past record.
MAN: If he can do this, I
know I can fight this thing.
You ready?
Yeah.
Let's go.
WOMAN: You know, everybody wants
to hear the crowd roar for him.
And they want to be
part of something
bigger than themselves.
He runs because he loves it.
I know that.
But he also runs because
he wants to make me better.
Where would anyone rather
be than around people that
understand you, and
are rooting for you,
and want to make you better.
You beat your record.
You're doing great.
WOMAN: And the feeling I
get of being part of this,
it's truly unimaginable.
I don't feel invisible.
I don't feel like nobody
knows my struggle.
Nothing beats that, nothing.
And I won't ring
that cowbell forever.
We're killing it.
He's doing it.
It's just becoming
more and more real.
I feel like he can see it.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
He wants to go to 2--
I knew it.
Hey, team.
MAN: Yes.
They called ahead.
They're at the carousel.
And he's powering through.
He's just going to want drinks.
He's going to eat and fly
by like he did at the start.
We're working.
This is it, we're doing
this all the way to the end.
Straight through.
[CHEERING]
Eric.
He's amazing.
I love him so much.
God bless him.
[CHEERING]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
TANI GELBER: In
20 to 30 minutes,
Eric's going to be coming in
after running his 32nd lap
around Central Park.
He started Friday at 8 AM.
And we're going to go off
and finish the last lap.
It's crazy.
It's going to happen.
It's real.
ERIC GELBER: Everything in life
is a matter of perspective.
When I'm done, I
mean, I'm like going
home and climbing into my bed.
And everything's fine, you know.
Except for the fact that
all my friends are sick.
They go climb into bed,
and they're still sick.
You know, and they can't
get away from that.
So, you know, I
think about that.
And I, you know,
want them to live.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
TANI GELBER: Alrighty.
WOMAN: Last loop.
[CHEERING]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
What do we do when
we go down hill?
Run.
[CHEERING]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
MAN: Let's go.
I can't believe it.
MAN: Where do you
want to go eat?
Around the corner?
MAN: I actually can't
see which one is Eric.
Bill's kind of get his--
MAN: What's his last name?
Eric Gelber.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
MAN: Dad, you ready?
Eric in front.
You guys good?
[CHEERING]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
We did it.
You did it.
I love you so much.
I love you too.
[MUSIC PLAYING]