( footsteps )
( lock clicking )
Fall in and catch it.
Rise up and let the wind take
you there.
Put your head down and keep it
down, girl.
Arms. More arm.
See what happens when you listen
to me?
Reach down and grab the victory.
Feel the power, Gail.
Inside and out.
Drive. Pull.
Speed merchant.
That's what you are.
They can't catch you, Devers.
Unless you want to be caught.
Get going, girl.
( gunshot, cheering )
Come on. Come on, now.
Yes!
( reporters clamoring )
The winner of the women's
100 meter hurdles, Gail Devers,
with a time of 12.68 seconds!
A new national record!
( cheering )
I won! Did you see me?
I saw it.
I set a record.
Barely.
Had a long takeoff, short
touchdown, head way up in the
clouds somewhere.
Bobby, I won today.
So did 100 other girls
in 100 other places.
And if you don't stay on it,
the Games, they're gonna slip
right through your fingers.
Keep trying to tell you,
you ain't gonna listen.
Okay, I'll practice my
takeoffs and work on my
touchdowns.
Hey, G. Congratulations.
You won today.
( bells chime )
Gail.
Hey, ma.
I can't believe it.
This is my day.
Come on, your Daddy's waiting
for you.
You were supposed to be here
30 minutes ago.
I know that.
How do you do?
Where were you?
The caterer was late.
I got the wrong caterer.
I'll never use him again.
Hello.
How do you do?
Thank you for coming.
Everything's okay, don't make
a fuss.
Don't you look nice.
Yes, okay.
Why do we always get nervous?
I don't understand.
I don't remember.
It's been so long since your
uncle and I got married, but--
One more.
Wow.
Is that the last one?
Just ten more.
Oh, no, no.
We have to get her ready.
Who's cousin are you?
I'm, um--
This is R.J.'s second
cousin.
Well, uh, yes.
Glad to-- glad to meet you.
But let's get her ready.
We'll see you outside.
Oh, okay.
Um, one more.
Coach Kersee, so glad to see
you.
You too, Reverend Devers.
Gail will be pretty.
Thrilled I'm not gonna make
her run today.
Thank the Lord I only have to
do this once.
What do you think?
Well, I think they might just
make it.
I'm getting a front row seat and
watch the festivities.
Okay.
Good luck to you, sir.
Okay, see you at the
reception.
Gail, what is--
Something's wrong.
I'm gonna have to take a tuck
in this.
On, no, Mom, we can't take
a tuck in this--
This fit you perfectly a week
ago.
How could you lose--?
My body's always changing.
How could you lose so much
weight in one week?
Come on, Mema, it's okay.
Nobody's gonna notice but you.
I know.
Get your granny's diamond
earrings over on the table.
Careful.
Congressman, how are you?
So nice to see you.
No. You are not gonna do this
again.
Not again.
Can't help it.
I'm so happy today, Mema.
Hope it stays that way
forever.
Kid, you deserve it.
( choir member sings )
We are gathered here today
to join this man and this
woman in the holy state of
matrimony.
It is a solemn moment and one
not to be entered into lightly.
You may now kiss the bride.
( applause )
( light jazz music )
You stepped on my foot,
Robert.
Get your foot out the way,
Jackie.
Sure you know how to do that,
don't you?
You used to be able to dance.
Oh, I'm just waiting for my
song.
I do. Come on.
Let's go visit Jackie and
Robert.
Hey!
Congratulations.
Hey, you.
Baby girl.
Congratulations.
Here I go again.
Hey, man.
I didn't know you owned a pair
of hard shoes, Coach.
I like to get off the track
from time to time.
You got a suit too.
Yeah. Come together.
You all leave my handsome
husband alone.
You heard that, huh?
Shall we dance?
Ooh, stop it, Bobby, behave.
( wine glass rings )
First of all, on behalf of
Mr. and Mrs. Hampton, my wife
and myself, I want to thank
each and every one of you
for coming.
I think it's about time that we
let these young people go and
begin their married life.
But before they do, I want to
say a few words, because that's
what ministers do and I paid
for the wedding.
( laughter )
You've got to know that this
is one of the happiest moments
in my life.
We've all seen Gail grow up
in this church family.
And we've seen her grow into a
champion runner blessed with
divine power.
R.J., her husband, is a fine
athlete in his own right.
He's not as fast as Gail, but
then again he is.
( laughter )
But at least, R.J., you don't
have to bring her in by 12:00
anymore.
Thank you.
But seriously, R.J., I can't
think of a better husband for
my daughter, or a finer
son-in-law.
Gail, R.J.,
to you Gail, and to you, R.J.,
I'd like to wish you both
God's blessing, God's grace,
and above all, Godspeed.
Godspeed.
( gulls calling )
Come on, Gail!
I thought you said this was
gonna be the last mile!
Catch up, R.J.!
All right, now.
Don't think I can't catch you.
Where are we going?
Where you going?
Come on, now.
Come on!
I got you! I got you now!
I'm coming! ( roars )
( both laugh )
Thought you'd get away, huh?
( laughs )
You want some fun, don't you?
I'm hungry.
Let's get some breakfast.
No. I'm not ready to eat yet.
'Cause, uh, there's nobody
here but you and me.
Come on, R.J.
Let's run.
Run?
I only have two more miles to
go.
It's my honeymoon.
Just two more miles.
I promise I'll be back before
you get out of the shower.
I'm going back, Gail.
I'm going back now.
I'm going-- Gail? For real.
Keep that water running!
I'm leaving now, Gail.
( R&B Pop music )
Honey, this is beautiful.
Careful, now.
I just got you, I don't wanna
lose you.
You're not gonna lose me.
Know what? Let's buy a house.
I mean a big house.
Yeah, with lots of rooms.
And a garden full of flowers.
And a fireplace.
Yeah, and a dog.
Oh, gots to have a dog.
Look after you, the kids when
I'm not at home.
So I don't have to worry about
my little family.
( starter gun fires )
I think I made it.
I wasn't supposed to win, I was
supposed to qualify.
Qualifying for the U.S. team,
and the Games in Seoul are
Kisha McCantz, Shannon Woods
and Gail Devers!
That's the point.
I just had to qualify.
( indistinct dialogue )
( pants )
( whistle )
Dammit!
Gail, what're you doing?
Nothing, I'm fine.
Look, this race takes fifty
strides, no more, no less.
You're four more better than
fine.
Just a little tired, that's
all.
Tired?
Tired as in, uh, you got too
much sleep, or tired as in,
you didn't get enough?
I got just the right amount.
Just got the right amount?
Mmm-hmm.
Hey, what do you see?
Where?
Down there.
Tell me what you see.
A lane.
Past that.
A wall.
I can't see past the wall.
Right.
Can't see past the wall.
You wanna win the gold?
Yeah--
Do you want to win the gold?
Yeah, I wanna win the gold.
See, what you don't know
is you already got it.
It's out there waiting for you
to claim it.
You got to use your mind and
your heart.
Got to imagine yourself already
winning that race.
Imagine yourself crossing that
finish line.
First. Huh?
Retrace the steps that got you
there backwards.
So you end up right here, right
now.
But--
I don't want to hear it.
Two 100 meter repeats.
Chop chop. Right now.
Right now.
Gail, shy do you take that
shit from him?
Same reason everybody else
does.
He's the best track coach in the
world.
Says him.
Says everybody.
I don't wanna talk about Kersey
anymore tonight.
I just wanna go to sleep.
My head is killing me.
Mama, what you got on?
Mmm. What you doing now?
Oh, my eye hurts.
Mmm, here.
I'm gonna kiss it and make
it better.
Mmm, you smell good. Oh.
R.J.
Mmm-hmm.
Where you goin'? Huh?
R.J.
What do you see?
What?
There. What do you see?
R.J. I'm too tired--
Oh, see, you're not looking.
But I am.
I don't just see a bed with some
sheets and pillows.
Oh, no.
Well, what do you see?
What you've got to see.
To the other side of that bed.
Past those sheets and pillows.
See, you gotta see your
fulfillment, already there.
Sexual ecstasy.
Just waiting to be claimed.
I'm not sure I wanna claim
it.
But you got to.
It's already there.
Gotta see it backwards.
See yourself.
Gail? I was thinking--
thinking about getting cable
hooked up.
What do you think?
Sure, yeah.
Don't forget to call that rep
for All Sports Endorsements.
He sounded serious.
Called me three times.
You hear me, baby?
Yeah. I heard you.
Can you bring me a towel?
Yeah.
Here you go.
We can be out here all night
if you wanna--
You wanna start moving these
numbers in the right direction?
Huh?
I don't know.
Is it fear, Devers?
'Cause fear is not real, you
know, just an excuse to keep
you from doing the work that you
ought to be doing!
I'm not trying to get--
No, you're not!
I'm gonna hit the showers.
Hey, Devers.
Think Europeans are hitting the
showers? Huh?
( distant thunder )
( gasps )
( groans )
( crowd cheering )
Go, R.J.!
Come on!
Qualifying for the U.S. Team
in Seoul in the Men's 400 Meter
are, George Chapall,
Michael Meadows
and Steve Heinke.
This can't be.
What's happening?
Oh, hey, girl.
Hey, Jackie.
You're trying to beat the
line too, huh?
Yeah, I gotta get out of
here.
Somebody's been doing too
much honeymooning.
Yeah, it's R.J.'s cooking.
I wouldn't say that to Bobby.
You know that's right.
What?
You're not pregnant, are you?
No, I'm not pregnant.
I just weighed in with my flats
on, that's all.
I know what can happen on a
honeymoon.
Well, it didn't.
Of course, when I think about
it, when Bobby and I first
got married, the next time
I looked up, I was carrying five
pounds of somebody else's boot
in my body.
And I know he had something
to say about it too.
Get up out the chair.
You're just in time.
Team weigh in.
Stand in line there.
No, I gotta go.
Sorry I can't stay, Dr. Otis.
( door closes )
R.J.?
Yeah?
Hi, baby.
When did you get home?
Three hours ago.
Practice ran long today.
I had to stop at the store.
Got home as soon as I could.
How was your meeting?
My job stinks, Gail.
I wanted to come home and tell
you about it, I even hoped that
maybe you might've even had
dinner ready for me.
Imagine that.
Well, I'm making dinner for
you right now.
I've already eaten.
Towels.
Three hours.
Three hours, Gail.
I told you practice ran long
tonight.
You don't have to run every
second of every day!
You're certainly living proof
of that.
I'm going out.
I don't need this shit.
I don't need this.
I'll be back on the 27th.
How am I supposed to reach
you in Korea?
There's a phone number on
the refrigerator.
Just in case.
They d=said it's gonna be warm
over there, so I'm not gonna
take a lot of stuff.
Oh, do you know where my red
sweatshirt is?
Uh, clothes hamper last time
I saw it.
( phone rings )
Hello?
Hi, Mema.
It'll take you about an hour to
get here.
I'll be ready for sure by then.
Hold on.
Baby, I gotta go.
Have a good time.
I'll call you, R.J.
( door slams )
( engines roar )
( crowd cheering )
( announcer speaks Korean )
Ladies and gentlemen,
this is the first qualifying
heat for the women's 100 meter
hurdles.
( announcer speaks Korean )
( starter gunshot, cheering )
Gail, you okay?
Jackie, something's wrong
with me.
What's wrong?
I'm going home, Bobby.
Is this the right position?
Are all the test results in?
Well, what could it be?
We want an answer.
It's nothing.
We can't find a thing.
Look, the x-rays are clear.
And that's all you can tell
us?
Here, see for yourself.
( machine clicks )
It's probably just stress.
Doctor, my daughter is an
athlete.
She's a fine tuned machine.
She knows when there's something
wrong, and so do I.
Please, you're always free
to seek a second opinion.
Mrs. Devers, I believe that
this is an emotional response.
Is there something bothering
you?
There's nothing bothering her
at all, thank you, Doctor.
I can't believe this.
Hey.
Nothin', huh?
That's what they say.
Unless they say I have
everything, which is the same
as nothing.
I'm the sickest healthy person
around.
Then they don't know what it
is.
They mostly say it's stress.
They're doctors, they ought
to know what they're talking
about, that's what it is then.
They don't know.
Only I know what's wrong with
me.
You do, huh? What is it?
When I started running,
it was almost by accident.
My mother said I had stolen
a star from the sky.
I would look up into the night
and I'd wonder which star
I'd stolen.
Then I got scared, 'cause
I realized if I had stolen
a star, it wouldn't be up there,
it would be with me.
Wouldn't God want it back?
I'm saying God came and took his
star and stuck it back up in
the sky.
Maybe he doesn't want me running
anymore.
What do you think?
What do I think?
I think it's the most words you
said at one time since I've
known you.
( thunder )
Hey, it's getting a little
late.
Let's go.
No, I'm gonna sit here for
a while.
Practice tomorrow, Devers.
Be ready.
( thunder )
Dammit.
You sure running is your gift,
Devers?
You added three tenths to your
time.
You must be marked or something.
The great Gail Devers.
It's Mrs. Hampton.
Excuse me. Mrs. Hampton.
Haven't seen your husband around
here in so many months, thought
you might've been a widow.
By the way-- hey!
We don't believe in godspeed
here on my track.
We rely on our own.
Got it?
Now do it again and faster this
time.
Come on!
Show you're right!
How come you didn't do that in
the first place?
Much faster when she's mad, huh?
Atta girl!
Check it out.
Hey, Gail!
Where's she going?
I'm glad you left.
R.J.--
No, no, who the hell is he?
Maybe I should go back.
Are you crazy? For what?
I'm trying to get you to see
him for who he really is
all along, Gail.
I knew you'd get it one day.
R.J., please.
Wouldn't talk to a man like
that.
You're not going back to him,
Gail, I'm serious.
I'm putting my foot down.
No sneaking behind my back.
And where am I going to find
myself a coach?
I'm not gonna give up running.
Where? I'll tell you where.
Me.
You?
Yeah, Gail.
I know everything he knows,
even more.
It'd be great, we can work
together every day.
Hey, who knows more about the
length of these legs and where
they lead than I do? Huh?
You'd really coach me?
You promise, R.J.?
I'm a man of my word.
And you know that. Come on.
Let's go. One more set.
Come on, hands up.
R.J., please.
Get the knees up.
Knees up.
Come on, let's go.
Get them up!
Slow down, slow down.
All right, let's walk it out.
Good. Yeah.
We can do this.
Hey, Gail.
How you feeling?
Okay.
Good.
Go in the house, baby.
She doesn't want to see you.
Ever.
Why don't you let Gail tell
me that.
She doesn't even want to see
you to tell you she doesn't
want to see you.
That's how much she doesn't want
to see you.
All right.
Hey.
So what happened?
R.J. is training her now.
What?
Did you talk to Gail?
No.
You know you didn't help the
situation any, Bobby?
What're you talking about?
I got her to the games.
And the fact that she lost,
that's not my fault.
You got her to the Games?
Yes, I got her to the Games.
No, she got herself there
with your help.
Maybe there's some other
runners who do want my help.
Yeah?
None as fast as Gail.
You know this makes no sense.
How is R.J. gonna help Gail win
anything, let alone some gold?
( alarm buzzes )
R.J. Come on, sweetheart.
Time to hit the track.
Come on, R.J., you'd promised
you'd come with me.
You said this morning you'd
come.
Not now. No. Ugh.
Are you gonna train me or what?
We'll do it this weekend.
I promise.
This is the third time, R.J.
I need you to come with me.
I gotta be at work at 9:00.
Come on, now. I'm tired.
( panting )
Gail?
I wouldn't have phoned,
Dr. Otis, but you're my last
hope.
It's fine. Sit down.
I-- I haven't been feeling
well.
Uh-huh.
Right. I see.
How long ago did this start?
I don't know, a year?
No, longer, while I was still
on the team.
I see your skin.
Something's wrong with me,
isn't it?
Gail, I believe something is
wrong.
I have a friend of mine,
Dr. Ginsburg.
He's a wonderful doctor.
And I want you to see him.
You tell him everything you told
me.
"It's nothing."
"Is there something bothering
you?"
"It's probably just stress."
Dr. Otis, I need you to come
with me.
Oh, Gail. You just tell him--
No, no, I need you to come
with me.
I need you to tell him.
You tell everybody.
Nobody believes me.
Okay.
I bet you just came from the
track.
I bet you're thirsty.
Yes.
Come on, let's get something
to drink, all right?
He was easy to talk to.
That's for sure.
We can get some answers.
Robin.
Dr. Otis.
Gail.
Well, Gail, your thyroid's
out of whack.
( chuckles )
What does that mean?
Well, the thyroid's a gland.
Located right about here.
And it secretes hormones that
control your metabolism,
your nervous system, and the
action of your muscles.
At least that's what it's
supposed to do.
Yours is not working very well.
It's also why your weight
goes up and down.
I knew I wasn't crazy.
I knew there was something wrong
all the time.
You're definitely not
imagining things, Gail.
That's good to hear.
Grave's disease is very real.
How serious is it?
You see your thyroid is twice
the size that it should be.
So?
We need to get it back down
to normal size.
Well, how are you going to do
that?
Well, to be honest, I'm going
to need some time before I can
advise you on the best
treatment.
Treatment.
So, there's a cure?
Doctor, there is a cure, isn't
there?
What are you telling me?
No cure.
Gail, where have you been?
I was just getting ready to
start calling around for you.
There's no cure, R.J.
Nothing.
For the rest of my life I'll
just have it.
Maybe they're wrong again.
No. No, not this time.
Come on, babe. Come on.
Everything's gonna be just fine.
He just comes in.
Read it and weep.
( overlapping dialogue )
Don't look at them till you
have to.
That was a 24 shot clock.
At the time, maybe.
Does not run long.
Hold on.
Time out!
( phone rings )
Yeah, he is. Hold on.
Bobby. Bobby? It's Dr. Otis.
Hey, Doc.
What?
Ugh.
All right. Thank you.
What'd she want?
Gail's not doing too well.
You already knew that.
Gotta get back to the game.
Y'all?
Gail's not doing too well.
She's worse than we thought.
Poor R.J.
You guys go ahead.
She gonna be all right?
Excuse me.
Leave a message, and we'll
call you back. ( beeps )
Hey, Gail? This is Bobby.
Pick up. Gail?
It's Bobby.
Call me when you get this
message, all right?
We got each other, baby.
No more heartbreak about
running after the gold.
We'll settle down and be normal.
Have a family.
Just be together.
When will I be able to run
again?
Well, you may be able to run
again someday.
When?
I'm recommending radiation
therapy to shrink your thyroid,
Gail, and I expect very good
results from that.
But the side effects can be very
uncomfortable.
Now, the beta blockers will
help your body through all of
that and help protect you.
Gail, you've gotta understand
one thing.
What?
This whole treatment is gonna
slow you down.
It'll be a very long time
before--
before you have the energy to
run again.
Hey, hey, Gail.
Hold up.
What's the word about you?
Dr. Otis called me and she--
she told me about your illness.
So it took Otis to convince
you.
Come on, I knew there was
something wrong, I just couldn't
put my finger on it.
I did try to call you.
Hey, hey, you're gonna beat
this.
You might even run again.
You don't know anything about
my business, Bobby.
Hey, Gail.
You hang tough.
Gail, let's go.
I'm parked in the red.
There's my ride.
You all right?
It's cool.
Come on, let's go.
You have reached the
International Athletic Medical
Hotline.
The following are a list of
drugs banned by current
guidelines.
All steroids, Corticotrophin,
Erythropoietin,
and Somatototrophin are also
included in this group.
All beta blockers are also
banned.
If the use of any banned drugs
are detected, the offender is
subject to due process and
possible expulsion from the
Games for two years to life.
( coughing )
Gail?
R.J.
What're you doing? You sick?
Give me some privacy, please.
Are you sick? Gail, not one.
You haven't taken one pill.
I'm not gonna sit here--
No! You're killing yourself!
And you're fucking killing me!
I'm not taking it anymore!
You better take these pills.
You don't understand!
I do understand!
I know right now!
You gotta stop, girl.
You gotta stop!
I'm not taking this shit no
more!
I'm not taking it, Gail!
( door opens, slams )
( thunder )
Not taking this shit.
Tell her to take this
medication, please.
She's hurting.
She's not taking this medication
because she believes you want
her to go back to the Games.
I didn't tell her that.
Doesn't matter.
You and I both know Gail is
never gonna run again.
So even if the beta blockers
are banned by the committee,
she'll never be tested because
her running career is over.
Look, you are her husband.
You tell her to take them.
You're the great Bob Kersee.
The guru. That's right.
She'll listen to you before she
listens to me.
She always has!
She hasn't done that in a
long time, and you know when
that stopped.
She can't sleep.
Her hair is falling out.
Her legs bleed, her face peels.
So would you please tell her to
take the beta blockers?
I don't know.
I'll think about it, okay?
I'll think about it.
Dr. Bates, please report to
radiation therapy.
Dr. Bates to radiation therapy.
Hey, hey.
Hey.
How's it going?
All right.
Pain's not as bad as they said.
Good.
The radiation will be over
soon.
How soon?
Soon enough.
Oh.
Soon enough for Barcelona.
I don't think we should be
worrying about Barcelona right
now.
This grass needs to be
watered.
You're thinking I should take
that medicine.
Maybe.
You can't even say it.
Bob Kersee never just thinks
maybe about anything.
You really don't want me to take
that medicine.
I can't tell you--
You can't do it.
You can't tell me to give up
any hope I have of ever going
to the Games.
Gail, listen, please.
Tell me to take them and
I will.
I can't tell you--
I lied about the pain.
It's bad. It's real bad.
Tell me to take them.
Gail--
I get night sweats.
My head aches so bad, I'm afraid
I'm gonna die, and then I'm
afraid of-- I'm afraid I'm not
gonna die.
Tell me to take them, Bobby.
Please, Gail.
Should I take them?
What're you doing?
Say yes, and I will.
Come on.
Gail-- hey!
Just pick one up and hand
it to me.
What're you doing?
Tell Jackie I said hi.
Gail!
Damn!
Mommy! Here I come!
( kid's laughter echoes )
I may pass you!
( birds chirping )
It's a beautiful day in
Los Angeles.
Rise and shine and I want Jesus
to walk with me.
( gospel music plays )
( laughter, doorbell )
Here's my baby.
Hi.
I'm so glad you're here.
Look, who's here, everybody!
( all saying hello )
How you all doing?
Um, Papa's in the den, right?
Yes, I think so.
Hey, Papa.
Hi, sweetie.
Happy Birthday.
This is for you.
Whoa. Look at this.
What is it?
Open it and see.
Okay, gimmie that.
I'm thirsty, I'm gonna get
something to drink.
All right.
Excuse me.
When's R.J. coming?
I don't know.
You don't know when he's
coming?
I don't even know where he's
at.
I haven't for over a week or so.
I don't understand.
Where would R.J. be?
I don't know, Papa.
He stopped leaving me notes a
long time ago.
Wait, I don't understand.
What did you do, have a fight or
something?
What is all this about, huh?
Look at me.
What do you mean?
Well, honey--
Sweetheart, this--
Would you all just look at
me!
That's going to go away.
Yes.
Somebody help me please!
We're here to help you.
Be patient.
I've always told you, god
will find a way--
Oh, please, Papa!
I don't know anymore prayers!
Don't you talk that way now.
Why does god hate me?
God does not hate you.
Why doesn't he help me?
Oh, baby.
Come stay with us.
Come home with us.
Stay here.
Did he leave you?
( overlapping dialogue )
I can't stay here.
You shouldn't be alone Gail.
You can't--
I'm going after her.
No, no, no, let her go.
Let her go.
She wants to be alone.
( guests murmuring )
That's our baby. She need us.
I know that.
There's nothing we can do about
it now.
In God's hands.
God's hands. God's will.
God, God, God.
When are you going to see
that it was Gail's will to
run all those hurdles?
Gail's will to break through all
those finishing tapes?
Wasn't Gail's will there
somewhere?
When are you going to give Gail
credit for what she's done?
When are you going to stop
putting God in your place?
( phone rings )
Maybe she just wants to be
by herself, Bobby.
( doorbell chimes )
She's not home.
Her car is still here.
She might not want to see us.
Bobby, what--
I'm going in.
Come on. Come on.
Hey, Gail!
Hey, girl!
Gail?
It's Jackie and Bobby!
Why are all these mirrors
covered?
I don't know.
This is strange.
I told you.
Told you she wasn't here.
Want me to leave a note?
We'll call her next time.
And next time she better answer.
( door closes )
( sobs softly )
Let's take a look at
highlights in today's
championship.
( garbled sportscast )
( jazz music plays )
And they're off!
Lawrence by a body length!
Gail?
Gail.
Oh, Gail.
Baby, wake up.
What have you done? Oh, God.
Oh, no.
Gail, wake up. Just wake--
No. Come on, baby.
( panting )
( no audible dialogue )
Nurse, have you heard
anything from the doctor yet?
Nothing, huh?
There's R.J.
R.J., where is she?
I found her at the house.
I didn't--
You didn't find her, you left
her!
No, no, no. I tried--
R.J., don't you stand there
and tell me you tried to do
anything!
You abandoned my daughter.
That's what you did.
I did not! I tried to--
She cut me out!
You did?
She didn't want me!
That's not true.
I told her to take that
medication and--
Where is she?
Where is she? What room is she
in?
I can't do this.
I'm outta here.
You won't listen to me, you
handle it.
Where's Dr. Ginburg?
Larry, here he is.
How is Gail? Where is she?
Mrs. Devers, Reverend.
Gail's been hemorrhaging a lot.
I'm going to see her.
Wait. Hemorrhaging from what?
It's a side effect die to the
high radiation toxicity level.
Gail's going to recover from
this.
And they're will be no more
radiation treatments.
Oh, thank God.
But the damage to her feet,
is critical.
How critical?
Not taking the beta blockers.
Wait a minute.
What are you talking about, beta
blockers?
I'm sorry, I gave her some
medicine that she was supposed
to take that would help her
through this period.
And for some reason, she didn't.
It's compromised her immune
system, it's left her vulnerable
to infection.
Doctor, please.
Worst case?
Yes.
She might have to have her
feet amputated.
Oh, my God.
I'm sorry.
Oh, no.
Can we go see her?
Why don't you look after
each other right now.
I'll come and get you when
there's time.
All right, sweetheart.
I need you to be strong, okay?
How is she?
Bobby, we don't know.
Still waiting to hear.
What happened?
Bobby, she is so sick, she
may never walk again.
Never walk?
Dr. Ginsburg said that he--
I mean she hadn't been taking
some medication she was
prescribed.
Oh.
Yeah, R.J. mentioned that
a few weeks ago.
So you knew? Huh?
I visited her and we talked
about it.
Bobby, are you telling me
that you never told her to take
that medication?
No.
She said, she knew what she
wanted.
I'm just a little confused.
For six years now, she's done
everything you've said.
Reverend Devers, on the track
and in the gym, I'm God.
She does what I tell her to.
But this came from inside Gail.
Said she knew what she wanted.
Nothing I could say.
If something happens to Gail,
it'll kill her mother.
We just have to have faith
and everything will be all
right.
You believe in God, Bobby?
I believe in Gail.
I believe you do.
Can I go see her?
Please.
Bobby.
Hey.
Bobby, they wanna take my
feet.
Don't talk, just stay relaxed
and take it easy.
You go out there and you tell
them, they can't have my feet.
I should've taken that
medicine.
What's that?
What's what?
What do you see?
You mean the wall?
That what you see? A wall?
Uh-huh.
That's not what I see.
'Cause I'm looking through it.
Past that.
Like I'm on a road and
houses to the track.
And I'm not just walking...
I'm running.
Look at me.
Bobby, you said--
You said the race I'm gonna run
is out there waiting for me
to claim it.
Well, I'm claiming it.
Right here, right now.
I'm already running that race.
Can you see me?
Can you see me, Bobby?
Yes.
Know something?
First time I've been able to see
through one of those damn
things.
I'll see you on the other side.
Yeah.
Please help us.
Give us your strength.
Help us to hear your voice.
Now be careful.
Here we are.
That's my girl.
You see Mr. Johnson peeping out
the window?
Where else would he be?
( overlapping dialogue )
Which key?
I can't see without my
glasses, baby.
She's not wearing them.
She doesn't want to wear those
glasses.
Just--
Here we go.
It's time we made that peach pie
for you.
Oh, I wonder what peaches.
And a clean kitchen to eat it
in.
Okay.
Hey, hey.
Hey, Bobby. I'm in here.
Oh, those are beautiful.
Who are they for?
You.
Ha ha. Thank you.
Where is everybody?
Called them all up, told them
not to come.
What?
I don't want a party.
Being alive's enough.
You got that right.
( both laugh )
Listen, Gail, I'm real sorry
about R.J.
R.J. had a right to run.
I've been running from him for
long enough.
Would you like some iced tea?
Yeah.
I made some for you special.
Bobby, I'm gonna be fine.
I'm gonna live with this for the
rest of my life.
But the medicine's gonna keep it
under control.
Keep me from having a relapse.
Bobby, I want to go to
Barcelona.
No problem, I'll get you box
seats.
Back side.
Where's the sugar?
Bobby, I want to run in
Barcelona.
I'm going to the Games.
You sure?
I'm sure.
You know, Barcelona is
only 18 months away.
The trials are no more than a
year away.
I know.
Are you sure you know?
Remember when I told you
about my star?
I said God took it away.
Yeah.
Well, I'm taking it back.
It's mine and I want it.
What about your feet?
Like you say, Bobby, what do
my feet have to do with
running?
No more than flesh on bone.
Just flesh on bone.
( grunts )
( panting )
Bobby, I-- I can't.
Sure you can. Come on, try.
No, Bobby, I thought
I could.
Okay.
But I can't.
Know what I'm thinking about?
I remember the first time
I ever saw you race.
It was high school. 1984.
Mmm-hmm.
Boy, you were something.
You ran just like a gazelle.
You were fast furious.
You won that first race by,
I think, about three inches.
You must've run 600 miles
in preparation for that race.
For three inches.
Hmmm.
Think you got three inches now?
Let's see those three inches.
Three inches.
Hmm? You can do that.
( gasps )
Hot dog! Whoo!
( laughs )
You remember the first time
you ran for me at S.C., right?
I must've run you 800 miles
in preparation.
You won that race by, I think,
by about four inches, right?
Yeah, four inches.
There. Four inches.
You just keep remembering
Barcelona!
( inaudible dialogue )
( motivational music )
Hold it. Barcelona.
( no audible dialogue )
Barcelona.
Do it again.
( motivational music )
( no audible dialogue )
All right. All right.
Let's go! It's Barcelona!
( engines roar )
( crowd cheers )
Next up is the first of the
preliminary heats of the Women's
100 Meters.
Now, Gwen Torrance is due
to race the last heat.
But this first heat has the
surprising presence of one young
lady, I'm talking about
Gail Devers!
Absolutely right.
Ladies and gentlemen at home,
it's not a ghost you see on the
screen, but it's Gail Devers
in the flesh.
She's back, she's ready to run.
But the question is, can she run
against this world class field
in the presence of Gwen
Torrance.
Gail Devers is in lane 5.
The main competition this heat
will come from Cuthbert of
Jamaica in lane 4.
And from Privalova from the
Unified Team in lane 6.
They're both excellent runners,
and right on either side of her.
Well, there's Gwen Torrance
sizing up her competition.
I'd say.
Not a good start for Devers,
but it is a strong start out
of the blocks for Cuthbert.
Devers and Privalova running
second and third.
And the top three, Cuthbert,
Devers and Privalova moving on
to the finals.
( cheers and applause )
Bobby.
There's something I wanna say
before the race, you know.
I wanted to-- damn!
I'm not good at this.
( cheering )
I just wanna tell you, Gail--
Bobby.
I'll see you on the other side.
Gail Devers.
I see your life in my mind.
It's on tape in my head.
I play it every day.
I rewind it, and I play it
again.
And when I put it on pause,
I stand back in awe.
Gail, you're a champion.
Get going, Gail. Come on.
Ladies and gentlemen,
the next event is the finals
of the Women's 100 Meters.
( announcer speaks Spanish )
The lane assignments are
lane 1, Dahl, Cuba.
Lane 2, Devers, USA.
Lane 3, Cuthbert, Jamaica.
Lane 4, Ottey, Jamaica.
Lane 5, Torrance, USA.
Lane 6, Numema, Nigeria.
Lane 7, Privalova, the Unified
team.
And lane 8, Punali, Nigeria.
( cheering )
( announcer speaks Spanish )
Ladies and gentlemen,
we have a photographic finish.
( announcer speaks Spanish )
The result of the Women's
100 meter are 5th place,
Ottey, Jamaica.
4th place, Torrance, USA.
3rd place, Pivalova, Unified
Team.
2nd place, Cuthbert of Jamaica.
And 1st place, Devers, USA!
With the time of 10.82 seconds!
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
Yes! ( all cheering )
( reporters clamoring )
Do you want to win the gold?
See, what you don't know is,
that you've already got it.
It's out there waiting for you
to claim it.
You gotta imagine yourself
already winning that race.
Imagine yourself crossing that
finish line first.
Baby girl! ( laughs )
You got it! You wanted it.
And you got it!
( cheers and applause )
Closed Captions provided by
Digital Post Services