*
[horse hooves galloping]
Enough
of the chicken shit, Sheriff.
Know as well I do,
you can't make us leave.
Alive, anyways, Sheriff.
[laughter]
Well, we don't want
any trouble here, Left Eye,
so just tell us what it is
you all want.
What we want is simple.
We hear your town possesses
a lot of,
what should I say, boys, uh.
A lot of natural materials.
That's right.
Underground.
Natural material?
Underground?
Jesus, you fellas must be
talkin' about
that cow dung problem.
That's not funny.
Okay.
It's all a rumor.
Okay, Left Eye,
it's all a rumor.
There is no gold in Flatridge.
I'll be the judge of that.
Listen,
see, I wanna play sheriff
for a couple of days.
My boys here,
they wanna be deputies.
That way, can't break the law,
'cause we'll be the law.
[laughter]
We also hear your town
possesses something else,
Sheriff.
Yes.
Hottest commodity
east of the Mexican border.
Women.
[screaming]
Don't knock it 'til you try it,
baby.
[gunshots]
[women screaming]
[outlaws laughing]
You disgusting bitch.
[gunshot]
*
[sighs]
What is it, Jake?
Left Eye and his
band of outlaws
have taken over
Flatridge County.
Lookin' for gold.
They, uh,
they killed a couple
of the woman who refused
to bed with them.
Your sister was one of 'em.
I'm sorry.
She didn't go without putting
up a fight, though, Rachel.
She cut one of 'em.
Right underneath the eye.
Thank you, Jake.
I'll take care of her now.
[wind howling]
"Let mine enemy
be as the wicked.
And he that rises up
against me, feel my wrath.
And the just
will have his day."
Oh.
I promised myself I would never
return to a life of guns.
God as my witness, Sally,
I'm gonna find the man
that did this to you.
I'm gonna find him
and I'm gonna make him pay.
I'm gonna make them pay.
[crying]
Oh, God.
*
Lord, forgive me.
Ha ha.
Yes, yes, yes.
Sorry, sweet cakes.
It was real,
but all good things have got
to come to an end.
Ooh.
My, my, my,
you're full of surprises.
Leaving so soon, Johnny?
Don't make me split your wig.
I take it you lie when you said
it wasn't all about the sex,
Johnny.
Technically, no,
it was about the sex...
...and the loot.
And Chastity, don't try nothin'.
I got backup.
You know Lou.
See you 'round.
My mamma said
there'd be days like this.
[gunshots]
Oh, by the way,
I was fakin' it.
We hear she's fast
with a knife.
No woman with a knife's
faster than me.
Hey!
I hear you're fast
with a knife.
How fast are you?
Hey!
I'm talkin' to you!
Quick enough.
Call it.
One,
two,
draw!
Geez!
Yes, ma'am.
Can I help you?
Fresh,
made this week.
Hi, big boy.
[speaking Chinese]
Little lady...
...I think you might
got the wrong man.
Maybe even the wrong country.
Ain't that right, boys?
[laughter]
[speaking Chinese]
Seems like you didn't bother
to learn English, either.
Can speak perfect English.
Let's just forget
about the English.
Doesn't seem like math is one
of your strong points, lady.
Kinda looks like you're a little
bit out numbered here.
[gunshots]
[people shouting]
*
Thank you all for coming.
We all thought you were dead.
Rumor had it you went out
in a blaze of glory
at Gatesfield.
No,
just layin' low.
So,
we're here.
The town's called Flatridge.
I've heard of it.
Mostly women.
That's where I settled after...
...You left.
Look,
we did what we had to do,
but after Wells
I started to feel like
we had outrun our course.
What does that mean?
It means, Chas, that what
happened that afternoon
has haunted me for a long time.
And I vowed never to return
to that life, ever.
So that's why you
disappeared soon after.
I found a different life
at Flatridge.
I stayed with my sister for a
while and everything was great.
But things started to change.
Rumors of gold
and a town full of women
seemed to attract
the scum of the earth.
I'm gonna give you cowards
one last chance
to get out of my town.
[gunshot]
Before long,
Flatridge was everything I was
trying to get away from.
I tried to persuade her
to leave.
She wanted to stay.
And they killed her.
And I wanna find them.
So let's get this straight,
Rachel.
You want only revenge?
They killed my sister.
I don't need more than that.
With all due respect, Rachel,
I do.
Fine, Maria, you don't
have to go.
Then I'm out.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hold up.
This ain't getting us nowhere.
Now all let's chill out
for one hot minute.
Okay?
Please.
Okay guys, listen up.
I know all about this town.
And if Rachel asked us
to come here,
the least we can do
is hear her out.
I wanna know about the gold.
Okay.
An ex-boyfriend told me
that some wealthy cattle farmer
left over
half a million dollars
worth of gold and jewelry
in that town.
Whaddya mean "left?"
Rumor has it that he left
it all to his only son,
who buried it
somewhere in Flatridge.
Where?
I would imagine
somewhere in a grave.
Maybe...
The problem is nobody knows.
Could be in a grave.
Could be under
some poor bastard's house,
for all we know.
No problem.
Then we find son.
That'd be kinda hard, Zhing.
He's dead.
- Here we go.
And the son is supposedly
buried right next to the chest.
The thing is
nobody knows where.
Simple.
We find the undertaker
who buried the son.
He died a year later.
Of course.
What about a map?
Rumored to be
somewhere in Flatridge.
And by the way,
how do you know so much
about the chest, anyway, Chas?
An ex-boyfriend I dated
told me.
What happened to him?
We had a bad breakup.
*
Where do you think
you're goin'?
I don't know
what I was thinkin'.
Those two ain't never
gonna change.
Don't take it personal.
Chastity, can you believe them?
My sister is dead
and they in there talkin'
about gold and jewelry.
I don't think they meant
anything by that.
Everybody's got different needs
now, Rachel.
It don't make it right.
It don't make it wrong.
Listen, when we
were robbin' those banks,
you made the decision
to leave that life.
I never judged you for that.
I had to leave, Chastity.
I know.
The problem is, when you left,
you left your friends behind.
We think about offer.
Gang worth big bucks.
Left Eye worth more.
I ride with you.
*
Maria?
I'm in.
That's my girls!
One favor, though.
While we're there anyway,
maybe keep an eye out
on that map.
Sure.
Little somethin' for everybody.
Can't hurt to take Him along.
Lord,
thou art my battle axe
and weapon of war.
For with thee I will break
into pieces the nations,
and with thee
I will destroy mine enemies.
Amen.
- Amen.
*
Wait a minute.
What about Kim?
[Judge]
For the crimes committed
against the sovereign state
ranging from horse theft,
cattle theft, bank robbery,
assault on persons
and properties, jailbreaks.
For crimes committed
against this state, Kim Brigham,
you've been tried
and condemned to death,
to be hung until you're dead.
Kim Brigham,
if you have any last words,
say them now.
You feel me, baby?
- Huh?
I can tell you ain't seen
a vagina
since your momma
gave birth to you.
[stammering]
Are those your final words?
Come on, baby, I know you
wanna spread my thighs...
Shut her up!
- ...and shove your big, fat--
[coughs]
[gunshot]
Good luck, ladies.
Ha! Ha!
[gunshot]
[people screaming]
*
Yo, Kim! Here!
I'm right here.
[bullets ricocheting]
[screams]
The gang is back, y'all.
Yah!
[gunshots]
*
I'm goin' back.
What?
Yah.
I'm going back.
Going back?
Kim, are you crazy?
You gonna get on
with that bullshit, girl.
Kim, no.
Those bastards
tried to kill me.
I'm goin' back!
It's payback!
I know this was a bad idea.
Kim, no!
Two roads, the past
and the future.
Leave the pain in the past.
Kim!
- Yah! Yah!
Yah!
Oh man, you gotta
be kidding me.
This is disgusting.
I mean, there's gotta be
a better way
of finding this chest.
Jean, when you find
a better way, you let me know.
Keep diggin'.
Looks to me he got
what he had coming.
[women laughing]
No, really,
I gotta thank you all
for coming through when you did.
'Cause it was close.
Hey...
...look like Chinese fish.
[laughter]
Yeah, want whiskey.
Here.
Kim, quit scoffin'.
[laughter]
Which one of you hussies
missed that first shot?
'Cause that shit was not sexy.
Well, actually,
I thought you looked kinda cool
swingin' back and forth
like that.
Any longer swing like that,
you woulda had my ass
in a trance.
[laughter]
What's wrong with her?
I think we found our hussy.
Thank God Chas hit
that second shot.
Oh, about that.
Got a confession.
- Yeah?
It wasn't me.
[giggling]
I was goin' for the judge.
That ain't funny.
Oh, yeah?
Whaddya gonna do about it?
On the count.
One...
...two...
...three.
I won that shit.
- Oh, no.
[laughter]
You know I did.
you know I did!
I won that shit.
*
Everything okay?
Everything's fine.
So...
...what's the plan?
Simple.
We kill 'em,
then find the jewelry
and the gold.
Sounds like a plan to me.
Hold up.
How we gonna kill 'em
if we don't even know
what they look like?
We're lookin' for Left Eye,
right?
Yeah.
Then we find the guy
with one good right eye
and kill him.
But what if they
call him Left Eye
because he's got
one good left eye?
Rachel?
We wait.
We settle in the inn
for a couple of days,
monitor their activity,
and then make our move.
And the gold and the jewelry?
We have plenty of time
for your gold.
And the jewelry.
Come on.
*
You think they recognize you?
I don't know.
I left here a long time ago.
I thought you said this town
was mostly women.
Used to be.
Things have changed.
I kinda like the change.
Don't you ever
get tired of that, Chas?
I feel about men the same way
you feel about money.
So much of it,
so little time.
*
I think we hit the jackpot,
baby.
*
I say we kill 'em all.
[giggling]
Can I help you ladies?
Yeah,
can I get four shots of whiskey
for my friends?
We don't serve your kind here.
And what kind is that?
Ladies.
Whoever said we was ladies,
snot bucket?
See,
my friends get a little nervous
when they're thirsty.
So I think you might
wanna rethink that order.
Yes, ma'am.
Pardon me, miss.
I just wanted to extend the
welcome to you and your friends.
I noticed you're not
from around here.
Stayin' for a while?
Actually, we're just
passing through.
You know, a couple days.
Business or pleasure?
I would say business.
Allow me to introduce myself.
My name is Malone.
And you are?
Chas.
Chas?
Short for Chastity.
[laughs]
Okay.
- What's so funny?
No, just... just your name.
Hey, Babyface.
I'll be right there.
Babyface?
It's just something.
When I was a kid. It just...
It just stayed with me.
Yeah, okay.
Well, um...
Maybe I could see you later.
Maybe?
Maybe.
[no audible dialogue]
Come on, let's go.
Wait, I haven't
finished drinking.
*
Here, take a look.
Yeah, that's them.
Damn, I didn't think there was
gonna be so many of them.
Bandits?
No. Dead people.
I worry about the ones
that are alive.
I think there's more of them
back in town.
Five or fifty, it don't matter.
We can do this right now.
What, you got a death wish
or something?
Why you gotta be all that?
I'm here to collect bodies,
not bounty.
Are you better than us?
Georgy, Sue!
The hell is it?
It's the map.
It's a map.
Stop digging.
Hey, we found it.
Whoo! We found it!
What's happening?
I don't know.
From the looks of things,
they must have found something.
You think it was the map?
I don't know.
Come on.
Let's head back into town.
Wait, by the way,
where's Chastity?
*
Wait a minute.
What?
We just met.
Actually, we met yesterday.
I can't argue with that.
[groaning]
What?
What is it?
I just have a feeling that
I know how this is gonna end.
Let's not worry
about that right now.
If I were you, I would.
Why?
Let's just say,
when I break up,
I really... break up.
Look, Chas, all I know is
when I first saw you nothing
in this world mattered to me.
You were so perfect.
I mean, you just looked right.
I got you this.
Oh...
...it's beautiful.
Oh, baby, it's beautiful.
*
Tell me what this is.
You lied to me!
Well, I uh,
I don't understand.
Let me help you understand.
Let me explain to you.
We found half of a map
inside of a coffin.
But what we didn't find
in that coffin
was a body,
or any chest of gold!
Seems to me, right,
whoever put this map
inside that coffin...
...probably knows
where the other half is.
And maybe you can tell us
who that other person is,
Sheriff.
I... I don't know.
[laughter]
Wrong answer.
What?
Hey!
Jesus Christ--
You know why ten is such
a beautiful number?
'Cause it's less painful
than nine.
[gunshot]
Ah!
So, what do we do now?
We keep digging.
The wells.
Grr, my f--
What'd you do?
[grunts]
Stop crying
like a little bitch!
*
You got a problem?
No.
No problem.
That's what I thought.
Why...
...would...
...they go after the sheriff?
Ain't he down with them?
He knows somethin'
he ain't telling.
About the gold?
- And the jewelry.
Maybe.
So they sent everybody
a message.
Exactly.
Shoot the sheriff
in the finger so...
...whoever has the other half
of the map
will be itching to make a move.
I say to hell with 'em.
I say they want drama,
let's bring 'em drama.
How many?
I count 25 total.
26 if you count
the nine-fingered sheriff.
What's the problem?
There's five of us.
Let's do this.
I don't see a problem.
I'll tell you
what the problem is.
They found a piece of the map.
So?
So, if they gonna lead us
to the chest,
then why we rushin'?
Look, Rachel said a little
somethin' for everybody, right?
A couple of more days
ain't gonna make a difference.
I'm just sayin', everybody
can get what they want.
Kim, another day doesn't
make a difference to you.
Kill 'em today or tomorrow.
Zhang, you still get
your bounty.
Rachel, another day doesn't
bring your sister back.
And Chas...
I already found what I wanted.
Fine, whatever.
Plus we all walk away with a
half a million dollars in gold.
Look, I want them as dead
as all of you,
but I'm just askin'
for a couple of more days.
A couple of more days.
We lay low one more day.
*
Welcome back.
What are you... ladies having?
[speaking Chinese]
Yes, ma'am.
Comin' right up.
I'll be right back.
I'm beginning to think that girl
even has sex with money.
*
Lots of deputies, but no law.
Funny, I was thinking
the same thing.
What will it be, pretty lady?
I'll raise five.
Mister?
I'll raise a ten.
Let's see 'em.
Read 'em and weep.
The world's full
of surprises, Mister.
I wouldn't touch that money.
I guess your momma
never taught you
that winnin' ain't everything.
It's how you pay the game.
[gunshots]
[people shouting]
So much for layin' low.
[gunshot]
Somebody in this town
knows where the other half
of that map is.
And I say
we raise a little hell until
that somebody comes clean.
[gunshot]
You're drunk.
That's something you never had,
Little Suzie...
...patience.
- I'm for that.
I'm ready to bring some
serious pain to this town.
We're gonna find the map
sooner than you guys think.
[gunshot]
They killed Otto and others.
What?
What are you talkin' about,
"they killed Otto?"
Who?
Some women. Girls.
They come in the saloon,
shot him up.
Girls?
Gunslinger types.
I ain't never seen them before.
How many of them was there?
Three, maybe four.
Were they wearing badges?
The girls?
- Otto!
Yeah, yeah.
Go!
Find them!
I wanna make sure these girls
are sorry they ever
stepped foot in my town.
Come on, let's go.
Damn it, Kim, it wasn't
supposed to go down like that!
What was I supposed to do?
Just stand there?
You were supposed to remember
the damn plan.
We lay low until we find out
their next move.
I don't lay low for nobody.
And you were about to use them
for target practice
with your damn knifes.
You tellin' me
about layin' low.
I wasn't gonna kill 'em.
I hadn't gotten my money yet.
Yeah,
look,
all I wanna know
is whether Babyface
is a part of that crazy gang.
Shit!
Now we're targets.
Let's go.
*
[people chattering]
Drink.
Any particular type, lady?
I'll bring you a whiskey.
You know somebody
named Chastity?
I might have heard
that name before.
What did she look like?
Everything all right?
Everything's cool,
just thinking,
that's all.
What are you thinking about?
Love.
Yeah, well, my mom always said
don't go looking for love,
look for respect.
Even that they ain't
gonna give you.
So you make them
give it to you.
With this.
How far you think
that's gonna get you, Kim?
Really?
Far enough.
Well, at some point
it's gotta stop, right?
All the shooting and killing.
Stop? Shit.
I'm going out
in a blaze of glory.
Just like the boys do it.
Boys either wind up dead,
in prison,
or hanging from a rope.
That's your idea of glory?
Well, it's plain stupid to me.
I don't know what you want,
but your
holier than thou attitude
is getting on my last nerve.
I'm not perfect.
I've made mistakes.
That shit I have to deal with.
You're not my mother,
you're not my father,
and I'm getting sick and tired
of your preachin'.
Don't you ever
call me stupid again.
I didn't mean nothin' by it.
You know how Kim is.
*
Kim?
- Shit!
I lost it.
- What?
I'll be right back.
Where the hell are you going?
For a ride.
Yah! Yah!
Where's Kim going?
She says she needs
to go for a ride.
*
Shit.
Here's your rifle, Sheriff.
Thank you, sweetheart.
[grunts]
Baby, let's get
out of here tonight.
Are you crazy or what, Brenda?
That'd be a mistake, sweetheart.
Wouldn't make it half a mile
before Left Eye found out.
Here, give me a hand, will ya?
Pull on that tight.
There you go.
Tight. Tighter.
Easy.
[gunshot]
Don't move, Brenda.
A deposit, please.
Everything okay?
Yeah, stick to the plan,
no one gets hurt.
I love you all.
- We love you, too.
Cool.
Let's go.
Hey, Kim?
I know, nobody gets hurt.
We're not gonna hurt you.
Get in front of us.
The sisters are in the house.
You're not gonna hurt nobody,
all right?
[gunfire]
No!
- No!
No.
Rachel?
You okay?
Somebody's comin'.
Kim! Kim!
- Wake up, wake up!
Get the canteen.
She's still breathing.
Drink.
No, wait.
She's trying to say something.
[coughs]
[grunts]
Sh- sh--
- What?
Don't talk, just drink.
Don't talk.
Now is the time.
I'm sorry.
* Amazing grace
* How sweet the sound
* That saved a wretch like me
* I once was lost
* But now am found
* Was blind but now I see
Why did she go back?
When she was seven years old
some men raped and killed
her mother.
That watch was all she had
to remember her by.
What now?
I stepped away from you all
to clear my head,
get closer to God.
Things ain't- ain't
makin' sense no more.
I've lost two of my sisters.
Kim's death is my fault.
These nightmares
about the bank...
I think my past is gonna
catch up to me.
I think we should go
our separate ways
and, um...
...I'm gonna go ahead
into Flatridge
and finish what we started.
Rachel?
I understand.
We understand.
Last year I hunted an outlaw,
Johnny Ringo.
And when I found him,
he was with his son
and his wife
and he begged for mercy.
And so I walked away.
A week later he tortured
a woman
in front of her child.
And then killed her.
I walked away
because of emotion.
We cannot allow emotion
to cloud the truth.
So, we here.
We still here.
I don't wanna lose you guys.
*
They're over there
in that old inn.
I say we give 'em
everything we got.
Leave the sheriff to me.
This time... it's personal.
Come on.
Hold- hold on.
Hold it. Hold it.
I wanna tell you,
whatever happens,
I love you guys to death,
and I ain't never stopped.
Okay?
I love you, too.
Yah!
*
[knife flies]
Going somewhere?
I missed on purpose.
[gunshot]
Hey.
[cocks gun]
You were the last words
on my dying friend's lips...
...and that really makes me mad.
Now wait a minute,
that wash't me.
Shut up!
[cocks gun]
What do you know
about a gold chest?
I don't know what
you're talkin' ab--
[gunshot]
Jesus.
[cocks gun]
That's the last time
I'm gonna miss on purpose.
You got that?
Okay.
This is the other part
of that map.
The chest is in a well...
...and I know where.
Wrong...
[cocks guns]
...you used to know.
[gunshot]
[horse hooves approaching]
What's the matter, baby?
- Shh.
What's- what's--
[gunshot]
[woman screaming]
*
I want them found,
now.
What do you think they want?
I don't know.
[gunfire]
Damn.
I didn't know there were
so many of 'em.
You down?
[speaks Chinese]
I'll take that as a yes.
[outlaw]
Let's go! Let's go!
*
Time to die.
[gunshot]
Chas!
*
[shouts]
I knew how this...
...was gonna end.
Bastard.
[gunshot]
[Little Suzie]
Left Eye, the sheriff's gone.
What?!
I have the men
searching everywhere.
Listen, I don't care-
I don't care
if you have to kill
every living thing
in this town.
Find him and kill him!
Will you do that for me?
Kill everybody! Everybody!
I'll find him.
[gun cocks]
Drop your gun.
You.
Turn around.
What is it you want?
What do you want, gold?
You want money?
You can't give me back
what I want.
Before you die,
I just wanted
to look into the eyes
of the murderers of my sister.
[gunshot]
[gun cocks]
Don't shoot.
[gunshot]
*
[crying]
Take her into your bosom,
Lord...
...and give her the love that
no man could ever give her.
*
Mmm-hmm.
Bingo.
Half a million dollars in gold.
How do we get to it?
Lucky for us the well is empty.
Lucky for me.
I can't swim.
[laughing]
Everything okay?
All the banks we robbed...
...all the robberies,
no one innocent ever got hurt.
That's what's bothering me.
I remember that day.
[gunshots]
The sheriff shot her...
No!
...not us.
I know.
Two roads...
...the past and the future.
Leave the pain in the past.
*
Y'all killed my sister,
but payback is a bitch.
Now we're even.
*