(dramatic orchestral music)
(atmospheric piano music)
(train chugging)
(steam hissing)
- You don't look like you
was born in Templeton.
You don't look Utah, even.
- Well, I was born here.
My father was Lars Eriksen.
- Oh my lord, you're the piano player.
- That's me.
- Erik Eriksen.
Me sitting next to a celebrity.
(Erik laughing)
(bright music)
(train whistle blowing)
(lambs baaing)
(train bell ringing)
(train whistle blowing)
- Oh, oh, there it is.
Oh my boy.
- Mama!
- Oh my boy.
- Oh.
- I'm so glad that you're home.
Only don't break my ribs.
- Seenie, so good to see you.
- You're gonna have one busy Summer.
I've got students lined up
all the way from Salt Lake
to take lessons.
- Good, I could use the money.
(Seenie laughing)
- Only I'm afraid you're not
gonna have any time for me.
I always like to improve my skills
while you're in town. (laughing)
So I hope you won't forget
your old piano teacher.
- Seenie, I could never forget you.
(Seenie laughing)
- I'll leave you to your mother.
I just wanna be part of
the welcoming committee.
- Oh, thanks.
- Bye.
- Everybody's waiting at Christine's.
- But Mother, it's been a long trip.
Don't I even get a chance to wash up?
- They're waiting.
- I don't know if I'm
ready for all that brood.
- Erik, they're your brothers.
- Half brothers, Mother.
Half brothers.
(car horn honking)
(bright instrumental music)
(dog barking)
- [Ivor] You, you too, come on.
All right, come on, everybody.
(horse neighing)
Oh, Well it's about time
that you two got here.
- How are you, Ivor?
- Oh, Erik.
Oh, my my my, don't you look fine.
You'll play for us later, I hope.
I had the piano tuned.
- Yes.
- [Christine] Ida, thanks
for getting him here.
It ain't always easy.
- Ivor.
- Little Erik getting too high up
for us country hicks.
- Ah, well, I gotta
get back in the kitchen
and see what's happening
with my leg of lamb.
You come on with me, Ida.
- (laughing) Erik.
- Hey.
Oh, Jens.
- Ah, hey, you remember Chel Bowen.
- [Erik] Well, I remember a little girl.
- Well, I grew up.
- [Jens] We're engaged to be married.
- Congratulations.
- Thanks.
- He's fixing up the Bessie house.
Dairy barn, latest equipment.
Capper, separator.
- Bottle washer.
(Jens laughing)
- She's way more than that.
Chel can do about anything she wants.
- She can also play the piano.
You're gonna have a little
competitions there, Erik.
- No, not really.
No it's, not like--
- She plays every night down at the show.
Hey, how about some lessons this Summer?
- Yes.
- Ivor.
- What?
It'll be a wedding present.
I mean, Erik will give
me the family reduction.
It's not like I'm one of
them jokers from Salt Lake
who pays two dollars a pop.
- Lessons are free.
Oh, and they're my wedding present.
You prepared for a lot of hard work?
- I'll practice night and day.
I promise.
Thank you.
- Well, you got me to
thank for this, Chel.
Don't forget that.
Come on, let's go get something to eat.
- Some meats today.
(group chattering)
I, I fixed these
- I know how you like
that chicken.
- special.
(group chattering)
- Erik.
Very nice to see you
back at the table again.
He look good, don't he, Mama?
- He's too thin.
- No thinner than he was.
He was always a hound.
- That's right.
- How long you planning on staying?
- Just for the Summer.
- Things prosperous for you back East?
- Still a musician.
Impoverished.
- Erik's not interested in money.
- When did I say that?
- Oh.
- Erik's an artist.
- Old pa always favored little Erik.
- Oh shush, your father
loved you all the same.
My boys got all the land,
and Ida's boy got the music lessons.
(laughing)
Alright, everybody eat up now.
There's lots more where that came from.
- All us boys in there, it was hard work.
- [Jens] You got that right.
- All Erik had to do was play the piano.
- Oh, no.
- Erik went off to war,
now don't you forget that.
- Erik also came back, didn't he?
- Ivor.
Don't let him get to you, Erik.
He needs a wife to rein him in.
- That's right.
- We was hoping to see
your wife this time, Erik.
- Well.
Maybe mama forgot to tell you.
Athena and I are divorced.
- Erik, please, not now.
- Mom, it's the truth.
It happens to a lot of
people in the other world.
- Well, look at Erik.
Throwing away wives,
and I can't even manage to get me one.
- Now would you just hush, hush.
- Ain't that somethin'.
(bright piano music)
- They enjoyed you so. (laughing)
Christine and the family.
- Are you kidding?
Patronizing.
They treat us like the poor relations.
- (laughing) Well Erik,
I guess that we are.
(laughing)
Uh.
You've been smoking.
- Mother, give up.
I smoke, I even drink.
I'm not a good Mormon, I never will be.
- Erik, stop it, I hate that.
- It's the truth.
Mother, you might as well accept it.
I am not like one of Christine's boys.
I am the bastard.
(hand whacking against face)
- Don't you say that.
Never.
Don't you say that.
(light somber music)
Oh Erik.
I'm sorry.
Oh.
And it's your first night home.
It's just,
if you're a bastard,
what does that make me?
(somber music)
- Mother.
- Lars Eriksen was a good man.
He married me.
It was legal under God.
- He already had a wife and six children.
Do you really think that
God had a hand in that?
- Yes, I do.
They changed the rules is all.
Polygamy was God's way.
And then all of a sudden they said,
that it was against the law.
But I am still married to Lars Eriksen.
And he will have both his wives,
Christine and me in the hereafter.
Erik.
He believed that.
And I know it's true.
(crickets chirping)
(hammer pounding)
- Hauled the hay into
the big barn yesterday.
Milk house just needs shingles.
Hey, can you see this?
A sign right over here.
Canyon Dairy.
Jens Eriksen, Proprietor.
(chuckling)
Did I ever tell you,
you have beautiful fingers, Chel?
- Yeah, good milkin' fingers.
(Jens laughing)
- Have a hard time keeping
my hands off of you.
So soft.
Don't think I ever felt skin so soft.
Can't sleep at nights just
thinking about holding you.
Don't know if I can wait.
- Not until our wedding night.
Come on, I can't be late
for my first music lesson.
- Oh yeah, your music lessons.
Hey Ivor,
bring the cows in before I get back.
- Alright.
- I'm nervous.
- Scared of Erik?
Good lord, Chel.
He can never do anything but play piano.
(bright organ music)
Gotta hand it to him.
Little Erik can sure play.
- Shh.
- You see, that's what I mean.
- I see, alright.
It's just I don't seem
to be able to bring it up
where it should--
- We'll try that part a few more times.
- You're too good, Erik.
Way beyond this family.
You must've dropped out of the sky.
- I've been working on
this piece for months.
He does it like it was magic.
- Seenie, I forgot to tell you,
I offered your student here a few lessons
as a wedding present.
I under you're her teacher.
I hope it won't interfere.
- And I thought marriage would
interfere with your music.
Seems like it can only help now.
- You oughta to try it
yourself sometime, Seenie.
Marriage.
- Oh.
(laughing)
I'm president of the hopeless club,
and you can't accept a marriage proposal
until you're a past president.
(group laughing)
Thanks Erik, I'll work on the piece.
- I guess we should get started.
Jens said that you wanted to learn
something for the Friday matinee.
- Oh no, Jens.
- You'll need some hero music.
Isn't that right?
(bright piano music)
And some villain music.
(dark piano music)
(laughing)
And some innocent young girl music.
(light piano music)
And some horse music.
(playful piano music)
- No, I want more than that.
I wanna really play the piano.
Not just for Friday matinees.
- Come sit down and
we'll see where we start.
- She's scared of you, Erik,
I keep telling her,
you're practically her brother.
- All right, uh.
Play anything.
Anything that you're comfortable with.
(melodic piano music)
(engine puttering)
- Chel.
Hey, don't let her compliments
give you a big head now, Erik. (laughing)
(bright piano music)
(woman weeping)
(audience applauding)
- I had no idea you were here.
- You have talent, Chel.
A sense of music, that's rare.
- Seenie always shows me the programs
from your concerts.
In places like England, even.
I feel so dumb playing
in front of the movies.
- Erik.
You probably don't remember me.
- Ruby Snow.
Of course I remember you.
I remember I always used to see
you and your mother up by Crystal Spring,
picking water crests in the Summer.
- Yeah, she's dead now.
- Oh.
- Got me a baby, Karina.
- [Erik] So you're a married lady.
- No.
- Well, you have a beautiful baby.
I hope things work out
alright for you, Ruby.
(baby whining)
- I never forgot that time
you ate my mother's cake, Chel.
- Of course I ate it.
It was delicious.
(soft music)
She brought a cake to school
for her birthday once.
Nobody would eat a piece of it but me.
'Cause I felt sorry for her.
- Well, people always said
they were up to no good
because they were half-breeds.
God, I hate that term.
Half-breeds.
- Erik.
Home for the Summer?
- [Erik] That's right, Bill Mac.
- You like the show?
- It was wonderful.
- Uh?
- Music was wonderful, too.
- Oh yeah, I can pick 'em.
- She's great.
- Goodnight.
- No Jens?
- No, he's working at the house.
- I'll walk you home, then.
- Oh, that's not necessary.
I always walk home alone after the show.
- I have candy corns.
(car honking)
(gentle music)
Have to eat candy corns
on the way home from the show.
(Chel giggling)
Perfect moon.
What do you say,
we go up to Temple Hill and we watch it?
I haven't done that since I was a kid.
- I used to do that with my sister.
We'd make wishes on the stars.
- What'd you wish for?
- I can't tell you what you wish for,
it won't come true.
- Well, let's go.
- Where?
- Up to Temple Hill
to look at the moon.
- We can't, they keep the
gates locked at night.
- That ever stop you and your sister?
- No.
But I just don't think I should.
- Jens won't mind.
I'm practically your brother now.
Isn't that what he said?
Let's go.
(bright orchestral music)
- [Chel] All the places you've
been, things you've seen,
even the war.
- [Erik] Two years I wanna forget.
- Jens feels guilty sometimes
'cause he was too young to go.
He told me you were wounded.
- Wanna see?
(crickets chirping)
Still packing some of the lead.
The shrapnel went in
too close to the heart
to get it out.
I laid for two days in the
Belleau Wood, bleeding.
Lost two of my half brothers
over there in those trees.
Lost some good buddies, too.
- I've seen death, too.
I held my mother's hand when
she was dying of influenza.
The way I see it, God needed her.
It's part of his plan.
- Yeah, nothing was ever that tidy for me.
I mean, even in my dreams.
All my life,
they always taught me that nothing
was as good as life was here in Templeton.
I mean, they even said.
They said that the world will come here.
It's hard when you discover
that that's not true.
There's a whole other
world out there, Chel.
And it's not coming here.
- You smoke?
- I'm a heathen, Chel.
I even drink tea, and,
hold your breath, coffee.
(lighter clicking)
- Don't make fun of me.
- I don't mean to.
Maybe, maybe I'm just jealous.
(light romantic music)
Maybe I wish I could believe,
have faith in some one thing.
Anything.
- Everybody knows you're different.
You've been out in the world.
- You ever wanna be out in the world?
- Oh no.
I could never live any place but here.
- Mr. Bowen, goodnight.
Goodnight, Chel.
- Goodnight.
(bright piano music)
Seems like a pleasant boy.
I don't know why Ida
worries about him so much.
Doesn't hurt the young to
have a mind of their own.
They come around sooner or later.
Well, I better turn the
water into the corn.
Water the lawn good and wet,
get that dry place by the fence.
(bright orchestral music)
(lighter clicking)
(melodic piano)
- Chel.
(engine puttering)
- Brought you and daddy some fresh eggs.
I hate gathering them. (chuckling)
Chickens are disgusting.
You can't touch 'em.
They all have mites.
Now.
Tell me about the piano lessons.
- Oh, well he's a wonderful teacher.
He really is.
He's just teaching me so much
about music and technique.
Things that Seenie could never teach me.
- Daddy says you're
practicing all the time.
- It's a wonderful opportunity.
I wanna make the most of it.
- I'd be sweatin' so bad,
my fingers would slide right off the keys.
- I have to confess,
my fingers have been sliding a little
(Esther chuckling)
It's his eyes.
The way he looks at me.
- Yeah, he sees right
down to your underwear.
- Esther.
(light orchestral music)
What time is it?
- Honey, I'm hurrying, but
these things take time.
- It's almost 3:30.
- Oh, I'm gonna have to lower this hem
by at least two inches.
- I don't wanna be late
for my piano lesson.
- Mama had the tiniest waist.
I can't believe you can get in it.
Goodness knows I tried.
Uh, it's Jens.
- C'mon, honey, turn around.
- Oh, no.
- [Esther] Go away.
You're not supposed to see her.
- How about I close my eyes?
- Oh, you can't see her.
- Come on, it's bad luck.
- Your dad says you was getting fit.
- Jens, stop, I'm in a hurry.
- Years ago, there was a Beale girl,
her fiance was a Henderson from Gunnison,
and he saw her in her wedding dress,
and two days later, she died.
She got a piece of fried
liver stuck in her throat.
- Well, Chel hates fried
liver, so don't worry.
Excuse me.
- Oh, Jens.
- Jens,
- Come on.
- Stop.
Come on now.
You're stepping on my hem.
Now, I'm already late
for my piano lesson, get.
- Come on, honey, turn around.
- That's it.
- Don't, goodbye.
- Come on.
(bright piano music)
- No.
No, you're forcing it.
You hear it, but you don't understand it.
Now, give me your hand.
The tip of the finger
reaches the key for what
the music wants right here.
It's a bent finger touch.
- Yes, bent finger.
- And here, the lento.
The fleshy part of the finger.
The flesh part reaches for the key.
It's a clinging touch.
- [Chel] The clinging touch.
- See, our passions, our ideas we express,
sees with the muscles, with the shoulders,
the arms, the hands, and then the fingers.
And in turn, they give force to the keys.
See, look at this.
(bright piano music)
Until I touch it.
The key gives force to the hammer.
- The hammer to the string.
- That's right.
Then the string vibrates,
and at last, our force
is given to the air.
As joy, or sorrow, anger.
Or love.
- I think we've run over my time.
- Okay.
- I have to get to the show.
That was good.
I mean, the lesson.
- [Jens] You think I'm worried about Erik?
- [Ivor] Women like him.
So-called sensitive types.
I won't say this, but just the kind.
- You think Chel's the kind?
- Of course not.
One girl like that get carried away.
- I'm not worried about Chel.
- Well, I don't trust him.
Never have.
Thinks he's better than us
'cause he lived in New York City.
Studied at the Royal College in London.
Some such place.
(lamb baaing)
- He's our brother, Ivor.
(hammer pounding)
- Maybe he got some of our
blood running through him,
but the other half is sissy.
- Yeah, well he went away to war.
Along with Hans and Soren.
Almost died there with 'em.
- You think I'm a slacker?
I was itching to go,
but mother had to have some--
- I know, I know.
You had to keep the farm
going after father died.
- I'll tell you one thing.
That bastard ever touch
your girl, I'd kill him.
(Jen scoffing)
(light orchestral music)
- You were in there?
- I wanted to watch you play
when you didn't know I was here.
Free and loose.
- I get carried away sometimes.
- You were on fire.
Chel, that was beautiful.
I brought candy corns.
(horse clopping)
- My sister was always
kind of in love with you,
and go to your recitals.
She'd practically swoon.
She says you look like a movie star.
- Maybe I should meet your sister.
- (chuckling) Too late.
She's already married.
To a farmer, Karl Dorius.
(crickets chirping)
- It'll make you happy,
Chel, the dairy farm?
- If it makes Jens happy,
it'll make me happy.
He's so excited right now.
He gets poetic talking about cows,
and fresh butter,
(Erik chuckling)
eggs.
I think it's meant to be, though.
Part of God's plan.
- Do you believe that?
That God looks down on each
one of us, makes a plan.
- Yes I do.
(light orchestral music)
My sister's probably waiting up.
Thank you.
- Is that part of the plan, Chel?
Are you gonna be like your sister?
Do your duty to God and
have a bunch of babies?
- I want babies, yes.
I don't know about bunches.
Goodnight.
- [Erik] Goodnight.
- I'm awake, Chel.
I thought it was Jens.
I was about to come down in my night gown,
and then I saw him in the porch light.
Erik Eriksen.
He walked home with you.
Does his wife know?
- Esther, it's nothing like that.
Besides, he doesn't have a wife anymore.
- Well that's because he
had so many love affairs.
Oh, I'll be so glad when I can sleep
on my stomach again.
- What do you mean, love affairs?
- Hmm?
(train whistle blowing)
- Well, you said Erik
Eriksen had love affairs.
- I've heard gossip, of course.
He's the only person I
know that's been divorced.
Anyway, he's so handsome.
There has to be love affairs.
I used to think that
if I knew Erik Eriksen,
I wouldn't care if I went
to heaven when I died
because I'd already have been there.
- Well, I'll tell him you like him.
- I'm sure he'll be excited.
Fat, old married lady me.
You got good nipples for nursing.
- [Chel] Esther.
- It's a fact.
Mine turn in.
So nice of Karl to let me come.
- I wish you could stay
for the Pioneer Day Dance.
It doesn't seem fair.
- My dancing days are over.
Too much to do at the farm.
(light orchestral music)
You know what married life is?
Hard work.
- It can't all be hard work.
- No, in the beginning, it's romantic.
Then it's hard work.
- Do I really have good nipples?
- [Esther] (Giggling) You're built, Chel.
(Chel giggling)
In case you didn't know it.
(bright orchestral music)
You're in for it, little sister.
You just wait and see.
You know, marriage wouldn't be so bad.
Men just end up spoiling everything.
- Take care, Esther.
- Thank you.
- Send me for as soon as
the pains start, okay?
- I will.
- Bye Karl.
- Bye Chel.
- [Esther] Oh thanks, Karl.
- Well, you'll be married
pretty soon yourself.
Don't know what I'm gonna do
without my two girls.
- Oh, you'll be fine, daddy.
(car engine puttering)
Anyway, I won't be far away.
I'll probably be here
more than I am there.
(upbeat music)
Jens, what will people think?
- I don't care what they think.
Hey, but listen, what's the matter?
- Erik.
(crowd clapping)
- Woo-hoo!
- Yeah, shouldn't surprise you.
Erik likes the ladies.
- But Ruby Snow?
I mean.
- Hey, why are you getting so upset?
Why do you care who he dances with?
- I don't care.
It's just degrading is all.
I mean, for the family.
It's a small town.
And We have to live here.
- Chel, what the heck?
Hey.
- Come on Jens, my turn.
(horse neighing)
(people chattering)
- Chel?
(hand whacking against face)
- I hate you, Erik.
- What is the matter, what did I do?
- Making a spectacle of
yourself with Ruby Snow.
- A spectacle?
- Yes.
She has a terrible reputation.
She's got a baby and
she's not even married.
Besides, she's a ha--
(crowd applauding)
- She's a half-breed, is
that what you were gonna say?
- No.
- That's what happens to
people that live in this town.
They become narrow and bigoted.
(Chel panting)
- [Chel] Uh, stop it.
- It will happen to you, too.
Your mind gets smaller and smaller.
If you stay here, it will seep inside you,
and shrivel you up into a little old lady.
- Don't say that.
I love this town, I'm not a bigot.
I'm not.
(distant country music)
My sister was right.
Men spoil everything.
You spoil everything.
(dramatic piano)
(audience applauding)
(audience chattering)
Oh, Jens.
- Well, who'd you think?
- Oh, you scared me is all.
- Hey, I come to walk you home.
- I just get so caught up in my music.
- I've been neglecting you lately.
Get so wound up in that darn farm.
Anyway, most of the heavy work's done.
I can start being a human again.
- Thank you.
- I got the reservations made already.
A bridal suite at a new
Grand Hotel in Salt Lake.
- Must've cost a pretty penny.
- Ow.
- I'm sorry.
- You're tired, miss.
My goodness, it's almost 11 o'clock.
You know, I try to tell her it's too hard.
Getting ready for a wedding.
All the time she puts in on her music.
Plus playing those silly shows at night.
- [Chel] I quit.
- Your piano lessons?
- Of course not my piano lessons.
I got the recital coming up.
I quit the shows.
Told Bill Mac this afternoon.
He's got that Elden boy who can play.
- Good.
There's plenty enough
to do up at the farm.
(train whistle blowing)
- Made some pie this morning.
- You're getting quite a cook, Jens.
- Well sir, just so you know,
I'm not marrying your
daughter for her pie crust.
(John laughing)
(light orchestral music)
(chuckling) To think, I
almost married Paulene Cox.
(Chel chuckling)
- Her father raises dairy cows.
It would've all fit perfect.
- You're the only girl for me, Chel.
The only one.
God just ordained it, I know he did.
I'm glad you quit Bill Mac.
I didn't like it, Erik
walking you home all the time.
It made me feel a little jealous, I guess.
- No cause to be jealous.
- Sometimes I wonder what
you and Erik talk about.
- Nothing really.
Just music.
- Kinda wish I could
talk to you like he does.
All about music and the like.
- Don't be silly.
I'll come up to the house
tomorrow and help you paint.
- Well, just as well as it stopped,
Erik walking you home.
(lambs baaing)
(dog barking)
(gun firing)
(horse neighing)
(lambs baaing)
(thunder rumbling)
- Let's go get him.
(horse neighing)
- What happened?
- Mongrel killed one of
Ivor's lambs last night.
- That's cause it was starving.
Did you see it, so thin.
- Hey Chel, Chel,
nothing to get so upset about.
It was a stray, mongrel.
- We could've fed it.
It would've left him alone
if we would've fed it.
- Once they start killing sheep,
there's no way stopping 'em.
(lambs baaing)
- You poor pup.
- [Ivor] Don't touch him.
No telling what he's got on him.
- How could you do that?
So brutal, a little dog.
- It had to be done,
he's eating all my lambs.
Go get a shovel, brother.
Let's bury this carcass.
Might have an owner come a lookin'.
- Guns.
I just hate guns.
- Chel, you want a dog,
I'll get you a real dog.
(lambs baaing)
(cows mooing)
(dramatic piano music)
- What do you think?
- It was beautiful.
But terrible.
- Yes, it was beautiful and terrible.
Both.
Not only pleasant things
are beautiful, Chel.
I didn't think you were coming.
- I'm late, is all.
I wouldn't just quit without telling you.
(bright piano music)
(sighing)
I had this perfect this morning.
- Perfect fingering.
But the feeling you miss.
(bright piano music)
What's the matter?
Shh.
(Chel sniffling)
- This town.
(sighing)
They're good people, I know they are.
Except.
- I know they are.
Chel.
I know.
- No you don't know.
Nobody knows.
- I know I love you.
- I'm marrying your brother
in a couple of weeks.
Jens would never do that.
He would never touch me like that.
- My God, if you two are so much in love,
what are you waiting for?
The millennium, Armageddon, what?
I thought you wanted me to kiss you.
I thought you wanted me to touch you.
I thought that you wanted
it as much as I did.
We are different than the
people in this town, Chel.
Can't you see that?
Jens said that I was
dropped here out of the sky.
So were you Chel, so were you.
I walk up Temple Hill every night,
and I watch your light go out.
And I keep thinking that
sometime you might come.
Don't marry him, Chel!
Don't!
(door slamming)
(birds chirping)
- Oh, I should've been there.
- We managed just fine.
Pretty little baby girl.
- Thank goodness it's over,
and everybody's okay.
Thank goodness it's over.
All of it.
(chickens clucking)
(baby whining)
- Are you happy, Chel?
You've been here almost a week,
and you never talk about him.
(chickens sounding)
- About who?
- Your future husband, who do you think?
Aren't you in love with Jens?
You can tell me.
- Esther, of course I'm in love with Jens.
- I mean, you don't act like a girl
who's getting married in a few weeks.
- How am I supposed to act?
My word.
- You remember how I was with Karl?
I couldn't stop talking about him.
He was always on my mind.
Seems like I was always
worked up into a hot sweat.
- Well maybe I'm not you.
Maybe I'm different.
You ever think of that?
Maybe I'm just not the kind to talk about
what's always on my mind.
- You used to be, with me.
- Since you ran off and left me,
I've gotten used to talking to myself.
(light dramatic music)
There's some poppies
blooming up by the road.
I'm gonna go fix a big bouquet.
(baby crying)
(dramatic orchestral music)
(Chel crying)
- Alright everybody, get a wiggle on now.
We've got to get this picture made quick
before the food gets cold.
- Yes.
- [Christine] Now we are going
to be late for the recital.
- Come on now.
- [Christine] Back, little
people in the front.
Alright, somebody get a chair
for Aunt Mary, right there.
Right there, Aunt Mary.
Alright, come on,
everybody, sit down here.
Alright, come on, Alex.
(group chattering)
You sit right over here.
You, you two, come on,
you're in this, too.
- No, Christine.
Not me, just Erik.
- Oh, don't be ridiculous.
Ida, my goodness, we go
through this every time.
Now when Lars was told to take
another wife to take care of,
he said if it was his
duty before God, he would.
And he did.
Now if he was still alive,
he'd be sitting right here
between us, his two wives.
(car horn honking)
All right everybody.
Sit up straight, children.
Come on, Rebecca, come back here
and sit with us, come on.
Come over this way, honey.
Well it's about time
that you two got here.
- Yeah, we're not late, mother.
You're early.
- Come on up here.
Chel.
You're not wearing your wedding dress.
- Oh, Chel doesn't believe
in all that hocus pocus.
Anyway, I already seen her in it.
- Well, Chelnicia, you
look just like an angel.
Look at her, she looks just like an angel.
- You had better face it.
People are gonna talk.
- It was my mother's dress.
I think that she would've wanted me
to wear it for today.
- Well I don't think she could have looked
any more beautiful than her daughter.
My goodness.
Sure fits.
Alright, somebody get a chair for Chel.
Alright everybody, sit up straight now.
We've got to get this made,
so we can eat and do the
dishes before the recital.
- I don't think I belong in it yet.
- Oh of course you do, darling.
- In two weeks, you'll be Mrs. Eriksen.
(birds chirping)
- [Camera Man] Alright everybody.
Now think of Christmas, kids.
Smile.
(flash bulb bursting)
(light piano music)
- She's very good, too.
- Oh, and she's doing unbelievable.
(audience applauding)
- Thank you, Seenie.
Our next performer will be Chel Bowen.
She'll play a piece by
Massenet from the opera Thais.
(man coughing)
(bright piano music)
Good, good.
(audience applauding)
- [Man] Bravo.
Bravo.
- Wasn't she wonderful?
(crowd chattering)
- I'll tell you what.
Best darn piano player I
ever seen or heard about.
- Splendid.
Chel, you were just splendid.
- I wanna see you.
I have to.
- Well, wasn't she wonderful?
- Oh it was wonderful.
They were all so good.
Thank you so much.
- Better than anybody.
- Crystal Springs.
(crowd chattering and laughing)
Mother.
- Yes, oh, we'll see you later.
- Goodbye.
- Erik, good work.
- [Ivor] I think you played better
than Erik.
- Yeah, I think you're right.
- I think she did.
(crowd chattering)
- [Woman] I'd have done
better if I had worn
my old black dress.
You never can trust what
you get from a catalog.
(dramatic orchestral music)
(water rushing)
- I've been trying to fight it.
I just couldn't anymore.
- You're not alone in this.
I'll go with you.
Right now, at Christine's.
We'll tell everyone.
- No.
Erik, no.
Jens is so good.
The family will hate me.
- No.
- My father.
- No, we'll do it together.
Then we'll head out across the continent
on the train to New York.
So many things I wanna show you, Chel.
- Erik, this is all I've ever known.
This town.
The church.
All I've ever wanted
since I was a little girl
was to be married in the temple,
and settle down and have children,
and grow old and die.
I guess it was just part of the plan.
- It's still part of the plan.
It's part of our plan.
And we'll have children.
(dramatic orchestral music)
We'll even grow old together.
- Oh my God, how do I live with this?
- You're my wife already Chel.
And you know it.
You're my wife.
And what am I?
Say it, Chel.
Say it.
- You're my husband.
My husband.
(crickets chirping)
- I'll go with you first thing
in the morning to tell Jens.
- No.
I have to tell him myself.
I owe him that much.
- But you'll get your things packed
so we can leave tomorrow night?
- Yes.
I'll be ready.
Just please, don't tell
anyone until I tell Jens.
- Okay.
Don't be frightened, Chel.
This is a little place.
It's not much of the world.
(light piano music)
You just happened to have been born here.
You'll bring your mountains with you.
Promise me that nothing is gonna stop us.
- Nothing's gonna stop us.
I don't care anymore
what they say or think.
- Thank you, Lord.
Thank you.
Yes!
- Oh, Lord.
Wilt thou redeem my soul?
Wilt thou make me that I may shake
at the appearance of sin?
That I may walk in the
path of the low valley.
That I may be strong on the plain road.
- Do you feel alright, Chel?
You look a little pekid.
- I'm fine.
(rooster crowing)
All the excitement, I guess.
(distant car honking)
- I'm sure gonna miss
our breakfasts together.
Once you're a married lady.
- Me too, Daddy.
(rooster crowing)
Daddy.
- Hmm?
- You and Mama were so much in love.
So maybe you can understand this.
It's kind of difficult to explain.
But,
I feel that way too about somebody.
- Chel, I think I know
what you're trying to say.
And I understand.
It's just natural to feel a little guilty.
You should love Jens
more than you love me.
He's gonna be your partner forever.
It doesn't take anything away from what
we feel for each other.
- Daddy, that's not--
- And I couldn't ask
for a better son-in-law.
Jens is a fine young man.
You know, you've made me very happy.
Ever since the day you were born.
(birds chirping)
Come on, eat up.
Put some color in your cheeks.
(light music)
This is good.
- [Seenie] Ivor, Sarah.
Wait for me.
- [Ivor] Hurry up, then.
- Seenie, what is it?
- [Seenie] There's a body in the river.
They found a body in the river, let's go.
(dramatic orchestral music)
- Daddy, what happened?
- Come here, you don't want to see this.
- Who is it?
- Wells Thursby found her this morning
when he was fixing to take his water turn.
- [Chel] Ruby Snow.
- Found her baby in the saw grass.
- No, not her baby, too.
Not her baby.
- Now don't get all upset, Chel.
- [John] Chel.
Chel.
(train whistle blowing)
(dramatic orchestral music)
- Jens.
Jens.
- Chel?
- Ruby Snow.
She drowned herself and her baby.
- Oh no, oh Chel.
Why on Earth would she
do a thing like that?
- I don't know, Jens.
Jens.
Oh, I want--
- What?
- You.
I wanna get married.
- (chuckling) Now, wait a minute.
What's this got to do with Ruby Snow?
- I don't wanna end up like her.
Desperate, crazy.
Please, you gotta marry me today.
Right now.
- Today?
My, my gosh, Chel.
That's impossible.
We haven't made arrangements
- No.
- at the temple.
- Now, we can go
to Nevada tonight.
(cow mooing)
Panaca.
We can get a seat on the
temple when we get back.
- Chel, I don't even know if Panaca's got
a justice of the peace.
My gosh, Chel.
Everybody'll think we had to.
- I don't care what people think.
- I haven't got the house ready.
No curtains, no furniture.
- Please Jens.
I'm scared.
- Hey.
Scared of what?
- Scared of losing everything.
So hold me.
Hold me tight as you can.
- Well heck then.
What are we waiting for?
You're in charge here, Heber.
I'll get Oley's kid Andy over
here this afternoon to help.
We're getting married.
I don't even have my dang
wedding pants hemmed up.
- 400.
(bell dinging)
And 500.
Now those are all brand new bills.
- Don't worry, Verla May.
I'll take very good care of them.
- Hide 'em in your shoe.
That's the best place.
- Also, I'd like to close out the account
my father left me.
(door slamming)
There should be about $2,000.00 in there.
- What are you trying
to do, break the bank?
Well, you gotta fill out a form.
Can't take any money
without filling out a form.
I hope you're not doing something dumb
like your brother Jens.
- Oh yeah?
What did Jens do?
- Oh, he came in this morning
to pick up some cash,
and then headed out for
Nevada with Chel Bowen.
- [Chuckling) What'd you say?
- You heard me.
They're getting married
before the wedding.
(ominous orchestral music)
Erik, you forgot your money.
(door slamming)
- Who made her do it?
- What's the matter with you?
Are you sick, boy?
- Somebody made her do it.
Somebody forced her.
It was you or Ivor.
- It was Chel.
Chel was the one.
- No.
- Yes.
You think I wanted this?
The whole family is upset.
They're gonna think it's a shotgun affair.
- She doesn't love him, I know that.
- You listen to me, you
listen to me Erik Eriksen.
I don't wanna know what this is all about.
But I think it's best you leave her be.
You understand me?
Leave my daughter alone.
- She doesn't love him.
- Yeah, well we'll see about that.
(dramatic orchestral music)
- Got nothing fancy here to say.
I don't marry folks much.
I'm just gotta read the ceremony,
if that's alright with you.
- That'll be fine, just read it.
- Yes well, here it goes.
Do you, Chelnicia Bowen, take this man,
Jens Perry Eriksen,
to be your lawful wedded husband?
- I do.
- I want you to know that I
butchered this pig myself.
Did my own curing.
I can't stand boughten ham and bacon.
Oh, Jens, you can take
a plate home to Chel.
- Ah, I don't think
she can eat it, Mother.
She was feeling so poorly when I left her.
- Well, anything we should know about?
- She's not expecting,
if that's what you mean.
She's been having some bad headaches.
- You're right about the ham.
Best I ever tasted.
- Thank you, Erik.
- Glad to see you're eating again.
- So what's the story, Erik?
You're going back, ain't ya?
New York?
- Yes, I will be going back.
- Well, when would that be?
- Erik hasn't been feeling good.
I tell him to stay right here in Templeton
where I can look after him.
- Looks like snow for the deer hunt.
- Looks clear to me.
- Snow's better.
Easier to see the deer.
Of course you wouldn't
happen to know that,
'cause you haven't been hunting with us.
Couldn't get them famous hands frostbit.
- Alright now, everybody eat up.
There's lots more in the kitchen.
- My hands have been frostbit, Ivor.
In France, during the war.
Maybe you forgot.
You know actually, I think
I might enjoy the deer hunt.
- [Christine] You don't even eat venison.
- Well, sorry to leave, folks.
But I promised Chel I'd be home by 7:00.
- Well you can't leave before dessert.
Erik's gonna play for us later.
- Jens doesn't need to hear me play.
He can listen to Chel.
- Yeah.
Well, I better get on home.
- Oh.
I think it's a sin, Erik.
You give those expensive lessons to Chel
for a wedding present,
and she's just plum give up on the piano.
I mean, they ask her to play
down at the Relief Society,
and she said she'd quit.
The girl is not herself.
She's just acting so queer-like.
(engine puttering)
(cow mooing)
(atmospheric orchestral music)
(dog barking)
- Come here, good boy.
That's a good boy.
Come to Daddy.
(dog barking)
(door clacking)
Yeah, that's a good boy.
Let's go see Mommy, hm?
Sister Chelnicia.
You were sorely missed.
- His feet, did you wipe his feet?
It's muddy in the yard.
Let's get this house in order.
- Yeah, I wiped his paws.
Hey, don't get mean.
He's a good boy.
Hey, sit boy, sit.
(snapping)
- [Chel] How was supper?
- Good.
Five kinds of salad, three kinds of meat.
Biscuits, of course.
Erik's still in town.
He looks sort of thin, pale.
- What are you staring at?
- You're beautiful, that's all.
You're just beautiful.
(light orchestral music)
- Oh Jens, he's got my slipper, Jens.
He chews up everything.
(dog whining)
- Yeah, no, he's a nuisance.
I just thought you wanted a dog.
I mean, after Ivor shot
that stray that time.
- Well, I don't.
I'm sorry, you smell like milk.
- Hey, come here, boy.
Come here, yeah.
That's a good boy.
(bell dinging)
(car honking)
(bright orchestral music)
(engine sputtering)
(horse clopping)
(people chattering)
(bell ringing)
(bike clattering)
(dramatic orchestral music)
- Are you gonna avoid
me forever, is that it?
- I've been busy.
I had to get the house all ready,
get everything moved in.
- Why did you do it?
- What happened between us was a mistake.
It was wrong.
- Answer me, why did you marry him?
- We sinned.
It was a sin.
You shouldn't stay here.
You don't belong.
(horse neighing)
- If somebody didn't know better,
they'd think you two was
fighting or something.
- I was just telling him
I don't need his help.
I keep telling you man,
I don't need your help.
- Well, as you can see,
we're not gonna starve up on the hunt.
- Fine.
Ah, Jens, I'll see you in the morning.
- Right, I'll be riding
up with you and Ivor.
(dramatic piano music)
I was out in the barn.
Heard the music.
I watched you through the window.
Ya, ya look like a picture.
Lamp shining on your hair.
- Peeping Tom.
- Hey I'm allowed.
I'm your husband.
First time I heard you
play since we got married.
It sounded good.
- I was just packing up your stuff.
- Oh yeah, don't want to
forget my red hunting coat.
It's in the basement.
Don't want somebody thinking I'm a deer.
- When have I ever
forgotten anything, Jens?
Aren't your meals always
ready, your house cleaned,
clothes washed and ironed?
- Yeah, I didn't mean that, I...
Sorry I interrupted.
(light piano music)
(crickets chirping)
(engine puttering)
(rooster crowing)
(horn honking)
Good lord, Chel.
I thought you did all this last night.
- Butter won't spread.
- Well, you gotta soften
it with warm milk.
That's the way mother does it.
- I don't care how your mother does it.
- Chel.
What is it?
(car horn honking)
- That honking, can't they wait?
It won't hurt 'em to wait.
(rooster crowing)
- Yeah, where am I here?
Gun, ammunition, rope, bags,
bedding, pillow.
- I made some hot barley,
it's on the stove.
I was gonna make bacon and eggs, but--
- Hey did you get my hunting
coat up out of moth balls?
- Yes, yeah.
- Hey, maybe I oughta ask those jokers
to come on in for a minute.
- No.
Jens.
I don't want anyone to
see my kitchen like this.
- Who are you trying to impress?
Ivor or Erik?
What, I'm drinking my
barley black this morning?
- Since when are we out
of cream, out of dairy?
- I could've got that myself, Chel.
I just--
- You're just used to having
your mother's way, haven't you?
Lord knows these sandwiches
aren't gonna be so beautiful.
- You cut the crusts off mine?
- Yes, I cut your crusts off.
- I'm sorry, Chel.
I just don't like the crust.
(car horn honking)
- God, can't you tell them to stop?
I can't concentrate.
- Chel.
Maybe I better not go.
- No.
Sorry, Jens.
You're so good.
I'm just not myself lately.
(rooster crowing)
(car horn honking)
- [Jens] I'm coming.
Will ya hold your horses?
- [Ivor] I've been
sitting out here forever.
I'm thinking about going
- Hey, Jens.
- home and shaving again.
- I got it.
- [Jens] It's my turn to drive.
- You get breakfast?
(engine puttering)
(dramatic orchestral music)
- Jens.
Jens, your coat.
- This thing is more
trouble than it's worth.
Give me a pair of horses anytime.
- She didn't pack my red hunting coat.
Gosh, I swear to God.
I only brought my milking jacket.
It's not warm enough for anything.
My red cap, too.
It's in the pocket.
- (chuckling) And you thought
you had the perfect wife.
- I've never known Chel
to forget anything.
It's your fault, Erik.
She's up half the night playing the piano.
Didn't even get around to making
the sandwiches 'til this morning.
- Here.
Take my coat, I won't
be doing much hunting.
- Who says you ain't huntin'?
You're getting your buck, boy.
We'll get you some warm duds.
Here.you put that around your hat.
Bright enough.
Never seen a deer wearing
a red handkerchief.
(geese squawking)
Hey let's go, let's get the lead out.
We'll be back soon.
(men chattering)
(light guitar music)
- Come on, you want some?
- No, no thanks.
- Come on boys, best
home brew in the county.
- Against my religion.
- Yes.
- Come on, Jens.
- Yeah, a little vacation won't hurt you.
I guess every man needs
that once in a while.
Whiskey makes me feel so glad
Oh Whiskey Johnny
Whiskey killed my poor old dad
Whiskey makes me feel so fine
I like whiskey all the time
Oh Whiskey Johnny
- Yeah.
(men laughing)
- Taking a whiz?
- No, just, a smoke.
You want one?
- (chuckling) No thanks, Erik.
I learned my lesson when I was 10,
smoking cedar bark in daddy's barn.
(Erik chuckling)
(Jens laughing)
Nearly burned it down.
My gosh, would you look at those stars.
It looks like you could
pick 'em like peaches.
- Yes.
- Moonlight through the pines.
(men chattering)
All I need is Chel up here with me.
You got a girl, Erik?
- What?
- You know, a girlfriend.
Waiting for you back East.
Your fancy free now since the divorce.
- Not really.
No one.
- Come on, Erik.
You can tell me.
I bet you got hot and cold running women
back there in New York.
Handsome guy like yourself.
(Erik chuckling)
So.
What am I?
The village idiot?
- What are you talking about?
- Or am I just a stupid country hick?
(dramatic orchestral music)
- I never thought that you
were a country hick.
I know you're not stupid.
- Then don't you think I know?
If I'm not stupid,
don't you think I figured it out?
There's something going
on between you and Chel.
I don't know what it is,
but hell, I don't like it.
- Hey, pouring up another one in here.
- Yeah, be right in in a minute.
Man, I could go for some
more of that home brew.
How about you?
- Jens, Chel is your wife.
- I know, I know.
Forget it.
I have to trust you.
You're my brother.
And blood is thicker than water.
Isn't that right?
- Isn't that right?
(Jens chuckling)
- Whoa.
(men laughing)
(water rushing)
(birds chirping)
- That the only handkerchief you got?
I knew a fella one time here,
had a white handkerchief.
Another fella thought he was a deer,
and blew his face all to hell.
- Yeah well we don't
shoot at a deer's backend.
- Yeah, well we're not
the only hunters up here.
Some of these boys get
pretty trigger happy.
Hey hold it up up there.
Let's figure this thing out here.
- Hey, watch for my red flag.
I'll take the first stand in the hollow.
- Alright.
- Alright Erik, you go on down there.
I'll get Oley here to send
you down a little doe.
- God, Ivor, I'm not gonna shoot a doe.
- Well, then I'll just tell him
to send down a big old buck.
I'll tell him little
Erik's got a beat on him.
(ominous music)
(birds squawking)
(birds chirping)
(branch cracking)
(hooves pattering)
(gun firing)
(suspenseful orchestral music)
(branch cracking)
(Erik panting)
- I got you now.
(gun firing)
(birds chirping)
(dramatic orchestral music)
Oh, God.
Jens.
No.
No, not you, Jens, not you.
Say something for me.
Oh, something, something.
Help!
Help.
- Erik.
Oh, brother.
Baby brother.
(gun firing)
It was an accident, wasn't it?
- An accident, Ivor.
My God, what else would it be?
- You knew where he was.
Here in the hollow.
You called about her.
- No, no, I, I wounded a buck.
I was following it.
- You and Chel.
- I didn't know where I was.
- You don't think I knew it.
- Uh!
God, help me.
- In this family, we take care of our own.
- No.
No, I wounded a buck,
and I didn't know where I was.
I didn't know where
I was going.
- Look at me.
Now you listen to me, Erik Eriksen.
You dare touch her,
I will kill you with my own hands.
(dramatic orchestral music)
- Ivor.
- [Man] Hey, let him up.
- Oh, my God.
Oh, my God.
What happened?
Jens!
Jens, good God, you killed him.
Jens, oh God!
- Your mother used to work for us.
Did you know that?
- Yes.
She told me.
- Used to do the washing,
scrub the floors.
Until my father decided
to take another wife.
Hell, I remember.
I was only so high, but I remember.
Saddest day of my life, until today,
was the day you was born.
(atmospheric orchestral music)
Mama tried to make the best of it,
even helped with the birthing.
Later on, I heard her.
Crying in her bedroom.
Not gonna tell anybody who fired the gun.
Could've been a stray
bullet from above the ridge.
Decided that.
After the funeral,
I want you out of this here town forever.
That's all I'm asking.
So as I don't have to look at you,
stuffy little sissy
bastard, in the eyes again.
- You boys got your buck already?
- Chel, I got some bad news.
(dramatic orchestral music)
(atmospheric music)
(birds chirping)
Jens was the baby.
He was born on Christmas Eve.
I always thought Santa Claus brung him.
10 years old.
He used to shine shoes
down at the post office.
One day, he was shining
a pair of cowboy boots,
and a man looked down,
gave him a rosy tip.
Quit right then and there.
He told me he ain't never
gonna shine no pair of shoes
again, as long as he lives.
Oh Lord, just take care of him.
(crying)
(Chel crying)
(mourners chattering)
- Chel.
(horse clopping)
(knocking on door)
Chel?
Brought a little food up here for you.
Make you feel better.
Get a little food in your stomach.
- [Chel] I'm not hungry.
- Whole family downstairs.
So many people turned out.
Jens had so many friends, it's a comfort.
- He was so cold.
When I touched him in his casket.
- That wasn't him, Chel.
That was just his earthly body.
Jens' spirit already left him.
It's taken flight, so to speak.
These things are hard for
us mortals to understand.
- I wasn't good to him.
I wasn't a good wife.
- Well, of course you was.
Oh he was proud of you.
My golly.
You kept that house neat as a pin.
- He tried so hard to make me happy.
- Well, you was happy.
The two of you, of course you was.
Hey.
I remember when you was just a little tot.
Perched up on your daddy's
knee at the baseball games.
You was just a little angel.
(dramatic orchestral music)
Mother and I was thinking you might
wanna come over here to live.
Oley's boy can take over the dairy.
- I can go home.
To my daddy's house, I mean.
- You're an Eriksen now, Chel.
You don't belong at your daddy's house.
I don't want you to be afraid of nothing.
Jens was my brother.
I'm gonna take care of you now.
- I don't--
- No, I don't mean nothing like marriage.
With my brother barely in the grave.
I mean, not unless
somewhere down the line,
that's what you want.
- I, I can't.
I can't.
- Listen,
I jumped the gun here.
I'm sorry.
I'm not good at these type of things.
I never learned to find a ways.
I'm not smooth like some we know.
You and me belong here, Chel.
One of these days, we're gonna
be buried right out
there alongside of Jens.
I care about my family.
And about doing the right thing.
You can count on me,
that's what I'm trying to say.
To take care of things.
Keep it in the family.
I'll wait outside the door for you.
(dramatic orchestral music)
- [Man] Accept my condolences.
- [Woman] Such a shame.
(mourners chattering)
- Dear, Ivor.
- Mercy.
- [Woman] Oh my dear.
(mourners chattering)
- I'm so sorry, Christine.
- I'm glad that you was here.
That you two had some time together.
Erik, I know my boys give you a bad time,
but Jens always stood up for you.
He always said you was a artist.
(crying)
It was them Salt Lakers.
They come down here to shoot
at anything that moves.
- I'll be leaving in the morning.
I have to pack.
- Two of my boys lie buried in France.
And I guess with war,
(dramatic orchestral music)
you come to expect it.
But little Jens.
I keep remembering how he
wouldn't eat his bread crusts.
Even when he was grown up.
- I have to pack.
I have to.
I have to pack.
- [Christine] Jens, Jens.
(dramatic orchestral music)
(atmospheric orchestral music)
(knocking on door)
- What is it?
- Chel is here.
She doesn't seem right, Erik.
She seems to be confused or something.
She looks so strange.
You shouldn't go back to
New York so soon, Erik.
The strain of all this.
- Chel.
- Erik.
I love you.
I never stopped.
- Wait.
Chel.
There's something that you don't know.
The boys decided not to tell you.
They decided not to tell anybody.
On the hunt, I wounded a deer.
I was following it, the blood.
I saw a flash of red, and I fired.
It was his handkerchief.
It was his red handkerchief.
I'm the one that killed him, Chel.
I'm the one.
- He didn't have his red hunting coat.
(bell ringing)
You would've seen him if I
had remembered to put it in.
I've gone over it and over it.
It was my fault.
- No, I knew he didn't
have his red hunting coat.
I knew where he was
standing, in the hollow.
As I pulled the trigger,
Chel, I think I knew.
- Stop.
Don't say that.
- No it's true.
I think somewhere deep inside,
I wanted to kill him.
- Erik.
Don't ever say that to anybody.
Never.
(door clacking)
- Chel?
Maybe a cup of Mormon tea, hmm?
- No.
Mother.
Chel's going home to her father's.
I'm taking her home.
(dramatic orchestral music)
(crickets chirping)
- It just came to me.
It's so clear.
I didn't go with you to New York
because it wasn't part of God's plan.
He needed Jens in heaven.
- Chel, you can justify anything
by saying it was God's plan.
It doesn't make a difference, he is dead.
He was moving one minute.
Alive.
He was laughing.
If you can find a plan for that.
- You still love me.
I know you do.
- Listen to me.
I can't be with you, ever.
- We'll wait.
- Ivor knows.
- Ivor will never tell anyone.
He would never do that to the family name.
We'll wait a long time, even here.
- You don't know what you're saying.
- I only know that I love you.
I have always loved you.
- How could we ever live with it, Chel?
Do you really think that Jens
is in the clouds celebrating,
doing a special job for God?
- Yes.
I do.
- No, he is nowhere.
I killed him, he's dead.
I even think I meant to.
Don't you understand that?
- That day, rolling in the grass,
with the sun and the
trees above our heads.
- No, you were right.
It was a sin.
I cheated on my brother.
- Erik, we couldn't help ourselves.
We were burning up.
- I love you, Chel.
(dramatic orchestral music)
I loved you before.
And I love you still.
I always will.
But I can't take you away from here.
I'll never see you again, Chel.
(dramatic orchestral music)
- You'll come back for me.
I know you will.
(bright piano music)
(gun clacking)
- Erik.
Don't wanna shoot you in the back.
- No.
Ivor.
(dramatic piano music)
- I told you.
In this family, we take care of our own.
(gun firing)
(dramatic orchestral music)
(bright guitar music)