Granny: The park
sure looks lovely today.
Ah, there's nothing like
a nice, relaxing game of whist
at the looney club.
Both: Hi,
granny.
Hello, kids.
How are things
at my favorite
children's park?
Best read it
yourself.
"This park to be closed
in 80 days."
Unpaid debt?
E-Excuse me, kids.
I need time
to think about this.
[Gasps] Huh?
[Ticking]
Uh...
Mmm...
[Growls]
[Snarling]
Sylvester: I detest the sight
of ribs from the inside.
[Pop]
Grr...
Man: Pure balderdash,
I say!
I've suffered
the last defeat
at the hands
of my cursed Nemesis
cool cat.
Why, his
preposterous antics
have been
my absolute undoing.
Unh.
Still, it's best
to be bested
by an intelligence
better than mine.
There! I said it.
What is it that you said,
colonel rimfire?
Well, that, simply put,
there is no greater
intelligence on earth
than the feline
intelligence.
Well, he certainly
got that right.
Get back here!
Eek.
Some globe-trotter he is.
Colonel, do you mean to say
that no creature on earth
is capable
of outsmarting a cat?
Madam, I'll stake
my entire fortune on it.
What about it?
Do you gents concur?
[Discussing]
Hmm...
You're on.
[Slap]
[Gasps]
I know a certain
little canary who is more
than a match for any cat.
[Tweets]
Poppycock!
No, tweety.
What crapulous rubbish!
Why, I've never heard
anything like that
in my life.
I propose that my tweety
can travel around
the world in 80 days,
collecting the pawprints
of 80 cats.
Ha!
Ohh, for granny,
I'll do it.
I was getting tired
of outwitting the same
old puddy tat anyhow.
Since today is
October 2nd, tweety
will encircle the globe
and return with
a canceled passport
and his 80 cat pawprints
to this very spot
on December 21st
in exactly 80 days.
Madam, you've
made yourself a wager.
Oh, bully for you,
granny.
You stood up
to him, you did.
Well done, granny.
[Rattling]
Ever get the feelin'
you just missed
something?
Now tweety, with the looney
club's high connections,
I've obtained your own
special royal passport.
Royal passport?
You get customs in each
country you visit to stamp
the up-front pages,
and these extra pages
in the back are for
all the pawprints
you'll collect
along your route.
Now, I don't want
to overburden you,
but I did bet the farm
that you could safely
pass every port of entry.
Sheesh, already
with the guilt.
I'll pass every
point--paw, too.
I'm off!
[Crowd cheering]
Can it be done?
Certainly not.
Circle the globe
in time and then
return to this spot?
There isn't a hope,
a ghost of a chance.
I bet from London,
tweety won't even
get to France.
It's all in vain.
Well, it can't be done.
And when this thing
is over I'll have won.
He can make it
all the way.
It's impossible,
I say.
Is it yes, or no?
* can little tweety go *
* around the world
in 80 days? *
* england, France,
Tibet, Peru *
it's impossible to do.
* to make it 'round
the world in 80 days *
to Argentina, Rome, Seville,
Tibet, Berlin, Japan, Brazil.
* you can't traverse
the world in 80 days *
* it's all in vain,
why, it's insane
to even try *
* to go from Budapest,
Malaysia *
* through Nepal
and half of Asia *
* out to Spain,
the mid-Ukraine *
* and French versailles *
are you ready?
On my Mark.
Are you steady?
Then embark.
* that's the bird *
* we all adore *
* I'm gonna do what no one
else has done before *
* he's going 'round
the world in 80 days *
* right through
to Pakistan *
* Taipei, and China,
Budapest, Bombay *
* I'm gonna see
the world *
* in 80 ways *
all those
exotic habitats.
Outsmarting
puddy tats!
* around the world
in 80 days *
* I gotta check
but you can bet *
* that when I'm through *
* I'll be back
to say I won *
* on December 21 *
* oh, yes indeedy *
* I'll be speedy *
that's my sweetie.
All: Hooray for tweety!
* it's the chance,
I'm gonna take it *
* I say he'll
never make it *
* no one's ever
done it all the ways *
* gone around the world *
* in 80 days *
gotta run.
"Royal passport stolen."
Sooner or later,
you'll have company, mate.
Those foreign pussycats
gonna nab my lunch?
I'll fix that canary.
[Tweeting]
Hey!
First, you gotta
catch me, puddy.
Well, first
things first.
Tweety: I'm right on course
for Paris, France.
Hey, I'm being
blown too far east
by this stiff wind.
I'm lost some place
over the alps.
Unh.
Whoa!
Oh!
Unh.
Excuse me,
Mr. Mountain climber.
I could use a hand.
A hand?
I could use
my own movie.
You canary.
Uh, that's
beyond my control.
Some assistance,
please.
Huh! Mr. Popular.
Ahh!
When life hangs
in the balance,
you can always depend
on one thing.
Extreme sports.
Nyah!
Ahh!
Ah!
Some cameo this is.
How the heck
did I get here?
[Stammering]
Ahh!
Oof.
Thanks.
You're a couple
of crown jewels.
Eh, it's a living.
Humph.
Show off.
Sheesh.
10 days in Paris
and no sign
of that stupid bird.
They must
have dropped
a whole sequence
or something.
A pussycat can't live
on decaf cappuccino
trailmix cafe au lait,
for crying out loud.
He must have got lost.
Probably be another
month before tweety
finds old gay Paris.
[Cat snarling]
Huh?
Hey!
Watch it, sister.
No, you don't.
Whew. That Paris customs
office better be close.
Nobody swipes my canary
croissant, mademoiselle.
Merci.
Oh, Mr. Customs man,
this might interest you.
[Speaking French]
You 2 skunks must
not fight over moi.
Skunks?
Tch, tch, tch.
It is so
UN-mademoiselle.
Merci.
That's one down,
79 to go.
[Snarls]
French bubblegum.
Sylvester: Listen,
i--i--i know how it looks,
but you've got it
all wrong.
I'm not a skunk.
Skunk: May love
can never be wrong.
[Kissing]
[Sylvester screams]
Foghorn: Place your bets here.
Place your birdseed bets.
Step, I say, step right up
and place it on tweety.
Yeah. He's leaving, I say,
he's leaving France.
Jet streams are
blowing him southeast
way ahead of schedule.
[Beeping]
[Indistinct voice]
We've set
the odds at 20 to 1
in tweety's favor.
[Indistinct voice]
Come on.
Bet some birdseed.
Don't be chicken.
My goodness.
Haven't we
come far enough
to stop using
that horrid term?
Keep your shirt on,
prissy.
He's just, I say, just
stirring the wagering pot.
Looks like
our fine feathered friend
is heading
into venetian territory.
Uh, venice, Italy,
that is.
Whew! I'm famished
from tasting nothing
but bubblegum.
Oh, boy.
Italian grub.
Birdseed with your
best marinara sauce.
Mm-hmm.
Oops. I overdid it
on the basil.
Unh!
Oof!
Whew.
Unh!
Oof.
Well, there are other
modes of transport.
Unh!
Ahh!
Row me to
the venetian consulate.
Ah, venice.
City of romance,
architecture,
food, and--
uh-oh.
Italian puddy tats!
Of course, this
completely wrecks
the present
digestive situation.
Oh, Mr. Gondolier?
[Snarls]
[Gasps]
I've got
a queasy feeling,
and this bridge has got
5, 10, 15 puddy tats.
Oof!
[All gasping]
[Tweety burps]
Tweety: It was all gas.
Who knew?
Thank you.
[Cats snarling]
Not only does this rest
my little wings,
but it's a great way
to find pawprints.
Lola bunny here, with
an lnn tweety update.
That trusty ankle
transmitter indicates
our globe-trotting
canary
has successfully
navigated the canals
of venice.
Venetian locals confirm
tweety has amassed
a grand total thus far
of 37 feline pawprints.
[All murmuring]
Pure dumb luck.
Absolutely.
Prepare to back
that up, colonel.
I am. I'll add
to the wager
my complete Nash
hubcap collection.
Oh, why I'll break out
my moustache wax reserves
and triple my wager!
Ho ho. You, colonel,
are the latest in
a long line of people
to underestimate
tweety.
[Breathing heavily]
Whew.
Oh, you must be
the Egyptian counsel.
There's one thing
I need right here.
Your stamp.
Oh, and love
your Fez.
[Yawns]
Whew. I just flew in
from Italy,
and boy, are
my arms tired.
Wow!
Now that's what
you call a snub nose.
Sticks and stones
may break my nose,
but names will
never hurt me.
[Yawns]
I think this is
a good time for me
to take
a little catnap.
Ooh, what I just said.
[Giggling]
[Yawns]
[Slurping]
There's my little
desert oasis.
Let's get 'em,
boys!
[All snarling]
Uh-oh.
I thought I saw a pack
of desert puddy tats.
Give me about
a 20-second lead,
then follow me.
I did. I did see a pack
of desert puddy tats.
Hah!
Mmm, humph.
Huh?
Cat: Duh,
18, 19, 20!
Sylvester: Oh, stupid
mercenary pussycats.
[All snarling]
I better hide in here.
Come back here,
you desert sandwich.
Whew.
I should be safe
in here from that
bad old puddy tat.
Oh, look.
A piccolo.
[Playing]
Doesn't look
like any mummy
I ever met.
Say, pretty lady,
do you know
what tunnel
I can take to get
out of here?
Ah, ah, ah!
Ahh.
[Gasping]
You've heard of
the Lincoln tunnel?
Well, that's
the stinkin' tunnel.
Ah!
Pf-ooey!
Oh, what's this?
Lucky for me,
I'm a graduate
of the hooked-on-
hieroglyphics program.
"Death comes on wings
to he who enters
the tomb
of the pharaoh."
Say, I have wings.
And I've got you.
Oh, puddy, can you
read hieroglyphics?
Certainly.
Well, then.
You better read that.
Ah, um, "no shirt,
no shoes, no service."
Hmm. Nothing like eating
in a classy joint.
You've been on my menu
for a long time.
Just a minute, bub.
Say, pal. Can't you see
I'm about to dine here?
[Muffled snarling]
[Weakly] Mommy.
Looks like Egyptian cats
have more than 9 lives.
Now, if I could only find
a way out of here.
[Sylvester screams]
Thanks,
bad old puddy tat.
Ooh, there will be
plenty of opportunities
to collect pawprints
in the jungle.
[Loud stomping]
Say, cousin,
could you tell me
where I might find
some cats around here?
[Snoring]
Hmm?
Unh.
Oops. Dead end.
Tweety: Could you
stamp this passport?
Thanks.
Don't go in there.
It's scary.
Huh?
Lucky for me,
that lion swallowed
the local counsel.
[Growls]
[Roars]
Tee-hee-hee-hee.
Oof.
Oof, oof.
[Laughing]
And you call yourself
the king of the forest.
Sheesh.
Target in sight.
Bombs away.
Direct hit.
Uh-oh.
Uh-oh again.
[Both snarling]
Huh?
Ah!
Guess they never
heard the saying
"birds of a feather
flock together."
[Laughing]
Hmm.
Odds are way--i say--
way up on tweety.
Right now, it looks
like our bird's
heading for Tibet.
Tibet?
He's supposed
to be the one
everyone else
is wagering on.
No, no, son.
Tibet the country,
not the infinitive.
Uh, verb, that is.
Well, why didn't
you say so?
Nice boy,
but his skylight
leaks a little.
Ahh!
Thanks.
Whoa!
Talk about
your air turbulence.
Say, what
a spectacular view.
Strange. I didn't know
there was anything else
built this high
up in the himalayas.
Subtle, isn't it?
Hmm. Looks like these
locals are gonna put on
some kind
of peaceful ceremony.
[Tweeting]
[Gasps]
Male voice: Oh,
great yellow one,
please accept
our meager sacrifice,
this puny canary,
known as awooga.
Tweety: Oh, my gosh, those
cats are about to sacrifice
that poor little canary
in the name of a statue
that looks just like me.
Here goes nothing.
What the--hey!
Whaa!
[Moaning]
Pfffttt!
What force of nature
dares disrupt our peaceful
canary sacrifice?
This force
of nature, bub.
[Gasps]
It is you,
oh, great one.
Please forgive us
for displeasing you.
Your wish is our command.
Name it and
it shall be yours.
Well,
there is one thing.
[Tweeting]
Aw, stop it.
You're embarrassing me.
Besides, I got
some rules to dictate.
Now, take this down.
We promise never
to sacrifice any more birds,
by order of
the great one himself.
Promise?
Oh, I suppose so...
But what will
we do with ourselves
on Saturday nights?
Well, I picked up
a friend here
who might be able
to answer that question.
Oh, I always wanted
a little kitty cat
to love and play with me.
Now I got me a whole bunch
to call my own.
Are you always such
a kind, caring person,
tweety?
When I have the time.
Oh, my gosh, time!
It's an honor to offer
your pawprints
to the great canary, guys.
How lucky you are.
Say, you're pretty handy
at this, awooga.
When you're the only canary
in a land of cats,
you catch on quick.
Whoa, that's enough.
Leave some for
the other countries.
Other countries?
I've got half the world
yet to see
before I get back to
england on December 21.
Mind if I join you?
Why not? Just one
question, awooga.
Why do they
call you awooga?
Heh heh heh heh.
[Horn sound]
Awooga!
Never underestimate
a small package.
Come on, awooga,
half the world
is our oyster.
Ohh!
Extreme sports
are a ubiquitous
global commodity.
Whoa!
[Speaking Chinese]
Thanks.
Please, ship it ahead.
Now that was off the wall.
Whoa!
We're at the mercy
of the jet stream.
Mexico?
Man, that was one powerful
gust of wind.
Thanks.
We can't carry
all these trophies.
Whoa, ho ho!
Whoa!
This must be rio.
Duh...by the sea-o.
Ohh!
Button youse
lip, mugsy.
We're supposed
to be hidin' out in
this here country.
Ohh.
Mmm.
Tweety: Much obliged.
Oops. Wind express.
Lovely detour,
but we've gotta
get back on track.
Ow! That chafes.
Ha, hi!
Ahh.
We'll be fine
as long as you don't
run out of sticky notes.
Whoa!
Enough of this
backwards business.
Let's show the jet stream
who's boss.
Whee!
TV anchor:
The world continues
to marvel at tweety.
That's just peachy,
but the world is made up of
a lot more than just birds.
Besides, I'm hungry.
TV anchor:
Tweety seems to have added
a traveling companion
along the global route.
Well, I say, all right.
2 birds, one mission,
more birdseed bettin'.
Ah, yes.
[Cheering]
First China,
then Mexico to Japan.
Now that's takin'
the direct route.
Hurry up, awooga.
There goes our boat
to america.
[Horn blows]
[Breathing hard]
Take a rest, awooga.
I know that your
hair must be tired.
I always heard
there was lots of food
on these cruise ships.
[Laughing maniacally]
Oh--oh!
Ah, you must be
the cat we got
to catch
those pesky mice.
They're in the galley.
Get to it!
Uhh!
You can come back up
when you've caught 'em.
He don't know him
very well, do he?
Might as well have
a couple of mouse
appetizers down here
then go topside
for the main course.
Mmm...heh heh heh.
Hey, Bert, we're on
a boat leaving Japan,
headin' to america
eatin' Swiss cheese.
Yeah, hubie, ain't
it great bein' a mouse?
Sure thing, Bert,
sure thing.
Say, hube,
what do you say we take
a jog around the deck
to work off
some of this cheese?
Right behind ya, Bert.
All we need to do is run...
For our lives!
Aah!
Come back here,
you p-p-pesky stowaways.
Heh heh.
Don't ask us where
the skillet went.
[Laughs]
Ok, here's what
we're gonna do, Bert.
First you...
[Whispering]
Hee hee hee,
and then I will...
Hee hee hee.
Heh heh heh.
Riot. Heh heh.
Pffttt! Pffttt!
Help!
Pussycat overboard.
Pffttt!
[Roars]
Got ya!
What--whoa, ho!
Whoa, ho!
[Gasps]
Nice effects.
Yeah, aah!
[Whimpers]
Aw, the poor puddy
wants to go play
with those sharks,
but his claws
are all stuck.
Don't worry,
puddy tat,
I'll liberate you.
Ohh...unh!
Aah!
[Splash]
[Chomping and fighting]
Ooh, look how fast
that puddy tat can swim.
Heh heh heh.
Yeah. Riot.
Help! Help!
Cat overboard!
Gee, I think puddy
is in real trouble.
We'd better help.
Ready, awooga?
Both: 1, 2, 3!
Come on.
[Gasping]
Phew.
What I won't do
for Warner brothers.
You saved my life.
How's that for irony?
There goes our ride.
If you use
your imagination...
And here comes
the tide.
Aah!
[Panting]
[Coughing]
Where are we?
It's not on
my itinerary,
but look!
Thanks.
G'day.
Wow! Wherever we are,
they sure grow
big mouses.
Those aren't mice,
puddy tat.
They're kangaroos.
We're in Australia.
Well, I see a shrimp
I'd like to put on
the bar-b.
Hey!
Cut that out.
Ha--huh?
What--ha ha!
Ms-5 water spout!
Duck and cover!
[Babbling]
Aah, ha ha!
It's a twister with
really big teeth.
Mmm...eee!
Tas hungry.
Heh heh heh.
I thought you were
Australian.
Heh heh.
Time for tas dinner.
[Gulps]
You look like
the kind of guy
who savors
a fine gourmet meal.
Well, let me
tell you what.
[Whispering]
A couple of canaries...
That puddy's
up to something.
We'd better take off.
Going somewhere?
Fly for it!
Get me outta here!
Smells like
a butcher shop.
Huh?
[Growling]
Eep.
Uh-oh.
Let's peel rubber!
Huh? Hmm?
Ohh.
Hmm.
Heh heh.
Varoom.
Punch it.
Whoa.
Safety first, mate.
Look!
There they are!
Hey, it's extreme sports,
not extreme peril.
Yeah, aah!
Aah...
Uh, uhh!
Cats hate water.
What am I doin' here?
Hey, puddy,
what's cookin'?
[Growls]
Aah!
Where did those
2 snacks go?
Now, don't you
be gettin'
any ideas.
Wait. Stop! Nooo!
Eeee....whoa!
Whoa, ho ho! Oh,
ow, oww, whoa, whoa!
[Laughing maniacally]
Aah!
Uhh!
Va-varoom!
Mmm, mmm, mmm!
Heh heh heh.
Varoom-varoom.
[Sputtering]
Heh heh. Heh.
Tas like.
There goes
our deposit.
[Breathing hard]
Whoa!
Got ya.
Either you got
low blood sugar
or you're
just plain pooped.
I can't continue.
You go on without me.
No way, awooga.
We'll find a boat
out of here.
Well, we'd better
find it quick.
Look.
Hey, bright eyes,
step on it.
My lunch--
I mean, our lunch
is getting away.
[Groaning]
Hiya!
Heh heh heh.
Aah!
Huh?
Ooh.
[Splash]
[Grunting]
Uh-oh. We got a stowaway
on the forward mast.
Time to bail, awooga.
Hiya, puddy.
Got ya!
Careful, silly,
you could fall.
Whaa!
Ha ha ha.
So long, puddy.
Aah! Ha ha ha ha!
Meeeeeooooow!
Puddy can fly
about as well
as he can swim.
Oh, no,
not the water again.
Huh?
Aah!
Uhh...
Oh, no.
Gee, puddy,
you think of everything.
Looks like we're gonna
ride the waves
all the way
to San Francisco.
Ahh, San Francisco.
Be careful, tweety.
This bay is rather
crowded.
Whaa!
That puddy tat
just can't stay
out of the water.
Ohh!
Let's land on the famous
fisherman's wharf sign
and breathe
some fresh smells.
We can find pawprints
around the wharf,
but we gotta go into town
to get my passport stamped,
then head over
to the train station.
Well, that takes care
of the United States.
Where to, awooga?
I'm hungry.
How about some--
lunch?
Yikes!
Oh, no, you don't!
[Snarls]
Hmm?
Whaa-ha!
Eeh! Uh...
Talk about your fast food.
Uh-oh.
Hold on, awooga.
It's gonna be
a bumpy ride.
We could just fly,
but what fun
would that be?
Meow!
Come back here!
Whee!
[Trolley bell rings]
Canaries,
the San Francisco tweet.
Next stop: Union square.
Hey! What the--
Ohh! Ohh!
Stop it! Stop it!
You'll never make the turn
if you don't slow down
at the bottom of the hill!
Pull back on the stick,
ya nitwit!
[Groans]
Give me that there
brake throttle!
There's a reason they don't
hire kitty cats
for this job.
Hmm?
Uhh!
Oww!
Oh, now you done caused us
to jump the track,
you furry galoot!
Uhh!
[Whistles]
You take it!
No, you!
No, no, no!
You take it!
No, you!
Ohh!
Aah!
Razzin' frazzin' fog.
I blames you for this.
Whoa!
Gee, I wonder
where we are?
Aah!
Get us down
off of here,
ya itchy feline!
Ohh!
Aah!
Slow up,
ya dang cat!
I think we're back
on market street.
Huh?
"Welcome to
Alcatraz."
That's a closed-up
hoosegow...
Built on an island!
[Bawling]
Ya got us stuck on
this stupid rock,
ya good for nothin'
feline.
Ya no good razzin'
frazzin' kitty cat!
Get back here
and take what for!
Come here, boy!
He must be the cat man
of Alcatraz.
Heh heh heh.
We'd better get goin',
awooga.
Our train will be leaving
the station any minute.
Look! A beautiful
f-1 antique diesel
to commemorate
my global trip.
What a maroon!
Ha ha ha ha ha.
[Groaning]
[Train door opens]
Huh?
Holy smokes!
We've got to highball!
Great horny toads!
I've been railroaded.
I'm 30 seconds
ahead of schedule.
We can afford to pause
and check my odds.
"Check our odds
on tweety's global trip."
Hmm! The odds are
I'll eat that darn canary.
[Screeching tires]
Jeez, this must be
where all pussycats go
on their 3-day weekends.
Hey! Uh--uh--what's
the big attraction?
Catnip samples?
He's somewhere
here in Vegas,
but he won't finish.
No bird can pull it off.
Yeah, what do they
think they're doin'?
Tweety, I don't believe
they want you to win.
Tch, tch.
Just like puddy cats.
* those birdies are lost *
* it's over and done *
* they're callin'
'em frauds *
* they're puttin' the odds
at 100 to 1 *
* it's a walk in the park *
* it's a kick in the pants *
* we're standin' on top and
tweety don't stand a chance *
* he thought he could win *
* you know what I say? *
* they yell congrats,
you're smarter than cats *
* well, baby, no way *
* you're fallin' behind,
so I'll say in advance *
* it's in the bag and tweety
don't stand a chance *
* he's gonna do great *
* he's comin' on home *
* he got past Cairo, London,
Frankfurt, Paris, and Rome *
* he can't be stopped *
* and he's gonna win *
* so place your bet 'cause
tweety bird's headin' *
* I said, headin' on in *
* there ain't no way *
* he's on his way *
* he's going to fail *
* he's gotten those prints *
* he's starting to sweat *
* and you can bet *
* he's going to fail *
* he's almost home *
* he's way behind *
* he's out in front *
* he's in a bind *
huh?
* that's why
we're bettin' the farm *
* 'cause none of you
stand a chance *
excuse me.
Hey!
Pardon. Pardon me.
Ow!
Oh. Shut up!
* he knows the way *
* old tweety's lost *
* he's almost here *
* he'll never get home *
* he got past Cairo, London,
Frankfurt, Paris, and Rome *
* he's given it up *
* he'll keep his cool *
* he'll blow a fuse *
* he's gonna win *
* he's gonna lose *
* and I'll tell you now *
* that none of you
stand a chance *
[doorbell rings]
Waiter: May we help you?
Boy: If you please, sir,
we'd like to see granny.
Granny, we hate
to bother you in here,
but we just got
kicked off the street
for selling flowers
without a permit.
We can't afford
a permit.
There, there. Granny
hasn't forgotten about you.
[Granny whispering]
* I'm tellin' you now
that none of you stand a-- *
hold it!
Granny pledges the bulk
of her winnings
to save a destitute British
children's park.
* I'm tellin' you now that
none of you stand a chance *
[cheering]
Save a park? Like
I need a stronger push.
Ooh!
Oww!
Look, it's them!
All: Tweety!
Get the bird!
[Gasps]
Ohh!
I got your pawprints
right here!
Ooh!
Ooh, tough crowd.
Whoa!
Heh heh.
Huh?
Got ya!
Awooga!
Ooh.
Cat: Hey,
there they are.
[Painful laughing]
Stick with me, hon.
You're good luck.
[Purrs]
Ohh.
Ohh, we gotta scoot.
That last song made us
a whole minute late.
Ah, New York, New York.
Flying by night
through the poconos
put us a whole day ahead,
awooga.
Your internal
sense of time is truly
infallible, tweety,
but can't we enjoy
the sights for once?
Mmm, well, I suppose so.
Look.
There's Times Square.
It looks like
the center
of the universe.
Eh, you might say that.
Awooga, if you
were a hotdog,
what kind of hotdog
would you be?
A plump, tasty,
juicy one...
With lots of mustard.
Ohh!
Whaa!
Oh, drat.
You've sabotaged
my Manhattan
destruction weapon
with an inferior grade
of earth condiment.
Another dissatisfied
customer. Huh?
Hold the onions.
Awooga!
[Growls]
Got ya this time,
ya little--
Jeez, nothin' like gettin'
your nose rubbed in it.
Oh, there's just
gotta be some way
of catchin' that bird.
Huh?
"Stolen royal passport"?
As granny might say,
aha.
Stolen royal passport
still missing!
Here's where I get to be
scintillatingly incandescent
and downright smart, too.
[Laughing maniacally]
Oh...2 canaries,
one concorde ticket.
Just think, tweety...
In an hour and a half
you'll be in London,
finished with your global trip
a full day early.
Yeah, I know.
What's wrong?
It's just that
I'll be there in no time
and down to just
one puddy tat to outwit.
Where's the stretch?
You mean you want more
of a challenge?
That's it, awooga.
Who needs supersonic?
We can ride the jet stream
back to england instead.
After all, we are
a full day ahead.
Whoa. Isn't that
cutting it close...
And risky?
Risk is my middle name.
How hard can it be?
Just look at our success
so far. Are you with me?
What do you think?
Give this concorde ticket
to somebody that
really needs it.
I'm flying home
the old fashioned way.
[Meowing]
Hey, what you got there,
pussycat?
Holy cow!
[Whistle]
Official police business.
Oh!
Hey!
What's goin' on here?
Hmm?
Got ya!
There ya are!
Hmm.
Heh heh.
Heh heh heh.
Sorry, lads,
you'll have to exit.
Time to take off and
all that, you know.
Huh.
Those birds have got
to be someplace aboard
that stupid supersonic plane.
We do have one extra ticket
if you want to come to
London that badly, sir.
I'm flyin' to London!
What the--
so long, puddy.
See ya in London.
Awooga!
Uhh!
Tweety: That's puddy.
All noise and no results.
I don't like the look
of those dark clouds, tweety.
They just mean we'll
have to flap harder,
that's all.
There's nothin'
I can't do. I have...
Both: An infallible
inner sense of time.
Whoa!
TV anchor: For reasons known
only to tweety,
the brave canary
has forgone the prearranged
concorde passage home
and chosen instead to make
this final flight leg
the hard way.
Ha! Rather plucky, what?
TV anchor: Complicating
tweety's trek
is this sudden
unusually late season
Atlantic hurricane.
Oh?
Uhh! Ooh!
Oh, my.
Drat. There goes
my electronic transmitter.
Try to hold on,
awooga.
Whoa!
Oh, my gosh.
Awooga has flown.
Awooga!
Tweety's fin--i say,
tweety's finished, boys.
His signal's lost.
This is it.
* there ain't no way *
* he'll blow a fuse *
* he's going to fail *
* he's gonna lose *
* I'm tellin' you now *
* that tweety
don't stand a chance *
TV anchor: The planet's
next crazy global long shot,
millionaire entrepreneur
Mitch Hansen is rolling
around the world
in a wooden barrel,
starting right this minute.
* it's the chance,
he's gotta take it *
* we say he'll
never make it *
* 'cause no one's ever
done it all the way *
* ride a barrel 'round
the world in 80 days *
both: Just business.
Unh! Unh! Unh!
Awooga!
Oh, my gosh!
This can't be!
I always come out ahead.
Maybe because I always
care about that the most.
Well, there's only one thing
that matters to me now.
* you can win every race
you ever run in *
* you can take home
every prize *
* have a meteoric rise
to the top of the world *
* and when you get there *
* you'll be there
by yourself *
* with just a trophy
on your shelf *
* the best thing
you can win is a friend *
* someone who can guide you *
* be there right beside you *
* hand in hand
until the bitter end *
* the only thing
worth winning *
* is a friend *
* you can fight to get
the gold and silver medals *
* you can smile
and hold them up *
* win the golden victory cup *
* and someday when you're
all alone you'll see *
* that trophies
lose their glow *
* and that's when
you will know *
* the best thing
you can win is a friend *
* when those medals
start to rust *
* and your memories
turn to dust *
* who'll be there
beside you in the end? *
* who cares about the race? *
* who cares
about first place? *
* the only thing
worth winning *
* is a friend *
[sighs]
[Object falling]
[Crash]
Now that's
product placement.
Oh, the eye
of the hurricane.
Why couldn't awooga have
held on till we got here?
Now it's too late.
I'm in the eye, yet I'll
never see my friend again.
How's that for irony?
[Horn blares]
Huh?
[Blares]
Hold that thought!
[Gasps]
Your passport,
it floats.
Oh.
Unh!
Well, there's
your problem!
Uh, thanks for saving
my passport.
Are you always
such a kind, caring
person, awooga?
When I have the time.
[Snarling]
[All meowing]
What do we do now?
Oh, wait about
20 more seconds.
Straight up,
the only way to fly!
Brrr! Come on,
that's got to be
the English coast
up ahead.
Oh, oh!
Hello!
Well, guess there's
nobody--hey!
That's a good
little birdie.
I've been followin'
you all over
the bloomin' planet
just so I could have
your special passport
for my collection.
Got any problem
with that, do ya?
[Gulp]
Ha ha ha!
[Horn blaring]
Hey! Nobody
puts one over on me!
[Police whistle blowing]
[Gasps]
[Meowing]
Here's the culprit.
What, me?
You, tweety,
are under arrest
for stealing
the missing royal passport.
This delay kills
the last chance I had
of making London in time
to win for granny.
Wait! Look!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Ho ho ho ho ho ho!
Hee hee hee hee!
I'll take that.
Hello. What's this?
What's this?
"By special appointment
to tweety and the looney club
by her royal majesty."
Here, remove those cuffs.
Tweety is no thief.
Your papers are genuine,
old boy.
Sorry we ever doubted you.
It was just that cat,
you see.
Heh heh heh heh.
Huh?
Blimey! This belongs to
the Duke of Edinburgh!
[Gasps]
Aah!
You're under arrest
for stealing a missing
royal passport.
Aah!
Take him to
Scotland yard.
[Siren]
Now that it
doesn't matter,
I can tell you--
I think I've lost
my infallible
sense of time.
Oh, tweety.
Mmm.
It would've been the second
royal passport I ever stole.
I should've never put 'em
both in the same pocket
where I keep
my fish and chips.
Went and caused 'em
to stick, it did.
Course, it would've
aided me greatly
to have properly learned
my left from my right, too.
[Bell tolls]
Aw...
I blew it,
awooga.
Oh...it's not
the worst thing
in the world.
I let granny down.
We lost so much time
in that hurricane,
and then on the island,
those wild cats,
that snow storm,
being falsely accused
and arrested...
It was all too much
to control.
Tweety...control
is an illusion.
But I had it made,
awooga.
I was one day ahead
in New York.
[Gasps]
I should have taken
the concorde.
I could've been
a contender.
[Ho-o-onk!]
Holy smoke! You mean
that subtitle was wrong?
Mm-hmm.
Tch, tch, tch.
You just can't get
good help hiring
freelance.
You see,
we picked up a day
crossing
the international
date line here
but then thought
we lost it in
the hurricane here.
But I lost my infallible
inner sense of time
here, too.
What kept me on track
after that?
Tweety, don't you have
someplace to be
right now?
Oh, my gosh!
Oh, no, granny...
'Tisn't easy
admitting defeat.
You should have heard
my sage wisdom
before you made this
foolhardy wager.
[Tweeting]
Can it be?
It is!
Tweety!
What?!
Yay!
Hmph!
This is most
unexpected.
Hmph! Let's see...
France and Italy,
check and check.
So this is your new
friend, eh, tweety?
Birdy! Birdy!
Hold it!
Just a minute!
This document
is incomplete!
There are but 79
feline impressions
in here!
Huh?
Oh, my gosh!
I forgot Sylvester!
Sylvester: Hey,
cut it out!
That tickles!
Pawprint number 80!
Oh...balderdash!
All right,
all right!
Blast it!
You win!
The park and my Nash
hubcaps are saved!
Confidentially,
my sympathy
was, like,
with the bird.
British woman:
I dub thee sir tweety
for helping recover
the stolen royal passport.
Thank you.
I also have an infallible
inner sense of time,
but why spoil it
for him?
[Sobbing]
Captioning made possible by
Warner Bros.
Captioned by the national
captioning institute
--www.Ncicap.Org--