(lively Scottish music)
(man gasps)
- Don't you move.
Now, I'm looking for a man, a traitor, a deserter,
and a wanted criminal, goes by the name
of Alan Breck Stewart.
- I have never heard of any such a man.
- Oh, he's what they call a Jacobite,
a rebel against our true King George, God bless His Majesty.
And, you say to me you never heard of such a man?
- I never did.
- There's a fine reward, dear lad, 100 guineas.
But, since your head seems to be so empty,
perhaps I'll fill it with some shot.
- I swear to God, I never heard of any such a man.
- Well said, Rory lad.
- Huh?
Alan! (Alan laughing)
Alan, you, you misbegotten dog!
(lively Scottish music) (children chattering)
- Well, James.
- You're back.
- I am.
(both laugh) (crowd cheers)
- You rascal.
I know it's not much, but it's all we could gather
for the king in France.
(coins clattering)
- So, when I come through Appin there was talk
of fresh evictions.
Is that true?
- Yes, it's true.
But, I've consulted with the lawyers.
- Oh, it's the lawyers again, now is it?
- We can't fight them with sword and pistol.
- Well, you cannot fight 'em with parchment and pen, huh?
- [James] Will you listen to me?
- I will not. (dog barking)
Colin Campbell is not gonna rest till he's thrown
every last loyal Highlander off this land.
You think a wee, dusty, penny-pinching lawyer
is gonna stop him?
- You don't understand the man.
- Well, he sold himself to the Redcoats 30 years ago.
What's more to understand?
- (laughs) You would never listen to another opinion
not even when you were five years old
when I first took you in.
- Please.
- Colin Campbell's a reasonable man.
- Did you hear that, Maggie?
The Red Fox.
He's called him reasonable.
Just lies, deceit, and treachery.
And, you wanna legalize that?
- I believe you two will be still quarreling
beyond the grave.
- Then you tell him.
- There is no telling him anything nor you.
- Yeah, you stand in Colin Campbell's way, man,
he'll find means to remove you.
- No, it's the new man we're afraid of, Alan,
the London man.
- Alan wouldn't know of him.
- I know something of Mr. William Reid.
- Are you straightaway for France?
- Aye.
- Good.
I've arranged a meeting between you and the Red Fox
at the Bear Inn.
- Twos are four-- (somber flute music)
- Three.
- [Children] Three twos are six.
- [Man] Four.
- [Children] Four twos are eight.
- [Man] Five.
- Five twos are 10. - Good luck, David.
- [Man] Six.
- [Children] Six.
- Good morning, sir.
- What?
Ah, good morning.
- I've come to say farewell.
- Are you sorry to leave Essendean?
- Oh, it's a good place, indeed, sir.
But, then I've never been anywhere else.
- (laughs) True enough.
Well then, to come straight to it,
when your mother was gone and your poor father
began to sicken for his end,
he gave me in charge, a certain letter.
He said it was your inheritance.
- Inheritance?
- "So, soon as I'm gone," he said,
"give my boy this letter and start him off
"to the house of Shaws by Cramond."
- May I see it, Mr. Campbell?
- Eh what?
Oh, of course.
Your father was a gentleman, of course, no doubt of that
and a learned man, too good for a country schoolmaster.
He never talked about his past, Davie,
but your mother did once.
She hinted at some great quarrel in the family.
"At least my boy is safe," she said.
"God forbid he should ever see the House of Shaws."
I'm afraid for you, Davie.
Stay here and keep the school as your father did.
- I'll be all right, sir, I swear.
- Well, I didn't think I'd persuade you.
You'll be wanting to pay your respects.
(gentle violin music)
(church bells ringing)
(somber music)
(birds chirping)
(men chattering)
- [Marie] Oh, haven't seen you in a long time.
- Marie.
- There's your ale.
- Steady, Alan.
- [Alan] I thought this meeting would be friendly.
Guns are so unnecessary.
(door slams)
- Ah, you're no ordinary bone-headed
- You're no ordinary traitor, Colin.
Judas himself could've taken a lesson from you.
- You always did have wit.
- Aye.
- Take a drink.
You know, I never could understand it.
How a clever man like you could throw his life away
on such a cause.
- I would never expect a Campbell to understand
the notion of loyalty.
- Think yourself.
What's your life now?
You're in exile, a fugitive, a fallen man
drowning in his own poverty.
- Have I had a choice?
- [Colin] Join us.
Come over to King George and the English cause.
- You know, somehow poverty
seems to strengthen my resolve, Colin.
(laughs)
- It hardly improves the condition of your people, Alan.
- Aye. - You know our policy
is to drive them off the land.
- Oh, is the policy to burn them off the land?
Is the policy to pluck the toys
from the hands of our children?
- Say yes to me and I'll protect them, all of them.
- Oh, you have that power?
- I am the King's Factor.
Of course I have the power.
(fire crackling)
- You'll swear to it?
All right, I have the dram.
Slunger.
- Slunger, Alan.
(dramatic music)
(furniture clattering)
(window shattering) (dog barking)
- He's escaped.
- This may go hard for you.
- The devil if I'll be questioned
by any jumped up Englishman.
I answer to no one but the King himself.
One word from me and you'll be packing your wee bag,
skulking back to where you came from.
Wherever that may be.
- An idle threat?
- No, I take it very seriously.
Very seriously, indeed.
(somber flute music)
(birds cawing)
(loud knocking)
(window clacking)
- It's loaded.
- I have a letter for Mr. Ebenezer Balfour of Shaws.
- Who's it from?
- That's no concern of yours.
Is he here?
- Put it down on the doorstep and be off with you.
- It's a letter of introduction.
- A what?
- A letter of introduction.
- Who are you?
- My name is David Balfour.
- Is your father dead?
Oh, aye, he'll be dead no doubt.
Well, man, I'll let you in.
You hungry?
(chuckles)
You can eat that bit of porridge.
- [David] Is that not your own meal?
- You can have it.
Now, let's see the letter.
- I told you before, the letter's for Mr. Balfour.
- Who do you think I am?
Take me for a servant?
I keep none.
Give me Alexander's letter.
- You know my father's name?
- It would be strange if I did not since he was my brother.
Boy, I'm your born uncle, Davie, my man.
So, just give us the letter and sit there
and eat your porridge.
Do you know what's in it?
- Uh, you can see for yourself, sir,
the seal's not been broken.
- But, what brought you here?
- To deliver the letter.
- Aye, but you'd have had some hopes no doubt.
- I confess, sir, that when I was told I had kin folk,
well-to-do, I did indulge the hope,
that they would help me in my life.
- No doubt, no doubt.
- But, I look for no favors.
I'm no beggar.
- You have the air of one.
- Uh, well, poor as I appear, sir,
I have friends who would gladly help me.
- Don't fly up in the air at me.
We'll agree fine yet.
Well, if you're done with that porridge,
I'll just take a bit of it myself.
Your father long dead?
- Three weeks.
- He was a secret man, Alexander,
a secret, silent man.
Did he ever say anything about me?
- I never even knew he had a brother.
- Oh, dear me, dear me.
We'll agree fine yet.
I'm glad I let you in.
(mysterious music)
You stay here awhile.
I've some business to attend to.
(moving to ominous music)
(book thudding)
(hammer thudding)
(beam clattering)
You a reader, Davie? (thunder rumbling)
- A great reader, sir.
- I meant to ask you before.
Your mother?
- She died two years ago.
Was my father very quick at his learning, Uncle?
- Alexander?
No, no, I was the clever one.
Why do you ask?
- Well, this book's inscribed to you.
To my brother Ebenezer on his fifth birthday.
- What's to that?
- Oh, you were the elder were you not?
- Of course.
- Well, that's no child's writing.
(mysterious music)
- It's our father's hand.
I remember now how Alexander asked our father
to inscribe the book.
Ah.
One excellent work of religion.
You could do worse than study it, Davie.
(tense lively music) (sword clattering)
- Alan Breck has walked into our trap, sir.
(ominous music)
(Alan sniffs)
(horses snorting)
(birds chirping)
(twig snapping)
(gun firing) - Ah, getting away!
(man shouting)
- [Man] Fire at will!
(dramatic music)
(horse hooves clomping)
(man laughs)
- Aye.
He left this for you, sir.
(laughs)
- Will you stop laughing?
Mr. Reid, John MacKenzie's my man.
If there's a reprimand to be given, I'll give it.
(birds chirping)
To Colin Campbell, the Red Fox and Mr. William Reid
of no man knows where.
King James the Sixth of Scotland and First of England
whose name of Stewart I have the honor to bear
said this of smoking tobacco.
A custom loathsome to the eye, hateful to the nose,
and harmful to the brain.
(both laughing)
He always had a pretty wit did Alan Breck.
Ah, you foolish wee man.
It was that stinking pipe of yours lost us the game.
(horse snorting)
(thunder cracking)
- Do you never take anything other than porridge, Uncle?
- No, no, never.
Davie, I've been thinking, and...
(thunder cracking)
There's some amount of money that I promised,
or half promised to you before you were born,
promised your father that is all,
nothing legal, you understand.
(thunder cracking)
I kept that bit of money separate.
It was a great expense, but a promise is a promise.
Stay back.
(thunder cracking)
Sit down, just sit you down, Davie boy.
(lock clattering)
(thunder cracking) (wind whistling)
Well, by careful husbandry
that bit of money has now grown
to be a matter of just exactly,
just precisely 60 guineas.
- 60 guineas?
- It's an important sum of money.
(coins clanking)
(thunder cracking)
Count it.
(wind whistling)
(thunder cracking)
There's more.
- More, sir?
- Much more.
We're the last of the Balfours of Shaws you and I, Davie.
There's the matter of the estate.
It's the question of how affairs will be settled
after I am gone and what provision must be made
for you now.
It's a complicated business, Davie.
We're talking about considerable, not to say,
extensive land and property.
And, the relevant papers
I keep in a chest at the top of the tower.
Will you fetch it for me?
- Of course, Uncle.
(ominous music)
(thunder cracking)
(stairs creaking)
(stairs cracking)
(Davie shouts)
(Davie grunting)
Uncle!
Help!
Oh my God.
Uncle!
Help!
(grunts)
(thunder cracking)
Uncle!
(screams)
(Davie thuds)
(ominous music)
(wind whistles)
(door clattering)
(footsteps clomping)
- Oh my God!
Davie!
You're back.
Why man, you're hurt.
Sit down, sit down.
I'll get you a cordial.
Whatever happened?
- Uh, the stairs.
- You had a fall?
- Yeah, uh, no, uh,
they gave way under me.
- The whole stairs?
Dear me, dear me. - Yeah.
- Let's see.
(Davie sighs)
No harm done.
- I was lucky to save my life.
(panting)
(ominous music)
- Tomorrow morning we'll walk over to Queensferry.
My lawyer, Rankeillor, he keeps a copy of every document.
And, then we'll maybe stop at the inn on the way
to see Captain Hoseason of the Breck covenant.
(lively flute music)
Captain Hoseason?
- Mr. Balfour.
- This is an unexpected pleasure, sir.
- Ah, well, I was passing and I remembered
that there are papers to be signed.
- May I present my second officer, Mr. Riach?
- Proud to know you, Mr. Balfour.
(birds chirping)
- This is my brother's son, David Balfour,
the heir to Shaws.
- Captain.
- [Captain] It's an honor indeed, Mr. Balfour.
- David will order meat and drink for us,
porridge and a mug of ale for me,
but whatever you fancy for yourself,
don't mind the expense.
- Thank you, Uncle.
Gentlemen.
- He's a pleasant young man, your nephew.
- He's a troublesome lad.
I'd like to be rid of him.
(patrons chattering)
- Are you kin to Ebenezer?
- Uh, yes, yes, I'm his brother's son.
- Mr. Alexander's son?
- Yes, yes, that's right.
- You must've been no more than a small baby
when he died.
- Uh, my father died three weeks ago, sir.
- (laughs) There's a grand story
against Ebenezer proved false, more's the pity.
- I don't understand you.
What story?
- That Ebenezer killed his brother.
- (laughs) No, no he did not, no.
Why would Ebenezer kill his own brother?
- For the estate, of course.
(ominous music) Here is a mystery.
If Ebenezer didn't kill his brother,
how come he's Laird of Shaws?
- Was Alexander the first-born son?
Was he?
- [Landlord] Of course.
- Do you know a lawyer by the name of Rankeillor, sir?
- I know him well.
- Could you direct me to his house, please?
(Davie grunts) (Riach grunts)
- Right.
Right, heave, push.
- [Driver] Yeah, here.
(wagon clattering)
(dark music)
(lamp squeaking)
(rat squeaking)
(footsteps clacking)
- Don't worry, lad.
The world's not ended.
Here, have a sip of this.
(footsteps clacking)
He has a high fever.
I want him taken out of this hull
and put in the forecastle.
- Well, what you want, Mr. Riach is of concern
to nobody but yourself.
- Look, I'm paid, and none too much either,
to be second officer of this old tub.
I'm paid for nothing more.
- Put him where you please.
- Right, lad.
Up you go.
Come on you get, lad.
(both grunting)
Come on lad, you're going up top.
- [Ransome] No, Mr. Shuan.
- [Shuan] Come here!
- It wasn't me. - You little thief!
Man!
I'll take the hide off you this time!
- (grunts) No, no, no, no, no (screams).
(Shuan grunts)
- For God sake, man.
- No, please!
Please, no!
Please!
Please no!
- Smartly.
- [David] No, no, sir, I beg you!
- There we go you now.
Aye, aye.
You know, it's a curious thing.
Mr. Shuan, sober, is a quiet, kindly sort of a fellow
and, the only true sailor on this old cursed ship.
You see Mr. Shuan drunk, he's a raging devil.
- You know I don't belong here.
- (chuckles) Now, me, I'm the exact opposite.
When I'm sober, I'm a sullen kind of man.
- I have friends who would pay you handsomely
if you helped me.
- You see, when I'm drunk, which most of the time I am,
I'm an angel.
- You let me write one line
to the Minister Campbell of Essean...
- If you please, Mr, Riach.
- Aye, Captain.
(ship creaking)
- No.
No.
I beg you.
No (cries).
(dramatic music) (horse hooves clomping)
- He was spotted two hours ago.
I think he must head either through Craighsheil or Draemore.
- Then split up.
You go to Craighsheil, send your ensign to Draemore.
I assume you have informants in both places.
- Uh, not that I know of.
- I suppose we'll have to rely on mine.
- Ewan of Appin.
- No, Thomas Clousten's my name.
- Aye, what was it last time?
Robert, gimme those guineas, lad, gimme the guineas.
- Your passage is arranged and paid for.
A French ship, the Bonaventure.
- Aye, I know her.
Captain Perrault is still aboard?
- On the night of the 4th she'll lie to,
just off the coast.
There's a bed for you at the inn at Craighsheil.
Wait there, friends will come for you.
And, be careful.
- Ah, lad.
- Ah, things have changed, Alan.
You don't find the same loyalty in the people
and there's a new man sent from London.
- Aye, that pipe-smoking lackey, Mr. William Reid.
- [Ewan] I've yet to encounter the man.
- [Alan] Well, you'll catch more than a whiff.
- [Ewan] I hope to soon.
I've taken a job as a servant in his own kitchens.
- [Alan] That's a dangerous game, Ewan.
- [Ewan] By all accounts, he's a man to be reckoned with.
(dramatic music)
- Food for the prisoner?
Good lad.
Keep him fit and strong now so he'll fetch a good price
and I'll see to it that you get your fair share.
- [David] You know where we're bound?
- Of course I do.
- [David] Well?
- South Carolina.
Old Heasy-Oasey says he'll get 60 guineas for you.
- What do you mean?
- I seen him do it too.
At the slave auctions, bidding up the price.
- They're gonna sell me into slavery?
- Well, Old Heasy-Oasey don't take no passengers
aboard his brig.
- Listen, listen, listen, listen.
You help me get away and I will set you up for life.
- Put me to a trade more like.
I know a trick or two worth more than any trade.
- For the love of God, man, do you not want to escape
Mr. Shuan's beatings.
- Lemme see him try it.
I stole that, I did.
I'll dare him to touch me.
I'll kill him.
He ain't the first.
(ominous music)
No, Mr. Shaun, no, (groans)
no (screams)!
(ship creaking)
- David Balfour, I want you to serve on the roundhouse.
You and Ransome are to exchange places.
(chains clanking)
(somber music)
- Drunken swine!
Do you know what you've done?
You've murdered the boy.
Mr. Riach, this must never be known.
The boy went overboard.
That's what the story is.
- You should've interfered long ago.
Gimme that.
- I'll kill you for that!
(men grunting)
- [Riach] Come on, man, I'll skin you alive,
you drunken slob!
- [Hoseason] Take onto himself the soul
of our dear brother here departed.
We, therefore, commit his body to the deep
to be turned into corruption, looking for the resurrection
of the body when the sea shall give up her dead.
(water splashing)
(gentle music)
- [Man] Can you see the French ship?
- There, there.
There she is now.
Hey Capitaine.
Capitaine Perrault.
- That's French.
- Why?
- Capitaine Perrault.
Hey Capitaine.
- Lower the ladder.
- Bless you, lads.
See, you safe home now.
(groaning)
There's a mistake here.
You've not the look of a Frenchman.
- Unlike you, sir.
You have a French soldier's coat upon your back
and a Scotch tongue in your head.
Step aboard, sir.
- Well, an invitation so prettily put
cannot be well refused.
I take it you're no Jacobites.
- I take it you are.
As to my causes, let me tell you where I stand.
I am for the prosperity of myself and my crew
and against everything else.
- You're a practical man.
- I hope so.
- I've an uncommon hunger and thirst.
(sword clacking)
- There's a remedy for that sir,
if you'll step into the roundhouse.
- Yes, I was bound for France.
There was a French ship cruising hereabouts
to pick me up but she must've give me the go by
in the fog.
So, if you can set me ashore to where I was going,
I have the means to reward you highly for your trouble.
- In France?
Oh no, sir, that I cannot do, but where you come from,
we might talk of that.
Davie, run out to the galley and fetch some meat
for the gentleman.
Lively now.
- Better off where he is.
He won't be able to swing his sword.
- True, but he'll be hard to come at.
- Half of it and I'm your man.
- I told you, not one penny of that belongs to me.
Belongs to another.
Now, I'd be a fool not to spend some of it
so that the rest might come safe.
But, sir, I'd be a dog indeed
to spend that much on my safety.
- 100 guineas, that's my price.
- 50.
- Done.
And, here's my hand on it.
And, we'll alter course at once.
I'll see to it.
- Thank you, lad.
- So, you're a Jacobite.
- Aye.
And, you by your long face should be for King George.
- Betwixt and between.
- Mr. Betwixt and Between, this bottle of yours is dry.
I'm paying 50 guineas for the cruise.
Be a hard thing to begrudge me a dram.
- I'll go and ask the captain for the key.
- You have your pistol, Captain.
- He has two.
The other firearms are locked up in the roundhouse.
- Here's our chance to get the firearms.
- Um, the gentleman's seeking a drink, Captain,
and the bottle's dry.
Would you give me the key?
- Davie, my man, that wild Highlander
is a danger to the ship besides being a rank enemy
to King George, God save him.
- Aye, we've swords and cutlasses enough
but the firearms are in the roundhouse under his nose.
- If I or Mr. Riach was to go in to get them,
he might start thinking.
- [Riach] But, a lad like you, Davie,
you could snap up a pistol or two without remark.
- Do it cleverly and I'll bear it in mind
when we come to South Carolina.
Here's the bit of money that you had on you.
And, with my apologies, Davie.
- I had 60 guineas on me.
- Davie, your uncle took that.
And, see here, that Jacobite has a belt full of gold.
And, I give you my word, you shall have your fingers in it.
(ominous music)
(keys clanking)
- Do you want to be killed?
- Why?
Is that how the wind sets?
- They're all murderers here.
It's a ship full of them.
Now, they've already murdered a boy,
and you, Mr. Jacobite, are next.
- Well, they haven't got me yet.
Will you stand with me?
- I'm no murderer.
I'm no thief.
I will.
- Good.
What's your name, lad?
- My name is David Balfour of Shaws.
- Of Shaws, indeed.
- My name is Stewart, Alan Breck they call me.
(ominous music)
They've three ways to come at us here, Davie.
These windows, that skylight, and the door.
- I'll shut the door.
- Not so.
I've but one face and so long as that door is open
and my face is to it, I have my enemies in front of me.
That's where I prefer to find them.
Can you use a sword?
- I never have.
- Cutlass then?
- No.
- A dirk?
- Could you contrive to pull a trigger?
I'll prime and load these pistols for you.
- Of course I can.
My father used to take me hunting rabbits.
- [Alan] Well, thanks be to God for that.
- But, I'm not very good shot.
- Aye, but you'll admit to it.
Bravely said.
Not many a soldier would not dare to say that.
Follow me close.
It is my part to keep this door
and look for the main battle.
Stay with the bed, you guard that window
and that skylight.
- I, too, have but one face, Mr. Stewart, I can't--
- [Alan] Ah, but you've ears on either side of it.
- They have to break the glass.
- There you go.
You've some rudiments of sense.
(men shouting) (swords clattering)
- Come on, lads, come on.
Here!
It's equal shares, now lads.
Come on!
(mumbles) Come with me!
Who's with me?
- Steady, Davie.
The crew's coming.
- [Man] (mumbles) for every man.
(all shouting) (swords clanking)
(men grunting)
(men shouting)
(gun firing)
(man screaming)
(punches thudding) (men grunting)
(man shouting)
(Alan grunting)
- [Alan] Arms, Davie.
(dramatic music)
(glass shattering)
(man shouting)
(gun firing)
(men grunting)
(swords clanking) (men grunting)
(Alan panting)
Come to my arms, Davie.
I love you like a brother.
And, I'm a no bonny fighter.
(panting)
(somber music)
(water splashing)
- We'll have to parlez.
There's nothing else for it.
- You know, I have these buttons
from my father, Duncan Stewart.
He died when I was a boy.
He was the greatest sword in the Highlands.
I want you to take that as a keepsake
for what you done.
(gentle flute music)
And, wherever you go, you show that
and my friends will come round you.
- Ahoy the roundhouse.
Ahoy, roundhouse.
Will you parlez?
- I tell you what I'll do.
I'll offer you an exchange.
That against two buckets of water.
And, if he's alive, I'll speak to your captain.
- Oh, he's alive all right.
(grunts)
- That's more than he deserves.
(water splashing)
Would you lend a hand, David?
- Ahoy, the roundhouse.
(water splashing)
Ahoy, the roundhouse.
You've made a sore hatch of my brig, sir.
- That's none of my choosing.
I'll give you 30 guineas
to set me on dry shore at Ardnamurhcan.
- I haven't men enough to work this ship.
And, my navigator, Mr. Shuan has had your sword
through his vitals.
50!
- 30!
- If I hadn't lost so much money on this plagiary cruise,
I'd see you at the rope's end.
Batten down the hatches.
There's a storm coming.
- You know, I trust that captain as I would a snake
in the grass.
(David laughs)
You see that?
That's gold.
Will you keep it for me, till we're safe ashore?
- If you want.
- That's a trust I'm putting to you, man.
- I told you before, I'm no thief.
- That's not what I mean.
You heard of tax?
My people pay it and heavily too to your King George.
But, they're through, David.
They've toiled and bled for many a year
and they scrape up a second tax.
That's it.
That's for the true king of this country.
He's just over the water there for awhile in France.
- They pay tax to two kings?
- Aye, and you're looking at the man that carries it.
(thunder rumbling)
- Well, I'll be honest, I am for King George, I am.
But, I call that noble.
- Noble.
Their hearts are staunch, David.
- I'll look after your gold as if it were my own.
- Sir, I believe you will.
But, let me tell you something more.
You see, when Bonny Prince Charlie was
there was a price put of 30,000 pounds for his head.
Not one man, woman, or child in all the Highlands
ever betrayed him.
And, you think on that, Mr. Betwixt and Between.
(waves crashing)
(men shouting)
(water splashing)
- Alan!
(water splashing) (men shouting)
Alan!
- Two points to starboard!
Starboard, starboard!
- Aye.
Captain, she can't take it. - Rock port side!
(ship rumbling) (men shouting)
(Captain shouting) (dramatic music)
- Alan!
Alan!
- [Alan] David!
- [David] Alan!
(Alan grunting)
- David!
David!
(David grunting)
(wave splashing)
- [Riach] Gimme your hand.
Come on.
- [Captain] Mr. Riach.
(dramatic music)
- David!
(men shouting)
David!
- On your oars, store that.
Get out the boats.
(David grunting)
(ship cracking)
(waves splashing)
- David!
David!
- Breck!
The powder's dry.
Get moving.
Move.
Go on.
Robbie.
Search him.
Get the money.
- There's nothing.
- It's with the boy.
- Then you've killed him.
- [Riach] Aye, with a weight like that round him,
he'll drown for sure.
- (laughing) Sunk like a stone.
(punches thudding) (men grunting)
(lively flute music)
(gun firing)
(birds chirping) (gentle music)
(waves splashing)
(uplifting music)
(somber rhythmic music)
- [Alan] Ewan?
- [Soldier] Go on after him.
Go on.
Bring him down.
(gun firing)
(horse whinnying) (Ewan grunting)
- [Soldier] After him.
Dismount.
After him.
Don't let him escape.
He's in the back of there.
Go on.
- [Ewan] Alan?
(Alan grunting)
- [Alan] Let's get you away from here.
- [Ewan] Good, Alan.
- To the left.
Guards up.
- There.
We've winged him anyway.
Half dead by the look of it.
But, be alert, men.
These Highlanders are full of tricks.
(birds squawking)
- You're a day behind him.
- He's alive?
- He had that appearance about him.
- Well, which direction did he take?
- Westward.
Towards his own place.
- And, what place would that be?
- Well, I'll tell you since you bear his token.
Acharn, ah
(somber music)
- [Alan] We'll be safe here.
(Ewan groans)
- Alan, listen--
- Hush now.
- Your man, Reid.
- You're in no case to talk.
- There's a plot, something deep.
A killing, Alan.
(groans)
- [Alan] Who?
- I have no name, but they'll lay the blame
on James of the Glen.
- Easy, now, easy, lad.
- The 14th day of May.
The woods of Lettermore.
(groans)
- [Alan] Easy now.
Rest you here now, I'll fetch you a drink.
- You have a dram with you?
- [Alan] Water.
- Water.
- [Alan] Ewan, Ewan.
(somber bagpipe music)
God rest your brave soul.
- Acharn?
You'd go south by east through the woods of Lettermore.
But, stay.
I take that road myself.
I'll walk with you.
If you don't object to bear company with a blind man.
- Sir, I would be honored.
- Your speech tells me you're a stranger,
a Lowlander perhaps.
- Perhaps.
- Aye, that's a young man's voice.
A gentleman's voice.
- Perhaps.
- These are all my eyes, young master.
May I know the look of you?
- Go on.
- Would you take my stick?
Aye, you have the features of a true gentleman.
(gentle flute music)
- [Men] Aye.
Aye.
(cow mooing) (calf bleating)
- Is every Lowland man as silent as yourself, young master?
(men chattering)
- I was just observing these people here.
They don't look like Highlanders at all.
There's no tartan, no kilts on any of them.
- Did you not know that King George
has put a legal ban upon the Highland dress?
Aye, no tartan, no kilt,
no bagpipes neither.
That's to break the spirit of the clans.
(footsteps thudding)
- [Soldier] Left wheel.
- [Forbes] I'm afraid he's disappeared, sir.
- [William] Disappeared?
- [Soldier] Hold your (mumbles).
- Men don't disappear, Captain Forbes.
- [Forbes] Evidently he had an accomplice.
They didn't leave any tracks.
- How badly was he wounded?
- Judging from the blood, mortally.
- [Soldier] Pick up those (mumbles), pick 'em up!
- Let's hope so.
Do you know who he was?
- A serving man in your kitchen?
- He was a spy.
- [Soldier] Control, keep up the pace.
- He used the name Clousen, but his true name
is Ewan of Appin.
(birds chirping)
- Is that the song of a burn I hear?
- Aye, it is.
- Would you be a Christian and fetch me
a sip of water, young master?
- Aye, aye, of course.
(cup clattering)
(cane thudding)
(David shouting)
(water splashing)
(men grunting)
(David laughing)
(sheep bleating) (gentle music)
(water splashing) (dog barking)
- [Flora] Alan Breck.
- Well, Flora.
- You can stop there.
I don't know how you dare to show your face.
- There's much I dare.
You've not forgotten surely.
- I've not forgotten, nor forgiven, Alan.
What do you want?
- Just a bed for the night, if you have one.
(sheep bleating)
- [Flora] I do not, not for you.
- And, where is Donald?
- Donald is in London.
- Why London?
- He has a petition to King George
to restore his estate.
- The King is in France, Flora.
- We've scrimped and starved long enough.
We have a bairn.
- I can believe a wee pluck of a man like Donald
would bend his knee to King George.
But, not you, Flora, just not you.
- I'd have died for you Alan Breck.
Such a love I had.
But, your king over the water whistled for you
and you were gone.
- My king?
Your king, your king.
And, you sheltered his son, Prince Charlie himself
in your own father's house.
- They burnt my father's house, they drove our people
off the land.
I had no man to turn to save Donald.
A poor wee pluck of a man you called him.
Well, he stood by me.
He wed me.
And, it cost him dear.
You left me naked, Alan, and that's the truth of it.
(cries)
(dramatic music) (horse hooves clomping)
(horse whinnying)
- Oh, you're not ready, man.
It's 9:00.
We've a long ride to Acharn.
Do you want to evict James The Glen or not?
- I'm perfectly ready.
- I see you like your comforts, Mr. Reid.
- Well, any fool can be uncomfortable.
(birds chirping) (gentle flute music)
(ominous music)
(horse hooves clacking)
(rifle clacking)
(horse hooves clomping)
- [David] Good day, sirs.
Good day to you both.
I'm bound for Acharn.
Can you tell me, is this the right road?
- [Colin] These are the roads of Lettermore, lad.
- What do you want in Acharn?
- A man who lives there.
- And, who are you?
- I'm an honest subject of King George, sir.
- Very well said, but if I might be so bold,
why is such an honest man so far from his own country?
(guns firing) (horse whinnying)
(dramatic music)
- Sir.
(Colin coughing)
(rifle thudding)
For God sake, Mr. Reid.
Don't go!
- He's been shot.
This boy's an accomplice.
- No I'm not.
- He was put here to keep us talking.
(dramatic music)
Get after him.
- Sergeants, after him.
(men shouting)
- [Alan] David.
Come away, come away.
Go on, go, go!
(guns firing)
(men shouting)
(panting)
They're not done.
They'll lay this claim at James's door.
They'll be making for Acharn.
(David panting)
What the devil were you doing in the woods of Lettermore?
- Following you.
- Well, come away, man.
- You entrusted something to me which I felt
it was my duty to return to you.
And, there it is.
I thank you for getting me away but now we part.
- I'll hardly part from you, Davie.
- There's a man lies dead down there.
And, the weapon that slew him is there, in your hand.
- So, you think I killed him?
- Goodbye, Mr. Stewart.
I doubt that we shall ever meet again.
- David, where the devil do you think you're going?
- [David] Home!
- Home?
Man, you're not gonna make five mile before they catch you.
- That's my affair.
- At least hear my defense.
- Defense?
What defense, what defense?
I liked you very, very well,
but your ways are not mine and they are not God's.
(somber music)
(gentle flute music)
(ominous music)
- [Soldier] Halt or we shoot.
Come on you.
- Now that we've got you, let's have your name.
- Breck, Alan Breck!
Would you have the goodness to order your men
to lay down their arms, Captain?
- Do it.
- Ground your arms.
- And, your sword.
If you please.
(sword clanking)
Would you walk with me, sir?
- You'd be well-advised to shoot me now, Mr. Stewart.
- What, shoot a man in cold blood?
Is that what the English do?
It's not the Highland way, Mr. Reid.
- [William] Fatal flaw
in the Highland character, Mr. Stewart.
- (chuckles) Well, perhaps I should shoot you.
(rifle clicking)
But, it's not loaded.
(adventurous music)
As you see.
- [David] Why don't we keep the horses?
- Because we're safer on foot.
- You are the boldest peacock of a man
I've ever come across.
And, it seems I have to thank you once again.
But, I can't change my opinion.
You killed a man in cold blood.
- [Alan] You know who that man was?
- It was a man, an innocent man.
- He was your King's Factor.
- That's your defense?
- Now, I tell you, Mr. Balfour of Shaws as a friend,
if I were about to kill Campbell of Glenure,
it would not be in Stewart's country to bring trouble
on my own people.
- What trouble?
- I told you William Reid will lay this murder
at the door of my kinsmen.
He'll hang 'em if he can.
He'll throw his people off the land.
- With no proof.
- He's a Stewart.
Can you understand that?
That's the proof.
- Well, how did you come by that gun then?
- The murderer struck me a blow with it.
He ran off before I could see his face.
Here, you can see for yourself of the blow there.
- Aye, well you've taken a knock certainly.
- Ah, what would you have me do, swear upon the holy cross?
I'll do it.
(stream gurgling)
- No, I believe you and I thank God for it now.
- Stop right there.
Do you know you never let me speak my defense
before condemning me.
(somber music)
- I was here in our cairn when the murder was done.
I've a score of my people to swear to it.
- Aye, your people, James,
Stewarts of Appin.
This is a Campbell that's been killed.
- Listen to him, James.
- You will be tried at Fort William.
There'll be 15 Campbells in the jury box
and the biggest Campbell of them all
the Duke of Argyle on the bench.
- Oh, for God sake. - Now, you'll take
to the heather with me away to France.
- No.
- It's best, James.
- [James] Hold your tongue, woman.
- How many times must I tell ya?
This is a plot by Reid.
Now, he won't be thwarted.
He'll see you hanged.
- Redcoats.
- Will you run?
- No.
- Then we fight.
(dramatic music)
- [James] This is madness, Alan.
- [Alan] Of your making.
- [James] You're not the chieftain here, curse you.
- It'll give you time, man.
- [James] For what?
- To din some sense into that stubborn old head of yours.
- [Alan] Put it in here, lads.
- Halt!
Fix bayonets!
- Fix bayonets!
(bayonets clanking)
Fixed!
- Forward march!
(drumming music)
(dog barking)
(horse hooves clomping)
- [Soldier] They've gone.
- [Alan] Not quite!
(dogs barking)
- This is folly.
Lay down your arms.
- You'd best lay down your own.
You'd be wise to.
(crowd cheering) (dramatic music)
- [James] They'll be back, Alan, with more soldiers.
(crowd cheering)
(dogs barking)
(crowd cheering) (bagpipe music)
(rooster crowing)
(birds cackling)
(cow mooing)
(fife and drum music)
(horse hooves clomping)
- Alan, Alan!
- I know.
It's death to stay.
- You and your friends slip away now
while you have the chance.
- We'll hang together, James.
- For once in your life, Alan Breck,
you'll listen to me.
For the sake of my people, I'll give myself over.
- Why do you persist?
- Listen to me!
I have only one hope for my life and that's you.
Find the one who did the murder.
If any man in Scotland can do it, you can.
Find him.
Produce him to the court with proof of the plot.
And, no Campbell jury can ever hang me.
(horse snorting) (horse hooves clomping)
I am James Stewart of the Glen.
- Come on, you (mumbles)! (dramatic music)
(people shouting) (baby crying)
- For the love of God, Mr. Reid.
- We must cleanse the Highlands, Captain Forbes.
That's my duty and it's your duty.
(men shouting)
- You see King George's men at their work?
Where do you stand now,
Mr. Betwixt and Between?
(fire crackling)
- Just find the real murderer and drag him into court.
That doesn't sound simple to me at all.
Unless you have some sort of clue.
- Well, I'd be something of a fool
to set about this business if I'd not.
For all that is a dangerous game
and you're not obliged to play.
- Do I have a choice?
- You do, you've a lot.
They haven't your name and our friends
will see you safe into the Lowlands.
- James of the Glen is as innocent of murder
as I am myself.
As a gentleman, I could say as an honest subject
of King George,
but I say as a gentleman,
it is my duty to see justice done if I can.
- Well, that's well said, lad.
My hand's on that.
(gentle flute music)
You'll hold this gold for me again then.
- If you like.
Why?
- I don't know.
I see you're honest, but I think you're the luck.
- Luck?
- Aye, the luck.
- Since I've left Essendean I've been assaulted,
I've been kidnapped, my uncle tried to murder me.
I've been attacked by a blind man
and I've been chased and harried half out of my wits.
- That's exactly my meaning.
It's a bloody miracle you're alive, man.
Now, fall in and step to.
(water splashing)
- Where are we going?
- Fort William.
- But, that's a garrison town.
It's fully of Redcoats.
- Aye, and it's the last place in Scotland
they'll be thinking to look for us.
(mysterious music)
- I say, Tom, come on.
- [Tom] That's a rather fine pistol.
- Not half as fine as the tavern I've got my eye on.
Come on.
- [Woman] Well give him something, Harriet.
- [Harriet] And, here you are now
and mind you buy food. - Ah, thank you, dear.
(bell ringing)
- It's an odd made piece, Alan.
Very odd.
I've seen nothing like it before.
(bird chirping)
Are you selling it?
- For shame, Angus.
And, you an elder of the church.
- I'll take a bible oath--
- I've no time! (glass clattering)
- Now, you tell me the name of the man you made it for.
- I never knew his name.
He would've been a fool to give it
and I would've been a greater fool to ask it.
- I'm gonna use that
to blow out that canny brain of yours.
- Well, I can give you his clan.
- Give me the name.
- Well, it was a Campbell killed--
- A MacDonald?
- Yes, a MacDonald he was.
- Mr. Reid. (ominous music)
- Sir, I know where Alan Breck Stewart is.
- No, sir, I've not seen a living soul all morning.
- Trade bad, is it?
- Terrible bad, sir.
- As bad as your memory.
(bag thudding)
(dramatic music)
- Could I crave one favor of you, Davie?
- [David] Of course.
- Well, let's just say the less you know
you notice here now, the better for me.
Duncan MacDonald is no open-mined man.
He's no time for Lowlanders and he hates King George
worse than poison.
I hope I don't offend you.
- [David] Certainly not.
(loud knocking)
- Still he was once the power here, you see?
He was the clan chief.
Just not now.
Good evening to you, miss.
- Sir.
- My name is Alan Breck Stewart.
- I know the name.
- Aye, is the Earl at home?
- He is.
- Might I crave 10 minutes conversation with him?
- Come in sir, sirs.
A moment if you please, Mr. Stewart.
(soft knocking)
- That man had five sons and he lost them all.
And, that be the granddaughter, Mary.
One bonny lassie.
- Oh, she's all right.
- You don't agree?
- Well, I've hardly had time to form an opinion.
- Well, how much time do you need?
A glance is enough I always say
if a lad likes the look of a lass
and a lass likes the look of a lad.
(door clattering)
- You may go in now, Mr. Stewart.
- [Alan] Thank you.
- Will you take some refreshment, sir?
- Uh, no, no thank you.
(gentle music)
- So, you're not accustomed to Highland manners.
It's a great tradition here to offer hospitality
to a stranger and a great offense for a
- Oh, I apologize, Miss MacDonald.
- May I know your name?
There are bills posted around every town and village
for the capture of Alan Breck Stewart and his companion.
- My name is David Balfour of Shaws.
- Honored, Mr. Balfour. - If never I cared.
They can hang him 50 times over!
Now, be gone from my house, sir, be gone.
- There've been grievances between us,
that's the past.
- Grievances?
There's been bloodshed.
- Let's bury 'em now while there's time.
We still have a common cause.
- I don't believe any kin of mind had a hand in the murder.
But, if one did then I honor him for sending
another Campbell to hell.
- James of the Glen is on a rope here, man!
- Begone from my house.
- Curse on you.
You're a fool.
Gotta go back to Fort William now to get him.
- What? - It's always the same.
You look for help, you get none.
It always comes down to this.
- Are you mad altogether?
They'll guard him as closely as the Crown Jewels.
- Closer, I should think.
Mr. Stewart, I have a kinsman, Hamish MacDonald.
- Mary!
Get you back to the house.
And you, get off my land before I shoot you.
- Tell them, Grandfather, tell them Hamish shot him.
- Mary, get back to the house.
- Will you shoot me if I don't?
- By the living God, I'd be justified.
You've betrayed your own kin.
- My kin?
What kin?
Who's left?
- Get away, girl.
- Where's my father?
Dead.
Where's my mother?
Dead, through grief like your own wife.
Where are your sons?
Dead.
Dead, dead.
You killed them all with your blood feuds
and your damnable obstinate murderous pride.
- I will help you to bring him to justice.
You'll find him at the head of Glen Cuillish.
Go by way of Kinkelly.
There's a path leading over Lauchran.
You'll find him at the head of the Glen.
- It's strange, I never heard of any such a path.
- You think you know everything, Alan Breck.
Mary will show you the way.
- There's porridge made, Grandfather
and cold beef and cheese in the larder.
- Ah wee girl.
If you kill him, Alan Breck,
I'll hunt you down like a dog.
- Well, why rob the hangman of his fee?
- [Soldier] Ten shun.
Shoulder arms.
Order!
- They've been seen.
Here, here, here, and here.
- That's Duncan MacDonald's land,
the Earl of Dunbrae.
- You're very well informed.
- I have been here three years.
The MacDonalds of Dunbrae and the Stewarts of Appin
are clan enemies.
Mind you the old earl has some feud or other
against half the Highlands.
- Good.
- [Forbes] Why so?
- Mark 3:25, if a house be divided against itself,
that house cannot stand.
A difficult old relic like the Earl
is worth a regiment to us.
- Yes, I see what you mean.
I hear you're to be made the King's Factor.
- Nothing's been decided.
- I think you're a man who gets what he wants.
- Oh, that's because I never allow myself to want
what I think I cannot get.
- Is Shaws a very great place, Mr. Balfour?
- I believe it is, yes.
- You don't know?
- My uncle has the house and lands at present.
- Ah, and you're his heir.
- I believe I am the legal owner.
When my father died, I discovered that
and my uncle the younger.
- Yet, he has the property.
- Company. - Well, that's strange.
- Regiment mount up. (tense music)
- There has been some great wrong, Miss MacDonald, some--
- [Alan] Get down!
- [Soldier] Advance!
Keep your (mumbles).
Keep your eyes peeled now.
- [Soldier] There he is!
(soldier shouting)
- Take your aim and fire. - Fire.
- [Soldier] Farther up!
(guns firing)
- [Soldier] Advance!
(dramatic music)
- [Soldier] Pull bayonets!
(swords clanking) (men grunting)
(David shouting)
- [Mary] David!
- Alan!
- Watch out!
(David shouting) (swords clanking)
(men grunting)
(kicks thudding)
(men shouting)
(swords clanking)
- Come on, come on!
- What happened?
- It was them all right, sir.
And, there was a girl with them.
(horse hooves clomping)
(soldier shouting)
- What girl?
- I have no idea.
They must've been making for Glen Cuillish.
(fire crackling)
Why on Earth would they do that?
- Well, it'll be trouble if we don't get there before them.
We still have a chance to catch Alan Breck Stewart.
(gentle flute music)
- I'm no fighting man and I never pretended to be.
- Then you should learn to be.
If you want justice for yourself with your uncle as you say.
- In the Lowlands, Miss MacDonald, we don't get justice
through the sword.
- [Mary] How do you get it then?
- Through the law.
- The law?
- Aye, the law.
Because we are civilized people, not savages.
(gentle flute music)
- I've always heard tell of you
as a great fighting man, Mr. Stewart.
- [Alan] Aye.
- The best in the Highlands.
- [Alan] Oh, you could say I was born to it.
- I've heard tell of you since I was a child.
(Alan chuckles)
You fought at Culloden, did you not?
- Aye.
I did.
- Even my grandfather would speak of you with respect.
- (chuckles) Well, that's pleasing to know.
I think a man could be judged for other qualities
more than his handiness with a sword.
- Are you going to speak in defense
of your friend, Mr. Stewart? - He's a young man.
- That's noble of you.
- He's got considerable book learning.
- Do you place a value on that?
- I do.
I wish I'd more of that in line myself.
I think he's a gentleman, too.
(somber music)
- [Mary] Be careful, we're nearly there.
That's where he is.
- Does your cousin know you well by sight?
- Aye, he does.
- Be best I go alone.
- No, I'll come with you.
- No, you wait here.
- If Hamish MacDonald is a dangerous man,
Alan Breck is a brave one.
- Or foolhardy.
- He knows fine what he's capable of.
You can't call such a man foolhardy.
- You seem to admire him greatly, Miss MacDonald.
- Don't you, Mr. Balfour?
(swords clattering)
(wind whistling)
(ominous music)
(birds chirping)
(roof clattering)
- Wheest!
- [David] What?
What is it?
- Will you hold your noise?
(horse hooves clacking)
Oh, we'll have to warn them.
- His own ears will warn him.
- Are you a coward?
- Use your brains, woman.
There's nothing to be done.
- Take your hand off me.
- Now, Mr. MacDonald, let me tell you what's to be.
You and I will go to Fort William
and you'll swear a statement before the justice
and you'll tell the truth.
You killed Campbell of Glenure.
For money. (Hamish choking)
Now, who paid you?
Was it William Reid?
- MacDonald.
- Alan Breck Stewart, I arrest you
in the name of King George.
- Well, while you're about it, you may arrest this man, too.
His name is MacDonald.
He murdered the Red Fox.
- What are you talking about?
- He was paid to do it by a gentleman
of your acquaintance, Mr. William Reid.
- Let go of that man!
(gun firing)
(sword clanking)
- Well, he attacked me.
Self defense.
(sword clanking)
(dramatic music)
(horses snorting)
- [Soldier] Company at the trot.
- I assume you have a family crest, Mr. Balfour of Shaws.
I suggest a new motto for it in Latin, of course.
There's nothing to be done.
(horse hooves clomping)
(door clattering)
- Unfortunately, you're to be tried
in Edinburgh, Mr. Stewart, on a charge of high treason
so I won't have the pleasure of hanging you myself.
I can't deny it's a disappointment,
but the law's the law.
- Alan, did you find the man?
- Aye, I did.
It's too late now.
He's dead.
- Then all is lost?
(somber flute music)
They try me tomorrow.
A whole pack of Campbells just as you said.
- I should've forced you into the hills.
- I never would've run.
You'd have had no choice, not at the end of my dirk.
Dear God.
You know, I don't know why
I always put such a value to your life
and never my own.
Here on my own, old man.
And, you're on your.
- I will not let him hang.
We must do something.
- What?
Rouse the MacDonalds?
March on Fort William?
Michael. - Why not?
- You're talking nonsense, girl.
- I agree.
- Well, you're not a fighting man, Mr. Balfour,
you say so yourself.
- No, but I flatter myself that I have a brain.
Now, if we could get-- - Mr. Balfour--
- Wheest!
If we can contrive to give Alan the means,
I believe he can effect his own escape.
- That's true.
In the hands of such a man, a pistol or a dirk.
We'll it'd be as good as a key to him.
- But, how?
- Are you known by sight to any at the prison?
- No.
- Nor am I.
Now, if we can stop quarreling for one minute
then perhaps we have a chance.
(horse hooves clomping)
- Thank you, no.
I have a question, Mr. Reid, to which I demand an answer.
The man you shot.
- In self defense.
- Was he the murderer of Campbell, the Red Fox?
- He was.
- Did you pay him to do it?
- Naturally.
- (chuckles) Oh God.
And, this is the way you serve, King George.
- I serve the king as the king
would wish to be served, efficaciously.
(footsteps clomping)
Forbes, you come of a good family,
but alas, not one endowed with much in the way of money.
- What do you mean, sir?
- Well, since you have not the means to purchase promotion
you must get it by your own merit
and your superiors think very highly of your merit, Captain.
- My superiors?
- Well, you don't suppose I could've acted alone
in a matter so grave.
No, no, no, no.
Men far greater than I, or you, gave it their sanction.
They think very highly of you.
They have it in mind to give you a regiment.
Think of it.
A colonel at the age of 26.
No, you see, Campbell of Glenure was not a sound man,
too soft on his own people.
I am a sound man.
And I believe you are too, a thoroughly sound man.
(footsteps clomping)
- James of the Glen?
You are summoned to trial.
- Well, Alan, if they condemn me, as they're sure to do,
they'll hang me straightaway.
(somber music)
- May we speak?
- I never knew you lost for words.
It's not the end, Alan, we'll carry on our quarrels
in a better place than this.
- [Man] It's time.
- [James] Trust in God, Alan, his mercy
and his justice.
(keys clattering)
(door clanking)
(chains clattering)
- Well?
- It's no good.
They've taken him from the prison.
- Let them be confounded and put to shame
that seek after my soul.
(somber music)
Let them be as dust before the wind
for they have laid their net
to destroy me without cause.
False witnesses did rise up,
they laid to my charge, things I knew not.
(drumming music)
Oh, deliver my soul from the calamities
which they did bring on me.
Judge me, oh Lord, my God,
(Margaret crying)
according to they righteousness.
- Man that is born of a woman has but a short time
to live and is full of misery.
He cometh up
but is cut down slow. (crowd shouting)
he fleeth also as a shadow (drowned out by shouting crowd).
(crowd applauding)
- I'm feeling rather hungry, Captain.
Care for some lunch?
- If you'll forgive me, I have other duties.
- [Soldier] About face, march.
(dark music)
(dramatic music) (punches thudding)
(men grunting)
(bales clattering)
(women screaming)
(men shouting)
(adventurous music)
(horse hooves clomping) (coach clattering)
- Hurry up, we're not free of the Redcoats yet.
Well, the sooner you're in the Lowlands, the better for you
and for me.
- With the coach, we could bring them there in a few days.
- No, we've done enough, more than enough.
We go home and lie low, devilish low.
- Will you cross the Firth by the Bridge of Sterling?
- Aye, most likely.
Good luck, Mr. Stewart.
Mr. Balfour, I hope we may meet again some day.
- I hope so, too.
(coach clattering)
- [Alan] Let's get you back to the Lowlands, Davie,
and your House of Shaws.
(somber flute music)
It's a fine country, you don't think so, David?
- [David] It's a wilderness.
- [Alan] (chuckles) You Lowlanders.
You've plenty of brains, but you've no poetry to your souls.
- [David] Well, from what I've seen of you Highlanders,
you have a deal too much poetry and not enough brains.
(Alan laughs)
(water splashing)
(fire crackling)
- It's really excellent, very good.
- So, were you courting a lassie when you left home?
- No.
- No broken hearts left behind?
- Hmm.
- I suppose you have broken many hearts.
- No.
Only one.
She was everything to me.
But, I was married,
to that, my sword
and my king.
- Alan, will you teach me to use a sword?
- Why?
- I just think it's uh,
a skill every man should acquire.
(bird squawking)
- En garde.
Allez.
(swords clanking)
Not a great beginning.
(upbeat music)
Not bad, Davie, just don't hurt yourself.
(David grunting)
(swords clacking)
Eh yah!
(sword clanking)
- Well, you have more weapons than me.
- Brains, Davie, brains (laughs).
(birds chirping)
(David grunting) (rifle thudding)
- Ah no.
(man laughing)
- Ian, get a grip on yourself, man.
Francis, look at you, God love you,
you're as fat as a cow.
(men laughing)
These are the sons of Cluny MacPherson, man.
We fought the English together.
- He's wanted by the Crown.
The Crown, the Parliament, and the Redcoats.
He's probably more hunted than I am myself.
- I thought they was in hiding in France.
- Ah, not Cluny.
Lives like a fighting cock in his own country,
with his own people.
You'll have a taste of the real Highland life now, man.
(upbeat music) (David grunts)
What is it?
Ah, don't die on me now, Davie.
Come along, you're a Lowlander, through and through.
No strength-- (David grunts)
Whoop.
(laughs)
You're carrying the weight of the gold.
Come here, I'll carry you both.
(laughs)
You'll have a rest in Cluny's cave.
Cluny!
- Breck! - Lay out the cards,
you flat blackguard.
- Six, six, and seven.
All right, right.
This time's up right.
This time I'll (mumbles).
Get ahold on you.
I've seven.
It's only five.
- Jack!
- No, no, it's a queen.
Jack then.
- Queen.
- No Jack.
- [Alan] Jack.
- Seven, five, nine, Jack!
(Cluny laughing)
Are you fleeced, Mr. Stewart?
Have you more in your pocket or only stitches?
Or can you use this?
Eh?
(belt thudding) (ethereal music)
(chair clattering)
- [Alan] Davie, gimme a loan.
- [David] What?
- Money.
Lay out the cards, Cluny.
(coins clattering)
(Cluny laughs)
- [David] Did you win?
- [Alan] Did I win?
I lost.
- [David] All of it?
- [Alan] Every penny of it.
- You lost it all?
- Yours and mine. - I don't believe it.
(Alan laughs) That was my money, too.
You Highlanders, you're fools.
I can't tolerate your way of life any longer.
- David, it's not the way.
No way for two friends to take such a matter.
- Oh, and how should I take it?
- David, I owe you my life.
Now, I owe you some money.
A gentleman would try to make the burden light,
try to see the reason.
- You stand there and tell me
how a gentleman should behave?
- I think you've much to learn upon the subject, man.
- You gambled your Prince's gold at cards
and you stand there and preach to me
about what a gentleman should do?
- [Alan] What are you talking about?
I never risked a penny of it.
- Oh, I saw the money on the table.
- Never, ever suggest
that I betray my cause. (bagpipe music)
- Why not?
Your cause is lost, isn't it?
It's the past.
Scotland decided.
We chose King George.
Whose gonna rise up against us?
You?
Your time is over.
You Stewarts, you lost the throne through your own follies
and vices and you know it.
As for your Bonny Prince Charlie, what did he do?
What did he really do?
He brought ruin and destruction and civil war
to the Highlands.
And, he wasn't even Scottish.
Your cause is lost and you know it.
(somber music)
(cow mooing)
(horse hooves clomping)
- They're over there just beyond the hill.
- Wait here.
(men chattering)
Captain, they've been sighted.
- Where?
- [Soldier] About two miles to the north.
- Sergeant.
- [Sergeant] Sir!
- Fall in the men.
- Sir.
Stand to, men, stand to.
(men chattering) (horse whinnying)
First company withdraw your pickets.
- There we are, Captain, patience and perseverance.
- [Sergeant] Quick about it now.
Have a shot ready.
(ominous music)
(birds chirping)
(moving to dramatic music)
(David panting)
(ominous music)
- I think they caught us now.
(moving to dramatic music)
(coach clattering)
- [David] Alan.
It's MacDonald's coach.
- Get in.
Well, stay down on the floor.
- Stand to, men.
Whoa.
- I'm Mary MacDonald of Dunbrae.
My grandfather the Earl is gravely ill.
- My apologies, ma'am.
Let them pass.
- You old goat, your timing's impeccable.
- It's Mary you have to thank.
I said it could cost us our necks.
I said Alan Breck needed no aid from us,
but she wouldn't have it.
- Grandfather.
- Mr. Balfour's health, it seems is her great concern.
- So, you just happened to be on the road.
- We were fairly certain that you'd make
for the Bridge of Sterling, so we took a lodging
in the inn and waited.
- It isn't only the Redcoats that have their spies.
(coach clattering)
- Halt!
- What the devil are you at?
Let me pass.
Curse it, do you know who I am?
I am the Earl of Dunbrae.
(cane thudding)
(coach clattering)
- We're almost safe, Grandfather.
Gentlemen, we're in the Lowland.
(both grunting)
- [Alan] We made it, Davie.
We made it.
(Mary laughs)
(all laugh)
- The Earl passed by several hours ago.
I swear there were no others, only the old man
and his granddaughter.
- Cross the bridge, Captain and continue the pursuit.
Send me word when they're found.
- You want me to pursue them on my own?
- I have no authority beyond this point
but they're mine to hang.
Bring them to me, Captain.
- [Captain] Sir.
- Do you want promotion?
Get on with it.
- Go and catch a falling star. (gentle music)
Get with child a mandrake root.
Tell me where all past years are
or who cleft the devil's foot.
Teach me to hear mermaids singing
or to keep off envy's stinging
and find what wind--
- Miss MacDonald, uh, I wanted to,
I wanted to thank you for coming to our aid.
And, I wanted to apologize to you.
I believe I called you a savage.
- There's no need to apologize.
- Well, I take it back unreservedly.
- (chuckles) Forgive me, Mr. Balfour,
but you're so serious.
- I go this morning to learn my fate
from the lawyer Rankeillor.
- You come back and tell me how it turns out?
And if you got your estate back?
- I would like that very much.
(patrons chattering)
- So, you're bound for France.
- Aye.
(pouch jangling)
- Well, take that with you when you go.
(bagpipe music)
Well, don't gawk, man, take it.
And, you can tell His Majesty he's still has loyal friends
among the MacDonalds of Dunrae.
- Will you shake the hand of an Appin Stewart?
(horse hooves clomping)
(pedestrians chattering)
- Would you have a dram, Captain Forbes?
- What would we drink to?
- The future and the demise of Mr. William Reid.
(loud knocking)
(birds chirping)
- [David] I'm here to see Mr. Rankeillor.
- There is no great mystery, Mr. Balfour,
and there was no great wrong
until your uncle's wicked attempt at kidnap,
at which I still shudder.
Your father, Alexander Balfour and his brother Ebenezer
both fell in love with the same lady, a Miss Pitarrow.
- My mother?
- Aye, your mother.
The estate of Shaws is entailed.
Do you know what that means?
- Uh, no, sir.
- It means that it can never be sold,
but must be passed on entire from generation to generation.
Now, your father was the first born son.
- Ah, I discovered that.
- He, therefore, inherited Shaws.
Your Uncle Ebenezer had nothing except
the misguided affection of Miss Pitarrow
which he used to force a bargain.
Your father, to make over his rents,
your uncle to give up the lady.
- My father gave away all his rent
for the love of my mother?
- Aye, he did, but only for his lifetime.
The day that he died, you became the legal owner of Shaws.
You are the owner.
Small wonder that Ebenezer wanted you dead.
(clock ticking)
(somber flute music)
(loud knocking)
- Well, that's a civil welcome, indeed.
- One step nearer you're a dead man, Mr. Highlander.
- And a civil speech to go with it, let it go.
I just come for business.
As I said.
- You did not say what.
- There's been a lad who was cast up
on the shores of Ardnamurchan.
- [Ebenezer] Alive?
- Most certainly alive, sir.
David Balfour.
Tedious long business to nurse the boy
back to health.
'Twas a great expense.
- Aye, no doubt, just say on, Mr. Highlander.
- Well sir, a man's a fool to be spending his money
in that way, uh (chuckles).
Without giving a thought to a return,
a wee return (chuckles).
- Well, that's true.
Well, we agree together there, Mr. Highlander.
- It just come to my mind you might pay a wee bit more
to have him dead.
- Just what put that into your mind?
- Well, there was something he let slip, sir,
when the fever was on him.
You did have him kidnapped aboard a brig,
for 60 guineas.
- 60 guineas?
- Aye.
(Ebenezer laughs)
- Did he say that?
I never paid a penny piece, man.
I didn't have to.
They took him for the price of his hide
at slave auction.
(laugh) Kidnap cost me nothing.
(Alan laughs)
Not a copper coin.
- That was served excellently well.
Good day, Mr. Balfour.
May I present Mr. Crawford.
(Alan laughing)
He's a magistrate.
He heard every word and will witness to it.
(door clattering)
There is another door.
I have the key.
(coins clattering)
Mr. Balfour, take your hands off that money, sir.
It is not yours.
- He could take my rents, he can't take my gold,
not the gold I've saved.
- That's not what the law says.
- He can't take my gold.
- The law in this case states that any monies
derived from the estate which are unspent
remain the property of the estate.
- No, it's a lie, it's a damnable lie.
- In short, sir, every penny you've scrimped and hoarded
through your miserable life
belongs to your nephew, David Balfour.
(Ebenezer cries)
Poor, miserable wretch.
(horse hooves clomping)
- There's a boat waiting nearby to take him to France.
With your permission, we must proceed on foot.
- Form columns.
- [Soldier] Forming columns.
- [Soldier] Forward.
- [Soldier] Double forward.
- I suggest you wait here
until I've got my men into position.
- Trust there'll be no more mistakes, Captain.
- You can be sure of that, Mr. Reid.
(horse hooves clomping)
(birds chirping)
- Prepare to left wheel.
- Forgive me sir, but this isn't the way
to the coast, surely.
- I'm not going to the coast, Lieutenant.
We're going back to the barracks at Cramond.
- But, sir, I thought--
- That was Mr. Reid's order.
Do you question it?
- No, sir, of course not.
- Very wise.
He's not a man to cross.
Carry on, Lieutenant.
Come on!
Go on!
(horse hooves clomping)
(ominous music)
- [Alan] Mr. Reid.
(sword clattering)
- You're mistaking me for a gentleman, Mr. Stewart.
I've no intention of fighting you.
You'll have to kill an unarmed man.
And, I wonder which is the greater?
Your sense of honor
or your hatred of me.
Good day to you, Mr. Stewart.
(pistol clacking)
(pistol firing)
- Drive on.
- [Driver] Ho, hey!
Ha, ha, ha!
Ha!
(dramatic music)
(horse hooves clomping) (coach clattering)
(whip thudding)
(driver grunting)
(driver shouting)
(whip thudding) - Yah, yah.
Yah.
(moving to adventure music)
(whip thudding)
Yah, yah!
- Slow down!
- [Alan] Yah!
Yah!
- You...
(coach rumbling)
No!
(coach clattering)
(water splashing)
(birds squawking)
(waves splashing)
- Here's a parting gift for you, Davie.
I can't take your sword, Alan. - Take it.
I got no use for it now.
You hang it on the wall in your great house.
No doubt you'll be having sons now.
You could tell 'em it came from kings.
You've acquired some poetry to your soul now.
(gentle orchestral music)
Hey!
On my way now.
- [Man] Right.
Oh.
- [Alan] All right.
- [Narrator] Alan Breck Stewart and David Balfour
never met again.
Alan went on to have a distinguished career
in the French Army.
He died in Paris at the age of 65.
David Balfour married Mary MacDonald.
And, Alan was right, they did have sons.
They were neither Highlander nor Lowlander.
They were Scots.
(lively music)