[door opens]
[birds tweet]
[door closes]
[knocks]
- Are you all right?
Are you sleepin' out here?
- What?
- What're you doin' out here?
Are you sleeping?
- I, I might've dozed off.
- Is that drool?
You've got a pillow
and a blanket.
- What's the problem?
- "Problem?"
- Yeah, the problem.
Why are you knocking
on my window?
- Well, if somebody's just
sittin' out here in a car,
under a blanket, I gotta check.
- Check what?
- This is the library.
- So? What are you checking for?
Terrorists?
- What?
No!
I said this is the library.
I'm checkin' for perverts.
[phone vibrates]
- I have to take this.
Jane, hi! What a nice surprise.
Oh, it's a surprise for me.
Oh, it's not nice?
[phone bleeps]
Hello?
Jane?
[sighs]
Damn it.
[bright chamber music]
[car starts]
[heavy knocks]
[dryer blows]
[groans]
[heavy knocks]
I'm really gonna miss you guys.
I'm so grateful.
I'm gonna miss you too.
Hi, Mary.
- Isn't that same blouse
you wore yesterday?
[phone rings]
- Hey, Jane. It's Beta.
Just calling you back.
My phone died earlier.
I hope everything's okay.
I'm not going to be
going home tonight, FYI.
So just give me a call back.
Okay, bye.
- Not paying you to
make phone calls.
- I'm sorry, I just got a
call from my father's ex-wife,
which is really unusual.
- I'm just messing with you.
[Beta chuckles]
Surprised you even
came in today.
- Oh! Well, I wanted to
say goodbye to everybody.
- At least you didn't
shower, change clothes.
[chuckles] Just
messing with you.
Good luck at school.
You sure didn't give us
much time to prepare.
- I know, it was
all really sudden.
Some scholarship money
opened up, I guess,
so I haven't even had a
chance to tell my family yet.
- [Boss] Well, I don't
know what that's about,
but we're gonna miss
you around here.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Did you see that cake and
balloons in the conference room?
- Are you serious?
- I'm just messing.
[Beta chuckles]
Take it easy.
[footsteps recede]
- Hi, ZeeZee, it's me.
I'm calling to make sure that
we're still on for tonight.
I have some exciting
news to share
and I am looking
forward to seeing you.
Okay, bye bye.
Hi.
- I need you to cat
sit this weekend.
- Uh, I can't.
Remember I'm moving
to Connecticut?
- Maybe I'll ask Rebecca.
- Okay!
[copier hums]
[flatulence]
- Excuse me.
[knocks]
- Knock knock.
- Oh, hey, Brad.
- You're leaving us. [chuckles]
I'm just kidding. That's great.
That's great.
Congratulations on the
school. I'm sure it's great.
I mean it will be great.
- Yeah, thank you, Brad.
That's... That's
really sweet of you.
- Will you have a
drink with me tonight?
- Oh, um...
I'm actually getting dinner
with my sister and our father.
I haven't even told
them the good news, so-
- What about tomorrow?
- Um, tomorrow?
I'm...
- I've met Grant. I know
you have a boyfriend.
I'm not trying to have
intercourse with you.
- Oh, my god, no. It's
not that. [chuckles]
[phone rings and vibrates]
- I'll let you take that.
Good luck with life.
[phone rings and vibrates]
- Jane! Finally!
It is so funny that
you called me today.
Yes, yes, exactly.
And, um, I know that this
is last-minute, um...
Okay. Oh, yeah, sure.
Sorry. Go right ahead.
What?
[somber orchestral music]
- God, it's hot.
- You said that already.
- Oh?
- What the fuck is this?
- Hi.
- [Pippa] Can we help you?
- [Beta] Yeah! I'm just
looking for my sister?
She lives here?
- Oh?
- I think.
- What's her name, sweetie?
- Zelda Foreman?
- [Olive] Ah. Is that a fact?
- [Pippa] I didn't
know she had a sister.
- You don't come by, do you?
She hasn't been out
of her room all day,
and it's hotter than an
Arab's armpit up there.
[Pippa laughs]
- [Pippa] She also owes
us rent. Two months now.
- Why don't you get her
to join us down here
for some fresh air?
- If she wants to
sit on this stoop,
she's gotta pay her rent.
- [Beta] Nice meeting you both.
- Hers is the room at
the end of the hall!
- The one that smells.
[door closes]
[brooding piano music]
[knocks]
- [Beta] Zelda?
[door creaks]
[sighs]
[clears throat]
[keyboard clacks]
[sexual moaning from computer]
[window opens]
- What're you doing
on my computer?
That stuff is very private.
- [Beta] What are you doing?
- I don't like to
use the front door.
It's a very long story.
See? There, not so bad.
- [Beta] Why are you climbing
in through the window?
- You could try
it when you leave.
It's actually kind of fun.
- [Beta] Are you sneaking in
and out of your own house?
- I guess so.
I just don't like to talk
to the people out front.
It's funny, isn't it? That I'm
still sneaking out at my age.
I mean, it's not
funny, but it's sad.
It's just easier this way,
because I think they're
trying to kick me out.
- [Beta] They said you
owe two months rent.
- Yeah, well, I'm good for it.
I just haven't really had a job.
- I tried calling you today.
- Yeah, I know.
I mean...
Oh, you did? [chuckles]
I left my phone at
Henry's. I'm sorry.
- Jane called me this morning.
- [chuckles] That's why
I leave my phone places.
Not that she would ever call me.
What did old Jane want?
- Dad's dead.
- [Zelda] What?
Do you mean-
- They found him in his car.
- But the doctor said
that he was doing great.
See, that's why I hate doctors.
- In the garage.
- Huh?
- The car had been
running in the garage.
[Zelda sighs]
He was probably in there
for a couple of days.
- Do you have any cigarettes?
- I don't smoke.
We're going to go Jane's tonight
and meet everyone for dinner.
- What?
- ZeeZee.
- Fuck that!
- Who is "everyone?"
- Jane, our brothers.
- Half-brothers.
- Why don't you wanna go?
- Why do you want to?
- Because he's our
dad too, ZeeZee,
and we have just as much a right
to be there as anyone else!
- I wouldn't even wanna be
there, even if Dad was alive.
Like let alone right
after finding out
that he killed himself.
[Beta sighs]
- It'll be nice to
be around people.
- I'm a person!
And I'm a person that
doesn't wanna process these
initial stages of grief around
people who look down on me.
- They don't look down on you.
Jane called and
invited us to dinner.
She's making an effort and I
would really like to be there
and I would really like it
if you were there with me.
- Well, this is going
to be a disaster.
- Thank you.
[distant dog barks]
- We have to leave
through the window.
[baroque harpsichord music]
[laughter]
- How're you doing, Ma?
Are you putting on a brave
face or are you okay?
- I'm happy to have the
whole family in one place.
- [Guy] You just let us
know if you need anything.
- Ouch, stop.
- [Keith] Are Beta
and Zelda comin'?
- Oh-oh.
I forgot.
Who knows?
[Keith scoffs]
- If they're taking Beta's car,
they probably won't
be here till morning.
[door closes]
[brothers laugh]
- The last time
I ran into Zelda,
she didn't even have shoes on.
[brothers laugh]
Oh, boy.
- How's the fruit?
- Thank you.
- It's mostly melon.
- Well, uh, Ellie put
dinner away already.
- That's fine. I don't
really eat anymore.
- [clears throat] I'm
sorry for your loss.
It's never easy
to lose a father.
Even if you were close to him.
You may or may not know
that there will be
no funeral, per se,
because it was
Bobby's lifelong dream
to be cremated.
- Please, go on.
- We will be going to
your father's house,
tomorrow at three,
to sort through and
claim his belongings,
in accordance with the will.
And of course you are
welcome to drop by.
- We weren't
included in the will?
- [Jane] Oh, of course you are!
- So why wouldn't we be welcome?
- You are.
- Thanks.
- Does anybody want this
fruit before I throw it away?
- Yeah, [clears throat] yeah.
I'll have some, Mom.
I love melons. [chuckles]
- Maybe your daughter
would like one.
- Are we talking about tomorrow?
- Your mother was just telling
us that we are very welcome.
- [Guy] Course you are.
- No one should be surprised
that there isn't
any money coming.
But all the blood relatives
are more than welcome
to divide any
belongings they want,
you know, for
sentimental reasons.
- And that's the five of us?
- And Uncle Jerry.
- Who?
- Uncle Jerry?
- Wait a minute.
Who's Uncle Jerry?
- Dad's brother?
- Yeah, I guess I
understand how uncles work.
I'm just wondering why this is
the first I'm hearing of him.
- [Zelda] Yeah, we've never
had any male role models.
- He's been dead
for a long time.
- Well...
We don't know he's dead.
- We believe he is dead.
- I'm having trouble
wrapping my head around this.
Dad had a brother?
- Who is dead?
- Probably.
- [Beta] Why have we
never heard about this?
- Your Uncle Jerry
was a religious nut.
Your father hardly spoke to him
and nobody has heard from
him in almost 30 years.
- [Beta] Why isn't
anyone looking for him?
- He's been gone, a long time!
- [Zelda] But Dad
included him in the will.
- Take it easy!
Yes, he is included in the will
but given the circumstances-
- So we should be
trying to find him.
- Will you take it easy?
Given your father's
state of mind,
who knows what was
going through his head.
- That he wanted to
include his brother
in the divvying up
of his belongings,
that doesn't seem very
difficult to suss out.
- Then go find him.
We're still going through
your father's house tomorrow.
- I will find Jerry,
and I can't wait.
- You are being selfish.
- No, you are being selfish.
- I'm being selfish?
I'm not the one
that killed myself!
- Well, there's still
a little bit of time.
- You have a point.
So nice to see you, Beta.
I'm off to bed.
- Goodnight, Mom.
[melancholy chamber music]
[brothers sigh]
- [Waiter] How's the tea?
- It's fine.
- Can I get you anything else?
- [Beta] No, thanks.
- Are you sure?
Some soup? String cheese?
[Beta chuckles]
Any dessert?
Slice of pie?
On the house.
- Uh, no.
- [Waiter] You have
really beautiful eyes.
- Oh!
Okay.
- That's not the response
I was planning for.
- I'm not in the mood
to be hit on just now,
I guess, but thank you.
- Must be nice to be
so selective about when
and where someone
pays you a compliment.
- My dad died today.
And I'll also take the
check, when you get a chance.
What do you keep doing in there?
- Douching.
[Beta chuckles]
See? Made you laugh.
- I'm not happy
with you, ZeeZee.
- That will pass.
My tea is cold.
- Well, then you
should've brought it
in the bathroom with you.
- Are you seriously mad at me?
- Why do you have to
be so antagonistic?
You need to learn how
to control yourself.
- Um, I control
myself all the time.
You're asking me to let other
people control me, and I...
I refuse to do that,
especially with them.
- Our opinion of them was formed
when we were practically
children and we now have
the opportunity to get
to know them as adults.
Don't you wanna be
close to your brothers?
- Half-brothers.
- So what?
- Um, so Keith kept
looking down my shirt.
- That's ridiculous.
- Um, I'm sorry.
Uh, I think what you meant to
say was "that's disgusting."
- Well, why were you wearing
such a low-cut shirt
to the occasion?
- Because you showed up to my
house and demanded that I go,
white male oppressor,
not because I wanted my
brother to stare at my tits.
Jesus Christ, are
you kidding me?
- Okay.
- Half-brother.
- I'm sorry.
[Zelda groans]
- Don't you think it's selfish
that they're not even
gonna try to find him?
- I agree, but-
- I mean, the fact that they
assume he's dead only makes it
more likely that he's not dead.
I mean, like, who assumes death?
Like, that doesn't
even make sense.
They don't wanna find him
because they don't want
anything to do with him,
just like they've never
wanted anything to do with us.
They hope he's dead,
is more like it.
- It's weird, I agree,
but Dad wasn't in
contact with him either.
- Dad included him in his will.
He could be the family
that we never had.
I mean, what if we find
him? Do you have your phone?
- It's about to die.
[Zelda groans]
- Can we go to your place
and use your computer?
- Why don't we go to your place?
- I'm not allowed to have
people over at night.
Oh, let's go to Henry's.
He's got a computer and
that way I can get my phone.
- Who's Henry?
- The guy that I'm
sleeping with. I told you.
- You want me to go to Henry's?
- I mean, not if it's...
You don't want to.
- Um, no, of course I want to.
I'm just surprised
to be asked, I guess.
- Well, don't make
it weird, okay?
Why can't like one nice happen
without you farting in its face?
- This will be fun! Or, is fun.
- When was the last
time that we hung out?
- High school?
- We hung out in high school?
[car door closes]
That waiter didn't
even look at me.
He was cute.
I wanna stomp on his dick.
- I'm not as sad
as I want to be.
- What? About Dad?
- Yeah.
- That's a great quote.
"I'm not as sad
as I want to be."
- Do you know what
I mean, though?
Like, I just feel kinda guilty.
Like I'm not sad enough.
- Yeah, it's uh...
Hard to get sad these days.
[clears throat]
[car starts]
- This, okay, this is it?
- Yeah.
[car doors slam]
- What is this place?
- [Zelda] Henry's loft.
[door creaks]
[giggles]
- [Beta] What does Henry do?
- [Zelda] He builds sets
or something for plays.
You know, like the rooms
and bridges and stuff?
- [Beta] "Bridges?"
- I don't know. He's like
a carpenter but for plays.
Henry's old, by the way.
- What?
- Henry's an old man, just FYI.
Be cool.
[keys clink]
[door creaks]
- Hello. [chuckles]
What were you saying about me?
- Oh, I was just
telling Beta here
that you are not the young
man she perhaps envisioned,
but are, in fact,
an aged pre-vert.
- I've always been
that way. I'm Henry.
- Hi, I'm Beta.
- Nice to meet you.
You're a friend of Zorba's?
- Uh, actually, I'm her sister.
- Oh!
Well, in that case, it is
actually very nice to meet you.
I would say "finally meet you"
but I didn't even know
that Zelda had a sister.
- Yeah, that sounds about right.
- I don't like to brag.
Did you find my phone?
[Beta chuckles]
- I didn't know it was here.
You want some apples and cheese?
- What're you making?
- Apples and cheese.
Sit, sit. Yeah.
[Beta chuckles]
- Thanks.
[glasses clink]
- If I'd known we were
expecting company,
I would've bought another apple.
- Oh, uh, just the
cheese is fine.
- I'm just joking.
- He was kidding.
- Yeah, me too.
- Yeah.
So what've you two
little angels been up to?
- Henry, our father died.
- Oh, my...
Whoa.
I thought he was doing okay?
- Yeah, he did it
himself. We think.
- Oh, my god. I'm sorry.
[Zelda chuckles]
- No, please don't come near me,
'cause I'm just gonna lose it.
- Is there anything I can do?
- No.
- [Beta] Thank you, Henry.
- The world is old,
but we are young.
- Henry, can we
use your computer?
[cork pops]
[Henry chuckles]
- I mean, by that time I'd
already been at sea for almost
three years remember, so
whatever skills I had had
at conversing civilly
with people on land
had gone completely
out the window.
And when I'd get my shore leave,
I was literally a monster,
crawling up out of the ocean.
[Beta and Zelda chuckle]
- How long were you
on the submarine?
Is it "in" or "on?"
- Uh, six years.
- Wow.
- And what the hell were
you doing in the Navy?
I'm assuming it
wasn't patriotism.
- Well, there's nothing
wrong with patriotism,
depending on the country.
But, uh...
[Zelda and Beta laugh]
I don't know what I was
doing on that submarine.
I was pretty lost back then.
I mean, I think the
only thing I really had
in common with anybody
on that sewer pipe
was the fact that we had
all taken a long look
at our life on land and
decided to chuck it.
So, still nothin', huh?
- Um, well, unless he is a
real estate agent in Arizona,
or the murderer-rapist
Jerry the Whoreman Foreman,
who died in 1902,
then the internet has nothing
to say about our uncle.
- Maybe he is dead.
- But wouldn't there be an
online record of his death?
- [Beta] You'd think so.
- If Dad put him in the will,
then that means
that he was alive.
Dad must have known that.
Maybe we can find
something at the house.
- At Dad's house?
- Yeah.
Like a letter or something.
- Are you suggesting
we go to Dad's house?
- Yes, why? Do you not wanna go?
- Of course I do, but
I want it to be nice.
- Well, I'm sure it won't be.
- I mean I want you
to apologize to Jane.
- For what?
- For...
For me.
Just say you're sorry.
You're emotional.
- I would rather
sit on Keith's face.
- Maybe there's a middle ground?
- Mm.
- If you don't
apologize, I'm not going.
- No!
- I'm not going!
[Zelda groans]
- [Zelda] Okay, okay, I
will apologize to Jane.
- You promise?
- I promise.
[brooding piano music]
- Thank you.
[distant whistling]
[car door slams]
[man coughs]
[keys clink]
[door creaks]
[door closes]
[keys clink]
[water splashes]
[door opens]
[muffled footsteps]
[door closes]
[door opens]
[dog barks]
[phone vibrates]
- [Zelda] Thanks, Doug.
[garage door hums]
Hi.
- Hi.
- What? Are you
sleeping in here?
- Oh, no! [chuckles] No.
Just in case.
- That's good thinking.
[seatbelt clacks]
[sighs]
It's from a dog, Beta.
It is seriously from a
dog. Let us go, okay?
- Oh! Um, what'd Jane say?
Everything okay?
Did you call?
- I don't have a phone, so...
- You didn't call?
- I don't have a phone. I don't
know what you want me to do!
- Oh, my god. You have
got to be kidding me!
- I don't know where
it is! I told you that.
- Yeah, you also told me
that you would call Jane!
In fact, you promised me.
- How do you want me to call
Jane if I don't have a phone?
- [Beta] They don't have
a phone at doggy day care?
- Of course they do but I don't
know Jane's number by heart.
- Well then you
should've called me.
- I don't know your number.
- Well, [sighs] you must've
known you didn't know
anybody's number and that
you didn't have a phone when
you promised you'd call Jane
and you knew how important-
- I didn't think that far ahead!
It wasn't like it was
a conscious decision
to disobey you.
- I'm not asking you to obey me.
- Well, you don't occupy that
much space in my head, okay?
For me to like think ahead
of ways to disappoint you.
- You don't think
about me, period!
That's precisely the issue I'm
trying to highlight for you.
You don't think about
anybody, except yourself.
- Well, thanks for the
ride. This is my stop.
- Just once I would like
to communicate with you.
- Maybe instead we
should just be quiet.
- Maybe you should take
my phone out of my purse,
and call Jane.
Right now.
[car doors slam]
- Hm, you know,
it would be great
if you could have like
a plastic bag for this.
Or like a cap for the brush,
because it's kind of disgusting
to let it roll around
loose in your bag.
- In two seconds I'm going to
use it to gouge out your eyes.
- Mm!
Whoa, you have seven
missed calls from Grant.
[Beta sighs]
That's a mystical
number. [chuckles]
[phone rings]
[grunts softly]
[Beta chuckles]
[phone rings]
[grunts softly]
[grunts]
[phone rings]
[Beta laughs]
Hi.
No, it's Zelda.
Yep.
One of your husband's children.
Ex-husband, yeah.
Beta and I are on
our way to Dad's,
and I just had to call and
apologize, because my behavior
yesterday was very
bad and inappropriate.
And so, I'm sorry.
My dad is dead and I'm sad.
Oh, really?
I'm sorry to hear that.
Well, you just take it slow.
You know, it would be a
shame if you fell again.
- [Beta] What?
- We'll see you there, okay?
[phone clicks]
Oh, she hung up.
- What happened?
- Jane fell out of
bed and hurt her neck.
- What? Oh, my god!
- Who...
Who falls out of the bed
past the age of five?
Did she go poopy, too?
- Is she okay?
- We're gonna have to check
her underwear and find out.
[melancholy chamber music]
[car starts]
- When did Jane say
they would be here?
- Hm, maybe they got
into a car accident.
- I'm sorry I got so...
Grant and I broke up.
- What? Why?
- Why not?
- Are you still living together?
- I just sort of left.
- So that's why your car looks
like an episode of Hoarders.
- I'm also moving.
I wanted to tell you that,
but it got kinda overshadowed.
- Oh, my god. Could we
get a place together?
- I'm moving to Connecticut.
- Oh. Um...
What's, what's in Con-
- Um, I got into grad school.
[Zelda chuckles]
And I'm gonna get to go.
- That's fucking awesome.
- [chuckles] Yeah.
- When do you leave?
- Monday.
- Monday, as in
two-days-from-now Monday?
- Yeah.
- Well, we'll always have
that weekend that Dad died.
I'll be right back.
- Where are you going?
- Take a dump.
[car approaches]
- Hi.
- [groans] Jesus fuck.
- You okay, Ma?
[hushed chatter]
[car door slams]
There you go.
- Ow, ow!
- I got ya, I got ya, Ma.
- [Keith] Can you
feel your legs?
- [Guy] I could feel yours.
- Hi, everybody!
- Hi, Beta.
- Hi.
- Hey, hey.
- You all right?
- Let's get this over with.
Is Zelda here or not?
- Oh, um, yeah.
She's here, she's...
- Whoops.
[purse zips]
- Are they here yet?
- Yeah.
Did you really take a dump?
- Yes.
- [Beta] Where is it?
- I buried it, you sick fuck.
- What was going on back there?
- [Beta] We're just
looking around.
[Adam sniffs]
- Did you just sniff me?
- ZeeZee.
- [Adam] I thought
you got sober, no?
- [Zelda] What?
- Are you smoking grass out
back your old man's house?
- No, I'm not "smoking grass
out back my old man's house."
Are you for real?
- All right, I'm sorry.
All right, no big
deal. Just checkin'.
I'm sorry. After you.
Let's just try and
behave ourselves.
- Yes, let us.
[door closes]
[Adam sighs]
- Well, I'm gonna hit
up the wine cellar.
[brothers laugh]
- [Jane] How are we
going to do this?
- Um, every man or...
Woman, for his or herself.
And if we wanna trade later,
then we can discuss it.
- [Adam] Shotgun
the VHS collection.
[Keith and Guy laugh]
I'm not joking.
- All right.
Break!
- Help me to the couch.
- [Guy] Ma, I'm losing
valuable time here.
- Okay, if there's anything
here, it's probably downstairs,
but in the interest of
time, shall we split up?
- Okay, yeah. I'll
go check his bedroom.
- [claps] Okay.
[melancholy chamber music]
[doors close]
[chuckles]
[sighs]
Gimme, gimme, gimme.
[chuckles]
Mama mia.
[melancholy chamber music]
- [Keith] Find anything good?
- You scared me.
[Keith chuckles]
- I'm a creep.
- [Zelda] Got it.
- [clears throat] You
know, it's too bad
it took Dad's death to bring
us all together like this.
But regardless, nice to see ya.
Beta, too. [chuckles]
Don't you think it's silly that
we all live in the same city
and yet we never see each other?
- Kinda makes sense.
[Keith chuckles]
- Hey, we even have the same
sense of humor. [chuckles]
Look, you know, I think
you'd actually like me,
if you'd just knock that
chip off your shoulder.
I'm pretty cool.
- Narc!
[Keith laughs]
- Hoo! [laughs]
See? That's effin' funny!
Hey, look.
I'm not gonna give you
shit like Adam did outside.
He told me what happened.
- I wasn't doing drugs.
- No, hey, it's okay.
Adam's an asshole,
everybody knows that.
But, uh...
If you did have some
pot, [clicks tongue]
I know somebody who'd
like to smoke it with ya.
[chuckles] Looks like
a cigarette, right?
It's a one-hitter, you know?
[inhales sharply]
[chuckles]
Brand new.
What the fuck?
- [Zelda] Ow! Get off!
[muffled clattering]
Don't!
Stop, don't! Ow!
- Quit it!
- Let go of me, asshole!
- What's going on?
- Relax!
[slap]
[groans] You stupid bitch!
- Zelda? What the hell
is going on down there?
- [Keith] Man, she
is crazy! [chuckles]
- [Jane] Zelda, get out.
- Ma.
- No.
No, you get out of here. Why
do you have to ruin everything?
- "Why do you have
to ruin everything?"
That's all anyone
here ever says to me!
Why doesn't somebody
invite me in
and lift me up and
not just my skirt?
- Whoa!
- Your father, God rest his
soul, was not with your mother
for two years before
he came back to me,
and this family has been
paying the price ever since.
- And how long did he
stay with you that time?
- It was mutual.
- [Beta] Did you
lift up her skirt?
- No. No, she's lying!
She cuts herself. She's
got cuts all over her legs.
And I tried to get a look,
you know, and she attacked me.
I was concerned, she
was fuckin' bleeding,
and she fuckin' slapped
my fuckin' face!
- You have no right to do that.
- Is that
a marijuana pipe?
- It's not mine!
- Unbelievable.
- It's not-
- That's it!
- Adam, what is that?
- Okay.
- It's illegal drugs.
[door slams]
- Keith, are you okay?
- Yeah.
- Unbelievable.
[Jane sighs]
It's always something
with her. Unbelievable.
- "When is someone gonna
lift me up, invite me in."
Hah! We've been inviting
her in for 20 years.
And this is the thanks
we get. [laughs]
[Keith chuckles]
- [Beta] Excuse me.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
- Zelda?
- [Guy] Hey, Beta!
- What?
- I'm sorry.
- For what?
- I don't know.
- Okay?
Thanks.
- Hey!
Take care of yourself, okay?
- [Zelda] Can we go?
[car door slams]
[Beta chuckles]
- [Waiter] Are you sure you
don't want any cream or sugar?
- Um, I can just use these.
- That's butter.
- You sure you
don't want anything?
- Can you, can you just
take me back to Henry's?
I wanna get my phone.
- Sure.
Now? I just got my coffee.
- Sorry.
- It's okay.
♪ I can't
♪ Sing at all
♪ For my heart
♪ Can't recall your
[Beta slurps]
- Okay, let's go.
- Thanks for not
making me say anything.
- Was there anything
you wanted to say?
- That wasn't my hitter.
- You don't have to
explain yourself to me.
[Zelda chuckles]
- And I'm not gonna
got cut myself anymore.
- I'd like it if you stopped
wanting to cut yourself, too.
[Zelda chuckles]
[Zelda sighs]
[car door slams]
- You're not gonna sleep
in here again, are you?
[chuckles]
Come on.
[warm chamber music]
[door creaks]
Henry?
He's probably at the theater.
He left us half
a bottle of wine.
- He's so nice.
- Yeah, what's wrong with him?
- I think he cares
a lot about you.
- I'm afraid I'm gonna hurt him.
- I like him, ZeeZee.
[glass clinks]
I think he's good for you.
- I mean, he's a
bigger mess than I am.
And I'm a psycho, so-
- You're not a psycho.
[Zelda chuckles]
- Everyone's a psycho.
Especially me.
[Beta chuckles]
I mean, look what I did today.
I'm sorry.
Not that it's any excuse
for Keith's behavior.
I mean, I don't care
what his motives are.
My body is not for
his inspection.
I feel like I'm
trespassing,
just by being alive.
And like the whole world is
just pinching me.
Just pinching me.
All the time.
You know?
- Oh, Zee. [chuckles]
[Zelda chuckles]
Who's going to take care of us?
[both chuckle]
I wish there was someone to...
Somebody to go to.
To...
- To what? [chuckles]
[Beta chuckles]
[Beta sighs]
- I don't know. [chuckles]
An adult.
To help us.
- But you are an adult.
[Beta chuckles]
[both chuckle]
- But I need help.
- If you need help
in this country,
you're gonna have
to take it by force.
If you wanted a family so
bad, you could've done that
20 years ago with
someone your own age.
That would've made
sense, wouldn't it?
- Yeah, that
would've been great.
[door closes]
Jesus!
- What?
- I'm sorry, Beta.
Good morning.
- Henry, you are
being so immature!
- You're probably
too young to realize
how stupid you sound right now.
[door slams]
[Zelda sighs]
- [Beta] Zelda, what's going on?
[footsteps approach]
Are you okay?
- Of course.
- You wanna talk about it?
- No.
- You want me to go?
- Still wanna get breakfast?
- Henry didn't get what he
wanted, so he threw an tantrum.
They get so offended when you
take control away from them.
- Yes, they do.
- I'm talking about
set designers.
I am hungry.
But the thought of being
in a room full of eggs
makes me wanna hang myself.
Oh, my god. [chuckles]
[bright chamber music]
- What?
- Oh, my god, Beta.
- [chuckles] What?
- Oh, my god.
- What? What are you doing?
What is happening?
- This.
- ZeeZee, is this
what I think it is?
- I found it with Dad's
coat and I completely forgot
when Keith tried to
take my batteries out.
- Oh, my god, I was too scared
to ask. Have you read it?
- No, I wanted to save it so
we could read it together.
- [squeals] ZeeZee!
- Read it again.
- Okay.
"Hello, Bobby.
I'm hoping this letter
finds you well and warm.
I once heard someone say no one
can know you like a brother.
I'm sure you will disagree.
Of course, we are all
brothers on this earth,
and I prefer to
think of it that way.
'Only people know just
how to talk to people,'
as the song goes.
However, I've never been very
good at talking to people,
and yet, nevertheless,
for some strange reason,
it remains very difficult
to find happiness alone.
Isn't that odd?
Even living in a house
of God, full of God,
surrounded by and full of God,
there is no replacement
for company.
We are compelled to share our
love of God, not hoard it.
But I did not write
you to speak of God.
I know your feelings on him.
I only wanted to say 'hello.'
Your brother, Jazz."
- What a cool fuckin'
nickname. "Jazz."
- Do you think he
ever wrote him back?
- Well, if they did reconnect,
then nobody ever
heard about it, so-
- It's sad to think
he never responded.
Is there a return address?
- No.
- What about a date?
- November 19th, 2007.
- Let me see that.
Hey, hey, hey! Look
at the postmark.
- What's that?
- Carol Stream.
- What does that mean?
- It means that Uncle
Jerry still lived here,
or in this state, anyway,
when he sent the letter.
- Chow time, ladies!
Be sure to clear your plates.
- Hey, where's that cute waiter?
- How cute?
- Real cute.
Makes you wanna twist his
dick off and smash it.
- I know who you mean, um...
Jill.
Oh, um, Will. That's it.
He went back to college.
Can you believe people
are still doing that?
- What? I like school.
[Zelda chuckles]
- You know, I don't even
know where you're going?
- Yale.
- Seriously? I didn't
know you were that smart.
- Me either.
- We should celebrate.
- We are!
Cheers.
[Zelda chuckles]
[forks clink]
[chuckles]
- Um...
Did Dad know?
- What?
- That you got into Yale?
- No.
- Well, I'm sure that
he would've been proud.
- [Waitress] How's
everything tasting?
Just like Mom used to lay?
- These eggs are so warm.
- Hey, you guys wanna
hear something crazy?
They just fired the janitor
at my family synagogue,
for hiding cameras
in the boys bathroom.
Phew!
- So what's the next step?
- To what?
- To find Jerry. Do
you have your phone?
- [Beta] It's dead.
- [sighs] Give me the letter.
See this?
- Mm-hm.
"M-O-O-S-E, moose."
- It's an acronym.
- Mm-hm, for what?
- I don't know.
[Beta chuckles]
But he said that he was in
the house of God, right?
I mean, doesn't this
look like it could be
from some new age
church or something?
- Hm, I guess so.
- Pardon me. Hi.
Sorry to bother you. Are
you having a nice meal?
- Yeah, I like it pretty good.
- I was wondering if you
could quickly tell me
whether this acronym
means anything to you.
- It certainly does.
That's the Midwest Order
of the Soul Eternal.
- [Zelda] Oh, yeah?
Is that a church?
- I guess. They had a
yard sale like a year ago.
My wife bought a blender
that we've never used.
That's all I know.
- Oh, where is it?
- [Diner] Damen and
Sunnyside. It's right-
- Thank you.
Damen and Sunnyside, you
fucking bitch. Let's go.
- [Beta] I probably
smell terrible.
- [Zelda] We are going
to a new age church
and everyone is going to
smell like an old dick.
- [Beta] Are you nervous?
What if he isn't there?
- [Zelda] He'll be there.
[gospel piano music]
♪ I feel you
♪ Calling me
- [Beta] Hello!
- Hi.
- Hello.
- [Zelda] Is this the Midwest
Order of the Soul Eternal?
- It used to be.
- Now it's just the
Midwest Order of the Soul?
- Humor's an important
tool in times of crisis,
if it's utilized properly.
- Okay.
- Uh, what is this place now?
- Today?
[sighs] It's a building.
Tomorrow, maybe a bank.
Or a jail?
- Okay.
Were you a member of the Order?
- I thought so.
Uh... I suspect I never
really had enough faith.
- [Beta] Faith is hard.
- No.
Doubt is hard.
- [Zelda] Amen.
- Are you here to buy
the bulletin board?
- No.
- I was emailing with a
girl on Craigslist today.
- [Zelda] No, sorry.
- What happened to
everybody? To the Order?
- People scatter. Things change.
The cosmic spirit seeks
not to restrain us,
but to lift us, stage by
stage, into wider spaces.
We ran out of money.
- Do you know someone by
the name of Jerry Foreman?
- Brother Jerry, of course.
- He's our uncle.
- You must be mistaken.
- Is he alive still?
- [clears throat]
As far as I know,
he works at the Heart
and Sold Piano Gallery.
But he was always very open
about not having any family.
- Uh, Heart and Sold.
Are you sure of that?
- Not really.
- [chuckles] Okay,
we'll check it out.
- Thank you so much.
- What's your name?
- I'm Brother Blake.
Tell him...
Brother Blake says "hi."
- You got it.
- Tell him, tell him, tell
him to come and see me.
- Okay.
- Tell him, I'm...
Here until the end of the month.
- Okay, we will.
Thank you, Blake.
- Sure you don't want
the bulletin board?
Five dollars.
- [chuckles] No, that's okay.
- And I could throw
in some prayers.
- [Zelda] No.
- Um, actually, is there
a phone that I could use?
- Five bucks.
I'm joking.
[Beta and Zelda laugh]
It's in the room
around the corner.
- Okay, [chuckles] thank you.
I'm gonna go check my messages.
- Take your time.
[phone keypad bleeps]
[phone rings]
- [Machine] Zero messages.
[phone clacks]
[phone keypad bleeps]
[phone rings]
- Operator.
- Hi, yes.
May I be connected to-
- What city?
- Oh, Chicago, sorry.
May I be connected to Heart
and Sold Piano Gallery?
- One moment.
[phone rings]
- Thank you.
- [Man On Phone] Heart
and Sold Piano Gallery.
- Hi! Uh, yes, may I
please speak to Jerry?
- [Man On Phone] Sure. Hold on.
[phone clacks]
[muffled chatter from radio]
- You two are sisters?
- Exactly.
- You must be the baby.
- I'm going to wait outside now.
- What did I say?
- Okay, thank you, Blake.
- [Blake] Bye bye.
[door opens]
- Hey, I just called
the piano gallery,
and he's there right now.
Where'd you get that cigarette?
- Off the ground.
- You lit a random
cigarette butt?
- It wasn't a butt.
- That's disgusting.
- Okay, let us go.
[warm chamber music]
- Wait for me!
[door closes]
[door opens]
- Is he in here?
- Shh!
- What?
- I'm looking.
- It's not for me.
- Well, who's it for?
- I told you!
For a neighbor boy.
- Well, perhaps you
can return with him
and he can help you
pick something out?
- It's a surprise! I told you!
- You wanna surprise the
neighbor boy with a piano?
- Are you deaf?
- A little, in one ear.
But I suspect your
question was rhetorical.
- Excuse me?
- I'll be with you
as soon as I can.
- Um, we're actually
looking for Jerry.
- Oh, of course.
[woman sighs]
All day long today. What
is it, his birthday?
Meg!
[woman sighs]
Go get Jerry.
My daughter.
- I have never waited for
a piano so long in my life!
- [Beta] Thank you.
- Sure.
Come, I'll show you some
other things we have.
- Let's get out of here.
- What?
- This doesn't
happen in real life.
People don't get what they want.
He doesn't wanna meet us. He
didn't even want a family.
Who are we to track him down
and force ourselves upon him?
I feel like I'm gonna puke.
- You're just scared.
- I think I preferred looking
forward to meeting him.
- Fear means you're alive
and anything that makes you
feel alive is good,
even if it's scary.
- He says to come out back.
[thuds]
[door squeaks]
- Oh, can I help you ladies?
- We were told to
come back here.
- By who?
- Um, by the girl inside.
- [chuckles] I know that.
- Oh, okay. Um, we
are looking for Jerry.
- You are?
- Yeah.
- Um, again, who told you
that Jerry would be here?
- Uh, we called.
I called, earlier.
- [Man] Why?
- Maybe we should
go back inside.
- I don't know you, right?
You here to buy a piano?
- No.
- Then what the fuck
are you doin' back here?
- We thought Jerry
was back here.
I'm sorry, we're looking
for Jerry. We'll leave.
- I'm Gerry.
- What?
- I'm Gerry!
- Oh.
Um...
We were looking
for somebody else.
- You're not here to buy weed?
[vomit splatters]
- Oh, my god!
- Nah, keep it.
- Thanks.
- You sure you're okay, ZeeZee?
- Yeah, sorry. Thank you
for cleaning that up.
- Oh, no problem.
I've never seen anything
like that before.
You just straight up
puked for no reason.
- Well, I was nervous, I guess.
- I make white girls
nervous every day.
All I have to do is leave
the house. [chuckles]
Never seen one throw
up before, though.
- Well, it wasn't
you. I promise.
- I was nervous
myself too, I guess.
I sell a little weed, you know?
The job doesn't pay that much.
See two young rich white girls
walkin' up, asking about me.
Spidey senses started tinglin'.
- We're not rich. [chuckles]
- You're white.
- Is it okay that we're
like sitting here?
I mean, do you have
to get back to work?
- Oh, no, no, it's cool.
Nobody buys pianos.
- What was on that truck?
- Weed.
[all chuckle]
- [Beta] Well, I
guess we should go.
- So who are you
guys looking for?
- [Beta] Oh, someone told
us our uncle works here.
- You don't know how
to find your uncle?
His name's Gerry?
- Yeah.
- Nah, nah. I'm definitely the
only Gerry that works here.
It's pretty much
just Richard and me.
And Meg, if you
wanna count bodies.
- Definitely nobody else?
- Nobody else.
[door closes]
- At least we had fun.
- Ladies, ladies.
I'm going to a party later
on at a buddy's house.
You should come with.
Have a couple of drinks.
Still goin', what, Honore and
Wellington, in Lakeview.
- I don't wanna play beer pong.
- Just take my number, you know?
You never know what you're
gonna need in the future.
- Well, I don't have
a phone. [chuckles]
- Mine's dead.
- You don't have
to use the number
if you don't want it, okay?
But at least just take it!
Have some respect for
my feelings, okay?
- I'll tell you what. Here.
Okay, it's right there.
Write your number on my hand.
That way, when I
masturbate tonight,
I can smear it all
over my vagina.
- Wow. [chuckles]
You know what? You crazy, man.
I wasn't expecting that.
- And you can keep the pen.
- Oh, I can? Thank
you, I'll keep the pen.
- [Zelda] Mm-hm.
- You just don't forget
to masturbate tonight.
- I won't.
- My god.
- Have a good day, ladies.
[Beta sighs]
[Zelda and Gerry chuckle]
Oh!
We do have someone
else that works here.
It's an old guy that
comes in after we close.
He cleans the pianos,
tunes the pianos.
But his name is Jazz.
Oh, come to the party if
you feel like puking again.
[Zelda chuckles]
[car door slams]
[car starts]
- I doubt he comes every night.
- Gross.
- How long do we sit
here until we decide
that he's not gonna show up?
- I have a lot of places
to avoid going back to.
- I might go to the
store and get a cookie.
- Will you get me an Advil?
- Yeah, you have any money?
- No.
- Okay. [chuckles]
Anything happens, just slam
your head against the car horn.
- Roger.
[car door slams]
[melancholy music]
♪ Blue-Eyed baby
♪ Cries in a cradle
♪ Mama said to Papa
♪ Look at them eyes
[purse unzips]
♪ Over the ocean
♪ In a great ship
[knife flicks]
♪ The captain said
to the cabin boy ♪
[lighter flicks]
♪ Look at that water
♪ And in high places
♪ In the Rockies
♪ I said to Carl
♪ Look at that valley
- Shit.
[lighter flicks]
♪ Oh, yes
[Zelda gasps]
- Ouch, ouch.
♪ The gardener is gracious
♪ His son is so kind
♪ The lips of his
that I've kissed ♪
♪ On the wheel of time
- Were you ever gonna come home?
Answer me, please.
[scoffs]
What about all your stuff?
Should I just throw it away?
- I don't care.
- Yeah, I don't care either.
For a little while, I did. I
was really worried about you.
But then it morphed into
frustration and then anger
and now I'm just like
you, I don't care.
I don't care what
you've been doing,
where you've been or whose
bed you've been sleeping in.
- Okay.
- Don't walk away from me.
I'm talking to you.
- I can do whatever I want.
- [scoffs] Yeah,
and you have been.
And I hope it's been awesome,
but after this moment right now,
you're never going
to see me again.
So can you stop acting so
fucking forlorn and selfish
for just one minute and
let me say my piece?
Then you can run off
to whoever's heart you
plan to step on next.
- I'm not going to be
running off to anyone,
because I haven't
been with anyone.
Not that it's any
of your business.
It's also none of your
business that my dad died,
or that my sister's been
cutting herself again,
or that she lives in a boarding
house, or that we've been
completely removed from
any family we have left,
and that instead of
returning to the paranoid,
possessive oppression
that is your love,
I've been sleeping in my car
like some kind of fugitive.
- Your dad died?
When?
- You don't care!
Remember?
I might as well
be a stolen bike,
for all our separation
means to you.
- That's not fair, you don't
know what it means to me
because you haven't been around.
- I was around for a long time.
- And was it so bad?
What did I do to
you that was so bad?
I never yelled at you, I
never told you what to do.
I never hit you!
- [Beta] Is not hitting me
supposed to be a selling point?
- A lot of women do get hit!
That might seem
inconceivable to you,
because your life hasn't
contained that kind of violence.
Nevertheless, it happens a lot.
If you were more open-minded,
you might realize how
fortunate you are.
- If I were you, I wouldn't
mention any of that
on your OkCupid profile.
[Grant chuckles]
- Okay.
Okay.
I sound like an
asshole. I'm aware.
- I have to go.
- Come home with me.
- Grant.
- I don't wanna end
things like this.
- And yet, this is
how they're ending.
- Let's not make this
our goodbye fighting
in a parking lot.
I just want one
nice night together.
- No.
- Why not?
You're leavin' anyway.
I'm not gonna lock
you up. [chuckles]
Still let you go to school.
- Thanks for your generosity.
[Grant chuckles]
But, uh, I think I'll
leave prison now,
rather than suck the
warden's dick one last time.
- Fuck you!
[Beta scoffs]
I'm sorry!
[Beta sighs]
[car door dings rhythmically]
[car door slams]
- Oh, my god.
[car doors slam]
[door rattles]
Zelda?
Zelda!
Zelda.
Zelda?
[sighs]
Zelda!
[trash can rattles and clatters]
- What're you doing back there?
Are you gonna stand
up and show yourself?
Or should I go inside
and call the police?
- I'm, I'm going to stand up.
- I was expecting a lower voice.
I have to admit.
- Sorry.
- Yeah.
- I was looking for my sister.
- Uh, she wasn't
in the trash can?
- [Beta] [chuckles] No.
- Is that your car out front?
- [Beta] Yes.
- If your sister was the young
lady who was in that car,
then she got out
and caught a bus.
- What?
- Yeah!
The same one I take.
- That...
Doesn't make any sense.
- Well, neither does you,
rolling around in
the trash out here!
- Well, it made
sense at the time.
- Are you all right?
- I'm Beta.
- Say again?
- I'm...
Beta. Your niece.
- Oh.
Well, I don't to my
knowledge have a niece.
- You have two nieces.
And I'm one of them.
- I should get back inside.
I think you're mistaken.
- Your name is Jazz and your
brother was Robert Foreman.
Correct?
- What do you mean, "was?"
- Can I give you a ride home?
[car door opens]
[Jerry sighs]
[car door closes]
- 300 North State Street.
Do you know where that is?
- Yes.
[Jerry sighs]
- That's where I live.
[moody soft rock music]
[car starts]
♪ Have you seen my lover
with the long blonde hair ♪
♪ Everything we did
just went so wrong ♪
♪ Last time that I saw her,
she was standing near ♪
♪ Now I've come to
wonder where she's gone ♪
♪ Where she's gone, oh,
where she's gone, oh ♪
♪ Now I've come to
wonder where she's gone ♪
♪ And have you seen my mother
♪ She's out looking
for my father ♪
♪ Didn't think that
she'd be gone this long ♪
♪ He's gone where you can't go
but I let her have her fun ♪
♪ Now I've come to
wonder where she's gone ♪
♪ Where she's gone, oh,
where she's gone, oh ♪
♪ Now I've come to
wonder where she's gone ♪
♪ And what about my sister,
she looks just like me ♪
♪ Looking into her
is like a mirror ♪
♪ And when we were young,
we weren't two but one ♪
♪ Sometimes I come to
wonder where she's gone ♪
♪ Where she's gone, oh
♪ Where she's gone
- It's tough to find
parking around here.
- Am I looking for a spot?
- [gasps] There's one.
- Oh, should I take it?
- I think you'd better.
♪ Over my head
♪ Don't believe
what they told you ♪
- Would you like to come up?
♪ Believe what you heard
- I would love to.
♪ Oh, what I said
- Then it's our lucky day.
[door creaks]
[sighs]
[hums]
[footsteps clack]
I have no visitors. That's
why there's no furniture.
- Is that a harpsichord?
- [Jerry] I built it.
- No.
- Uh-huh.
Don't get too excited. I
didn't do a very good job.
- It's still very impressive.
- [Jerry] The view
is impressive.
Go on out.
Take a look.
[high harpsichord note]
[distant horns honk]
[traffic hums]
So, Bobby had girls?
- Zelda and me.
- He must've been getting
up there when he had you.
What are you, uh...
- Uh, I'm 25.
Zelda's 23.
- And your mother is...
Jane.
- Well, no.
[chuckles] God, no.
- [chuckles] Oh?
- Yeah.
We don't really get
along with Jane.
- Ah, so, um, who's your mother?
- Mona.
Um...
Dad left Jane and had an affair.
You might know some of this.
Prolonged affair with my mother,
which resulted in me
and Zelda, and um,
they split after a few years
and he went back to Jane.
- I see.
- And then eventually
they split, too.
- And where...
Where is Mona now?
- I don't really know.
- Uh-huh.
- She travels a lot.
So, Mexico, maybe?
[both chuckle]
She's a free spirit,
I guess you could say.
- So, it's just you
and your sister, then?
- Yeah, I suppose so.
Except, I'm going to
grad school tomorrow.
- Good for you.
- But I'm nervous
about leaving Zelda.
She's having a hard
time. She needs somebody.
She's struggling.
- [sighs] Those who are
not struggling are dead.
[chuckles]
I take it we can add
your father to that list?
- Yeah.
- How?
- He killed himself.
- Aww.
- Dad included you in the will,
but everybody
thinks you're dead.
- He did? [chuckles]
- Yeah.
There's, um, there's not
much, with the medical bills.
- Mm.
- It's more of a
gesture, it seems.
- I don't know what
to make of that.
- Why'd you disappear?
- I'm right here.
- I know, but-
- It doesn't matter.
For a while, I thought
you could help people,
but you can't help anyone.
Relying on other people
to help you is...
[sighs]
[chuckles]
Only God can help you
and that's the truth.
- Do you believe in that?
- It doesn't matter what
anyone thinks of you.
Stay in touch, lose
touch, whatever.
I get in touch with God
and that's all there is.
He will help you.
- He will?
- Of course.
- How?
- God can change your life
by believing in him, because,
you see...
He is, [sighs]
the belief in him.
Positive thinking.
Those who believe in
God are helped by God,
in that they are helped
by their belief in him.
- So, you just believe in
what you know isn't true?
- What difference does it
make? It's all a dream anyway.
"Merrily, merrily,
merrily," as the song goes.
- And you feel you're happy?
- I'm happy to
have met you, Beta.
- Me too.
You have no idea.
I just wish Zelda was here, too.
[chuckles]
You'd like her.
- [Jerry] Mm.
- I should probably
try and find her.
I don't wanna go, but
I'm getting worried.
- Oh, okay.
- But maybe we can come back
tomorrow morning before we go?
She really wants
to meet you, too.
- I don't think so.
- Not a good time?
Huh.
- This was a nice
treat, I feel satisfied.
- Okay.
Do you...
Can we exchange phone
numbers, so I can call you?
- I shall carry you with me,
and you should feel
free to do the same.
That's probably the
best way to leave it.
- Okay.
Um...
Well, we can always find you
at the piano store, I guess.
- I'd rather you not.
- [Beta] What do you mean?
- I have a very
comfortable routine.
This has been an
exception to that.
- But...
I wanna have a
relationship with you.
- This is the only
relationship you need.
Look to him.
Like I do.
[brooding chamber music]
[door creaks]
[door closes]
- Beta!
- Hey, Henry.
Sorry to show up like this.
- Is Zelda with you?
- [Beta] She's not here?
- No, [moans] I got
excited when I saw ya.
- I'm looking for her, too.
[Henry sighs]
You shaved.
- [Henry] I had a job interview.
- Oh, yeah? How'd it go?
- Not well.
Sit down, have a drink.
- I should go.
I'm gonna go see
if she went home.
- Did she go to the clinic?
- [Beta] The clinic?
- Yeah, she left her phone here
so I have no way of knowing.
- Um, as far as I
know, she didn't, but-
- Hey, tell her not to. If you
find her, tell her not to go.
Or if she's gonna go, at
least let me go with her.
I'll go with her, if
that's what she wants,
but I hope she doesn't go.
- Henry, is Zelda pregnant?
- [Henry] Yeah. You
didn't know that?
- No.
- Oh. [sighs]
I'm such an idiot.
I'm an idiot. [scoffs]
No wonder she doesn't want it.
The only reason I want it
is because it's my
child, and I'm me.
If I was anybody else,
I'd run away too.
I'm drunk.
- [Beta] It's okay.
- If I don't have a kid soon,
there's gonna be no
one to take care of me.
Yeah and I can't raise a kid
in this shit hole anyway.
- I have to go.
- [Henry] [sighs] Wake me
up when you get back, okay?
- Okay.
[Henry sighs]
[lively blues music]
♪ I used to wander
when the sun go down ♪
♪ Looking for my baby but my
baby ain't nowhere around ♪
♪ Screaming and crying
♪ Asking everybody oh I
wonder where did my baby go ♪
- [Zelda] I would like it if
you would go away from me.
- [Beta] What do you mean?
- I mean I'm having a good time
and I would like to
keep it that way.
- Why did you leave
me at the piano store?
- See? That's what I'm
talking about, just-
- Henry told me what's going on.
- Beta, you get outta here!
I don't wanna fucking
talk to you about that.
- What are you doing here?
Let me take you home.
- Gerry's coming to get
me and he's gonna take me,
so you're relieved
of your duties, okay?
- Who?
- Gerry from the piano store.
- Let me take you home.
[Zelda chuckles]
- Gerry and I are going
to another party first,
and then he's gonna take
me home in the morning.
[car approaches]
- If you don't let
me take you home,
I am going to drive
to your place anyway
and sit on the street until
I know that you're safe!
- Whatever you want.
[lively blues music]
[car door slams]
[door closes]
- I don't like when I wake
up and you're not there.
- I'm worried.
- She's a grown woman.
I'm sure she's fine.
- Certainty is foolish and
she is hardly a grown woman.
- She's young and that's
what young people do.
- Not come home for three days?
- Sometimes.
I had a few wild
weekends myself.
- [Olive] Oh, really?
- Anyway, she's not
your responsibility.
Olive, she's your tenant, and
she doesn't even pay rent!
- Well, whose
responsibility is she, then?
[melancholy folk music]
♪ One morning I rambled
♪ Down by the sea shore
♪ And the wind it did whistle
♪ And the water did roar
♪ I heard some fair maiden
♪ Give a pitiful cry
♪ And it sounded so lonely
♪ It swept oh so high
♪ Said William to Molly
♪ If you will agree
♪ To give your consent, love
♪ To marry me
♪ My mind is to marry
♪ And never to part
♪ For the first time I saw you
♪ You wounded my heart
♪ Go away from me, William
♪ And leave me alone
♪ For I'm just a poor girl
♪ And a long way from home
♪ I never will marry
♪ I'll be no man's wife
♪ I intend to live single
♪ All the days of my life
♪ These shells in the ocean
♪ Shall be my death bed
♪ While the fish
in deep waters ♪
♪ Swim over my head
♪ She cast her fair body
♪ In the water so deep
♪ And she closed
pretty blue eyes ♪
♪ Forever to sleep
♪ I never will marry
♪ I'll be no man's wife
♪ I intend to live single
♪ All the days
♪ Of
♪ My
♪ Life