Deployment orders.
Origin: Titan moon base and
Cryo interment facility.
Destination: Cape Canaveral AFS Earth.
Escort transport of
insurrectionist Python Diamond
for sentencing proceedings
before the court
of supreme justice.
Be advised that the prisoner has a history
of violent behavior.
So that's Python Diamond.
Doesn't look so dangerous to me.
Nobody looks
dangerous and conscious, rookie.
Shuttle's ready for departure, sir.
We just need our cargo.
How was he?
Vitals are stable and he started to show
increasing neurofunctions.
He should be back with us momentarily.
That's a pity.
I still don't like this.
Excuse me?
After all we went through
to capture this man,
after how many soldiers
killed, after Baltimore
we're shipping him back to Earth?
Be on ice 'till the sun burns up.
It's not your call, Uxbridge.
Order was for five years.
No less by some miraculous circumstance.
You got your communications
geared back up and running.
I haven't heard differently.
Now once you're in closer
the shuttle comm unit
should work.
Just make sure you send up
some parts on the resupply.
Yes, sir.
Godspeed.
Oh, welcome back, Diamond.
Why won't my legs move?
Five years in Cryo could take its toll.
Oh, hey captain, good to see you again.
It's major.
Really?
Congratulations.
Load him up.
Wait.
I'm glad you remember Major Uxbridge here
'cause he's gonna be overseeing
your trip back to Earth
for sentencing.
I can't wait.
And of a personal note, Diamond,
I'm glad to see you go.
Cryo was too good for you.
No, I wanna watch your life tick away
in the confines of a cell.
You lash out all you want, Diamond.
You've got four months.
Four months to watch Earth get closer,
four months to watch your last
seconds of sunlight dwindle.
And if you're very
lucky, you might not have
an accident on the way.
I have a hunch my
luck won't be that good.
Believe it!
Major Uxbridge!
Sorry, sir!
No need to apologize.
I didn't see anything.
Anybody else see anything Major Uxbridge
need to apologize for?
No, sir.
Not me.
I can't say I did, general.
You see, no need to apologize.
Now get this man off my moon.
All right, you heard the general,
load him up and move him out.
Thank you, sir.
Absolutely.
Scott, enjoy your vacation.
I'll see you in 16 months.
Oh, I hear they've got a
great fettuccini Alfredo
where you're going, enjoy.
Thank you, sir.
Got any three's?
Go fish.
Eight.
Fuck you, lieutenant!
Even this flight's not that long, kid.
Oh honey, please.
Edwards, where's the major?
He's in the back with Diamond.
You want to disturb them, it's your call.
Right.
Maybe you should come take
a look at this instead.
For a man with your
mouth, you don't say much.
Well, if you ask better questions.
Seriously, you don't get bored of this?
And every day the last week
you're just throwing that left
like it's gonna change something.
I need to know what's
your insurgent buddies
have plan for our return!
Whatever useful
information is in your head
is coming out one way or another.
And is it hitting me in
the head counterproductive?
What if you give me a
concussion I forget something?
Yeah, that's much better.
We caught those comrades
of yours, you know.
Most of them tried to resist arrest.
So if you have some idea that
all you have to do is last
until your compatriots can break you out
now that you're Earth
bound again, too bad.
If you had all of them, you wouldn't
be asking me questions.
Look, Scott, do you mind
if I call you Scott?
Look, Scott, it's been fun this whole
punch-me-taunt-you
thing that we have going
but I'm getting bored.
So either you find yourself new questions
or you don't get another word, all right?
Major.
You made contact with control?
Not exactly.
You need to see this.
What is it, Drake?
Take a look at this, sir.
That's impossible.
That explains the silence.
No lights.
Anywhere on the planet?
They have in view.
The scanners can't reach the far side.
Still nothing.
I mean that's--
Impossible, yes.
We need to get closer.
Glass, I want you to stay here
and monitor the situation.
Edwards, Drake with me.
No, I don't wanna go school time, mom.
Yeah, rise and shine, buttercup.
We got trouble.
It appears we are returning to a world
somewhat unlike what we left.
Between communications blackout
and the lack of any major power readings
I have to presume that a catastrophe
of unparalleled proportion
struck while we were in transit.
The nature of which is uncertain.
What we need to do now
is an atmospheric pass.
Scan for anything that might give us clues
or lead us to people.
Wait, we left and the world died?
So it would seem.
Well, shit!
I told you I was important, serg.
This isn't a joke, Quinn.
Gather your gear and
give it a combat check.
We could have boots on the ground
20 minutes after aero braking.
Yes, lieutenant.
Yes, ma'am.
Sir, what about the con?
Something's wrong.
Yes, no communications.
And even stranger there's
no power signatures
over the Western Hemisphere.
We'll be making combat recon
after our initial flyby,
get some hands on intel.
We is an interesting choice of words.
We're on the move the
second we touch down.
I don't wanna spare a single
soldier guarding you here.
You help us with this, maybe
I put in a word for you.
Which means what,
that they won't kill me?
Or that they will?
You want a single solitary comfort
for the rest of your days?
This is your only chance, convict.
Okay, I'll be right behind you.
Do I get a gun?
The only guns you get to
see will be at your back.
You're taking point.
Well, that's a lucky
gift towards in the mouth
but that sounds shitty.
What else you got?
You've infiltrated places
we thought were unbreakable.
You saying you lost your nerve?
Melting the walls of the Silver Cape
to spring political dissidents
was a public service
and well worth the effort.
This?
Between the soldiers you slaughtered
and the innocents in
Baltimore you're lucky
I'm not solving my problems
by splattering the walls
of this cell with your brain.
That's option B.
That is option B.
Why didn't you say so?
Let's go see how fucked up the world is.
Pretty fucked up, sir.
Structural damage is heavy.
We've got multiple airstrikes against
most major metropolitan areas.
And there's fires burning
in forests across the globe.
This is insane.
Yeah, well that's not all.
Sensors are showing doses of
radiation in the atmosphere.
I mean nothing at dangerous levels,
but it's pretty widespread.
It's what I'd expect of the
aftermath of a nuclear fallout.
You call me a sociopath
and you all nuked the planet?
But the levels are safe.
On the Western Hemisphere.
On the Eastern Hemisphere,
I'd be surprised
if cockroaches didn't have five heads.
So that only leaves a
question of where we search.
Even at this close we're not getting
any serious energy signatures.
I mean most of it could
easily be incidental readings,
but there's definitely
a couple major hotspots.
Course for the closest
and we'll take a look.
Okay, we'll be there in five minutes.
All right people, check your packs.
Travel light but any
protective gear we're wearing.
No knowing what we're
running to down there.
All right then, don't talk.
Boss, boss!
Hey, boss, boss!
What is it?
You better come see, Gazeebo.
Look!
Well, fuck my monkey.
That's a military shuttle.
Rag, Tag, get the boys together.
We're hunting nine jockeys tonight.
Whoo-hee!
Instruments indicated the
power signature subterranean.
It must be a basement of some kind.
A fallout shelter?
Not a lot of cover
coming towards the doors.
We aren't using the door.
Why not?
Because you watch a door
and trap a door.
We don't know who's in there.
We don't give them the first move.
It's the ingress that
allows its field to fire.
Let us use five guns effectively.
Against how many of theirs?
Concentrating on your force is great,
knowing where to
concentrate them is better.
The shuttle's locked up tight, sir.
No ones getting in without the key codes.
How are we doing this?
We aren't, I am.
Give me a flash bang and a cutter.
I'll bust their home when
they aren't expecting,
scatter around, get the
door open when it's safe.
Major?
Get us in.
If you make me regret my
choice, I can always shoot you.
Not in the chest though, progress.
Quinn, follow him.
Keep an eye on him.
If he tries anything shoot him.
Yes, sir.
Quinn.
Sir?
In the head.
Permission to speak freely, sir?
Of course, Edwards.
Is this really a good idea?
You have your doubts?
Frankly, sir, I don't
know what use he'll be.
He's no soldier, he's just a terrorist.
Sometimes you forget you all joined up
since the rebellion was broken.
You've never seen him in action.
You've never found his
insurgence waiting for you
inside secure facilities.
You never had the gem cutters rise up
from the ground itself like ghosts.
He's a superb asset, but
a lousy excuse for a man.
Do I trust him?
Never.
But as long as we've landed
on a world we don't recognize
I will make use of him.
He's good at this.
It's what he does.
And make no mistake, if
he endangers any of us
I will put a bullet between his eyes.
I might just do it for the satisfaction
once we figure out what
the hell happened here.
Major!
Move, move!
Hey everyone, say hello to Wren.
Wren, this is Scott but he
likes to be called Admiral--
What the hell are you doing?
Getting myself a gun.
You said you aren't gonna give me one.
Wren here was nice enough
to oblige me though.
Weren't you, Wren?
Yes, Jesus fuck, yes.
Hey, Scott, watch this.
Wren, how many people are downstairs?
There's nine, no, wait, I'm up here
so that means there's eight
down here, eight people.
I swear to God.
That's how you interrogate.
Wren, kindly show us the way downstairs?
Okay.
I gotta admit, that was pretty slick.
He's just getting started.
Any traps, Wren?
Thank you.
You've been very helpful.
I don't like this, it's too confined.
It's the only way down and
we wanna talk to these people.
So this is the only way down, right?
See, only way.
Unless you got shovels in a couple of days
or a mow machine.
You don't have one of those, right?
The only way you're
getting a molecular excavator
is over my dead body, Diamond.
Oh, Scott, don't be so formal.
Just call me Python.
Python?
Python Diamond?
You're him, you're the, wow!
Just wow.
Always nice to meet a fan.
I hope you know what you're doing.
He knows what he's doing.
And if he doesn't, he's first in line,
him getting shot give
us plenty of warning.
It's a goddamn maze down here.
And you're sure you
know where you're going?
Oh yeah, these tunnels
run on the whole complex
but I know 'em like the back of my hand.
Been here about four months now.
You gotta find your privacy.
So, Wren, what are we
gonna find behind the door?
Just like I said, there's nine of us.
With the folks, my wife,
sister's lab and all.
It's tight.
Kathy's been trying to make it nice.
No one's got their own room or anything
but it's okay, we're kind of a cozy bunch.
Oh, you sure got friendly in a hurry.
It's not every day
you meet a genuine hero.
Wren, is there some chance
that they knew we were coming?
Yeah, we saw you... upstairs.
That's why I went up in the first place--
Okay, okay, that's
really the sort of thing
you need to mention earlier.
Drake, Quinn, grenades around the corner
No, give me a flash bang!
Not on your life.
Fuck it!
Quinn!
Eyes!
You should put that thing
down before you get hurt.
Clear!
Hey Josh.
Hey Wren.
Josh huh, nice to meet you.
I just got here from Saturn.
Take me to your leader.
Well, you already
met Josh and Ryan here.
This here is my wife
Kathy and her sister Lucy.
Good afternoon.
And that's Vic and Gwen over there and,
don't mind them, they're a little sullen
since the world ended and there's no more
that they've never had to do without.
Somewhere behind that curtain there is--
Michael Thurber, star
of stage and screen.
Mayhaps you've heard of me.
No.
I played Willie Thauman, Richard III,
Reb Tevye...
Maybe you saw "The Night
the Japs Attacked".
Can't say that I have.
Well, he was very good in it.
Yes, he was.
Kathy, honey, this is, I'm sorry.
Major Uxbridge, ma'am.
Lieutenant Edwards, Sergeant Drake,
Privates Quinn and Glass.
And this here--
Who's she?
Oh who, Meg?
Don't mind her, she's--
Are you here to see the dragon?
Meg, honey, not now.
But the walls are
soft, they're too soft.
He needs to get out.
She has her good days.
It's sad really, she was a prodigy,
brilliant in chemistry and biology.
We could really use her now.
Ma'am, what happened here?
Well, the world ended.
That much we know.
Nobody really knows what
happened, at least none of us do.
A couple nuclear bombs went
off halfway around the world.
Some people suspect it was terrorists
because they all went
off at the same time.
But me, personally, I think
it was one of them governments
had a secret nuke program
that screwed the pooch.
No matter, once they went
off nobody could live
in that side of the world so
they all decided to come here.
The Western Hemisphere couldn't
house all of the refugees
and some of them had
been so badly irradiated
and carrying mutated viral strains
that they would've infected
the people around them.
Turning them away led to some backlash
from the world community.
Oh backlash is such a mild term.
It was an invasion,
an invasion by desperate forces.
It turned them back though.
Oh yeah, they took out
a city here and there
but we pushed them out
through sheer force of will.
That's when, well.
That's when some punk ass bitch decided
if we can't have it, nobody can.
A suitcase bombed us
back to the Stone Age.
Yeah, thanks for that douche bags.
Oh smoke a ball, jackass.
What, you wanna go?
Yes, yes, I do.
Will you two mutton chops cut it out?
All that blustering for nothing, please.
At any rate, Josh, Ryan, Meg and I
had been finding ways to
reverse the radiation damage
in the refugees when the
second round of bombs went off.
We knew Wren had a shelter
so we hid there for a while,
but it just, it got too
cramped so we found a new place
once the radiation levels
had dropped enough.
We retrofitted this
place to work as a lab
so we can continue trying
the fix the damage.
The damage?
You all seem okay.
Yeah, sure, externally we got lucky
but internally, well.
Humanity's pretty screwed.
Even those of us who are in shelters
for the actual blast,
as near as we can tell,
the radiation affected
the viability of 99%
of human reproductive cells.
We're probably the last generation.
Wait, everyone's infertile?
Everyone we've tested,
at least a thousand samples
going back to our work with the refugees.
Last men on Earth, huh?
Fuck yeah!
Just me, you and the major, Diamond,
how do you like that?
What about me?
You don't count, Drake.
You're, well, funny.
I'm bisexual, jackass!
Really?
Yes.
And how do you not know that?
Hey, don't--
Shut up!
Diamond?
Oh damn.
That's right, the one and only Python.
No shit!
Oh, Josh, I got punched
out by Python Diamond.
The insurrectionist?
Been called worse.
The stones ought to come
in but they shouldn't.
They need to leave.
Meg, honey, what did we say about that?
Give me the mirror.
But I can see the shining in it.
I'm shining in it.
I'll find you one
that isn't broken, okay?
Okay.
Josh, why don't you go
see who's at the door?
Oh, Kathy rig things
so a doorbells plays
when the motion sensors go off.
I told you it was homey.
Are you really Python Diamond?
That's what they tell me.
Peach?
Guys, come take a cool.
I take it they're not the neighbors.
As unfortunate as it may sound,
they are indeed the neighbors.
They found us.
Son of a bitch, they found us.
It looks like they're inside.
So we're going in after 'em.
Well, that all depends.
On what?
On if they are fucking stupid or not.
For now, we lock it down.
When Silver gets here
or if they make a play
plans will change.
Take some of the boys.
Put eyes all around the building.
No one gets in or out
unless I say so, got it?
Got it.
Good boy, Ollie.
These guys come sniffing
around every once a while
trying to collect food and supplies.
Two months ago they found someone,
who's another scavenger.
He had a canned food and a shopping cart,
he was collecting scrap.
They left with his food,
his cart and his skin.
Edwards, get the squad ready to move.
Numbers like that, I'd
rather not risk an assault
so our next move will be
establishing communications
but I want us ready to punch
through them if we need to.
Wait, wait, wait, hold
your horses there, commodore.
You're just gonna leave us here?
We don't know what'll happen next.
I'm simply taking precautions.
This can't be a coincidence, Uxbridge.
They followed us.
We have an obligation--
My obligation is to
my men in this uniform.
Your obligation is to make me not regret
the current cohesiveness of your skull!
Private Glass, you keep this prisoner here
along with the civilians.
Edwards, Drake, Quinn, gear up.
You'll be covering me during negotiations.
They're here for us, they won't know
there are others hiding.
Permission to speak freely, sir.
Denied.
What's stopping them from
shooting you in the head?
My helmet.
You have your orders, private.
Uh sir?
What?
We found some gear
on some dead riot cops
when we moved in here.
Maybe you could use a shield.
Oh yeah, that's a great fucking idea.
Ranger Rick and the Starship Troopers
are gonna save the fucking day, right?
Bullshit!
All right, tight formation
on the other side of this door.
Move!
You wish you were out there, don't you?
Well, look at this.
Whom among you should
I be speaking with?
Well, I guess that'll be me.
Folks around here call me Gazeebo.
As leader of this unlawful gathering,
I ask that you all disperse
before any violence become--
Unlawful gathering?
Hell, don't you need laws
for something to be unlawful?
I swear, you think they
didn't steal you iron jockeys
with some common fuckin' sense
of that academy of yours.
By virtue of the martial
law instituted on--
Oh save it!
Really, that's your line here?
Not we have the guns
and we have the trainin'
and all you got is corpses
that ain't stop breathin' yet.
Seriously, which one of us do you think
considers you anything but a pompous man
trying to throw around weight
that you just don't have?
Now that you've mentioned
it, we do have the guns,
we do have the training and all you have--
And all we have are
exploding fucking arrows
in vastly superior numbers.
I'm guessing the people
you got stashed down there
aren't fighters, given I ain't seen
hide nor hair in these past months.
So you got what, the four
you and one or two more
down there minding the sheeple?
Downstairs, I don't know
what you're talking about.
Sure you don't.
That shuttle of yours, an
argo military class transport,
standard crew of three, possible transport
for a maximum of eight, six
for interplanetary transit
which if you're talking martial
law with a straight face,
is abso-fucking-lutely where
you've been these past months.
That means you got back
to a world gone to hell
and I'm bettin' you went
straight for the first evidence
of people you found.
This is your last chance to disperse
without losing any of your people.
And this is your only
chance not to wind up dead,
you insufferably egomaniacal prick!
You walk us in, you hand
us 80% of your rations,
100% of your guns and you all can eat
the last of your fig mutants in piece.
You cross me and things get bloody.
They get bloody for you.
This is not gonna end well.
Damn it!
We have what, two rifles and a shotgun?
That's about it, yeah.
I'm coming, too.
Okay.
Oh Josh, Wren, you guys come with me.
I have a bet we're gonna need
all firepower we can get.
What about me?
You have a concussion.
I'm not putting you in harm's
way if we can avoid it.
Let's hope it doesn't come to that.
Anyone else use a gun?
I can.
Let's move.
Okay, be serious.
You even like this guy?
You wanna die for this guy?
Because if you come over
this side of the line
we take care of each other.
Seriously, it's like a
commune but with more vibes.
Plus, you get to call yourself
a pirate and chicks dig that.
We're not pirates, we're soldiers.
And if you try to take this building
you'll find out exactly what that means.
All that means is that
you have things I want.
I got her.
No, I got her.
Inside!
Drake!
No, back in the warehouse!
We are fucked!
Come on.
Quinn, find something
to brace the door with.
Move.
Move!
I'm sorry, sir.
For what?
I won't be much help in the fight.
I can't feel my fingers.
We're gonna have Glass take
a look at you, fix you up.
Don't you worry.
I found something.
Give me a hand over here.
Go help Quinn, sir.
Well, when you're right, you're right.
No sense waiting when
they're on the ropes.
I guess Silver is just gonna miss the fun.
Rag, Tag.
Hurry up!
I'm all right, sir.
The fuck you are, lieutenant.
Shit, shit, shit, this is bad!
We gotta get her over the bunker.
We have to stop this bleeding, sir.
We can't move her like this.
I'm fine!
Quinn--
You're killing yourself, Holly.
I know how this looks,
lieutenant, but I promise--
What--
Not even a thing.
Cock sucker!
Quinn.
Quinn!
Come on, come on.
Downstairs, come on.
Go, go, go!
You're supposed to aim for the girl.
You were supposed to aim for the girl.
All right, come on.
Wren, give me the shotgun.
Get Uxbridge and Lucy back to the bunker.
You got it, kid.
Come on, little miss.
Josh.
I know, go.
Look, I don't think they're
stupid enough to follow us
but if they are we can funnel them
straight into our crosshairs.
Edwards is still alive up there.
No, she's not, Quinn.
She is, Lindsey.
If she was, she's not anymore.
You're a soldier, Quinn, get it together.
Now find cover and get ready.
Clear, boss.
Well, you don't look
like..., do you?
I've patched my share of holes, you know.
Start talking, maybe I'd do what I can.
Well, iron jockey..., ain't you?
Figures.
I found a way down, boss.
Yup, just waiting on you.
You wanna go dig them out?
Nah.
But we gotta 'em on run, boss.
On the run.
You got 'em cornered you gotta 'em hurt.
That's when people get dangerous.
I'm not sending people down the entrance
they fucking led us too.
Smells like strap all day long.
We got number, boss.
It smells like food in our bellies.
Yeah, and some of the boys
had been eating so good lately.
They wouldn't be eating at
all if they weren't weirdoes.
They can wait until tonight.
That when we bust in.
That's when Silver gets here.
Does it feel like no
one's coming to anyone else?
We should pull back.
Uxbridge will know what to do next.
They are pushing the offensive just yet,
so regrouping's the right move.
Let's go.
Your soldiers have a lot
of faith in you, Uxbridge.
Be it for trolls and
unicorns, not soldiers.
Wren, take busy.
Watch the wall, okay?
Shot if anyone's coming.
Yes, sir.
Yeah, your boy here took
quite a hit to the head.
Lucy said he's gonna be all right though.
Well, he's not my boy, so whatever.
Oh, you heartless bastard!
There was a metal bat
that they hit him with!
He is lucky to remember his name.
I don't think you realize
the level of irony you're--
I should've shot you in
the head, let you in the ship
because you're the best
lieutenant I ever noticed
in the hands of those--
Enough!
Hey, I got you and Quinn out of an ambush
you willingly you walked into
because you are stupid enough to think
that this uniform somehow
makes you invincible.
All right, three people are dead!
She wants to be mad at me
'cause of Josh, that's fine.
It was my call to bring him
but you got your men killed
and if I could trade you for them I would.
I am not pissed because of Josh!
He and I both came with you, remember?
If these soldiers die, we lose
our only chance of survival.
Look, Josh was my fault, but this prick
he doesn't get to blame me for anything!
Damn straight--
Holly damn, beat them down.
For... sakes!
Can we stop arguing
about who's fault it is!
Just mind the present, if you...
The issue I had is chain of command.
No, it isn't.
Issue at hand is staying alive.
Ryan, you got any movement outside?
What on Earth is that?
That's not something you see every day.
The fox was in with the chickens
but it's back to the
bands stand with her now.
Fly with home birds.
Meg, honey, eat your cereal.
Okay.
Where did she get the ammunition?
The shit does it matter?
It matters.
Look, if they're
getting additional weapons
they might be prepping a push.
That hatch is the only way down, right?
Yes.
Okay, is it too much to
hope that we have cameras
inside the warehouse.
We had to scavenge them to
get the exteriors working.
Line on in the interior, okay.
Look, we'll keep eyes on the tunnels,
give a warning if they try anything.
In the meantime everyone gets some rest.
I'm feeling we're gonna need it.
I wasn't sure even you could
get through military coding.
I can crack any lock three
years before they invent it.
It's what these old bones know.
Lord knows I ain't kept around
'cause I'm pretty to look at,
not these days.
Prettier than most at a company I keep.
Don't you
go saying anything bad
about these two little cherubs.
Those iron jockeys, they leave anything
interesting behind?
I don't think you're just
dealing with soldiers, deary.
That shuttle, it was refitted
as a prison transport.
Tightened craft, huh.
I thought they seem like they were stiff
than a crane for way too damn long.
Silver, come on, don't tease.
What'd you find?
Yeah, where are the toys?
Well, not too much left, I'm afraid.
Just some cases of rations, some water.
You know, the just the
basics you'd expect to find
in military stock.
Essentials, huh, good.
Anything else?
Ammunition, by the cartload.
But it's all military, so I don't think
it's gonna fit our guys
without some tinkerin'.
Oh, I can tinker.
Let me tinker, let me tinker.
Boss, let me--
Not fair!
You tinkered last time.
We busted in to a military
shuttle and you're telling me
all we got is spare parts
and bullets we can't shoot.
Well, I think there might
be one thing you might like.
Well, shit on toast!
I ain't seen one of these in--
Lord, it must be five years.
Not many of them left.
Not since they were
outlawed and rounded up.
So we're kicking in the door?
Soon.
First, we let them get tired and cranky
and scared out of their fucking minds.
Well, we just found a backdoor.
So my friend Bill is playing Santa
and I'm driving the fire
truck into the town square,
all the kids are there, as
Bill steps up off the truck,
he ain't wearing any underwear,
and Santa's pants go down on his ankles
he goes down like a bag
of hammers.
Comes up, I run around the truck
and there's Santa standing there,
blood running down his face
and Santa's little helper
is taking on it in front
of all the kids
and a couple of parents.
Oh man.
Look, I appreciate you
helping me keep watch, Wren,
but you're shot, all right?
Get some sleep.
Hey, I may not be a puppet anymore.
But I can live the life when I have to.
No, living's... head down, okay?
Start anything, we're
gonna need everyone sharp.
Here you go, just in case.
And, Python, you're a good sort.
Don't let anybody tell you different.
Yeah, well, good luck
convincing Uxbridge
and Lucy of that.
You know, Lucy had a husband
in Baltimore, well, you know.
Yeah.
All right, I'm gonna
go curl up with Kathy
'cause she gets mighty crabby
when I don't take the time.
Oh, we can't have that.
No.
Hey, if I find anybody up
there that's awake enough
I'll send them down here to
keep you spelled, all right?
I appreciate it.
All right.
Be safe.
I thought you could use a blanket.
Nothing else that'll make
the sitting more comfortable?
You looking for company?
I'm a bit surprised that you are.
Okay, the staring's getting creepy.
What is it with you?
You're gonna have to be
more specific than that.
To hear Uxbridge talk
about you you're the devil
and then Gwen starts
and you're a rock star.
You're Charles Manson
and then you're Gandhi.
And?
And I wanna know the real story.
That all depends on
whose side you're on.
Whose side are you on?
Come on, you could've
left Uxbridge to die.
Yeah, well, I have a
soft spot for hard cases.
What happened in Baltimore?
Baltimore.
Well, it happened.
That's not good enough.
And that's just tough.
Thanks for the blanket.
Boss!
Hey boss!
You smell that boys?
Smells like it's time.
Are we ready to dig?
For holes.
If we can flank 'em all the better.
Boss says it's time to go.
Oh, did he now?
All right, well, let's get started.
Oh, these old bones don't
move the way they used to.
Don't worry, we still love you.
Stand clear boys.
Great Jesus dick!
Gather up!
Boss man says four squads.
Squid, pick your team,
you're going down this hole.
Imson , Chuckie D, Frank,
time to go hunting.
Wait, whose got the next one?
Odds or evens.
Evens.
One 10,
two 10, three 10, four!
Yes!
Damn it!
I'm not a stone, I'm
a person like people:
squishy and bright.
Yes, you certainly are that.
You think like me, don't you?
Dragons and stones,
trolls and bits of metal
that sting like spiders.
You see, you listen.
I--
I can hear swimming.
Swimming.
The others don't swim.
I like to camp, it makes them mad.
Yeah, I'll bet it does.
Whirl of the ocean in the end.
And the beginnings, water and salt.
Swim, swim, swim.
Little heads hoping for bodies.
Okay, my head they're
kind of at war right now
so why don't you put this on and you--
We need to swim.
The stones would sink us, gulping water
'till our lungs bleed.
No one can swim ever again.
Okay.
Meg, I am more than happy to swim.
But right now I think you need to sleep
and maybe take your meds.
I can't sleep, not since the
light burned brightness away.
What the hell.
The avalanche is here now
but the dragon will stop it.
The avalanche, huh?
Well, let's go see what we can find out.
The dragon doesn't like visitors.
Come on.
Get inside.
There's only darkness now.
Swim, swim.
Clear.
Bastard's dead?
It's hard not to be when you're head's
in three different places.
Yeah, it's never pretty.
What the hell killed them?
It wasn't us, so.
What else is in these tunnels?
Those sewer crocks.
Who the fuck knows.
Hey, just out of curiosity,
do you know how to swim?
What?
Never mind.
Yo, D, take a look at this.
Oh, that shit burns.
What is that?
Fuck if I know.
That looks like--
Looks like what?
Nothing.
Hang on, if you know what this is--
I don't need to answer to you.
You wanna blame me for
Baltimore that's fine,
but right now we have
other goddamn problems.
Yeah, we do.
And someone like you
doesn't get to figure out
how to solve them.
Someone like me?
Yes, someone like you.
What gives you the right?
Necessity.
Necessity?
Yes.
You're nothing but a
cold-blooded murderer.
And I will not let you get us killed, too!
I am not--
Hey, back off, Diego!
Zip your ass down and think real hard
about what you want your
next move to be, kid.
It's all right.
Let him go.
Look, I'm not a hero, okay?
Sometimes I'm wrong.
In Baltimore, I was very, very wrong.
Wrong a lot of times I bet, dickweeds!
It sure was.
Diamond!
Bugger!
Stop doing that!
Yeah, stop killing our guys.
What?
Damn!
Well that blew!
Gems and stones may mend my bones,
but wasps will cut and sting me.
No, honey, there aren't any wasps here.
Not for a long time.
There weren't, but they just hid,
disguises people but wasps beneath
like the stones put backwards.
Except now the people
crack, the stones go soft
and the insides go outside.
The facade of humanity
has long been a part
of our existence, my dear.
Meg, honey, we're all people here.
You are, I am, Michael, Major Uxbridge--
Okay, okay.
Even Mr. Diamond all people.
I'm a person like
people: squishy and bright
surrounded by wasps and stones and fish
that gasp for air.
Diamond's becoming more
a liability than asset.
While we're still under siege
I don't think we should do--
I'm not denying he's at his uses
but he's outlived them at this point.
I suppose so, sir.
You suppose so?
I mean, yes, sir.
Good.
And be on a lookout for opportunities.
Go, go!
Glass, we got wounded.
Clear the couch!
Victor?
What happened to him?
Where's Lucy?
Where's the boy?
In a second, sir.
Where's Lucy?
What the
hell happened out there?
We were ambushed by Gazeebo's soldiers.
Pirates.
Whatever.
Look, the thing is two
of them are already dead
when we arrived.
That raises a question.
The only question is
how many more people
you're gonna get killed?
It wasn't his fault, sir.
The dragon breathes and boils away:
green and grim and hungry.
Meg, come on, shut up
about the dragon, okay?
The air is too thick, it...
Meg, you're not helping!
We definitely got broken bones here.
Femur, clavicle, skull.
Jesus Christ they really
did a number on him.
I know, I was there.
Do what you can.
I'm not sure how much that is.
Do it!
In the meantime, I have a question.
What is this?
Sewer kunk maybe, mold.
I've eaten army rations,
I know what mold looks like.
That ain't it.
I say, unhand me!
Just speaking from
experience, I wouldn't touch it.
Where did you find that?
It leaks from the walls.
The walls are soft and the dragon can--
Meg, be quiet.
But--
No!
No, what?
Look, she doesn't know
what she's saying anymore.
You got any questions, just ask us.
I did ask you.
You weren't answering.
You put my soldiers in harm's way
I'm gonna hold you responsible.
And you're gonna find
that extremely unpleasant.
Kathy, sweetie, maybe
we should tell them.
No, we took you in.
What are you gonna do, shoot people?
For fuck sake!
I'd rather be embarrassed
than dead, Kathy.
They deserve to know.
Look, it was back before you found us,
before we had Mr. Thurber and Gwen here.
They were still doing their
experiments in the lab.
Our work with the
refugees wasn't producing
the results that we had hoped.
Most of our subjects
were dying and quickly.
They weren't dragons, they were people.
Most.
One didn't.
Stable vitals, although he
was in pretty constant agony.
We were just trying to
find out why his body
wasn't dying of the radiation.
When we had to move from the lab to here
we left all the other specimens behind
and then we set up and started working
and that's when Lucy, she found that--
That's when we started
trying to figure out
what would kill those cells.
Okay, and what would?
Well, nothing, at least
nothing we could figure out.
It was the damnest thing.
We tried anything we could think of.
And eventually, we did see deterioration
but vitals stayed solid.
It started to leak these fluids
that we didn't recognize.
Green fluids, I'm guessing.
Spot on.
And with physical deterioration
came mental collapse as well.
Soon he grew increasingly violent
and he couldn't cognize properly.
Where is the gent at the moment?
Dead, well, at least
we thought he was dead.
We locked him in one of those rooms
and checked up on him the
next morning and he was gone.
A couple of globs of
that stuff on the floor
but otherwise nada, we
figure that he suffered
a rapid deterioration overnight.
Well, it seems like you were mistaken.
So, what, we have a radioactive
refugee torture victim
on the loose in the tunnels?
Who wants a hug folks?
Shit!
You led them here?
I didn't notice a tail.
We were dragging Victor.
We made plenty of noise.
Damn it, we should've thought--
Yes, you should've.
And of course, by a hug
I mean axe in the head.
Look, it's in the past, all right?
Right now they aren't
really the biggest problem.
Maybe they can help.
Might I remind you how
[poorly] you progressed
on our last attempt?
That was the douche bag over here.
This time it's me.
You all hear me okay in there?
Come on out and play.
You think you can do better?
Yes, yes, I do.
You killed my boys.
But you come out nice and
easy maybe I let a few
of your sheep survive the night.
Rodriguez, go upstairs and
grab the mole from Silver.
Door this heavy, explosives
just ain't gonna do.
I think it's about time
we had a conversation.
Well, shit.
If that ain't a blizzard in July.
You're about the last
face I expected to see
with those iron jockey fuck heads.
Good to know you remember
your old buddy Python.
Leonard Diamond, you expect
one of your gem cutters
to forget your face?
Five years is a long time.
It's good to see you
doing well for yourself.
Well, as can be expected
with the world ending and all.
Yeah, I heard something about that.
So pleasantry is out of the way.
I'm gonna ask you once more, what the fuck
are you doing with that
iron ridin' jackass
of a meat puppet?
Well, details are hazy
but they certainly involve
punching me a lot.
Things changed when we arrived.
I bet.
It changed now, too.
How so?
We aren't the only teams in the field.
I don't like this.
Speaking of teams,
you wanna switch sides?
Just for old time's sake.
Joint forces really against
a radioactive monster?
Yeah, right.
Pull the other one.
It plays Chopin.
You know me, I'm not bullshitting.
If I want your squads dead.
What the fuck is that?
Well, what a merry little shit show.
Full of sound and fury
signifying nothing.
Dragons breathe, they falter, they burn.
Now!
Get everyone out!
We're having no effect.
Fall back.
You heard the man, let's move people!
Watch how a real man does it, kiddos.
Jesus, would you be careful with that?
You know, I gotta hand it to you
you always had a no
nonsense sort of approach
to problem solving.
See, easy peasy.
Now, let's talk payment.
No.
I don't think she
understands the situation here.
You're in no position
to say no, little girl.
Leave her be.
Target is up!
Shit!
Move, move!
Move!
Don't leave him.
We have to move!
Victor!
You root out those hooligans yet?
Where are the rest of the boys?
I sent them to ferry the
shuttle parts back to camp.
You said you have this in hand.
I promise you, nothing is in hand!
Everything is fucked.
Jesus, Wren, Kathy.
Quinn, Glass, perimeter.
Listen, you just reign in
the horses there, young man.
Does anyone care to tell old Silver
what in the Sandhill is going on?
Monsters.
Oh, well, all right then.
It's fucking Baltimore all over again.
So what's the plan?
I'd say get back to the ship.
But judging by the ammunition
in this old bag's cart
that options out of the--
You show her some respect,
you little jockey fuck!
I'll show respect when someone--
You show respect or
I'll beat some of you!
Hey, seriously!
Now is not the fucking time!
Damn straight.
Run, run, run.
What?
That means bad thing.
Scatter!
Move, move!
Sick him!
Fuck this.
You ungrateful little cur!
Supper time bitches!
Fall back!
Shit!
Sir, who are you aiming for?
Opportunities, private.
After all I'm trying
to kill that creature.
Hey, I ain't done yet.
That's an impressive piece of equipment.
Yeah, I always like those things.
Hey, did we just win?
Well, he didn't.
You son of a bitch!
What, you're gonna shed tears
over some iron jockey prick?
I hope this would end
differently, Gazeebo.
I gotta say, I hope you join up.
Be quite the coupe having
a fella called Diamond
as my new second.
Not really the deal anymore.
Call him off.
I can't have you out
there as an independent.
You're sporting the name
people will flock to,
even these days.
Says the guy who named
himself after a lawn ornament.
Cute.
And it's not too late to walk away.
Yeah, it is.
Looks like it hurts.
It does, don't worry.
Damn shame.
Well, it looks like you got a little fire
left in you after all.
Don't get me wrong, it hurts like fuck.
It's going as bad as I made out.
I could fix that.
Well, well, one of the
sheep is still alive.
I'm a person, like people.
The fuck is wrong with you?
You aren't.
There's too much stone around you.
You need to break the stone.
I reflect a person, you reflect a stone.
But you weren't.
Just what are you gonna do
with that now, little girl?
Let the person out.
Ain't that a punch in the dick.
Leonard, do an old pal a favor.
You stupid, stubborn bastard.
Why did he let the squishy out?
I'm pretty sure he didn't mean to.
Glass, get to Quinn.
Bullet wound, left shoulder.
Damn it!
Are we stones now?
No chance.
I swear to God, sometimes
I think you make sense.
There's too many bad
surprises in those tunnels
and you, you must've come from somewhere.
It's that or going to knit?
My thoughts exactly.
What did I miss?
Shit, man, you're really hurt.
Yes, yes, I am.
Would not mind the gauze pad.
Yeah, and I could use a shirt.
I'll loan you one of mine.
Downstairs must be
medical supplies, right?
Do you mind?
Okay.
What about you?
I just need some air.
Okay.
Let's get out of here.
I can swim, you know.
Swim, swim.
Yeah, swim, swim.
Let's ride.