Subsynced balloumowgly
♪ I said, don't you think like that ♪
♪ I will love you endlessly ♪
♪ If you only believe me ♪
♪ Don't you think like that ♪
♪ I will love you endlessly ♪
♪ I said, don't you think like that ♪
♪ If you only believe me ♪
♪ Don't you think like that ♪
♪ I will love you endlessly ♪
♪ If you only believe me ♪
♪ Don't you think like that ♪
♪ I will love you endlessly ♪
♪ I said, don't you think like that ♪
♪ If you only believe me ♪
♪ Don't you think like that ♪
♪ I will love you endlessly ♪
♪ I said, don't you think like that ♪
-  Why you peeking
around the corner?
-  Come on.
- Oh my goodness.
- No peeking.
- What are you up to?
- No, no peeking.
- I got you.
- Hmm hmm.
- Uh uh, stay right there.
- Okay.
- Yeah, let me shut the door.
Okay.
- Oh my goodness.
- Go ahead, keep walking.
- I'm walking, don't let me fall.
- I'm not, of course not.
- Hmm.
- Straight ahead.
- You know I hate surprises.
- I know, it's not gonna stop me.
Keep right on going.
- Can I stop?
- I got you, keep going.
A little bit more, we're almost there.
- Oh my goodness.
- Almost.
- What are you up to?
- And whala!
- Surprise!
- Thank you, thank you, thank you.
Oh my goodness.
I haven't seen y'all in forever.
I can't believe you didn't tell me.
Oh my goodness, Lord.
Thank you, thank you.
- Can I have everyone's attention, please?
Lynn, come here, baby.
I wanna thank everyone
for coming this evening
to Lynn's surprise birthday party.
- Yes, thank you, baby.
This has been incredible, such a surprise.
I thank you all for coming.
- I know you were very surprised, babe,
but there's one more
thing that I need to do.
You know that I love you, right?
- Yeah.
I love you, too.
- Well, this is not just
a surprise birthday party,
but I was hoping
that this would also become
an engagement party.
- Babe, what are you doing?
- Lynn.
I love you very much.
And I was hoping
that you would do me the honor
of becoming my wife.
Will you marry me?
- Yes.
- I love you, babe.
- I love you, too.
- Man, look at her.
She don't even want to get married.
- Yo, chill, man.
Look, he love that girl.
So we gonna do what best friends do.
And we gonna support whatever
he wanna do, all right?
- Excuse me.
You two have something you want to share?
- Oh nah, we good.
- Oh, I didn't think so.
- Yeah, I just keep it to myself.
- You, chill, man.
- Man, you know I don't like her.
- Girl, what's wrong?
You don't look like somebody
that just got engaged.
- What, I'm cool.
I'm fine.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
- Girl, look at that fine
man you got over there.
You should be happy.
- Only Jackson don't have any money.
- Is he still working nights
and going to school during the day?
- Hmm hmm, which leaves me at
home with that child of his.
- Just think, once he get
that big lawyer money,
you not gonna have nothing
to worry about, girl.
- I wish he hurry up and get it.
- It's okay, girl.
He about to get it soon.
Now, let's go and enjoy this party.
Girl and plus, you know I got to find me
one of them fine brothers
over here, tonight.
- To add to the list?
- Girl, yes.
- You have enough, already.
- Okay, you know I keep
a new one every month.
- Oh, God.
Can you believe, I'm getting married?
- Girl, no, I can't believe,
but we can cheers to that.
- All right, cheers.
- 'Cause I'm so happy for ya.
- Jackson, I'm proud of you, man.
- Appreciate you, Brian.
I'm trying to get to your level.
- Hey man, you already there, bro.
- Man, you breaking up up the crew
with all this marriage stuff.
- Man, come here, fellas.
- Tracy, we're in our 30s now, man.
It's time off for that running around
with different women, night in, night out.
- Hey, that's right, Jackson.
Now, this man done married up.
You got yourself, a fine
woman in there, bruh.
- Hmm hmm, Tracy, you need
to get yourself a woman
so you don't have to worry
about what my man is doing.
- Hey, Lynn.
- You need to find yourself another man
to trick into marrying you.
- Hey, B.
That's my woman, man.
- Man, my bad, man.
- Come on, B.
- Congratulations.
- No doubt.
- B, let's get up out of here, man,
'for I say something I really regret.
Let's go, man.
- Hey, hey, I'm home!
Lynn, I'll said, I'm home.
- I heard you the first time.
You want me to turn cartwheels
because you're home?
- No, but asking your
husband how his day was
from time to time, what
would be a nice start.
- Have you seen these bills, hmm?
They're all overdue.
And you're talking about
asking how your day was?
You can't be serious.
- Yes, I'm very serious.
Mmm.
- Don't touch me.
- It's like that?
After only six months?
- Have you not noticed?
- I'll tell you what I have noticed.
A wife that hasn't made love
to her husband in a month
and seems to be letting
stress affect her marriage.
- Hmm hmm, go on and continue.
- And I'll add,
that I'm starting to feel like
I'm in this marriage alone.
- All right, let me be honest.
I thought I was marrying a man
that was going to be successful.
Not a man that's going to night school.
- You talk as if I'm going to night school
to get my damn GED.
I'm six months away from being
done and taking my bar exam.
This close!
From my dreams becoming reality.
- Look, I get having goals
and dreams and all of that.
But I'm tired of struggling.
I want a house, a nice car to drive.
You know the finer things in life.
- I told you.
Taking over to my parents'
company after they retired
was just an option in the event
that law school doesn't pan out.
- Well, it doesn't look
like it's working out to me.
- Oh, I will run my own
law firm one day, Lynn.
Now that's funny,
because there's no way
that's going to happen.
- Wow, thanks for the encouragement.
- Oh, I'm encouraging you
to run your family business.
There's no doubt we'll
be successful, then.
- Your definition of success is what?
A big house?
A nice car?
Oh, and these designer
clothes you like to be buying?
- Hmm hmm, yes, why not?
You know Karen and her
man are very successful.
Now he works
and she takes care of the new house
they just had built from the ground up.
- Hmm hmm, and where's the
love in the relationship?
- Oh Karen loves her house
and her new car.
- Let me tell you something.
Love is about being there
through thick and thin.
It's not about what you
have or where you live.
Those things are only temporary.
- Yeah, but what's
wrong with wanting more?
- Nothing, if you stay
committed to work together
to achieve those things!
- Look, I'm ready to see the
benefits of me being patient
and playing step mommy to your kid.
- Okay, you know what?
We need to end this conversation
before things get out hand.
- Oh no, let's not.
Go on, what's on your mind, Jackson?
- No, I'm done with it, now.
I'm tired!
- Look, when you're at work,
who's at home with her, huh?
Me, that's who!
- And you should love her
like she's your own daughter.
- Oh, shut up, Jackson, I've tried.
- Listen.
Courtney's been with me
since she was two years old.
When she was born, I wasn't
ready to be a father.
After her mother died, I
had to drop out of college,
put my basketball career on hold,
grow up quick and become
a full-time father.
And you know what?
I'm proud of the job I've done.
Whoop-de-do!
You also promised to
take care of me and her.
Because this right here
is not what I imagined.
- So what!
So what, Lynn!
We don't have a big house or the Mercedes.
You and I, we have each other.
And if that's not enough,
I'm sorry, I don't know what it is.
- Look, I'm done talking about this.
-  I think we need counseling.
- No, I don't need any counseling.
Good evening, Jackson.
- Lynn.
- I am going upstairs.
- Lynn!
- Get off of me!
- Hey, girl.
Girl, I'm outside your house.
Come outside.
- Hey, girl.
- Girl, this is nice.
- I know, right?
Girl, that's why I had to stop by.
I had to show you my new
car that my man bought me.
- Your man, which man is it this week?
- My new man that bought
me this new car.
- Well, what is the model?
- I don't know.
Something fast!
- How do you not know
what kind of car you have?
- It don't matter, girl.
I just matter that I'm not paying for it.
- I know that's right.
Whew, chile, I remember those days, hmm.
We have all these bills.
We can't afford a new car.
We can barely afford a Hyundai.
- Well, he's close to graduating, right?
- Yeah, he's close, but,
I'm tired of waiting.
I'm ready to get what I deserve now.
- What you deserve?
Girl, that man is your husband.
He ain't your father.
- I know, but it's his
job to provide, right,
and giving me everything that I want.
I mean, if I can get it from him,
then I'm gonna have to
get it from my sponsor.
- Lynn?
Your sponsor.
Are you saying what I think you saying?
- I'm saying what you think I'm saying?
But he's just a friend.
- Just a friend?
Lynn, you are a married woman.
How do you have just friends?
- You know, it just kind of happened.
- Girl, how does cheating just happen?
- He was someone that I confided in.
Ah, this is him now, hold on.
Hey, baby.
How are you doing?
Can I give you a call back in a minute?
All right, will do.
What?
Why are you looking at me like that?
- Like, I'm about to ask you
if you creeping on your husband?
- Listen, it's none of your concern.
He is just a friend.
- Okay, just a friend.
Well, listen, I'm gonna mind
my business in my new car.
But for real though, I love you, okay.
And I think you really need to
fix that before it fixes you.
- Hmm, I'm good.
Listen, when are you
gonna take me on a ride
in this new car?
- You crazy,
but we can ride out right now.
Let's go!
- Jack, B, what's up man?
Mind telling me where the party at?
- Yo man, I just got here.
This fool been sitting here
like he just lost his best friend, man.
- What's up man?
What's going on, man?
Everything all right?
- Man, this marriage this is hard, man.
- Oh, so y'all having some issues?
- Every day, she whining about something.
One day, it's about bills.
The next day,
it's about me not wanting to
take over the family business.
Man, real talk,
I couldn't even tell you the
last time I've gotten some.
- You ain't getting none?
Look, man, we tried to tell you
what she would like from the jump.
She a gold digger!
-  What are you talking about?
- Man, things ain't happening
fast enough for her, man.
She can't handle with, Jack.
- Nah, she just mad because
I haven't been able to give
her the things that she wants.
- Come on, man.
Don't start doing that to yourself.
- Don't start doing what?
- Blaming yourself for her ways!
- I'm not blaming myself, Tracy.
But, maybe I should listen to her
and take over the family business.
We wouldn't be hurting so
much financially, like we are.
- Bro, you need to come out of that.
Like real talk.
This for rich or for poor.
- Till death do you part, right?
- Man, so what, everything tight.
That's everywhere.
She can't accept that?
She just showing you who she really is.
- Man, I knew it was
something about this girl
I ain't like, man.
- Really?
- Fellas, she wasn't like
that in the beginning, man.
I...
I don't know what changed.
- Bro, nothing changed.
You was just so caught up in her, man,
you didn't see her for the real her.
- Look, man.
All relationships go
through rocky situations.
And they resort to counseling.
Y'all tried that?
- I mentioned it to her
numerous times about going,
but she just keeps
shooting that idea down.
- Bro, you hurt.
And I don't like to see that.
- What makes you think I'm hurting?
- Oh, you hurting, bro.
- Man, you sitting there by yourself.
Two empty glasses
and you telling me
and B
that your girl ain't giving you none.
Bro, you hurt.
- Yo, you think she might be cheating?
- Yep.
- Nah, she's not cheating.
- I mean, I ain't saying she cheating,
just something to think about, man.
-  I'm going to the bathroom, man.
- Man, I told you a long time
ago, I ain't trust that girl.
- Man, I ain't trying
to hear all that, man.
-  Fellas,
I'm gonna shut it down early tonight, man.
- What?
- That's a good idea, man.
-  I gotta go talk to the wife.
All right?
- Damn.
- Let's go.
- Let's be out.
- Just gonna roll on me, huh?
- Really?
- Girl, what you got up in that bag?
- Oh, it is so cute.
And I got it on sale.
- Whew, you know I love a good sale, girl.
Jackson is going to love that.
- Hmph, you sure it's right for Jackson?
- What you gonna do with that thing?
- Oh, my man is going to love me in this.
- You've got to give me all the details.
- You know I'm going to
give you all the details,
come on now.
I am going to put it on him.
- 20% off.
Girl, now you know we got
to go up in this store.
-  You know, I've been
wanting to check this store out
for the longest.
- Ooh, baby, that's going
to look so good on you.
- I know, Mr. Jackson.
- So why don't you put it on?
So I can take it off.
- No, I'm going to bed.
- Can we talk about what's going on?
- Good night, Jackson.
- Damn!
Thanks for seeing me today, Rev.
- Oh, anytime.
You know I always have time
for one of my favorite members.
How's Lynn?
- That's why I'm here to discuss.
Seems like we hit a rough
patch in our marriage.
- Explain, Jackson.
I'm listening.
- I don't want it to seem like
I'm going behind my wife's
back talking to you.
I just...
- Hmph, I'm your spiritual
leader as well as hers.
Let's talk.
- I really don't know where to begin.
- Hmm, well, just start
from the beginning.
We got all the time in the world.
-  Well...
Basically, Lynn's not interested
in being married anymore.
- Hmm, what makes you feel that way?
- Because, she's always complaining
that I don't make enough money
and mad that I haven't taken
over the family business.
-  Is that all?
- I feel funny saying this,
but she's not even giving me any, Rev.
- Giving you any, what?
- No sex.
She's not giving me no sex.
- Hmm, what are you doing
to work on your marriage?
- What do you mean?
- I mean, you made a vow to provide.
Are you following through with that part?
- Shouldn't it be about more
than just providing, though?
- Yeah, it should be, but
you know what they say?
There's no romance without finance.
Have you at
least prayed about it?
- Rev, I pray all day, every day about it.
- Hmm, well maybe you two
ain't meant to get married.
Divorce may be an option.
- Per this Bible?
Divorce is not an option.
- Hmm, I'm just saying,
Lynn is a very, very attractive woman
and you can't force nobody
to stay in something
they don't want to be in.
- I came here to get help
and all I'm hearing from
you is get a divorce?
- I'm just saying,
if you can't provide the type of lifestyle
that she's accustomed to,
maybe you should let somebody else do it.
I mean, I know it don't sound easy,
but, I'm just keeping
it real with you, bro.
- Are you serious right now?
-  You can't make
somebody stay in something
they don't want to be in, my brother.
Hold on a second.
Hello?
Hey, what's up sweetie?
Okay.
All right.
- Wow, that's beautiful.
Your wife calls just to check on you.
- Yeah, she loves her some Reverend Smith.
Anyway, hey man,
I got to get ready to go.
I gotta cut this short.
I got an appointment I gotta make it to.
- Hey, but you said-
- I understand man, but
something, something came up,
so uh, look, I'm gonna be
praying for both of y'all.
- All right.
Thanks for seeing me again, Rev.
- Ah, no problem, my brother.
Anytime.
- Yeah.
-  Yeah.
Yeah.
- Hey, where are you?
The gym?
Okay.
I'll see you when you get home.
All right, bye.
- Hey, sexy.
You just missed Jackson.
He just left here requesting help for you.
-  Do you think he saw me?
- Of course not. I told
him I had to cut it short
so I can meet up with my wife.
- And just where's that wife of yours?
- Hmm, that's not important.
You're here.
And she's not.
That's all that matters.
- Well, did you tell him
that you're sexing me?
- Nah, but I told him you deserve better.
- And who's gonna give me the best?
- Me, of course.
Soon as I get some things situated.
- Don't keep me waiting.
You know, I have needs, you know?
- Hmm, well you better get outta here
before your husband get a
whiff of what we got going on.
I see you later on tonight, baby.
- All right.
Whew, reverend, reverend, reverend.
♪ It's amazing how good love feels ♪
Whew!
- How you feeling?
- A little tired.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- I've been waiting for you all day.
- Yeah, you know I had
to wrap up some business
at the church first.
- Oh, well, you look nice.
- Hmm, you do, as well.
♪ Got me like this, must be love ♪
What's on your mind?
- Jackson was acting really strange
before he left this evening.
-  You think has a clue
that you plan on leaving him?
- No.
All he talks about is counseling
and he's so caught up
what he's going through,
he doesn't have a clue.
- No, don't underestimate Jackson.
You need to be careful about
having me come by here.
- Hmm, at this point, I don't really care.
- Nah, it's not that simple.
- It's simple for me.
I mean, you don't want us to be together?
- Of course.
But, you know we gotta wait
until the time is right for both of us.
- All right.
I'll be patient for you.
- Hmm, that's what I like to hear.
- Come on, let's get
this party started then.
♪ Got me like this ♪
♪ Oh, this must be love ♪
♪ Is this love? ♪
- Do you know when my dad will be home?
- Courtney, your dad
will be home soon, okay?
- Well, can you help me with my homework?
- No, I'm busy right now.
- You're always too busy to help me.
- Hey, watch your mouth
when you're talking to me.
- Well, my dad always
helps me with homework.
- Then, your day can
help when he gets home.
Go to your room while I take this call.
- Hey, baby, how you doing?
Yeah, I'm here with the brat right now.
Her dad should be home soon.
So I'll see you soon.
Okay, all right.
- Was that my dad?
- Didn't I tell you to go to your room?
What am I going to do with you?
- Nothing, like you always do!
- Sit your tail down.
- Hey, what are my
favorite girls watching?
Hey baby.
Daddy don't get no hug?
How you doing?
- Good.
Lynn, that includes you, too.
- Hmm hmm.
- How was your day?
Did you miss me?
- My day was fine.
And no, I didn't miss you.
- That's all right, well at
least one of my girls did.
Right, Courtney?
- Yep.
- And for the record,
I'm a grown ass woman.
- Hey!
Watch your mouth around my daughter!
And I'll assume, that once again,
that you didn't cook dinner!
- And you will assume, right.
I was a busy.
Is that okay, your majesty?
- Busy doing what?
You don't work!
- Look, I didn't get married
to wait hand and foot on you two.
- Courtney.
- Hmm?
- Go to your room, sweetheart.
- Would you like to tell
me what you did today
that kept you so busy?
- Nope.
Not really.
- You want a divorce?
Is that it, Lynn!
- Jackson, I don't know what I want.
I just need some time to
think about all of this, okay?
- You know what?
- Just give me 50 feet.
Please.
- You know what?
Take all the time you need.
I'm going to bed.
Good night.
Somebody has to work around
here to pay these bills.
- Hmm, barely.
- Yeah, whatever.
- Whew boy, I know you
didn't call me over here
'cause you want me to work
out with you, now, did you?
- Ah, hey, mama.
- 'Cause, you know, I ain't
doing it.
- How you doing?
- I'm good, baby.
How you doing?
-  Thanks so much for coming, mama.
- Okay.
- I really need to talk to you.
- Well, what's wrong, baby?
-  It's more like,
what's not wrong, mama.
I mean...
- Talk to me.
- It feels like my marriage is crumbling
right before my eyes.
- Hmm.
- You know, bills are overdue.
Lynn and Courtney, they
can't stand each other.
- It's just starting
to become overwhelming.
- Well, baby, what can I do to help?
- Oh mama, I know you can help,
but I'm a grown man
with a wife and a daughter.
There's no way I'm allowing
my mama to pay my bills.
- Uh uh, boy, you better stop that.
Now, there's nothing wrong with
you needing help, sometimes.
I don't care what your daddy said.
And don't you let your pride keep you
from asking for that help.
Now, your father and I
worked hard for our children.
Just like you working
hard for your family.
Now, how can I help you?
- Well, I also want to talk to you
about the family business.
- Ah, what about the family business?
- I was wondering if the
offer was still on the table
to run the business.
- Baby, it's never been off the table,
but you were never interested.
Why now?
- Lynn's been sweating me about it.
You know, she's complaining about bills
and not being able to buy
a new house and a car.
- Are you serious?
- Yes, I'm serious.
- Oh!
- Look, it's to the point
where I'm beginning to feel
like she might be having an affair.
- Oh, boy, uh uh, don't you say that.
- Hey, listen.
I don't want to believe it, mama,
but something in my spirit
just telling me something not right.
- So now let me get this straight.
You thinking about quitting school
and giving up on your
dream of becoming a lawyer,
for that gold digging wife of yours?
Oh Lord, I'm sorry, let me stop.
But I feel like she don't love, no how.
- Mama, why would you
say something like that?
- Hmm, baby, truth of the matter is,
your daddy and I always felt like
she only married you for the business.
- I didn't know y'all felt like that.
- Well, baby.
If you like it, we loved it.
But sorry, it's better
that you hear it from us
than somebody else.
- I wish dad was here.
- I know, baby.
I do, too.
- How do I fix this?
- Well, you can start by not
giving up on your dreams.
And then you can try counseling.
- I told Lynn, we needed
to go to counselor.
She just feels like we don't need to go.
- Hmm, well baby, this is
all the counseling you need.
And I need to say something to you.
I gotta be honest.
And I know it might hurt your feelings.
But , I need to say it.
- About what?
- Honey, the old folks always say
when a woman don't want to
make it work with a good man,
it's because she already
getting under another man.
Now I know that might hurt your feelings,
but now, truth is truth.
- Nah, mama.
I don't believe that.
I think she's just upset
about our finances,
you know, but,
I don't believe that.
- Oh, oh okay then, baby.
Well, I tell you what.
When Lynn get home,
you talk to her
and you find out what the problem is
and you fix it.
- I appreciate the advice, mom.
- All right, baby.
I'm going home
and work on my greens.
I'm cooking greens for Sunday dinner.
- All right.
- Y'all oughta come over.
Keep pumping that iron, boy!
You looking good.
- Lynn said she had an appointment today.
I want to see exactly what she's doing
every day when I'm at work.
- Man, you need me to
hire you a private eye?
- Nah, I don't need no
private eye, scratch that.
I am going to see exactly
what's on her computer
to see if anything is on that.
- That's what's up.
Hey man, who keys is these?
I thought you said, won't nobody here.
- Shouldn't nobody be here.
Let me see those keys.
- You heard that?
That came from upstairs.
Hey man, somebody upstairs.
I'm going to get my gun.
- Hey, hey, nah, Tracy.
I don't want her to
think I'm spying on her.
- And I heard that again.
Somebody upstairs.
- Hey, Tracy!
- Come on, man.
- Jackson, what are you doing here?
- The question is, what
are you doing here?
I thought you were at the gym!
- Yeah, babe, I, I'm,
I'm getting ready to go.
I just gotta put my clothes on
and you can walk me downstairs.
- You ready to get this party
started? Oh shoot, Jackson.
- Man, what the hell are you doing here?
- Look, man, it's not what you think, bro.
- Man, you in my house!
Half naked!
And it's not what I think?
- Jackson, come on. You
were supposed to be at work.
What are you doing here?
- I'll tell you what I'm doing.
Catching my wife with
this fake ass preacher.
- Look, man, let me explain, bro.
- Man, the only thing you need to do, man,
is stay the hell up out of my face.
- Come on, Jackson, I'm sorry.
Now, you know, we've been having problems.
- So you decided to screw around
because we're having problems?
- Look, man, can we talk
about this, man to man?
- Man, hell nah!
- Look, I'm sorry, okay?
I'm really sorry.
- You know what?
You two deserve each other.
I hope it was worth it!
- Look, I'm sorry.
That's all I can say.
- Yeah, you sorry, all right.
- You a sorry ass excuse for a woman!
And I should lay these
hands on you, my man.
But it's best, I let God handle you.
Man, you got 30 seconds
to get up out of my house!
And in case you didn't know, it's over!
- Can we at least talk?
- There's nothing for us to talk about.
- I only went to him for counseling.
- You went for counseling
and just happen to wind up screwing him?
- No, no, I mean, look, I
don't know what to say, okay?
It just happened.
- So, it just happened, huh?
- Yeah.
Yes.
And I might as well be honest with you.
We're going to be together.
- Together?
You think this man gonna
leave his wife for you?
You can't be that stupid.
- Look, that's what he told me.
And I believe him.
- You have to be out show rabbit ass mind,
if you think this man gonna leave his wife
for the likes of you!
- And what the hell is
that supposed to mean?
- It means a man doesn't leave
his wife for his mistress,
his jump off or whatever
it is you are to him.
- Look, I'm more than a mistress.
I'm a hundred percent woman, okay.
And he knows that!
He knows I deserve the
finer things in life.
- So this is all about you
wanting the finer things in life?
- And there's nothing that
you can provide for me
with that low-paying job that you have.
You have a wife and a daughter!
And you're a fork lift driver.
How can you expect to take
care of us off of that salary?
- Let me tell you something.
This forklift driver works hard every day
to provide a roof for you,
food in the refrigerator
and gas in your car.
- You call that out there, a car?
- So he promised you a car, huh?
- As a matter of fact, yes, he did.
- So let me get this straight.
He told you he was leaving his wife,
buying you a car
and getting you everything
you deserve, right?
- That's right.
- Oh Lynn, Lynn, Lynn, Lynn.
You a lot dumber than I imagined.
- Look, you can call it
whatever you want, okay?
I'll be well taken care of with him.
- Wow, you that shallow
that you're willing to
walk out on your marriage
for a married man?
- Say what you wanna say?
I don't care.
My mind is made up.
- Oh, believe me, I'm not
trying to change your mind.
You made your choice!
- Good, so we are in agreeance, okay.
'Cause this relationship
has ran its course.
I want a divorce, Jackson.
So what are you doing now?
Where are you going?
- I'm not leaving, but you are.
This my house.
You want to be with your lover,
but think you're going
to be able to stay here
until you decide to leave?
- Look, I have no where to go right now.
- Sounds like an issue for
the two of you to work out.
- Who's going to keep Courtney?
- Oh, you never cared
about Courtney, no way.
Don't worry about it.
- That's not true.
I kept her.
When you went to school, at work.
- Hmm hmm, and what does that mean?
Nothing.
Look here, I want you to get your bags,
pack all of your things and leave.
We don't need you here.
- That's fine, Jackson, okay.
I'll leave.
And you can have all of this stuff.
There's nothing I want to
remember about this place, anyway.
- Lynn, I've only loved, respected
and treated you the way a woman should be.
Never, not once
disrespected you as my wife.
I would have done anything
for you and Courtney
because that's what a real man does.
- Oh, a real man?
My new man is a real man.
- Lynn, you need to get
the hell out of my house
before I throw you out!
You have five minutes
before I help you get your
stuff and put it out myself.
- All right, relax, already.
That's five minutes more than I need.
- Get the hell out!
- I don't want any of this stuff.
Please.
My man will make sure I have
everything I need, loser.
- God, I've done all I can do.
I tried to be a good father and a husband.
How could you let this happen?
It's bad enough, my wife is cheating,
but it's with someone that
claims to preach your ways.
Doing things your way,
didn't work, it didn't work!
So, you know what?
From now on,
I promise you,
I'm doing things my way.
Thanks for nothing!
- Yes?
- Hi, I'm here to see the reverend.
- Hmph, he's with someone right now.
- That's fine, I'll wait.
I'm sure, he'll be glad
to know that I'm here.
- Okay.
You can have a seat in the
sanctuary and I'll go get him.
- Thank you.
- What are you doing?
You can't just pop up like this.
- Baby, I'm sorry.
I just couldn't wait to see you.
- That's what we need to talk about, too.
- Talk about what?
- About me and you, us.
- That's why I came by. Look,
I told Jackson everything.
I told him I was leaving
him so we can be together.
Now baby, we don't have to deal with this-
- No, look, that's what I
need to talk to you about.
We can't do this anymore.
- What do you mean, anymore?
- I'm talking about, we need to stop, now.
- All right, baby,
please just tell her that you
playing with me, right now.
- Look, we should have never
got involved in the beginning.
I already got a deal with God about it.
And I'm not leaving my wife for you.
- Don't do this.
Please, don't do this.
Come on, baby, why are you saying this?
- And you really wanna know?
- Yes, why?
- Do you really wanna know?
- Yes, I wanna know.
What did I do?
I'm sorry for popping up.
- That's not the reason.
- Well, what is it?
- The reason why we can't be together
is because I don't love you
and I'm not finna' be responsible
for stealing another man's wife.
- Oh, so you don't want to
steal another man's wife
but you'll have sex with one?
-  Man, also, if
you cheated on your husband,
I definitely know you'll
cheat on me or any other man.
- I would never cheat on
you because I love you.
- So you're the woman that's
been messing with my husband?
- Excuse me?
- Don't play dumb with me, Lynn.
I know exactly who you are
and what the two of you have been up to.
My husband told me everything.
- What is she talking about?
- Look, I told my wife everything
and we're gonna get some
marriage counseling.
- I love you.
- You don't love him.
You love the idea of him
and what you thought he could do for you.
Just like you thought
you loved your husband
because he was taking
over the family business.
I know everything.
- But you don't know me, okay?
And you're wrong.
I love him.
- You don't even love yourself.
Look at you.
You had a good man at home
and now you standing here,
begging my husband to be with you.
- So I was just a piece of ass?
- Hey, you watch your
mouth in God's house.
- Was it God's house when
you stood here, kissing me
and caressing me?
- Look, look, now, I already
asked for forgiveness
and I prayed about it.
Me and my wife, we're gonna
get some marriage counseling.
We're going to work on our marriage.
And I suggest you do to same.
- Just like that?
It's over?
- Lynn, go home and try
to fix your marriage.
- Go home, Lynn.
- So you were never
going to leave your wife?
So, you lied to me.
You misled me this entire time.
I meant nothing to you?
You are nothing but a
johnny-come-lately preacher
that was trying to get laid
and I hope you rot in hell.
- You got some explaining to do.
- I'm so sorry, baby.
- Son, you sitting here like
you done lost your best friend.
What's going on?
- Lynn's having an affair.
- An affair?
Are you sure?
- Yes, I'm very sure.
- And how do you know this?
- Mama, I caught her red-handed.
- What the hell!
Oh Lord, forgive me.
I'm sorry, but that just burns my butt
when somebody mess over my baby.
- Yeah, well, it's worse than that.
- Now, how can it get any worse than that?
You mean to tell me that you know the punk
that's been sleeping with your wife?
- Yes, I caught her in our bedroom.
- Who is it?
- Reverend Smith.
- Who?
- Mama, he was the same
preacher that married us.
- Oh, the devil is a lie!
- You know, your daddy
used to always tell me
that them preachers ain't no good,
that all they want is all your money
and to chase them no good
women all around the church.
And I used to tell him
that it wasn't true.
The truth of the matter is, baby,
it's happened more than
I can shake a stick at.
You do know why your daddy
stopped going to church a long time ago?
- Hmm hmm, and daddy was right.
And that's why I'm not stepping foot
in another church again.
- Nmm mmm, boy, now, you watch your mouth.
You cannot lump all the other churches
and preachers into this.
- Mama, I respect everything
you and dad taught me as a child,
but I'm not stepping foot
in another church, again.
Why would God allow this to happen?
Tell me that!
- Baby, I can't explain it.
But I do know that God did
not allow this to happen.
Lynn made a choice to cheat
and that's because she's a tramp.
And that man, well, he
need a good beating.
Baby, I know you're hurt.
But please, don't turn your back on God.
I taught you better than that.
- Mama, I've been on my
knees every day, praying,
and asking God to fix my marriage.
And this is how he answers my prayers!
- Oh, Lord.
Thomas, I know, I got to let
him go, but that's my baby.
God, just take care of him.
- Girl...
You are not going to believe
what this man did to me.
- What man?
Jackson?
- Nmm mmm, the reverend, Reverend Smith.
- Oh him, what he do?
He finally told you he
was gonna leave his wife?
- Yeah, he told me that but then he-
- And then what?
- Then he said he wasn't leaving his wife.
- Now sis, you know, I love you.
And I really hate to tell you this, but,
I told you that!
- Yeah, I know.
But this man told me, he loved me.
- Lynn, that man didn't love you.
He just loved that you wanted him!
- I really loved him.
- Girl, you did not love him.
You just loved what he was doing for you
that you thought you were
missing in your marriage.
That is not love.
- I know, but what am
I supposed to do now?
I mean, I treated Jackson terrible.
I can only imagine what
he thinks about me.
I'm sure he hates me.
- You need to go home
and fix your marriage.
- But do you think he'll forgive me?
- Chile, I don't know. But
that sounds like a conversation
you need to be having with your husband.
- Ah, yeah, mmm.
Thanks, sis.
You know, you always have
my back girl.
- I know.
What would you do without me?
- I don't know.
- I always got your back.
Listen, and if we need
to go pull up on the Rev,
you know we can.
- All right, well, let's do it now.
I'm down.
- Let's go.
- You crazy.
- What are you doing here?
Did you come to get the
rest of your things?
- I was just wondering if we can talk?
- What is there to talk about?
- Jackson, just let me come
in and talk to you, please.
- Go ahead, you have five minutes.
- Listen, I made a huge mistake.
- What does that supposed to do for me?
- All right, I know you're upset
and you have every right to be.
- Get to the point, Lynn.
- Jackson, I still love you.
And I want us to try and make it work.
- Tell the truth, he left you, didn't he?
- Yeah, he said he
wasn't leaving his wife.
You were right.
I should have listened to you.
- Well, that's too late for that, now.
What'd you expect me to do?
Take you back?
- Yes or at least see me.
I mean, we can still talk.
We can hang out.
We can see each other.
- Are you kidding me?
- Listen, Jackson, I love you, all right.
I'm just not in love with you.
And I think it's best
that we remain friends.
- Lynn, I put everything I had
in me into this relationship.
- I know, but it's better this way.
-  This is truly amazing.
You chose to be a mistress
instead of being a wife.
- Look, you're out of line, okay.
I'm not gonna stand here
and let you talk to me any kind of way.
- No, you're gonna stand
here and you're gonna listen.
So you like when man treat you like dirt.
You love to be the other
woman, you get off on that.
You want the perks of being married,
but you don't want to do the work.
- All right, Mr. Husband of the Year,
Mr. Perfect Father.
You know, you're not the only
man in this world, right?
Yeah, you provided for me.
Yeah, you were good to me.
But don't act like you deserve something.
-  Finally, the
real you is coming out.
- Look, I came by here so we can talk
and try to figure out a
way to move forward, okay?
But all you want to do
is talk bad about me.
- No, you say you want a good man,
but every time you get one,
all you do is mess it up.
- All right, that's enough.
You've said that already.
- No, it's far from enough.
I never cheated on you
regardless of the countless opportunities.
And, as corny as this may sound,
I never even thought about it
because I only had thoughts of you.
You were my everything.
But you was too blind to see it.
- Jackson, I don't know what else to say,
but I'm sorry for hurting you.
- Just remember this.
You may meet men that
say they care about you.
They may buy you gifts,
take you to fancy places, all of that.
But eventually,
they'll see past all the looks
and realize you for who you really are.
- Jackson, that'll never happen.
- Oh, you think it can't happen to you?
- Nah, you see all of this.
I'm not worried.
- You know what?
Your five minutes are up.
Unless you have something
else to get off your chest,
you can leave now.
- You know this whole pipe dream
of you becoming the next Johnnie Cochran,
yeah, I doubt that's gonna happen.
And I was okay before you came.
So trust me, I'll be fine without you.
- Be honest with yourself
and realize for a moment
that being with half a
man because of money,
isn't true love.
And after all this, Lynn,
I still love you, but I
can't stand the sight of you.
- Hey, I can't say that I blame you.
I do hope that we can at
least be cordial one day.
Take care of yourself, Jackson.
Just know that I love you.
Tell Ms. Courtney, I said, bye.
- Jack, just left work.
Liking that corner office, man.
How are you liking it?
- Yeah, it's okay, man.
I never thought I'd see that day,
I'd have my own office in a law firm.
And to make junior partner this fast?
Just the icing on the cake.
- I know how you feel.
Well, nah, not really.
You know, you being the Golden Child
of the law firm and all.
- Yeah, it's been a long road.
A lot of ups and downs.
But do you believe this?
We made it, bro?
- We made it.
Who'd thought, me and you?
Lawyers, right now.
- I know, right?
So tell me about that nurse
you went out with last week.
Did she check your temperature, yet?
- Man, she checked my temperature,
my blood pressure
and gave me a sponge bath.
- Boy, you know, you're wild.
Do she have any friends?
- What, you want one like mine?
- What type would that be?
- No self-esteem.
Show 'em a little bit of attention
and you all the way in.
- Remember, I just asked
if she had any friends.
Nevermind, scratch that, bro.
I'm good.
- How you doing?
- Hey.
- I'll have a large coffee, black please.
- Okay and what can I get for your friend?
- Oh, I'm not with him.
- I'm sorry, I just...
It seemed like you two were here together.
- That's okay.
- Add whatever she's having to my bill.
- Thank you, but I got it.
So matter of fact,
you can add whatever
he's having on to my tab.
- Okay, and that's your
usual order, right?
- Yes, a large espresso, to go.
- Gotcha, coming right up.
- Do you always turn a man down
when he tries to buy you coffee?
- Only today.
I'm just kidding.
Never had anyone ask me before,
so, thank you very much.
- Well, don't say I didn't try.
I'm sorry, I didn't,
what'd you say your name was again?
- You never asked me for my name.
- Ah, I'm Jackson Thomas.
And your name is?
- Well, hello, Mr. Jackson Thomas.
- I'm Shawn.
It's a pleasure to meet ya.
I've never seen you in here before.
- Pleasure's all mine.
And this is my first time coming here, so,
I'm sure that's the reason
you haven't seen me before.
- That would explain it 'cause I
definitely would have remembered if I had.
- Oh, is that right?
Well maybe I'll stop back in tomorrow
if you're gonna be here.
- Sounds good.
- Well, I better get going.
I have to get back to work,
but I guess I'll be seeing you again soon?
- Maybe.
Maybe not.
- Oh, believe me, I will.
- What's up, bruh?
- Dang, bro.
I see, I'mma have to
start locking my door.
-  man, look, Tracy told me
about that how new temp worker
back at the office, man.
You checked that out, yet?
- Yeah, man, I saw her,
kept right on the moving.
- You a trip, boy.
But look, you still trying to
check out that new spot
down there on third?
- Yeah, I'm with it.
- Cool, cool, man.
I'm gonna go call Tracy, man,
and see if he wanna roll with us.
- All right, cool.
- All right.
- Hey, hey, hey Brian.
Come here for a second, man.
Have a seat.
- What's up, man?
Everything good?
- Yeah, yeah, everything's cool, man.
Other than, the weirdest thing
happened to me the other day.
- What happened?
- I stopped by the coffee shop
on my way to the house
the other day, right?
- Okay.
- I'm standing at the counter.
I place my order
and standing next to me
is the most beautiful
woman I have ever seen.
- So what you tripping for?
- Bruh, I ordered my coffee.
Right?
- Hmm hmm.
- And the clerk assumed we were together.
So she asked what she was having.
- Hmm hmm.
- Bro, check this out.
Not only did she let her
know we weren't together,
but she offered to buy my coffee.
- But did you get her last name though?
- Man, what I need her last name for?
We talked all of three minutes.
- Bro, always get their last name.
That way you can Google them
and see if they're crazy
or got all kind of crazy
baby daddies and stuff, man.
- Man, that's not even
a weird part though.
What's crazy is,
man, I've been thinking
about this woman all day.
-  That's 'cause she fine, bro.
- Nah, man, it's much
bigger than the looks.
I can't really explain this.
Something about her.
- You should have asked her out, bro.
- I don't know, man.
I'm probably just tripping.
- Look, man, if it's something real, bro,
go back there tomorrow, man.
If she there, ask her out.
You don't want to miss out on
something if it's real, man.
I'mma call Tracy, man.
- No doubt.
Hmm.
- Excuse me, I'm sorry.
- I've seen you before.
- Coffee shop, right?
- Um, Jack-
- Jackson, yes, yes.
Are you following me?
Oh, you know what?
That's right, I owe you
money for the coffee, right?
- Don't do that, you
know what, don't even,
don't even, don't try that.
- So tell me, how is it that
we both ended up at this spot
at the same time?
- Because I work inside of this building.
- Get out of here.
Are you serious?
- I'm very serious.
I work on the 15th floor.
The only office I know on the 15th floor
is Wright & Collins, which happens to be
the biggest law firm in the city.
- Bingo.
- You work there?
- Yes, I work there.
You sound surprised.
- I didn't know any of us
worked for that law firm.
Are you the secretary?
- No, I'm not the secretary.
I have my own.
- I didn't mean to offend you.
It's just-
- That I'm black?
That I'm a woman?
- Honestly, it's both.
- I guess being a single
African-American woman
lead defense attorney in
a high-profile law firm
would be shocking to most.
- I'm honestly impressed.
- What, that I'm a lawyer?
Or that I'm single?
- Oh, you just gonna tell me,
you just came right at
me with that one, huh?
Wow.
- I'm just playing.
I'm just playing, so.
What are you doing here?
- I'm a lawyer, as well.
- Oh, both lawyers.
Drink coffee.
And single.
- Was that a pickup line, young lady?
- I'm just playing.
That is none of my business.
- Well, for the record, yes, I'm single.
- Listen, I don't wanna come off
as being too forward or anything but,
I know a nice cozy little restaurant
not too far away from here,
if you're not busy,
would you like to grab a bite to eat?
- Maybe.
Yes, I'd love to.
- That way, we can get to know
each other a little better.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
After you.
- Hey baby,
girl. How was your day?
- It was good, real good.
- You were out later than normal.
- Everything is fine, dad.
What you doing up so late?
- Prepared my lesson for Sunday.
Time of a pastor is never dull.
- This is true.
What is the lesson about this Sunday?
- Honesty,
love and trust.
- Hmm, that was one of
mom's favorite messages.
- Yeah, I really miss her.
But I'm grateful to God
for giving me such a wonderful daughter
who looks after her daddy.
- I know you miss mom.
I do, too.
But that's why I'm here to
make sure that you are okay.
- I am.
And I know, I didn't want you
to have to give up your place
to look after me.
It's been two years.
I want you to enjoy your life
and not have to worry about your dad.
- Daddy, when it's time for me to leave,
I'll let you know.
So quit trying to get
me up out of the house!
- Okay, baby, so what else is new?
- Well, I met a new guy.
His name is Jackson
and he works at a law firm
in the same building as mine.
- A lawyer?
That's nice.
- Now, what that's supposed to mean?
- Remember the last guy?
- I know, I know, but,
Jackson is different.
I can tell from today, he's a great guy.
- Whoa, slow down baby girl.
What you know about
this Jackson character?
- I know we have a date tomorrow.
Going to a basketball game.
- Granted, basketball
game, dinner is nice.
Not enough to know if he goes to church
or if he loves the Lord.
- Daddy, that is not how
people typically meet.
Like, what am I supposed to say?
Hello there, good looking.
My name is Shawn.
And do you love the Lord?
Like...
- You don't have to downplay,
you're the daughter of a
man of God, for anybody.
- I know, daddy.
I'm about to go to bed.
It's been a very, very long day.
- Don't forget to say your prayers.
- Daddy, I am 35 years old.
You don't have to remind
me of that every night.
Good night, I love you.
- Good night, baby girl.
- So do you take all your
dates to a basketball game?
- I haven't dated much recently.
- Me, either.
It's so hard to find a good guy
that just wants to know you
and not sleep with you, you know?
- Yeah, I feel you.
It's hard finding a woman that
wants a regular simple guy.
You know, most women want the athlete,
the celebrity,
you know, driving a fancy
car and a big house.
- Yeah.
I am not into none of
that superficial stuff.
- Like those two women sitting
court side at the game.
Do you honestly think they
were there to see the game
or there to pick them up a baller?
They probably couldn't even
tell you who was playing?
- Well, I don't know about them,
but I love the game.
- You love the game?
- I sure do.
- Really?
- Yes, really.
I grew up watching the game
and I played at the high school.
- Were you any good, though?
- Man, I was better than good.
I was the starting point guard
on the championship team.
- Okay, all right.
I see, I'mma have to check you out.
Get you out on the court
and see what you got.
- Boy, don't let these stilettos fool you.
I gets down on the court.
- Okay.
- And in the court.
- Look at you.
Well, you've just earned
yourself a basketball beat down,
pretty lady.
- Oh, did I?
- Yes, you did.
-  Boy, look at this wrist.
You see this wrist?
- It'll be blocked, off into the stands.
- Oh, whatever, that's
what I'mma do to you.
Three pointers, all up
in your face.
-  This is so beautiful.
- It is.
- You might find this
hard to believe, but,
it's the best date I've
been on in a long time.
- Really?
A good man like you, having
a problem with the ladies?
- It's the women I've been meeting.
And why are you asking
me all the questions?
Why are you single?
- Hmm, I guess the right man
just haven't caught me yet.
I mean, I'm not looking for a man, but,
I do expect for a man to find me.
- Well, that right man might
be right here in front of you.
- Maybe.
Mmm.
So...
So what do look for in a woman?
- I like to look a woman in her eyes.
You can tell a lot
about her soul that way.
- Oh, I see you laying it on pretty thick.
- Hmm hmm.
- I also like a woman that
has drive and ambition,
a woman that knows who she is
and not concerned with the
material things in life.
- I like that.
Tell me more.
- I love a woman that doesn't run away
the first sign of trouble.
- Sounds like you experienced that.
- Oh, I'm definitely
speaking from experience.
- I can see it in your eyes.
I can feel it.
I know those words came from a deep place.
- Is that right?
- Yeah.
Jackson, I feel a connection with you.
I just want you to know,
that you can be open with me.
- Yeah, I feel a connection with you, too.
And it scares the hell out of me.
I don't let too many people
into my personal space.
You know, I don't share much
about my past with them.
But I feel like I can with you.
- Jackson, you can.
- I need to tell you something
before we go any further.
- Please do not tell
me that you're married.
- No, no, it's nothing like that.
- Gay?
- No, all right, look,
let me just tell you.
- I'm listening.
- I have an eight-year-old daughter.
- That's it?
I am sure she is a beautiful little girl
and you are great father.
- Yeah.
I raised her after her mother died
and was a single dad for a long time.
- Hmm.
- Then I met the woman
that would eventually become my ex-wife.
- Oh, so you were married before?
Yes, I was.
- You mind sharing what happened?
I mean, we don't have to talk about it.
We can talk about something else.
I understand.
- No, that's fine.
She cheated on me six
months into the marriage.
And...
After that, I just promised myself,
I wouldn't allow myself to
fall in love ever again.
- Yeah, but, just because
one woman hurt you
doesn't mean that all of them will.
- I left one thing out.
- What's that?
- It was with a preacher.
And not just any preacher,
but the one who married us.
- Oh.
Sorry, but,
just seems like God knew you
deserved better than that.
- God?
Yeah, right.
It's the same God that
allowed it to happen.
- Okay, so I know you're hurt, but,
let's not, you can't blame
God for what happened?
- I don't blame God,
but I'm definitely not a fan
of his right now, for sure.
- And what's that suppose to mean?
- That I don't trust preachers,
pastors or anyone that's
associated with them.
- Hmm.
Jackson, I'm ready to go.
- Why, is everything okay?
- Eh, um, just gotta get caught
up on some work, that's all.
- I definitely understand that.
Hey listen,
I'm glad I feel like I can trust you.
- You can.
- Come on, let's go.
- Hey man, we ain't seen you
all month, bro, what's up, man?
- I know, I work with you and
I don't even see you no more.
- Hey, it sound like somebody all booed up
and can't even call his boys.
- Man, it's not even like that.
- Yeah, all right, bro.
- I've just been a little
busy with Shawn, that's all.
- Shawn?
She got that nose so wide open,
I can drop a tractor trailer
through that mug, B.
- Hey, bro, that girl do look good, bro.
- Hmm hmm.
- Man, I don't know what it is.
But being with her, does something to me.
- I know what it is, B.
She got that.
♪ Ohh wee ♪
- Fool clowning.
- Man, Tracy, is that
all you think about, man?
♪ Uh ha ♪
- Ain't no secret.
- Man, we haven't even
made it to that level.
- Tracy, man, it's a concept, bro.
Maybe if you take the time out
to get to know a woman like Jackson,
you might get a second date, bro.
- All I know is
she makes me happy in a way I haven't felt
in a very long time.
- Hey, that's great, bro.
- Speaking of which,
she's swinging by later.
I'mma introduce her to Courtney.
- You 'finna introduce her to Courtney?
- Yeah, that's what he said, bro.
- Man, you must really like this girl.
- Like I say, it's not
something that I was expecting.
It just happened.
- Well, I'm proud of you, bro.
- Hey man, as long as it,
I'm proud of you, too.
- Man, I appreciate that, fellas.
But you know what I
like about her the most?
- What's that man?
- Man, that she's honest.
You know what I mean?
- Yeah.
- We can talk about everything.
Like, we talk about our past,
our future, our goals.
Nothing's off limits.
- Hey, B, sound like we ain't go see Jack
for another two months, man.
- Man, it's gonna be like that?
- Hey, yo-
- I mean.
Just invite us to the wedding, man.
- It's all good.
- Hey, I want you on your best behavior
when my friend gets here, now.
- Yeah, I know, I'm a good kid, dad.
- I know.
It's just, I'm a little nervous
about the two of you meeting.
- Why are you so nervous, dad?
- Because, you're my favorite girl.
And I really hope that you like her.
The moment I've been waiting for.
Courtney, this is Ms. Shawn.
Shawn, this is my lovely
daughter, Courtney.
- Hey, Courtney.
I've heard so many good
things about you, young lady.
- Hi, Ms. Shawn.
- You could just call me, Shawn, sweetie.
- You can call her, Ms. Shawn.
- This is such a beautiful
sweater you have on.
- Thank you, my dad bought it for me.
- Well, your dad has good taste.
Mmm, this looks good.
- Yeah, my dad made spaghetti.
He's a great chef.
- Did you help your dad?
- Just a little bit because he said
he wanted it to be great for you.
- Is that so?
- Courtney, go wash
your hands, sweetheart.
- Jackson, she is adorable.
- Yeah, she's a pretty good kid.
- I can see where she gets her charm from.
- I wish I could take
all the credit for that.
But my mom, she helps me out a lot.
- Well, hopefully I'll get
to meet your mom, also.
- I think we'll let our guest say grace.
Let's hold hands.
- God, I thank you for this
food we're about to receive
and I thank you for this time
that we're spending together.
And God, I ask that you
bless the three of us
with more opportunities
to break bread together.
Amen.
- Amen!
- Let's dig in.
Courtney, it's time to call
it a night, sweetheart.
- Oh dad, can I stay up
just a little while longer
with you and Ms. Shawn?
- No, it's already past your bedtime.
- Please?
- Come on, Jackson.
- See?
- Okay, good night, dad.
Good night, Ms. Shawn.
- Good night, sweetheart.
- Good night, baby girl.
Daddy loves you.
I said, daddy loves you.
- Love you, too!
- Somebody is mad at you.
- Oh, these kids are a mess.
I think she likes you.
- You think so?
- Yeah, I can tell.
- That's good,
because I really like her dad.
- Her dad really likes you, too.
- What are you going to
do about it, Mr. Jackson?
- This.
- You've been hanging out a lot lately.
- I know, been with Jackson.
- Jackson?
- Yeah, we been hanging.
I even met his daughter
a couple of days ago.
- How old is she again?
- Eight, she's such a lovely girl.
- I got an idea.
Why don't you invite them to service
and afterwards, they could
come here for dinner.
- I don't know, Dad.
Maybe, some other time.
- Some other time?
You all have been dating a while now.
You're always together.
You even met his daughter!
- I know, but I just don't think
inviting them to church
is the right thing.
- Right thing?
Are you ashamed to be
the daughter of a pastor?
- Of course not, dad, it's just-
- Does he not believe in God?
- Yes, he just doesn't know
my father is a preacher.
- Sounds like you're ashamed.
- Dad, his ex wife cheated on him.
- What does that have to do with you?
- Everything, it was with a preacher.
- I can understand that,
but you don't have to
be somebody you're not
just to make him happy!
- I know, dad.
I'mma tell him.
I am.
I just need to figure out how.
- Do you think you love him?
- Yes, I do.
He's a good guy, a great father.
He actually reminds me of you.
- Well, if you love him, you'll tell him
and he'll understand
and everything you say,
he won't change nothing.
The last thing you want to do
is build a relationship on a lie.
- I'mma tell him.
I just need to do it on my own time.
- How was your day, today?
- It was great.
I won my third case in a row.
Now, I'm here with you.
Things couldn't be any better.
- Okay, that's what I'm talking about.
- And you're well on your way
to being the top lawyer in Atlanta.
- I mean, you know...
- Baby, I believe in you.
- You believing in me, that means a lot.
- Baby, the sky is the limit.
- Eh, you're not too
shabby, yourself, now.
I mean, don't act like that.
- What can I say, what can I say?
- That's not what we gonna do. 1842 You
know, I could see us being a power couple.
- Couple?
- Yes, a couple.
Did I say something wrong?
- No, it just kind of caught
me off guard, that's all.
Was that your way of
asking me to be your woman?
- Shawn, you know, I
really care about you.
- Yeah.
- You're constantly on my mind.
I even find myself thinking
about you whenever we're apart.
- I'm so glad you said that 'cause,
I feel the same way about you.
- Ew, that's a relief.
I was hoping that you didn't
want to be just friends.
-  I want way
more than just friends.
- I want to share something with you.
- What's that?
- I trust you with my heart.
- I don't, Jackson, I
don't know what to say.
- Just say,
that you love me.
- You love me?
- Yes.
Shawn, I love you.
- Wow.
Jackson, I need to,
I need to tell you something.
- As long as it's not anything
that's going to mess up this
moment and this feeling.
Go right ahead, baby.
I just wanted you to know,
that um,
I love you, too.
- That's what I wanted to hear.
- Hey, cheers.
- Cheers.
- To us.
- Hey Shawn, what's going on, family?
- All is well, all is well.
How you been?
- I've been well.
- Good.
- I'm just pressing in there,
trying to keep it together, you know.
- I get it.
- Indeed.
- Who's this little cutie
you got with you, today?
- This little princess is Courtney.
My boyfriend's daughter.
- Okay, well, hello, Courtney.
Welcome to the Listening Tree Bookstore.
How old are you?
- I'm eight.
- Eight years old.
And we got a lot of good stuff
for eight year olds, okay.
Are you looking for
anything in particular?
- Nothing in particular.
Today is our girls' day,
so we decided to come and get some books
and go and get some ice cream.
- Girl's date, ice cream.
- Yes.
- You excited?
- Yeah.
- All right, well listen,
let's get excited about
some books first, all right.
Look, check these out.
Got a few recommendations for you.
Check those out.
- All right.
- If you need anything,
let me, and you know what?
How about this?
This one's especially for you, all right?
If you guys need anything, let me know.
- Sure will, thank you.
- All right, I'm here.
- I'm so glad my dad let me
spend time with you today,
Ms. Shawn.
- Me too, sweetie.
- Girl, why are you dragging
me to a bookstore in the rain?
- Only going to be here five minutes.
I've just got to grab
this book for my niece.
- It better be five minutes.
- Lynn, isn't that Courtney over there?
- That sure is.
I wonder what she's doing here?
- Let's go see.
- Hey, boy!
- Oh, hey, mama.
- Where that grand baby of mine?
I bought her some clothes.
- Oh, she's out with Shawn.
I thought you were them.
- Oh, well it's safe to assume
that y'all are more than just friends now.
- Yeah, mama, we're
more than just friends.
- I really care about it, too.
- Hmm.
- And I know she cares a lot about me.
- Well, what about Courtney?
- Oh my gosh.
Courtney loves her to death.
- Oh, well, then that's
all that matters, baby.
I'm so happy for you, son.
Lord knows, she shole is better
than that last one you had.
- Thanks, mama.
- All right, baby.
- All right.
- All right, tell Courtney to call me.
- I'll have her call you, you be safe.
- I will.
- Well hello, Ms. Courtney.
Hey, it's me, Lynn.
- I know who you are.
- Okay, well, how are you?
Haven't seen you in such a long time.
And look at you, growing up so fast.
How is your dad?
- Her dad is doing just fine.
Thank you.
- So, your dad sent you here?
- No, her dad did not send her here.
She's here with me.
- I'm Shawn.
- Oh, okay.
- So, you probably don't know who I am.
- Oh, I know exactly who you are.
Lynn, the ex-wife of
my boyfriend, Jackson.
- Ladies, is everything okay?
- Oh, we're fine.
- Cool.
Well, if you need me, let me know, okay?
- So you do know who I am?
Courtney, please be sure and
tell your dad, I said, hi.
- Oh, we'll make sure to
tell hi, you said, hey.
- You ready, Courtney?
- Yeah, I'm ready.
- Let's go.
- Hmm, I don't know what he sees in her.
- Well, somebody's a little jealous.
- Oh please, if I want him,
I'll get them back now.
Plus, I hear he's this
big time lawyer now.
Oh yeah, I may have to get my man back.
- Good luck with that girl,
'cause ole girl and Courtney looked like
they was kind of happy together.
- Oh, I don't care what they look like.
Yeah, I'mma go by there and get him back.
- All right, sis.
- Well hello there, Mr. Thomas.
Oh, you're looking good.
- What are you doing here?
- Can I get a hug?
- Can I help you with something?
- Oh, I can't come in, okay?
- No.
- Look, I know you're busy.
You're probably working right now,
but you don't have to
be so formal with me.
It's me.
- Look, I'm very busy
with a case right now.
- Listen baby, I want you back.
I miss you.
I miss us.
I want my family back.
- What family?
- You and me and Courtney.
- Are you serious?
Okay, where are the
cameras that you brought?
Because I must be getting punked.
- Listen, I've given this a lot of thought
and I think that we
deserve a second chance.
- Do you not remember a certain
preacher that you screwed?
Hmm?
- Baby, that was in the past, okay.
I know I made a huge mistake
and I've learned from it, trust me.
I don't want the lifestyle.
I want you.
- Well, you should've thought
about this when you had me.
Now, I'm supposed to welcome
you back into our lives?
Are you crazy?
- No, I don't expect that right now.
I just want you to tell me
that you'll consider us.
- Lynn, I'm moved on
and I'm happy.
- Are you really, Jackson?
Because I bumped into
your little girlfriend
at the bookstore.
She is not your type.
- And what type would that be?
- Baby, come on now, look at me.
She is not me.
- You're right.
She's not you.
She's honest.
Trustworthy.
And that's more than I
can ever say about you.
- Listen, just think how
well we will be together now.
I mean, word on the street is,
you stopped renting,
you bought this house,
you made partner.
- Oh, I see what this is about.
I get it.
See, when I was working
that late night job
and going to school,
it wasn't enough for you.
- That's not it.
- Yeah, it is.
You thought I wasn't going to be nothing,
but now you think I'm this hot shot lawyer
and you want to walk right back into me
and my daughter's life.
- That's not it.
- Yes, it is.
- Baby, that's not it.
- That's exactly what it is!
Unfortunately, for you,
that will never happen.
So thanks for stopping by, Lynn.
I'mma have to ask you to leave my home.
- Don't do this.
Don't do this, you're not gonna do this.
- Have a great life, Lynn.
- Come on, baby-
- Babe, that workout was so intense.
I have never ran so many miles in my life.
-  I know, I'm so sore.
- I'm all sweaty.
- I see.
Maybe I should help you
get out of those wet, sweaty clothes.
- Jackson, you are a complete mess.
- I'm so tired.
- I am exhausted.
- Oh, you won't believe
who popped up today.
- Who?
- My ex-wife, Lynn.
- And what she want?
- Some nonsense about wanting
us to be a family again.
-  That don't surprise me at all.
Me and Courtney seen her at
the bookstore the other day.
- Why would that make her
want to pay a visit back here though?
- Ah, you're not a woman,
so I don't expect for you to get it.
Okay, so here it is.
The ex bumps into the new woman,
with her ex-husband's daughter, right?
- Okay.
- Jackson, a woman can have a good man,
a good thing going, mess
it up and be fine with it.
But as soon as he decides to move on,
all of a sudden, she wanna
go back down memory lane.
- Hmm hmm.
The vapors.
- The vapors.
- Got it.
Well, she definitely
won't be back around here.
- And how are you so sure about that?
- Because I told her that I'm happy.
- Hmm hmm.
- And that you are exactly
what Courtney and I needed in our lives.
- Hmm hmm.
- And that we love you.
- Hmm.
- So you don't have
anything to worry about.
- No, I'm not worried.
- Well, that's good to know.
- But I am tired,
so I'mma go and take a shower.
- Do you want me to join you?
- Enter at your own risk.
- I'll see you in there.
- Mm, that feels so good.
- How good does it feel?
- So good, that, I don't want you to stop,
at just my legs.
- I don't wanna stop either.
- It's gonna be much
harder after you leave.
- Who said anything about me leaving?
Courtney is at your mama's, right?
- Yes, until tomorrow.
- Then you don't have to stop.
You do love me, right?
- Baby, I'm in love with you.
- I'm in love with you, too.
♪ To show me exactly how
a true man should be ♪
♪ And I'll be right there to show you ♪
♪ How much I adore you ♪
♪ I don't think you know just
how much you mean to me ♪
♪ 'Cause your love ♪
♪ Is so amazing, baby ♪
♪ I could tell the world... ♪
-  All right.
There we go.
Good morning, beautiful.
- Good morning, handsome.
What you over here doing?
- Making you a nice, healthy smoothie.
- Oh, well, aren't you special?
- Try it out and let
me know what you think.
- Let me see what you're working with.
- Hmm, that's pretty good.
After last night, baby,
you deserve it.
- Wait, what are you talking about?
We didn't go all the way.
- We didn't?
- I know, I'm just playing.
- You know what?
You play too much.
- Baby, I gotta tell you.
What we shared last night was incredible.
I mean, I never,
held any woman all night.
- Never?
- Never.
- Jackson, do you know I've
dreamed of having a man
feel this way about me?
I need to tell you something.
- Oh, baby, look at the time, I gotta go.
I'm running behind.
- It'll only take a second.
- It's gonna have to wait.
- Just a minute.
- We'll talk about it later on.
I promise, we'll talk about it later on.
- I guess, it can wait.
- It's good to see you again, Ms. Ray.
- Good to see you, too, Mr. Thomas.
- Did you have an opportunity
to upload the documents
that I requested?
- Yes, I did.
- Let me take a look and
make sure we received those.
Okay.
Yes, we're good.
- Now, be honest with me.
Does it look like I have a case here?
- Absolutely.
I had a chance to look
over the police report
and we're definitely going to
move forward with your case.
- Yes, thank you.
- Oh, you're welcome.
- Thank you.
Wow, is this your wife?
- Oh no, we're not married.
Maybe, one day.
I sure hope so.
- Now listen, I hate to pry,
but I swear, she looks like
someone I go to church with.
Is her name Shawn?
- Yes, her name is Shawn.
- Wow, gorgeous.
- Did you say,
that you know her from church?
- Yeah, church.
Wait a minute.
You mean to tell me
that you two used to go
to the same church, right?
- No, we go to the same church right now.
Her dad is Pastor Reed
down at Second Baptist,
over on First Street.
Yeah, he took over for a guy
that stepped down last year.
Now, listen,
I don't mean to be messy,
but I heard he was messing
with one of the member's wives.
Hmm hmm, cheating.
- Is that right?
- Yes.
- You're sure we're talking
about the same person?
She never mentioned that
her dad was a pastor.
- Whoa, whoa, listen.
I am so sorry.
I didn't mean to cause any confusion.
Listen, I just assumed that you knew
that your possible future wife
would let you know that
her father was a pastor.
- You know what?
No need to apologize.
Matter of fact,
she did mention that one day.
I just, I must've forgot.
- Well, now that you put it that way,
listen, when you see her,
be sure to tell her I said hi
and make sure to let her know,
I will see her this Sunday at church.
- Oh, believe me, I definitely will.
-  So glad you got
me out of the office.
I was just thinking about you.
- Really?
What were you thinking?
- How you've changed my life
in ways that I couldn't even imagine.
But that's not the reason
why you had me to come by.
So, what's going on?
- I was wondering if you wanted to
go with Courtney and I
to the movies on Sunday?
- This Sunday?
- Yeah, this Sunday.
Is that an issue?
- Can I check with you or-
- Wow.
I didn't know your man had to get in line
to spend time with you.
- Jackson, that's not it.
- It's not?
What is it, then?
Is there something you
need to share with me?
- I tried to tell you before.
- Tell me what?
- Can you just hear me out, please?
- I'm listening.
- The reason why I'm unsure is because
I'm the head of that church.
My father pastors Second Baptist Church.
And I direct the choir
and they need me at service.
I am so sorry.
I know I should have told you way earlier.
- So why didn't you?
-  Because I know
how you feel about church.
- So you keep it from me, instead?
You let me tell you over and over again,
how I feel about these
churches and these preachers.
Never found a time to tell me?
That was selfish!
- I tried to tell you at
the house and at the park.
- I trusted you, Shawn.
Had you around Courtney.
And all this time, it's
been nothing but a lie.
- I didn't want something so small
to come in between what we have.
- Well, from the looks of things,
what you and I were building
was built on nothing but lies.
- What do you mean, were?
- What I mean is,
I don't want to see you anymore.
- We're done.
- Huh, so you gonna walk away from us
because my father is a pastor?
- No, I'm walking away because you lied
and can't be trusted.
- Can't be trusted?
Well, if what my father does
bothers you enough for you to leave me,
did you ever really love me?
- Oh, hell no.
Don't try to flip and twist this up on me.
I'm not the one who lied.
- Listen, I know your
ex-wife hurt you bad,
but that was her, not me.
And yeah, I should've
told you, but I didn't.
So what now?
You're gonna run away like you always do?
Huh?
Well, you just keep on running, Jackson.
Did it ever cross your mind that maybe,
just maybe, you was the
one to make the mistake
and marry the wrong person?
- The only mistake I made
was trusting you.
- I love you.
And what I feel for you is real.
But you need to quit having a pity party
and get over it!
Because you will never,
and I mean never be able to move on
unless you let go of your past.
Bye, Jackson.
- Y'all crazy.
- I'm telling you man.
Y'all need to get with them triple D's.
Okay.
Why not?
Hold on, hold on.
J, you tell Brian about the argument
you got into with baby
girl the other night?
- Man, what happened?
- I'd rather not get into it.
- Whatever it was, had to be bad
'cause baby girl left out of
here with smoke behind her.
- What?
- Tracy, just drop it.
I said, I'd rather not talk about it, man.
- Damn man, she was
nice, man. I liked her.
- Yeah, well, looks can be deceiving.
- I feel you on that, man,
'cause women like that,
always got something to hide.
- You can say that again.
- Women like that always
got something to hide.
- Hey man, what was she hiding?
- Man, she just wasn't
what she appeared to be.
That's all I'm saying.
- I tried to tell you, man.
Them pretty girls is the ones
you always got to watch out for.
Was she a stripper or something?
- No, she lied to me about her father.
- And that's why it won't work?
- Her father is a pastor.
- And that's why I won't work!
- Man, you think I would get involved
with a woman whose father is a preacher
after everything I've been through?
- Oh man, you got to let
that bitterness go, man.
- I don't have to let anything go, man.
- Man, hold on, hold on, hold on.
You're trying to tell me,
because Lynn cheat on you with a pastor
and Shawn father happen to be a pastor,
that you walked away?
Man, that got to be the dumbest thing
I've ever heard you say.
- Man, we gonna hang out
and are were gonna sit here
and kick it like females?
I'm done.
- Nah, I'm done, man.
- Let's roll, man.
♪ Here I am, all alone ♪
♪ Know exactly how I ended here ♪
♪ How can you love when
you don't give your all ♪
♪ How can you love your fears ♪
♪ It's impossible for me to do this ♪
♪ Forcing my will ♪
♪ I know I'll be okay ♪
♪ I know I will if I trust ♪
♪ In ♪
♪ You ♪
- Baby girl, you ready
to let the saints of God
hear your wonderful voice?
- I guess so.
- Is something wrong?
- Everything is fine, dad.
- Did your friend come today?
- No, he couldn't make it.
Maybe, next week.
- Next week is good.
We need more men, positive role models
and good fathers in the church.
Do you think he'd be
interested in helping us out?
- Dad, can we drop it, please?
You got a Sunday service to get ready for.
- I'll drop it for now.
But we're gonna to talk about it later.
- I said I'd rather not discuss it.
Besides,
I don't think I'm going to be seeing
much more of Jackson, anyway.
- Well, I'm sorry about that,
but God knows what's best.
- Dad, can you stop it
with the God stuff, please?
Every, since I was a little girl,
it's been God this and God that.
And then if I just trust in God,
that everything will be just fine.
Here it is, I meet the man of my dreams
and I can't even be with him
because of what a
so-called man of God did?
Save it!
- Baby girl, your mother
and I raised you right.
We raised you to have a
relationship with God.
And just because you are a believer,
does not exempt you from
trials and tribulations.
And there are people that
call themselves preachers,
all of them are not called.
And those that are, guess what?
They have issues, too.
These people that are out here,
they're going through
trials and tribulations,
but it should not make you waiver
from what God has called you to do.
- My faith is not wavering.
I just wish Jackson wasn't so hurt.
And I don't even know
what to do to help him.
- The best thing you can
do for him is pray for him.
Now, get yourself together
and let's go out here and praise God.
♪ Lord, I trust in you ♪
♪ Lord, I need you ♪
- I'm glad you finally
decided to accept my offer.
I was beginning to think you
didn't find me attractive.
- I usually don't date coworkers.
That's all it was.
- So you do find me attractive?
- Very much.
But, that's all I know
about you right now.
Tell me,
what are some of your likes and dislikes?
- Well, I like shoes, clothes, purses,
you know, things like that.
- All right, okay.
So where do you see
yourself in five years?
- Can I get you guys anything to drink?
- I'll take a glass of Chardonnay.
- Excuse me, Chardonnay?
We don't serve that here.
- I wouldn't think that you did.
- I'll take a Long Island, instead.
- Ma'am, we don't serve liquor here.
This is a cafe.
- Well, in that case,
bring me a hot chocolate
since he's so hot and chocolate.
- And for you, sir?
- We'll just take two espressos, please.
- Gotcha, coming right up.
- Thank you.
- You do know I could
order my own beverage?
- You ordered a Chardonnay
and a Long Island.
How old are you again?
- 30.
- 30, and you didn't know
that there's no liquor at coffee shops?
- So you're trying to say
that you're better than me,
Mr. Lawyer with a corner office?
- No, not at all.
- Here you go.
Would you guys be ordering any brunch?
- Yes, I will just have the
grilled veggie burger, please.
- Okay, and for you?
- I'll take the corn dog
with the chili cheese fries.
No, wait, I'll take
chicken fingers.
No, wait.
What is this?
A pu-nan-i?
- Ma'am, it is pronounced panini.
- Okay, you keep that.
I'll just take whatever he's having.
- Okay, will that be all, sir?
- Yes, it will be.
And please, make it quick.
I'm sure you understand?
- Oh, I do.
I definitely do.
I'm gonna get started on that.
- Thank you.
You do realize that this is a cafe, right?
- What's that supposed to mean?
It means that you don't have to act
like you at the local Coney Island.
-  Whatever.
Anyway, how did you become
this big time lawyer and stuff?
- There is no stuff.
I studied and went to
school to get my law degree.
- That's what's up.
You're so sexy.
- Oh, would you look at the time?
You know what, I'm sorry.
I forgot, I have to pick up my daughter
from her piano practice.
Wait, can we get those
two orders to go, please?
- Of course, you can.
- Yes, thank you.
- No problem.
- You know what?
I do love a man who has
his priorities straight.
Maybe we could hook up later.
- That's not possible.
We do homework afterwards,
but maybe some other time.
- That is such a turn on.
- And this is such a turn off.
- J, what's up with you and
honey, man, from the job?
What happened to the
date y'all had yesterday?
- Eh.
- So we keep it secrets now?
- Hmm hmm.
-  Man, she
ordered some chili fries.
- Okay?
What's wrong with that?
- Bro, we were at a cafe.
- Okay, what's wrong with that?
- Brian, tell this clown
that booty and no brains,
equals zero chance of a relationship.
- Who said something about a relationship?
Man, just have some fun.
-  Come on, Tracy.
Me and Jack's both seen some
of the women you mess with.
Let's just say,
neither one of them gonna
be winning a beauty contest,
no time soon.
- Yeah and you know, you
don't screen them, at all.
- Really, really?
Hey, y'all hating on the process, man.
Y'all know I love my
women with the triple D's.
- What's the triple D's?
- Dingy.
Dumb.
And desperate!
Hmm hmm.
- We all three intelligent,
smart brothers, right?
- Hmm hmm.
- Hey, hold on, B.
I don't know about all three of us.
- Come on, man, think about it.
I'm the vice-president
at one of the largest banks in Atlanta.
You two are lawyers at one
of the biggest law firms.
So we don't have to settle
for none of these women
who don't got their stuff together, man.
- You got a good point there, B.
- Look man, I ain't
telling you to get married
and have a bunch of kids.
I'm just saying, Jack, have some fun, man.
- Man, I don't know.
- Listen, man, call Shawn.
You miss her.
- Thanks for inviting me.
I knew you'd reconsider.
- Yeah, I'm actually glad that I did.
- Me, too.
This is such a nice neighborhood.
I could see myself living here.
- Really?
- Yeah.
You know what?
- What's up?
- We're going to have so much fun tonight.
- Yes, we are, Shawn.
- Shawn?
Who is Shawn?
- I didn't call you, Shawn.
- You just call me, Shawn, Jackson.
- I did?
-  Yeah.
- I'm so sorry.
-  Let's go inside.
- You know what?
Oh, I'm sorry.
I can't do this.
- You can't do this?
- I can't do this.
- You know what, Jackson, this
is the second time with you.
When you get it together,
you know my number.
And the name is Sherry.
- Damn.
- I heard this movie was pretty good.
- Yeah, me too.
Thank you for the invite.
- I'm glad you can make it.
- Hey, what are you doing?
Oh no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Nope, nope, nope, nmm mm.
- Come on, don't fight it.
- Fight what?
- This.
I'm feeling you.
I wanna be with you
and I want to be your woman.
- You don't even know me!
- I feel like I know enough.
- Okay.
I think it's time for you to leave, now.
Go ahead and go.
- Leave?
The movie just started.
- I know, but it has ended for you.
- Do you wanna talk about it?
'Cause we can talk about it.
Wait, first off, just please tell me,
who hurt you?
You can tell me.
- It's time for you to go, now.
- Okay.
- What is wrong with y'all brothers?
Y'all say y'all want a good woman.
Y'all get it and then
y'all just push them away?
- If you don't get your
fast tail up outta here.
- Now, I'm fast?
That's my cue.
Before I leave,
something is definitely wrong with you,
turning all this down.
So when I leave,
you better get a good look.
Okay?
- Bye, bye.
Hey, mama.
- Hey, baby.
You haven't answered your phone.
I've been calling you for days.
- Mama, I have a lot going on right now.
Is this an emergency?
- Yes, it's an emergency.
Anytime you don't answer
my call, it's an emergency.
What's going on?
- Mama, I just want to be left alone.
- Hmm, so I take it, this
about that girl you dating?
What happened?
- I'd rather not talk about it.
- Baby, that was the happiest
I had seen you in a long time.
Now tell me what happened?
- Mama, she lied to me.
- Oh.
Okay.
I want to share something with you.
- Mama, please.
I don't want to hear one of
your long drawn out stories.
Mama, I'm not in the mood.
- Oh, you gonna want to hear this?
When I first met your father,
I did not share with him my
inability to have children
because all he talked about
was having a son.
When I didn't get pregnant,
he wanted to have tests done
because he thought it was him.
And when he found out it was me, baby,
he was devastated.
Completely upset.
- Mama, if you couldn't get
pregnant, how did I get here?
- Baby, let me finish.
I did not tell your father
that I couldn't have children
because I didn't want
to hurt his feelings.
Now when he first found
out, baby, he was angry.
But after some time, he got past it
and he realized that I was
just trying to protect him.
We worked it out
and after a small routine
procedure, I got pregnant.
- So, am I adopted?
-  Boy, of course not.
- I have to check, I have to check, mama.
- Listen, the point is,
if he hadn't forgiven me,
baby, you wouldn't be here.
- Hmm, thanks, mama,
I needed to hear that.
- Hmm hmm.
- I think I know why Shawn didn't tell me.
It wasn't to deceive me.
It was to protect me.
- Oh, baby, now you're starting to get it.
- Mama, I treated her so bad.
- Hmm, that's okay.
Do you love her?
- I really do love her.
- Well then, get up off your behind, boy,
and go get that woman.
- Okay, I'mma get out of here, mama.
I appreciate you.
- Aw, you welcome.
I love you, now.
- Hmm hmm.
- See you later on.
- All right.
And stop all that moping.
Thomas' don't mope, baby.
- All right, mama.
I see you later.
- See ya later.
I love you.
- Love you, too.
- Hey, Jackson.
- Robin, how are you doing?
- I'm doing good.
It's good to see you, man.
- Yeah, it's good to see you, too.
- Look, I know you probably think
that I was okay with what Lynn was doing,
but I told her that she
was making a big mistake
and now you're the one making the mistake.
- What are you talking about?
I'm talking about how you
need to learn how to forgive.
You can't keep holding on to
what you and Lynn went through
because once you probably
learn how to forgive,
you'll be able to love again.
-  Love again?
Yeah, right.
- Yes, love again.
I heard about you and your new little boo
and how you willing to let go of her
over something so small.
You need to forgive that girl.
But, I gotta go.
I gotta get on up out of here.
I see you later, Jackson.
- Take care, Robin.
- Come in!
- Hello, Jackson.
- If you don't mind me asking,
what brings you by?
- I came to talk to you about my daughter.
- With all due respect,
what Shawn and I are dealing with,
that's between the two of us.
- I understand that,
but I have something I just
need to share with you.
- Speak your piece.
- Jackson, I don't normally
get into Shawn's personal life,
but this time, I think I need to step in.
I'm very much aware that
she did not tell you
that I was a pastor.
And I agree, she should have.
But her not telling you
let's me know how much she cares for you.
- So, what you're saying is
her not telling me your profession,
suppose' to prove that she cares?
I don't understand.
- She knew how hurt you were
due to the actions of your
ex-wife and the pastor.
And she sympathizes with you,
but son, don't let the actions
of someone else make
you miss your blessing.
- Well, man comes before the cloth.
And it's not just one man.
Every time I turn on the television
or watch the news, it's
pastors, preachers or priests,
all in the news for wrongdoing.
- Well, Jackson, to be
honest, you're mad at them,
but you're also mad at yourself
for allowing it to happen.
When you married her, you
knew something wasn't right,
but yet, you married her anyway.
So the first thing you need to do
is forgive yourself.
- And what happens when I forgive myself?
- Then, you'll forgive others.
- Good morning, church.
- Good morning!
- I said, good morning, church!
Good morning!
- This is the day that the Lord has made
and we shall rejoice
and be glad in it!
I will say that we're going
to have a wonderful day
in the Lord today.
He has gifted me to be able
to give a wonderful message
and the message will encourage us today
that he is a possible God
that can do the impossible.
But before I deliver that message,
we're going to be favored by selection
with our choir being directed
by my daughter, Shawn.
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Give ♪
♪ Thanks ♪
♪ Unto the lord ♪
Good morning!
-  Good morning.
- Can we go to the mall, today?
- I was thinking something else.
How you feeling about
going to church, instead?
- We haven't been in so long.
- I know, right.
I think it's about time,
we start back going.
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Give ♪
♪ Thanks ♪
♪ Unto ♪
♪ The ♪
♪ Lord ♪
♪ For His mercy endureth ♪
♪ When I ♪
♪ Should have been cast out ♪
♪ God kept me ♪
♪ Kept me ♪
♪ And when I should have been forsaken ♪
♪ God kept me ♪
♪ Loved me ♪
♪ Now I'm living out ♪
♪ Abiding God ♪
♪ Your grace ♪
♪ Thank you ♪
♪ For saving ♪
♪ Me, Lord ♪
♪ So thank you ♪
♪ For saving me ♪
♪ Lord, I thank you, yeah ♪
♪ For loving me ♪
♪ I thank you, Lord ♪
♪ For holding me ♪
♪ Lord, I thank you ♪
♪ For keeping me ♪
♪ His mercy ♪
♪ It endureth ♪
♪ Every time I wake up in the morning ♪
♪ You bring me mercy ♪
♪ Your mercy ♪
♪ It endureth ♪
♪ Lord, your mercy ♪
♪ Endureth ♪
♪ Say yeah ♪
♪ Say yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Say yes ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Say yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
- Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Yeah, come on, come on, and bless 'em.
Come on and bless 'em.
Give him 'em a yes.
Give 'em a yes in the house!
He is worthy.
He's worthy, come on, Zion.
Come on, Zion, let him hear your yes.
Let him hear your yes.
Let him hear your yes!
- Yes!
- Let him hear your yes!
Let him hear your yes, in the house!
And we bless him.
Thank you, choir.
Thank you, choir, for
that wonderful selection.
And we bless you all.
And we bless you.
God, we bless you today, y'all.
We we thank God for who he is
and what he has done.
God is speaking to us.
So many of us have gone through
trials and tribulations.
And God is saying to
you, I've heard your cry!
I know exactly what you're going through.
And I am here
just like I was with
the children of Israel.
I am now come down, to
deliver you out of your trial,
to deliver you out of your tribulation.
Will there be one?
There is a voice that
God is speaking to you
and God is saying unto you,
I am your Father and you are my child.
He's pulling you up right here and now.
And he's asking you,
will you head the call?
Will you understand that He loves you
with an everlasting love.
The doors of the church are open.
And we're asking now, will you come?
Is there one?
Is there one, that will
hear the voice of God
knowing that he's speaking to you.
I know it's several people in here,
but God is speaking to you.
He's calling you by name.
He's saying my son, my
daughter, come onto me.
All that labor and a heavy laden,
I will give you rest.
Is there one?
This is safe harbor here.
You don't have to worry about drowning.
You don't have to worry about
nobody letting you fall.
This is a safe place.
This is a good place.
It's a wonderful place.
Will you come from the darkness?
Pastor, I don't know if I'm in darkness.
You're surrounded by
things you can't explain.
You're surrounded by things
you don't understand.
You cannot see from your
left, from your right.
God is saying, now, I
want to open your eyes.
I want to shine the light down on you.
Will you, will you hear from God
to walk in the light,
no longer walking in darkness.
I can't guarantee you money,
cars, houses, and land,
but I can guarantee you
that you now have a help
in dealing with whatever
you're dealing with.
Will you allow your life
to be turned around?
Will you allow your life now
to be turned around by God?
Nobody's gonna judge ya.
Nobody's looking at your past.
All God is saying,
I have a future for you.
Will you now go
from your past to the
future God has for you.
Now allow your life to be turned around.
Is there one?
The light is shining on you, now.
Come from your darkness.
Your darkness of hurt,
your darkness of pain,
your dark of humiliation.
God is speaking to you.
Yes, my brother.
Yes, my sister.
Is there another?
That's it, that's it, come on.
Let's celebrate.
God has come in.
Is there another?
God is speaking to you.
God is saying, they're not the only ones.
Is there another?
Will you come?
Will you come and be with God?
God is commanding us.
He's speaking to us.
He's saying to us,
come, each and every one of you, come,
I have a place for you.
We bless your name, God.
We glorify you, God.
We thank you, God.
Bless you, son.
Thank you for coming to be with us today.
- Yes.
- On behalf of the church,
we welcome you to our church family.
Thank you for coming.
God, we bless you.
- Yes.
- Can I say something, pastor?
- Sure.
- You know, I've allowed
personal anger,
hurt and pain to
determine how I felt about coming here.
And because of that,
I've hurt a lot of people
that cared about me.
I want to apologize to everyone,
for the way I've been acting,
especially to you, Shawn.
I've let go of those things
I've been holding on to.
Thank
you, God, thank you, God.
- And to prove what I'm saying.
- Jackson, what are you doing?
- Something I should've
done a long time ago.
Pastor, with your permission.
- Yes.
- Shawn, will you marry me?
- Oh, praise God!
Praise God, praise God!
This is a wonderful time, in God's house.
It's a wonderful time, in our family.
Come on y'all, let's celebrate.
Let's celebrate.
Joy is in this house.
Love is in this house.
The greatest thing in
this house is forgiveness.
Forgiveness is in this house.
This is what God loves
and it's marvelous in his eyes.
- Can I say something?
Look, Jackson, I know I'm the last person
you want to see right now.
I mean, I disrespected your home.
You, as a man.
I embarrassed my wife.
- Yes, you did.
- The church.
And for that, man, I'm deeply sorry.
So I humble myself to ask
you for your forgiveness.
Will you forgive me, Jackson?
- I forgive you, man.
- Aw, man.
- Amen, come on, y'all.
Let's give God praise.
This is what forgiveness
is like in the flesh
and we bless God
and we celebrate.
We celebrate, it's a
joyous time in our family.
It's a joyous time in our church.
And we thank God for this.
Come on, saints.
Clap your hands and
bless God for this sign.
Subsynced balloumowgly