Narrator:
IN AN OLD HOUSE IN PARIS
THAT WAS COVERED
WITH VINES...
[WOOF WOOF]
LIVED 12 LITTLE GIRLS
IN 2 STRAIGHT LINES.
THEY LEFT THE HOUSE
AT HALF PAST 9:00
IN 2 STRAIGHT LINES
IN RAIN OR SHINE.
HEE HEE HEE!
THE SMALLEST ONE
WAS MADELINE.
FRESH SNOW HAD FALLEN
THROUGH THE NIGHT.
ALL OF PARIS
WAS UNDER WHITE.
THE GIRLS WAITED,
SHIVERING, AT THE GATE.
IT WASN'T LIKE MISS CLAVEL
TO BE LATE.
[COUGHS]
AH-CHOO!
NOW WHAT IS
THAT SOUND THEY HEAR?
OHHH!
SOMETHING IS AMISS, I FEAR.
MISS CLAVEL, IT SEEMS,
HAS CAUGHT A COLD.
NOW, LET THIS NARRATIVE...
UNFOLD.
YOU ARE UNWELL,
MISS CLAVEL?
DO NOT WORRY,
LITTLE GIRLS.
I WILL BE BETTER
TOUT DE SUITE.
AH-AH-AH-CHOO!
[WHIMPERS]
ALLO?
DR. COHN?
C'EST TRAGIQUE!
AN EMERGENCY!
COME AT ONCE,
S'IL VOUS PLAIT.
MERCI, MRS. MURPHY.
BE CAREFUL.
HMM.
MERCI,
GIRLS.
WHATEVER WOULD I DO
WITHOUT YOU?
OH, THIS IS NOT GOOD.
YOU MUST STAY IN BED.
BUT MY GIRLS...
Dr. Cohn: THEY
WILL LOOK AFTER YOU.
[OUT-OF-TUNE VIOLIN PLAYING]
OHH!
MY HEAD!
IT ALREADY ACHES
SO BADLY!
Narrator: THE DISTURBANCE,
IT SEEMS,
CAME FROM NEXT DOOR
AT THE HOUSE
OF THE SPANISH AMBASSADOR,
WHERE PEPITO WAS,
SO TO SPEAK,
SETTLING A SCORE.
PEPITO!
HUH?
HOLA,
MADELINE!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
MAMA INSISTS I LEARN
TO PLAY THE VIOLIN.
PEPITO,
MISS CLAVEL
IS NOT WELL.
YOUR MUSIC IS
HURTING HER HEAD.
OH.
¡PERFECTO!
I WILL TELL MAMA
NO VIOLIN
TILL MISS CLAVEL
IS BETTER.
TILL TOMORROW!
AH-CHOO!
KEEP HER WARM
AND GIVE HER LOVE.
SHE WILL RECOVER
SOON ENOUGH.
Girls:  MERCI, DR. COHN!
THERE. ALL TUCKED IN.
MISS CLAVEL, YOU MAY
PLAY WITH MY MARBLES.
THEY WILL CHEER YOU UP!
THANK YOU,
MA PETITE,
BUT YOU KEEP THEM.
I KNOW
HOW YOU TREASURE THEM.
DO NOT WORRY,
MES ENFANTS.
YOU MAKE ME HAPPY.
TOMORROW, I WILL BE BETTER.
[COUGHS] AND
I WILL TAKE CARE OF YOU.
Narrator: MISS CLAVEL
WENT TO SLEEP
AS THE GIRLS TIPTOED OUT.
SHH! DON'T WAKE HER!
QUIET NOW!
Narrator: BUT THAT EVENING
AT BEDTIME,
THEY STILL HAD SOME DOUBTS.
All, sadly: OHH!
WHAT MORE CAN WE DO
FOR MISS CLAVEL?
PAPA READS BOOKS TO ME
WHEN I AM SICK.
IL ETAIT UNE FOIS.
HEE HEE HEE!
GRANDMAMA MAKES ME
HER SPECIAL ONION SOUP.
OHH, C'EST BON!
MAMA COMES HOME LATE
FROM HER PERFORMANCES,
BUT WE STILL PLAY
WITH MY DOLLS.
[SQUEAKING]
HEE HEE HEE!
OHH, I REMEMBER,
MAMA WOULD LET ME
STAY IN HER BED
AND BRUSH MY HAIR.
SHE LET ME WEAR
THE NECKLACE
PAPA GAVE HER
WHEN THEY FIRST MET.
BUT NOT ANYMORE.
OHH.
AT LEAST YOU STILL
HAVE YOUR FAMILIES.
I HAVE NO ONE NOW.
[CRYING]
PAUVRE
MADELINE!
NO FAMILY!
HOW SAD!
[ALL CRYING]
SOMETHING IS NOT RIGHT!
SOMETHING IS QUITE WRONG!
[GIRLS CRYING]
LITTLE GIRLS,
WHAT IS WRONG?!
WE ARE SORRY,
MISS CLAVEL.
WE ARE FEELING SAD
BECAUSE--[SNIFFLES]--
POOR MADELINE
HAS NO FAMILY!
Miss Clavel:
MES ENFANTS,
DO NOT FORGET.
WE ARE NOT ONLY BORN
INTO FAMILIES,
WE CAN ALSO FIND THEM,
JUST AS WE HAVE FOUND
EACH OTHER.
FAMILIES COME IN
ALL SHAPES AND SIZES.
IS IT THE SAME,
MISS CLAVEL?
I DO NOT THINK SO.
WHAT DO WE SAY
AT EACH MEAL?
WE LOVE OUR BREAD,
Girls: WE LOVE OUR BUTTER,
BUT MOST OF ALL,
WE LOVE EACH OTHER.
PERHAPS IT IS SO.
I KNOW
IT IS!
BUT, MISS CLAVEL,
YOU MUST GO BACK TO BED.
YOU WILL GET MORE SICK.
AND THEN
WHERE WILL WE BE?
All: OH, PLEASE, MISS CLAVEL!
YOU MUST STAY WARM!
GO BACK TO BED,
MISS CLAVEL!
I WILL GO TO BED
IF YOU
WILL GO TO BED.
[ALL YAWN]
I WILL GO TO SLEEP...
IF YOU
WILL GO TO SLEEP.
WILL YOU HAVE SWEET DREAMS
IF WE HAVE SWEET DREAMS?
OUI, MA CHERIE.
Narrator:
THE MORNING ARRIVED
AND THE POSTMAN AS WELL...
[DING DING DING]
WITH A LETTER ADDRESSED,
"CARE OF MISS CLAVEL."
[WOOF WOOF]
BONJOUR,
MISS CLAVEL.
HOW ARE YOU FEELING?
MUCH BETTER,
MA PETITE.
MERCI.
BON,
GENEVIEVE!
OOH, LA LA!
AN ANNOUNCEMENT?
AN INVITATION?
A BIRTHDAY CARD?
All: FOR WHOM?
MADELINE.
OUI,
MISS CLAVEL?
"MIT
LOVE,
FROM YOUR LONG-LOST
UNCLE HORST."
I AM PART OF A FAMILY!
I HAVE AN UNCLE!
FROM VIENNA!
AND HE IS COMING HERE!
TO SEE ME!
All:
C'EST MERVEILLEUX!
HOW WONDERFUL!
Miss Clavel:
GIRLS, GIRLS!
WE MUST PREPARE!
EVERYTHING
MUST BE READY
FOR MADELINE'S
UNCLE HORST!
HE IS HER FAMILY!
♪ ARMS THAT WARM ME
♪ WHEN I'M COLD
♪ LIPS THAT SMILE
♪ AND NEVER SCOLD
♪ EARS THAT LISTEN
♪ HANDS THAT HOLD
♪ ONCE MORE,
I HAVE A FAMILY ♪
♪ HOMEMADE CHOCOLATE
CREME SOUFFLÉS ♪
♪ PICNICS
ON ALL HOLIDAYS ♪
♪ SUMMER BEACHES
♪ WINTER SLEIGHS
All: ♪ ONCE MORE,
SHE HAS A FAMILY ♪
♪ FAMILY
♪ THE ONES
WHO HELP YOU UP ♪
♪ EACH TIME YOU FALL
♪ FAMILY
♪ THE ONES WHO HANG
YOUR DRAWINGS ♪
♪ ON THE WALL
♪ FAMILY
♪ THE ONES WHO TRULY
LOVE YOU MOST OF ALL ♪
♪ ONCE MORE
♪ I HAVE A FAMILY
♪ WORDS OF COMFORT
WHEN I'M SCARED ♪
♪ AGE-OLD STORIES
TO BE SHARED ♪
♪ GIFTS THAT SHOW ME
SOMEONE CARED ♪
♪ ONCE MORE,
I HAVE A FAMILY ♪
♪ FAMILY
♪ THE ONES WHO
WIPE YOUR TEARS ♪
♪ WHEN YOU FEEL SMALL
♪ FAMILY
♪ THEN ONES WHO'LL
ALWAYS BE THERE ♪
♪ WHEN YOU CALL
♪ FAMILY
♪ THE ONES WHO TRULY
LOVE YOU MOST OF ALL ♪
♪ ONCE MORE
♪ I HAVE A FAMILY
♪ FAMILY
♪ SHE HAS A FAMILY
♪ THE ONES WHO TRULY
LOVE YOU MOST OF ALL ♪
♪ LOVE YOU MOST OF ALL
♪ ONCE MORE
♪ I HAVE A FAMILY
Miss Clavel:
DOUX REVES, MES CHERIES.
SWEET DREAMS.
TOMORROW WILL BE
AN EXCITING DAY!
SLEEP WELL.
All: GOOD NIGHT, GOOD NIGHT,
DEAR MISS CLAVEL.
Chloe: PSST! MADELINE!
ARE YOU AWAKE?
OF COURSE!
THIS IS NO TIME
FOR ME TO SLEEP.
NOR ME!
OR ME!
DO YOU THINK
HE'LL HAVE RED HAIR?
LIKE MINE?
WHO WILL HE BE,
THIS UNCLE HORST?
I KNOW.
A FAMOUS NOVELIST
FROM THE ACADEMY,
LIKE OUR BELOVED
VICTOR HUGO.
A BRAVE SOLDIER.
NON, NON.
A GENERAL
WITH MEDALS
AND DECORATIONS.
OR...
AN ADMIRAL
IN COMMAND
OF HIS OWN FLEET.
NON,
NON!
HE MUST BE A PRINCE
WITH A CASTLE
AND FINE HORSES.
MADELINE?
WHAT DO
YOU
SEE?
HE'S SURE
TO BE HANDSOME...
AND INTELLIGENT...
AND RICH...
AND SLENDER...
AND VERY, VERY KIND.
MONSIEUR PERFECT.
Narrator: IN THE MORNING
AS THEY LEFT
THE OLD HOUSE BEHIND,
THERE WAS ONLY ONE SUBJECT
ON MADELINE'S MIND.
BUON GIORNO!
DID YOU KNOW?
MY UNCLE IS COMING!
SÌ?
FROM VIENNA.
AH! HA HA HA!
THEN HERE IS A WALTZ
IN HIS HONOR.
[HURDY-GURDY
PLAYS WALTZ]
[GIRLS LAUGH]
DID YOU KNOW?
TODAY I HAVE
A VISITOR.
WHO CAN THAT BE?
[WHISPERS] It's
my uncle from Vienna.
FOR YOUR UNCLE.
MERCI.
Miss Clavel: MADELINE!
GUESS WHO THOSE ARE FOR!
YOUR UNCLE, MADELINE?
[GASPS] WHO TOLD YOU?
HEE HEE HEE!
[ALL LAUGH]
NOW EVERYBODY KNOWS!
Narrator: POOR MADELINE
COULD DO NOTHING BUT WAIT.
FINALLY, A TAXI
PULLED UP AT THE GATE.
HE'S HERE!
HA HA HA!
ALORS!
WAIT!
WE MUST MAKE A GOOD
FIRST IMPRESSION,
NON?
OUI!
All: HA HA HA!
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
FRAULEIN CLAVEL,
I PRESUME.
JA,
I AM MADELINE'S
UNCLE HORST.
MAIS OUI, MONSIEUR.
AND THIS IS MADELINE!
BONJOUR, MONSIEUR.
AH, HOW COULD I NOT
RECOGNIZE MY OWN KIND?
AND EVERY BIT
AS BEAUTIFUL
AS YOUR
MUTTER.
MAMA?!
YOU KNEW HER?!
HA HA HA! BUT OF COURSE.
I AM YOUR UNCLE,NEIN?
FAMILY!
FAMILY?
I DID NOT KNOW
I HAD ANY.
IST GUT, JA?
OH,
OUI!
JA!
All:
AND NOW...
THE GIFTS!
Girls: OOH!
AHH!
Girls: WHAT CAN IT BE? HE
BROUGHT GIFTS FOR ALL OF US!
Narrator: THERE WERE
RIBBONS AND BOXES
ALL OVER THE PLACE
AS EACH GIRL UNCOVERED
A COLLAR OF LACE.
SO BEAUTIFUL!
AND FROM MY UNCLE!
All: MERCI
BEAUCOUP,
MONSIEUR HORST!
YOU ARE MOST KIND,
HERR HORST.
NO, NO, NO.
IT IS MY PLEASURE.
IT IS GOOD ETIQUETTE,
JA,
TO BRING
PARTING GIFTS.
Both: PARTING?!
I DO NOT
UNDERSTAND.
PERHAPS I SHOULD START
AT THE BEGINNING.
AS YOU CAN SEE,
THE COURTS HAVE MADE ME
MADELINE'S NEW GUARDIAN.
AFTER ALL, THAT IS
HOW IT SHOULD BE,JA?
WE ARE FAMILY.
FAMILY!
BUT...
Girls: BUT?
I LIVE IN VIENNA,
AND MY WORK
IS IN VIENNA.
AND THERE IS
A VERY, VERY FINE,
EXCLUSIVE
FINISHING SCHOOL...
All: [GASPS] IN VIENNA?!
JA.
EXACTLY.
I KNEW YOU WOULD
UNDERSTAND.
LEAVE MY FRIENDS?
LEAVE PARIS?
FOR THE FINE VIENNESE
FINISHING SCHOOL.
OOH, LA LA!
MADELINE IS
TO BE FINISHED?!
YOU WILL BE EDUCATED
MIT
ROYALTY!
ROYALTY?
OH, IT IS THE VERY BEST
OF SCHOOLS.
I BELIEVE YOUR MOTHER
MAY HAVE ATTENDED
AT ONE POINT.
THE SAME SCHOOL AS MAMA!
IT MUST BE WONDERFUL!
TOMORROW, WE TAKE
THE ORIENT EXPRESS.
TOMORROW?!
Girls:
ORIENT EXPRESS?!
IT LEAVES FOR VIENNA
AT PRECISELY 10:05
IN THE MORNING.
I WILL BE HERE AT 9:00.
PLEASE,
YOU WILL BE PACKED.JA.
BUT...
Girls, sadly: OHH!
OH!
EH, MONSIEUR.
EH, WE HOPED
YOU WOULD DINE
WITH US
THIS EVENING,
NON?
MOST HONORED.
MEIN
LIEBCHEN,
UNTIL THIS EVENING.
AU REVOIR,
UNCLE HORST!
[WOOF WOOF]
OH, GENEVIEVE.
IT IS SO WONDERFUL
TO HAVE AN UNCLE,
BUT IT IS
NOT SO WONDERFUL
TO LEAVE.
YET IT MUST BE
THE RIGHT THING TO DO.
MY UNCLE WOULD ONLY WANT
THE VERY BEST FOR ME.
NON?
HEE HEE HEE!
OUI!
Narrator:
THEN SOMETHING OCCURRED
OUT OF MADELINE'S VIEW.
UNCLE HORST PAID THE CABBIE
AND BADE HIM ADIEU,
THEN STRUCK OFF ON FOOT
DOWN THE LONG AVENUE.
REMEMBER, GIRLS,
WE MUST SHOW
MADELINE'S UNCLE HORST
THAT WE ARE AS GOOD
AS ANY VIENNESE
FINISHING SCHOOL.
THEN PERHAPS HE WILL
LET HER STAY WITH US!
WE WILL BE
TRÈS
DELICATE,
NON?
All:
OUI!
TRÈS
POLITE!
ELEGANT!
All:
TRÈS
LADYLIKE!
I WILL ASK PAPA
AND MAMA TO ATTEND.
THEY, TOO, HAVE
DINED WITH ROYALTY.
AH! PERFECT!
AND I WILL INVITE
THE CHAIRMAN
OF THE SCHOOL:
LORD CUCUFACE.
WE WILL MAKE
A VERY GOOD IMPRESSION.
All:
MAIS
OUI!
SEÑOR AMBASSADOR
OF SPAIN
AND HIS WIFE.
ES UN PLACER.
LIKEWISE, I AM SURE.
OH, AND I HAVE THE HONOR
TO REPRESENT THE KING.
AND MADELINE PLAYS
WITH OUR SON PEPITO.
I AM A PERSONAL FRIEND
OF MANY KINGS.
AND AT THE SCHOOL
IN VIENNA,
MADELINE WILL STUDY
WITH PRINCESSES.
Miss Clavel:
LORD CUCUFACE.
HERR HORST,
I'M SURPRISED
WE HAVE NEVER MET.
I HAVE MANY FRIENDS
IN HIGH PLACES
IN VIENNA.
JA?
YES, INDEED.
FOR EXAMPLE,
THERE'S BARON, UM--
UH, COUNT, UH--
[COUGHS]
SO MANY
PERHAPS YOU FORGET.
WELL, UH, Y-YES.
QUITE--QUITE RIGHT.
MESDAMES
ET MESSIEURS,
DINNER IS SERVED.
HERE AT SCHOOL,
I HAVE LEARNED
TO PLAY THE PIANO.
MOST BENEFICIAL,
BUT IN VIENNA,
YOU WILL LEARN
TO PLAY THE FLUTE.
SHE HAS ALSO
LEARNED TO PAINT.
IN VIENNA, YOU WILL
LEARN TO SCULPT.
AND SHE'S
LEARNED, UM...
FOOTBALL!
[GASPS]
SHE MEANS...
PHYSICS.
[CHUCKLES] YOUNG
LADIES DO NOT NEED
TO KNOW SUCH THINGS.
OUR GIRLS ARE--ARE
QUITE TOP-OF-THE-LINE,
ARE THEY NOT?
NOT AS TOP
AS VIENNA.
REALLY?
I SAY, WE HAD
A GIRL YEARS AGO--
MARRIED A DUKE.
AND ONE WHO IS NOW
A FAMOUS WRITER.
IN MADELINE'S NEW CLASS,
THERE WILL BE 3 GIRLS
WHO ARE ALREADY DUCHESSES.
4 CONTESSAS,
2 PRINCESSES,
AND AN EMPRESS TO BE!
[GASPS]
Lord Cucuface: UM...
I BELIEVE
THAT OUR GIRLS HAVE
SOMETHING VERY SPECIAL
FOR US THIS EVENING.
I COUNT
LIKE A COUNTESS.
[PLAYING]
I SPEAK DUTCH
LIKE A DUCHESS.
[PLAYING]
AND SHE PRINTS
LIKE A PRINCESS!
♪ WE CAN SING,
WE CAN DANCE ♪
♪ WE WRITE POEMS
WITH COMPASSION ♪
♪ WE CAN DRAW,
WE CAN PAINT ♪
♪ ALL IN TRUE
PARISIAN FASHION ♪
♪ WE ARE DAINTY, PROPER
♪ AND WELL-BRED
♪
TRÈS, TRES
WELL-TRAVELED ♪
♪ AND
TRÈS, TRES
WELL-READ ♪
[WHISTLES]
♪ WE ARE ELEGANT
AND CULTIVATED ♪
♪ HONEST AND SOPHISTICATED
♪ GRACEFUL,
MUSICALLY INCLINED ♪
WE CAN DRIBBLE.
MY, HOW REFINED.
♪ WE CAN DANCE BALLET
IN ALL POSITIONS ♪
♪ CURTSEY
FOR THE POLITICIANS ♪
♪ SKETCH A PORTRAIT
FOR THE LOUVRE ♪
♪ SING AT THE OPERA
♪ MI MI MI-MI-MI
MMM, HOW VERY SMOOTH.
♪ WE CAN SWIM,
WE CAN SKATE ♪
♪ WE CAN GALLOP
WITH PERFECTION ♪
♪ WE CAN COOK,
WE CAN BAKE ♪
♪ EVERY CORDON BLEU
SELECTION ♪
♪ WE ARE DAINTY, PROPER
♪ AND WELL-BRED
♪
TRÈS, TRES
WELL-TRAVELED ♪
♪ AND
TRÈS, TRES
WELL-READ ♪
♪ A FINE UPBRINGING
YOU'VE BEEN GIVEN ♪
♪ CONSIDERING THE PLACE
YOU LIVE IN ♪
♪ BUT TO LEARN CORRECTLY,
IF YOU PLEASE ♪
♪ I'LL FIND A TEACHER
♪ WHO'S VIENNESE
♪ THEY CAN WEAVE,
THEY CAN SEW ♪
♪ WITH THE FINEST
SILK OR SATIN ♪
♪ THEY CAN QUOTE
FROM THE CLASSICS ♪
♪ IN FLUENT GREEK
AND LATIN ♪
♪ THEY ARE DAINTY,
PROPER ♪
♪ AND WELL-BRED
♪
MUY, MUY
WELL-TRAVELED ♪
♪ AND
MUY, MUY
WELL-READ ♪
[PLAYING OFF-KEY]
♪ WE CAN SING,
WE CAN DANCE ♪
♪ WE WRITE POEMS
WITH COMPASSION ♪
♪ WE CAN DRAW,
WE CAN PAINT ♪
♪ ALL IN TRUE
PARISIAN FASHION ♪
♪ WE ARE DAINTY, PROPER
♪ AND WELL-BRED
NEIN, NEIN!
♪
TRÈS, TRES
WELL-TRAVELED ♪
♪ AND
TRÈS, TRES,
TRÈS, TRES, TRÈS ♪
♪ WELL-READ
OUI,
OUI!
[CLAPPING]
THAT WAS, UH,
MOST ENTERTAINING
FOR MUSIC LOVERS.
DO NOT WORRY,
LIEBCHEN.
YOU WILL ATTEND
MANY CONCERTS IN VIENNA,
JUST AS YOUR
MUTTER
LOVED TO DO.
NOW, TOMORROW,
WE HAVE AN EARLY START.
THE ORIENT EXPRESS
WAITS FOR NO ONE.
BE ON TIME.
MAIS
OUI, UNCLE HORST.
ALLOW ME TO DRIVE YOU.
OF COURSE.
OH, YES!
I, FOR ONE,
WILL CERTAINLY MISS
OUR MADELINE.
JA.
THERE ISN'T
ANY CHANCE, UH...
NEIN.
THERE IS, UH, OF COURSE,
THE MATTER
OF HER INHERITANCE.
O-OH. HMM.
OF COURSE.
QUITE SUBSTANTIAL.
JA.
AS HER GUARDIAN,
I AM RESPONSIBLE.
QUITE, QUITE.
I HAD NO DOUBTS.
Narrator: UNCLE HORST
HAS POLISH, GRACE, AND WIT.
THAT SEEMS
TO BE THE SUM OF IT.
BUT IS THERE MORE
THAN MEETS THE EYE
TO BE UNCOVERED
BY AND BY?
SLEEP WELL,
MES CHERIES.
Girls:
OUI,
MISS CLAVEL.
WE WILL TRY.
OHH!
I CAN'T BELIEVE
THIS IS MY LAST NIGHT.
C'EST HORRIBLE!
NON, NON.
IT IS WONDERFUL
FOR MADELINE.
[CRIES]
OH, MADELINE.
WHAT EVER WILL
WE DO WITHOUT YOU?
DO NOT WORRY,
MES AMIES.
I WILL COME AND VISIT.
PROMISE?
SOON?
SOON AS I CAN.
All: FRIENDS...
FOR NOW
AND FOREVER!
Narrator: WHILE OTHERS
WERE SLEEPING,
ALL WRAPPED
IN THEIR DREAMS...
[RINGS]
THE MUCHACHO
NEXT DOOR
WAS HATCHING A SCHEME.
[SNORING]
[GATE OPENS]
SQUAW--
SHH.
POR FAVOR!
IF YOU WAKE THE SUN,
THE DAY WILL BEGIN,
AND MADELINE
WILL BE GONE!
A FULL BEAK WILL
KEEP YOU QUIET.
EAT SLOWLY!
CHEW!
AY YAY YAY!
SQUAW--
¡SILENCIO!
DON'T WAKE THE SUN!
GO BACK TO SLEEP!
HMM.
SQUAW--
SHUSH!
[GASPS]
COCK-A-DOODLE-DOO!
Narrator: TRY AS HE MIGHT
TO STOP DAYLIGHT
FROM BREAKING,
PEPITO HAD FAILED,
AND ALL PARIS WAS WAKING.
AND 12 LITTLE GIRLS MET
THE MORNING WITH DREAD...
THINKING OF SORROWFUL
GOOD-BYES AHEAD.
AS THE GIRLS
MADE THEIR BEDS,
IT WAS HARD TO IGNORE
THAT MADELINE, SADLY,
WOULD SLEEP THERE NO MORE.
AND AT BREAKFAST, THE MOOD
WENT FROM GLOOMY TO WORSE
AS THE GIRLS ALL RECITED
THEIR FAVORITE VERSE.
Girls: WE LOVE OUR BREAD,
WE LOVE OUR BUTTER,
BUT MOST OF ALL
WE LOVE MADELINE!
[CRYING]
LITTLE GIRLS,
YOUR TEARS WILL MAKE
THE HOT CHOCOLATE SALTY.
Narrator:
AS TIME GREW SHORT,
THERE WAS PACKING TO DO
WITH MADELINE'S CLOTHES
AND SOME MEMORIES, TOO.
[KISS KISS]
GO WITH MADELINE.
[SQUEAKS]
Narrator:
THE SUITCASE CLOSED,
BUT DID NOT CLICK...
UNH! UNH!
TILL 3 MORE BOTTOMS
DID THE TRICK.
Pepito: AH!
PEPITO WAS SEARCHING
AND HOPED TO FIND
A FAREWELL GIFT
FOR MADELINE.
WHAT WOULD SHE LIKE BEST?
MY SLINGSHOT?
MMM, MAYBE NOT.
AH, MY TOP!
BUT WHERE IS THE STRING?
MY PRIZE TOAD.
SUN-DRIED, OF COURSE.
MMM.
¡SÍ, SI!
THE BEST OF ALL!
A PRESENT FROM
THE AMBASSADOR OF BRAZIL.
A GENUINE IMITATION
SHRUNKEN HEAD.
[REOW]
¡PERFECTO!
Narrator:
WHILE PEPITO WAS BUSILY
WRAPPING HIS TREAT,
A TAXICAB WAITED OUTSIDE
IN THE STREET...
AS UNCLE HORST
GESTURED AND SAID...
NOW, MY SWEET.
[RAR RAR ARF ARF]
GENEVIEVE RAN
AND JUMPED UP ON A SEAT.
[ARR ARR RAR]
NEIN, NEIN, NEIN.
GENEVIEVE WANTS
TO GO WITH MADELINE.
WE'VE ALL AGREED.
Girls:
OUI, OUI.
SHE WILL KEEP
YOU COMPANY.
UHH!
MERCI, MES AMIES.
THERE ARE NO DOGS
IN THE SCHOOL IN VIENNA.
All: OHH.
THEN THERE
IS NO MADELINE
IN THE SCHOOL
IN VIENNA.
[ALL GASP]
[SIGHS]
JA.
[WOOF WOOF]
Girls: AHH.
AHEM!
I HAVE SOMETHING
FOR THE TRIP.
ALL MADELINE'S NEEDS
ARE PROVIDED FOR,
BUT ANY SPENDING MONEY
MAY BE ENTRUSTED TO ME
FOR SAFEKEEPING.
THIS IS FOR MADELINE.
IS IT VALUABLE?
PRICELESS.
MADELINE,
CLOSE YOUR EYES.
NOW OPEN...
OHH.
MAMA'S BEADS.
I WAS TOLD TO PUT THESE
IN SAFEKEEPING
UNTIL IT WAS TIME
TO GIVE THEM TO YOU.
NOW IS THAT TIME.
I THOUGHT PERHAPS,
UH, DIAMONDS?
EMERALDS? PEARLS?
UHH.
VELL, NO MATTER.
BEADS CAN BE ENTRUSTED
TO A LITTLE GIRL.
MERCI,
MISS CLAVEL.
AHEM.
JA,
VELL,
YOU HAVE ME NOW,
UND
IT IS TIME
TO GO.
VE MUST BE PUNCTUAL.
AUF WIEDERSEHEN!
Girls: OHH.
Girls: GOOD-BYE, MADELINE.
WE'LL MISS YOU.
Girl: WE LOVE YOU,
MADELINE!
[WHIMPERS]
Girls: GONE FOREVER!
[ALL CRY]
LITTLE GIRLS,
DO NOT CRY.
[SNIFFLES]
WE MUST BE HAPPY.
All: HAPPY?
FOR MADELINE.
SHE IS WITH
HER UNCLE HORST,
AND HE IS FAMILY.
WE CAN WRITE,
AND ONE DAY
PERHAPS EVEN VISIT!
WHEN?
PAUVRES PETITES.
[WHIMPERS]
Pepito: WAIT!
AM I TOO LATE?
WHERE IS MADELINE?
SHE IS GONE.
Girls: FOREVER!
NOOO!
Narrator:
THE AMBASSADOR'S CAR,
WITH THE GIRLS AND PEPITO,
SPED OFF TO THE TAXI
AS HE YELLED...
¡RAPIDO!
FASTER!
WHILE THE TRAIN DEPOT
WAS JUST AHEAD,
THE TAXI CAB STOPPED
AT THE METRO INSTEAD.
UNCLE.
UNCLE?
HMM?
JA, LIEBCHEN?
WHY DO WE STOP HERE?
THIS IS NOT
THE TRAIN STATION.
BECAUSE, UH,
BEFORE THE TRAIN,
VE NEED TO GO TO,
UH, THE...BOUTIQUE.
LA BOUTIQUE? POURQUOI?
WHY? FOR...A DRESS.
UND
VAT A DRESS.
A FORMAL
PRESENTATION DRESS.
MIT,
UM, UM,
SPARKLY THINGS
ALL DOWN THE FRONT.
COME!
BUT...
PEPITO.
WHAT IS IN
YOUR PACKAGE?
[ALL GASP]
[TIRES SCREECH]
PUT IT AWAY!
Narrator: DOWN IN
THE METRO, TRAINS COME,
THEN THEY LEAVE.
EVERYONE WAS ON BOARD...
[WOOF WOOF]
EXCEPT GENEVIEVE.
GENEVIEVE!
NO DOGS ALLOWED
ON THE METRO.
SHE VILL VAIT
UNTIL VE GET BACK.
NON!
JA.
GENEVIEVE!
[WHIMPERS]
SOMETHING IS NOT RIGHT.
SHH, SHH,
SHH, SHH.
SHE'S VERY EXCITED.
GREAT CHANGES
ARE HAPPENING
IN HER LIFE.
[WHISPERS]
Be a good girl.
WHO IS IN CHARGE?
I AM IN CHARGE.
YOU WISH TO SEE
THE COURT PAPERS
AGAIN?
NEIN?
GOOD. WE WILL
DISCUSS THIS LATER.
Narrator:
GENEVIEVE WAS ALONE,
AND SHE HOWLED IN DESPAIR.
AWOO! AWOO!
MEANWHILE, IN THE DEPOT
WITH NO TIME TO SPARE,
MISS CLAVEL HURRIED FORWARD,
UNAWARE THAT
THE ONE SHE WAS SEEKING
WOULD NOT BE THERE.
Danielle:
VOILÀ!
Chloe:
THERE IS STILL TIME.
[TRAIN WHISTLE BLOWS]
WE MUST RUN!
GIRLS, GIRLS!
KEEP IN LINE.
OH, NEVER MIND.
RUN!
TRÈS VITE!
OH! OH! MONSIEUR.
HAVE YOU SEEN
A LITTLE GIRL
DRESSED LIKE THIS?
WITH AN UNCLE?
AND A DOG?
NON.
IT IS
TRÈS,
TRÈS
IMPORTANT.
TRÈS BIEN.
I WILL CHECK
LES TICKETS
RÉSERVATIONS.
UN
MOMENT.
JE REGRETTE
I FIND
NO LISTING FOR THEM.
NO LISTING?
SOMETHING IS NOT RIGHT.
♪ OH, DEAR, OH, DEAR
♪ SOMETHING IS NOT RIGHT
♪ OH, DEAR, I FEAR
♪ A QUIVER, SHIVER
KIND OF FRIGHT ♪
♪ THERE'S SOMETHING
GOING WRONG ♪
♪ OUI, OUI
♪ SO WRONG
THAT I SUSPECT ♪
♪ OH, DEAR,
OH, DEAR, OH, DEAR ♪
♪ SOMETHING IS NOT CORRECT
SOMETHING IS WRONG. VAT?
THIS IS...
THE END
OF THE LINE?
OUI.
TRUST ME. I AM
YOUR SMART UNCLE HORST.
♪ OH, DEAR,
OH, DEAR ♪
♪ SOMETHING
IS NOT GOOD ♪
♪ OH, DEAR, LOOK HERE
♪ I DO NOT LIKE
THIS NEIGHBORHOOD ♪
♪ THERE'S SOMETHING
GOING WRONG ♪
♪ WHAT IS IT?
QU'EST-CE QUE C'EST? ♪
♪ OH, DEAR,
OH, DEAR, OH, DEAR ♪
♪ SOMETHING IS NOT OK
♪ WE'RE SEARCHING HIGH,
WE'RE SEARCHING LOW ♪
♪ WE'VE GOT
TO FIND A SIGN ♪
♪ OUR FAVORITE FRIEND,
WHERE DID SHE GO? ♪
♪ OH, DEAR, DEAR MADELINE
♪ OH, HAD I
ONLY REALIZED ♪
♪ WHEN THE STRANGER
CAME TO CALL ♪
♪ OH, HAD I
ONLY RECOGNIZED ♪
♪ THE DANGER TO US ALL
♪ THE DANGER
TO US ALL ♪
♪ NOW, DEAR, NOW, DEAR
♪ EVERYTHING IS FINE
♪ MY DEAR, WHY FEAR?
♪ JUST PUT THE CHIN UP,
MADELINE ♪
♪ THERE'S SOMETHING
GOING WRONG ♪
♪ I DON'T KNOW
WHAT TO DO ♪
♪ NOW HEAR,
MY DEAR, NOW HEAR ♪
♪ JUST GRIN, HA HA,
AND SAY POOH-POOH ♪
♪ POOH-POOH
♪ OH, DEAR, OH, DEAR
♪ SOMETHING IS NOT RIGHT
♪ IT'S CLEAR OUR DEAR
♪ HAS VANISHED
IN THE MIDDAY LIGHT ♪
♪ THERE'S SOMEONE
DOING WRONG ♪
♪ THAT UNCLE, HE'S THE ONE
♪ OH, DEAR,
OH, DEAR, OH, DEAR ♪
♪ SOMETHING HAS TO BE DONE
♪ OH, DEAR, OH, DEAR,
OH, DEAR, OH, DEAR ♪
♪ OH, DEAR,
♪ SOMETHING HAS TO BE DONE
[TRAIN WHISTLE BLOWS]
Narrator:
MISS CLAVEL AND THE GROUP
LEFT THE DEPOT DESPAIRING...
[WOOF WOOF
WOOF WOOF]
WHEN A SOUND
FROM THE DISTANCE
[WOOF WOOF WOOF WOOF]
HAD NICOLE DECLARING...
GENEVIEVE!
Girls: GENEVIEVE?
Danielle:
SHE CAME FROM THE METRO.
SOMETHING
IS DEFINITELY WRONG.
Narrator:
UNCLE HORST LED HIS NIECE
PAST DECREPIT OLD PLACES,
THEN STOPPED AT LAST
UNDER A SIGN
WHICH READ "LACES."
WHA--OOH!
AHH!
SACRÉ BLEU!
MON PIED!
UNCLE HORST,
WHAT HAPPENED TO
YOUR VIENNESE ACCENT?
VIENNESE?
MOI?
UM, UH...
JAWOHL. JAWOHL.
YOU ARE NOT
FROM VIENNA, ARE YOU?
LITTLE TROUBLEMAKER.
[GASPS] NO!
DON'T PUSH!
WHO ARE YOU?
HENRI, TO YOU.
[GASPS] HENRI?
NOT HORST?
NOT MY UNCLE?
I HAVE NO FAMILY?!
WHAT YOU HAVE, PRINCESS,
IS A NEW HOME!
Woman: CLOSE THE DOOR!
SUNLIGHT RUINS LACE.
WHUH! OOH! OOH! OW!
[APPLAUDS] BRAVO.
SUCH A NOBLE ENTRANCE.
HENRI, THE FAILED ACTOR.
ONLY GOOD AT ACCENTS.
I HATE BIT PLAYERS
ALMOST AS MUCH
AS I HATE LITTLE GIRLS
WHO DON'T KNOW
WHEN TO BE AFRAID.
I AM AFRAID.
BUT ALSO I AM BRAVE.
HA! I AM LA CROQUE.
SHORT FOR
LA CROCODILE.
HEH HEH.
WOULD YOU BELIEVE
THEY ONCE CALLED HER
LA JOLIE FLEUR?
NOBODY GAVE YOU
LINES TO SPEAK!
LA JOLIE FLEUR?
THE PRETTY FLOWER?
WHAT HAPPENED?
SHE WILTED.
YOU DO NOT HAVE
PERMISSION TO SPEAK.
AND YOU--NO QUESTIONS.
[ALL GASP]
YOU'LL DO
AS YOU ARE TOLD!
MAKING LACE
FOR AS LONG
AS I CHOOSE,
AND IF YOU
ARE NOT QUICK,
I WILL CUT OFF
YOUR HAIR
AND USE IT
TO MAKE LACE.
JUST AS I FORGED
THE COURT PAPERS,
I WILL FAKE REPORTS
FROM A VIENNESE SCHOOL
THAT DOESN'T EXIST,
AND SEND THEM TO THE BANK
THAT CONTROLS
MADELINE'S FAMILY FORTUNE.
AND...
AND EACH MONTH...
A NICE FAT CHECK
WILL COME...
POUR MOI!
WE GET MADELINE'S MONEY
WHILE SHE'S HERE
UNDER LOCK AND KEY.
IT'S BRILLIANT!
IT IS CRIMINAL.
SHH.
YOUR APRON.
YOUR PILLOW.
FOR
THE LACEWORK.
SEE HOW I DO IT
WITH THESE BOBBINS?
SO COMPLICATED.
OUI.
AT FIRST,
IT TAKES MUCH TIME.
BUT YOU ARE SMART, NO?
YOU WILL LEARN FAST.
[WHISPERS]
Just be careful.
Do not get
La Croque angry.
HOW CAN I HELP IT?
THEY TRICKED ME.
AND HOW LONG WILL
SHE BE OUR GUEST?
OH, A LOOOONG TIME.
LIKE FOREVER?
AH, HENRI,
YOUR MIND
IS SO FAST.
TRÈS RAPIDE. BRAVO!
REMEMBER,
WORK FOR YOUR KEEP.
AH, THE RAREST LACE OF ALL
IS RED LACE FROM RED HAIR.
COME, HENRI.
[GASPS]
Narrator: WHILE MADELINE
WAS TRAPPED, IT SEEMS,
IN ONE OF LA CROQUE'S
CROOKED SCHEMES,
HER FRIENDS
ON THE OTHER SIDE OF PARIS
WERE WORKING TO FIND HER.
WHERE COULD SHE BE?
GIRLS, I WILL GO
WITH
MONSIEUR LE GENDARME
AND MAKE
A MISSING PERSONS REPORT.
YOU WILL WAIT HERE
WITH MRS. MURPHY.
Girls:
OUI,
MISS CLAVEL!
[SIREN]
All: OHH.
WHAT IF WE CANNOT
FIND MADELINE?
WE MUST LOOK
FOR MADELINE OURSELVES.
All:
OUI!
WE MUST BE WATCHFUL.
WE MUST EXAMINE
ALL EVIDENCE.
INTERROGATE
ALL WITNESSES.
BUT, FIRST,
HOW TO LEAVE MRS. MURPHY?
All: HMM.
PEPITO!
WHAT IS THAT?
MAMA'S.
IT WAS PAPA'S
FIRST GIFT TO HER.
ONLY ONE BEAD?
[GIGGLES]
NO, NO.
IT WAS A NECKLACE.
THIS IS
THE LAST BEAD LEFT.
HOW SAD. YOU HAD
TO SELL THE REST?
NO. I DROPPED THEM.
PAUVRE
MADELINE.
YOU LOST THEM ALL?
THAT IS WORSE.
NO, NO, FIFI.
LISTEN, WHEN
I BEGAN TO THINK
SOMETHING IS WRONG,
I KNEW I MUST
LEAVE A CLUE.
AH, LIKE HANSEL
AND GRETEL?
EXACTEMENT!
A TRAIL FOR THE OTHERS
TO FOLLOW AND FIND ME.
WHO ARE
THESE OTHERS?
MES AMIES.
MY VERY GOOD FRIENDS.
YOU ARE SO CLEVER,
AND SO LUCKY
TO HAVE FRIENDS
WHO WILL LOOK FOR YOU.
[COUGHS]
BUT TO LEAVE
YOUR MOTHER'S BEADS--
THAT MUST
HAVE BEEN HARD.
THAT'S WHY
I KEPT THE LAST ONE.
THE LION?
TO MAKE YOU STRONG?
OUI,
AND FOR HOPE
THAT MY FRIENDS
WILL FIND ME.
THERE IS NOBODY
TO LOOK FOR ME,
NO ONE TO FIND ME.
[COUGHS]
YOU HAVE SOMEONE, FIFI.
MOI.
I WILL BE
YOUR FRIEND.
SEE? YOU MUST
ALWAYS HAVE HOPE.
[DOOR OPENS]
WHY AREN'T YOU
WORKING?
[GIGGLES, COUGHS]
A GIGGLE?
HEH HEH.
POSSIBLY A CHUCKLE?
TRÈS PETITE.
THERE WILL BE
NO LAUGHING HERE!
LAUGHTER IS BANISHED!
SMILING IS BANNED!
HAPPINESS IS--IS...
VERBOTEN?
WHEN I
NEED YOUR HELP
WITH WORDS, HENRI,
YOU WILL BE
INVITED TO SPEAK.
[ALL GIGGLE]
[ALL GASP]
Narrator: MEANWHILE, INSIDE
OF THE VINE-COVERED HOUSE,
PEPITO ARRIVED
WITH A PLAN AND A MOUSE.
AS MRS. MURPHY
PREPARED HER MEAT PIES,
SHE DID NOT EXPECT
AN UNWELCOME SURPRISE.
AAH!
WHOO, WHOO!
SHH. WE MUST
BE VERY QUIET.
Narrator:
THE CHILDREN RAN QUICKLY
WITHOUT LOOKING BACK,
LEAVING POOR MRS. MURPHY
STILL UNDER ATTACK,
WHILE ANOTHER SMALL RODENT,
MORE FRIENDLY THAN FOE,
WAS BEGGING FOR BREADCRUMBS
FROM SOMEONE WE KNOW.
HE'S OUR PET,
BUT DO NOT
TELL LA CROQUE.
WHY WOULD I
TELL LA CROQUE?
SHE IS A MONSTER.
[GIGGLES]
WELL, SHE IS.
YOU SHOULD
BE ALLOWED A PET.
STOP YAPPING!
DO YOU NOT WANT TO EAT
YOUR LOVELY LUNCH?
TRÈS BIEN!
IT WILL BE TAKEN AWAY!
All: WE LOVE STALE BREAD
WITHOUT THE BUTTER.
BUT AT LEAST
WE HAVE EACH OTHER.
BEFORE, AT
YOUR WONDERFUL SCHOOL,
YOU HAD A PET?
OUI.
ALL OF US
HAD GENEVIEVE,
THE BEST DOG
IN PARIS.
IF ONLY I KNEW
SHE WERE SAFE.
MADAME, THE POLICE ARTIST.
UH, PLEASE TELL ME
ABOUT THE SUSPECT,
THIS, UH, UNCLE HORST.
MONSIEUR HORST
WAS TALL, ELEGANT.
Narrator: MISS CLAVEL
CHOSE HER WORDS
AND DESCRIBED HORST
WITH CARE,
WHILE THE ARTIST
WAS SKETCHING
WITH TALENTED FLAIR.
VOILÀ!
UH, NO.
HIS HAIR,
IT WAS WAVY,
RATHER LIGHT.
AH.COMME ÇA!
[GASPS]
OH, NO, NO.
HIS FACE--
A LITTLE LONGER.
[GASPS]
N-NOT QUITE.
OH, DEAR.
I'M NOT SURE
THIS IS HELPING
FIND OUR MADELINE.
Narrator: AT EACH METRO
STATION ALONG THE ROUTE,
GENEVIEVE
SNIFFED FOR A CLUE.
BUT WHEN THEIR TIME
WAS RUNNING OUT...
Girls: AHH.
THEY HAD TO DECIDE
WHAT TO DO.
NEXT STOP IS THE LAST.
MAYBE THERE.
IT IS TOO LATE.
WE MUST GET BACK
BEFORE MISS CLAVEL.
TOMORROW, THEN?
Girls: TOMORROW!
Narrator: AS THEY LEFT,
THEY WONDERED
HOW MADELINE
WAS DOING NOW.
I HOPE
SHE'S ALL RIGHT.
I HOPE SHE'S NOT SICK.
I HOPE SHE'S NOT COLD.
I HOPE
SHE'S NOT HUNGRY.
PAUVRE
MADELINE.
Narrator: WHEN THEY HEARD
THE FACTORY CLOCK,
THE GIRLS LINED UP
TO FACE LA CROQUE.
I'LL TAKE THAT!
THERE ARE
A LOT MORE ANTIQUES
TO BE DONE TOMORROW.
LOOK WHAT YOU'VE DONE!
ALL YOUR COUGHING HAS
TURNED THE LACE YELLOW!
RUINED!
I'M S-S-SORRY.
FROM NOW ON--
MADAME, PLEASE, NO.
I WILL BE CAREFUL.
I WILL NOT COUGH.
[COUGHS]
YOU WILL WORK
ONLY ON...
BLACK LACE!
OH, NO!
I WON'T HAVE
MY PRECIOUS WHITES
DISCOLORED!
REMEMBER THAT,
ALL OF YOU!
[ALL GASP]
WHAT IS WRONG?
WITH NO LIGHT,
WORKING
ON THE BLACK LACE,
IT TAKES OUR EYES.
MY GRANDMAMA
TURNED BLIND THAT WAY.
YOU CAN'T DO THAT
TO FIFI!
IT IS HEARTLESS
AND CRUEL!
SHE IS SICK!
I BEG YOUR PARDON.
SHE NEEDS SUNLIGHT.
SHE NEEDS MORE FOOD.
SHE NEEDS--
WHAT YOU NEED
IS A LESSON!
SILENCE!
UHH!
SPOILED BRATS
HAVE TO LEARN
THE HARD WAY!
AND YOU ARE
THE BEST TEACHER.
[BOTH LAUGH]
I DON'T SEE
WHAT IS SO FUNNY.
[SIGHS]
OH, MAMA.
[SNIFFLES]
♪ HERE I SIT
SO COLD AND HUNGRY ♪
♪ FEELING LOST
AND FAR AWAY ♪
♪ HAPPINESS
IS JUST A MEMORY ♪
♪ A PATCH OF SUN
FROM YESTERDAY ♪
♪ WHERE IS THE HOPE
THAT I ONCE KNEW? ♪
♪ MY DREAMS HAVE VANISHED
♪ IT IS TRUE
♪ WHEN WILL THE SUN
COME SHINING THROUGH? ♪
♪ WHERE IS THE HOPE
♪ THAT I ONCE KNEW?
♪ FRIENDS WOULD CALL ME
"BRAVEST LION" ♪
♪ I ONCE HAD
THAT KIND OF ROAR ♪
♪ IF I REACH INSIDE
FOR COURAGE ♪
♪ PERHAPS I CAN
BE STRONG ONCE MORE ♪
♪ I'LL FIND THE HOPE
THAT I ONCE KNEW ♪
♪ AND I WILL MAKE
MY DREAMS COME TRUE ♪
♪ I'LL SEE THE SUN
COME SHINING THROUGH ♪
♪ FULL OF THE HOPE
♪ THAT I ONCE KNEW
Factory girls:
♪ WE'LL FIND THE HOPE
THAT WE ONCE KNEW ♪
♪ AND WE WILL MAKE
OUR DREAMS COME TRUE ♪
♪ WE'LL SEE THE SUN
COME SHINING THROUGH ♪
FIFI!
♪ FULL OF THE HOPE
♪ THAT WE ONCE KNEW
FIFI? ARE YOU THERE?
MADELINE,
WE WERE WORRIED.
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
MAIS OUI.
FIFI, I'VE DECIDED
WE MUST ESCAPE.
AH, THAT
IS NOT SO EASY.
I TRIED. [COUGHS]
AS PUNISHMENT,
LA CROQUE
CUT OFF MY HAIR
TO MAKE BLACK LACE.
WHY IS LA CROQUE
SO HORRIBLE?
THEY SAY SHE WAS
A CABARET STAR ONCE.
[CANCAN MUSIC PLAYS]
Fifi: THEN
SOMETHING HAPPENED.
Narrator: FIFI EXPLAINED
THAT LA CROQUE WAS A DANCER
WHOSE KICKS
DAZZLED ALL OF PARIS.
AND ONE FATAL NIGHT
THROUGH A "SEAMING" MISCHANCE...
[FABRIC RIPS]
[ALL LAUGHING]
UHH! [CRASH]
[ALL GASP]
Narrator: HER FAME
ENDED MOST TRAGICALLY.
ALORS?
THEN SHE COULD
NO LONGER PERFORM
BECAUSE SHE FELT
SO HUMILIATED.
QUEL DOMMAGE!
SHE HAD NO MONEY,
SO SHE SOLD
HER LONG HAIR
TO MAKE LACE.
NOW SHE RUNS
THE FACTORY.
[COUGHS]
AND SHE WILL CUT OFF
YOUR HAIR LIKE MINE
IF YOU MAKE TROUBLE.
IT WILL GROW BACK.
I WILL TAKE THE CHANCE.
I WILL FIND A WAY OUT.
YOU ARE
NOT SCARED?
I AM ANGRY.
MOI AUSSI.
WE HAVE NO FAMILY,
NONE OF US.
LA CROQUE AND HENRI
LIE TO THE COURTS.
THEY SAY THEY WILL
TAKE CARE OF US,
THEN TREAT US
LIKE THIS.
DON'T WORRY, FIFI.
WE CAN LOOK
AFTER EACH OTHER.
LIKE REAL FRIENDS?
BETTER.
LIKE FAMILY.
FAMILY?
YOU REALLY THINK SO?
I KNOW SO.
[MOUSE SQUEAKS]
[GIRLS LAUGH]
[THUNDER]
BOTHERSOME BRAT.
DO NOT LOSE HEART,
MES PETITES.
WE WILL FIND
OUR MADELINE.
WHERE COULD SHE BE?
I HOPE SHE
IS NOT LONELY...
[THUNDER]
OR HUNGRY...
[WATER SPLASHING]
OR WET AND COLD.
SHE KNOWS
WE LOVE HER.
THAT IS TRUE.
AND WE WILL BE
LOOKING FOR HER.
TOMORROW I WILL
GO AGAIN WITH
THE GENDARMES.
MAIS CERTAINMENT!
Miss Clavel:
AND WE WON'T GIVE UP...
Girls: TILL WE FIND HER!
EXACTLY!
BONNE NUIT,
MES CHERIES.
Girls: SLEEP WELL,
MISS CLAVEL.
Narrator: THEIR HEARTS
WERE WITH MADELINE.
WHERE WAS SHE NOW?
AND THEY PRAYED
THAT THE NEXT DAY
THEY'D FIND HER SOMEHOW.
Mrs. Murphy: BYE-BYE!
AH!
Narrator: MISS CLAVEL
LEFT THE HOUSE
JUST THE SAME AS BEFORE...
BUT THE CHILDREN
DID NOT EXPECT
WHAT LAY IN STORE.
[GASPS]
[CAT GROWLS]
[MRREERW]
¡CARAMBA!
SHE'S BORROWED
MY MOTHER'S CAT.
WHAT TO DO?
¡JASE!
I KNOW!
Narrator:
WHILE PEPITO RAN OFF
FOR THE THING HE FORGOT,
CLEVER MADELINE TRIED
A NEW LACE-MAKING KNOT.
[BOBBINS CLACKING]
[FOOTSTEPS]
Narrator:
AS THE FACTORY VILLAINS
INSPECTED THE WORK,
IT WAS MADAME LA CROQUE
WHO FIRST SPOTTED A QUIRK.
REGARDEZ!
I CAN READ.
La Croque:
COME UP HERE! ALL OF YOU!
AHA!
La Croque: HELP...
I AM A PRISONER...
IN A...
LACE FACTORY.
YOU WILL STAND HERE
ALL DAY, ALL NIGHT,
ALL YEAR
TILL I FIND OUT
WHO'S RESPONSIBLE
FOR THIS SACRILEGE.
PERHAPS A FLAW
IN THE THREAD, MADAME?
THINK
THIS IS A HOLIDAY?
GET BACK TO
YOUR BOBBINS, BRATS.
[GASPS] [GASPS]
Narrator:
LA CROQUE AND HENRI
MADE THEIR WAY TO THE TOP
AS MADELINE PLANNED
A SURPRISE FOR THE SHOP.
Narrator:
BACK AT THE OLD HOUSE,
PEPITO POPPED IN
WITH SOMETHING TO GIVE
AN OLD TRICK A NEW SPIN.
[MRREEERW]
[HISS]
[RREEER]
AAH!
AAH! GET OFF!
GET OFF ME!
OW, GET AWAY
FROM ME!
GET OFF!
OH, OW, OOH, AAH!
OH HO, NO!
GET AWAY!
Narrator: POOR MRS. MURPHY
WAS IN DISTRESS.
PEPITO'S PLAN
WAS A SUCCESS.
¡PERFECTO!
[BOBBINS CLACKING]
Narrator: MADELINE HAD
A SLY TRICK UP HER SLEEVE,
AND SHE AND THE GIRLS
TRIED A TASTEFUL NEW WEAVE.
Narrator: WHO SAYS THAT A MOUSE
CAN'T APPRECIATE ART?
IT LOOKS SO REWARDING,
HE'D LIKE TO TAKE PART.
OH, NO!
MADAME LA CROQUE.
THE THREAD IS BROKEN.
ARGH!
[[GIGGLES]
[SQUEAKS]
OOH, LA LA!
MONSIEUR,
MINE IS GONE, TOO!
[GIGGLES]
[SQUEAKS]
UH-OH!
MINE, TOO!
[GIRLS GIGGLING]
STOP!
WHAT IS GOING ON?
WELL?
THERE IS A PROBLEM?
[GIRLS GIGGLING]
[SQUEAKS]
[SUBWAY TRAIN APPROACHING]
[ARF ARF]
[SNIFFS]
LOOK! SHE IS
TRACKING SOMETHING.
A CLUE?
A HINT?
A LEAD?
A SCENT?
AW, THE RAIN WASHED
AWAY THE TRAIL.
WHAT NOW?
WE CANNOT
LOSE HOPE.
MADELINE WOULD
NEVER DO THAT.
BUT WHICH WAY
DO WE LOOK?
[WOOF]
[WOOF WOOF WOOF]
[YELPS]
WHAT IS THIS?
A BEAD
WITH A SWAN?
MADELINE'S!
HER MAMA'S NECKLACE!
LOOK!
[KIDS CHATTERING]
[GASPS]
AHH.
HERE'S ANOTHER.
LOOK! I FOUND ONE, TOO!
WHICH WAY NOW?
Girls: HMM.
Narrator:
THE LONG TRAIL OF BEADS
HAD NOW COME TO AN END.
NO MORE CLUES COULD
BE SEEN ON THE GROUND.
WITHOUT ANY NEW LEADS
TO THEIR MISSING FRIEND,
HOW WAS MADELINE
THEN TO BE FOUND?
[KIDS LAUGHING]
Nicole: OOH, LA LA!
MARBLES!
NO, NO. THIS IS
NO TIME TO PLAY.
Nicole: BUT LOOK!
EXACTLY LIKE--
HEY!
Boy: WHAT
ARE YOU DOING?
WE FOUND THEM.
WHERE?
OVER THERE.
TRADE?
NICOLE!
YOUR PRECIOUS
MARBLES?
I MUST.
FOR MADELINE.
DEAL!
[LAUGHS]
THE VERY FINEST
HANDIWORK.
LA CREME
DE LA CREME.
AN ANTIQUE BELONGING
TO A NOBLE FAMILY
FALLEN UPON
HARD TIMES.
[GASPS]
SO VERY FRAGILE.
ALSO I BELIEVE
YOU HAVE SOMETHING
ZUPER SPECIAL.
La Croque: BLACK LACE.
[GASPS]
MADE FROM HUMAN HAIR.
OOH! EXTREMELY RARE.
EXTREMELY ZUPER-DUPER.
MAGNIFIQUE!
BUT I HAVE
A RED SILK DRESS.
POSSIBLY, EH...
LACE MADE
FROM RED HAIR?
I THINK THAT IS
VERY POSSIBLE,
BUT TRÈS
CHER,
VERY EXPENSIVE.
[COINS CLINK]
YOUR DEPOSIT
IS ACCEPTED.
I WILL MAKE
DISCREET INQUIRIES
TO SEE
IF THE MASTERPIECE
CAN BE OBTAINED.
COME BACK
IN A FEW DAYS.
THERE'S MORE WHERE
THIS CAME FROM,
BUT NEXT TIME,
DON'T OVERACT.
HMPH!
THERE.
UNDER THE WINDOW.
GOOD.
OUCH!
OH! BE CAREFUL!
READY NOW.
YOU MUST HOLD STEADY.
WE WILL TRY.
Girls: OW, OOH, OUCH!
WHOA-OHH!
WE'LL HAVE OUR
LITTLE LADIES MAKE
A UNIQUE ANTIQUE,
RED LACE
MASTERPIECE.
HERE.
TAKE MADELINE'S
SUITCASE.
SELL ALL
HER NICE THINGS.
SHE DOESN'T
NEED THEM HERE.
AND BUY A LOCK.
A LOCK?
A BIG STRONG LOCK
FOR THE
DETENTION ROOM.
THAT'S WHERE
SHE CAN STAY
FROM NOW ON,
THIS LITTLE
TROUBLE-MAKER,
AFTER SHE
GETS A HAIRCUT.
[CHUCKLES]
[GRUNTING AND MOANING]
FIFI!
WE NEED YOU!
I DON'T LIKE HEIGHTS.
HURRY! IT IS
NOT SO DIFFICULT.
Girls: OW! BE CAREFUL!
YOU HURT ME!
Fifi: I'M SORRY.
SORRY.
Madeline: HERE.
HERE. TAKE MY HAND.
[COUGHS]
Girls: OH! OH!
AAH!
I AM SORRY.
IT IS ALL RIGHT.
WE WILL DO IT AGAIN.
Girl: NO.
HUH?
IT IS NOT
GOING TO WORK.
WE ARE NOT BIG...
OR STRONG.
WE MUST BE BRAVE.
BUT WE
ARE SO SMALL.
BEING SMALL
NEVER STOPPED ME
FROM BEING BRAVE.
BESIDES...
WE DON'T HAVE
TO BE SMALL.
♪ ONE ANT, A LONE ANT,
CAN HARDLY BUDGE A ROCK ♪
♪ BUT WHEN SHE
JOINS WITH OTHER ANTS ♪
♪ THE ROCK
MOVES DOWN THE BLOCK ♪
♪ SO SMALL BUT SO SPUNKY
♪ ANTS PUSH 10 TIMES
THEIR WEIGHT ♪
♪ WHEN THEY BECOME
A MIGHTY TROOP ♪
♪ TOGETHER THEY ARE GREAT
♪ ONE BIRD, A LONE BIRD,
SINGS SOFTLY IN THE MORN ♪
♪ BUT WHEN SHE
SINGS WITH OTHER BIRDS ♪
♪ A SYMPHONY IS BORN
♪ THE FLOCK FORMS A CHORUS
♪ THAT ECHOES FROM A CLOUD
♪ ECHOES FROM A CLOUD
♪ THOUGH WE ARE EACH
LIKE TINY BIRDS ♪
♪ TOGETHER
WE ARE LOUD ♪
WE ARE BIG ♪
♪ TOGETHER
WE ARE STRONG ♪
♪ TOGETHER IT IS CLEAR THAT
WE MOST CERTAINLY BELONG ♪
♪ JUST THINK ABOUT
WHAT WE CAN DO ♪
♪ IF WE WORK AS A TEAM
♪ TOGETHERNESS
HAS SET US FREE ♪
♪ THE ANSWER TO OUR DREAM
♪ ONE HAND, A LONE HAND,
TOO SHORT TO REACH UP HIGH ♪
♪ TOGETHER IT IS POSSIBLE
TO TOUCH THE BLUEST SKY ♪
♪
VOILA,
WE ARE A TOWER ♪
♪ NEVER WILL WE STOP
♪ A PYRAMID OF POWER
♪ TOGETHER TO THE TOP
♪ TOGETHER
WE ARE BIG ♪
WE ARE STRONG ♪
♪ TOGETHER
♪ TOGETHER IT IS CLEAR THAT
WE MOST CERTAINLY BELONG ♪
♪ JUST LOOK AT US
♪ WE'RE PRETTY GOOD
AT WORKING AS A TEAM ♪
♪ TOGETHERNESS
HAS SET US FREE ♪
♪ THE ANSWER TO OUR DREAM
♪ TOGETHER WE ARE BIG
♪ TOGETHER WE ARE STRONG
♪ TOGETHER IT IS CLEAR THAT
WE MOST CERTAINLY BELONG ♪
♪ JUST LOOK AT US
♪ WE'RE PRETTY GOOD
AT WORKING AS A TEAM ♪
♪ TOGETHERNESS
HAS SET US FREE ♪
♪ SET US FREE
♪ THE ANSWER
TO OUR DREAM ♪
[DOOR UNLOCKING]
[DOOR OPENS]
[GIRLS GASP]
WHAT?!
ARGH!
OH! OH!
[CRASH]
THAT IS IT!
[CHATTERING NERVOUSLY]
[SOBBING]
WHERE IS SHE,
THE REDHEAD?
[SNIP SNIP]
[GASPS]
Narrator: MADELINE KNEW
THAT SHE HAD TO HIDE,
FOR LA CROQUE WAS FURIOUS
AND FIT TO BE TIED.
WHEN I FIND
THAT TROUBLE-MAKER...
[SNIP SNIP]
[GASPS]
[PANTING]
RED HAIR FOR RED LACE.
[GASPS]
[CLOTH TEARS]
YOU WILL PAY FOR THIS!
Narrator: AS HENRI
HURRIED DOWN THE STREET,
HE SNUBBED A LAD
HE CHANCED TO MEET.
HE ROUNDED THE CORNER
BUT FAILED TO SEE
A WITNESS
WHO KNEW HIS IDENTITY.
Miss Clavel:
ALORS!
THAT IS HIM!
BUT SO DIFFERENT.
[BRAKES SQUEAL]
[SIREN WAILS]
[GASPS]
Narrator: HE HAD BEEN
SPOTTED, HENRI KNEW,
AND WILDLY DOWN THE STREET
HE FLEW.
[PANTING]
OHH!
Narrator: POLICE PURSUED,
BUT SOMEONE SMALL
WOULD FINALLY CAUSE
HENRI'S DOWNFALL.
[PANTING]
AAH!
OOF!
[BRAKES SQUEAL]
Miss Clavel: THAT'S HIM!
UNCLE HORST
FROM VIENNA.
UM,MOI?
I AM HENRI.
I AM FRENCH.
I AM INNOCENT.
WHY WERE YOU RUNNING AWAY?
I WAS WALKING BRISKLY.
THAT IS NO CRIME.
THIS IS MISTAKEN IDENTITY.
CAN YOU PROVE
HE IS THE MAN?
OUI!
[SARCASTICALLY]
AW, YOU ALWAYS
PLAY WITH DOLLIES
AND WEAR
THE LITTLE DRESS?
[DOLL CRIES]
[GIGGLES]
TELL US
WHERE MADELINE IS!
IF YOU DO NOT,
IT WILL GO
VERY HARD ON YOU.
MMM!
IF HE IS SILENT,
HOW DO WE FIND
MADELINE?
WHAT NOW?
[WOOF]
LOOK AT GENEVIEVE!
[WOOF WOOF]
[PANTING]
NOBODY
IS THERE.
[GASPS]
MADELINE!
VOILA.
HUH?
YOU DO NOT GET OFF
SO EASILY.
[GASPS]
AAH! OOF!
NOW!
WHY, YOU...
UN MONSTRE.
[GASPS]
POOR MADELINE.
AY AY AY!
¡BUENO!
STOP!
STOP, I SAY!
WHEN I GET
OUT OF THIS,
THERE WILL
BE HAIRCUTS
FOR EVERYONE.
[NERVOUS CHATTERING]
GUESS WHERE
I'LL BEGIN.
NO ONE CAN
GET DOWN HERE...
TO HELP YOU.
Narrator: WHILE MADELINE'S
FATE HUNG BY A THREAD,
HER FRIEND PEPITO
WAS PLANNING AHEAD.
La Croque: THAT'S
THE OLDEST TRICK
IN THE WORLD.
THINK
I'LL LOOK BACK?
[CHUCKLES]
THINK AGAIN!
THERE IS NO ESCAPE.
Narrator: WHILE HENRI'S
CROOKED ACT WAS THROUGH,
IN MISS CLAVEL'S MIND,
THERE WAS STILL MUCH TO DO.
IF ONLY THERE
WERE JUST A CLUE...
MONSIEUR, SURELY,
IF YOU HELP,
THE COURTS WILL NOT
BE SO HARD ON YOU.
WHAT IS IT
YOU ARE SAYING?
THEY WILL GIVE YOU
A LIGHTER SENTENCE
IF YOU LEAD US
TO MADELINE.
YOU CAN PROMISE THIS?
HMM.
ALL RIGHT.
I'LL TELL YOU.
I THINK YOU WILL
LEAD US THERE.
[MADELINE LAUGHS]
[LAUGHS]
LAUGHTER?
YOU WILL NEVER LAUGH
AT LA CROQUE AGAIN.
Narrator:
LUCKILY FOR MADELINE,
PEPITO ACTED JUST IN TIME.
UNH!
AAH!
[LAUGHING]
OHH!
[LA CROQUE GASPS]
AAH!
OHH!
HELP! GET IT AWAY FROM ME!
Narrator: AS LA CROQUE
TRAPPED HERSELF
IN THE LACE ON THE FLOOR,
FIFI RUSHED OFF
WITH THE KEY TO THE DOOR.
HURRY! WE MUST
HELP MADELINE!
HURRY! TIE HER UP!
Narrator: THE GIRLS AND PEPITO
DASHED INTO THE SHOP
JUST AS THE GENDARMES
PULLED UP TO A STOP.
La Croque:
HORRIBLE CHILDREN!
MADELINE, YOU ARE
THE WORST OF ALL!
VOILA!
MY ANGEL.
[KIDS CHATTERING]
UNH!
ARGH!
MADELINE!
MISS CLAVEL!
Girls: AWW!
MY LITTLE ONE.
MES
ENFANTS, WHAT
ARE YOU DOING HERE?
RESCUING MADELINE!
[GRUNTS]
HENRI?
[LAUGHS NERVOUSLY]
YOU RAT!
IT WAS
ALL HIS IDEA.
IT WAS HIS SCHEME!
EVERYTHING!
OOH!
La Croque:
OOH, LET ME AT HIM.
Narrator: AND THEN
AT THAT INSTANT,
HENRI TOOK FLIGHT.
[BLOWS WHISTLE]
Narrator: AS THE GENDARMES
PURSUED HIM,
HE DODGED LEFT AND RIGHT.
THEN LA CROQUE
JOINED THE CHASE
WITH A WELL-POINTED KICK...
HA!
AAH!
AND PEPITO PERFORMED
AN OLD ARGENTINE TRICK.
Pepito:
¡ARRIBA!
WHOA-AAH!
¡OLE!
WHOA-OH! OW!
OOF!
Girls: YAH! UNH!
DAAH!
A FITTING CURTAIN
FOR A COWARD.
[GASPS]
[GIRLS LAUGH]
All: YAY!
[LAUGHING]
THERE WILL BE
A SUBSTANTIAL REWARD
FOR THE CAPTURE
OF THIS ONE.
Narrator: THE GENDARMES
LED THE VILLAINS AWAY.
THEIR MISDEEDS WERE ENDED.
NOW THEY WOULD PAY.
MY BRAVE MADELINE.
I WAS BRAVE
BECAUSE I HAD FRIENDS
ALL AROUND ME.
VOICI.
LOOK.
MAMA'S BEADS!
ALL OF THEM.
EACH AND EVERY ONE.
[GIRLS CHATTERING]
YOU WERE RIGHT,
MISS CLAVEL.
FAMILIES COME IN ALL
SHAPES AND SIZES.
AND NOW
I WANT TO GO HOME.
[WOOF]
Miss Clavel:
OUI,
MADELINE.
HOME SOUNDS GOOD, NO?
[GIGGLES]
Narrator:
THE VERY NEXT MORNING,
THE OLD HOUSE
WAS CHEERFUL,
THOUGH MADELINE'S HAIRCUT
WAS STILL A BIT FEARFUL.
AS THE GIRLS
LEFT THE HOUSE,
MISS CLAVEL WAS IN SHOCK...
[GASPS]
WHEN SHE SAW THEY HAD ALL
COPIED MADELINE'S LOCKS.
[GASPS]
[CHUCKLES]
TRÈS BIEN,
LITTLE GIRLS.
WE ARE THANKFUL
THAT MADELINE
IS BACK WITH US
SAFE AND SOUND.
Girls:
OUI, OUI!
BONNE NUIT,
MES PETITES.
I HOPE
YOU SLEEP WELL.
Girls: GOOD NIGHT, GOOD NIGHT,
DEAR MISS CLAVEL.
YOU ARE LUCKY
TO RECEIVE SUCH
A LARGE REWARD
FOR CAPTURING
THOSE THIEVES,
MADELINE.
OUI,
THAT IS TRUE.
I KNOW WHAT I WOULD DO
WITH THE REWARD MONEY.
ME, TOO! I WOULD GO
SHOPPING FOR WONDERFUL
CLOTHES AND JEWELRY.
AND TRAVEL AROUND THE WORLD
TO EXOTIC COUNTRIES.
I WOULD HAVE
A PRIVATE ZOO
WITH ALL OF
MY FAVORITE ANIMALS.
OUI,
THOSE ARE
TEMPTING CHOICES,
BUT I HAVE SOMETHING
VERY SPECIAL IN MIND.
Narrator: AT LAST IT ARRIVED,
THAT WONDERFUL DAY
WHEN ALL DREAMS CAME TRUE
IN MADELINE'S WAY.
[GIRLS GIGGLE]
THEN LORD CUCUFACE PROUDLY
STEPPED FORWARD TO SAY...
MESDAMES, MESSIEURS,
ET MES
ENFANTS, IF I MAY,
I NOW DECLARE
THE NEW CITY SCHOOL
FOR GIRLS,
FUNDED SO GENEROUSLY
BY OUR VERY OWN MADELINE,
OFFICIALLY OPEN!
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERS]
AND MAY I SAY
THEY'RE ABSOLUTELY
TOP-DRAWER GIRLS,
THE VERY BEST.
POR USTED.
MERCI.
GRACIAS, PEPITO.
PERMISO.
FIFI!
[APPLAUDS]
MERCI
BEAUCOUP,
MADELINE.
I AM NOT COUGHING
AT LAST.
DR. COHN,
HE HAS
MADE ME BETTER.
FIFI IS
MY STAR PATIENT.
YOU WILL VISIT OFTEN?
OF COURSE.
WE ARE SISTER SCHOOLS.
I AM VERY IMPRESSED
YOU HAVE CHOSEN TO
DONATE YOUR REWARD
TO THE NEW SCHOOL,
MADELINE.
IT IS WHAT MAMA
WOULD HAVE WISHED--
TO SHARE WITH FAMILY.
I AM SO LUCKY
THAT MY FAMILY
IS SO VERY BIG.
AND SO IS
YOUR HEART,
MA PETITE.
♪ ARMS TO WARM ME
WHEN I'M COLD ♪
♪ LIPS THAT SMILE
AND NEVER SCOLD ♪
♪ EARS THAT LISTEN,
HANDS THAT HOLD ♪
♪ MY FRIENDS ARE
JUST LIKE FAMILY ♪
♪ FAMILY
♪ THE ONES WHO WIPE YOUR TEARS
WHEN YOU FEEL SMALL ♪
♪ FAMILY
♪ THE ONES WHO'LL ALWAYS
BE THERE WHEN YOU CALL ♪
♪ FAMILY
♪ THE ONES WHO TRULY
LOVE YOU MOST OF ALL ♪
Madeline: ♪ MY FRIENDS
ARE JUST LIKE FAMILY ♪
♪ OUR FRIENDS ARE
JUST LIKE FAMILY ♪
Narrator: MADELINE HAS
FRIENDS AND FAMILY GALORE,
AND THAT'S ALL THERE IS.
THERE ISN'T ANY MORE.