Male announcer: ON THIS
EPISODE OF PAWN STARS...
- I GOT SOME WORLD WAR Il
STUFF HERE FROM MY DAD.
THIS IS THE JACKET THAT
HE WORE. HE FLEW P-38s.
- SOME OF THESE CAN BE
WORTH A LOT OF MONEY.
- GOT THE FIRST THREE
SEASONS OF SPORTS ILLUSTRATED.
- BACK IN THE '50s, THIS IS
HOW YOU KEPT UP WITH SPORTS.
- GOT THE FIRST-EVER
SWIMSUIT EDITION.
- WAH, WAH, WHEE-WAH.
- I HAVE AN OLD MUSKET HERE.
- SHOULDN'T THAT BE
A LITTLE BIT BIGGER?
- YEAH, IT IS A
REALLY SMALL RIFLE.
DID YOU CHECK TO
SEE IF IT'S LOADED?
- NO.
- AH!
- OH, MY GOD.
I'M RICK HARRISON, AND
THIS IS MY PAWN SHOP.
I WORK HERE WITH MY OLD
MAN AND MY SON, BIG HOSS.
EVERYTHING IN HERE
HAS A STORY AND A PRICE.
ONE THING I'VE
LEARNED AFTER 21 YEARS,
YOU NEVER KNOW WHAT IS
GONNA COME THROUGH THAT DOOR.
Captioning by CaptionMax
www.captionmax.com
- OH, IT'S YOU AGAIN.
TRYING TO SELL ME
SOMETHING ELSE, HUH?
WHAT YOU GOT THERE?
- I GOT SOME WORLD WAR Il
STUFF HERE FROM MY DAD.
THIS IS A SURVIVAL KIT.
- FIRST AID KITS IN THE
SECOND WORLD WAR,
THEY HAD GUM:, THEY
HAD CANDY BARS:,
THEY HAD SPEED, MORPHINE.
- SO I GUESS IF YOU WERE SHOT
DOWN AND HURT REALLY BAD,
YOU COULD TAKE SOME MORPHINE
AND HAVE SOME FRESH BREATH.
[laughs]
- I DECIDED TO COME TO
THE PAWN SHOP TODAY
TO SELL MY DAD'S WORLD
WAR Il PILOT JACKET,
A FIRST AID KIT, AND A HAT.
WE FOUND IT IN HIS CLOSET.
IT'S BEEN THERE FOR YEARS.
MAYBE SOMEBODY WHO
REALLY APPRECIATES IT
CAN BUY IT AND
DISPLAY IT SOMEWHERE.
I'M HOPING TO SELL THESE
ITEMS FOR ABOUT $2,000 OR $3,000.
I MIGHT GO AS LOW
AS ABOUT $1,500.
MY DAD WAS STATIONED IN ITALY.
HE FLEW MISSIONS,
PRIMARILY BOMBING TRAINS
AND POWER STATIONS.
THIS IS THE JACKET THAT
HE WORE WHILE HE FLEW.
IT'S GOT THE AIRPLANE HE
FLEW, THE P-38, RIGHT HERE.
- OKAY.
THE P-38 LIGHTNING WAS A
WORLD WAR Il FIGHTER PLANE
THAT WAS REALLY UNIQUE
BECAUSE IT HAD TWIN ENGINES.
IT WAS SO COOL-LOOKING
THAT THE 1948 CADILLAC HAD
ITS TAIL FINS MODELED AFTER IT.
I MEAN, THERE WAS
BASICALLY TWO WARS GOING ON.
THERE WAS THE PACIFIC CAMPAIGN
AGAINST THE JAPANESE AND EUROPE.
ITALY WAS BAD.
I MEAN, WHEN WE FIRST
WENT TO INVADE ITALY,
THE GERMANS WERE DUG
IN:, THEY HAD GOOD WEAPONS.
YOU KNOW, THEY COULD DIAL
THE GUNS IN AT 10,000 FEET.
AND ALL THEY HAD
TO DO IS BLOW UP
A FEW HUNDRED FEET FROM
YOU:, IT WOULD TAKE A PLANE DOWN.
REMEMBER, THESE
THINGS WERE, LIKE,
MICRO-THIN ALUMINUM
ALL AROUND THEM.
- AND HE WAS LUCKY
ENOUGH NOT TO GET HIT.
NEITHER DID ANY OF HIS FRIENDS.
HE WAS JUST A KID.
HE EVEN SAID IF
HE WAS ANY OLDER,
HE PROBABLY WOULD HAVE BEEN
TOO SMART TO BE FLYING OVER THERE,
'CAUSE HE WAS 19
OR 20 YEARS OLD.
THEY THOUGHT THEY
WERE INVINCIBLE,
AND HE ACTUALLY HAD A
GOOD TIME OVER THERE.
- THE JACKET
INTRIGUES ME, THOUGH.
SOME OF THESE CAN BE
WORTH A LOT OF MONEY.
DO YOU KNOW HOW
MANY RUNS HE MADE?
- I REALLY DON'T, BUT HE WAS
THERE, I THINK, TWO YEARS.
- THE HAT, I DON'T THINK
IS WORTH A LOT OF MONEY,
TO TELL YOU THE TRUTH.
A LITTLE MOTH-EATEN TOO.
AND...
- WE COULD OPEN
THAT IF YOU WANT.
- NO, I DON'T WANT TO OPEN IT.
I DON'T THINK ANY OF THIS
STUFF IS REALLY GOOD ANYMORE
BESIDES MAYBE THE MATCHES.
THE ONLY QUESTIONS I HAVE IS,
I KNOW THIS INSIGNIA RIGHT
HERE IS FROM ITALY, OKAY?
- OKAY.
- THE THING THAT REALLY
WEIRDS ME OUT HERE, THOUGH:
I'M PRETTY SURE
THE P-38 LIGHTNING
WAS PACIFIC THEATER ONLY.
- NO, I KNOW HE WAS IN ITALY,
'CAUSE HE HAD
RELATIVES OVER THERE.
HE WENT AND SAW THEM.
- I JUST WANT SOMEONE
TO CHECK THIS OUT,
MAKE SURE IT'S
ACTUALLY NOT SOMETHING
THAT THE GROUND FORCES
WORE OR SOMETHING LIKE THAT:,
IT'S AN ACTUAL FLIGHT JACKET.
I WANT TO FIND OUT
ABOUT THE FIRST AID KIT,
'CAUSE I'VE NEVER HAD ONE.
THE HAT, WE MIGHT AS WELL
HAVE HIM CHECK IT
OUT WHILE HE'S HERE.
- OKAY.
- ALL RIGHT, GOOD.
IF THESE ITEMS WERE
USED BY A FIGHTER PILOT
DURING WORLD WAR Il, THERE'S
NO QUESTION I WANT THEM.
BUT I'VE NEVER HEARD OF
A P-38 BEING USED IN ITALY,
AND THAT CONCERNS ME,
SO I HAVE TO HAVE
THEM CHECKED OUT.
WHAT DO WE HAVE HERE?
- GOT SOME CIVIL DEFENSE ALL
PURPOSE SURVIVAL CRACKERS.
- WHAT DO THEY DEFEND?
- HUNGER.
- SOUNDS ABOUT RIGHT.
- I CAME DOWN TO THE PAWN
SHOP TODAY TO SELL MY CRACKERS.
THESE ARE ABOUT 48 YEARS OLD
BUT IN, YOU KNOW,
PRETTY GOOD CONDITION.
I'M HOPING TO SELL THESE
FOR AT LEAST $75 TODAY,
BUT I'M WILLING TO TAKE $40.
- SO WHERE DID YOU GET THESE?
- A BUDDY OF MINE WORKS
FOR A REAL ESTATE COMPANY,
AND THEY WERE ABOUT
TO REMODEL A BUILDING.
TOOK ME DOWN INTO THE
OLD FALLOUT SHELTER,
AND THERE WERE SEVERAL OF THESE
CRACKER CONTAINERS DOWN THERE.
- I LOVE SOME OF
THE INGREDIENTS.
"PROPYL GALLATE"
AND "PROPYLENE GLYCOL
ADDED TO PRESERVE FRESHNESS."
- SOUNDS GOOD.
- CHUM, YOU CAN'T EAT THESE.
I GUARANTEE YOU, AFTER 48
YEARS, THEY'RE PROBABLY BAD.
THE NATIONAL BISCUIT
COMPANY. YOU KNOW WHO THAT IS?
- NOW THEY'RE KNOWN AS NABISCO.
THAT WAS THE NAME
BEFORE "NABISCO."
- DURING THE COLD WAR,
MANY BUILDINGS' BASEMENTS
WERE DESIGNATED
AS FALLOUT SHELTERS.
THIS IS WHERE YOU WOULD GO
IN CASE OF A NUCLEAR ATTACK.
NABISCO WAS ONE OF THE COMPANIES
THAT STOCKED THESE
FALLOUT SHELTERS WITH FOOD.
WELL, IN THE EARLY '60s,
A LOT OF PEOPLE THOUGHT
THAT NUCLEAR WAR WAS INEVITABLE
AND THAT WE REALLY NEEDED
THESE FALLOUT SHELTERS.
THEY MORE OR LESS
STOPPED DOING IT
BECAUSE THEY
REALIZED IT WAS... STUPID.
[laughter]
I MEAN, IF A NUCLEAR
BOMB IS DROPPED,
FALLOUT SHELTERS
AREN'T GONNA DO A LOT.
- I'M FIGURING IT'S A
GOOD THING FOR SOMEONE
THAT'S INTO COLD WAR, YOU
KNOW, COLLECTIBLES AND...
- I MEAN, IT'S NOT, LIKE,
REALLY COLLECTIBLE,
BUT IT IS SORT OF
LIKE A NOVELTY.
THESE CRACKERS ARE A REMINDER
OF ALL THE CRAZINESS GOING
ON DURING THE COLD WAR.
I'M SURE I CAN FIND
A BUYER FOR THEM.
I'M JUST REALLY GLAD
NO ONE HAD TO ACTUALLY
EVER OPEN THESE THINGS.
SO WHAT DO YOU
WANT TO DO WITH THIS?
- I WAS HOPING TO SELL IT.
- WHAT WERE YOU LOOKING FOR?
- THEY WERE GOING
AS HIGH AS $99 ONLINE.
I WAS HOPING TO GET AROUND $75.
- REALLY?
- $75 FOR SOME OLD CRACKERS?
CAN'T YOU DO MORE LIKE $35, MAN?
- THERE'S NOT A LOT OF THEM
I'VE SEEN THAT ARE NABISCO,
AND IT'S IN GREAT SHAPE.
HOW ABOUT $50?
- I CAN DO $40,
MAYBE, AT THE MOST.
- $45.
- YOU'RE REALLY
BEATING ME UP, MAN.
I'LL MEET YOU IN
THE MIDDLE AT $42.
- [laughs] OKAY.
- IT'S A DEAL.
- I'LL DO IT.
- RICK, GO DO THE PAPERWORK.
- YEAH, WHATEVER. GO
DO THE PAPERWORK, CHUM.
- I ENDED UP GETTING $42 FOR IT.
I WAS HOPING TO GET MORE, BUT
THE GUY THAT WAS NEGOTIATING
WAS DRIVING A
PRETTY HARD BARGAIN.
- HEY, WHAT CAN I HELP YOU WITH?
- WELL, I HAVE AN
OLD MUSKET HERE.
I'D LIKE TO GET RID OF IT.
- I'M NO EXPERT, BUT SHOULDN'T
THAT BE A LITTLE BIT BIGGER?
- OKAY, YEAH, 'CAUSE
IT DOESN'T REALLY...
IT FITS, LIKE, A KID.
[laughs]
USUALLY THESE
ARE, LIKE, THIS BIG.
- YEAH, I REALIZE THAT, BUT...
- IT HAS A BAYONET. I'M
ASSUMING IT'S MILITARY.
- MAYBE IT WAS FOR
SMALL SOLDIERS.
PEOPLE WERE A LITTLE
SHORTER BACK THEN.
[laughter]
- I'M COMING TO THE
PAWN SHOP TODAY.
I'M TRYING TO SELL
AN OLD MUSKET,
COULD USE EXTRA CASH FOR
SOMETHING ELSE I WANT TO BUY.
I'M HOPING TO GET $1,500.
I MIGHT TAKE $1,000.
- WHERE IN THE WORLD
DID YOU GET THIS?
- OH, I PICKED IT UP
AT AN ESTATE SALE.
- OKAY.
IT'S A LOT SMALLER THAN A NORMAL
MILITARY FLINTLOCK OF THE DAY.
I MEAN, IT LOOKS LATE 1700s.
I KNOW THERE WAS KIDS
IN THE MILITARY BACK THEN
THAT WERE, LIKE,
13, 14 YEARS OLD.
MAYBE THEY ISSUED
THEM DIFFERENT GUNS.
I MEAN, EVERYTHING
DOWN TO THE BAYONET
IS SMALLER THAN NORMAL.
A BAYONET FOR THIS
PERIOD WOULD BE, LIKE...
THAT BIG.
- OH, MY.
- A TYPICAL 18TH-CENTURY MUSKET
IS RIGHT AROUND 60 INCHES LONG.
THIS THING IS MAYBE A LITTLE
BIGGER THAN HALF THAT SIZE.
IT'S REALLY ODD.
IT'S NOT A HUNTING
RIFLE MADE FOR A KID.
IT'S A MILITARY WEAPON.
I JUST DON'T KNOW
WHAT TO MAKE OF IT.
SO WHAT DID YOU
WANT TO DO WITH IT?
- WELL, I'D LIKE TO
PART WITH IT, SELL IT.
- OKAY. HOW MUCH WERE
YOU LOOKING TO GET OUT OF IT?
- OH, I'M THINKING
SOMEWHERE AROUND 15.
- HUNDRED?
- YES.
- OKAY, THAT MIGHT NOT
BE OUT OF THE QUESTION.
I MEAN, EVERYTHING LOOKS
GOOD EXCEPT FOR THE SIZE,
WHICH HAS ME REALLY CONCERNED
WHY SOMEONE WOULD
MAKE A GUN LIKE THIS.
I DON'T WANT THIS THING
BEING A MOVIE PROP
OR SOMETHING LIKE THAT
AND ME SPENDING A
LOT OF MONEY ON IT.
- SURE, I UNDERSTAND.
- I MEAN, I DON'T THINK IT IS,
BUT THEN AGAIN, I'VE BEEN
WRONG A LOT OF TIMES.
DO YOU MIND IF I HAVE
SOMEONE LOOK AT IT?
- NO, THAT'D BE FINE.
- LET ME MAKE A PHONE
CALL, I'LL GET HIM DOWN HERE,
AND WE'LL GET THIS
THING CHECKED OUT.
ALL RIGHT?
- SOUNDS GOOD.
- IT'S POSSIBLE
THIS COULD BE, LIKE,
A SCALED-DOWN REPRODUCTION.
OR IT COULD BE A
CHILD'S MILITARY MUSKET,
WHICH WOULD MAKE IT REALLY RARE.
I'VE NEVER HAD ONE BEFORE,
SO THIS IS SOMETHING
I'M REALLY INTERESTED IN.
- EARLIER, I HAD A GUY COME IN
TRYING TO SELL SOME OLD
AVIATOR STUFF FROM WORLD WAR Il.
I HAVE SOME
QUESTIONS ABOUT THEM,
SO I INVITED MY BUDDY PAUL
DOWN TO TAKE A CLOSER LOOK.
HEY, PAUL. HOW'S IT GOING?
- HEY, RICK. HOW YOU BEEN?
- I'M DOING GREAT.
- I'M PAUL MILBURY OF MILITARY
HISTORICAL ARMS AND ANTIQUES.
I'M AN EXPERT IN ALL
TYPES OF MILITARY STUFF
DATING FROM WORLD
WAR Il BACK TO ABOUT 1776.
RICK, WHAT'S YOUR CONCERNS
OR QUESTIONS ABOUT THE JACKET?
- WHAT'S IT WORTH?
MY OTHER CONCERN
WAS THE P-38 ON THE BACK.
I THOUGHT THAT WAS
PACIFIC THEATER ONLY.
I COULD HAVE BEEN WRONG.
- THE P-38 LIGHTNING WAS USED
BY THE 97TH FIGHTER SQUADRON
FROM 1942 TO '45.
THE LATIN NAME WAS
GERENVETSO SATANA.
WHICH IS LATIN FOR "DEVIL CAT."
- SO THIS WAS FROM
THE DEVIL CATS.
- YEAH.
- OKAY.
- THE PAINTING ON THE
BACK IS FAIRLY WEAK.
ONE OF THE SAD THINGS IS,
IT'S BEEN ON A HANGER TOO LONG,
AND YOU SEE THAT WHERE
IT'S BROKEN THROUGH.
- NOW, WHAT ABOUT
THE SURVIVAL KIT?
- YOU DON'T SEE THESE TOO OFTEN
ANYMORE WITH THE CONTENTS.
- SO WHAT'S SOMETHING
LIKE THAT WORTH?
- THIS ISN'T IN THE
BEST OF SHAPE, SO...
- YEAH, RIGHT.
- MAYBE 75 BUCKS.
- OKAY, AND IS THE
HAT WORTH ANYTHING?
- THE HAT IS NOT IN
TOO GREAT OF SHAPE.
YOU HAVE A LOT OF MOTHING HERE.
IN THIS CONDITION,
YOU'D BE LUCKY
TO GET $35, $45 OUT OF IT.
NOW, DO YOU HAVE ANY
OTHER ITEMS THAT GO WITH IT?
'CAUSE ACTUALLY, WHAT'S
GOING TO MAKE THIS VALUABLE
IS THE PAPERWORK AND THE HISTORY
SAYING WHAT HE
DID, WHERE HE DID IT.
THAT'S WHAT BRINGS
IN THE VALUE NOW.
THE JACKET, I'D SAY, PUT
BETWEEN $1,000 AND $1,500.
WITH HISTORY BEHIND
IT, WITH THE PAPERWORK,
WITH OTHER STUFF, I MEAN,
THE JACKET COULD BRING,
YOU KNOW, $1,500 TO $2,500.
- OKAY. THANKS A
LOT. I APPRECIATE IT.
- FLIGHT JACKETS
ARE REALLY GREAT.
I MEAN, YOU DON'T
SEE THEM TOO OFTEN.
THEY'RE DISAPPEARING FROM
THE COLLECTOR'S MARKET.
- SO WHAT DO YOU
WANT TO DO WITH THESE?
- PROBABLY SELL IT.
- OKAY.
HOW MUCH DID YOU WANT FOR THEM?
- I WAS THINKING AROUND $1,500.
- THAT'S NOT GONNA HAPPEN.
- NO.
- I'M THINKING, LIKE,
$750 FOR ALL OF IT.
- WE'RE NOT COLLECTORS.
WE'RE SELLERS.
- RIGHT.
- AND WHEN WE
PAY YOU $100 BILLS,
THEN WE HAVE TO TAKE
AND HOLD IT, MARKET IT,
AND THEN WE TRY TO
ACQUIRE MORE $100 BILLS,
BUT SOMETIMES WE DON'T.
- LISTENING TO
PAUL, I'M THINKING...
I GOT PAPERWORK AT
HOME THAT GOES WITH THIS.
MAYBE I'LL HOLD ON TO IT,
PUT THE PACKAGE TOGETHER,
AND BRING IT BACK IN HERE.
- YEAH, BECAUSE IF
YOU BRING THAT IN,
I COULD PROBABLY MAKE
MORE MONEY WHEN I SELL IT.
- WE CAN ALL DO.
- WE CAN ALL MAKE MORE
MONEY. IT WOULD BE NICE.
- THEY WANTED TO OFFER $750.
THAT'S A PRETTY GOOD PRICE,
BUT I'M HOPING TO PUT TOGETHER
MORE OF A COMPLETE COLLECTION,
BRING IT BACK HERE,
MAYBE GET $5,000 OR $10,000.
- EARLIER, A GUY
BROUGHT IN A MUSKET
THAT'S A REALLY ODD SIZE.
IT MIGHT BE FOR A KID,
BUT I JUST DON'T KNOW,
SO I CALLED MY BUDDY SEAN
DOWN TO TAKE A CLOSER LOOK.
HEY, SEAN. WHAT'S UP?
- CHUM.
MY NAME IS SEAN RICH,
AND I OWN TORTUGA TRADING INC.,
AND I SPECIALIZE IN
ANTIQUE ARMS AND ARMOR.
ALL RIGHT, RICK, SO I'M SURE
YOU'VE GOT SOME QUESTIONS.
FIRE AWAY.
- WHAT IS IT?
THAT'S BASICALLY IT.
IT SEEMS LIKE A 3/4 SIZE GUN.
- THIS IS ACTUALLY A HALF
SCALE OF A FULL-SIZE MUSKET.
THESE WERE MADE
JUST THE SAME WAY
AS THE FULL-SIZE
MUSKETS BUT FOR A YOUTH.
SO A WEALTHY OFFICER
WHO HAD A CHILD...
SAY, 13 YEARS OLD...
HE WOULD TEACH HIM
THE PROPER WAYS TO HANDLE
A MUSKET, JUST LIKE DAD,
WITH THE BAYONET AND EVERYTHING.
THE OTHER GREAT THING
ABOUT THIS IS THE MAKER.
"H. NOCK" IS HENRY NOCK.
NOCK WAS ONE OF THE BEST AND
MOST WELL-KNOWN GUNMAKERS
IN ENGLAND DURING THE LAST
QUARTER OF THE 18TH CENTURY.
SO THIS DATES
BETWEEN 1770 AND 1780.
THIS IS JUST NOT RARE.
IT'S EXTREMELY RARE.
- THAT'S CRAZY.
ALL I GOT WHEN I WAS
A KID WAS A BB GUN.
- THIS IS A VERY
UNIQUE PIECE TO FIND.
I HAVE NEVER SEEN ONE OF THESE.
NOT ONLY IS THIS SPECIAL
BECAUSE OF THE SIZE
AND THE QUALITY OF IT,
BUT THE FACT THAT THIS
IS MADE BY HENRY NOCK
JUST PUTS IT OVER THE TOP.
- SO WHAT'S THIS THING WORTH?
- [sighs] THAT'S A
VERY GOOD QUESTION.
I'VE BEEN COLLECTING
SINCE I WAS TEN,
AND I'VE ONLY SEEN
SOMETHING LIKE THIS IN A BOOK.
SO I HAVE TO KIND OF
GO ON THE GUT BY THIS.
I THINK THIS IS SO RARE
THAT IN AN AUCTION SETTING,
PEOPLE WOULD FIGHT OVER IT.
I WOULD EXPECT
THE BID RANGE TO BE
IN THAT $5,000 TO $10,000 RANGE.
- [laughs] JACKPOT!
- YOU KNOW, THAT'S NO GUARANTEE,
BUT IT'S JUST... THAT'S
WHAT I'M THINKING.
- OKAY, THANKS, JOHN.
- ANYTIME, RICK.
- WHEN HE SAID IT WAS WORTH
BETWEEN $5,000 AND $10,000,
MAN, I WAS PUMPED.
THAT WAS GREAT NEWS.
- SO HOW MUCH YOU WANT FOR IT?
- WELL, HE SAID IT WAS
WORTH AROUND $5,000,
AND, HEY, I JUST WANT
TO START OUT AT $5,000.
- THAT'S NOT GONNA HAPPEN,
BECAUSE THAT'S WHAT I'M ASSUMING
I'M GONNA GET OUT OF IT, MAYBE.
I REALLY THINK $3,000'S IT.
- HOW ABOUT $3,500?
- I'LL GO $3,200.
- YOU KNOW WHAT?
THAT SOUNDS GOOD.
- OKAY. ALL RIGHT, MAN.
GO WRITE HIM UP, CHUM.
- I'LL MEET YOU OVER THERE.
- I'VE FIRED A LOT OF
OLD GUNS BEFORE,
BUT I'VE NEVER FIRED
A 200-YEAR-OLD MUSKET
MADE FOR A KID, SO
LET'S SEE WHAT IT'LL DO.
- HEY, HOW'S IT GOING?
- GOOD. HOW ARE YOU?
WHAT DO WE GOT?
- I GOT THESE FROM MY COUSIN.
AND I KNOW THEY'RE
AT LEAST 25 YEARS OLD,
BUT I'M NOT SURE.
WE ASSUMED THEY
WERE CASINO MARKERS,
WHERE THEY'D PUT
THEM IN FRONT OF YOU
IF YOU OWED THE CASINO MONEY.
- YOU GOT TO BE IN
PRETTY BAD SHAPE
IF YOU'RE GONNA BORROW
20 BUCKS FROM A CASINO.
[laughter]
- OKAY, YEAH.
COME DOWN TO THE PAWN SHOP TODAY
TO TRY TO SELL WHAT I THINK
ARE VERY RARE CASINO MARKERS.
SO I THINK THEY'RE
WORTH SOME MONEY.
PLUS, THEY LOOK PRETTY COOL.
I'M HOPING TO GET $1,240,
BUT THE LOWEST I'LL GO ON
THEM IS $620, THEIR FACE VALUE.
- SO WHERE DID YOU GET THESE?
- MY COUSIN'S HAD THEM
FOR THE LAST 20 YEARS.
MY ASSUMPTION WAS, THEY USED
TO THROW THEM IN FRONT OF YOU
WHEN YOU'D BORROW MONEY
AND YOU'RE SITTING AT THE TABLE.
- NO, THESE ARE NOT MARKERS.
WHAT THESE ARE IS,
THEY'RE BACCARAT CHIPS.
I THINK THEY'RE CALLED PLACARDS.
THE REASON THEY
MADE THEM LIKE THIS:
IT'S SO MUCH EASIER
TO TELL WHAT THEY ARE
AS OPPOSED TO A PILE OF CHIPS,
AND THAT'S WHY THEY USE
THEM LIKE THIS IN EUROPE.
AND THESE PARTICULAR
ONES LIKE THIS,
MUCH MORE DIFFICULT
TO COUNTERFEIT.
WHAT I CAN TELL
YOU ABOUT THESE IS,
THEY DID NOT MAKE A LOT OF THEM.
BACCARAT IS A CASINO CARD GAME
USUALLY RESERVED FOR
THE HIGHEST OF HIGH ROLLERS,
AND CASINOS CAN WIN OR
LOSE MILLIONS IN A NIGHT.
BUT MOST OF THE TIME, I
THINK THE CASINO WINS.
- I WAS ASSUMING
THEY WERE MARKERS,
WHICH I THOUGHT THAT
WOULD MAKE IT COOLER.
I'VE NEVER BEEN IN A
BACCARAT ROOM, SO...
- I THINK IT MAKES
IT A LITTLE COOLER
THAT IT'S, YOU KNOW, BACCARAT.
YOU KNOW HOW BIG THE JAMES
BOND FLICKS HAVE ALWAYS BEEN.
BACK IN THE DAY, JAMES
BOND PLAYS BACCARAT, OKAY?
SO WHAT DID YOU
WANT TO DO WITH THEM?
- I WANT TO SELL THEM.
- HOW MUCH YOU WANT FOR THESE?
- FACE VALUE?
- THAT'S NOT GONNA HAPPEN, NO.
A LOT OF PEOPLE THINK
IF THEY HAVE AN OLD CHIP,
THEY CAN JUST GO TO
THE CASINO AND CASH IT IN.
DOESN'T HAPPEN THAT WAY.
CASINOS DO THIS ALL THE TIME.
THEY PUT AN AD IN THE NEWSPAPER.
YOU GOT 30 DAYS TO
TURN IN YOUR CHIPS.
AFTER THAT, THEY'RE WORTHLESS.
EVEN THOUGH THESE
CHIPS HAVE NO CASH VALUE,
THEY'RE STILL WORTH MONEY
TO COLLECTORS OF CASINO STUFF.
SO NOW THAT WE KNOW THAT,
HOW MUCH DO YOU WANT FOR THEM?
- HOW MUCH WILL YOU
GIVE ME FOR THEM?
- I WILL GIVE YOU $100,
I WILL GIVE YOU $50,
AND I WILL GIVE YOU $20.
- SO $170.
- THAT IS IT.
- YOU CAN'T DO BETTER THAN THAT?
- AT LEAST YOU GET
THE FACE VALUE ON ONE.
[laughter]
- AT THE BOTTOM. HOW ABOUT $270?
- I'LL GO $200 BUCKS. I
WON'T GO A DIME MORE.
- I CAN'T DO IT FOR $200.
- OKAY.
ALL RIGHT, WELL, THANKS
FOR BRINGING THEM IN.
I APPRECIATE IT.
- THANK YOU.
YEAH, I'M KIND OF DISAPPOINTED.
I WANTED TO MAKE A FEW BUCKS.
AND, AH, I'LL JUST KEEP THEM
AND PUT THEM UP IN MY BAR.
I THINK THEY LOOK PRETTY COOL.
I'LL GIVE THEM ANOTHER
20 YEARS TO SIMMER.
- WHAT DO WE GOT HERE?
- GOT THE FIRST THREE
YEARS OF SPORTS ILLUSTRATED.
- YOU GOT THE ISSUE WHERE
LEBRON WENT TO MIAMI?
- NOT OUT YET.
I DECIDED TO COME TO THE PAWN
SHOP TODAY TO TRY AND SELL
MY FIRST THREE SEASONS
OF SPORTS ILLUSTRATED.
FOUND THEM IN THE ATTIC.
THEY SHOULD JUST BE OUT THERE.
SOME COLLECTOR SHOULD HAVE 'EM.
I DON'T WANT THEM
TO GO TO THE WAYSIDE.
I'M LOOKING FOR, YOU
KNOW, MAYBE AROUND $1,000.
- IT'S A REALLY COOL MAGAZINE,
AND A LOT OF PEOPLE COLLECT IT.
I MEAN, THE FACT THAT YOU GOT
THE FIRST THREE SEASONS OF IT,
THAT MEANS A LOT.
- WHEN YOU USED TO
GET THESE AS A KID,
THOSE BIG, BLOWN-UP PICTURES,
YOU NEVER SAW IT BEFORE.
I HAD THEM TAPED ON MY WALLS.
- A LOT OF PEOPLE STILL LISTENED
TO THE GAMES ON THE RADIO.
AND THEY ONLY GOT
ONE GAME AT A TIME.
THIS IS HOW YOU
KEPT UP WITH SPORTS.
WHEN SPORTS ILLUSTRATED
CAME OUT IN 1954,
PEOPLE LAUGHED AT THE IDEA
OF AN ALL-SPORTS MAGAZINE.
NOBODY THOUGHT
ANYBODY WOULD READ IT.
WANT TO SHOW ME SOME OF
THE COOLEST ONES YOU HAVE?
- SURE. THE FIRST ISSUE.
REAL BIG, AND THE DRAW
IS, THEY HAVE ALL THESE...
ALL THE OLD COLLECTOR
BASEBALL CARDS IN THEM, INSERTS.
IF YOU CUT THEM
UP, THEY'RE NO GOOD.
APPARENTLY, IF YOU
KEEP THEM IN THE BOOK,
THEY'RE WORTH SOME MONEY NOW.
SECOND ISSUE AS WELL,
BUT THEY'RE ALL THE YANKEES.
THE BIG DRAW IS MICKEY MANTLE.
THEN, OF COURSE, YOU GOT
THE FIRST-EVER SWIMSUIT EDITION.
CHECK HER OUT. SHE'S HOT, HUH?
- WAH, WAH, WHEE-WAH.
[laughter]
- SO ARE ALL THE MAGAZINES
IN GOOD CONDITION OR...
- RIGHT FROM THE STAND.
- WOW.
THIS IS AN AMAZING COLLECTION,
AND IT'S GREAT THAT
THEY'RE FROM A NEWSSTAND
AND DON'T HAVE
MAILING LABELS ON THEM.
THAT MAKES THEM
MUCH MORE VALUABLE,
BUT THE PRICE HAS TO BE RIGHT,
BECAUSE IT'S GONNA TAKE A
LONG TIME TO SELL THEM ALL.
SO WHAT ARE YOU LOOKING TO
DO, MAN, PAWN THEM OR SELL THEM?
- I'M GONNA SELL THEM.
- ALL RIGHT, WHAT ARE YOU
LOOKING TO GET FOR THEM?
- COULD BE WITH 1,000
BUCKS, AND THEN YOU GUYS
COULD PROBABLY DOUBLE
YOUR MONEY ON THAT.
- YOU GOT TO REMEMBER,
EACH ONE OF THESE MAGAZINES,
A GUY'S GOT TO
SIT AT A COMPUTER,
WRITE A DESCRIPTION ON,
AND IT COULD TAKE A LONG TIME.
- I HEAR YOU.
- MY COMFORT
AREA IS AROUND $500.
- WELL, $500, I MEAN, THE
FIRST TWO ISSUES ALONE,
YOU GUYS COULD
PROBABLY GET $400, $500
FOR THOSE FIRST COUPLE ISSUES.
SOMEONE WILL BUY THIS WHOLE SET.
BUT, YOU KNOW, $900?
- I'LL TELL YOU WHAT, MAN.
I'LL SPLIT THE DIFFERENCE.
I'LL GO $750. IT'S THE
BEST I'M GONNA DO.
- THAT'S FAIR. I'LL TAKE IT.
- THAT'S FAIR? ALL RIGHT.
- YOU GOT A DEAL.
- MY MAN CHUMLEE
HERE WILL WRITE YOU UP.
- GREAT. WELL, WE GOT
DONE WITH THE DEAL.
I MADE IT FOR
$750. THAT'S GREAT.
I'M GONNA PROBABLY
TAKE MY WIFE OUT
TO A NICE DINNER TONIGHT.
- EARLIER, I BOUGHT
AN 18TH-CENTURY HALF-SIZE
MUSKET MADE FOR A KID.
SO SEAN AND I ARE ON OUR WAY
TO GO SEE IF THIS THING FIRES.
SINCE WE DON'T WANT TO
RISK HARMING ANY ACTUAL KIDS,
WE BROUGHT CHUM ALONG INSTEAD.
- NOW, BACK IN THE
DAY, THIS GUN WAS USED
BY PROBABLY A 10-
OR 12-YEAR-OLD BOY.
THE ORIGINAL MUSKET WOULD
HAVE HAD A 46-INCH BARREL,
WHERE THIS WHOLE ENTIRE
GUN IS ONLY 46 INCHES,
BUT EVERYTHING IN DETAIL,
AGAIN, IS JUST HALF THE SIZE.
BUT WE'RE GONNA SEE WHAT
KIND OF DAMAGE IT WILL DO.
- ALL RIGHT.
I'M READY TO DEFEND YOU.
[laughter]
- EVEN THOUGH THIS GUN
WAS MADE FOR KIDS AND...
I'M NOT GONNA LET CHUM
JUST TAKE IT AND RUN WITH IT.
IT'S A GOOD THING THAT I'M HERE.
OKAY, WE'RE GONNA LOAD THIS
WITH ABOUT 70 GRAINS OF POWDER.
THE STANDARD MILITARY MUSKET
WOULD TAKE ABOUT
100 TO 120 GRAINS.
WE'RE GONNA DO
THIS WITH HALF THAT.
- JUST ENOUGH TO HURT ME, HUH?
- JUST ENOUGH.
ALL RIGHT, SO, CHUM,
THIS IS YOUR TARGET.
- ALL RIGHT.
- SO I'M GONNA BE
STATIONING CHUM
ABOUT 25 FEET AWAY
FROM THE TARGET,
WHICH IS A WATER-FILLED BALLOON.
- ALL RIGHT, CHUM,
YOU MAKE THIS,
YOU GET A BUCKET
OF GREASY CHICKEN.
- NOW YOU'RE TALKING
MY LANGUAGE, RICK.
LET'S DO THIS.
[gunshot]
[laughter] BAM!
DO NOT MESS WITH UNCLE RICKY!
- CHUM DID REALLY, REALLY GREAT.
THE FIRST SHOT, HE HIT THE
TARGET, BLEW THE BALLOON UP.
IT'S A REALLY GOOD FEELING
WHEN YOU PULL THE TRIGGER
AND YOU ACTUALLY HIT THE TARGET,
ESPECIALLY WHEN
YOU HAVE AN AUDIENCE.
- NO ONE'S GONNA GET
YOU WHILE I'M HERE.
- THAT'S RIGHT, CHUM. AND
YOU GET A BUCKET OF CHICKEN.
EXTRA GREASY.
- THAT'S HOW I LIKE IT.
- [laughs]
- NICE.