[music playing]
[blasts]
NARRATOR: Its creators
do not want you to know.
They have achieved
the next level.
[blast]
"Cybertracker 2"
Look at my masterpiece.
I can put any face on it I want.
Governor--
The governor is dead, as
required by our contract.
It was a perfect
duplicate of Connie.
It was perfect.
You can assassinate any world
leader, anywhere on the globe,
at any time.
NARRATOR:
Jesus Christ, it's you Eric.
NARRATOR: The inventor's
program is genius.
Police pursue the innocent--
[blasts]
--while they pursue profit.
The advanced cybertechnology
made us millionaires.
NARRATOR: But their
formula for success
does not allow for error.
[blast]
We've gotten rid
of his kind before.
NARRATOR: The replicated
must be terminated.
You are to be executed now.
An army couldn't stop it.
We're not going to be
able to shake this thing.
[blast]
You might kill a president,
or a king, or a prime minister.
He's going to be famous.
NARRATOR: But their
immediate target--
[gunshots]
--fights back.
[crash]
[blast]
[music playing]
[blasts]
[laser shots]
[gunshots]
[blast]
[blasts]
Someone's trying to trace our
tap into the police cyberbase.
But there's evidence
of our operation there.
I think I've got
enough information.
He's too close.
Somebody's got
to listen to me.
Witnesses are confirming.
NARRATOR: The world
believes only what it sees.
[blast]
"Cybertracker 2."
[music playing]