Ring announcer:
Ladies and gentlemen,
from Jersey city,
New Jersey,
it's the local attraction
that you've all
been waiting for.
( Bell dings )
( Crowd cheering )
Announcer: Now,
I just love this story--
the prosecutor
vs. The cop.
The two senseis both have
competing m.M.A. Schools
in the same
New Jersey town.
Two of their students--
Felix Sanchez,
who has already fought and won
in five professional fights,
and Anthony Rodriguez--
check it out--
an autistic savant who fights
with magic from within.
( Crowd cheering )
Announcer: Watch out.
He's in trouble here.
Announcer #2:
I think so.
Judge, I want
to object,
but it's more
that I'm confused.
Could you instruct
Mr. Carroll
to stop staring
at my client?
Judge:
Mr. Carroll.
Mr. Carroll,
are we going to continue?
He's the guy...
He's the guy you saw
bludgeoning the victim
when you arrived
at the party?
Man":
"Bludgeoning"?
No, not bludgeoning.
He was punching
the one kid who was
punching him back.
Please let the court reflect
that officer tantino just
identified the defendant.
So reflected.
So let me get
this straight:
When you arrived
at the party,
you and sgt. Randinski
had to physically
separate pello
from the victim?
Yeah, I had to grab one kid,
and sgt. Randinski grabbed
the other kid.
They weren't locked
in mortal combat,
fighting to the death.
These are two young kids
that had a little--
thank you.
No further questions,
officer.
You're really exaggerating
what happened here,
counselor.
I said,
no more questions.
Officer, you can't
just offer statements
on your own.
That means you're done.
You don't make speeches.
You understand?
Judge:
But of course.
Now the defense can
cross-examine you.
Miss Rodriguez.
So, officer tantino,
you seem to have
more testimony.
What exactly
did happen?
We didn't make any arrests,
and no complaints were signed,
but the victim in this case
decided to pursue
the matter in court
after speaking
to Mr. Carroll here,
who I believe
is not only the
prosecutor but is also
his martial arts sensei.
I object, your honor.
I guess since he didn't
train his student well enough
to defend himself--
I object!
( All talking at once )
What are you
looking for, counselor?
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Enjoy.
So three guys
are at a party
arguing about who's
got the best memory.
God help me.
First guy says,
"I remember my mother
putting on my diaper."
Second guy says,
"I remember being born."
Third guy says,
"that's nothing.
"I remember
going to a party
with my father
and coming home
with my mother."
( Man laughing )
You know--
oh, god.
That's almost
as funny as,
"why did the pothead
cross the road"?
Who else would
follow a chicken?
( Cell phone rings )
Hang on.
Yeah, detective toney.
Right.
Right. Gotcha.
Thank you.
Woods is on
his way to the barn,
and Nick is on
his way after him.
We're off
like a prom dress.
Oh, please. God,
you're so terrible.
Just come with me.
Hey-hey.
Corned-beef special
today, Nick?
No, I'm not here
for lunch today.
Oh.
You're here for Bobby?
That scumbag's
inside, right?
Ah, here we go.
Hey, baby.
How's it goin'?
Bobby woods.
Got a warrant
for your arrest.
Looks like
possession
of cocaine
with the intent
to distribute.
That's ugly.
Turn around,
put your hands
behind your back.
Sure, Nick.
Don't move.
( Siren wailing )
What?
Drop the goddamn knife!
Don't do it,
Bobby!
Just relax.
Don't hurt her.
You never could fight
like a man, could you?
( Bones snap )
( Bobby screams )
What is the greatest
American pastime?
Is it hockey?
Men:
No, sensei!
Is it soccer?
Is it even football?
No, sensei!
What is the greatest
American pastime, frank?
Baseball, sensei!
That's right.
And why is it
baseball, Megan?
Its statistics,
sensei!
That's right.
Its statistics.
Stat!
70 home runs, sensei!
150 rbi, sensei!
Stat!
300 strikeouts, sensei!
30 wins, sensei!
Stat!
.400 batting average,
sensei!
And is this
a game?
No, sensei.
Is what we do here
a pastime?
All:
No, sensei!
This is real!
It's our way
of life!
And you know what happens
when you don't properly train?
( Coughing )
This could happen
to you at a party,
this could happen
to you at a bar,
on the street.
Man, get this
little girl
off my mat.
Class, hut!
Dan, Felix, contact.
All right, now,
don't start.
I'm not even
gonna ask,
but it couldn't
have happened to
a more liberal judge.
( Muffled curse )
Officer tantino!
Chief's looking for you.
Officer tantino,
Sandra chilton.
I represent
judge demitro.
What can I do for you,
miss chilton?
Don't you think it's
a tad disrespectful,
arresting the judge
in his robes?
"Disrespectful"?
I let him put it on.
I don't understand.
The only thing
the judge was wearing
when I found him
was that gag
in his mouth
and nothing else.
Oh, now, that is
ridiculous.
( Muffled exclamations )
You got something
to say, judge?
The state supreme court
has put our free speech
rights in jeopardy.
I've done all
that I can
in the courtroom.
Now I'm taking it
to the streets.
Gagged and naked
is how they have
left US,
so gagged and naked
is how I will be.
Officer, put that gag
back in my mouth.
Oh, judge.
( Chuckles )
And besides,
I'm the most
muscular judge
on the planet.
Have you seen
the size of my arms
or my chest?
And everything else--
all right,
that's enough.
I don't want to hear--
let's go.
Hey.
Hey. Chief
wants you, Nick.
Yeah, yeah.
The chief is livid
about this arrest.
Man:
Why is it that
you have to get
suspended so many times?
I'm being suspended
for speaking
the truth in court?
How about
Zane carroll, Nick?
Why do you want to
embarrass this guy?
He's part of our team.
He's a dangerous person.
He's a powerful
person, Nick.
Do you have any idea
how badly I'd like to
kick his ass?
You couldn't.
( Scoffs )
Yeah, sure.
Zane carroll wants
your head in a basket.
I'm not gonna give it
to him, of course,
because...
You're my boy.
Thank you.
Don't thank me yet.
I have a new
assignment for you.
A little change
of scenery, Nick--
at the high school.
So, how much
can you bench press?
Really?
Girl:
Come on.
What do you bench?
Hmm.
I would say...
300 pounds?
Yeah.
Girl: So if you had to pick
one of these kids who'd become
a murderer, who would it be?
I don't know.
Shouldn't you be doing
something about that?
Is it my job
to stop them?
I don't think so.
( Whistle blows )
( Shouting )
Face off again!
So what's
your job here?
I have no idea.
( Bell ringing )
Woman:
Anybody tell me who are
some of the major players
in the courtroom
in the criminal
justice system?
It could be a man
or a woman
who sits
at the bench.
Come on, guys.
He's the one who makes
all the decisions.
He's the judge.
Right.
I know because my mom
just paid him
a lot of fines
for drunk driving.
( Students laughing )
Thank you, Juan.
I think that's more
than we need to know.
Oh, yeah.
There's also a lot
of pigs in the court too.
I think the men
and women in blue
have a more proper name.
Police officers.
Woman:
Yes. I think what
Juan meant to say
was "police officers."
Now, Anthony,
I bet that you know
a lot about the courtroom,
with your sister
being a lawyer.
Man:
Anthony, can you
help US out?
I'll bet you
she's in the court
all the time, right?
Cassie is
a defense attorney.
Anthony, do you want
to try and tell US what
she does in the courtroom?
He's not gonna answer you,
miss gause. He never does.
Okay.
We all might be
a little slow in here,
but Anthony,
that's a real moron.
( Students laughing )
Hey, we don't like
new kids in our school.
Especially
real stupid ones
that don't talk!
Get up and go to
the vice-principal's office.
What, are you taking
the dummy's side,
miss gause?
Man:
That's enough, Juan.
Let's go.
I don't want to be here.
Leave.
Excuse me.
Get out.
I hope you enjoy
your last few moments
here alone, Nick.
You obviously
have a point.
Why don't you
make it?
I'm buying this school.
I outbid you.
Man:
How do you get
a fat girl in bed?
Piece of cake.
( Laughing )
Good one, Dutch.
You and I, we're
under contract, right?
Yes, we are.
No, no, no.
That's for the building.
Stevie ray, he owns
the martial arts school.
And I just offered him
ten more large than
Nicky boy here.
You know what
a crying shame is?
A crying shame is
a busload of lawyers
gone over a cliff...
Both:
With two empty seats.
Yeah, I've never
heard that one before.
Don't pretend you got
a sense of humor.
Stevie's been
bullshitting you,
Mr. Prosecutor.
I've got a lien
on the school
for failure
to pay rent.
And the sale
of the hawthorne institute
of martial arts
goes to...
Drum roll...
( Imitates drum roll )
Nick tantino.
Carroll:
We'll see
about that.
Maybe in court.
Yeah, maybe.
Hey, we can settle this now.
Step on the mat, counselor.
Now, now, don't.
Okay, guys.
Appreciate you
having my back.
Means a lot.
Thanks.
Don't thank me,
pay me.
You got it.
Miss gause,
I'm Cassie Rodriguez.
Please,
have a seat.
Thank you.
You settling into
New Jersey life
all right?
Must be a huge adjustment
after living
your whole life
in Florida.
Oh, no.
Not my whole life.
Uh, Anthony and I
were actually both
born in Manhattan.
Then after
my parents died,
we moved to tampa.
We lived with
our grandmother,
and then
unfortunately
she passed
when I was just 19,
so it's just been
Anthony and I
ever since then.
Well, I had no idea.
I'm really sorry.
Oh, thank you.
So how's Anthony doing?
Well, I'm very glad
we're having this meeting,
because I do have
some serious concerns.
Okay.
He hasn't connected
with anyone.
Not me;
not my aide, Mr. Watson;
Not a single student.
Well, he just
needs more time,
and then he'll warm up
to a few students.
Well, we haven't seen
even the slightest
indication of that yet.
I have yet to receive
much information from
his previous high school,
but, uh, I see here
that his diagnosis
is autism,
not asperger's.
No. Doctors have said
that he showed some
signs of asperger's,
like high intelligence--
I'm sure you've seen that
in his schoolwork.
Yes. The high intelligence
is very evident
from his tests.
And honestly, that's...
That's the main reason
I have yet to refer him to
an alternative school setting.
No. He doesn't need
This is the right
place for him.
Trust me on this.
At home, he's
very organized,
and he knows exactly
what he needs to do
for your class.
He speaks to me in full
sentences the majority
of the time.
He will talk to you.
He will communicate
with you.
He just needs
a little bit more time.
Well, it's...
It's obvious
that you know your brother
better than anybody here.
I will give him
a little more time--
say, a month or so.
But we really do
need to see some
social progress.
At minimum,
some more
communication.
Thank you,
miss gause.
I really
appreciate it.
And I'd be
more than happy
to be a guest speaker.
Oh, that would
be great.
Yes, I think that
that would really help
motivate Anthony.
Yes, I do too.
Thank you.
And the capital
of Maine is...
Augusta.
Right. Vermont.
Montpelier.
Good.
The capital of
New Hampshire is Concord.
The capital of Connecticut
is Hartford. The capital of
Rhode Island is Providence.
New York, Albany;
New Jersey; Trenton;
Very good. Keep going.
The capital of Delaware
is Dover; The capital of
Maryland is Annapolis.
See, Anthony?
This is what you
need to do at school:
Speak to people
in complete sentences.
Do you think you can
try and do that?
I'm hungry.
What's for dinner?
( Rap music plays )
Hello, Nicholas.
Hey, Jill.
So, this is
the place.
Yeah, this is it.
Want me to
give you a tour?
Sure.
This is
the weight room.
I can see that.
This is the women's
change room--
lockers and showers.
You look good.
Thank you.
So do you.
This is the men's room.
Got some sweaty,
athletic guys
hanging out in there.
I can see you spending
some time in there.
Not funny, Nick.
Oh, and back there is
just an unfinished area.
I'm still
working on it.
What are you gonna
do with it?
I'm gonna finish it.
Come on. Can't wait
to show you this.
This...
This is the main
fight room.
It's where it's all
gonna go down.
Pretty nice,
right?
It's a palace.
Palace for you,
Nicholas.
Jill, this is
what I want.
This... this is
what I need.
What you need
is to support me,
your wife,
and not spend
our entire savings
on a midlife crisis.
How many students
do you have?
It's not about
students right now.
It's about having
a place to train,
get back into shape,
and fight professionally again.
Nick, that was
15 years ago.
And are you kidding me?
This entire place
for just you?
Jill, you know what?
I've had enough.
I can't stand my job.
I don't want to be
a cop anymore.
They've got me
babysitting kids
in the high school.
I just
want to fight.
I'm not going down
with you, Nick.
I've stood by you
through all your
suspensions,
all your violence.
Yeah, you've been
a gentleman to me,
but all your violence...
And that one time
long ago--
how many women
would've stood
by you for that?
No more. You've got
a shower here. Move in.
This is
your new home.
I came here hoping
that I wouldn't
have to give you this.
It's over, Nick.
Funny how you
don't fight this.
Anthony:
Food? Food? Food? Food? Food?
Food? Food? Food?
Food? Food?
Anthony, you have to
get along at school.
You have to
participate.
( Sighs ) Miss gause
called my office. She wants
me to be a guest speaker.
Guest speaker, good.
You will be a good
guest speaker.
Anthony, they don't
know about your past
and what happened
in Florida.
Boy:
I wanna see it.
( Chattering )
Hold on.
Yeah, I'm tubby,
but that's the dummy.
Yeah, you are one
moronic son of a bitch,
aren't you?
Yo.
This'll wake you
from your sleep.
( Spanish )
Hey.
Hey, get off him!
( Blows whistle )
Hey.
Calm down.
Relax. It's okay.
This is where it happened,
over by this basket.
Really, I've never seen
anything quite like it
before.
So athletic, but brutal.
He's autistic?
Yes, but he's
not brutal.
Miss Rodriguez,
when we spoke,
you didn't tell me
about Anthony's past,
but today our principal did.
I have Anthony's files
from south tampa high school.
Ninth and tenth grades.
Seven fights,
four suspensions,
one expulsion.
Eleventh grade--
well, half of it--
three broken ribs,
one broken nose,
and several stitches--
mind you, that with
three different boys.
Now, here's
my favorite:
The balance of
eleventh grade
and one month
of twelfth grade
at St. Joe's--
14 fights. I--
you don't have to say
anything else, Dr. Conci.
Priests and nuns
perhaps have
a little bit more Patience
with their students,
maybe because they have
a certain higher calling
they're beholden to.
As principal of
a public high school,
I have a different
higher calling
to deal with:
A superintendent
and a board
of education.
And they're worried
about things like
getting sued.
I could definitely see
a lawsuit here.
He mercilessly beat
Felix and Juan.
No provocation.
Excuse me.
That's not accurate.
You were there,
and you know it didn't
happen that way.
Look, both of these kids
were teasing Anthony
almost to the point
of harassment,
and the one kid, Felix,
he whipped the ball
at Anthony's chest
from point-blank range
and then he put
his hands on him.
This is the kind of thing
that's happened before.
Look, Anthony
gets provoked.
It seems so this time,
based on what
officer tantino witnessed,
but all his prior schools
seem to describe
a ticking time bomb.
And we've discussed
his antisocial behavior.
With this new development,
I really think that
he needs to go to
an alternative school
setting.
No.
I'm sorry.
Look, he's already in
a special ed class,
and I really don't want him
any more labeled.
I'm sorry, Ms. Rodriguez,
but his past is so
very, very troubling.
Look, Dr. Conci,
what if I was personally
responsible for Anthony?
What?
I'm here as the school
resource officer.
I'm supposed to be
teaching kids.
What if I focus all
my energy and concentrate
on just one student?
I'm a veteran
police officer
and a seasoned
black belt.
I know I could
help that kid curb
his violence.
I could help him
control it
and maybe even find out
what causes it.
Okay, I'm sure if
he was under your
constant supervision,
you could protect
the other students,
but you don't have
any education or experience
working with autistic
children, do you?
You're right. I don't have
any training or expertise
in autism,
but that kid made
direct eye contact
with me.
That's not usual
with autistic kids.
Am I right?
That's absolutely right.
I've been around
the block a few times,
and I know a few things
about combat.
There was something strange
going on with that kid when
he was fighting those boys,
something that took him
completely out of
his cocoon.
I want the opportunity
to train Anthony.
I know that through
the martial arts, I could
help him cultivate
and develop those
incredible skills
he has.
You not only want US
to keep him in high school,
but you want US
to allow you to
teach him
how to fight even more?
Well, yeah.
Nick:
I'm gonna teach you
some grappling, Anthony.
Now, watch this.
Show him
the arm bar.
Anthony, pay attention.
Ho!
I have Glenn's arm,
and if he doesn't tap,
his arm's gonna break.
Okay!
I hope you've
got this kid
on a short leash.
Very short.
It was no small task
convincing
the superintendent.
I don't know, man.
I really want to
help this kid.
We'll show him some kicks.
Get your helmet on.
Come on!
Please, Anthony.
This is the
roundhouse kick.
I got a low kick
to the thigh...
( Exclaims )
Up to the ribs,
nice and high.
Nice head kick, Anthony.
Roundhouse to the head.
( Exclaims )
I'd better see
some results
in 60 days.
Like what?
How should I know?
I don't know anything
about retarded kids.
Nick:
I want to teach
you that, man.
You're gonna get it.
Get up.
Anthony--
Anthony.
Anthony!
( Exclaims )
You know, I really
love you guys.
You're not just
my students,
you're my family.
And I really feel like
I'm letting you down.
I mean,
is it me
or is it you?
Riley, you got
your ass kicked
at a party.
Is it me
or is it you?
And the week
before that,
Toby, you got
your tooth
knocked out
in a bar fight.
Is it me
or is it you?
And Felix...
Felix, my prize,
my top student,
a brilliant pugilist,
an 18-year-old
high-school senior
who's never lost
a tournament fight--
5 and 0, beat m.M.A. Stars
with years of experience,
and you get your ass
kicked in gym class
by an autistic kid?
So I ask you again,
is it me or is it you?
Is it me
or is it you?
It's me! It's me! It's me!
It's me! It's me!
It's me.
( Phone numbers beeping )
( Line ringing )
"What about his father,
( Phone rings )
"A surgeon criminal,
a man responsible
for probably
many deaths?"
( Ringing continues )
So then
why should he worry about
letting his father go?
He couldn't be expected
to do everything right.
He couldn't be loyal
to everything
all at once.
Carroll:
Still teaching that
American literature?
Private lesson,
I'm assuming.
That's the only kind
I do now.
Katerina, can you
give me a minute?
Of course,
professor Cooper.
How is, uh,
New Jersey?
I have a problem
in our other world.
There's this--
this cop.
He's gotten so far
under my skin.
I just want to rip
his throat out.
I just want to kill him.
Focus. Streamline.
Think about
what you need.
A cop has been
training this kid,
and he's embarrassed
my most prized student.
Sounds simple.
Well, it's more complicated.
The kid, he's, uh...
He's, like, handicapped.
He's autistic.
Do you remember how
I taught you to fight?
Our creed?
Not only do I remember it,
sensei, I teach it.
Then live it.
Modify your officer
in every way that you can,
in every aspect of his life.
And the student?
You owe your student
your loyalty.
And remember,
you can't be expected
to be loyal to everything
all at once.
( Phone beeps )
Katerina.
Yes?
Where were we?
Here.
( Both chuckling )
( Line ringing )
Megan, come in here
for a moment, please.
Hello?
Felix,
I want you to come
here before school
tomorrow morning.
We're gonna start
a new type of training.
I need you to run
a criminal case
history for me.
On who?
Nick tantino.
But he's a cop.
So I'm investigating him.
About what?
Fraud.
Falsifying his
law enforcement
job application.
Aren't we a little
past the statute
of limitations?
Just listen to me
for a second.
I heard a story about him.
I just want to find out
if it's true.
If it is, then lying
on his application will
be the least of his troubles.
But it's what I need
to legally investigate him.
So you want me to
do this at the office?
Of course.
Where else?
Thank you.
How's Anthony
been doing?
Has he been taking
any interest in
the martial arts training?
Not yet.
I can't get him to
say two words to me.
I don't know if he's
absorbing the techniques or--
he's been
talking about you
here at home.
He has? Really?
Yeah.
And for him to talk
about something
so quickly
is unusual.
Anthony, dinner!
You know, most
autistic kids
lose a previously
acquired ability
to speak sentences
or even words.
But Anthony?
Anthony has actually
progressed.
There's
high-functioning
autism,
sometimes called
p.O.D.-N.O.S.,
and then there's
diagnostic categories,
such as Rhett's syndrome
and fragile-x syndrome.
This disorder is
very confusing.
I mean, there are
some autistic kids
that have
the messiest desks
at school,
and then there are some
with the neatest ones.
But there's one
unifying factor:
All have difficulty
communicating
and interacting
with others.
Anthony, dinner!
There he is.
Yeah. My brother
sure does
communicate when
he wants to,
through aberrational
reflexive
and fighting skills.
How do we figure
this out?
How do we put this
to a positive use?
I think I have somebody
that I can bring
into the fold
that can really help US.
Another martial arts
instructor?
Well, sort of.
Hi. Dr. Reno.
And who the fuck
are you?
Uh, I'm Glenn.
I work for Nick.
So he sent some lackey
to pick me up
from the train, hmm?
Uh, can I take
your bags?
Do I look like some kind
of fucking idiot? No.
You can't take my bags.
Just take me to Nick.
Come on!
Get your ass moving.
Okay.
Get up,
you lazy bastard!
( Chuckling )
Dr. Reno!
Good to see you, kid.
So, I'm staying here?
Of course not. I got
a nice hotel room
picked out for you.
Hell, no.
I'm staying on site
in this environment.
I just meant,
is this dump my room?
I'll put you in
another dump room.
Don't you know how
to treat a guest?
Pick up my fucking bags.
Take 'em to my room.
Yes, sir.
All right.
Get your ass moving.
Come on, pussy!
Yeah, come on!
( Exclaiming )
Kick!
One, two, three--
get up! You're never
gonna fall down
on me again.
Remember, we don't fight fair,
we fight to win. Now, say it!
We don't fight fair,
we don't...
We fight to win!
Zane.
Tantino's rap sheet
is clean.
Shit!
And I felt
really awkward
pulling his file.
Is everybody
a pussy here?
Zane...
I'm sorry.
As prosecutors, I know
we have the right
to investigate,
but I'm real unclear
of what we're doing here.
Call it.
Wrestle.
I think he killed
somebody.
What?
Like, 20 years ago.
How? When? Where?
How could he be a cop
if he killed somebody?
I don't know.
Give me 50.
Okay, listen to me.
In my office,
there's a promotional
agreement
for a professional bout
in Jersey city.
I want you to extend
that agreement to tantino
and his student.
I don't understand.
Do you want to fight
tantino or prosecute him?
Both.
Get out of here.
Come on!
( Clapping hands )
( Growls )
Doc, this is the file
with all Anthony's
information.
Did you forget?
I make my own
observations.
There's nothing in that file
that will help this boy.
Right?
You stupid prick!
Dr. Reno, easy.
Huh?
( Yells )
Jesus.
I don't know
what's wrong
with this kid.
So that's it?
Certainly not,
you buffoon!
We're gonna have to
get down and dirty!
Deal with his mind!
Get rough with him!
Goddamn it.
Get his sister
down here!
We need her help.
You got it.
Woman:
Judge demitro isn't
really nuts, your honor.
You understand that.
That depends how
you look at it.
How so?
Standing naked
in front of his house
is kind of crazy.
Well--
but he was
smart enough
to hire the two
prettiest lawyers in town.
We're from
the same firm,
your honor.
Then you have
a smart boss.
I am the boss.
Then the charge
will go away?
I mean, it was
his house,
and he thought
he was walking
into the bathroom,
but he accidentally
went out the front door.
Well, I shouldn't
talk about the case
without the prosecutor.
But can you
give US a hint?
That judge demitro
sure is a smart man.
Court is adjourned
for today, ladies.
Thank you, judge.
Thank you, your honor.
You know,
30 years back,
I could kick
higher than you
and hit much harder!
Oh, Jesus!
I didn't mean to
make it a challenge.
You know I'd never
hurt you, doc.
Anthony...
That kid's the challenge.
I'm gonna really need
your help with him.
We've got
a challenge for you.
Hey.
Come on in, baby.
Zane carroll's
promoting a bout.
Ten professional fights,
all weight classes.
My buddy Zane carroll, huh?
Where's this gonna take place?
Jersey city.
And who does he
want to fight?
Is this your student?
No, no, no.
I'm the, uh,
teacher, honey.
Aren't you a lawyer
or something?
And a black belt.
Wow! Wow!
What a woman. Hey.
Take a swing
at me, baby.
( Chuckling )
Wait a minute.
He wants Anthony
to have
a professional fight
in less than a month?
What is he thinking?
It's against Felix.
He already
knocked him out
in school.
Well, I'll tell him
the offer's rejected.
No, no, no. Hold on.
You got a pen?
I'm only in town
for a few days,
so why don't we have
a little pre-fight?
Who is this guy?
Don't ask him.
He doesn't know how
to treat a lady.
Come by my room.
It's kind of a dump,
but I can show you moves
that you never even heard of.
Hmm?
So it's on?
Give that to Mr. Carroll.
Yeah.
Show me the moves.
I'll see you in,
let's say, an hour?
I'll see you
and your sensei
in Jersey city.
Oh, wow.
I wanna do...
Something for you.
Well, I hope
it's something better
than that rhyme.
Oh, it is.
Do it.
All right.
Well, it's called
"pushups for love."
What?
Yeah, 'cause
you're a hottie
and I love
your body
and I wanna get
real naughty.
So I do these
pushups, baby--
pushups for love.
Yeah.
Can't we just go
get something to eat?
No, I got, like,
three more.
One... pushup... more...
For love.
All right, let's go.
Whoa!
What's brown
and hides
in the attic?
The diarrhea
of Anne frank.
I don't get it.
Yeah, of course
you don't.
'Course not.
( Chuckles )
Come on.
Anne who?
Nick:
Really going to town
on that bag, big guy.
Hey, doc,
here's that kid.
Oh! Hey!
So, this is
my specimen, huh?
( Chuckles )
( Growls )
Come with me,
my son.
So you're
the smart-ass
who's gonna help me
figure out this
conundrum, hmm?
Juan:
What's a "cundrum"?
( Chuckles )
You asshole.
What was that?
What's going on?
I'm back to falsely
arresting criminals.
Is that an oxymoron?
Get outta here.
Cassie, time out.
I know it looks bad,
but trust me,
it's all under control.
Believe it or not,
this is my team.
Cassie, you came!
Yeah.
Let me show you.
Atta boy.
Good job, champ.
Dr. Reno:
Come on, ya grimy
little sea urchin.
Come on.
I want you to talk.
I don't know what
you want me to say.
Don't be a wise-ass.
Doc, we don't
need him.
We can do
whatever this is
without him.
You, hit
the bricks!
Hit the bricks!
Oh, come on.
Hit the bricks.
Hit the bricks,
you motherfucker.
Out of here!
It means "leave."
Let's go.
I'm Dr. Reno.
Cassie: Are you
a medical doctor?
No, he's a psychiatrist.
One of the best.
The meat-head knows this
from personal experience.
You're Anthony's sister?
Yeah.
This is really unusual.
He doesn't normally
rock like this.
That's because he's not
your usual autistic.
I should take him home.
No!
With all due respect,
I don't even know you.
Your brother is a savant!
Stop rubbing his fucking arm.
He's autistic.
He's not an idiot savant.
He's an autistic
savant!
( Spanish )
Calm down!
Just relax.
Shh.
Anthony understands Spanish
with feelings like
any other person.
We don't even
communicate
in Spanish.
He knows it
innately.
Grazie.
Rod carew, 1977 m.V.P.,
American league.
National league 1977
m.V.P., George foster.
Dr. Reno:
An autistic savant
is a person
who has
an exceptional skill.
...1977, when rod carew
won American league m.V.P.
About 10 percent of people
with autism are savants.
...303 batting average.
And the most common are
splinter skills.
This is
a person with a hobby--
maybe great at trivia
like m.V.P.S
and batting averages.
...16 at-bats.
And then there are
those very few
with prodigious
skills,
a person who can play
an entire Mozart concerto
on the piano after
hearing it only once.
Or a kid who has
fifth-degree
black belt abilities
because he saw
a Bruce Lee movie.
It's believed that
there are less than 25
autistic savants in the world
who hold prodigious skills,
and Anthony...
Is one of them.
Even more confounding,
it seems that
Anthony has two
savant skills.
The Spanish.
Yes.
Though it's clearly not
a prodigious skill because
he only seems to fully
relate to the language
when something
harshly negative
is said to him.
Probably a splinter skill.
But, doc, let me
ask you a question.
How did you figure out
the whole Spanish thing?
Can I take your main course?
What the fuck
is wrong with you?
Can't you see
we're talking here?
Get your ass
out of here.
So, how did
I figure it out?
I asked that punk Juan
how the fight started.
They cursed
at Anthony
in Spanish.
That's it?
You got it
from just that?
No, pencil-head.
I read that thick
file you gave me.
What the fuck's
the matter with you?
Almost every kid
he got into a fight with
had a Spanish
last name.
The one school
he went to had
a very small
hispanic population.
That's why he had
only one fight there.
But that St. Joe's was
chock-full of latinos.
Thus the 14 fights.
This isn't brain
surgery, huh?
So now we have
to get Anthony
to understand Spanish
in all different areas,
not only when
it gets him angry.
Dr. Reno, can you
continue to help US?
No.
Nick: "No"?
What do you mean, doc?
We really need you here.
No, no, no.
He needs practical help.
This isn't a...
A mind that can be
manipulated by
a psychiatrist.
You just needed
the right doctor to learn
what the real deal is.
And now you've got to
use that karate room
and the Spanish language
to hone those skills,
and I ain't
gonna be around
when you're calling him
a dick head in Spanish.
No way.
Where the hell
is the waiter?
I'm hungry!
Yeah, that's right.
I'm here at Anthony's
karate school.
Mixed martial arts,
judo, karate, whatever.
It's all
the same thing.
No, the cops didn't
bring me here again.
I came by myself because
I'm gonna kick this kid's ass.
All right, Anthony.
All right, all right.
It's time to
get going.
Come on.
Oh!
( Chuckles )
That was just luck.
I wasn't looking.
Well, I guess Felix
wasn't looking either.
Elizabeth, shut up.
You're talking a bunch of crap.
I know you were there.
I'm telling you, it was
just dumb luck.
Haven't you ever
seen me box?
I'm faster than
Mahatma Gandhi.
Well, that's what I mean.
Muhammad Ali.
And you've seen how many
pushups I can do.
I would've did more if it
wasn't for those stupid cops.
Anyway, I got to go, all right?
And you're gonna eat your words,
'cause I'm gonna
kick his ass.
Hi, Juan.
You know,
back in the day,
I could take
those punches and kicks
from that kid.
Better than
I ever could.
Oh, hell, no.
Not better
than you, Nick.
Not too long ago,
you were on your way
to being the best.
You let the killing
sidetrack you.
You know, doc,
some people are dead.
And deservedly so.
I have no regrets.
Yeah. I agree.
Think about this, Nick:
You became a cop,
not a professional
fighter.
Sidetracked you.
But I think now
you're back on track.
Help that kid.
Thanks, doc.
Good to see you.
God bless you, baby.
Stay well.
All right.
I'm out of here.
Arrivederci.
Cassie:
Ladies and gentlemen,
today, a message
needs to be sent,
a message
not only heard
in Los Angeles,
Washington D.C.
and New York City,
but also right here
in New Jersey--
a message to
the police department,
to the prosecutor's office
and to the public at large:
Stop the corruption.
Stop arresting
innocent people
and altogether
ruining their lives.
Stop the power abuse.
That's the beginning
of a closing argument.
( Students applauding )
Now, here's the important
message that I want to
tell all of you today:
I know that miss gause
told you yesterday
that my brother Anthony
has some very rare
and remarkable abilities,
but he needs some help
to use these abilities
in a good way.
He needs help
from me,
from officer tantino,
from miss gause
and other teachers here
at hawthorne high.
He also needs
your help.
Will you help him?
Anthony, I'll help you.
Miss gause:
All right. Everyone
clap if you'll help
your friend Anthony.
( All clapping )
Mr. Watson:
Come on, guys. Let's go.
I'll try to.
I'm in.
All right.
Juan, what about you?
Oh, come on,
miss gause.
Tell Anthony that
you'll be his friend,
in Spanish.
Miss gause...
All is
forgiven, Juan.
Please help.
Yo soy tu amigo.
Uno, dos,
ciento,
tres...
That's very close,
Elizabeth.
No, it's, um,
uno, dos, tres,
cuatro,
cinco...
Seis, siete,
ocho, nueve,
and diez.
Hey, Antonio,
Nick--
Nick and Anthony.
Nick and Anthony, win.
And that's it.
Basic wrestling move.
It's a good technique.
I want you to learn it.
Uh...
Okay? Yeah.
Try to follow, man.
You can do this.
Come on.
Level change,
drop the knee.
Penetrate, shoot in.
Take somebody
right to the mat.
Level change,
drop the knee,
penetrate,
shoot in!
Can you do it,
Anthony?
( Mouthing words )
Nick: Okay.
Uh, tell you what. Um...
Oh, yeah!
Oh, nice!
That's what
I'm talking about, kid.
Way to go.
Let's get it on.
Come on! Hup!
Get them hands up.
Ha! Ha! Ha!
Come on.
Whoa! Easy!
Aah! Easy.
That's it.
High five.
Come on.
Get that upper body.
"Music, art, mathematics,
and other skills,
"such as knowing the time
without seeing a clock
or committing a map
to memory are found
in autistic savants."
Come on. 21.
22. Get that
stomach hard.
Come on. 23.
"Aside from memory,
other factors
"that assist a savant
in honing their skills
"include the ability
to focus and concentrate,
"the desire to
practice endlessly,
"positive reinforcement
from family,
friends and teachers."
Watch out. Come on!
Defend it!
"In rare cases,
the person may be unusually
gifted in languages."
( Spanish )
Come on! Yeah!
Yeah! Ooh!
Ha! Get that
head down.
Ha! Good.
Ha! Move.
That a boy.
Anthony, write it
in Spanish.
"Every autistic brain
may have untapped
savant skills."
( Metal clanging rhythmically )
Get ready for the ass-kicking
of your life,
savant boy, in the cage.
What's the matter?
You don't have the guts to
say it to him in Spanish?
Amd that doesn't
even affect you?
Why should it?
Herbert hoover was the president
during the great depression.
Say it in Spanish.
Anthony, I just
don't understand.
Was that Felix, my student,
I just saw leave here?
Yes, and he was just
threatening my brother.
So this is Anthony.
Yes.
Look, I'm really
sorry about Felix.
I had a feeling
he was gonna
head down here.
I'm gonna straighten him out.
Thousand laps around the gym.
Sure, Zane.
Really.
All he needs is
a little bit
of charm school.
Of course. And you're
probably headmaster
of that school.
I am.
Go sit in the car.
Nice ride.
I think yours
might be a bit
more expensive.
I really think this
fight's gonna be great
for these two kids.
Teaches them discipline.
It's in a controlled
environment.
Nick says
the same thing.
Nick...
I really need
to talk to you
about Nick.
I don't think this
is an appropriate
conversation, Zane.
Anthony would be much
better off training
at my school.
Lawyer to lawyer?
Speak, Mr. Attorney.
Nick tantino's
not the man
you think he is.
Goodbye.
He killed someone,
Cassie.
In a fight, in cold blood.
Is that the type of man
you want training Anthony?
Prove it to me.
I will.
You bet
your sweet ass
I will.
Jill:
That was fantastic.
I'm so glad we got
together again...
After all this time.
You were on fire!
I guess fighting
keeps you strong.
Pass me the strawberries?
These past few months
have been so lonely.
If I'm telling the truth,
the past year, really.
I want another kiss.
You know, I could see US
rekindling those old
high-school flames.
Jill, I need you
to tell me something.
Something about Nick.
It'll really help me
with the divorce.
The more you help me,
the more I can help you.
The truth is,
he doesn't even
deserve this house.
He doesn't even
deserve half of it.
Okay?
Did I tell you
how beautiful you are?
Did I?
Hey.
Whatcha doin'?
Something I couldn't do
in the prosecutor's office.
Huh?
This isn't true.
It's Nick tantino's
international rap sheet.
This says he was charged
but not convicted
of murdering somebody
in Italy when he was 22.
This isn't real.
Does it matter?
He did kill somebody
in Italy. Who cares
if he was never charged?
This is in the international
criminal justice
computer system now
because I added it.
When he applied to be a cop,
there was no international
computer system.
So now it will
be discovered.
I want you to
give it to Cassie
tomorrow, okay?
Okay, Zane.
Thank you.
( No audible dialogue )
Nice work, Cassie.
Thank you.
See you at the office?
Nope.
I am going to
get a beer.
Okay.
Maybe two.
Hello, Sandra.
Always a pleasure,
Megan.
Cassie, I'd love
to speak to you.
That's funny, Megan,
'cause I wanted to speak
with you as well.
I'll bet my conversation's
more interesting than
your conversation.
I'm not so sure
about that.
Do you know Jill,
Nick's soon-to-be-
ex-wife?
Sure. Real bombshell.
Hard act to follow.
Mm-hmm. Yeah.
It seems that Jill
likes to videotape
herself with men--
a new hobby.
Yeah. And it also
seems that Zane
wanted to hear that
Nick was a murderer,
and when Jill told him
that that just wasn't
the case,
Zane didn't
like that very much,
so he cut her off.
Now Jill's
a wee bit upset.
Well, what you'll see
in this file is
also not true.
It's another
phony act from Zane.
Trenton's the capital
of New Jersey.
Trenton-- capital.
Paterson, passaic,
Camden, Jersey city--
come on, Anthony.
Fight back.
Big cities. Trenton.
At least block.
Trenton, the capital.
Paterson, passaic,
Camden, Jersey city--
let me try it.
Ah! Tap, tap!
Whoo-hoo! Yeah!
What was that?
Nick:
That was
a flying arm bar.
I've been training in
martial arts for a long time.
I could never master that move.
Wow.
He's doing so good.
I get energized
every time I work
with him.
His progress--
it's amazing.
I know. It's amazing.
He's on-again,
off-again, and...
I mean, I don't think
he'll ever be
totally cured,
but the improvements
are just unbelievable.
You know,
I wonder why he never
responded to Spanish before
unless it was something violent.
Yeah. I mean,
we never spoke it
at home.
We're completely
americanized.
I only know Spanish
from taking classes,
and Anthony never
learned it at school.
Kids rarely even
spoke to him.
I mean, they spoke
in front of him,
but I think...
I think there's
a big difference.
He was never
nurtured in Spanish.
You know,
what worries me
is that...
Felix knows that,
and he's not gonna be
cursing at him
on the night of the fight.
Do you know what
he just said to me?
He just said that you can
master that move if he
worked on it with you.
He did not say that.
He did say that.
Are you sure he said that?
I'm sure. I'm positive.
( Screams )
( Growls )
( Crowd cheering )
Announcer:
I'll tell you, Jack,
we've got a lot of excitement
in this place tonight.
Jack:
Richard winfield
is sheer muscle
with some serious
jiu jitsu skills.
These guys got energy
going. This is the way
to fight. Ooh!
What happened to
Henderson's boxing?
Winfield's punching
his lights out.
Cassie:
Yeah! Yes!
This is crazy!
This is an all-out
street brawl!
Unbelievable!
Look at this guy hit!
I tell you what.
If I got hit with
one of those,
I'd be in
the back row here.
I'm telling you!
Here we go. Round 2.
Mickey nettles tore Roy rivers
apart in the first one.
This guy's an incredible
grappler. He's got skills
in every area,
but it's on the mat
where he really shines.
What?
Oh, my goodness!
Man, he can really
rocket a punch.
This one's gonna be
a bloody finish.
And there we go.
Ladies and gentlemen,
what's a fight without
the flip at the end?
Well, I'll tell you, Jack,
we've got a lot of excitement
in this place tonight.
Now, I just
love this story.
Two 18-year-old
high schoolers--
Felix Sanchez,
who's already fought
and won in five
professional fights;
and Anthony Rodriguez,
an autistic savant,
who fights with
magic from within.
Cassie:
What are you doing?
Getting ready.
I'm getting ready
to fight.
Not Anthony?
No, not Anthony.
Why don't you sit
down for a minute?
Look, your brother's
got incredible talent,
but these prodigious
fighting skills only come out
when he's taunted in Spanish.
Felix knows that,
and I'm sure he's gonna
do everything he can
to speak to him
strictly in English.
Even if I'm on the sideline
yelling nasty things
to him in espanol,
it's too much
of a risk.
We'll continue to work out,
but I've found that training
has helped him so much mentally,
and that's so much more
important.
I don't want to see him
get in that cage and make
a spectacle of himself,
and I'm not gonna
let him get hurt.
I'm falling
in love with you.
I'm already in love.
So you're gonna
fight Felix instead?
No.
I'm gonna fight
Zane carroll.
Jack:
Oh!
Oh, my goodness!
( Bell rings )
Announcer #2:
And there it is.
Another fight
comes to an end.
The crowd is
on their feet.
The people got
their money's worth
tonight,
and we haven't even hit
the main event.
Jack:
Got to tell you, though,
Grady, this next one
is the one that
I've been waiting for.
It's time
to win, Nick.
Win, Nick.
Win.
Win. Win, Nick.
Ladies and gentlemen...
Jack: What's this?
They're saying
there's a change
in the fight line-up.
Nick tantino, the cop,
pulled rodriquez
at the last second.
Any reason why?
We don't know why.
But I tell you,
there's an awful lot
of animosity
between he
and Zane carroll,
the prosecutor.
Ring announcer:
In the red corner,
fighting out of
the spitfire academy
in hawthorne, New Jersey,
standing 6' 2"
and weighing 215 pounds,
Zane "the persecutor"
carroll!
Both senseis
are from the same
New Jersey town.
Neither has fought
professionally
in years,
but both were stars
on the rise.
And in
the blue corner,
also fighting out of
hawthorne, New Jersey,
representing
the hawthorne institute
of martial arts,
standing 6 feet
and weighing in
at 225 pounds,
Nick "the law man"
tantino!
Your referee,
samad Rafael.
All right, gentlemen.
You know exactly
what time it is.
I want a good,
clean fight.
You obey my commands
at all times.
Gentlemen,
tap gloves
and back up.
Are you ready?
Here we go.
Fight!
All right, punk!
Jack: Oh!
Nick tantino disrespected
right off the bat
by carroll.
Jack: I'll tell you,
this isn't a cop you want
to meet on the street.
Grady:
You got that right.
Straight right by Nick.
Ooh!
Yes!
Come on, Nick!
He's got to
switch it up here.
Aah!
That's a low blow to
the groin by Zane carroll.
He's in trouble.
Yeah, he's got him
in trouble now.
( Shouting in Spanish )
( Shouting continues )
( Bell rings )
Jack: Chalk one up
for the police, Grady.
I'll tell you what--
this one is o-v-a, "ova"!
Counselor just
got schooled.
Get off me!
Stay down,
sucker!
Come on, you.
Cover up.
Okay, okay, okay.
All right.
You got me.
It appears as if
you've succeeded
with the kid.
I think we'll take you
back on patrol.
Except I don't
want to retire.
Once a blue,
always a blue.
Don't retire
just yet.
That arm bar was lucky.
I'll fight you again
right now.
Hey. What do you say to
a prosecutor that just got
his ass kicked in a fight?
"You have the right
to remain silent.
You're under arrest."
For what?
How about
official misconduct
for initiating an
illegitimate law enforcement
investigation against Nick,
for tampering with
government computers
and creating
a false rap sheet?
None of this crap will
hold up in court.
You have the right
to an attorney.
You know that already.
If you can't afford
an attorney,
sell the Ferrari.
( Rhythmic whooshing )
( Pounding )
Nick:
Come on, let's go.
Come on. The crime
can't beat you.
Come on.
It's Zane carroll,
and he's beating you.
Nice.
Nick:
Want a soda?
No soda. No soda.
Cassie says no soda.
Anthony,
orange juice or water?
Milkshake.
I want a milkshake.
There you go.
You got your order.
Want a milkshake too?
No, I'll stick
with the water.
Anthony, do you
want to try the tire?
I'd better
tell you this
in English.
You're probably not
gonna totally get it,
which is okay,
but at least
I'll get it
off my chest.
You see, Zane was trying
to convince your sister
that I killed somebody.
A long time ago
in Italy,
I went to visit
my grandfather.
He wasn't paying
to the people he was
supposed to pay to,
so they sent some guys
over to his house to
straighten him out.
I saw what they were
doing, Anthony,
and I snapped,
you know?
Do you understand
what I'm telling you?
I will tell her.
Atta boy.
Come on.
Don't stop.
A little harder.
Come on!