(film reel rattling)
(upbeat jazz music)
(hip-hop music begins)
♪ Back at it again
♪ Was just with your broad
♪ We left in our heater then hopped in a Benz ♪
♪ Huh, felt like Lil' Uzi
♪ I ain't got no friends
♪ My life is a movie in real life ♪
♪ You a show on demand
(clicks tongue)
(pressing telephone buttons)
- Yo, you still out?
- Yeah.
- Yo, how long you gonna be gone?
- I just gotta make a run real quick.
I'll be right back.
- But it's Christmas Eve, Keys.
Yo, what the hell?
You bugging right now.
It's our daughter's first Christmas,
and you have the need to run the streets.
- Yo, why is it every time I gotta leave the house,
you gotta cause a problem?
These streets providing for your ass though, right?
(sucks teeth) You breathing hard, Kenya.
You got something you wanna get off your chest?
- It don't matter if I do or if I don't,
because Keys still gonna do
whatever the hell Keys wants to do.
- Look like I said, I'll be back.
- Mm hmm!
Your daughter's waiting for you.
(slams telephone) Fuck!
(funky hip-hop music)
(suspenseful music)
(banging on door)
(banging continues)
(door slams open)
(repeated gunshots)
(Kenya breathing heavily)
- So, your man Keys thought it was cool
to steal from me, huh?
Still got that fight in you, I see.
(Kenya spits)
(chuckles)
Still disrespectful, too.
(metal cane clanging)
(Kenya screaming)
Save your high seated head for Chop, bitch.
(intense music)
(suspenseful music)
(Keys panting)
- Fuck!
(knocking on door)
(knocking continues)
- I'm coming.
I'm coming.
(baby crying)
Jesus.
(choir harmonizing)
Baby,
I know it's tough out there.
Look at me.
It's time for you to come into your calling.
Baby, Are you listening to me?
Listen to me, baby.
You gotta hear me.
I cannot lose you.
I can't lose you.
I can't lose you, I can't.
- You right, mom.
I gotta do better.
If not for myself than for her.
♪ I'll take my crown now
♪ These voices in my head
♪ I'm telling you to bow down
♪ You don't got control, no
♪ So bow down
♪ I don't give you control, no
♪ Yeah
♪ I'll take my crown now
♪ These voices in my head
♪ I'm telling you to bow down
♪ You don't got control so bow down ♪
♪ I don't give you control, no
♪ So bow down
♪ Yeah
♪ Bow down
♪ You gotta tell 'em, man
♪ You gotta tell them to bow down ♪
♪ If you don't match up with the work ♪
♪ Then you gotta tell 'em to bow down ♪
♪ You gotta a crown now
♪ You gotta tell 'em to bow down ♪
♪ Yeah
♪ Voices in my head
♪ Telling me that I won't make it ♪
♪ But I like a challenge
♪ So I just keep going
♪ Trust in the Lord
♪ The more that I know
♪ The more I grow
♪ The more that I show the devil ♪
♪ That he's on the bottom of my soul ♪
♪ Yeah, he's on the bottom of my soul ♪
♪ The time is now and I ain't going nowhere ♪
♪ When fear comes and round I tell it ♪
♪ Bow down, down, down
♪ (singer harmonizing)
(gospel music playing)
♪ Oh
♪ I
♪ Know I've been changed
♪ I said that I
♪ Oh, I know I've been changed
♪ Good Lord
♪ I
♪ Know I've been changed
♪ You know the angels in heaven done ♪
♪ Signed my name
♪ Yeah Lord
♪ I
♪ Know that I've been changed
♪ I said that I
♪ Oh, I know I've been changed
♪ Good lord, I
♪ Know I've been changed
♪ You know the angels in heaven done ♪
♪ Signed
♪ They signed my name
♪ Oh yeah
♪ Oh
♪ Thank you Jesus - All right!
♪ Hallelujah
♪ Oh (singing) Yeah!
(congregation clapping)
- Thank you, Lord.
Thank you, Jesus. - [Women] You're so good!
- If you could turn with me
to the book of Genesis. - [Women] Uh huh.
- You know, I was in my study this morning
and I was praying and
I wanna talk to you on the subject of, uh,
from the pit to the palace.
- So brother, how was the three o'clock service?
- Hey pastor. - Oh, excuse me.
- Amazing service pastor. - Thank you.
- I just love you.
- Oh, I love you too, sister.
- Hey, deacon, how are you? (Pastor laughing)
- So wonderful to see you. - Hey, good to see you.
- Thank you so much, God bless you.
- God bless you.
God bless you. - God bless you.
- I had such a good time today.
- I, oh, good! Good, good, good.
Thank you.
Hey, you tell your mama, I said hi, all right?
- Okay, I will. - All right. Thank you.
(chuckling) - Thank you for coming.
- Thank you.
- All right.
Yeah, how was that?
- (speaking faintly) It was about 300 people in.
We, I'm sure we collected at least
uh,
about 10 grand.
- Hey, that's, all right, all right.
- Hey, pastor. - Hey, how you doing?
- Here's your water. - Oh, thank you.
- You're welcome.
You know,
that was a powerful word you talked today.
I know the angels in heaven are just rejoicing.
Mm
and God
is very well pleased.
- Well to God be the glory, sister.
- Yeah.
Glory to God.
Uh, pastor, is there anything else that I could do for you?
(women clearing throat)
- Pastor,
we need you to sign off on the count
for the deposit tomorrow.
- Thank you for the water, sister.
Is there anything else?
- Yeah, but um, I would like to talk to you in private.
- Well, uh, make an appointment,
just like everybody else.
You know, pastor's a busy man
and we can't make exceptions for just
anyone.
- Okay.
(Sister Brianna chuckles)
- I'll be so glad when Satan come to collect
this little minion
and get out pastor's face.
- It's the loose ones running up on the men of the church
with the Jezebel ways. - Mm hmm.
I just wish the pastor would put her out of God's house.
- And you know what I wish you would do.
- Mm? - Shave that mustache
above your top lip
or at least line it up
to where it met your goatee.
- You are dis respectful harlot.
- Right?
- There's a special place for people like you.
- Right, right.
Right up on the elder Allen. (chuckling)
Oh, and the next time you talk to him, let him know,
I need my money up friend, okay?
All right. (giggling)
- She need to be baptized.
- Hey, sister Brianna.
Have seen my daddy?
I don't know.
Ask sister Shaunie.
- [Together] Shaunie?
- Girl you lying.
- I can't stand her.
- Mm.
Stop.
- Why you let her get to you like that?
- Because Hosea,
it's like,
(scoffs)
everyone else can see what she's doing
and you don't stop it.
It's like she done sunk her acrylic nails into
every other man at this church.
And you keep letting her think she has a chance.
And until you stop that, she's gonna keep trying it.
- I have never,
never
given in to any of her advances.
The whole church knows who she is.
And they know they never seen me be anything
but professional with her.
♪ Who made this?
- And that better be all you ever are with her.
- That's right. (R&B music begins)
♪ Lay it down
♪ I'm a real one
♪ And I didn't come here to play around ♪
- That's right, that's right. (door knocking)
(record scratch) Sh.
Uh.
(clears throat)
Come in!
Hey, my baby girl. - Hey, daddy!
- Hey, Mila. (nervous laughter)
(Hosea sighs)
Hey. - How are you?
So finals are coming up soon and
me and Mila are gonna go to
her house to study.
- All right, all right.
You do that, do that.
You know, uh,
I just can't believe my one and only daughter is about to be
a college graduate.
- Yeah.
I can't believe it either.
You know, one semester left.
(Haven chuckling) - Yeah.
I know.
You just make sure you don't stay out too late, all right?
- No, of course not.
Love you daddy. - Mm hmm.
- See you later, Uncle Hosea. - [Hosea] Bye, Mila.
- Hm, that's pastor Reynolds.
- I wasn't talking to you.
And I said what I said. (heels clacking)
(R&B music)
- Hello?
(scoffs)
♪ Who made this?
- Now,
where were we?
♪ Lay it down
♪ I'm a real one and I didn't come her to play around ♪
♪ Scream my name
- [Mila] Ah. (cackling)
(tapping phone screen)
(Mila laughing)
- Girl, if you don't put that phone down so you don't fail.
- (sucks teeth) My head hurts. - (mockingly) My head hurts.
- And I'm starving.
You know, I can't work on an empty stomach.
Can we go get something to eat?
We've been studying for hours.
- No, me and Bree have been studying for hours.
You, however, have been doing God knows what on that phone.
- Probably all on TikTok.
- You know she is. (Mila scoffs)
- So y'all just gonna talk about me like
I'm not right here? - Yup.
- Girl, you know we don't beat around the bush.
- Yeah, whatever heifers.
Let's go.
- Where? - Oo!
- Tacos?
- I'ma have to catch up with y'all later.
Me and Spin finna go on a date.
- Oh. (trap music playing from car)
- [Haven] You know,
you love that boy. - Oh, he's here.
- Ah.
Well, bye.
- Must be nice.
- Right?
I'm trying to get like you, my boy.
(both laughing)
- So tacos? - Absolutely.
- Let's go.
- Hm?
- Yes.
Thank you.
- You know,
one of these days,
I'ma have to fight Shaunie old, gold diggin' ass.
- (laughing) Girl what is wrong with you
and where did that come from?
- I dunno, it just dropped in my spirit.
- Mm, sure dropped in your. (both laughing)
You know, but you're right though.
I can't stand her.
And what is she even doing at the church?
She used to go on somewhere.
- I bet your daddy know why she's still there.
- Uh-uh.
Where did that come from?
- Calm down.
I'm just saying,
you know, she been trying to get close to your daddy
so that she could be first lady.
Deacon Jones can see it and he's blind.
- That woman ain't even my daddy's type.
- And he definitely ain't hers.
- But what's that supposed to mean, though?
- Look, any woman would be lucky to have my daddy,
even Shaunie's little gold diffing self.
- I know!
I know your daddy's a good man.
Just not what she's used to.
- Mm-hmm.
- Remember how I told you how she doesn't say anything
when I be giving her hell every time I see her.
- Yes, but you never tell me why.
- Well, imagine this,
me and Keem booed up in the trap house
and then boom!
In comes the pastor's assistant trying to buy an eighth
and some percs.
Mm-hmm.
- Uh-uh, I know you lying.
- Mm, nope.
Why you think she don't be saying nothing to your daddy
when we give her hell?
Little honey ain't stupid.
She knows if she comes for either one of us,
I will crash her whole face.
- Mm mm, nothing's sinning up in the church.
Look at. - Mm-hmm.
- Hey, pull over real quick, pull over, pull over.
- Man. - You don't see that?
Shorty thick as fuck.
- Man, no. - What?
- We got to do.
- (sucks teeth) Man, it don't take that damn long, man.
Just pull over right quick.
Gonna take me about a few seconds.
- But you know what?
I ain't listen to Moontse's fine chocolate self today yet.
- Oh my God.
You seen that man one time.
(music playing on cellphone)
Oh! It's my song too, aye!
- Which one is it?
- Aye, here.
(music continues)
- Oh, and we. - Oh!
Yeah.
- Hey, shorty.
Let me holler at you.
- Mila!
- Girl, I'll be back.
- [Man In Car] What's good?
- Hey, daddy.
- How you doing, what's your name?
- Mila.
- Mm, Mila, beautiful name for a beautiful goddess.
(Mila giggles)
I'ma talk to her.
Yeah.
I'm saying, though, where y'all finna go?
I'm finna chop it up with you.
- [Mila] Probably go home.
We just got something to eat.
- Got something to eat, huh?
You ain't bring me none.
- Now why you standing over here looking all scared.
- I am not scared.
Just giving my girl a little privacy.
That's all.
- Oh, okay.
- Hmm.
- What you looking at?
- Where's the rest of it?
- The rest of what?
- Scripture?
- Oh, well that was the most powerful part to me.
I know God is with me
so that's no need to fear anything.
Everything guess it'll fall into place.
You know. - Hm.
What church you go to?
- (scoffs) Nah, shorty.
I don't get down like that.
Look, I believe in God or whatever, but that's about it.
But anyway, what's your name?
- Um,
it's Haven.
- Oo, Haven,
I like that.
(Haven chuckles) It's different.
Do that mean, I can find safe space in you?
(Haven scoffs) Right?
- What's your name?
- My people call me Trouble.
- Ha, I bet.
- But you can call me Asa.
- Hmm.
How old are you?
- Old enough.
- And what college you go to?
- Look, I don't really have time for school, beautiful.
I'm out here getting money.
You feel me?
- Yeah.
Um,
we gotta go.
I gotta study for a finals.
- All right, all right.
All right.
- Uh, Mila!
It's time to go.
- [Mila] Here I come, boo.
- I'm saying, though,
we just start chopping up, you finna slide already?
- (sucks teeth) I guess that just means
you're gonna have to use my number
so we can get together.
- That ain't no problem.
- (giggling) But I don't play about school, though.
I need this grade to graduate and you fine,
but you not fine enough for me to fail.
- I can respect that.
I'm saying, you going,
you gonna answer if I call?
- I'll see what I can do.
- Yeah, all right.
- Girl, slow down.
- I need you to take you to church
and put you on the alter for that lie you just told.
- What lie?
- About that boy being fine.
- (scoff) Don't do my new boo, okay.
You know he's a cutie
and did you see what he had on?
Little daddy had that drip so you know he got them coins.
Ah.
- He need to use them coins to get that face fixed.
- Uh!
- Lookin' like a donkey. - That's not funny.
(hip hop music) ♪ We can catch a vibe
♪ Pull up on me
- I ain't gonna hold you, bruh.
I'ma give shorty all my kids.
You hear me? - Man,
have Ina find out.
Watch, she gonna cut you like she did the last time.
- Ah, man.
All right. - Ha.
- Look, what Ina, don't no won't hurt her.
You heard me?
- All right.
- Mm.
Anyway.
What your old dude had want?
- Man, I don't even know.
Nigga call me talking about, we need to fall through.
Mother fucker hung up. (Fangaz takes sharp breath)
- Sound 'bout right.
Uh oh, look like stepmom here.
(laughing)
(Asa sucks teeth)
She fine as a mother fucker, boy.
- Stop saying shit like that, bruh.
- (laughing) Come on, let's go.
(R&B music begins)
♪ I wanna be the one that you call at 3 in the morning ♪
♪ Call my phone
♪ And I'm the one you laying on ♪
♪ I wanna be the one that you call at 3 in the morning ♪
- Fuck.
(Asa clears throat) God damn.
Nigga, either close my door
and let me finish what the fuck I'm doing.
Or have a seat and watch.
- For real, bruh?
- What?
He gave us a option.
- Man, let's get the fuck out.
Come on, Fangaz, bro.
- See.
You go first.
(sighs) I'ma let you have that, bro.
- Hell yeah.
God damn, uh huh.
Go deep, go deep go deep.
Oh! Sh, go deep, go deep, oh.
Suck that dick.
(rap music)
- Hey man,
Chinirika can station on OG with that mouth, dude.
- My nigga, shut fuck the up.
- What?
- I don't wanna hear that shit.
- I'm just being real, bro.
You can be real.
But she fine as a mother fucker thought, ain't?
Ain't she fine?
She fine ain't?
- Nah.
(blows raspberry)
You ain't got no taste. - Where the fuck my glasses?
- Your glasses fell off in the car.
(rap music playing from room)
- Trifflin' ass.
- Hm. Your daddy like it.
- His homeboy like it, too.
- Shut the. - What, bruh?
She like a sexy plum.
(imitates biting)
(somber piano music)
- I don't got all day.
- Me neither.
I'm here, so what's good?
Us sitting here all day
is taking away from all the business that we got to handle.
- (chuckles) Little nigga, don't get beside yourself.
You move when I allow you to.
Sit your ass down.
- I need you to find her.
(intense music)
- What you want with her?
- I need you to as close as you can
and get me some information.
- What kind of information?
- Nigga, why are you questioning me?
- You trying to send me on a wild goose chase
with no details.
So pops, again.
What kind of info?
- (scoffs) We'll discuss that later.
For now, I need you as close as you can
and get me my fuckin' information.
Now get the fuck out my office.
Go take care of my business, little nigga.
- Man, let's be out.
Come on bruh, before I act up on dude.
- Yup, yup.
- Act up one that, nigga!
(scoffs)
- For now.
For now.
- Mother fucker.
(trap music begins)
♪ Right back
♪ Get into it
♪ Sweat game, behind I'll lose it ♪
♪ I'm with Cage, Johnny hit like uzi ♪
♪ Bring your girl to the part, it's a movie ♪
♪ I winning that fight, we was losing ♪
♪ Ain't no eating, just pick out the sauce ♪
♪ I get high and I throw my lil' sauce ♪
♪ Cut a check and get go, the exhaust ♪
♪ They would go to you, you gotta lay with them ♪
♪ Wipe them up like clean up, don't play with him ♪
♪ Clean him up like the cleaner, it stay with him ♪
♪ If you can do, I can, man, I play with him ♪
♪ At the show we gone come through the back ♪
♪ Back to back, it's a wifi no fax ♪
♪ Get your G's up like you were fat ♪
♪ Nothing less, no act, run it back ♪
♪ Boom! ♪ She ain't have no emotion
♪ Run round the city counting paper, get into it ♪
♪ Put down on my jewelry
♪ Get ape in my city boy, you is a tourist ♪
♪ This a cat, no Pumas
♪ In the 607, I don't need no Uber ♪
♪ Living like something cooler
♪ Yeah, I lead a scat pack, can't talk to you losers ♪
(rap music playing muffled)
(Asa counting faintly)
- Boy, what the hell got you so googly eyed today.
- What?
Googly eye? Who?
- What? Who?
Nigga, you. - Watch out.
- Count up all this money. - Watch out.
- Showing up that fucked up as grill of yours.
- (mock laughing) You know my shit ain't fucked up.
Watch out.
- Yeah, a little bit.
- But you. - Who me?
What you, what? - We, what?
- We could talk about you teeth, though.
- Boy stop. (scoffs)
We low key got the same dentist.
- Nah, there ain't no way.
Ain't no way. (laughing)
- Just like my mother used to say
beauty is in the eye of the beholder.
- Didn't mom dukes have like cataracts.
- Hey, leave my mom alone, please.
- All right, you got it.
- All right? - You got it.
- I told you that in confidence.
- Yeah. (laughing)
- And what the hell that gotta do with anything, anyway?
- Nothing, man, look.
Nothing, man, you right.
You got everything straight, though.
We good?
- Oh yeah. Hell yeah.
Hell yeah.
Shit, all we gotta do is
drop the rest of the off at the other trap houses.
- Mm hmm.
- And then yeah, we gonna be super straight.
- Go on pack your shit up.
- Oh, yeah, will do.
- Money first.
Cocaine after, right?
- Yeah.
- For sure.
You gotta take some of these this time, man.
Last time, feel like mines was like way heavy than yours.
- That's a bet, that's a bet. - So yeah.
- And make sure you tell the Laron and them
I need all that up front. - Y'all talking about.
- I know last time we had - Yeah.
- A situation. - Yeah, yeah.
I got, I got you. - On the play.
- I got you, I got you. - All right.
- You know that nigga that,
that nigga Puerto Rican, man.
- I don't care about none of that.
- They be spicy.
- All right.
- [Asa] Shh.
Yo.
- Yo.
- What up, what up, what up? - My boys.
- What it do, what it do?
- Good, my g. - Y'all all right?
- Y'all sit tight.
We gonna get y'all right.
- Sup, nigga? - Sup, man?
- Okay, one, two.
- [Sleeze] Y'all boys straight?
- For sure.
- Yeah, everything, everything.
You take some to Laron.
All right?
Take some to Kobe. - [Man] All right.
- And drop the rest off to the warehouse.
- [Man] Say no more. - All right.
- Oh, and another thing, man.
Y'all niggas vacuum and
spray some air freshener or something.
This shit stink in here, man. - Fuck outta here, man.
- [Asa] Let's go. - I'm just saying, man.
- Man, shit, fuck wrong with these niggas?
Fuck we is, maids here?
God damn. (scoffs)
I got three bitches ready to go hard on a four way, though.
(hip hop music begins)
♪ Squad
♪ A1 feeling like a meal ticket ♪
♪ Look, aye, ho, I'm feeling like a meal ticket ♪
♪ Plus four
♪ Times eight
♪ And my shooter right here
♪ So get your mind straight
♪ And I came here to vibe
♪ Don't get your dime taken
♪ Don't be violating
♪ All that trouble making
♪ You gone turn to uh oh
♪ And that money got you up but you gone fumble ♪
♪ Don't get it twisted, I can hit you were it hurt ♪
♪ But I rather see you fall on your own face first ♪
♪ Here me out
♪ Foot on the gas
♪ I'm off a perc - [Hosea] Haven!
- Living room. (tapping laptop keyboard)
- Yeah, I'll be back in the morning.
All right, baby?
- Hold on, daddy.
You said that you would stay home this weekend
so we could spend time together.
- (groans) Ah, baby. - Ah.
- You are
right.
You're right.
I promise I'll make it up to you.
- Mm-hmm.
- I have to go do the Lord's work.
That's what I call to do.
- But daddy, your first ministry is at home
and you're hardly here.
- Ouch.
(Hosea chuckling) - [Haven] Ouch.
- Using my own teachings against me.
- [Haven] Hm.
- I guess you have been paying attention in church.
- Have I, now?
- Uh.
How about this?
After this weekend,
I'll take some time off
and the three of us can hang out.
- The three of us?
- Yeah, you, me, Shaunie.
- I'll pass.
- Come on now.
Why you gotta pass, baby?
- I'll pass you.
You go on to your ministry, dad.
I'll see, when you get back, safe travels.
Will you be back tomorrow or whenever?
It doesn't matter.
Love you.
- I love you too. - mm-hmm.
- Father, son.
Holy ghost. (both laughing)
All right.
Look when I get back, I'll take you shopping.
All right? - Mm-hmm.
- All right?
Praise the Lord.
- Hallelujah. - Hallelujah.
Let's go.
(slow melodic music)
(door knocking)
- [Haven] Coming!
- Hey, best friend! - Hey, girl!
(door knocking) (Asa speaking faintly)
- [Fangaz] It was you, bruh.
Should have left your ass in the car.
(door knocking repeatedly)
(knocking continues)
- Nice house.
- Girl, I can smell that chicken all the way out here.
- Uh-uh.
- What is this?
- What?
You too good to let a nigga up in your house?
- Aye, bruh, don't. - What?
- Don't do that.
- Listen little ugly.
It ain't got nothing to do with me
being better than anybody.
It's a simple fact that
my dad don't even play these type of games
and Mila,
you know what would happen if he came back here right now.
- Girl, that's not gonna happen.
The last thing your daddy gonna do is come back here
with Shaunie in the car. (Haven scoff)
- What do you mean with Shaunie in the car?
My daddy went to go do ministry.
- Ministry?
Is that what they callin' sneaky linkin' these days?
'Cause our show did see them get on I-75 on my way here.
- Yeah, we did.
- Okay, come on, y'all.
Hey, best friend. - Hm, best friend.
- Smell like chicken, mm.
- Hey, you. (smooth jazz music)
- Hey, you.
- Good to see you.
- It is.
- It's nice place you got.
- Thank you.
- After you.
(Haven sighs)
- The chicken. - Man, that shit
better be good, the way you keep
talking about it. - It is! I promise you.
- What is wrong with you?
- What?
- Why you bringing these strange men up in my house, Mila?
You know, we don't get down like that.
- [Mila] They're cool people.
- [Haven] Says who?
- I've been talking to Fangaz for weeks.
- So.
- He's cool and so is Trouble.
He asked about you the other day?
- No, he did not.
That man doesn't know much about me from
the conversation we had three weeks ago.
- He did too.
And judging by that smile you're trying to hide
I can tell you glad about it.
(Haven mocking Mila)
Mm-hmm.
- Oo. - Okay.
So y'all can take a seat at the island.
I didn't know that we were having extra company,
but there should be enough for everybody.
- Yeah.
- Ooh. - You know, you know.
- You not even like that, bro.
- Right? He's faking.
- [Mila] Don't to him.
- Bruh, stop playing me, bruh.
- I've been teaching him, okay?
- [Haven] Mm, I know a phony when I see one.
- A real gentleman.
Chivalry.
- Spell chivalry. (Haven laughing)
- [Haven] Spell it. Spell it!
- C-H-ilvery. (group laughing)
- Shut up.
- [Haven] I'm surprised you got the first two, right?
- Oh whatever. (girls laughing)
- Makes my life, I ain't gonna hold you.
- [Mila] Mm-hmm.
- You got some hot sauce, right?
- Yes. - [Fangaz] Okay, let's go.
- You don't see the color of my skin?
Of course we got hot sauce.
- [Asa] Say that. - Just checkin'.
Just checkin'.
(Haven laughing)
- You not even gonna need it.
- Oh, it's that good? - Mm-hmm.
- [Asa] Thank you.
- [Haven] Of course.
- Okay.
I just feel it. (plate hits countertop)
(Asa laughing)
- [Asa] God damn. - [Haven] You're welcome.
(Mila laughing)
- [Asa] I mean, she have to do all but.
(both laughing)
- Hold on, my man's can't show me up, like that.
- Show him how to do it right.
- Oh, now he trying to be a old gentleman.
- [Asa] Come on now, this regular.
- Y'all wanna be us, so bad. - [Asa] This regular.
- Oh, really? - I try.
- I promise you. (Mila laughing)
- It's missing something.
- Mm, okay.
- Shut up. - Hot sauce.
- Okay.
- [Mila] This chicken good.
- Okay. - Mm-hmm.
- [Fangaz] Need some hot sauce but.
(Asa laughing)
- You know, put little the mm. - A little something.
(Haven laughing)
- Stop doing that.
- Doing what?
- Pulling on your clothes.
- I'm not.
- You are.
Why you got that kiddie portion of food on your plate?
- I'm just not that hungry, that's all.
- I'm gonna break you out of that shell.
Sooner or later.
- Can I get some hot sauce or something?
What?
- Is it good?
Would you like something to drink too?
- Mm-hmm.
- It's all right, still waiting on hot sauce though.
(Mila laughing)
- You don't need it.
- Trouble, would you like something to drink?
- Water?
- I'm saying, though you,
see us all sitting out eating all this nice ass shit
and the only person that you gonna offer something to drink
is this fool?
- [Asa] Bruh.
For real?
- First of all, don't cuss in my house.
Secondly,
the reason why I didn't ask you
is because we don't have enough Proactive cocktail
to clean up that face of yours
from the inside and out so. (all laughing)
- [Asa] God damn.
- Okay.
I told you to stop coming from my boo like that.
- (chuckling) And now see that's why
she gonna be my baby mama.
Keep on taking up for me like that, girl.
Keep it up, keep it up, now.
- This guy.
- [Haven] I hope you were gonna get one from overseas, Mi.
- Get what from overseas?
- A baby.
Because you having one with that one right there
is not the move. (all laughing)
- [Asa] Pull up.
- (laughing) It's funny.
- Shut your fat ass up, bitch!
- Say, bruh.
- What?
- Now, you can't do that.
- What you not about to do
is come for that one right there.
- So you taking up her? - Yeah!
- All right.
- This right here is a lifetime bond.
You just got here.
You not about to come from my sister.
- All right.
- I'm gonna go. - Haven.
Bruh, you see that?
That's some foul shit, bruh.
- What, bruh?
- Call her a bitch in her house.
- You on her side, too?
- Definitely.
- Nigga, we were supposed to be boys, though.
(Mila sucks teeth) - We boys.
We are boys but that's why I can tell you why you wrong.
That shit a foul, bruh.
- Let me go check on her.
- Nah, let me.
- Second door to the left.
- Captain save a, hmm.
- [Asa] Get your mans. - Shut up.
- We gonna talk. - Why don't you say that?
- Because she ain't gimme no hot sauce and I'm still upset.
What?
- I wanna see you. (lofi music)
(Haven faintly praying through tears)
God, let me know that you're here.
(crying)
- Hey, hey.
Hey, hey, shh.
Come here, shh.
It's okay.
It's okay, it's okay.
Relax.
(breathing heavily) (Asa shushing)
(whispering faintly)
Come on, breathe with me, breathe with me.
Breathe with me.
(both taking deep breathes)
Come on.
He, he gonna be him.
He ain't mean it.
He didn't mean it.
- Yes he did.
- No, he didn't.
Look, no he didn't. - Yes he did.
He didn't.
He didn't, I promise.
Now you may now see it right now but
you gonna get over this.
Fangaz ain't mean that stuff he was saying.
You just crushed his little manhood.
(Haven laughing) That's it.
About his future child and (chuckling)
that sh,
I mean, that stuff was low key funny.
(both laughing)
- Right? - Just a little bit.
- Yeah.
Just relax.
Don't worry about him.
What are um,
what are those?
- Uh, my writings on the wall?
- Yeah.
- Um, those are my prayer requests.
- That's like that lady from the movie
where she sat in closet the whole time.
She actually told him how to pray.
- War Room? - War Room.
(Haven laughing)
That's it.
And my grandma, she took me to it
as soon as it came out.
I didn't, I didn't want to go
but
she wasn't having that.
- Sounds like she don't play.
Not even the radio. (Haven laughing)
- You gone see.
- Mm.
I wish I had someone to spend time with me like that.
You're lucky.
- I mean, from the pictures on the hall look like
you had a pretty good life to me.
- Oh.
Material things don't move me.
My dad spends all his time to the church and everyone else.
He doesn't really have much time for me.
Those material things,
they don't move me.
He uses those to fill the void.
I guess.
- Where you're old lady?
- Huh?
- Your mom.
Where your mom?
- Oh uh,
yeah.
She died when I was three.
- I'm sorry to hear that.
- Yeah.
What about yours?
- She died house two.
Oh.
I'm sorry to hear that.
(sighs) I guess we have more in common than we thought.
- Yeah, let's get me at this war room
(both laughing) (cell phone ringing)
before I turn it to one of them ladies
(Haven laughing) from the movie.
(cellphone ringing) - Oh shoot, um.
My dad's calling.
Okay so if I don't answer, he's gonna send
Mrs. Easley from the church to come check on me.
- Okay, I'll give a little privacy.
- No, no, no, stay. (cellphone ringing)
- All right.
- Hello?
And before you ask daddy, yes I'm okay.
- [Shaunie] Did you tell her yet?
- [Hosea] (sighs) Not yet. - Hello?
- [Shaunie] Well, you better hurry up.
- Daddy. - [Shaunie] We don't have long
and I refuse to walk down this aisle with a big stomach.
- [Hosea] Yeah, yeah, well, um.
- [Shaunie] I'm not bringing this baby
into this world, unmarried, Hosea.
(Asa clears throat) - [Hosea] Baby.
I got you.
(phone beeps)
- Haven.
You okay?
Haven.
You all right?
(door knocking)
- Yo.
Yo, Haven.
Haven.
Yo, real quick uh,
I just wanted to apologize about earlier.
That was my fault, for real, for real.
- (scoffs) It's fine.
You're good.
Uh, Mila, do you have any of that famous juice of yours?
- Uh, are you sure?
'Cause you know my drink is strong.
- Yes or no?
- [Mila] Okay.
You good? (sucks teeth)
- Haven.
(gulping)
(Haven coughing) - God damn.
- Haven.
- Ah, slow down girl before you end up flat on your ass.
- (gasping) Jesus.
- Uh-uh, don't call on him now.
It's too late for all that. - Yeah,
why trying to kill yourself,
trying to hang with us?
- Maybe they hang with me.
- Mm. - [Haven] Mm.
- Mm, now's it's party of y'all.
I got these edible too.
- Mm, that. - Okay.
- All of that. - Y'all want in?
- Yeah, definitely. - Yes.
- Make sure y'all leave me a little piece of that.
- I won't. (Mila laughing)
- This is your apology.
- That right? - [Haven] Thank you.
- Shit, they doing their own thing,
might as well do our own thing.
- Mm.
- Slow down.
(hip hop music begins)
♪ I know you think that
♪ I shouldn't still love you
♪ Or tell you that
♪ But if I didn't say it
♪ Would I still have felt it?
♪ And where's the sense in that? ♪
♪ Swept me off my feet
♪ Lighter than a feather
♪ Haters hated on us, they ain't wanna see us together ♪
♪ Know they really wishing that our ties could be severed ♪
♪ But this feeling that I'm feeling ♪
♪ It was feeling like forever
♪ Ah
- Shea!
What the fuck you doing in my house, man?
Unannounced, at that.
- Little nigga, it's my money to pay for this house
and everything up in this mother fucker.
So I can come and go as I got damn please.
- Hey, why you here?
Huh?
- Trouble, don't fuck this up tonight.
- Hey, what's up with you too, huh?
Like I don't do this shit.
Hey, stop.
Stop playing with me, Shea.
- Yeah, alright. - Yeah.
- 'Cause you know what happened to your ass if you don't.
- What?
Lock my fuckin' door when y'all leave, man.
I'm out!
- Fangaz.
Remember, there's an open spot right next to me.
'Cause we all know that little nigga,
he ain't built for this shit.
Once everything done, you know what to do with him.
- Already.
- Dig it.
(R&B music)
♪ If it feels right
♪ Then do it
♪ Only if it feels right
♪ You can trust me, I won't let you go ♪
♪ If it feels right
♪ Then do it
♪ Only if it feels right
♪ You can trust me, I won't let you go ♪
- I got you ♪ I can take this thing
♪ Slow tonight
♪ And we know what we came for
♪ It's just me and you
♪ You know that it's true
♪ If it feels right
♪ Then do it
♪ Only if it feels right
♪ Your can trust me, I won't let you go ♪
♪ If it feels right
♪ Then do it
♪ Only if it feels right
♪ You can trust me, I won't let you go ♪
- [Haven] (voice over) God.
I know I've disappointed you with some of my actions and
there are no excuses.
I just pray that you will forgive me.
I don't know why Asa was brought into my life,
but I am so thankful for him.
- [Asa] (voice over) There are so many things about him
that I don't know, but you do.
The trials and tribulations
only come to make him stronger.
Touch his heart God so that
he knows he's more than a conquerer.
You creating him for your glory.
And as young as we are,
I can still see the calling that you have over his life.
Allow him to see it and walk in it.
- [Haven] I find your strength in him.
I find your peace in him.
I feel your love through him.
Allow me to live up to the meaning of my name so that
I can be his safe place and that he might find you in me.
- [Together] Whatever your will for our lives are
I thank you in advance.
Amen.
(trap music playing)
- Aye, my boy, look, bruh.
I'm telling you, once I come through the Chop,
big dog ain't gonna have no other choice
but to put me in my rightful position right next to him.
- [Sleeze] Man, what make you think
Chop gonna put you in front of his son, though?
- What? Boy, what you mean?
Playing with me, bruh.
Asa is not about that life, bruh.
I'm telling you, I promise.
- Look to me like, bro, been holdin' his own though.
- Man, stop.
If it wasn't for me,
that nigga would have never ran into
that fat ass bitch to begin with bruh.
Done fucked around and fell in love.
- But why she so important to Chop, though?
- Ah, let me tell you,
Chop and shorty dad,
they used to be like best friends back in the day.
I think he was by the name of like, uh,
like, Keys?
Yeah, it was Keys.
So look keys was around hittin' stash houses,
fuck around the stash house that he hit,
was Chops!
- Get the fuck outta here. - Bruh!
- I know you lying, nigga.
- Bruh, I can't lie to you bruh.
- You can.
And you doing it now.
I'm not.
I promise you, I'm not. - Hmm.
- So then right.
Look, bruh.
When Chop found out he returned the favor.
Hit one of Keys spots
but keys wasn't even there.
- Nah, that's wild.
Where the boy Keys at now?
- Bruh, that nigga is a pastor.
- Get the fuck outta here. - A pastor, bruh!
- Nah, I know you lying now.
- Nigga, I'm not lying.
That was like fuckin' smart as fuck, bruh.
Hell, Chop killed Trouble mama.
- [Sleeze] What?! - [Fangaz] Yeah.
- Nah, nigga, I know you lying.
They said shorty got killed at a, a store
or some shit like that.
- And she did.
Chop sent the hit.
- [Sleeze] Damn.
- So apparently I guess shorty was trying to like
skip town with her and Trouble.
Went down south, Chop finds out.
Sent his niggas to go handle that.
- [Sleeze] Shit. - Yeah.
Yeah.
- [Sleeze] But how,
how they knew where she was, though?
- Chinirika.
Chinirika was Trouble's mama's best friend.
She told him everything, bruh.
- That's crazy as fuck. - I know, bruh.
- What the fuck? - [Fangaz] Yeah.
- Yo, you straight?
- Yeah.
I'm good. - All right.
- I'm just think about tonight.
- All right, bro, so uh,
you know we gotta be on our shit tonight, right?
- Bruh, don't start that shit.
- I'm just saying, bro.
- Man, chill.
Don't start that shit.
I told Shea.
Damn. - All I'm saying is, bro
we can't afford no slip ups. - I got it.
- All right.
Shit, if you ready then let's be out.
♪ See, had a dollar and dream
♪ Nigga moved to Atlanta
♪ Been grindin' all my life
♪ Trying to sit up in that Phantom ♪
♪ Came from the mud and now I'm so clean ♪
- [Asa] Man, I hope there ain't a lot of people here.
- [Fangaz] It's a church, bruh.
- Hey, you know, you need to put
your good boy act on, right?
- Yeah, whatever.
Miss me with all that.
I'ma do what I'm supposed to do.
Just make sure you do what you're supposed to.
- (scoffs) All right.
You ready? - Yeah.
- I'm glad you took them goofy ass shades off.
In the house of the Lord. (both chuckling)
- And it's my favorite scripture in the bible
because he went through great test.
- [Women] That's right. - But he kept the faith.
- [Women] Amen.
- The race is not given to the swift nor the mighty.
- Mm.
- But to those who endure to end.
- Glory to god. - Amen.
- [All] Amen. - Amen.
I will see you next week.
I love you.
Love on somebody on your way out, all right?
(indistinct group chatter)
- [Mila] Bye.
- [Haven] Oh, my God, it's time, okay, okay.
- Stop fidgeting, you look amazing.
- Okay. - You look amazing
and Trouble's gonna love it. - [Haven] You think so?
- [Mila] Yes.
- [Haven] All right, let's go, let's go.
(Haven clears throat)
- [Asa] What's up, gorgeous.
- [Fangaz] Hey, beautiful.
- Hey handsome.
- I love this look on you.
- Thank you, yeah, you know, um
Mila's starting to do her little hair braiding thing
and now I'm her walking guinea pig.
(both laughing)
But, uh, I kind of like it.
- Yeah, it's fire.
It's fire but that's not what I mean.
- What do you mean?
- I love this look of confidence on you.
- How come you don't ever say nothing like that to me?
- (sucks teeth) First of all, baby,
that's corny.
All right, baby, I'm a big gangster.
Big gangster.
- You get on my nerves
so bad. - The biggest gangster.
I'm the biggest gangster.
Yeah, he'll tell you.
He can vouch for that, yeah.
For real.
- [Mila] You get on my nerves so bad.
(Haven giggling) - This guy.
- Are you ready? - Yeah.
- Are you sure?
- (sucks teeth) Yes.
Okay, just.
Okay. (Haven giggling)
Daddy.
- Hey baby.
- Hey, thank you.
- (chuckling) Who's this?
- Okay, um, daddy.
This is Asa. - Mm.
- Asa, this is my dad,
Pastor Reynolds.
- Nice to meet you young, man.
- Nice to meet you, sir. - Mm-hmm.
- So, uh, you go to school with the girls.
- I do.
Um, we actually take a few classes together.
(Shaunie clears throat)
- Excuse me, sorry.
My throat is dry.
I'm gonna go get some water, I'll be right back.
- So, uh,
how's your grades, Asa?
- Daddy, you don't have to do that right now.
- It's cool, beautiful.
It's cool, I don't mind answering his questions.
I mean, if it was my only daughter
bringing me some guy I never met before,
I'd probably be the same way.
But to answer your question, sir,
I've been an honor student since the ninth grade,
before then I was a little rebellious acting out.
'Cause I missed my mom, - Mm hmm.
- But my granna sat me down and explained to me
how important school was.
- Hmm.
- Ever since then
got it together.
- (chuckling) That's nice.
Nice. I like that.
We're gonna have to have you over to the house for dinner.
Me and you can talk. - [Asa] Yeah.
- Get to know each other a little bit more.
- Yeah. - Yeah, I like that.
- Well, I ain't gonna keep you, baby girl.
I know you got to go do your thing.
- Yeah. - All right.
You don't try to stay out too late.
- I won't, we'll be home on time.
- Mm-hmm.
- Nice to meet you.
- Same.
- Asa.
- Pastor Reynolds. - Hmm.
- See you later, daddy.
- All right, baby.
- All right, all right, preach.
- Yeah. (Haven laughing)
- [Haven] That kind of went okay.
- [Asa] It was good. - [Haven] Slightly.
You know. - [Asa] It was good.
(indistinct group chatter)
- Oh.
- Yo, why you leave like that?
- Oh baby, I told you I was thirsty.
I had to go get a drink of water.
My mouth was dry.
You would've heard me
if you were listening to me and instead of Haven.
- Don't start with that.
You know when my daughter is concerned, it's about her.
- (scoffs) Yeah. - All right.
- Yeah, you right.
- But what about when this baby gets here? Hm?
Is this baby gonna get that same treatment?
Hm? And does, does Haven even know?
- When this baby gets here,
I'm going to treat her the same way.
- Mm-hmm, you better.
'Cause one thing I won't have
is my baby feeling inferior to Haven.
You don't have to worry about that.
- Uh-huh, okay.
It's not the right time.
No, no, when you're gonna tell her?
You gonna wait 'til I'm pushing or something?
- I got it, baby, okay?
I promise you, I'm gonna tell her.
- Okay.
- Who was that on the phone, when I came in?
- Oh, nobody.
It was a wrong number or something.
- Yeah?
- Mm-hmm, yeah. - Okay.
(R&B music begin)
Well, let's get this done.
So I can get you home
to get you something to get rid of that attitude.
- (scoffs) Why we gotta wait 'til we get home?
(secret door opening)
(mischievous music)
- I'ma have pastor singing in tongues tonight.
Who me?
Yeah.
(tense music)
(Hosea and Shaunie moaning)
(trashcan tumbles)
- Oh, God.
(keys hit ground) Get it together.
Get it together.
(gunshot)
(hip hop music) (indistinct party chatter)
(car horn honk)
- Okay, it's lit!
- Damn, girl, it's about time y'all pulled up!
- Girl, you know uncle Hosea was not about
to let Haven go nowhere without him meeting Asa.
- I'm saying, though, who the fuck is Asa?
- This nigga, old bubble gum name having.
- Man, watch out, you know my mama
named me after my grandfather.
- (mockingly) You know
my mama named me after my grandfather.
(all laughing)
- Y'all boys straight?
Y'all got some more gas, right?
All right.
Oh, shit, I know this person right here.
(party music drowns out conversation)
- Okay, okay.
- Oh, shit.
Come on, man.
What's up, nigga?
♪ Everywhere we go, I wanna make you feel like you brand new ♪
♪ All I care about is money and women ♪
♪ Lord forgive him
♪ We gonna take a trip out to Montego Bay ♪
♪ She got big thighs
♪ She throw it back and out like cocaine ♪
♪ I'ma hit it like a Dodge but I won't ram it like a train ♪
♪ We go through ups and downs
♪ But at the end you know that's just a phase ♪
♪ Up down, side to side
♪ Let me show you love tonight
♪ Let me show you love
♪ No it ain't about the money
♪ Its about what you feel
♪ Tell me what I gotta feel just to make sure that it's real ♪
♪ Wasn't acting like myself
♪ They said bro, you gotta chill ♪
♪ People dying everyday, we don't want you to get killed ♪
♪ Baby can we go?
♪ I don't wanna make you feel like you brand new ♪
♪ All I care about is money and women ♪
♪ Lord forgive him
- Is this not your scene?
You don't usually come to parties like these?
- Yeah, just.
- Mi! - What's going on?
- You always coming through the drink.
- You know I'm.
(indistinct group chatter)
It's my fault! (all laughing)
- I'll get you in a minute.
Is this for me?
- No. (Mila giggling)
- What's wrong?
- I'm good.
- (sighs) I know we haven't been together that long,
but I can tell when something's wrong with you.
Can we go somewhere and talk real fast?
- Yeah, um, that'll be perfect.
I have to tell you something, too.
- All right, come on.
♪ I'ma make 'em call me big papi ♪
♪ David Ortiz
♪ Lookin' like my future baby mama ♪
♪ Yeah, she gettin' money and she smokin' za-za ♪
- (deep exhale) It's really crowded out here.
- Yeah, it is. Lets.
Let's hurry up then.
- Oh, okay.
Uh, what do you gotta tell me?
- You first?
- Okay.
(chuckles) Um.
Okay, um. - You good?
- Yeah, uh.
- I'm pregnant. - What?!
- How do you know?
- Okay, so I was feeling weird and,
and Mila was like, let me go get the test and I took it.
- Damn!
(intense music)
Fuck!
Look, Haven, listen to me!
Look, I need to listen to everything
I'm about to tell you.
Haven! - Yeah.
- I need to listen to everything I'm about to tell you.
(repeated gunshots) (crowd screaming)
- Haven, look at me!
We gotta get the fuck outta here.
Okay? (woman screaming)
- Get off me!
What is going on?!
Please get off me!
Get off me, what is going on here?!
- [Kidnapper] Ah, shut the fuck up!
(all shouting)
(Haven panting)
- Fuck.
Oh my god, Mila.
Breathe, shit.
Okay, I hope everything's all right.
(suspenseful music)
(Asa panting)
- Yo, what the was that?!
Huh? We had a plan!
- Look, bruh.
Your man felt like you was taking too long
to do what he needed to be done so he said his own plan
in motion, you feel me?
- I told y'all niggas I had it covered?
- So why you ain't grab her then, huh?
Why you ain't grab her?
Why you ain't do what we needed to be done.
You feel me?
- Who the fuck are you taking orders from,
me or Chop?
- Whatever, bruh.
- You take orders from me, nigga!
- Look like not one of y'all boys
know what the fuck y'all doing.
- Man, get your ass out.
- Whatever, bruh.
(kidnapped girl screaming)
(cocks pistol) - Shut the fuck up.
(girl's screams muffled)
- [Kidnapped Girl] (muffed) No! No!
No!
(gunshot)
- What the hell happened?
Answer the mother fuckin' question!
- Look, man,
when Sleeze and 'em started shooting outside,
I went ahead and put the bag on shorty head
and got up out of there.
How the fuck I was supposed know them school niggas
was gonna start busting back?
They ain't supposed to have guns on campus.
- Where was you at?
- In the bathroom.
Draining my balls.
I saw Fangaz running, shit, I started running behind him.
I guess they grabbed old girl,
'cause she had the same hairstyle.
Same shirt.
So here we are.
- Here we are.
(gunshot)
Where your grand mama at?
- Man, hell if I know.
- Give your god damn phone.
- I ain't talked to the lady in years.
- I said gimme your God damn phone, little nigga.
Camo.
- We gone spare his ass for now.
- [Shea] Don't say shit!
- Let's ride.
- Make sure you find that little bitch
and have somebody follow Trouble.
I know he know where his grandma at
and he gonna lead us straight to her.
Once you find everybody
take all their asses out,
including that nigga Trouble.
- Gotcha boss.
- Don't fuck this shit up, Camo.
If you do, you might as well
kiss that fine ass wife of yours
and them snot nose kids, goodbye.
Last time you see them,
is when the funeral director dropping their in the ground,
you dig?
(police sirens) (church organ playing)
(dial tone)
- Come on, baby girl.
Haven, pick up the phone.
- [Automated System] You have reached the voicemail box of.
(dial tone)
- Damn it!
- Excuse me, pastor, pastor, the family's already arrived.
- Ah, I'll be in there in a minute.
- Listen, wherever your daughter is,
I'm sure she's okay.
My wife Edna and I
have been praying for her return fervently every night.
- I thank you, deacon.
- Absolutely.
- Lord knows, I need all the prayers I can get.
- Yes we do.
- If anything ever happened to my baby.
- Listen, listen,
we not even gonna think like that.
Okay?
You know, God is gonna return her to us safely.
The girls covered in the blood of Jesus.
- Amen.
- Amen. - Amen.
(church organs playing)
(sharp exhale)
(dial tone)
Baby.
Pick up the phone.
- [Automated System] You have reached the voicemail box of.
(church organs continue)
- Sister Brianna was a
sweet and wonderful soul - [Women] yes, she was.
- And she dedicated her life
diligently to loving and serving
God with all her heart. - [Woman] Yes, she did, amen.
- [Women 2] Glory! Glory.
- I'm sure now that the angels are in heaven,
rejoicing for her home going.
(congregation praising)
Ah, she will be missed.
(clears throat)
At this time,
we would like to open the floor for the friends and family,
if they would like to say a few words
about the dearly departed,
but we ask that you keep it brief.
- [Women] Amen.
- For we all love Sister Brianna,
and want to love and share in her memory.
- [Women] Amen.
(soft crying)
- [Detective] Hosea Reynolds.
- Yes, I'm pastor
Hosea Reynolds
and we are in the middle of a home going service.
- This is my daughter's funeral officer, please.
- And I'm sure that the friends and family of a
miss Brianna Stevens would like to grieve their loved one
in peace. - [Man] Right.
(indistinct group chatter)
- Yes.
- You mean the loved one that you murdered?
- [Man] Oh, murder? - No.
No, pastor, that can't be true (indistinct group chatter)
- Oh no, no, no, this a misunderstanding.
I just don't.
I have, I, (faint chatter continues)
I have this, mama.
I'm sorry.
I, I do not know what you're talking about.
We already have a full confession
from a miss
Chinirika Stanberry.
- I'm sorry, officer.
- Detective.
I do not know a miss Chinirika Stanberry.
- Oh, that's right.
Just like these good unsuspecting people
don't know you as the infamous Keys.
- [Women] Oo!
- One of the drug Lords on the east coast.
- [Brianna's mother] What?! - [Women 2] Oh, no, no, no.
- [Women 3] Okay. - No.
This is a misunderstanding. (group chatter rises)
This is a misunderstanding.
What are you doing here?
Coming up here.
David, look. (women shouting)
- [Brianna's Mother] Oh, my god!
What are you, no! (group shouting)
What are you doing?
That's my daughter's casket.
What are you doing?!
Oh, my god!
- [All] Oh!
- Woo, hell is might hot!
Using the name of the Lord,
in his house for this foolishness!
You better pray and you better pray hard.
(shouting continues) The streets say God forgives.
They don't.
- [Brianna's Mother] They're framing him.
- Officer, officer,
again, who is a miss Chinirika Stanberry?
- [Shaunie] That would be me.
- [Asa] Trifflin' ass. - [Fangaz] Mm.
- Your daddy like it.
- [Women] Oh God.
- You no good-- - Oh pastor,
I know you weren't about to curse in church.
- [Woman] Oo! - [Bri's Mother] Oh, my god.
- [Detective] You have the right to remain silent.
- [Bri's Mother] Look Officer.
- Anything you say - Pastor.
- It's a misunderstanding.
- Can and will be used against used
against you - No officer, please.
- In the court of law. - It's a misunderstanding.
- Pastor, please.
Pastor, you didn't kill.
You didn't do anything to my baby?
- Get your hands off him!
- It's all right. (all shouting)
It's just a misunderstanding.
It's okay. (shouting continues)
- What have you done?! - He ain't done nothing
to nobody. - Oh my God.
- He ain't done nothing to nobody!
- Ye,
though I walk through the valley of the shadow of death
I will fear no evil.
For you are with me.
Your rod and your staff, they comfort me.
You prepare a table before me in the presence of my enemies.
(gospel music)
You anoint my head with oil and my cup runs over.
Surely goodness and mercy shall follow me
all of the days of my life
and I will dwell in the house with the Lord forever.
♪ Keep trusting (door knocking)
♪ And believing - [Granna] Sweetie it's me.
Can I come in?
- Yes. Ma'am.
- How you feeling baby?
- Not so well, granna.
(sighs)
I just don't know what to do.
- I understand.
I do.
But you know, we gonna have to trust God
in all this here mess.
I'm just
grateful
that you and that precious little one was spared that night.
We both know it could have been much worse.
- Yeah, I guess you're right.
- Have you heard from Asa?
- No ma'am and they gave me strict instructions
not to call him.
I know that the good Lord is tired of me
calling out that boy's name before him.
- You and me both.
- Well, that's enough of that.
Come on, get you some of this here food I done cooked.
You gotta eat.
You got to feed my great grand baby.
- I never turned down a meal. (both laughing)
- Oh baby, I can't wait for you to see
what I done cooked, girl.
- Mm, it sure smells good.
- (laughing) Sit on down, let me make you a plate.
- Oh no, granna, I can make it myself.
Oh,
okay.
- Sassing me.
You gonna get my great-granddaughter all upset.
- Uh-uh, granna, how you know it's a girl?
- Oh, granna got a perfect record.
I ain't never been wrong yet.
- [Haven] Oh really? (both laughing)
- (gasps) Granna. - Mm-hm.
- Is that Jamaican food? - Mm-hmm.
- Oh my God!
You know I love you me some Jamaican food.
- I do know that baby.
You know, Asa, told me everything.
- Did he?
- Yes, ma'am.
- [Haven] Okay.
Mm,
the plantains.
- Yes, ma'am. (Haven laughing)
- Here you go, sugar.
- Thank you. - You're welcome, baby.
- Granna, if you keep feeding me like this,
I'ma be showing before it's time.
- Well, we gonna take our plates
and go on in the living room and eat.
I got to catch up on my stories, baby.
- What we finna watch, granna?
The Young and the Restless?
Oh, The Bold and the Beautiful.
- Oh no, no honey.
That for folks.
Granna gotta catch up on her Love & Hip Hop.
- I know you lying. (both laughing)
- That Stevie J.
I love me some Stevie J.
They need to bring that boy on back.
- Let me find out you trying to be a cougar, though.
- Let me tell you something, sugar.
If that boy ever run across my path, honey,
I'll make him forget about that
so-called Puerto Rican princess,
Molly The Maid and his dang wife.
What her name?
- What's her name? - Faith.
- Mm-hm. - Sure will.
- Mm, it doesn't even matter. (both laughing)
(dramatic piano music)
- [Guard] Reynolds,
your lawyers here.
(indistinct chatter from inmates)
You know the routine.
Open cell five!
(cell buzzes)
- Got 10 minutes.
Make it quick.
My nigga.
That orange look good on you, home boy.
Think you might have found your color.
(chuckling)
- What the fuck are you doing here?
- Since you pastor and all,
figure I come and confess my sins.
(intense music)
I don't have time for this shit, man.
- Nigga, you got all the time in the world.
- [Hosea] Get out.
- You know what?
You was smart as fuck,
setting up shop at church.
God damn, I wish I would've thought of that shit.
Especially after you uh,
ran like a little bitch
after what happened with your baby mama.
And I never took you for a family guy either.
But you did a good job
raising that beautiful daughter of yours.
As fine as her, mama.
(chairs and table rustling)
Get the fuck off me, nigga.
- Stay the fuck away from my daughter, nigga!
- Fuck you nigga, fuck your daughter!
You think I was gonna let you steal my shit
and let it ride, home boy?
Fuck that shit, nigga.
You know how this street go.
- You still that same bitch ass nigga
from way back when. - [Chop] Yeah.
- I'll see you in hell, O'Shea.
- I'll see you in hell. - Hand of the father
shall be laid upon the child, nigga!
Yeah.
I'll have my son, Asa...
- Daddy, this is Asa.
- give Haven your regards.
- (shouting) Mother fucker!
- [Chop] Scream, bitch ass nigga!
Scream, bitch ass nigga!
Touching my shit.
(granna laughing)
(upbeat R&B music)
♪ Woo
♪ We run the city
♪ The places that we can go
♪ Like the wind
♪ Just let it blow
♪ Blow all over you body
♪ Just let it blow, blow, baby
♪ Blow all over your body, baby ♪
♪ Let it blow
♪ Blow all over your body
♪ Just let it blow
(doorbell rings)
- [Asa] Granna,
it's me.
(Haven crying)
I know, I'm sorry.
I know, y'all okay? - Thank you, Jesus.
Just worried about you, is all.
- I know,
I'm sorry, granna.
I just had to be careful.
- I know, come on.
- You all right?
- Better now that you're here
but okay what's going on?
What's, where's everybody is everybody?
Is everyone okay?
Have you seen my dad?
- [New Anchor] WTFGO, Missionary Baptist church.
Trapper turned preacher caught red-handed.
Turns out he was preaching lies.
I'm going pass it on over to our field anchor, Chad,
who's reporting live on scene, now.
Chad.
- Reporting live here from Missionary Baptist Church
where pastor Hosea Reynolds has just been arrested.
Charges remain unseen. - It's gonna be all right.
Just calm down.
It's just a misunderstanding, it's okay.
It's all right, calm down.
- [Chad] Mr Reynolds do you have any quotes?
- [Hosea] No comment. - But Mr Reynolds.
- [Hosea] No comment. (Haven crying)
No I do not.
- He, he.
He.
I can't.
He's been an dope dealing liar this whole time.
- Just relax.
- You listen to me.
Your daddy,
he might be a lot of things,
but something tells me if nothing,
he does
love you.
Unlike that no good bastard
that killed
my daughter.
Not that man.
That man is Satan himself.
You see, my gift of discernment is sharper.
I can read anybody.
From the moment I laid my eyes on that negro,
I knew he wasn't no good.
I begged and I begged and I begged her to cut him loose,
but he had a hold on her so tight.
It almost suffocated me.
And then
she told me
for my family,
but baby,
the night you showed up on my porch,
I promise you, girl was like,
like granna had seen my angel straight from heaven.
- Thank you, granna.
- Your mother
is proud of the woman that you are becoming baby.
- I can't believe your father wanted to kill me.
Why? I had nothing to do with anything.
- That nigga ain't my daddy.
Just some nigga that nutted in my mama.
That's it.
Haven, the day that Chop showed me that picture of you
I literally was tripping.
I just met you.
And he talking 'bout, get close to you.
Get you to trust me.
I was supposed to bring you into him.
- Were you gonna kill me?
- Honestly,
I was just, I was just gonna listen to his orders,
but Haven something changed.
Everything changed, Haven.
Look,
it's not just because we had sex.
It's that conversation we had in your closet.
I knew you were a real deal
and I understand why you were sent to me.
I get it, now.
Look, it may have started out,
by some plan the enemy started,
but God turned it around for us.
- Hey, hallelujah!
Okay. Yes, grand baby. - Grandma.
- Oh, baby,
I'm sorry.
You know how I get what God shows himself approved.
I'ma hush.
- Is that what you' trying to tell me that night.
- Yeah.
- I meant everything I said Haven.
I meant it.
I just hope that you can forgive me.
- Okay, what about Chop? - [Asa] Look.
- What if he tries to kill me?
- You ain't gonna have to worry about him no more.
Okay?
My three girls are protected.
All right?
- What?
What are you talking about three girls.
- Granna.
You.
And my little princess baking in there.
(Haven chuckles)
- And here you go.
How do you know it's a girl?
- I don't, but granna said it, so
it must be law. - [Haven] Not granna.
(all laughing)
- We just gonna run with it.
We just gonna go with it but look,
we gonna start a new life.
Us three.
Our love,
honesty,
respect,
all that other stuff you were telling me.
It's over now.
Okay?
All right?
Don't worry.
I got you.
Okay?
(police sirens)
- [Guard] Reynolds.
- [Kidnapped girl] Get off me!
What is going on?
Please get off of me!
No!
- [Kidnapper] Ah, shut the fuck up.
(gunshots)
(bible thuds)
(Hosea exclaims)
- Love you.
- I love you too.
(intense music)
(inmates speaking indistinctly)
(dramatic music)
- You good?
(sighs) I'm so disgusted by these charges.
I won't even beat around the bush.
You're going down.
And if I have anything to do with it,
it's gonna be for a long time.
- Whatever, man
- I've seen people get arrested for
almost everything under the sun.
So the drugs and the murders don't really surprise me.
But what doesn't surprise me is that you
have the audacity to play with God
by claiming to be a servant of his.
You give good pastors
who are really about this life,
a bad name.
- I don't know what you're talking about.
Those things that you found,
don't belong to me.
And I don't know how it got there.
All right?
As a man of God,
as a man of the cloth I would never, never,
never do anything to disrespect God.
- Wow!
Unbelievable.
I stand in front of my congregation
every Sunday and Wednesday doing my best
to lead God's people back to him
and pray that I don't do anything to make them fall
while under my leadership.
I'm responsible for those souls that I'm teaching.
Do you not understand
that their blood is on my hands
if I were to lead them astray?
(deep breath)
- Those people are grown
and they're gonna do what they wanna do,
no matter what I say.
And if they were really so
holy,
they would realize that I picked out the scriptures
that hyped them up to make them fork off for money.
- They may be grown.
But what about your daughter?
- Baby?
What are we doing here?
- Get out.
(thunder roaring)
(trap music) ♪ I don't trust ya
♪ I don't love you bitch
♪ I'm cold as ice
♪ I thought you was the one
♪ Now I'm thinking twice
♪ Bitches fuck me, I'm a thug, I don't feel a thing ♪
♪ I gave you all had
♪ Ain't no more than that
♪ Look me in my eye and tell boldest lie ♪
- [Chop] Move!
♪ Bitch you know I'm gangster
♪ Know the ball on fire
- What is he doing? - Sit down.
Sit your ass down!
♪ The nerve of this little pussy ♪
♪ It's an evil eye
- You think I'm some kind of fool, baby?
- No, baby, no.
No, no, no.
You know I don't think that.
- I don't know that shit.
But what I do know
is just that you still haven't told me
that you was pregnant.
Fuck is up with that.
- I was, I was going to, I swear I was, baby.
Just listen.
I was just trying to find the right time to tell you.
I thought, I thought that maybe if I told you the right way,
he would accept it.
(Chop scoffs)
- Believe this broad? (both chuckle)
- I, I'm telling the truth, baby.
Listen,
I just,
I know you weren't there for Trouble when he was born and
maybe this is our chance.
Maybe now we can be a family.
Maybe God is giving you another chance.
- (laughing) You said, God?
You talking about the same God that
you and that bitch ass nigga Keys is using
to pimp the saints whenever the door to the church is open?
(thunder roaring)
You talking about that God?
You funny as shit.
She funny as shit, ain't she? (laughing)
You is a funny mother fucker.
(Chinirika laughing)
- You know the only thing funny
is trying to reason with a man like you.
Shit, I should have been left your ass.
(tense music)
None of this shit is worth it.
And Keys,
would've been a way better daddy to this baby
than you could ever be.
Shit, he was a way better boss.
That nigga stole your dope.
Started from nothing and still leveled up on your ass.
(scoffs)
I see why you mad.
(gun clicks)
(repeated gunshots) (Shea shouting)
- Put that on God!
Put that on God!
- Damn.
I ain't see that coming.
(cocks gun)
Just like you didn't see this.
Yeah.
See you and Keys are alike in many ways.
Y'all both about money.
Get rid of any nigga that get in y'all way.
But the difference between y'all two is;
unlike him, you let your feelings guide you.
And you don't always know who on your team.
Big ass mistake.
- Nigga, I always know who I got in my squad.
- Really?
So tell me,
you knew Kenya's brother was on your team?
(thunder roars)
- What the fuck you talking about?
(gunshot) (Chop screams)
Ah shit!
- Bitch ass nigga.
- You bitch ass nigga! (gun clicks)
- Probably shouldn't have used all your bullets
on your little boo right here.
(chuckles) Imagine.
Just imagine
your mother gettin' the car the night before Christmas,
and the police telling her her only daughter being shot.
Nigga, you know how it feel
to hear the woman that birthed you
struggle to breathe after hearing that shit?
But oh, what a God we serve, right?
What a God we serve.
'Cause right when we rushed in,
the doctors told us they was able to bring Kenya back.
(cocks gun)
- Kenya alive?
(gunshot) (Chop yelling)
- Did I fuckin' say talk?
- You bitch. - Did I say talk?
- Bitch ass nigga.
- I made my sister a promise
sitting next to her hospital bed.
I told her my niece will be taken care of.
(chuckles)
Before I take my last breath
you and keys will already taken yours.
(Chop wincing)
- Nigga, you must have forgot
you talking about,
ah shit.
Nigga,
you was saying all that shit about
who all on everybody team you early.
You must've forgot who had on my fuckin' team, nigga.
(Chop winces)
If I don't show up as planned later on
Trouble and all them niggas gonna be on your head.
'Cause they knew I was coming to meet your bitch ass.
(wincing) Oh shit.
- [Man On phone] Is it done yet?
- Almost.
Your boy here seems to think
that y'all gonna be on my head
when he don't meet up with y'all later.
You know, considering the fact
everybody knew he was me.
- [Man] I thought you was calling to tell me
his body was stinking by now. - What the?
- [Man] After all the shit that he done caused us.
- [Chop] Fuck.
- Indeed. - Man, fuck that nigga.
- Indeed.
I'll pull up when it's done.
- [Chop] (whispering) Fuck.
- My mama's favorite scripture for as long as I can remember
was Galatians six and seven.
Do not be deceived.
God will not be mocked.
A man reaps what he sows.
Good or bad.
You reap the benefits of what you plant.
- Nigga, shut that shit up!
Don't nobody wanna hear no god damn sermon.
Nigga wanna commit a sin and it all holier than thou.
Nigga, you might as well go ahead kill me now, nigga, so.
- As you please. (gunshot)
- [Guard] Reynolds, you got a visitor.
(inmates shouting indistinctly)
Open cell five.
(cell buzzes)
- Baby girl.
You alive.
God knows I was worried about you.
- You was worried about me?
Were you worried about me when you lied to me my whole life?
(intense music)
- Haven, listen to me.
I don't know what you heard about me,
but I did
what was best for you at the time?
- (scoffs) No.
What was best for me?
What was best for me would've been
for you to tell me the truth.
What was best for me was be,
be for you to open your eyes!
For you to have not have lied and preached things
that you didn't even believe your damn self.
That's what would've been what's best for me.
But instead
you knew
how hurt I was
that I didn't have a mother
and instead,
instead of you,
instead of you
spending as much time with me as you could.
What was best for me would you for you to live
a life of honesty,
but you lied to an entire congregation.
I already lost my mother to cancer,
but here you are sacrificing your life and mine
every day
and you have to audacity to try to tell me
what's best for me.
(deep exhale)
You're right, baby girl.
I was selfish
and consumed with being the biggest kingpin to ever do it.
But your mama,
she really was the love of my life.
And I put her in harm's way too.
- What?
What do you mean, you put her in harms way?
(slams table) Dad,
what do you mean you put her in harms way?
Stop lying to me.
What? What happened?
- She didn't die of cancer, baby.
(Haven crying) Baby.
Baby, what's wrong?
Haven?
Baby.
Yo, guard, guard, get my daughter!
Get my daughter. - What's wrong with her?
- She's breathing heavy, man.
We was just talking right there.
I don't even know
what happened! - Get back.
Medic, we need a medic in here.
We need a medic in here.
Have a seat!
Sit down! (suspenseful music)
(Haven hyperventilating)
- What's her name? - Haven Reynolds.
- Haven, can you hear me? - [Hosea] Baby.
- She's hyperventilating. (Haven breathing heavy)
- Check her pulse.
- How far along are you? - [Hosea] Pregnant?
- Ma'am, how far along are you?
Yeah, she's pregnant, we have to take her to the E.R.
Let's go. - I guess you're not
the only one with secret.
(heavily breathing) - [Medic] Come on, let's go.
Let's go, let's go.
(Haven breathing heavily)
(intense electronic music)
- (gasp) Ooh, Mi's here.
- [Asa] Hey babe, babe, what you doing?
- Hmm, here come little miss fastness.
- Uh-uh, granna.
Don't do my bestie like that.
- I got it, baby.
Just rest, okay.
Gonna go and get Mi.
- Mm.
- Hey, bro!
- What's good, sis!
- How you doing? - I'm good, I'm good.
- I see you still your Omarion's in.
Okay! (Asa humming)
Touch! (both laughing)
Granna, darling!
- Hey little miss fastness.
- Oh. (Asa chuckling)
- Come on over and gimme my hug.
- Hi.
(Haven laughing)
(Haven and Mila screaming)
- Look at, Ti Ti baby.
- Stop that, you psycho.
You know, every time you do that,
it takes her hours to settle back down.
- Man.
- Well hurry up and spit her out then
so I can spoils her. (Haven laughing)
Oo, before I forget.
Ba-yow!
- Wow. What?
- One for you
and one for you, sir.
Yeah, mm-hmm.
- Uh huh.
- What's that?
- Ah!
Is this what I?
Ah!
Yes!
(Haven squealing)
- Well what is it?
- It's my degree!
With
honors!
- Praise god! (Granna laughing)
- Yes, I'm so proud of you.
- Oh, my goodness, I actually did it.
I am so sorry that I couldn't walk with you
like we always planned, Mi. - Oh, I know.
That's why I didn't walk.
- What?
- Calm down.
You know, I wasn't about to walk that stage
without my sister.
- Oh.
- So this just means when we get our masters,
you better not be full of another baby 'cause we
gone twerk across the stage. (Haven exclaiming)
Ah, ah! - Aye, ah, ah!
(both celebrating)
- Aye, oh, baby mama!
Ah, ah.
Ah!
- Hey, what's wrong, babe?
Hmm?
- You open.
- What is is?
Baby you went and got your GED?
- Yeah.
- What, why didn't you tell me?
- I ain't wanna disappoint you just in case I failed.
- Maybe you can never disappoint me.
The fact that you stepped out on faith and took the test,
I am so proud of you.
(Asa sighs)
- All right now,
what does it say?
- Oh, okay. (Asa deep takes deep breath)
Okay.
- If you don't spit out that tea.
- Um.
Uh.
It says, (mellow guitar music)
it says,
that my baby passed all four sections
with honors! - (clapping) Hallelujah.
Praise god! - I passed?
Yes, look, babe! - [Mila] Yes!
- Ah! (both laughing)
- Oh, my God.
- Yes. - [Granna] Amen.
- I'm so proud of you.
- Thank you for not making me feel dumb.
Talking down on me.
Granna you too.
That really helped me.
- I will always believe in you
because I know for a fact that
God has higher plans for you.
Congratulations.
- Thank you. - Mm.
- Look, I know, God got something better for me.
- Oh?
- 'Cause instead of going to just,
you know, regular college. - Mm-hmm?
- I'ma go to seminary school.
- Oh, hallelujah!
Won't he do it?
- No he didn't! - Go head, grand baby!
Yes, Jesus. - [Haven] Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Ah!
Okay, so what's going on?
Oh, what's going on?
- I think I met someone.
- Child, you think or you know?
- You know what I mean?
- No, I don't know what you mean
because you definitely pick the crunchiest men
I've ever found, - Uh.
- in your entire life.
So tell me
which creature from the Bikini Bottom
have you chosen this time? (laughing)
- If you weren't pregnant I would push you off this bed.
They are not that bad.
- They are horrible.
Like horrid.
- Mm-hmm.
- So. - Yeah, you right.
- Okay. - Justin did look like
he was related to Squidward.
- The way that he sounded! - (nasally) Squidward.
- (nasally) He was like, Mila, I love you.
(both laughing)
- Oh, I was so bad. - Oh!
Oh.
Ow.
- You okay?
- I think my water just broke.
- What?
Oh my.
- No, no.
Ow.
- Grandma! Asa!
Breathe, are you okay? - (heavily breathing) Yeah.
- [Both] What's wrong?!
- I think her water just broke.
We gotta go.
- [Asa] Uh.
- We gotta go.
- Boy, if you don't get your shoes
and get that damn car!
- Okay, I'll get it, all right.
Do, granna, do I need to the um.
- Boy that day dropped you on your head
is coming back to haunt me, move!
- He is something, is he? (laughing)
Oo, ooh, oo, okay, okay, okay.
(gentle music)
(monitor beeping)
- [Doctor] You did great, Haven.
- Thank you.
- You too, dad.
- Thank you. - My babies done had a baby.
(soft chuckles)
- Oh my gosh.
I can't believe, I'm a mom.
- Oh, well believe it, honey.
And it's about to get real, real.
Wait 'til that child start waking up every two hours to eat.
- [Haven] Oh.
- And don't come looking for granna
'cause I'm going to be down Mr. Rufus' house.
(laughing)
Oh,
what? - [Asa] Granna.
- This old lady ain't dead yet.
Besides Mr. Rufus as fine as he wanna be.
Look like a young Billy Dee.
- I know that's right. (both laughing)
- You know, I'ma have to,
I'ma have to go down and see about this, Mr. Rufus.
And see what he talking about.
'Cause granna you can't.
- You don't be out here hating on granna.
- Mm-hmm. (Haven laughing)
- I ain't hatin'. (granna laughing)
- Mm, you wanna hold her?
- Yeah - Yeah.
- Yeah. - All right, now.
- Come on, you got her. - Easy, grandson.
- Hold on. Hold on.
- Hold her head.
- Okay, okay.
(monitor beeping)
- Just like that. - [Haven] Daddy.
(Mila chuckling)
- What's wrong with you, baby girl?
- (sighs) Nothing, it's.
I'm so,
I'm so appreciative
of you guys all thank you with me,
it's just,
I'm just realizing that
neither of my parents are here to experience this with me.
- Look, I understand baby,
but I, I'm just grateful
you got an opportunity
to talk to your daddy and forgive him.
Forgiveness is everything, baby.
- [Haven] Yes.
Yeah.
- Now,
have you all decided
what you gonna name this child?
I mean,
we can continue to call her gorgeous
because that's exactly what she is.
- (laughing) Yeah, we did.
That's unfortunate that Haven's parents aren't here
to experience this with us but
we still wanted to honor them so
we decided to name her
Kenya Hosanna Thomas.
- Amen.
- Did someone say my name?
(granna gasps)
- Mom?
- Oh, that's the God I serve.
- Mom? - Yes, baby, yes.
(both crying)
(indistinctly speaking through tears)
- Oh, my good.
Oh, let me see my baby.
- Oh, you gotta meet her. - Oh, my god.
- Oh, look at.
(Asa chuckling)
- Oh, you're a grandma.
- You sweet beautiful baby.
(whispering indistinctly)
- [Kenya] Granny's here now.
(laughing)
- We did it. - We did it.
- Oh, look at.
- I'm so proud of you.
- Hey. - Asa!
If you had to taken any longer to open that door,
you was gonna have to change my diaper.
(Kenya laughing) - I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
- How you doing baby? - I'm good.
- You ain't keeping up no trouble, are you?
- No. - Okay, good.
Now, get out my way.
I'm here to see my granddaughter.
- Yeah. - Where is Gigi's baby?
- She's right here.
- [Kenya] Gigi's baby, come here to grandma.
- Here she is. - Bring her to me.
Let me see here.
- Hi there,
little Kenya benya. - Hey.
- Hi, stinker. (Haven sighs)
- Hey, Meech.
Let me holler at you
for a minute. - [Kenya] How are you
doing baby? - All right.
- [Kenya] Oh my goodness.
Did you know that your name was...
(Asa sighs)
- Man, they say
whoever killed O'Shea,
put two bullets in his body.
- It was three.
- Man, look.
I know you was O'Shea's right hand man for years,
but I need you to understand,
I need to make sure I can trust you.
- Look, man.
My business was with O'Shea.
Long as you take care of Haven and that baby,
we good.
- (chuckling) All right.
(hip hop music begins)
- Damn, fool.
How is he?
- Well, he's finally resting.
I'm surprised he's still alive
after all the blood he's lost.
You sure you don't wanna take him to the hospital?
- Look, no hospitals, no visitors.
Nobody can know he's here.
Just do what the fuck I pay you for
and keep the nigga alive, all right?
- Yeah, all right.
♪ Killers on my side, ready to drill something ♪
♪ Get you touched at the next spot ♪
♪ Went to spill something
♪ Can't be claiming that you rich ♪
♪ Steady preaching last week
♪ Then riding in my car, you know I'm slanted now ♪
♪ Nightmares are nothing
♪ I make double my own team
♪ Some night I don't smoke nothing ♪
♪ But just pray I don't stop breathing ♪
♪ I need a safe haven
♪ All this bullshit going on, it drive me crazy, baby ♪
♪ Stand on business, he in trouble ♪
♪ Think about trying to play me, baby ♪
♪ We the ones that's bringing danger ♪
♪ We'll cut off his fingers, maybe ♪
♪ For real nigga
♪ Came straight of the block
♪ Feeling like Chop
♪ King of the kill nigga
♪ Feeling all on my own
♪ Just leave me alone
♪ I'm chasing a mil, nigga
♪ And all the folks doubled me
♪ I went and did it
♪ Whenever I'm gone, just know that I'm in it ♪
♪ Write on my stone
♪ I'm tired of reading scripture ♪
♪ Still pray that God that my soul ♪
♪ I just hope I make it out
♪ Run up an M before I'm old
♪ Run with real ones in my circle ♪
♪ Jeopardy on full
♪ I get you like cheese, but you a rat ♪
♪ You shouldn't have told
♪ Yeah that nigga a rat
♪ He ain't my kind and shit
♪ Keeping it real
♪ Ain't talking about NFL but bullets flying in your field ♪
♪ Just stay in your lane and play the game ♪
♪ Just how the game go
♪ I ain't really trippin'
♪ That's my old vibe, lame ho
♪ They telling you check 'cause I'm really poppin' ♪
♪ In the game, take off like a rocket, on god ♪
♪ They know they pussy, I'm pullin' the car ♪
♪ I blackened the coupe, I can just see stars ♪
♪ I'm poppin', I got this shit on ♪
♪ She love the smell of my cologne ♪
♪ Leave me alone don't call my phone ♪
♪ I'm tired of reading scripture ♪
♪ Still pray to God he take my soul ♪
♪ I just hope I make it out
♪ Run up an M before I'm old
♪ Run with real ones in my circle ♪
♪ Jeopardy on full
♪ I get you like cheese
♪ But you a rat, you shouldn't have told ♪
♪ I pray withy all my soul to keep ♪
♪ Fuck ♪ Pray for my dogs
♪ We spinnin' for a week
♪ Yeah, we spinnin', told me to tell the truth ♪
♪ You told me all lies
♪ Bitch I'm a big dog
♪ I don't be with small fries, like not at all ♪
♪ I told them
♪ Better watch your move
♪ Better keep your tool
♪ Bitch I run with steppers
♪ Them niggas stepping like some shoes ♪
♪ This one on the ground
♪ 'Til we caught him out of bounds ♪
♪ That boy say he be trappin'
♪ He can't even get off a pound ♪
♪ Can't get off a pound
♪ I just might take it down
♪ Tell my ops we make a diss
♪ Tell him let's go round for round ♪
♪ Tell that bitch that I don't need her ♪
♪ We pullin' cars, they talkin' greezy ♪
♪ Niggas talkin' swiss, eat 'em ♪
♪ Had him runnin' out his sneakers ♪
♪ When they come for mine, I die for mine ♪
♪ Every time
♪ They get in the both and tellin' lies on every one ♪
♪ They done told you that price, and you fold ♪
♪ Yeah, under pressure I won't bend or fold ♪
♪ Like no
♪ Yeah, I ain't fold then
♪ Think you trippin' on my dog like I ain't ♪