♪ WELL I STAND
OUT ON THE DESERT ♪
♪ WATER AND THE SEA
♪ AIN'T ONE THING
WORTH TALKIN' ABOUT ♪
♪ AND IT'S
LOW-DOWN MISERY ♪
♪ IT AIN'T NO GOOD
♪ IT AIN'T NO GOOD THIS WAY
♪ I SAID IT AIN'T NO SECRET
♪ I'VE SEEN BETTER DAYS
♪ I KNOW WHEN I GET UP
EVERY MORNING ♪
♪ PUT ME ON SOME SHOES
♪ I'M GONNA TAKE OUT WALKING
♪ UNTIL I WALK AWAY
THESE BLUES ♪
♪ IT AIN'T NO GOOD
THIS WAY ♪
♪♪
♪ YEAH I WANT TO SAY
THAT SHE LOVED ME ♪
♪ AND I DIDN'T
HAVE TO FEAR ♪
♪ BUT IF SHE LOVED ME
SO DOGGONE MUCH ♪
♪ THEN WHY AIN'T SHE
SITTING HERE ♪
♪ IT AIN'T NO GOOD
♪ IT AIN'T NO GOOD THIS WAY
♪ IT SURE LOOKS LIKE
THEM BLUES ARE HERE TO STAY ♪
♪ ALL RIGHT,
YOU TAKE IT DOWN ONE TIME ♪♪
[SPEAKING JAPANESE]
SO, MR. SMITH,
WHAT BRINGS YOU AND YOUR FRIEND
TO BEAUTIFUL LOS ANGELES?
BUSINESS OR PLEASURE?
BUSINESS.
♪ WELL SHE MAKES ME
STAGGER ♪
♪ EVEN MAKES ME FALL
♪ THESE BLUES DON'T MAKE ME
DO A DOGGONE THING ♪
♪ BUT JUST SIT HERE
AND CRY AND MOAN ♪
♪ IT AIN'T NO GOOD
♪ IT AIN'T NO GOOD THIS WAY
♪ A MAN AIN'T GOT
NO BUSINESS ♪
♪ IN THE SHADE
♪ WELL THAT'S
WATER IN THE DESERT ♪
♪ SAND OUT ON THE SEA
♪ THESE DAYS I AIN'T REALLY
SURE BUT THESE BLUES
AIN'T GETTING TO ME ♪
♪ IT AIN'T NO GOOD
♪ IT AIN'T NO GOOD THIS WAY
♪ I SAID IT AIN'T NO GOOD
AND THAT'S ALL I GOT TO SAY ♪
AND THAT'S ALL I GOT TO SAY ♪♪
[ROCK MUSIC PLAYS]
[SPEAKING JAPANESE]
COME ON, ENOUGH
OF THAT ALREADY, HUH?
YOU LOOK FINE
WITHOUT IT.
I'M GONNA CATCH
THE BUS BACK, OKAY?
HEY, I WOULDN'T DO THAT
IF I WERE YOU.
NOT IN THOSE CLOTHES,
ANYWAY.
CHELSEA!
WHAT?
TELL YOUR MOM I SAID
HAPPY BIRTHDAY.
NO. SHE HATES BEING REMINDED
OF HER AGE.
YEAH, I KNOW.
[SPEAKING JAPANESE]
[MUSIC PLAYS]
Talk Show Host: IN CASE
YOU JUST JOINED US,
TODAY'S TOPIC IS
"WOMEN WHO LOVE LOSERS."
AND WE'RE TAKING CALLS.
WE WANT TO HEAR YOUR STORY.
TELL US ABOUT THE LOSERS-
NUTS.
Audio Tape: YOU CAN
CONTROL YOUR ANGER.
ANGER IS DANGER
WITHOUT THE "D".
ELIMINATE ALL
NEGATIVE THOUGHTS.
BREATHE.
SLOW DOWN.
TELL YOURSELF HOW CALM
AND CONFIDENT YOU ARE.
DO IT NOW.
I AM CALM
AND RELAXED.
IN CONTROL-
[MOTORIST YELLS]
[HORN HONKS]
ASSHOLE!
NO. STOP.
I'M IN CONTROL.
I'M TOTALLY RELAXED.
Loan Officer: HOW MANY TIMES
DO I HAVE TO SAY IT?
THERE'S NOTHING MORE
I CAN DO.
WE HAVE TO TAKE THE HOUSE.
I'LL ALSO HAVE TO NOTIFY
YOUR WIFE.
EX-WIFE.
AND NO, YOU DON'T
HAVE TO NOTIFY HER.
BECAUSE, WELL, SHE'S JUST
GONNA USE IT AS AN EXCUSE
TO TRY TO GET MY KID BACK.
SHE IS A CO-SIGNER AND
AS SUCH SHE MUST
BE NOTIFIED.
OKAY, FINE.
BUT FIRST, JUST GIVE ME
A LITTLE MORE TIME, OKAY?
JUST A MONTH.
GIVE ME ONE MONTH.
GIVE ME A MONTH.
I THINK I CAN GET IT TOGETHER.
I'VE SPENT TOO MUCH TIME
WITH THIS.
I WON'T DISCUSS IT
ANY FURTHER.
WELL, YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO!
YOU UNDERSTAND ME?
BECAUSE I NEED MORE TIME.
BOB, DON'T BECOME
A REPEAT OFFENDER.
I HAVE CALLED SECURITY
IN THE PAST
AND I'M FULLY PREPARED
TO DO SO AGAIN.
THANK YOU FOR COMING IN.
HAVE A GOOD DAY.
WHAT?
COME ON.
GIVE ME BACK MY CARD.
GIVE ME THE CARD BACK!
EXCUSE ME.
COULD YOU MOVE FORWARD
A LITTLE?
YOU GOT ME BLOCKED IN.
GET LOST.
LOOK, I JUST WANT
TO GET MY CAR-
GET LOST, JERK-OFF!
FINE. I JUST THOUGHT
I'D ASK.
JUST THOUGHT I'D ASK.
[BANK ALARM RINGS]
[POLICE SIREN WAILS]
UNBELIEVABLE! WHO THE HELL
WAS THAT?
SOME RAMBO WANNA-BE
AT THE ATM?
DOES EVERY DIRTBAG IN THIS CITY
GOT A GUN NOW?
THE NRA'S GETTING
WAY OUT OF CONTROL.
I GOTTA GET OUT
OF THIS TOWN.
YOU CAN'T EVEN ESCAPE ANYMORE.
[SPEAKING JAPANESE]
[SIGHS]
[POLICE SIRENS WAIL]
Dussecq: MALONE,
PUT THE GUN DOWN.
SAVE IT, DUSSECQ.
YOU KNOW THE ROUTINE.
DOWN ON YOUR KNEES.
PUT YOUR HANDS
BEHIND YOUR HEAD.
YOU EVER HEAR OF
SELF-DEFENSE?
HEY. NOW WE CAN EITHER
DO THIS MY WAY
OR THE HARD WAY.
NOW PUT THE GUN DOWN
AND GET ON YOUR KNEES.
NOW!
I SMELL BACON,
I SMELL PORK,
I SMELL PIGGY ON MY PORT.
HEY, PIG!
GIVE A GUY A BREAK.
THAT OTHER GUY SHOT FIRST.
WHY DON'T YOU CHASE HIS ASS
FOR AWHILE?
HOW'S MY DRIVING?
DIAL 1-800-PSYCHO.
EXCUSE ME, SIR.
THERE'S NO SMOKING HERE.
WILL YOU BE JOINING US
FOR LUNCH?
YES.
AND THE RESERVATION.
WHAT'S THE NAME, PLEASE?
IT DOESN'T LOOK LIKE
A RESERVATION IS NECESSARY.
THERE IS PLENTY OF ROOM.
OH. IS THAT WHAT YOU THINK?
MOST OF OUR TABLES
ARE RESERVED.
SO WHAT DO YOU THINK NOW?
DO YOU CARE TO CHANGE
YOUR STATEMENT?
OKAY. WE WILL WAIT.
WILL YOU, NOW?
HURRY UP. FOLLOW ME.
I'M GONNA HAVE TO
BOOK YOU.
ON TOP OF EVERYTHING
ELSE,
IT'S A FEDERAL
OFFENSE TO TAMPER
WITH A CASH MACHINE.
AND YOU KNOW THAT.
IT ATE MY CARD.
LET ME ENLIGHTEN YOU.
YOU DON'T HAVE A BADGE
AND YOU'RE NOT
A COP ANYMORE.
AND YOU JUST CAN'T
PULL A GUN AND START
SHOOTING PEOPLE.
IT'S AGAINST THE LAW.
NOBODY DIED THAT
DIDN'T DESERVE IT.
TAKE HIM IN AND
CALL HIS DAUGHTER.
TONY, COME ON, LEAVE CHELSEA
OUT OF THIS, WOULD YOU?
TONY! KEEP CHELSEA
OUT OF THIS!
[POLICE SIRENS WAIL]
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
YOU WANT SOME OF THIS?
IF YOU CAN READ THIS,
YOU'RE TOO CLOSE.
[AUTOMATIC GUNFIRE]
HOW'D THAT FEEL?
WHO'S LAUGHING NOW?
[CELL PHONE RINGS]
YEAH?
WE'RE FIVE MINUTES OUT.
TAKE A WALK.
HAVE A LOOK AROUND.
YEAH. NO PROBLEM, BOSS.
WHO'S NEXT?
AW, GODDAMN IT!
A LOT MORE WHERE
THAT CAME FROM.
PLENTY TO GO AROUND,
ENOUGH FOR EVERYBODY!
WHO PACKED MY BAG? STUPID IDIOT!
WHO PUT THE CLOTHES ON TOP?
YOU GOTTA DO SOMETHING RIGHT,
YOU GOTTA DO IT YOURSELF.
COME ON, CHICKENSHIT!
BACK OFF! BACK HER OUT!
422, OFFICER NEEDS BACKUP.
SHOOTS FIRED. SOUTHWEST
CORNER, LA TIJERA AND ADAMS.
YOU DUMB BASTARD,
THIS RESTAURANT BELONGS TO-
NOBODY LEAVES!
Radio: ALL UNITS RESPOND,
CODE TWO.
4-ADAM 22 WITH CODE SIX
AT LA TIJERA AND ADAMS.
THIS IS 4-L-19.
SHOW ME EN ROUTE.
OKAY, LUNCH TIME PEOPLE.
THIS IS THE STORY.
ANY OF YOU TRY TO LEAVE
WITHOUT MY SAY-SO...
IT'S COFFEE TIME WITH GABRIEL.
YOU GET THE PICTURE?
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
I'LL GET IT.
IT'S PROBABLY FOR ME.
ALWAYS HAPPENS WHEN
YOU'RE TRYING TO EAT.
HELLO. HOW CAN I HELP YOU?
THIS IS LIEUTENANT
TONY DUSSECQ.
WHO AM I TALKING TO?
YOUR MAMA'S GREASY ASS.
LISTEN, I GOT FOUR VERY
IMPORTANT WORDS TO
SAY TO YOU, ASSHOLE.
SWEDISH ANTI SNIPER
DETONATOR.
[BEEPS]
SOUND INTERESTING? GOOD.
I NEED A CHOPPER HERE
IN 30 MINUTES
OR I'M GONNA SEND
SOME OLD LADY'S HEAD OUT
ON A BED OF LETTUCE.
IS THAT CLEAR?
I UNDERSTAND. BUT I NEED YOU
TO STAY ON THE LINE WITH ME.
[CLICK]
HE HUNG UP. TUCKER!
WE TALKED TO THE BANK GUARD.
HERE'S WHAT WE COULD DIG UP
ON THAT DETONATOR.
I KNOW WHAT IT IS.
THE PSYCHO LETS GO,
THE WHOLE PLACE GOES UP.
WE'RE SCREWED.
ALL RIGHT. I SEE. THANKS.
I'M SORRY, MR. DELORENZO.
IT LOOKS LIKE YOUR RESTAURANT'S
GONNA BE CLOSED FOR
A LITTLE WHILE.
IT'S OVER.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
HOW ABOUT SOMETHING DIFFERENT?
MAYBE A LITTLE SUSHI?
HOW ABOUT SOME THAI FOOD?
MAYBE PIZZA.
YEAH, I'LL GET THAT.
I'LL GET THE MILK.
I TOLD YOU, YOU CAN ONLY USE
THE PAGERS FOR POLICE BUSINESS.
[PHONE RINGS]
SO ONLY FOR EMER - HANG ON.
I'LL BE RIGHT THERE.
HONEY, I HAVE TO GO.
THE FINGERPRINT...
I'M IN THE LIEUTENANT'S -
I HAVE TO GO.
ALL RIGHT. BYE.
I'M SORRY, MR. MALONE.
DETECTIVE.
BOB.
BOB, I'M SORRY,
DETECTIVE.
BOB.
RELAX, OKAY?
YOU'RE JUST DOING YOUR JOB.
LISTEN UP!
HERE'S THE DRILL.
EVERYBODY IN THE MIDDLE
OF THE ROOM!
ON YOUR BELLIES!
COME ON!
LET'S GO!
PLENTY OF ROOM, NO WAITING.
EVERYBODY DOWN! DOWN!
DOWN!
WHAT THE HELL?
WHAT WERE YOU,
RAISED RETARDED?
JUST GET DOWN!
HEY, SULU.
THIS AIN'T NO SLEEPOVER.
WHAT'S WITH THE LUGGAGE?
[SPEAKS JAPANESE]
SHUT UP.
OPEN IT!
WHAT THE HELL
IS GOING ON IN THERE?
MOVE THESE PEOPLE.
Cop: EXCUSE ME, SIR.
WE'RE GONNA NEED YOU
TO STEP RIGHT OVER-
[WOMAN SCREAMS]
[AUTOMATIC GUNFIRE]
GET DOWN!
GET HIM!
HI, MIKE.
HI, SWEETHEART.
HOW YOU DOING?
FIND A SUMMER JOB YET?
NO, NOT YET.
SO, WHAT DID HE DO
THIS TIME?
DRUNK AND DISORDERLY?
NO, JUST DISORDERLY.
BUT IT GOT A LITTLE
MORE COMPLICATED THAN THAT.
TELL YOU WHAT.
WHY DON'T YOU TAKE
A SEAT OVER THERE
AND IF YOU'RE
GOOD, I'LL BRING
YOUR FATHER IN MYSELF.
OKAY.
WHY DON'T YOU
TAKE A SEAT?
I STILL NEED TO ASK
YOU SOME QUESTIONS.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND WHY
THIS IS NECESSARY.
EVEN THOUGH YOUR ACTIONS
MAY BE JUSTIFIED,
THIS IS STILL A HOMICIDE
UNDER INVESTIGATION,
AND I NEED
A STATEMENT FROM YOU.
SO WHY DON'T YOU
TAKE A SEAT?
PLEASE.
HEY. WHAT'S UP, DUSS?
I HEAR YOUR BANK ROBBER
GOT BLOWN TO PIECES
ON YOU.
THAT'S VERY FUNNY, MIKE.
LISTEN, I WANT YOU
TO RUN THIS FOR ME.
IS THERE SOMETHING ABOUT
THIS GUY YOU DON'T KNOW?
MAYBE. I DON'T KNOW YET.
HE WAS JUST A LITTLE BIT
TOO SMOOTH IN ALL
THAT CHAOS.
I THINK IT MIGHT BE
IN EVERYBODY'S BEST INTERESTS
IF I SWEAT HIM A LITTLE.
OKAY. DONE.
THANK YOU.
HI.
CAN I ASK YOU
A QUESTION?
I GUESS.
ARE YOU A PROSTITUTE?
DO YOU WANT SOMETHING?
I'M SORRY.
I DIDN'T MEAN TO INTERRUPT.
SAVE YOUR APOLOGIES
FOR SOMEONE WHO CARES.
I JUST THOUGHT MY HELP
MIGHT BE NEEDED.
DO I LOOK LIKE
I NEED YOUR HELP?
NO, NOT YOU.
HIM.
I'M SORRY. I GUESS IT'S JUST
BEEN ONE OF THOSE DAYS.
THAT'S OKAY.
I'M CHELSEA.
I'M KOJI.
NICE TO MEET YOU.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I DON'T KNOW.
I'M JUST CURIOUS TO SEE
WHAT'S GOING ON UNDER THERE.
Cop: SETTLE DOWN!
HE WAS GUNNING FOR ME
BUT HE'S DEAD.
IT'S LIKE I COULD
TALK TO THE ANIMALS.
CALM DOWN.
Prisoner: [INDISTINCT]
I DIDN'T LISTEN TO THEM.
SOMEBODY WANTS ME DEAD
'CAUSE I KNOW TOO MUCH.
I KNOW TOO MUCH.
I KNOW TOO MUCH!
PLEASE HELP ME.
TELL YOUR DOG WHERE
THEY'VE TAKEN ME.
HE'LL KNOW WHAT
TO DO.
LET GO!
KOJI.
HEY, KOJI!
SIR. EXCUSE ME,
I THINK THAT GIRL
IS TALKING TO YOU.
YOU FORGOT YOUR GLASSES.
THANK YOU.
NO, THANK YOU FOR
GIVING ME A HAND.
HELLO, CHELSEA.
MIKE'S BRINGING
YOUR DAD UP.
IF YOU'LL EXCUSE US,
THIS WAY, MR. SUGAWATA.
NICE TO MEET YOU,
KOJI.
REMEMBER, YOU HAVE THE RIGHT TO
HAVE A LAWYER PRESENT
DURING ANY QUESTIONING
BY THE POLICE.
BYE.
SO THIS IS IT?
THIS IS THE WAY
IT WENT DOWN?
YES.
EVER DO ANYTHING
LIKE THIS BEFORE?
NO.
EVER PULL ANYBODY
OUT OF A CAR WRECK?
NO.
EVER RUN INTO
A BURNING BUILDING?
NO.
EVER IMAGINE YOURSELF IN
YOUR WILDEST DREAMS DOING
ANYTHING THIS HEROIC?
NO.
THEN TELL ME SOMETHING.
I'M CURIOUS.
WHAT MAKES A MAN LIKE YOU,
A 35-YEAR-OLD VIDEO
GAMES SALESMAN,
WANT TO RISK HIS LIFE
TO STOP A PSYCHO
CARRYING AN AK-47
AND WEARING A VEST
FULL OF C-4?
I'M ON VACATION.
WELL, LOOK WHO'S HERE.
OKAY, BOYS AND GIRLS,
YOU ARE ON YOUR OWN.
THANKS, MIKE.
YEAH, THANKS, MIKEY.
LOVE ME AND LEAVE ME,
JUST LIKE THE EX.
I'D SAY MOM HAD
HER REASONS.
WOULDN'T YOU?
LISTEN, KID, I'M SORRY.
JUST SAVE IT, BOB.
AS I KEEP TELLING YOU,
I'M ON VACATION.
IS THAT A CRIME?
NO.
BUT LYING TO THE POLICE IS.
YOU STATED EARLIER THAT
YOU WERE VACATIONING ALONE.
NOW, ACCORDING TO THE OTHERS
AT THE RESTAURANT,
YOU WERE HAVING LUNCH WITH
ANOTHER JAPANESE GENTLEMAN.
A MAN WITH
A METAL BRIEFCASE.
HE'S A BUSINESS ASSOCIATE.
YOU MET WITH
A BUSINESS ASSOCIATE
ON YOUR VACATION?
WE JAPANESE ARE
WORKAHOLICS.
MAYBE YOU KNOW THAT.
YOU KNOW WHERE YOUR
BUSINESS ASSOCIATE IS NOW,
MR. SUGAWATA?
NO. I WAS HOPING YOU
MIGHT TELL ME.
AND I WAS HOPING FOR
A LITTLE BIT MORE HONESTY.
LET'S START OVER AGAIN,
SHALL WE?
I'D LIKE MY PASSPORT BACK,
PLEASE. I'M LEAVING.
I CAN'T DO THAT.
WHY? I'M NOT A CRIMINAL!
YOU LISTEN TO ME,
YOU LYING SACK OF SHIT.
THE WAY THINGS WORK
IN THIS COUNTRY,
IS THAT I CAN HOLD YOU
FOR 24 HOURS,
JUST FOR LOOKING AT ME
SIDEWAYS.
SO WHETHER YOU LIKE IT
OR NOT,
YOU'RE STAYING RIGHT HERE.
LIEUTENANT,
I NEED TO TALK.
Cop: WHAT WAS THAT?
Second Cop: I DON'T KNOW.
First Cop: GO DOWN THERE
AND CHECK IT OUT RIGHT AWAY.
[ALARM BLARES]
Bob: HOW MANY TIMES
I GOTTA TELL YOU,
I DON'T WANT YOU
DRIVING THE TRUCK
ANYMORE.
THE DAMN THING'S
A DEATH TRAP.
SOMETHING'S GONNA
HAPPEN, I'M GONNA BE
HELD RESPONSIBLE.
YOU, RESPONSIBLE?
THAT IS A LAUGH.
HI, CHELSEA.
KOJI. HI.
WHAT THE HELL
IS A KOJI?
GET IN THE TRUCK.
HEY, HEY. JUST TAKE IT EASY
THERE, ALL RIGHT?
NOW.
ALL RIGHT.
[TELEPHONE DIAL TONE]
[DIALING BEEPS]
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
Answering Machine: HEY,
YOU'VE REACHED
JOE SNAPPER'S,
HOME OF THE MOST GLORIOUS
RED HOT LADIES IN
EXOTIC ENTERTAINMENT.
NOW HERE'S A LIST OF
TODAY'S LOVELY AND
TALENTED ARTISTS.
KATRINE, CINNAMON, SASSY,
CHERRY, FANCIA, SHASHA,
MISTY, CANDY, YVETTE,
STACI, SUNSHINE,  KISSY,
HONEYDEW AND BARB.
REMEMBER, NO COVER CHARGE,
TUESDAY THROUGH THURSDAY.
AND EVERY SUNDAY IS
LADIES' NIGHT.
WE'LL SEE YOU HERE.
ALL MODELS ARE OVER THE AGE
OF 18 AS REQUIRED
BY LAW.
HE'S NOT IN THE BUILDING.
WE HAVE AN APB OUT ON
HIS PARTNER WITH
THE SUITCASE, TOO.
AND WE ARE SEARCHING
THE VICINITY.
I KNEW THIS PASSPORT
WAS A FAKE.
I WANT THAT
SON OF A BITCH
AND I WANT HIM NOW!
YES, SIR.
[MUFFLED SCREAM]
OKAY, LAFAYETTE.
LET'S TRY IT ONE MORE TIME.
WHO DID KOJIMA SEND AND WHAT
DID THEY COME HERE TO DO?
[MUFFLED REPLY]
WE KNOW YOU SOLD THEM
THE METAL BRIEFCASE
AND WE'D LIKE TO KNOW
WHAT'S IN IT.
[MUFFLED REPLY]
YOU KNOW WHAT?
IF YOU DON'T START
TO OPEN UP A LITTLE BIT,
THINGS ARE GONNA GET UGLY
AROUND HERE.
[MUFFLED REPLY]
[SCREAMS]
THAT'S RIGHT.
CHECK THAT WATCH.
BECAUSE IN ABOUT
5 MINUTES
THIS WHOLE AREA IS
GONNA BE CRAWLING
WITH COPS.
WE HIT A ROADBLOCK,
YOU'RE AS GOOD
AS DEAD.
SO WHY DON'T YOU
JUST GIVE IT UP, PAL?
GIVE ME YOUR WALLET.
FINE, HERE,
TAKE THE WALLET.
LEATHER'S WORTH MORE
THAN WHAT'S INSIDE,
ANYWAY.
IS THIS YOUR ADDRESS?
NO, THAT'S OLD.
WE GOT AN APARTMENT
DOWNTOWN NOW.
IF WE DRIVE TO THIS APARTMENT
AND YOU'VE LIED TO ME
I WILL KILL YOU.
SOUNDS FAIR.
HE'S LYING.
THAT IS OUR ADDRESS.
WILL YOU JUST CHILL OUT
AND DO WHAT HE SAYS, BOB?
LISTEN UP, PAL.
YOU WANT TO GO
TO THE HOUSE, I'LL
TAKE YOU TO THE HOUSE.
I'LL DRIVE YOU ANYWHERE
YOU WANT TO GO.
BUT LET'S DROP
THE KID OFF FIRST.
NO.
YOU DON'T NEED HER.
WE'LL DROP HER OFF.
BOB, JUST SHUT UP.
HEY, YOU SHUT UP AND
STAY OUT OF THIS.
WILL YOU QUIT TRYING
TO PROTECT ME?
IT'S A LITTLE LATE FOR YOU
TO START ACTING LIKE
MY PARENT.
I TOLD YOU TO
SHUT UP, DIDN'T I?
IT'S ALL YOUR FAULT,
ANYWAY.
HOW THE HELL DO YOU
EVEN KNOW THIS GUY?
GUESS WHAT?
YOU MEET A LOT OF
VERY INTERESTING PEOPLE
ALWAYS BAILING YOUR FATHER
OUT OF JAIL.
OH, REALLY?
WHY DON'T YOU GO LIVE
WITH YOUR MOTHER AND
HER CPA BOYFRIEND
AND THE REST OF YOUR
PERFECT LITTLE
BROTHERS AND SISTERS?
I HATE YOU!
YOU'RE SUCH AN ASSHOLE!
WHY DON'T YOU JUST DO US
ALL A FAVOR
AND TAKE THIS TRUCK AND JUST
SMASH IT INTO A TREE
SOME NIGHT?
MAYBE I WILL.
OKAY. FINE.
GO AHEAD, CRY.
I'VE HEARD IT
BEFORE.
HEY, HEY, HEY, HEY.
EXCUSE ME, MISTER.
MISTER. HEY, WAIT UP, MISTER.
THINK YOU CAN HELP ME OUT
A LITTLE BIT HERE?
MAYBE A DOLLAR OR TWO,
WHATEVER YOU GOT.
NO.
HEY, EVEN A QUARTER
WOULD HELP. I AIN'T PICKY.
YOU KNOW, NO PROBLEM.
DO YOU KNOW WHERE
SEPULVEDA BOULEVARD IS?
SEPULVEDA? YEAH, YEAH.
SURE, I KNOW WHERE IT IS.
IT'S GONNA COST YOU, THOUGH.
A MAN'S GOTTA MAKE
A LIVING, YOU KNOW.
CHECK IT OUT.
IT'S MY LUCKY DAY.
IT'S A PENNY.
A PENNY HERE, AND PENNY THERE,
IT ALL ADDS UP.
YOU KNOW, PEOPLE DON'T
PICK UP PENNIES NO MORE.
I FIGURED IT OUT ONCE.
THE TIME YOU SPEND
PICKING UP A PENNY,
YOU'RE MAKING $18 AN HOUR.
THAT'S A DAMN GOOD WAGE
IF YOU'RE INTERESTED
IN WORKING.
YEAH, IT IS. FIND A DIME,
THAT'S $180 AN HOUR,
ALL RIGHT. I HAD A LAWYER ONCE,
HE DIDN'T MAKE THAT MUCH.
THAT NO-GOOD PECKERHEAD,
HE TURNED ME IN TO THE COPS.
CAN YOU BELIEVE THAT?
YOU EVER HEAR OF
ATTORNEY-CLIENT PRIVILEGE?
ALL RIGHT. THAT NO-GOOD
PECKERHEAD, YEAH, HE WAS.
I TOOK CARE OF HIM, THOUGH,
THAT SQUEALER.
THE SNITCH GETS STICHES.
WHOA, TAKE IT EASY THERE,
BUDDY.
SNITCHES GET STICHES.
YEAH, THEY DO.
NOW I GOTTA REPRESENT
MYSELF, THOUGH.
SEE, I'M SUING THE STATE
OF CALIFORNIA.
YEAH, YEAH. I'M SUING THEM.
TWO BOUNTY HUNTERS,
THEY DRUGGED MY ASS.
THEY DRUGGED MY ASS,
CAUSED BRAIN DAMAGE.
YOU MIGHT NOT KNOW IT
TO LOOK AT ME,
95% OF MY BRAIN
HAS BEEN DESTROYED.
YEAH, IT HAS.
GENTLEMEN, ACCORDING TO
THE RECENTLY DEPARTED
MR. LAFAYETTE,
2 JAPANESE LOWLIFES
ARE IN TOWN.
PROBABLY TO TAKE A SHOT
AT THE BOSS.
THE COPS HAD THIS ONE
IN CUSTODY BUT HE ESCAPED.
HIS PARTNER'S WALKING AROUND
WITH A METAL BRIEFCASE.
PUT OUT THE WORD.
FIND THEM.
BOY, IT SURE IS HOT, HUH?
I BEEN SWEATING BRICKS
ALL DAY.
I DON'T LET IT GET TO ME,
THOUGH.
YOU KNOW, YOU GO TO KEEP
AN OPTIMISTIC OUTLOOK.
MY GRANDMA ALWAYS USED TO SAY,
SMILES THROUGH TRIALS.
I BELIEVE IT.
YOU KNOW, THE MAN WITH THE GRIN
IS THE MAN WHO WILL WIN.
DON'T YOU THINK?
SEE YOU'RE CARRYING
THAT SUITCASE IN
YOUR LEFT HAND.
YEAH, I'M A LEFTY, TOO.
YOU KNOW, THEY SAY
THE LIFE SPAN OF
LEFT-HANDERS
IS 9 YEARS LESS THAN
NORMAL PEOPLE
AND LEFTIES ARE 5 TIMES
MORE LIKELY TO DIE
IN AN ACCIDENT.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
I BELIEVE IT.
YOU KNOW, I'M ALWAYS
GETTING INTO ACCIDENTS.
DON'T YOU BELIEVE THAT?
YES!
HEY, THAT'S A QUARTER.
THAT'S $450 AN HOUR.
CHECK IT OUT.
IT'S MY LUCKY DAY.
WAIT. ROLL THAT BACK.
HE WALKED RIGHT OUT
THE DOOR.
NOW WHERE THE HELL
WOULD THIS GUY GO?
COULD YOU MAKE IT
A LITTLE TIGHTER, PLEASE?
DO YOU HAVE A MAP OF THE CITY
AND A PHONE BOOK?
I THINK SO.
HEY. WHY ARE YOU
HOLDING US HERE?
YOU DON'T NEED US.
YOU COULD...
...LEAVE. YEAH,
YOU COULD TAKE MY TRUCK.
THE KEYS ARE RIGHT
IN MY POCKET. RIGHT THERE.
I'LL BE STAYING HERE
FOR THE NEXT FEW HOURS.
IF YOU DO WHAT I SAY,
I WON'T HARM YOU.
HEY, YOU KNOW WHAT?
IF YOU'RE JUST
KILLING TIME NOW,
WHY DON'T YOU GO GET
YOURSELF A MOTEL ROOM
OR SOMETHING?
HOW ABOUT THAT?
Chelsea: IT'S
DISCONNECTED.
WE HAVEN'T PAID
THAT BILL LATELY.
IF WE'RE JUST
GONNA SIT AROUND,
WOULD IT BE OKAY
IF I WENT AND
WATCHED TELEVISION?
HEY.
COME ON, MAN.
I'LL BE A GOOD BOY.
UNDO ME, HUH?
I'LL SIT HERE
REALLY QUIETLY, I PROMISE.
HOW ABOUT IT?
I WON'T SAY ANOTHER WORD.
COME ON.
[ROCK MUSIC PLAYS]
OH, NO!
OH, NO, YOU DON'T!
HEY! HEY!
I TOLD YOU A THOUSAND TIMES
I DO NOT WANT YOU TO WATCH
THAT GARBAGE IN MY HOUSE!
YOU CHANGE THAT CHANNEL
RIGHT NOW!
NO.
CHELSEA, I SAID
CHANGE THAT CHANNEL!
WE'RE NOT WATCHING
THAT GARBAGE!
SHUT UP, BOB.
YOU CHANGE THAT CHANNEL
RIGHT NOW, GIRL,
RIGHT THIS MINUTE!
NO!
HEY! DON'T YOU TELL ME NO!
CHANGE IT!
I SAID NO!
I SAID CHANGE IT,
CHANGE IT-
YOU SAY!
BE QUIET.
SHE STARTED IT.
AND I WILL END IT.
COME ON.
HEY, HEY, HEY,
DON'T GET ROUGH, BUDDY.
HEY, TAKE IT EASY!
Bob: CHELSEA, DON'T FIGHT.
JUST GO WITH HIM.
Bob: YOU'LL BE OKAY.
I'M RIGHT HERE.
MAKE SOME FOOD.
WHAT?
COOK.
OH.
OKAY.
I HAVE NO DESIRE
TO HURT EITHER OF YOU.
BUT YOU NEED TO BE
SEPARATED.
SORRY.
SOMETIMES I WONDER
WHY I PUSH HIM LIKE THAT.
NO ONE ELSE LIVES HERE?
NO BROTHERS OR SISTERS?
MY PARENTS ARE DIVORCED.
IT'S JUST ME AND HIM.
IT'S THE TRUTH.
LOOK AROUND. I MEAN,
WHY WOULD ANYBODY WANT
TO LIVE HERE?
I'M NOT EVEN SURE
WHY I'M HERE.
WHEN MY PARENTS SPLIT UP,
THE JUDGE GAVE US
A CHOICE, TOO.
MY BROTHERS AND SISTERS,
THE PICKED MY MOM.
IT ALMOST KILLED BOB.
EVERYBODY DESERTING HIM.
WHEN IT WAS MY TURN
TO CHOOSE,
I ENDED UP HERE.
MY MOM ... MY MOM
FREAKED OUT, TOO, BIG TIME.
WHAT CAN I SAY?
I KNOW IT WAS
THE WRONG CHOICE, BUT...
WELL, I FELT SORRY FOR HIM.
I MEAN, SOMEBODY
HAD TO TAKE CARE OF HIM.
I GUESS YOU THINK
THAT'S PRETTY STUPID OF ME, HUH?
DO YOU HAVE ANYTHING
TO DRINK?
WHERE WOULD THIS GUY GO?
DOES HE KNOW ANYBODY?
I GOTTA GO
CHECK SOMETHING OUT.
Thomas: I THINK HE'S
COMING AROUND.
Jimmy: HEY, GUY,
YOU ALL RIGHT?
WAIT. YOU SHOULDN'T
GET UP RIGHT NOW.
YOU'RE GONNA WANT
TO STAY STILL.
I KNEW THIS GUY ONE TIME,
HE BUSTED HIS NECK,
HE WALKED AROUND
FOR 2 WEEKS STRAIGHT
WITHOUT EVEN KNOWING IT.
HEY, DO YOU NEED HELP?
YOU WANT US TO GIVE YOU
A RIDE OR SOMETHING
TO THE HOSPITAL?
YES.
I NEED A RIDE.
THERE USED TO BE A LOT
MORE TO EAT AROUND HERE
THAN
MACARONI HELPER.
MY MOM'S A PRETTY GOOD COOK.
ARE YOU MARRIED?
NO.
[DOORBELL CHIMES]
Jimmy: JOE SNAPPER'S?
SURE THING, GUY.
BEEN THERE LOTS OF TIMES.
THAT'S WHERE I MET
MY OLD LADY.
SHE PRETTY MUCH
QUIT STRIPPING, THOUGH.
SHE MAKES MORE MONEY NOW
READING TAROT CARDS
IN THE NUDE
OVER AT
THE RENAISSANCE FAIR.
GET RID OF THEM.
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
COME ON, IT'S DUSSECQ.
NO KIDDING.
I NEED TO TALK TO YOU.
LOOK, I NEED
GO AWAY.
TO TALK TO YOU.
GO AWAY!
ARE YOU GONNA OPEN
THE DOOR OR WHAT?
SAY WHAT YOU WANT,
THEN GET OUT.
I SAW CHELSEA AT
THE PRECINCT THIS AFTERNOON.
SHE WAS TALKING
TO A JAPANESE MAN.
YOU KNOW ANYTHING
ABOUT THAT?
NO. WHY?
BECAUSE WE THINK THIS GUY IS
YAKUZA. HE BEAT UP WILLIAMS
PRETTY BAD.
IS THAT RIGHT?
LOOKS LIKE YOU GOT
YOUR NOSE STUCK IN
THE MIDDLE OF IT, TOO.
WHERE'S CHELSEA, BOB?
AT WORK.
WHEN'S SHE GONNA
BE HOME?
LATER. I'LL HAVE HER
CALL YOU.
YOU DO THAT.
I WILL.
IS THAT ALL?
YEAH, THAT'S IT.
FINE. GET LOST,
ASSHOLE.
WATCH YOUR TEMPER,
MALONE.
THAT'S WHAT GOT YOU
IN FRONT OF INTERNAL AFFAIRS.
OH, YEAH?
THAT'S REVISIONIST
HISTORY HERE, PAL.
IS THAT SO?
YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
YOU NEEDED A SCAPEGOAT
AND YOU HUNG ME OUT
TO DRY.
THE DEPARTMENT
WON'T PAY YOUR PENSION.
BUT THEY MIGHT COVER THERAPY.
LOOK INTO IT.
[PHONE BEEPS]
HE'S THERE.
WE'LL GET HIM.
[PHONE BEEPS]
I DATED A WAITRESS ONCE.
NO, YOU DIDN'T.
STANDING IN A BAR
WHERE SHE WORKS
IS NOT A DATE.
SO? I ONCE TIPPED HER
A 5-SPOT WITH MY
PHONE NUMBER ON IT.
DID SHE CALL YOU?
NO, BUT THERE WERE 6 OR 7
HANG-UPS ON MY ANSWERING
MACHINE.
REALLY? YOU THINK
IT WAS HER?
OF COURSE. WHO ELSE
WOULD IT HAVE BEEN?
WHY DO YOU DO THIS?
YOU KNOW YOU DON'T HAVE TO
DO THIS.
I'M NOT GONNA DO ANYTHING.
I'LL BE A GOOD BOY.
COME ON, MAN,
I'LL BEHAVE MYSELF.
WHY DON'T YOU JUST UNDO ME?
NO, YOU MUST
SIT THIS OUT.
OKAY. LET'S SEE IF WE CAN
GET YOU TO ANSWER
A FEW QUESTIONS.
LIKE WHAT THE HELL IS
A YAKUZA DOING IN MY HOUSE?
BOB, BE CAREFUL!
EVERYTHING'S FINE.
COME ON, OUT WITH IT,
TOUGH GUY.
YOU KNOW THAT COP THAT
WAS JUST HERE? DUSSECQ?
HE MAY BE DUMB BUT
HE AIN'T STUPID.
HE KNOWS SOMETHING'S UP.
MY DAUGHTER NEVER HAD
A JOB IN HER LIFE.
SO BEFORE THE BIG BOYS
GET HERE TO STOMP
YOUR ASS,
I'D ADVISE YOU TO TAKE
MY QUESTIONS SERIOUSLY.
OTHERWISE YOU
AIN'T GONNA HAVE
AN ASS TO STOMP!
YOU HEAR ME?
HOW ABOUT IT?
YOU'RE JUST SO COOL,
AREN'T YOU?
WELL
SAYONARA, KOJI.
NO, BOB, DON'T!
I HAD NO CHOICE.
I HAD TO ESCAPE.
YOU WERE MY OPPORTUNITY.
THAT'S A GOOD START.
NOW WHAT DOES DUSSECQ
WANT WITH YOU?
I DON'T KNOW.
THAT'S NOT GOOD ENOUGH!
DAD, LOOK!
COME ON, PRETTY BOY.
LET'S GO. UP YOU GO!
Bob: FRIENDS OF YOURS?
DELORENZO.
HOW DOES HE
KNOW I'M HERE?
RUDY DELORENZO?
YEAH.
WHAT THE HELL'S
THE MOB GOT TO DO WITH THIS?
HE TOLD THEM I WAS HERE.
WHO?
DUSSECQ.
THAT'S BULL!
YOU SAID IT YOURSELF.
HE KNOWS I'M HERE.
HE'S THE ONLY ONE.
NO ONE WILL
LEAVE HERE ALIVE.
IF YOU DON'T LET ME
HELP YOU, WE ALL DIE.
DAD, THEY'RE COMING!
[DOOR BATTERING]
DECIDE QUICKLY.
CHELSEA, COME HERE!
STAY DOWN!
[CELL PHONE RINGS]
[INDISTINCT VOICES]
YEAH?
RINGO, WHEN YOU FINISH UP,
TAKE THEM TO THE SHOP.
DUSSECQ!
MALONE? WELL,
THIS IS UNFORTUNATE.
YEAH, ISN'T IT?
LET ME GUESS.
WRONG NUMBER?
DO YOURSELF A FAVOR,
MALONE.
SEND THE JAP OUT.
AND I'LL THINK ABOUT
LETTING YOU LIVE.
OH, YEAH?
LET ME ASK YOU SOMETHING.
YOU BEEN WITH THE MOB
THIS WHOLE TIME?
YOU SET ME UP BEFORE, TOO,
DIDN'T YOU?
IN THAT CASE, WHY DON'T YOU
JUST COME ON OVER HERE
SO I CAN KICK YOUR ASS?
YOU GOT A LOT BIGGER
PROBLEM RIGHT NOW.
MALONE, DO THE SMART THING
FOR ONCE IN YOUR LIFE.
AND THEN WHAT? PRETEND
LIKE THIS NEVER HAPPENED?
I DON'T THINK SO.
I'M FAMILIAR WITH THE MAFIA,
REMEMBER?
I THINK YOU KNOW HOW
THIS IS GONNA END UP.
THAT'S WHY I CAN SAY THIS
WITH SUCH RELISH.
YOU ARE A PATHETIC LOSER.
GO TO HELL.
WHAT IS GOING ON?
STAY IN THIS TUB
NO MATTER WHAT.
THE SAFETY'S OFF.
USE IT ONLY IF
YOU HAVE TO.
TODAY IN THE TRUCK?
I DIDN'T MEAN ANY
OF THAT STUFF.
I KNOW. ME, NEITHER.
STAY IN THIS ROOM.
YOU HEAR ME?
LET'S GO!
THERE'S GO TO BE ONE
GOOD COP IN THIS CITY.
NO POLICE!
HEY! WE NEED HELP,
YOU STUPID ASSHOLE!
NO POLICE!
WE NEED HELP!
GO!
DROP YOUR GUN!
NO, YOU DROP IT!
SHOOT THE KID, JOEY.
SCREW YOU! I SAID
PUT YOUR GUNS DOWN!
HOLD ON, HOLD ON,
HOLD ON.
WE GIVE UP.
WE QUIT. YOU WIN.
Jimmy: YOU KNOW, SOMETIMES
YOU JUST HAVE TO WEAR
A PLAIN WHITE T-SHIRT.
IT'S UNDERSTATED.
CHICKS DIG IT.
WHAT? WHO TOLD YOU THAT?
A GIRL.
A GIRL?
GROW UP, MAN.
MY OLD LADY?
NOW, SHE IS A WOMAN.
HEY, WE MISSED A TURN.
HEY, JIMMY, OUR LITTLE
BUDDY BACK HERE SAYS
WE MESSED UP.
OH, WELL, HE MUST BE
KIDDING, TOMMY.
WE AIN'T DONE
NOTHING WRONG.
MR. DELORENZO ASKED US
TO FIND THIS GUY AND
BRING HIM IN.
AND THAT'S EXACTLY
WHAT WE'RE DOING.
RIGHT. AND WE GOT
A NICE, COMFORTABLE CHAIR
WAITING FOR YOU, PAL.
[COUNTRY MUSIC PLAYS]
MISERABLE SON OF A BITCH!
Chelsea: DAD, PLEASE!
PLEASE STOP!
DAD, STOP!
YOU, STUPID, STUPID,
STUPID-
PLEASE JUST STOP!
GET OFF HIM!
LEAVE HIM ALONE!
PLEASE,LISTEN TO ME!
IT'S ENOUGH, OKAY?
JUST STOP!
YOU REALIZE WHAT
YOU'VE DONE?
DO YOU?
YOU SEE THIS KID? HUH?
YOU KILLED HER.
THAT'S RIGHT.
YOU PUT US IN THE MIDDLE
OF YOUR STINKING
LITTLE WAR
AND NOW WE'RE STUCK HERE
WITH YOU.
WE'RE ALL DEAD!
AS LONG AS DELORENZO'S
STILL ALIVE, WE ARE DEAD!
I CAN CHANGE THAT.
OH, YEAH?
AND HOW ARE YOU
GONNA DO THAT?
FIRST, WE BUY SOME TIME.
THEN WE GO MEET SOMEBODY.
[STRIP MUSIC PLAYS]
YOU MAKE A MISTAKE,
YOU KNOW WHAT'S GONNA HAPPEN.
IT'S ALL UP TO YOU.
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
YEAH.
IT'S FINISHED.
CLEAN?
WE TOOK CARE OF
ALL THREE.
MR. DELORENZO WILL BE
VERY HAPPY.
HIDEO.
HIDEO?
THIS YOUR SOMEBODY?
HE DON'T LOOK TOO GOOD.
SORRY ABOUT YOUR FRIEND.
SO, WHAT DO WE DO NOW,
PARTNER?
WE?
NO.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN, NO?
YOU MUST TAKE CARE
OF YOUR DAUGHTER.
I APPRECIATE THE THOUGHT.
BUT IF I'M GONNA SAVE
MY KID,
I GOTTA MAKE SURE
DELORENZO CAN NEVER
GET TO US AGAIN.
I WILL TAKE CARE OF IT
FOR YOU.
UM-MMM. NOT A CHANCE.
YOU SEE, UNFORTUNATELY
I'M IN THIS THING
TOO DEEP.
THERE'S NO WAY YOU'RE
GONNA GET RID OF ME NOW.
AND IF YOU TRY,
I'LL JUST HAVE TO
GO SEE DELORENZO
ON MY OWN.
MAYBE SHOW UP AT THE
EXACT SAME TIME YOU DO,
SCREW UP
YOUR LITTLE PLAN.
PROBABLY GET YOU KILLED,
NOT TO MENTION MYSELF.
YOU WOULD DO THAT?
THAT I WOULD DO.
THERE'S JUST
ONE MORE THING.
CHELSEA.
MAYBE YOU CAN GET
SOMEBODY TO KEEP
AN EYE ON HER.
TILL WE GET BACK.
I ... I GOTTA GO SOMEWHERE.
AND KOJI'S GOT A FRIEND
THAT'S GONNA KEEP AN EYE
ON YOU TILL I GET BACK.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
GONNA SEE SOME PEOPLE.
I DON'T WANT TO STAY HERE
BY MYSELF.
I WANT TO GO WITH YOU.
LOOK, I'M SORRY,
BUT YOU HAVE TO STAY.
WHY?
BECAUSE.
BECAUSE WHY?
JUST BECAUSE, THAT'S WHY.
NOW STOP, PLEASE.
DAD.
I'M SCARED.
YEAH. ME, TOO.
COME HERE.
[TRAIN CHUGS]
[TRAIN WHISTLE BLOWS]
[METAL CASE CLANGS]
NO THANKS. I'M NOT HERE
FOR THE MONEY.
WHOA.
PRETTY FANCY HARDWARE
YOU GOT HERE, PARTNER.
P2-28, 9 MILL,
15 IN THE CLIP.
ONE IN THE CHAMBER.
YEAH. SHE'LL DO.
YOU WEREN'T PLANNING ON
LETTING THIS GUY
JUST WALK AWAY FROM
THIS WHOLE PARTY,
WERE YOU?
NOT WITHOUT MY PERMISSION.
YEAH. HERE.
WHAT THE HELL.
IF YOU DON'T KILL A GUY
WHEN HE'S OUT OF LINE,
HOW ELSE YOU GONNA LEARN,
RIGHT?
CHEERS.
THIS BELONGS TO YOU.
THANKS.
CHELSEA. BEFORE SHE WAS
A BRAT.
HEY.
RIGHT ON TIME.
GOOD PREDICTION.
HE'S A SLAVE TO HIS HABITS.
THAT'S WHAT MAKES HIM
AN EASY TARGET.
YEAH, WELL...
IT LOOKS LIKE THE ONLY WAY
TO PUT A BULLET IN
THIS GUY'S HEART
IS THROUGH HIS STOMACH.
ALL RIGHT.
LET'S GO PUT THE FAT GUY
ON A DIET.
HEY, LIEUTENANT.
SO WHAT'S THE STORY?
WELL, WE GOT A TOTAL OF
8 BODIES, ALL CAUCASIANS.
WHAT ABOUT MALONE
AND HIS DAUGHTER?
IT'S KIND OF STRANGE.
THERE'S NO SIGN OF
THEM ANYWHERE.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
ARE YOU CERTAIN?
YEAH. COUNT THEM YOURSELF.
WE GOT ONE RIGHT HERE,
ONE RIGHT THERE,
3 INSIDE, 2 IN THE KITCHEN,
AND-
ALL RIGHT. BEFORE
WE GO IN HERE, I WANT
TO ASK YOU SOMETHING.
IF I DON'T COME OUT
OF THIS, CHELSEA'S
YOUR RESPONSIBILITY.
ALL RIGHT?
YEAH.
MAKE SURE SHE
GETS AWAY SAFELY.
MAYBE TAKE HER
TO HER MOM.
NOW SHE AIN'T GONNA
WANT TO GO,
BUT THAT'S GONNA BE
YOUR PROBLEM.
OKAY?
AGREED.
I ALSO WANT SOMETHING
FROM YOU, BOB.
NAME IT.
I WANT TO ASK YOU TO DO
SOMETHING FOR MY FRIEND.
YOU GOT IT.
WHATEVER IT IS,
IT'LL GET DONE.
YOU GOT MY WORD ON IT.
WHAT IS IT?
POLICE EMERGENCY.
THIS IS CHELSEA MALONE.
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO
SEND SOMEONE DOWN TO
THE CIAO AMICO RESTAURANT.
HI, CHELSEA.
YOUR DAD ISN'T HERE TODAY.
I KNOW. THIS ISN'T
ABOUT MY DAD.
THIS IS ABOUT
LIEUTENANT DUSSECQ.
HE WORKS FOR SOME GUY
NAMED RUDY DELORENZO-
LIEUTENANT DUSSECQ
ISN'T HERE RIGHT NOW, EITHER.
I KNOW. YOU'RE GONNA
HAVE TO SEND SOMEONE ELSE.
CHELSEA, I'LL TELL
LIEUTENANT DUSSECQ
THAT YOU CALLED.
I GOTTA - THE OTHER PHONES
ARE GOING - I HAVE TO
ANSWER, OKAY? GOODBYE.
POLICE EMERGENCY.
I CAN'T TALK TO YOU
ABOUT THE CAT RIGHT NOW, HONEY.
WELL, GIVE HER ANOTHER PILL
AND BLOW IN HER FACE.
I HAVE TO GO. OKAY.
I LOVE YOU -
POLICE EMERGENCY.
Bob: WHOA, WHOA, WHOA.
TAKE IT EASY, GUYS.
RELAX. BRING IT DOWN
A COUPLE OF NOTCHES.
TAKE IT EASY.  I EVEN
BROUGHT SOME BEER.
I'VE GO TO TALK TO
DELORENZO.
MR. DELORENZO SAYS
YOU ARE DISTURBING HIM.
HE'S GOT A MESSAGE.
MR. DELORENZO DOES NOT
TAKE MESSAGES DURING MEALS.
[CELL PHONE RINGS]
EXCUSE ME.
YEAH.
MALONE AND THE JAP
ARE STILL ALIVE.
WE KNOW.
THEY'RE STANDING HERE
IN FRONT OF US.
YOU HANG UP ON ME?
YOU SON OF A BITCH!
MR. DELORENZO.
YOU HAVE VIOLATED
YOUR BUSINESS AGREEMENT
WITH MASAO KOJIMA.
AND HE DEMANDS
COMPLETE RESTITUTION.
IF YOU DON'T AGREE,
I WILL KILL YOU.
LET ME TELL YOU SOMETHING.
WE OWE MR. KOJIMA NOTHING.
THIS INTERVIEW IS OVER.
THESE GENTLEMEN WILL
SHOW YOU THE DOOR.
Bob: NO, NO, NO, NO.
HOLD IT.
TAKE IT EASY. TIME OUT.
YOU BOYS JUST DON'T
SEEM TO GET IT, DO YOU?
MY FRIEND HERE HAS
SOMETHING TO SAY TO YOU.
IF YOU GIVE US JUST
A LITTLE BIT OF
YOUR TIME,
WE'LL BE OUT OF
YOUR HAIR. OKAY?
GOOD.
GO ON, KOJI.
LAY IT ON THEM.
SECONDLY, LEAVE BOB MALONE'S
DAUGHTER, CHELSEA, ALONE.
WHAT'S THE OTHER ONE?
AND THIRD. DUSSECQ.
YOU CAN SAY
YOUR GOODBYES,
'CAUSE HE'S MINE.
YOU WILL LEAVE. NOW.
I DON'T THINK THEY
LIKE YOU.
I GET A LOT
OF COMPLAINTS.
I DON'T THINK SO,
CHELSEA.
NO, NO, NO, NO.
NO, NO, NO.
NICE AND EASY.
ALL RIGHT.
WAIT A MINUTE.
LET'S TALK.
I UNDERSTAND
HOW THIS WORKS.
IT'S A NEGOTIATION.
YOU GUYS GO HIGH,
I GO LOW.
WE KILL A FEW OF YOUR GUYS,
YOU KILL A FEW OF MY GUYS.
THEN WE COME TO
A SETTLEMENT.
I LIKE YOU GUYS.
YOU'RE STAND-UP
KIND OF GUYS.
SO WHAT'S
THE NEXT STEP HERE?
WHAT DO WE DO?
THERE SEEMS TO BE
ONE LITTLE PROBLEM.
WHAT'S THAT?
I WANT TO KNOW WHAT
I CAN HELP YOU WITH.
'CAUSE I CONSIDER
YOU BOYS PARTNERS.
AND I CONSIDER MY PARTNERS
LIKE FAMILY.
ACTUALLY,
IT'S FAIRLY SIMPLE.
KOJI HERE'S JUST GOTTA
FIGURE OUT A WAY TO GET
YOUR HEAD THROUGH CUSTOMS.
TELL YOU WHAT.
I'LL GIVE YOU DUSSECQ.
NO PROBLEM.
AND I WANT YOU TO APOLOGIZE
TO MR. KOJIMA FOR ME.
TELL HIM
I'LL BE HAPPY TO SPEED
THOSE SHIPMENTS ALONG.
THERE'S NO NEED
TO APOLOGIZE.
DROP THE GUN, MALONE.
YOU, TOO.
WHAT, ARE YOU
HARD OF HEARING?
THAT'S IT.
HEY, BOYS, I'M SORRY
I'M LATE TO THE PARTY.
KILL THEM. QUICK!
SHUT UP!
YOU DOUBLE-CROSSING
PIECE OF SCUM.
I HEARD YOU
GIVE ME UP.
TAKE IT EASY, DUSSECQ.
I WOULD NEVER GIVE YOU UP.
I WAS JUST BUYING TIME.
WE'RE PARTNERS.
YEAH, WELL, LET ME
MAKE THIS CLEAR.
I HOPE YOU ENJOYED
YOUR MEAL.
'CAUSE IT WAS YOUR LAST!
[GUNSHOT]
GO AHEAD AND SHOOT.
AT LEAST I'LL DIE
KNOWING I WAS RIGHT ABOUT YOU.
YOU'RE GONNA DIE,
ALL RIGHT.
STOP IT!
CHELSEA!
I SAID DROP THAT GUN!
CHELSEA! SHOOT HIM!
LISTEN TO YOUR FATHER
FOR ONCE IN YOUR LIFE
AND SHOOT HIM!
Dussecq: YOU'LL NEVER
SHOOT ME, CHELSEA.
DON'T MOVE!
Dussecq: GO AHEAD.
BEFORE YOU PULL THAT TRIGGER
I'M GONNA SPLATTER HIS BRAINS
ALL OVER THIS FLOOR.
SO GO AHEAD, SHOOT ME!
COME ON. PULL THE TRIGGER,
CHELSEA. COME ON.
SHOOT ME.
THAT'S A GOOD GIRL.
NOW, YOUR TIME'S COMING,
BUT FIRST, YOU'RE GONNA
WATCH YOUR DAUGHTER DIE.
BOB!
COME ON. LET'S GO.
[POLICE SIRENS WAIL]
[MUSIC PLAYS]
WELL, IF NOTHING ELSE,
I HOPE YOU LEARNED
YOUR LESSON ABOUT
TALKING TO STRANGERS.
[MUSIC PLAYS]
Radio: THAT ONE'S CALLED
MEMPHIS SUN.
NOW HERE'S
AN INTERESTING NOTE.
THIS MORNING, CARETAKERS AT
THE ELVIS PRESLEY ESTATE
FOUND A WHITE ASH SPRINKLED
OVER KING'S GRAVE.
FACT BEING STRANGER
THAN FICTION,
IT TURNED OUT TO BE
THE CREMATED REMAINS
OF A HUMAN BODY.
NOW, SOME ELVIS EXPERTS ARE
CLAIMING IT TO BE NONE OTHER
THAN THE KING HIMSELF,
RETURNING TO GRACELAND
FOR ONE LAST TIME.
IS ELVIS FINALLY GONE?
WELL, YOU BE THE JUDGE.
THIS ONE'S CALLED
SOME YOU WIN, SOME YOU LOSE.
♪ SHE WAS SITTING BY THE BAND
WHEN I FIRST SAW HER ♪
♪ SHE HAD LONG TAN LEGS
AND LONG BLACK SHINY HAIR ♪
♪ WELL I SAW HER
LOOK MY WAY ♪
[ROCK MUSIC PLAYS]
Bob: DO YOU MIND
CHANGING THAT BACK,
PLEASE?
Chelsea: UH-HUH. AS SOON
AS IT'S OVER.
[COUNTRY MUSIC PLAYS]
SORRY. YOU DON'T WANT
TO LISTEN TO ANY OF
THAT GARBAGE IN THIS TRUCK.
PUT IT BACK.
LET ME LISTEN TO SOMETHING
THAT I WANT TO LISTEN TO
FOR ONCE.
DON'T TOUCH IT.
[ROCK MUSIC PLAYS]
IT'S MY TRUCK, MY MUSIC.
[COUNTRY MUSIC PLAYS]
[ROCK MUSIC PLAYS]
♪ AS I LOOKED INTO THOSE EYES
THAT SEEMED SO WILLING ♪
♪ I RECALLED THE WORDS
MY DADDY ONCE TOLD TO ME ♪
♪ WELL THERE'S SOME YOU WIN,
BOY, THEN SOME YOU LOSE ♪
♪ AND SOME THAT GET
RAINED OUT ♪
♪ THERE'S THEM THAT PLEASE
AND THEM THAT TEASE ♪
♪ AND THEM THAT'D RATHER
DO WITHOUT ♪
♪ A MAN NEVER KNOWS
WHICH WAY TO GO ♪
♪ OR WHAT A LADY'S ALL ABOUT
♪ THERE'S SOME YOU WIN, BOY,
AND THEN SOME YOU LOSE ♪
♪ AND SOME THAT GET RAINED OUT
♪ WELL WE DANCED A WHILE AND
I KNEW I WAS WINNING ♪
♪ I COULD FEEL THE FIRE
A-BURNING HOT INSIDE ♪
♪ YEAH THEN THE COURAGE CAME
SO I TOOK HER HAND
AND I ASKED HER ♪
♪ IF IN THE MORNING I'D
FIND HER LYING BY MY SIDE ♪
♪ YEAH SHE SMILED AND BLUSHED
AS IF THE THOUGHT WAS PLEASING ♪
♪ AND I KNEW MY DESIRES WOULD
SOON BE REALITY ♪
♪ YEAH BUT IN A FLASH SHE
TURNED HER CHARM THE OTHER WAY ♪
♪ AND SHE SAID THE SAME THING
MY DADDY ONCE TOLD TO ME ♪
♪ WELL THERE'S SOME YOU WIN,
BOY, AND THERE'S SOME YOU LOSE ♪
♪ AND SOME THAT GET
RAINED OUT ♪
♪ THERE'S THEM THAT PLEASE
AND THEM THAT TEASE ♪
♪ AND THEM WHO'D RATHER
DO WITHOUT ♪
♪ A MAN NEVER KNOWS
WHICH WAY TO GO ♪
♪ OR WHAT A LADY'S
ALL ABOUT ♪
♪ THERE'S SOME YOU WIN, BOY,
THERE'S SOME YOU LOSE ♪
♪ AND SOME THAT
GET RAINED OUT ♪
♪ WELL, THERE'S SOME YOU WIN,
BOY, AND SOME YOU LOSE ♪
♪ AND SOME THAT
GET RAINED OUT ♪♪
♪ HEY THERE, MOURNING LADY
♪ DON'T YOU BE SO BLUE
♪ I'M THE RAINBOW MAKER
♪ I'M HERE TO RESCUE YOU
♪ SO PUT ON A SMILE
DRY UP ALL THOSE TEARS
OH YEAH ♪
♪ DON'T WORRY BECAUSE
THE RAINBOW MAKER'S HERE ♪
♪ YEAH YOU KNOW THE SKY
IS CLOUDY ♪
♪ DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO
YEAH. I DON'T GIVE A RAT'S ASS
WHAT THE MAYOR WANTS.
YOU CAN TELL - I'LL TELL HIM
MYSELF.
YEAH, YOU CAN-
[PHONE RINGS]
HELLO. YEAH, I'M JUST
CLEANING THE OFFICE.
I'LL BE RIGHT THERE.
♪ WELL I GOT ME
A TECHNIQUE ♪
♪ HONEY IT AIN'T NEVER
FAILED ME YET ♪
♪ GUARANTEED TO DRIVE AWAY
DARK CLOUDS OF LONELINESS ♪
♪ I'M THE RAINBOW MAKER ♪