- I have this
reoccurring dream
where I'm cooking pasta.
When it's ready, when the
time comes to drain the water,
I can't bring myself
to let go of the water.
I don't want to drain the water,
I wanna keep all the water.
It's just hot water, just
hot, murky, pasta water.
And I think it means
I'm afraid of letting go
of something I don't need
anymore.
I don't know why.
- You have
two new voice messages.
- Hey, hon,
hope the flight was okay,
and the pills weren't
too strong in the end.
Let me know how the meeting
goes.
Erm, call me soon so I can
tell you how badass you are.
I promise, promise the
weekend's gonna fly by, okay?
Love you, Pat.
- Next new message.
- PS, all the hotels on
your list
were fully booked, but I
managed to get you a room
at a boutique hotel just outside
of town.
Hope it's okay. Love you, Pat.
It's Taylor, by the way.
- Hi, do you have a booking with
us?
- Yes.
- First room on the right.
- Are you kidding me?
This room is ugly.
- Hello, excuse me!
I didn't hear anyone arrive.
I'm sorry about that, I was
loud,
but I didn't see anyone come in.
Hello!
Hello.
Is anyone in there?
I'm sorry about the noise, I
didn't know anyone was here.
I'll leave you to it.
- Can I help you?
- You?
- Hello.
- What are you doing here?
Are you all right? Did
you know I was here?
I kind of live here.
- You live here!
Of all the places? I'm
just staying in this hotel.
- I can't believe it,
the last I heard you
were living in America.
- Hello!
Idris, Idris!
Idris!
- Hey, hi!
- Guess what?
- What?
- I fucking did it!
- I knew you would.
- I'm a writer now!
- Sh!
- Oh, shit, sorry.
- Come and tell me downstairs,
tell me everything.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
- Well, I mean, it was good,
she literally got me to
do a bit of like a dance
and a bit of a thing.
- Yeah.
- And literally gave me
the job there and then,
because the thing that I
couldn't be dealing with,
is two weeks of like did I get
it.
- No.
- Did I not get it?
- No, no.
- Hey, hey, you okay?
And like, she told me there
and then like, you know,
you've fucking got the part.
I mean, it's amazing.
- Amazing, totally.
- I literally couldn't have
wished for anything better.
Be excited for me, be happy for
me.
- Totally excited, this is
amazing.
- Yeah?
- Yeah, of course I am.
- It could've just gone on for
ages
or they could've been like-
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, ssh!
- What do you mean, shush?
- No, no, I don't mean...
I don't mean.
I don't mean shit.
- What are you thinking?
- Not shush, shush, shush.
- I'm so excited.
- I know.
- Are you not excited for me?
- I'm so excited.
- Oh, my God, you know where she
saw me?
The casting director?
- No.
- She saw me
in that fucking gig in
Manchester.
- Yeah.
- That terrible gig.
- No, you're kidding.
- Yeah, apparently,
and she was just like, I
remember
seeing you that night and-
- Great.
- You were just like, electric
and like, dynamic.
The gig that you told me
was like the first time,
that you were like, oh, no,
I actually like this girl.
That's the gig that she came to
see,
so clearly I was like
exuding amazing energy
that night or something.
And then it was cool, because
that they actually had me do
in the end with a guy.
- A guy?
- So they cast, they got the
cast in so as to do it with me.
But he was quite good actually.
- Yeah.
- You don't feel well?
- No, I feel really
good, I think I'm just...
I think I'm just excited about
everything you're telling me.
- Oh, yeah, did anyone come?
- Where?
- What do you mean, where?
Here. What have you been doing?
- So you arrived there and
then you were in a big room,
there's a stage?
- What? No.
- It's just like a regular room?
- It's like a
rehearsal room.
- It looks like a regular room.
- Yeah, it was-
- How many people
were in there, like, there's
three people in there?
- Did the guests arrive?
- I was tryna set up the decks.
- Right, so you
were doing your fucking thing,
the one thing I asked you to
do--
- No, the electricity went.
- No.
- Hear me out.
- No, I get it, you were
setting up the decks.
I'll check the books.
- No, no, the music was really
loud. Louis, so this is--
- If anyone's here, it'll be in
this book.
- This is the thing and
this is what you think.
- What are you doing? I need
to see if someone's here.
- The thing is that this
is what the thing is.
- Oh, my...
Someone is here, I told you
before--
- I've got to tell you
something. People...
History, time.
- What the...
- Old time.
- Oh, I'm sorry, two seconds,
I've been meaning to...
Hi.
- Here's hoping, I am tired.
- Sir, excuse me.
- Louise, wait.
I'm so lucky to have found you.
No, are...
You're just amazing.
My ex-wife is upstairs.
- What?
- Yeah.
There, that's her.
- Wow!
- Yeah.
I thought you'd invited her
but then I wondered why
you would even do that,
but then I realised that would
be crazy.
- That would be insane.
- You wouldn't do that.
- I would never, why?
- So she's just here.
- Because?
- She's a guest,
she happens to be a guest.
- She happens to be a guest.
- It's a coincidence.
I haven't seen her for 10
years, I haven't spoken either.
I haven't spoken to her.
- Does she know you have a
girlfriend?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. No, I
said--
- So it's not gonna be weird,
she's not gonna be like,
oh, who are you there?
- She's not here to see me.
- Well, no.
- She's not come looking for me.
- Right.
- She's...
- She's just here.
- Was it awkward when,
when you spoke to her?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, I can't really explain
what it was like. It was...
She's, she's an ex but I love
you.
- Right, did you tell-
- I'm so happy
you got that role, though,
it's amazing, yeah.
- You have two saved
messages.
- Hey, hon,
hope the flight was okay
and the pills weren't
too strong in the end.
Let me know how the meeting
goes.
- I, erm, feel a bit
underdressed.
- You look great.
- You look great and I like the-
- Well, I thought, you know-
- You thought?
- It's my 40th coming up.
- All right, yeah.
- I just...
Well, I thought I'd make a
bit of an effort for dinner.
- For dinner?
- For dinner.
- Yeah.
Hello.
- Patricia, this is Louise.
- Hi.
- I've got on
oatmealy hands, but hi.
- It's okay, I'm, I'm sorry,
I don't mean to interrupt.
I just thought, erm, since
my phone isn't working,
if you could, if I could borrow
a phone
just to call a taxi to get some
dinner or-
- Yeah, definitely.
- There doesn't seem to be
any self-service here, so-
- I mean, absolutely,
but I'm cooking dinner.
- No, no, I don't wanna
trouble you at all.
- I'd like it if
you'd stay, if you wanted to.
- Yeah, why not?
- I'm aware of how acutely
uncomfortable the situation is.
- Oh!
- Not at all.
- No, not at all.
- No.
- Listen, I'm
glad you said something
but it's fine.
- It's just, it's just
an incredible coincidence.
- Yes, it's fine.
Louise, it's fine,
please, you can come in.
I mean, only if you want to,
if you wanna go out you can go
out,
but, I mean, I'm making
enough bolognese for-
- It smells delicious.
- So please.
We were supposed to have a
nice couple of days
and damn life happens
and Idris' ex-wife,
Patricia, comes to stay.
They haven't seen each
other in a long time,
in like 10 years, so they need
time to catch up, I guess.
But in the time being,
erm, it'll be all good.
We'll have a lovely birthday
and, erm, like my mum always
said to me,
resentment is the poison you
drink
while you're waiting for
the other person to die.
- So Louise, she's really
lovely.
- Yeah.
- Seems like
she's been a good influence,
you're not drinking.
- I feel great,
I feel really good.
- I can see that, you look good.
- I need to stop, we're having
fun,
we're having a great time.
- Now I'm gonna feel really bad
when I get you to start
drinking.
- No, I couldn't imagine.
So what d'you, what
d'you do, what d'you do?
- I travel and I make
television.
- You make television?
- It's amazing, I love it.
- I'm still playing, by the way,
you didn't ask how I'm doing,
but I'll tell you anyway.
- You're playing?
- Yeah.
- That's good.
- Still doing music.
- Are you still
writing songs about me?
Might be.
- So you're
doing the same thing?
I'm a bit disappointed.
- Hi, how are you
getting on with the menu?
- Good, actually.
- Could I have a look
at what you've got?
- Yeah, I mean, to be honest...
I wanted to show you my notes.
- Yeah.
- Erm, and there's no fish on
the menu,
so I was thinking we could put
some--
- Classic scampi and chip
on the dinner there go,
gets a lot of compliments.
- I just feel like we
should incorporate fish
into the menu in...
Well, if we switch out the
Caesar salad
for like a tuna swirl or
something.
- What about sort of kipper?
- A kipper kip?
- Okay, I can do kipper.
- Boil a kipper.
- Er, boil a kipper.
Mm, what do I like just fresh
fish but it's lemon salt-
- Like a battered cod. That I
can do.
- See, that's sort of exactly
the opposite
of what I was saying.
I said fit, I want something
healthy,
something nourishing my soul.
My soul needs a little bit of
love
bit of nourishment and healthy
energy.
So I'm gonna say it's healthy
fish,
bit of salt, bit of lemon,
bit of olive oil, done, fish.
- I'm not sure.
- Not sure.
Okay, I'm gonna make it really
easy then.
I'm sure and I want sea bass.
So what we're gonna
have is sea bass, okay?
- What is she doing?
- It's a nice way to wake up
actually, bang, bang, bang!
- Stop it.
Morning.
- Morning, you're pissy, Idris.
- Shut up.
- Hi.
- You're up already?
- Yeah.
- What are you doing?
- What's it look like
I'm doing? I'm thinking.
- Can you think without the
ball?
- That's how I think.
- Do you want to use another
wall?
You might break a window.
- No, no, no, I hit
the window,
they're not breakable.
- It's glass.
- I'm coming down.
- No, no, don't bother.
- Hi.
She blew me a kiss,
she just blew me a fucking kiss.
If she offers again to
get a taxi and leave,
you know the answer this time,
yeah?
- Oh, I'll take a nap.
- Feeling a bit better
to say?
You're disgusting.
- You're impossible.
♪ This is one is taking you
on, this one is taking you ♪
♪ do where you do where you
wanna be ♪
♪ This one is taking you on ♪
♪ This is one is taking you on ♪
♪ Come on ♪
- You're going, you're
going. You're not going.
Why can't you just talk
to him? Just talk to him.
♪ This one is taking you on,
this one is taking you on ♪
♪ Come on ♪
♪  Come on ♪
- Still playing the classics.
- The remix of the remix
I have a remix, yeah.
That's what they want to hear so
yeah,
but I'm a bit outta practise
really.
- What's this?
- Oh, fuck, no don't look in
there.
- What's this?
- Don't look in there?
- Well, I wasn't going to
but I pay attention too.
- Come on.
- Old stuff that
I brought over for the...
Oh, God.
- Look at you.
- Yeah, it's stupid.
I was putting them up,
but then I kind of--
- What are you doing?
- I brought it with me,
Louise wanted to bring 'em,
she thought it'd be funny
to have decorations-
- Let's keep it.
- But actually looking at it,
sort of a little bit
embarrassing.
- It's not.
- Okay.
- Idris Thomas, lover boy.
- I think I'm just wanting
to reminisce, I guess.
- Uhuh!
- I dunno what brought that on.
What does it feel like being
back in Komo?
- Erm, it feels like...
Have you ever gone into a house
where there's been a murder?
Not knowingly.
- Okay, feels like coming
home, and it feels like...
Well, right now I feel like
I'm at my funeral.
- Did you see the house?
- Yeah, I stopped by.
- Me too.
- Did you think
it was gonna be there?
- I dunno, I dunno what I was
thinking.
- It was weird.
- Yeah, it's weird.
- It's like it was frozen in
time.
- Yeah.
- Wonder what
lives are being ruined.
- Inside, you mean?
- Yeah.
- I haven't checked for
the key under the mat
the last time I went.
- I did too.
- Did you?
- Yeah, no key.
If there was, I probably
would've gone inside.
- I know you would've done.
- Such a weirdo.
- Yeah.
- I wanted to see what colours
they painted the walls.
I mean, it's not a good look.
- What's not a good look?
- I mean, me showing up here.
- Well, it's not a bad look,
it's just was surprising, is all
of this.
- Well, you
were the last person
I thought I would see, my God.
- We're here now,
aren't we? For some reason.
- Yeah, for some God awful
reason.
- For some
fucking God awful reason.
- No, I mean, honestly,
I spent many, many years
thinking I would see you,
and then I never did.
It's really something because
the first couple years
that I didn't see you,
it was as if you were just gonna
show up
when I turned a corner
in London and New York.
- Yeah, I have exactly the same
thing.
- In Africa.
It could have been anywhere,
could have been on a safari.
I didn't come in to talk
about the weather, Adam.
I came here to talk about us.
I didn't come in to talk
about the weather, Adam.
I came in to talk about...
What do you think it is?
I didn't come here to talk
about the weather, Adam.
about the weather Adam,
I came here to talk about us
or I didn't come here to
talk about the weather, Adam.
No, that's weird.
- Were those different?
- Okay, so I didn't come here
to talk about the weather, Adam,
I came here to talk about us,
that's it.
'Cause it's not weather, it's
us.
So I didn't come to talk
about...
I didn't come here to talk
about the weather, Adam,
I came in to talk about us.
You do it, you do it. Do
Adam, and then do weather.
So he says, it's such
a beautiful day today.
It reminds me of that
day in May back in 2016.
- I say that.
- No, you say my bit, yeah.
- Sorry, I dunno if this
is my sort of forte,
I'm more book person.
- I'll say it,
you say my line 'cause I just
don't need to hear my line.
Oh, it's such a beautiful day
today.
So my line is,
I didn't come here to talk
about the weather, Adam,
I came to talk about us.
- I didn't come
here
to talk about the weather,
Adam, I came to talk about us.
Is that good?
- I have no idea
what I'm doing or why they gave
me this,
it's so hard.
- Yeah.
- Acting is like, this is hard.
- Yeah, maybe
the less you rehearse it,
the better it will be,
you know, just sort of-
- Yeah, maybe.
- What have you been doing?
- I mean,
working, working, working my
butt off.
- In New York?
- Yeah,
New York, I live in New York.
- I know you live in New
York.
- How do you not know this?
Don't you have like Instagram? I
dunno.
I don't know via me.
You don't like, I dunno, intrude
at all, you don't like...
You're not curious and ask
anybody when I'm doing?
- Yeah, I've always been...
Well, no, I've always been
curious.
What do you do when you
travel? Sort of work, is it?
- I travel for work, I discover
talent.
Yes, turns out I'm very
good at discovering talent,
writers, writers, writers.
- I'm a writer.
- Yeah, well, no,
I mean novelists, and then I-
- Is that what you're doing
here?
- Well, I turn
their art into television.
- How cool, TV!
- Yeah.
- So that's what you do,
you travel around and you like
developing?
That's amazing, but that's
great.
- Yeah, and I meet writers.
- Yeah.
- And I get to crush their
dreams.
And that's really what I do.
- Is that some sort of
revenge
or something, you think?
- It's my greatest revenge.
- Revenge, yeah, and
what about your writing,
don't you write anymore?
- Oh, not really,
I'm not really...
I'm not any good at that,
I'd rather discover talent.
- You're not gonna believe this.
- What?
- This.
When I was looking through this.
You remember that?
- That's gibberish.
- It's got some beautiful-
- Shit.
I'm not a career novelist, d'you
know?
That was just a little...
That was a game, that was a--
- A game? It wasn't a
game, it was more than...
It wasn't just a game. It wasn't
a game.
Well, it wasn't a game to me.
- No, it wasn't a game, you
know,
It was kind of like, it was
like, rehearsal for real life,
and now, and now, we're living
real life
and you know, real...
And it's reality. Get rid of
that box.
- But you had talent and
you had passion for it.
- You're holding on to the
past, why d'you have that?
I have an idea, we should
have a bonfire tonight
and burn that box, and
burn that, that's garbage,
burn it, just burn it.
- Oh my God, this is a
nightmare.
Is it just me or do the
words actually not sound
like words anymore?
Weather, weather,
weather, weather, weather.
Is that a word?
- Sounds like the word
weather.
- Yeah, I just...
It sounds, starting to
sound like the robot, right?
- I'm sort of tryna do the
numbers,
number crunching over here
so I actually need to focus.
- I didn't come in to talk
about the weather, Adam,
I came here to talk about us.
I didn't come...
Oh, my God, I have literally
no idea what to do.
Can you help? Will you
read some lines in me?
Even just running lines
'cause honestly, at this point
I don't even know if I know any
of them.
Do you mind?
- I've got quite a lot brains of
it.
- Okay, understood.
It's just...
Yeah okay, fine.
- Maybe you should take
this sort of to another room
and I could do the books in here
and then you can have proper-
- Maybe, but I've tried that.
I spent all of last night
doing this like, on my own
and it's really, yeah.
- Go on, go on.
- Oh, thank you, thanks so much.
I wouldn't normally ask,
I completely understand
it's not your job.
- Is your uncle coming back
soon?
- In like, I think in like
two days or something.
- Okay, okay.
- Just 'cause there's been
quite a lot of screaming.
- It's a nightmare situation
for everyone involved.
Yeah, it's
not easy for me either,
so it's just, you know...
I mean, you know who. You
know, it's Idris' ex-wife.
- Oh.
- And she...
I dunno, I think she saw him
and sort of went into a bit
of a tail spin or something.
- Get it away,
get it away, get away.
I can't, I can't deal
with this, just like-
- But this was good, this
is what you wanted to do.
- No, it's not,
it's not, it's not good.
- It was what wanted to
be, you're gonna be writer.
I was gonna be a song writer.
- That is...
Listen, why didn't you
tell me your dad died?
I'm sorry about Danny.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, it's okay.
I loved Danny.
- I'm sorry.
- Danny was like my dad too
and I deserved a call,
and I just had to say that.
- I'm sorry,
I should have called you.
- Yeah, because Danny couldn't
called me.
- Patricia, oh, gimme some of
that.
- Fucking up.
- Did you just drink that?
- Yeah.
- That's not water.
- Oh, no, it's not water.
Okay.
Oh, boy.
- Missed the thing they
had for him as well.
- Well, you know, you have
to do what you had to do.
- Yeah, but I'm never
around in the right place
when I'm meant to be, I'm never
in the...
Always in the wrong place.
- That's truthful.
We're so alike.
- Thank you for dealing with all
that.
I never said anything.
He would've been so happy
that you were there.
- He loved me, all right?
He loved me, isn't he?
- He loved you, yeah.
We all loved you.
I started playing this this
morning.
I think you've inspired,
inspired me.
I don't have any words of it,
anything.
♪ Look at her ♪
♪ Look how far she's gone from
home ♪
♪ Remember the day, seem like
the world will go way just now ♪
♪ It's just a pinny hell's drive♪
♪ She's alone, she is alone ♪
- Yeah.
- That's just not it.
- Keep working.
- I didn't come here to talk
about the weather, Adam.
I didn't come here to talk about
this,
I don't want to talk about it
anymore.
I don't care about the weather,
Adam, I care about you.
I care about us. What do
you mean you're leaving me?
That's exactly what I said,
what do you mean you're leaving
me?
And today of all days,
I can't stay any longer.
Don't you understand?
No, I don't understand.
I thought you loved me.
- Here we go. Whiskey, favourite
drink.
- Now you're just asking for
trouble.
- Oh, I think you brought the
Now you, now you are asking for
trouble.
- I don't think it's a good
idea.
- I think it's fucking great
Come on, cheers.
It's not for the taste, is it?
Are you sure this is okay?
- I don't have any problem
with it, it's just-
- I mean, just don't drive.
- These old miserable bastards!
You're fine, you're
fine.
Fuck!
Happy birthday. almost birthday.
- Yeah, 40, huh?
- 41, you are 41.
Are you lying to Louise?
No, you're actually 45.
- No.
- You're 50.
- I'm 39, I need seven.
- You're forty-
- I'm not 41.
- You're 41.
- I'm not 41, don't tell
everyone that,
she's gone through a lot of
effort.
- No is 50.
- Better the save a sperm.
- That's not cool.
Come on, how old's Taylor?
65, he's in his 60s.
Come on, you were bound to
go for an old guy, older guy.
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
- How old is he?
- 50.
- Does he have kids?
No way.
- Yeah, yeah.
I love them,
they're great.
I didn't have to change their
nappies.
I have already made family.
- Cool, you wanna marry him?
- I got a family-
- You wanna marry him?
- I don't wanna marry him, I
will never..
I told you, I will
never get married again.
♪ I'll never fall in love again♪
- No, no, no.
♪ I'll never get married again ♪
- How was that, bad, huh? Right
together.
♪ I'll never get, never married
again ♪
♪ I'll never get married again.♪
♪ I'll never get married again ♪
♪ I tried once, it was no fun ♪
♪ I'll never get, mm ♪
♪ We're, I think we're done ♪
♪ I think we're done ♪
♪ I'll never get married again ♪
♪ I tried it was, it wasn't fun♪
♪ I tried it once ♪
♪ I won't try it twice ♪
♪ It wasn't nice ♪
Voila
- Two, three.
- What have I got?
Are these all yours, then? Okay,
no!
Come on, you rigged this.
You fucking rigged
this, this is ridiculous.
Yes.
- These cards, I don't-
- Yes.
- Get 'em outta here.
Oh.
- Oh, no, that's mine,
give those back, cheats.
You look really beautiful,
by the way.
Oh, fuck, yes, the first time I
saw you
I was kicking in a cigarette
machine.
- This is three, right? There's
three girls on this card.
We've been on,
we've been on, you were
incredibly impressed-
- Charming.
- By my charm, and my moves.
What?
- And you came over and
you said, "Can I help you?"
- Are you talking?
- Something like, I
dunno.
- Push the button.
- Yeah, push the button.
You have to put coins in it.
What are you fucking talking
abut?
We made it.
That was the scariest that I've
even done.
- That was likely, that was
fine. Okay, let got scare her.
- We're gonna dress up. Let's
go.
- Let's do it.
- Yeah.
- You take off your cloths.
- You're a fucking girl,
take off your cloths first.
She's gonna, she's gonna love it
though.
- She's gonna shut herself.
- Let's scare her.
- No, what if I am a silly
killer.
I mean, I'm, I think I'm
capable of murder. Let's do it.
Okay, that will fit you.
I've got pyjamas, look I've got
pyjamas.
- Oh, my god, that's beautiful.
- Oh!
Oh!
Close your eyes,- close your
eyes, I'm getting naked.
Don't come in here.
- Okay, I'll wait here.
- I found some, I found some
paint.
Okay, here you go, this is
cycleboat.
- This is like-
- A ghost.
Okay, you put makeup on me
and I'll put makeup on you.
There you go.
Okay, make me a pretty
ghost.
- Oh, yeah.
- I'll make you an ugly ghost.
Ow, it's a bit
scratchy.
Okay.
- You look like a-
- Don't.
Look at our ghost, his house.
- Oh, yeah.
- We're terrifying.
- Hey, this makes Gary.
- I mean, we're terrifying.
- You smell the same.
- You like me even though I'm
terrifying.
- I could, I get that.
- I'm terrifying.
- No, it went terrifying.
We're haunting this house.
- It's gone just in one.
- Okay, hold on.
Are you ready?
- Oh, really good.
- Wait.
Is she there?
- Yes, she's there.
You look really lovely.
- So do you.
- D'you think?
- Yeah.
- We're playing ghosts.
Where are you going? Where are
you going?
Louise, don't be like that,
it's, it just happened to be...
We were just playing
around, having a bit of fun.
Are you not even gonna talk to
us, please?
Hi.
Erm, is it...
I didn't...
Is it 'cause I've had
something to drink?
I got upset and then I just
really...
I love you so much.
- Sh!
- I love you
- Fucking great.
- She'll be fine.
- D'you think?
- I always was.
- Ready?
- Ready.
- I'm fucking ready.
- You're fucking ready.
- Got me fucking Parker on, got
me shoes,
got me tennis racket, got me
balls,
I'm fucking mad for it.
- I'm fucking mad for it.
- I'm fucking...
I'm eating the balls.
- I'm eating the ball.
- I'm fucking having it.
- I'm having it.
- Come on, then,
fucking here.
- Mm!
- Come on, Gallagher,
gimme that sexy stuff.
- Come on, Patricia,
we're fucking you know, fucking
you know.
I told you the drunk
test is a stupid idea.
- You're a stupid idea.
- Yes, your fucking stupid...
Your a stupid idea.
D'you play tennis with in New
York, pals?
- Er, to be honest with you
I don't play much of anything
but you know how it is.
- Oh, fuck.
- You're all right.
- Ow!
- Come on, get up. Oh.
- You got me riding a baby
maker.
- Oh, not much used to you now,
is it?
- Oh, I dunno, Louise
wants to have a baby.
- What, what did you just say?
- I was out.
- What'd you just say?
- We was out.
- No, that's not what you just
said.
- Really, that did actually
hurt.
- Oh, yeah, you want a baby?
- I think I'm gonna go inside.
- You want a baby?
- Come on, can't be,
tennis like, is this anyway.
- You want a baby, yeah?
Ah!
Idris, come out.
One.
- What the fuck,
come on, come on.
- Two.
- come on, come on, be a man.
Let's play a song.
This one's for Dad.
♪ Oh, Danny, boy, the pipes,
the pipes are calling ♪
♪ From Glen to Glen and
down the mountain side ♪
♪ The summer's gone and the
roses fallen ♪
♪ Tease you, tease you
who goes, but I must buy ♪
♪ But come you boy when
summer's in the middle ♪
♪ Oh, when the vel is
hash that what was known ♪
♪ And I'll be here in
sunshine or in shadow ♪
♪ Oh, Danny boy, oh,
Danny boy, I love you so ♪
♪ If you come and all
the flowers are dying ♪
♪ And I am dead as
though I will meet you ♪
♪ You come and find the
place where I am lying ♪
♪ And you haven't say and
I'll be there for me ♪
- Really?
To Danny, to Danny.
To your dad.
- To Danny.
To Danny.
And to Lily,
to Lily Sophia Thomas, our
forgotten baby.
What the fuck are you doing?
- Look, it's broken.
- Are you fucking crazy? Don't
touch it.
- It's broken.
- You I knew you're hurting.
- What the fuck are you doing?
You're be joking!
- You kept saying
that you're gonna have a baby.
Deal with it. You are a coward.
- You're a coward?
- You're a coward.
- You're coward.
- You're fucking a coward,
shut up.
- You weren't there for me
when I went to the clinic by
myself
to get the baby straight from my
womb.
- Oh, shut up.
- Fuck you.
- Poor Idris.
- Oh, for fuck's sake, shut up.
- Shut up.
- Poor victim Idris, you
can't even go near the glass.
- Oh, shut your fucking mouth.
- You can't deal with anything
broken.
- Shut the fuck up!
- You can't deal with anything
broken,
that's why you go for Louise.
- You break everything you
touch.
- The only good part about
you is your dad and he's dead.
You have no courage-
- I have no courage?
- Just to be there,
just to admit the truth.
- I've got no courage?
I've got no courage?
- You won't tell the truth,
I mean, you can't tell the
truth.
- Stop talking!
- He's dead and he's-
♪ I don't believe in an
interventionist God ♪
♪ But I know, darling, that you
do ♪
♪ But if I did I would
kneel down and ask Him ♪
♪ Not to intervene when it came
to you ♪
♪ Well, not to touch a hair in
your head ♪
♪ Leave you as you are ♪
♪ If He felt He had to direct
you ♪
♪ And direct you into my arms ♪
♪ Into my arms, oh, Lord,
into my arms, oh, Lord ♪
♪ Into my arms, oh, Lord, into
my arms ♪
♪ But I believe in love ♪
♪ And I know that you do too ♪
♪ And I believe in some kind of
path ♪
♪ That we can walk down me and
you ♪
♪ So keep your candles burning ♪
♪ Make a journey bright and pure♪
♪ That you'll keep returning
always and in the mourn ♪
♪ Into my arms, oh, Lord,
into my arms, oh, Lord ♪
♪ Into my arms, oh, Lord, into
my arms ♪
- I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I've hated
you for so long, for...
I don't hate you,
I thought I hated you.
I thought I hated you because
I thought that you
convinced me not to be pregnant
and called it a miscarriage.
It wasn't you.
Idris, I don't wanna be a
mother.
I don't wanna be a mother, I
never have.
And I blamed you, and I'm sorry.
I don't think I'd be any good at
it.
And that's
okay, but I blamed you.
I thought if I didn't have the
baby
it meant I'd love you less,
so I ran away.
I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry, you don't have to
be sorry.
- You ran away too.
- Look.
- They look
like they're in love.
- They were in love.
I loved you.
♪ I'll never get married again ♪
♪ I tried it once, it wasn't fun♪
♪ I tried it once and now it's
gone ♪
- Mm!
- Hi.
I love you.
- Oh, fuck.
You had a good time, didn't you?
- Yeah!
- Who's that?
- I dunno.
Hi.
- Hi.
- Alice, right?
- Yeah, I, erm, I followed
you back from the the party.
- She's a big fan of
yours,
she has an amazing voice.
- Hello, you okay?
- Oh, yeah, you are such
a big inspiration to me.
Erm-
- Okay.
- Yeah, you're, you're kinda
like my hero.
- I hear that a lot. That's
okay.
It's the thing is...
You sure you're all right?
- Yeah, yeah.
Lovely.
- I am fucking starving.
I can eat a horse.
I can eat anything, really?
- New guest?
- Something like that.
- Thank you, Louise.
- Bye.
- I'm not very good at goodbyes.
- No, you never were.
- Be good.
- And if you can't be good?
- Be careful.
♪ Look at us now, look at
how far we've come along ♪
♪ Remember the day ♪
♪ It feels like the world
will go way just now ♪
♪ This choice that got me hell's
drive ♪
♪ In the dreams we felt each
other, we felt in real life ♪
♪ But I didn't see it through,
but I see it all again ♪
♪ You give me everything I've
got ♪
♪ Look at us now, look at
how far we've come along ♪
♪ Remember the day ♪
♪ It feels like the world
will go way just now ♪
♪ This choice that got me hell's
drive ♪
♪ And I still see you on my run♪
♪ And I will still solemn
see you on my run ♪
♪ I didn't know it then, baby,
why don't we do this again ♪
♪ And I didn't see it then
but I see it all again ♪
♪ You give me everything I've
got ♪
♪ Look at us now, how did
we get to where we are ♪
♪ Remember the way, far
from love and us now ♪
♪ This choice that got me hell's
drive ♪
♪ And I still see you on my run♪
♪ And I didn't see it then,
baby,
why don't we do this again ♪
♪ And I didn't see it then
but I see it all again ♪
♪ You give me everything I've
got ♪
♪ Yeah, you give me everything
I've got ♪