Grant me the serenity
to accept the things
I cannot change,
the courage to
change the things I can,
and the wisdom to
know the difference.
Thank you.
We have a new member joining
our program this week.
I know she just moved
into her new place.
How are you settling in, Julia?
Yeah, hi, I'm Julia.
I'm an alcoholic.
Hi, Julia.
Yeah, I was living
with my sister,
but I knew I needed to take
control of my life and get away.
So this place is not
Costa Rica, but it's mine.
And as long as I come to
these, I can have that.
So yeah, here I am.
Anything else, Julia?
Alright, thank you, Julia.
Let's see, we have a few
announcements before we start.
We'll have two
10-minute speakers...
Thank you so much.
♪ I know I'm inviting ♪
♪ So new and exciting ♪
♪ When you don't
know me at all ♪
♪ When the novelty wears off ♪
♪ After all is said and done ♪
♪ Will you still like me? ♪
♪ When the
butterflies are gone ♪
♪ I hope you don't mind it ♪
♪ There's so much behind it... ♪
The serenity
to accept the things
I cannot change,
the courage to
change the things I...
Yeah, if you could
just double check
that I didn't actually
purchase those?
Could you spell your address?
1038, Cypress, C-Y-P-R-E-S-S.
Thank you.
Can I put you on a brief
hold as I find this for you?
Sure.
Hello, is Julia still there?
Yup.
Hi, I'm here.
I
just went through your account.
The last charge
we have on record
is a purchase totaling
140 dollars and 23 cents
That includes a wallpaper
smoothing tool kit--
I know, these are packages
that I received today
with your label on them.
I don't know if I have an old
account that's been hijacked
or what, I just wanna
know what's going on!
I apologize
for any inconvenience
this might have caused.
Mistakes like these can happen
at our warehouse sometimes.
You're welcome to
return the items to us,
or if you wanna hold on to them-
That's fine, I'll
just return them.
Sounds great.
Is there anything else I
can help you with today?
Hi there, someone is
posting reviews in my name
for items I did not order.
Hi.
Yes,
I'm calling because my credit
card has been compromised.
Can you please transfer me
to your security department?
Please, continue to hold
and we will be with you shortly.
Yeah, I need you guys
to track a package for me.
I'm getting things from
an unsolicited sender.
The number is 773-3028.
Hello?
Yes!
Hi, I'm here.
Is Fran still there?
It's Julia, Julia
Day, 1038, Cypress Lane.
One second.
Jesus Christ.
Yes, Julia,
I'm looking at your
account history right now.
It appears the reviews mentioned
are not under your account.
I see here the most
recent use of your account
was a purchase totalling
140 dollars and 23 cents...
Yes, I know that, okay?
Another user is posting
reviews for products
under an account, but
with my name, okay?
I need you to shut them down.
I understand, ma'am.
Unfortunately,
I can't share any details
about other accounts,
but I'm looking at your
information right now
and I can assure you,
your account has not been compromised.
No, you're not
listening to me, alright?
I am being frauded,
alright, do you understand?
You're not.
Is there anything else I can--
Julia, thank God.
Are you okay?
Tat, no, listen...
I think someone's
targeting me or something,
like someone's like...
No, no, Julia, it's okay.
I just read your text
and I looked it up,
and what's happening to
you is called brushing.
Brushing?
Yeah, brushing...
it's like this scam
where some asshole gets
paid to send you products
so they can write a 'verified'
review in your name.
They want reviews?
So long as there's proof
the product shipped to someone,
they write verified
reviews for money.
It's completely a scam.
It's really shitty...
No, I...
I mean, they had
all my information, I...
I had to change my card.
That's what's
so weird about it,
they don't charge anyone's
cards. They just want reviews.
And so people end up with a
bunch of crap... but that's it.
They sent me a corkscrew.
What?
They sent me a corkscrew!
I thought maybe they knew
that... I don't know.
No... I think
it's just a coincidence.
Check to see if it was
a sponsored product.
I think that's what they do.
It's just a stupid,
random thing, it's not you.
Okay.
I was worried
someone could see me.
I'm only an
hour and a half away,
I can come down this
weekend... or something?
I mean, if you want, I--
Yeah, I'll be there.
You know, it's hard
to hear you like this
when we're not living
together anymore, and I...
I can't--
Why don't we talk
about it later, okay?
We can talk about that later.
Well I mean, it's like
what mom says, right?
Focus on what you can control.
So... what are you
gonna do tonight?
Wallpaper.
That sounds good.
Then what?
Julia, you there?
Hello?
Julia, are you still there?
Are you okay?
You know what, actually, I...
I need to let you go, okay?
Have a good night, I love you.
Okay, I love you.
Are you--
Our surveillance on this
street is pretty touch and go,
but I'll let you
know if we find any--
Hey, um...
Let me know if you
change your mind, okay?
I don't have to come,
but I want you to
know I'm here for you,
you don't have to do this alone.
I'm proud you're taking control.
Talk soon.
I love you.
TAT?
TAT!?
My God.
No, no, no!
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
God...
Hey...
Let me know if you
change your mind, okay?
I don't have to come,
but I want you to
know I'm here for you.
you know, you don't
have to do this alone.
I just...
...I'm proud you're
taking control.
Talk soon.
Let me know if you
change your mind, okay?
I don't have to come...
but I want you to
know I'm here for you,
you know, don't
have to do this alone...
I'm proud you're taking control.
We have a
new member joining our program
I know she just moved
into her new place...
I just
went through your account--
God, grant me the serenity
to accept the things
I cannot change-
Please, continue to hold
and we will be with you shorty.
How are you settling in, Julia?
Unfortunately,
I can't share any details
about other accounts,
but I'm looking at your
information right now,
and I can assure you your
account has not been compromised.
God, grant me the serenity...
And the wisdom to
know the difference.
How are
you settling in, Julia?
I did not order...
God, grant me the serenity-
I don't have to come,
but I want you to
know I'm here for you,
you know, you don't
have to do this alone.
I'm proud you're taking control.
Talk soon.