(WOLF HOWLING)
(INTENSE MUSIC)
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
Bobby, what's the action?
Five to one, and
she's the five.
(TENSE MUSIC)
Five, one odds.
Five red, one blondie.
(CROWD CHEERING)
(INTENSE MUSIC)
CROWD: Oh!
MAN: Oh, that's gotta hurt.
(PEOPLE CHEERING)
(INTENSE MUSIC)
WOMAN: Oh, no!
These bills are
for me, blondie.
I'm never betting
against you again.
You should come
around more often.
I need to update my ride.
Didn't know you
were so interested
in coming back around, Kat.
I have my reasons.
Yeah.
I bet.
(GUNSHOT FIRING)
Times have changed since
you've been around, Kat.
Look around.
No really, look around.
This is all mine now.
It's no place for a
good girl like you.
I'd like to give you 24
to get out of town but,
I didn't get where I
am by trusting people.
And something tells me that
you just won't go away.
So,
sorry it has to go
down like this, Kat.
(FINGERS SNAPPING)
(INTENSE MUSIC)
What do you want?
(GATE CLOSING)
(MELANCHOLY MUSIC)
What you looking for, blondie?
'Cause you know there so
much to see around here.
So uh, if you find
anything let me know, okay?
You hear me.
Yeah, I'll let you know.
So what's your name?
Kat.
Word is you're in for
murder, is that right?
Okay, right.
Listen, no one's going
anywhere around here,
so let's be cool, okay?
I mean, I don't need enemies.
I'm Vegas.
People ask me,
what's it short for?
I say it's short for Vegas.
(VEGAS LAUGHS)
Okay, so I'm a jackass.
What are you gonna do?
(BUZZER BUZZING)
GUARD: Step on
out, lunch time.
Hey, wanna do lunch?
(SMOOTH GUITAR MUSIC)
We're not sitting over there.
Let's sit here.
Who is that?
VEGAS: Val.
Bad ass bitch in for
murder just like you.
Maybe you two will hit it off.
Whoa, slow down
chief, I said maybe.
What are you in for?
Dealing drugs.
Dealing myself.
And beating up my old
lover with a crowbar.
You ever love anyone, Kat?
Yeah.
And?
I shot him.
Cool.
So you know how it is?
Yeah.
(UPBEAT ROCK MUSIC)
Lookin' fit, Kat.
Eight,
nine,
ten.
Whoa.
You know, you look like a fire.
But you better keep it quiet.
You know, the girls will
challenge you around here.
So you're saying you don't
want to be tough in here?
No, I ain't a fighter.
I do yoga and,
I'd rather paint your nails,
take your drugs,
all of them.
(VEGAS LAUGHS)
Heads up, we got company.
Sup bitches, you
wanna work in with us?
Shut up, Vegas.
We're hear to talk
to the new girl.
Lay the ground rules.
Get assigned a job
here yet, Miss,
whatever your name is.
'Cause if so, we get 20%,
you get safe.
Cat got your tongue.
Yeah, they gave me a job.
Yeah, what's that?
Yard work.
(INTENSE MUSIC)
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
(KAT GRUNTING)
You, wait outside.
That's quite a first impression
in the yard out there, Kat.
It's Kat, right?
Well honestly, it
doesn't matter.
You're here off the record.
No one knows you're here
and no one ever will.
So my advice to
you is to be cool,
make some friends,
take up some hobbies,
and look forward to
our social events.
Because let me say,
you will look stunning
at the prison prom.
Or you can be this.
And this place kind of has a way
of policing itself at times.
So either the inmates
beat me, or you do.
No.
I don't do any of the
beatings, he does.
(KAT GRUNTS)
Do you feel any nausea?
Dizzyness?
Headaches?
No.
(KAT GASPS)
What exactly are you
checking for, doc?
I'm looking for
signs of a concussion.
Well, it's kind of
my ribs and my lip.
Here's a balm.
Put it on, it will help
expedite the healing process.
It'll help the
bruises heal faster.
And don't fuss with
it for several hours.
Anything else?
Guard, we're done here.
My advice to you, leave the
balm on and stay out of trouble.
(INTENSE MUSIC)
Your girl is
quite the handful.
She's a Hellcat.
What plan do you
have here for her?
I want her alive,
just uncomfortable.
Break her.
That's not going to be easy.
Is that a problem?
No, no problem.
I just wish I had a little more
knowledge on this situation.
She stays in permanently.
I don't want her dead
and running the risk
of making her some kind of
martyr hero for the Hellcats.
Or the Vipers for that matter.
If they find out
she died in prison
for a crime she did not commit,
I think you know
what I'm getting at.
Keep her in there.
Keep her uncomfortable.
Keep everything off the record.
That's all the
Knowledge you need.
Right.
Better yet,
I'll go talk to her.
Sorry.
Hi.
I'm uh, not completely
prepared here.
I don't have a file
on you, which is odd.
But I'm working on that.
I'm Philip Boucher.
I'm the counselor
here at the facility,
but you can read that.
Um, it's Kat, right?
So um, I have a confidentiality
agreement with you so,
if you need to vent or,
I mean basically, whatever you
say with me, stays with me.
And if you're not comfortable
talking to other people
you can come to me.
I'm here for your
emotional support.
Also, if you need like
a specific job detail,
or you know, you want a
specific area of employment
or whatever, I can uh,
I can put in a good word
and try and set that up.
So, where would
you like to begin.
I think we're done here.
I get it, you're new here.
So am I.
I get my bachelors in psychology
and they send me here.
It's not exactly
paradise, I know.
I realize there's a
lot to process here.
So, we can check
in in a few days
and I'll see how
you're doing then.
In the meantime, if
you need anything,
I'm here from eight to
four, Monday through Friday.
(HARD ROCK MUSIC)
Hey chick.
Poker game going on in the
rec hall at seven, you in?
I'll be there.
Cool.
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
(INTENSE MUSIC)
(KAT GRUNTING)
(SEARING MUSIC)
Ow.
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
Get her up.
No no.
Liking your new home, Kat?
Fuck you.
You know Kat, I could
kill you any time I want.
Any time.
The thing I'm
struggling with is,
do I keep you around
for something special,
or do I just be done with you?
I like my women dangerous, Kat.
You know this.
You know.
(WOMAN SNIFFS)
But with you,
I
just
can't
decide.
I asked you something before.
What do you want?
I already have what I want.
Vipers and Hellcats are gone.
Just the Demons now.
What I want,
is to keep it that way.
(TENSE MUSIC)
(KAT GRUNTING)
(MELANCHOLY MUSIC)
Move.
(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
You guys just start?
Maybe.
Deal me in?
Cool with that?
You gotta put your
bet down, girl.
I'll be earning
cash here next week.
Asking the counselor to
hook me up with a job.
I'll put down a weeks pay.
Okay.
I'll raise.
(SMOOTH MUSIC)
Come on, bitch.
Till next time, suckers.
Hey,
good game.
Here's a consolation
prize, ladies.
You're all right, Kat.
Thanks for the cancer.
Hey, look at you,
making new friends.
Probably a good thing.
Yeah well, see how
long it keeps me alive.
Hey, you're growing on 'em,
but your fists in their
face will do that, too.
Can I ask you something?
If it was about the smokes,
I didn't give it to
them to win them over.
Gave it to them
'cause I don't smoke.
You're no murderer.
Why are you here?
I was set up by a
local gang leader.
But I'll leave it at that.
Less you know, safer you are.
Listen,
rumor is there's
a way outta here.
A tunnel.
I'm not sure where but
I know there are drugs
getting in to the
warden from it.
I think it's basement level.
What's down there now?
Laundry.
But I only did laundry
for three weeks.
That home ec shit ain't for me.
Trash detail down there, too.
Hm, okay.
Well it gives me a start.
I've got a plan.
So, you're interested
in a job detail?
Yeah.
What'd you do on the outside?
What do you do?
Fixed bikes.
Like motorcycles.
Mm-hm.
That's not your everyday
female occupation.
I've been around bikes my
whole life, so came naturally.
Well, I don't know what
you would do around here
that's similar to that, but um,
what do you want?
Well, I worked at a garage.
I'm used to getting
sweat, blood,
grease, oil, out of clothing.
Laundry detail?
Yeah, we could set up laundry.
You mind if I make a phone call?
Oh hey, before that,
I write poetry too.
I could try and
freestyle something
while you're on the phone.
Pen, paper?
Yeah, I'd love
to read your work.
KAT: Thanks.
(PHONE DIALING)
Hey Lonnie, we need
to get Kat a job.
I was thinking maybe
laundry detail.
I mean there's for sure, you
can squeeze her in, right?
There's gotta be one opening.
Uh-huh.
Okay yeah, tonight?
All right.
Thank you.
All right, bye.
Well I got good news.
You got laundry if you want it.
So, you interested?
When can I start?
Tonight after dinner.
So um, we'll check
in in a few days
and we'll see how
it's going for ya.
Great, thanks.
No problem.
Thank you.
(TENSE MUSIC)
KAT VOICEOVER: I think
you're a good person,
or at least I hope.
I'm not innocent in life,
but innocent in why I'm here.
Don't talk to or trust
anyone in this facility.
They're going to kill me, soon.
I need your help.
Kat down here?
Yeah.
You got mail, sweetie.
Thanks.
Did I get anything?
Let me check.
- Let me check.
- Uh, no.
You aint' got no mail.
Who would send you mail?
My brother, Dean.
Please, jackass.
You're the jackass.
(PENSIVE MUSIC)
(GATE UNLOCKING)
Come on, you.
(VEGAS SCREAMS)
Let's go!
- Come on.
- Pervert!
What the hell?
(VEGAS SCREAMING)
GUARD: Go!
You're going to have to
give me something, Vegas.
Something.
Look, I told you I
don't know anything.
Nothin' about the new girl.
(VEGAS CRYING)
Okay.
Okay look.
She was asking about
getting a job detail.
She asked me what
I thought was good.
All I know is she's
some fucking biker bitch
and she's in for murder.
- That's all.
- Job detail?
I don't know.
She's bored?
Wants to make some cash?
I don't fucking know.
That's not helpful.
(VEGAS SQUEALS)
Wait, motherfucker.
There is something.
Word is she's innocent.
(VEGAS CRYING)
Here off the record.
Some gangster from upstate.
Go on.
VEGAS: That's all
I know, that's it.
Maybe, wait.
Maybe one thing.
Maybe she's a murderer,
maybe she's not.
But you better watch
your fucking back,
because she's tough enough
to turn this place
to dust right up.
(VEGAS CRYING)
GUARD: Ah, shut up.
(INTENSE MUSIC)
Hey, that's too
bad about Vegas.
(INTENSE MUSIC)
(GUN COCKING)
Enough!
Take her to solitary!
Get off me.
GUARD: Move it!
(KAT GRUNTS)
Warden, found this on her.
Thoughts?
Probably a showdown
with one of the inmates.
I don't know.
What do you want us to do?
Let's play.
Make sure she's there on time.
(BOUCHET SIGHS)
(SIRENS BLARING)
(CAT MEOWING)
(PENSIVE MUSIC)
(BUZZER BUZZING)
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
(GUARD GRUNTS)
(INTENSE MUSIC)
Surprised to see me, baby?
I'm sure you know by now,
Rosie's taken control.
No more Hellcats,
no more Vipers.
Now there's just us, baby.
Snake?
Relax.
No time for old news now.
Vipers are gone temporarily.
I'm here to take my outfit back.
A few days ago I
followed Rosie in
and who I assumed
to be the warden,
and followed them
back to this place.
There's an old underground
tunnel leading out of here.
It's connected to solitary.
That's good to know,
but I'm not leaving now.
SNAKE: No?
I'm taking down the warden
and I made a promise to someone.
Suit yourself.
I need to gather more information
on Rosie's operations,
get us some leverage.
I'll be back in
two days, 6:00 PM.
Do something to
get into solitary.
Gets too hot around here,
you know the way out.
You know I wouldn't leave
you in a place like this.
But when things settle down
and you're on the outside,
we got some unfinished
business between us.
Till then we're a team.
Deal?
Doctor, I need you to come
back in 30 minutes, please.
Get up.
Get up now.
She smashed my
fucking face, man!
Look at this shit!
Shut up and listen carefully.
Kat and two guards were
found unconscious earlier.
Nobody saw anything.
I'm warning you,
this is the last time
you go rogue against
my instruction.
Man, I didn't go rogue.
I have nothing to do with this.
You told me not to kill
her, I haven't done shit!
But you can believe this,
payback is fucking coming.
She stays alive, period.
However, I give you
permission to use
whatever means necessary
to find out who did this.
Quickly.
(INTENSE MUSIC)
Something's really off here
and I don't know what yet.
Kat's confidant
isn't talking either.
Isn't talking, or
doesn't know anything?
Which is it?
It's getting harder to
keep Kat alive here, Rosie.
Well that's exactly
what I'm paying you to do,
and a raise could
be in your future.
I have a very important
deal going down.
Which includes the largest
acquisition of product
we've ever had.
Kat's dead, she's
buried in your tomb.
The Hellcats that
are in my outfit now,
they think she left them.
Abandoned them.
I don't need them
finding out she died
in some down state prison
for a trigger that I pulled.
Who could be helping her?
Who would put their life
on the line for her?
Only one man.
And he's dead.
(TECHNO DANCE MUSIC)
Here I thought it was
cats that had nine lives.
You ain't here for
a try out, are ya?
You're here for trouble.
If I was here for trouble
you'd know it already.
MAX: Well then,
what can I do for ya?
Kat's down state, why?
It's only Demons now.
No place for Hellcats
and Vipers anymore.
We'll see about that.
Mm, Rosie's merged them all.
She's the only game in town.
Kat's a strong woman.
It's better to have
her under lock and key,
know what I mean?
Go on.
Kat got set up during a fight.
Fighting for money,
doesn't sound like Kat.
I need something, Max.
Money wasn't for her.
Word is Frank needs the
money, for his shop.
Merger can take a toll
on everyone, Snake,
but Kat coming back
on Rosie's turf,
looking for illegal fights?
Not a smart move.
Rosie doesn't need a strong
girl like that in her back yard.
Next thing you know
she's rallying her girls
and there's a rebellion,
and the Demons are here.
Specially when Rosie's
making bigger deals.
Bigger deals?
She's pushing more product
than you ever could, Snake.
No offense.
None taken, Max.
None taken.
Here's what I propose.
You give me the
name of the location
where Rosie's pushing
drugs, weapons, whatever.
You give me the name of that
location within five seconds,
or else I kill you
within the next 48 hours
and burn this place
to the ground.
Maybe make it my new clubhouse.
Choose a side, wisely, Max.
Hold on.
Rosie's got a big
deal going soon,
but I don't know the
details on it, man.
All I know is she's
got a lot of product
coming out of that
warehouse downtown.
Now that's a start man, right?
I know your game, Max.
I know you talk.
When you talk to Rosie you
tell her someone was here.
But not me, Snake's dead.
Anything else I should know?
Yeah, something to put
in those memory banks.
The Vipers are back.
(TOUGH MUSIC)
♪ I'm the bitch with the money ♪
♪ You're the bitch
with the money ♪
♪ I'm the bitch with the money ♪
♪ You're the bitch with money ♪
♪ You're the bitch
with all the money ♪
♪ I'm the bitch with the money ♪
♪ You're the bitch
with the money ♪
♪ I'm the ♪
Yeah?
Word on the street's
the Vipers are back.
Get out, come back tomorrow.
Who gave you this information?
A reliable source.
Watch yourself.
Shit.
(INTENSE MUSIC)
You looked pretty fine to me,
but I can't say for certain
without a more
thorough investigation.
I'll see you in my
exam room tonight.
Solitary, six.
I'm getting scared here, Kat.
Any luck finding the
entrance inside of laundry?
Well, it's not in laundry,
but yeah, I know where it is.
What?
You didn't tell me.
Well, the less
you know the better.
It's just a matter of
time before they kill me.
Relax, they're keeping
me alive for a reason.
That doesn't
mean I'm safe, Kat.
We're on borrowed
time, both of us.
Well I'm finding
out more info tonight.
Get the ball, ladies.
(UPBEAT MUSIC)
Kat, confinement.
Hey, Mr Buck?
Hey uh, I'm about to
take off for the day
and I remembered you
wanted to discuss your uh,
your, your confidence issues.
Listen, I told
you that in private.
Hey, don't.
BUCK: That is not something
appropriate to talk
about in public.
Keep your head
down, just listen.
There's a big deal
going down soon.
I need to get more details.
You need to leave, like fast.
We'll talk about
this later, but,
in private again, please?
Hang in there.
- Thank you.
- You'll be all right.
Not yet.
I need 24 hours.
High noon, tomorrow.
We meet at the
entrance to the tunnel.
One more thing, I want my bike.
Who has it?
Who do you think
I would trust?
(CALMING COUNTRY MUSIC)
(HORE NEIGHING)
Think you have
something of mine, Frank.
I thought you was dead, Snake.
Yeah, I know.
Relax, I'm not here for trouble.
Well when you're around,
there's always trouble, Snake.
Maybe I shed some skin.
That doesn't
change who you are.
The world's different
around here.
Everything's changed.
I done retired.
I done bought this farm.
And sure, I still do
bikes here and there.
For Rosie's gang?
Now you know I don't
ask any questions, Snake.
I just take the money.
That's, that's what I
always liked about you, Frank.
Where's Kat?
She okay?
No, she's locked
up down state.
What?
Rosie set her up.
Why?
She was laying
low for a while.
Came back, made
her presence felt.
Strong woman like Kat,
strong woman like Rosie.
There's not room enough
for both of them.
Now you know Kat's
always been clean.
You know that.
Kat's in trouble, Frank.
Follow me.
Hey Snake.
(INTENSE MUSIC)
(ENGINE REVVING)
Hey.
How can I help?
(TENSE MUSIC)
Rosie told us this job was
soon.
Can you clarify that.
Means soon.
That's all you need to know.
(DOG BARKING)
Go check that out.
Look, it's a
shit ton of product
we're covering for you guys.
I need to know how close it is.
We ain't playing,
motherfucker.
Answer him.
(MAN CHUCKLES)
(TENSE MUSIC)
(INTENSE MUSIC)
Where's the party at?
Bitch.
No.
Maybe I'll go invite myself.
♪ Sweet bitch, bitch, bitch ♪
♪ Sweet bitch,
sweet bitch, bitch ♪
♪ Sweet bitch, bitch, bitch ♪
♪ Sweet bitch,
bitch, bitch, bitch ♪
♪ Sweet bitch, bitch, bitch ♪
♪ Sweet ♪
Yeah?
You need to be
on point with this.
I can't stress the
importance of this deal.
It's under control
and on schedule.
Be ready in 48.
Watch your back.
Let's get back to work.
(LIGHT TENSE MUSIC)
Dirty cops.
I know I can always count
on them to be there.
Feel that?
I need quick answers.
When's the next deal?
Who's it with?
BANDANA MAN: Bitch,
she'll kill you.
I'll take my
chances, three seconds.
Some buyer from the southeast.
I don't have a name man.
They'll fucking kill you, too.
Soon they'll be
doing business with me.
(GATE BANGING)
(GUNSHOT FIRING)
No please, continue
what you're doing.
I haven't seen you
in a while, Snake.
I heard you were.
Yeah.
Rosie's not unreasonable.
I bet she'd cut ya in.
Well that's mighty
generous of Rosie now.
I will seriously consider that.
Better than being
cut out permanently.
Speaking of Rosie,
(GUN COCKING)
(TENSE MUSIC)
where can I find her?
Bring up your right hand, slow.
Now your left.
(SNAKE CHUCKLES)
I don't think so, Rosie.
If you'll excuse me.
Normally I like this kind
of party, but not tonight.
(ROSIE GRUNTS)
Here I thought
Kat had nine lives.
Speaking of Kat, why?
Times change.
Look around, Snake.
If you weren't as
stubborn as you are,
you actually might like it.
I doubt it.
You know, Kat's replaceable.
Expendable.
It's time you see this.
This could be
mutually beneficial.
You know, you two are
seriously fucked up.
And now that Kat's
put away, for good,
so I just unfucked your
fucked up relationship.
You're welcome.
Guess what I got?
You know I like what you've done
with my place since
I've been gone.
Yeah, stay out of my way
and you'll see what
I can really do.
Sure.
60 for you, 40 for me?
90 me, 10 you, and I don't
put a price on your head.
I can be so generous.
Every one percenter
within striking distance
will come and
exterminate you for me.
Look Rosie, I don't
have some of your drugs,
I have all your drugs.
We'll meet in two days and
I'll bring every bag of it,
provided Kat's alive
and in one piece.
If I even suspect
you're tailing me,
if I suspect you're pressing me,
I'll torch every gram of it.
I'll be in touch.
(ROSIE CHUCKLES)
You're up.
(KNOCKING ON BARS)
You have a visitor.
Kat, I didn't expect
to see you in here.
You know when you're in trouble
you're supposed to come see
me, not anyone else, me.
I know.
You know?
Then why you sitting there
and I'm sitting over here?
I messed up, Frank.
I wanted to make
some quick cash.
Heard there were
fights going down.
In Rosie's back yard?
I was doing it for
your business, Frank.
I know the yard is hurting.
That's my business,
I'll manage.
It's our problem.
Look, there's no
one to trust here.
I'm sure that they're
probably listening now,
so watch what you say.
I got something to show you.
(HOPEFUL MUSIC)
You got that?
It was nice seeing you, Kat.
I'll see you soon.
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
Zoom in.
Enhance that.
Find out what that paper says.
It doesn't really
work like that, ma'am.
Do it anyway.
(TENSE MUSIC)
(HOPEFUL MUSIC)
(KNOCKING ON BARS)
Lunch.
I'll get that fucker,
believe it, you'll see.
Fuck you, Kat!
(DARK MUSIC)
We're cool now, right?
(VEGAS WHIMPERING)
Orders, Warden?
Confinement, both of them.
Infirmary first for the other?
Take them both to
confinement, now!
We're going to make this quick.
All these shenanigans are
making me anxious, impatient.
I'm going to ask
you direct questions
and I expect short,
direct answers.
I warn you, I can
become impatient.
I need a fucking doctor!
Rosie, whatever
you know of her,
drugs, meetings,
associates, talk.
Talk, Kat!
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
Drop it!
(TENSE MUSIC)
Now!
You, unlock her.
You, drop your
gear and sit down.
Okay, now cuff yourself to
your boyfriend over there.
Move it!
Now what, Kat?
Where exactly are
you going to go?
We're leaving.
There's no where to run.
I don't need to run.
(INTENSE MUSIC)
Can I help you
with something, doc?
You know, I'm pretty sure
this violated patient
confidentiality laws.
(DOC GRUNTS)
(INTENSE MUSIC)
(PRISONERS CHEERING)
(WARDEN SCREAMING)
(PRISONERS YELLING)
(INTENSE MUSIC)
No, get the fuck off of me!
Get off of me!
(PRISONERS YELLING)
(INTENSE MUSIC)
PRISONER: Get that bitch!
Thanks, Phil.
You shouldn't be here.
I don't want you to get
wrapped up into this.
Hey, don't worry about me.
I have a plan, okay?
So this is it, isn't it?
You are gonna make a
great doctor one day.
I just know it.
Frank!
I'm sorry.
Are you gonna make me
go through this again?
Kat, you're the only
family I have, you know?
Sorry.
Frank,
get them safe.
What about the warden?
It's taken care of.
Are you going to Rosie?
Yeah.
To give her back her drugs.
Yeah, about that.
I changed my mind.
I think I'm gonna keep her drugs
and then I'm gonna show
up to her little meeting
and I'm gonna take out anybody
that shows up with her.
Vipers are back, baby.
You're not going alone.
I owe you now.
Kat.
After this, we're even.
No more bad blood.
There's tools in the
barn if you need 'em.
I actually see this
going really well.
(ROOSTER CROWING)
(KAT SIGHS)
Oh God.
(SENSUAL MUSIC)
I'm glad I missed.
Tools?
(STRONG MUSIC)
Tools.
(INTENSE MUSIC)
I don't see what
belongs to me here.
You know it's funny, Rosie.
I leave after a little hiatus
and come back and I don't
have what's mine, either.
But that changes now.
You're playing your
cards wrong here.
(FINGERS SNAPPING)
(TENSE MUSIC)
But I knew you'd fuck things up.
Fuck it up for yourself, anyway.
What, a waste.
(KAT WHISTLES)
(GUNSHOT FIRING)
(ROSIE GRUNTS)
(GUNSHOTS FIRING)
(ROSIE GRUNTING)
(GUNSHOT FIRING)
(GUNSHOTS FIRING)
(GUN COCKING)
It's too bad, blondie,
we could have made a
lot of money together.
(GUNSHOT FIRING)
(ROOSTER CROWING)
(TENSE MUSIC)
(GUNSHOTS FIRING)
(BIKER GRUNTING)
(ROSIE GRUNTING)
(GUNSHOTS FIRING)
(ROSIE SPITTING BLOOD)
I'd like to cut you to pieces
and leave you lying here
baking under the sun.
Vultures come, wolves come,
it's the way you deserve to go.
Normally I see the value of
every low life around here,
but you, even with
all your value,
you're dangerous, and I like it.
But how long?
How long till your next
little revolution here?
How long till you
try to rise up again?
Finish this.
Not in cold blood, Snake.
Your way of life isn't my way.
(ROSIE LAUGHS)
If you were doing it her way,
you'd be locked up forever.
No Frank, no life, no hope.
Look at her.
Darn it, look at her.
(ROSIE LAUGHING)
Let that image burn in.
You know why?
'Cause she'd do it again.
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
Do it, Kat.
Do it.
(TENSE MUSIC)
(ROSIE MEOWS)
(ROSIE COUGHING)
(GUNSHOT FIRING)
You did the right thing.
Proud of you.
Hey.
I'm going to get Vegas.
I trust I can leave
you two, right?
So I'm thinking me and you
have some unfinished business.
What do we do now?
I won't live this life.
But I won't stand in your way.
I won't run forever.
What if you could?
Hey.
(ROSIE COUGHING)
(ROSIE CHUCKLES)
(INTENSE ROCK MUSIC)
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull