-Ugh, after two years.
I'm so sorry, Felicity.
-Unemployed and bankrupt
at Christmas.
I feel sick.
-You gave it your best.
Chicago's a big, hard city.
-A failed artist,
a failed wedding,
and now a failed baker.
It's so sad I could laugh,
but I just end up crying.
-Hang in there, Felicity.
We all believe in you
up here in Wisconsin.
-You all are way too happy.
-Mm, well, only room for one
moody artist in this family.
-How's she doing?
-I think she misses her aunt.
-That's nice of you to say.
I can't eat this. Here, Ginger.
And I just maxed out another
credit card on comfort food.
-Do not get another
credit card.
-Well, what am I gonna do,
Grace?
-Mom and Dad
would love to have you.
-No way.
-I mean, I do admit their
empty-nest honeymoon phase
has gotten worse.
-Much worse.
-You wouldn't have to pay rent.
Aspen Grove at Christmas?
I don't think
I could stomach it.
-What are you saying?
There is no better place
to be this time of year.
-I honestly don't even think
I like Christmas anymore.
-Okay, now you've
crossed a line.
You have always loved Christmas.
-Well, things change.
These last years
have been tough.
I'm now a Grinch.
-Don!
Don!
You could work at Don's office.
The front-desk assistant girl,
uh...
-Lily.
-Lily is going to Prague
for a month with her school.
I think.
-Grace, I cannot work
at your husband's office
like a teenager.
-Lily is not a teenager,
and you'd be doing
Don a big favor.
-She's 19, so technically
she's a teenage...
Huge. Big deal.
Very helpful.
-Maybe...
-Never mind.
-Maybe what?
-Maybe I should call Brian.
-Are you hearing yourself?
You called off the wedding.
I went with you when you tried
to get a refund
on your wedding dress.
I sat with you while you cried
when they said no.
-He was my best friend.
I mean, you are, too,
but you know what I mean.
-You're spiraling.
Come home. Work at Don's
office for a month.
Make some money.
Get back to Chicago
after Christmas.
-Bah, humbug.
-Speak for yourself, honey.
What choice do you have?
-One-month office job?
That's it?
-One month.
For Christmas!
-For Christmas.
-Mm-hmm.
-What are we doing here?
-Huh.
Come on, Ginger Snap.
-Sweetie!
-Welcome home!
-Oh!
-Okay. I can't breathe.
-How was the drive?
Are you hungry?
Thirsty?
-Let's get you some eggnog.
-No. Mom, Dad,
let's get one thing straight.
I just want to work
and make plans to start over.
I appreciate you letting me
stay, and I love you.
But I want as little Christmas
as humanly possible.
-Oh, sweetheart, you've got...
-Oh. Mm.
-Well, I'll just
have to help you.
I wish you would.
-Felicity!
Oh!
-I'm glad you're back.
-I'm not so sure I am.
-It's a good thing.
Just in time
for a Christmas miracle.
I know. I'm kidding.
No holiday magic allowed.
-Aunt Felicity!
-Maddie, look at you!
You're so grown-up now.
-Really?
-We are heading
to the farmers' market.
Do you want to come?
Or are we still in a mood?
-I can be in a mood and still go
to the farmers' market.
-That's the most she's talked
to anyone in weeks.
-I feel like I get along well
with sullen teenagers.
I can't imagine why.
-Ha, ha, ha, ha!
-So, Maddie's all grown-up.
When did that happen?
-Ugh, overnight.
She is just like you.
-Well, isn't she lucky?
I remember when I wanted
to move to Chicago and paint.
Take on the world.
-Well, didn't you?
-This has been a blast.
I'm gonna go grab a coffee
and sit in the car.
-Absolutely not.
You need fresh air
and small-town festivities.
And Maddie loves
Christmas in Aspen Grove.
Don't you?
Yeah, she tries to play it cool.
-I like Christmas...
cookies.
-That is exactly what we need.
-Yeah, but why do they have to
be Christmas cookies?
Couldn't they just be cookies
or cookies you eat
during the winter season?
-Let's go and leave
Lady Scrooge ...
or was it Lady Grinch?
-Both.
-To figure out Christmas
on her own.
-Hi, you!
Oh!
Who put this monstrosity on you?
We're done with Christmas.
-Done with Christmas?
We're just getting started.
-Excuse me, that was
a private conversation.
-With Pumpkin?
He's being oppressed
by Christmas.
-Oppressed?
It's the best time of year.
Come on, have some cocoa.
It's on the house.
Well, it's on the farm.
-Excuse me.
What are you doing
with my Pumpkin?
-Oh, nothing.
Sorry.
-Pumpkin, come here.
-Tried to tell her.
-I couldn't be mad at you,
though, could I, James?
-Right.
Well, sorry again.
-Don't you want your cocoa?
It's the season and all that.
-Yeah, it's not really
my season.
Not this year, anyways.
-I don't believe it.
-Don't believe what?
-You're Felicity Olson.
-Caitlin Rogers?
-So you're back in town?
-Um, just visiting.
I don't think I've seen you
since you and Grace
graduated high school.
Uh, how have you been?
-Fantastic.
I'm town chairwoman,
which means that I'm responsible
for making sure
that all of this runs smoothly.
Grace told me about the wedding.
What a shame.
-Caitlin, you would know.
Where is Mrs. Rockwell's
cookie stand?
-Oh, you haven't heard.
Mrs. Rockwell retired.
She lives in Florida now.
-Seriously?
-Oh!
-She fell in love
with Arnold Hollingsworth.
One day, he started
sitting in the window seat
at the coffee shop.
-Which was Mrs. Rockwell's seat.
So she started sitting with him,
and they fell in love.
-Oh, that is so romantic.
-So lame.
-It's true.
-Boca Raton is lucky.
No more Mrs. Rockwell's
Christmas cookies for us.
-Sound the alarm.
Just a bit of holiday humor,
-Felicity, I understand
that this may not be important
to someone like you,
but in a small town,
tradition matters.
Now if you'll excuse me,
I see a pair of wooden angels
that are about to go up
in flames
next to that candle display.
-Caitlin saves the day.
-James, talk soon
about the Snow Ball.
-Christmas cookies.
-No.
No. I'm in mourning.
-My sister's a baker.
-Was a baker.
-You could save Christmas.
-People can bake
their own cookies.
-Yes, but what about
all the town events
and the hardworking folks who
don't have time to bake and ...
and who want something
to bring to parties,
to school, to ... to church?
Maddie!
-Um, cinnamon rolls.
Bûche de Noel?
-It's a golden opportunity here.
-Okay, I've decided I'm leaving.
Goodbye.
It was nice to meet you.
-Please excuse my sister.
She is not in
the Christmas spirit yet.
-Ooh, it is a quick transition
after Thanksgiving.
-Yeah, maybe that's it.
-Felicity, this is James.
James was varsity quarterback.
He was a bit of a star.
-I don't think I knew
what a football was back then.
-Oh, it's a brown ball,
sort of spheroid.
-Oh, I thought that was
the baseball.
-Uh, two cocoas.
None for Felicity.
-Felicity, your name means
happiness, right?
-Oh, also joy, cheer, delight.
Everything my sister embodies.
-Ha.
-Well, lots of felicity
around the holiday
could be a good thing.
-Oh, can I get a quart of milk
and three pounds of butter?
-Three pounds?
-It's Christmas.
Time to bake cookies to eat
during the "winter season."
-I see what you did there,
Grace.
-All right. Later, Maddie.
Nice to meet you, Felicity.
-What is wrong with this town?
It's like everyone's
under a spell.
-You'll be under it, too,
soon enough.
-I'll be back in Chicago
-Wanna bet?
-So, after we log in,
we have to access the
patient-records library.
To do this, we click...
...the PDF and...
drag it over...
to the patient's name.
And let's see, where is it?
-I've got it.
-I tend to do all of my inputs
after lunch.
Oh, did you put your name
on your lunch?
-No, I didn't.
I guess I assumed
that sandwich in the fridge
was just named Susan.
Sorry, that was a bad joke.
I'll just go write my name
on my food.
That is too funny.
A sandwich named Susan.
-Yeah, I thought it was weird,
you guys all naming
your food like that,
but you know,
every office has its quirks.
-If you knew Susan,
you'd know why what you said
is so funny.
-Can't wait to meet her.
-Oh! Oh, a salad...
A salad named Jamal.
A soup named Benjamin.
-Okay, so that PDF
that you were talking about ...
-A smoothie named Ken.
-You laugh, but that joke
went on for eight hours.
-Hey, beggars can't be choosers.
-Okay, I am grateful
for the job.
I can just see myself
going insane.
-Did Felicity tell you what a
smashing success she was today?
A burrito named Don.
Oh, a new classic.
Ready for movie night?
-Yep.
See you in there.
-We're watching
"It's a Wonderful Life."
You're baking.
-Mom's shortbread recipe.
Whoops.
-That's the best whoops
I've ever heard.
Does this mean ...
-Hey, hey. What's the hold-up?
Oh, Christmas cookies. Nice.
May I?
-Mmm!
-Oh, my.
They just melt in our ...
-Salty but buttery.
-Yet sweet.
This is the best...
-Christmas cookie I've ever had.
-I mean, I knew you were good,
but these are insane.
Who are you?
-She's the new Mrs. Rockwell.
-What does that mean?
-It means, Don...
I quit.
-And I have the perfect gig
for you to get started.
We're talking high-profile.
-Cocoa delivery.
Am I late?
Hey, Maddie.
-Made it just in time.
Sugarplum fairies
are about to wrap it up.
-Good.
Had to finish up
a few things at the farm.
-Oh, I forgot, everyone here
is on Aspen Grove Time.
-Sure looks like you
found your holiday spirit.
-Well, there is an opening
in the marketplace.
I'm making money.
I'm thrilled.
Ho, ho, ho, et cetera.
-That's very Christmassy of you.
-What's more Christmassy
than rampant consumerism
wrapped in a warm blanket
of butter and sugar?
-So there is no room
for Christmas magic.
You are just all business.
-You say that like
it's a bad thing.
-I mean, it's a little...
Never mind.
-It's what?
-It's a little...
cynical.
And maybe that's a strong word,
but it's ...
-It's realistic.
If that's being cynical,
then so be it.
But I plan to do very well
this season.
I have to.
-So, how'd the butter
work out for you?
-Fine.
-Best butter in the state.
Looks like it inspired you.
-I inspire myself.
-Then you won't mind
if I try one?
-Those are for sale.
Besides, I thought
you were Mr. Humble
Christmas-Loving Farmer Man.
-Okay, what is wrong
with loving Christmas?
-Nothing.
It's very innocent
and small-town.
It's sweet.
-It's innocent because nobody
in Chicago loves Christmas.
Everybody's too busy being...
chic.
-Are you calling me chic?
Chic and cynical?
Wow, I sound very French.
Thank goodness
I left Aspen Grove.
-Hey, this is my town,
and it's your town, too.
-Please.
I wouldn't live here again
if somebody paid me to.
-Isn't that exactly
what's happening here?
-So, how did everybody do?
-Sold out.
-Oh, that's too bad.
I would have loved
to taste-test.
-She's even better
than she used to be.
-What? Used to be?
-Must be James' butter.
-It's definitely not the butter.
It's all technique.
What do you mean, "used to be"?
-Not in a bad way.
-Well, we all grow and change
over the years.
-Especially when we get back to
our innocent, small-town butter.
-I still remember how you were
in middle school.
Braces, glasses.
You hardly said a word
back then.
Grace's awkward little sister,
the artsy one.
How things change.
Let me be a shining example
of how middle school
does not define you.
-You're gonna do great, Maddie.
-It does plant seeds
for the future.
After all,
I was class president.
-Yeah, you got the school to buy
those extra vending machines.
-With no help from anyone,
I might add.
If I had a campaign slogan,
it would have been,
"Never mind, I'll do it myself."
-Always impressive, Caitlin.
And you didn't get
any hot cocoa this evening.
Don't worry.
I'll wear you down.
Evening, artsy ladies.
Felicity, good luck.
-Thanks.
-Let me help you with that.
-Thank you kindly.
-You're my hero.
You know that?
Being 13 is the worst.
-Tell me about it.
-You really think my baking's
gotten better?
-I-I didn't mean to ...
-No, that's okay.
It's good feedback.
Not everyone will give you
an honest opinion.
I do think James' butter
had something to do with it.
But if you tell anyone
I said that, I'll deny it.
-Got it.
-And disown you.
-My lips are sealed.
-So, how busy are
13-year-olds these days?
-I don't know.
What?
What?!
-Okay, hold it
straight up and down.
Perfect.
Look at that. You're a natural.
-Everybody ready?
Look at you two little elves.
-Look what Aunt Felicity
showed me.
-That's pretty cool, Mad.
-Ready to get a tree?
-I got plenty of rope
to tie it up
and a Thermos full
of Carol's delicious eggnog.
-Don's out front.
He actually likes that stuff.
-Let's wrap this up, Maddie.
-Okay.
-There's a happy kid.
-What did you put
in those cookies?
-Christmas magic.
-All right, let's go.
-I know.
-How come we don't get to
go to the Schumachers'?
I've never been here.
-They retired.
-Hey, guys, wait up.
Christmas trees.
Smells like childhood.
-You guys are slow!
-Hold your horses!
-Oh, you're kidding.
-Hey, folks,
-What's he doing here?
-Anderson Family Farm.
-He sells the trees, too?
Ugh!
-Right, ugh.
A kind, good-looking farmer
milks the cows,
makes the cocoa,
sells the trees.
He's the worst.
-I was kind of a crab
last night.
-Oh, I'm shocked.
-Well, he, like, loves Christmas
way more than most guys.
It's weird.
-Only you would make that
a bad thing.
-Caitlin Rogers seems
pretty interested.
-Aw!
Can you blame her?
-I don't remember him
from school.
-You were too...
-Moody?
-...preoccupied with your
future as an artist.
-This one's nice.
-And he was too focused
on going pro.
-Really?
-It's like a...
-Do you like him?
-I mean, I don't like like him.
I'm moving back to Chicago
as soon as possible,
and happy-go-lucky farmers
can stay in Wisconsin.
-Okay.
Look at these trees!
-Ooh, this one's perfect.
-Fraser fir ...
that is my favorite.
-That's a tall one, Mad.
I think I'll need to put
the angel up.
-No way!
You can still lift me.
-Somebody get lost?
-Did you make these?
-I did.
-They're beautiful, actually.
-That is the first compliment
you've given me, so...
I'll take it.
-Well, I have guilt over being
a Cookie Monster last night.
I'm sorry about that.
-I am sorry, too.
I can get defensive
about my butter.
It's my life's work
you're talking about.
-Well, your life's work
seems to be just the ticket
to getting my life's work
off the ground.
-So the lady wants more?
-The lady requires
about 30 pounds of butter.
-Well, you have come
to the right place.
-Anyway, I, um...
I need to bake my head off if
I'm gonna get out of Aspen Grove
in January.
-Sure.
Let's get you and your
humbug attitude out of here.
-Exactly.
Whoa.
-Uh...
It's a ... It's a weed.
Uh, mistletoe.
-Oh.
-Figured I would...sell it.
-That's ... That's a good
side business.
-It's not just a side business,
it's ... it's also fun.
-I'm gonna get out ...
I'm gonna go.
-Get you that butter!
-Okay, we've got a permit
for the farmers' market.
Now comes the fun part.
-Candy?
-Candy.
-Wait.
Look.
-Well, we're not sampling.
We're doing quality control.
-Mmm.
-Excuse me.
What are you doing?
-Quality control?
-There are no samples.
-My aunt is an amazing baker,
and she's gonna have a booth
at the farmers' market.
We're looking for candy
to use in the recipes.
-Wait.
Are you Felicity Olson?
-Yes.
Why? Did we go to high school
together, too?
-No. You baked cookies for the
dance recital the other night.
They were amazing.
-Thank you.
-Which ones were your favorite?
Market research.
-This girl's gonna
run the world someday.
-Well, I'm old-fashioned,
so definitely the sugar cookies.
Are you planning to open
a storefront?
-No.
-Not yet.
Right.
She's just visiting.
-Do you bake bread?
-Sourdough, country loaf,
pumpkin, you name it.
-What about croissants?
-Chocolate, pistachio,
or butter?
-Cakes?
-If it can be baked,
I can bake it.
-We've been in need
of a good bakery
ever since Mrs. Rockwell left.
-So I've heard.
-Look, Aspen Grove
is a good market...
if you can figure it out.
Mrs. Rockwell
was my biggest customer,
and I sent
a lot of folks her way.
It's one of the best parts
of small-town life.
We help each other.
But lately, things have...
slowed down.
-That's too bad.
-You're never alone in a town
like Aspen Grove.
That's what my parents
taught me.
This was their store.
It would break my heart
to close.
-Maybe if you allowed samples,
you'd have better word-of-mouth.
-Madison!
-No, you're right.
It's probably
time to update that policy.
-I am interested in getting
a sense of what you have.
Maybe there's a way
we can work together.
-Well, we don't do samples.
But we can do, uh, what was it?
Quality control?
Look, if I'm being honest,
I do quality control every day.
-Okay, I'll take them.
-Which ones?
-All of them.
-Oh!
-Wonderful. Really?
-Yes.
Oh, I also need some bulk
chocolate nibs ... 60 percent.
-What's the name
of your business?
For the order form.
-Oh, I don't know
if I have one anymore.
My bakery in Chicago was
called Ginger Snaps, but...
-What about Aspen Grove Bakery?
-Too generic.
Felicity's Cookies?
-But you bake more than
just cookies.
-Right.
Felicity's Christmas Treats?
-Christmas Treats by Felicity?
-Too many words.
-What about
Christmas with Felicity?
-Christmas with Felicity.
-Thank you. Merry Christmas.
-Thank you so much.
Here you go.
Enjoy!
-Awesome.
Hey there, Pumpkin.
Should I introduce you
to my ginger?
-Did you just ask
that dog a question?
-Yes.
-Bless you.
-Thank you.
Oh, glad to see
you and your niece
have gotten into
the Christmas spirit.
-Well, 'tis the season.
Cookie?
-Can I try one?
-Oh, this is Brenda.
She is a Snow Ball volunteer.
-And her cousin.
-Mmm!
These are really good.
-We added lemon zest
and cardamom.
-Wonderful.
But we don't have time.
-Stressed?
-Well, we have the Snow Ball ...
that's the yearly town party ...
in less than two weeks.
We need decorations
that aren't ready yet,
a DJ who, for no reason,
won't return my calls,
and a catering company
that isn't e-mailing me
in a timely manner.
What do you think?
-Sounds like a big deal.
It is. Everybody's getting
dressed up.
-And desserts.
-Really?
-And now this.
I hate to be the bearer
of bad news,
but the board didn't
receive your permit
to sell at the Christmas fair.
-Oh, well, I definitely
submitted my permit.
-That was for
the farmers' market.
This is the Christmas fair.
-They look the same to me.
When did that happen?
-This morning? Today.
Today is the first day
of the Christmas fair.
-Oh. Can I get a permit?
-Sure.
-Great.
-For next year.
This year is full up,
and it's too late.
-But I'm here.
I have a stand.
-These are really good.
-Felicity, this is a carefully
constructed fair.
Now, I know you've been enjoying
making money off the holidays
and baking your little cookies,
but you're not authorized
to be here.
You'll have to leave.
-But ...
-It gives me no pleasure.
But that's the final word
on the matter.
-What do we do now?
-I hate this town.
I hate making my favorite thing
into a business.
I hate Christmas.
-Looks like Brian
is spending Christmas
with his parents in Evanston.
That makes sense.
-It's strange, not having him
around this year.
You talk to him much lately?
Aww!
You used to love this one.
-Oh, yeah, the angel
with the trumpet.
-I recall you and Grace
almost breaking
that one during a fight.
-Sweetie, how are you?
-I'm tired, Mom.
-I'm sure you are.
-I tried so hard in Chicago,
and it didn't work.
And now it's like
I'm just repeating myself here.
It's like I'm on a failure loop.
And I lost Brian.
-Now, you broke up with him,
isn't that right?
He wasn't supportive?
-He was when we started.
But I pushed him away.
I don't know, I just ...
I wanted to prove to myself
that I could do it.
-It's hard to start a business.
-Yeah, but at least
I had someone.
Now I'm all alone.
All I have is Ginger.
-Sorry, Ginger Snap.
-You know, a lot of businesses
fail in the first year.
The fact that you made it two
is impressive.
-Thanks, Dad.
-Hello, my dears.
-As a person who mopes,
I can say this.
You're moping.
-I'm not moping.
-You are moping.
It's annoying.
-Don't ruin Christmas
for everybody.
-Okay, harsh.
Do you feel this way, too?
Wow, okay, not only did I ruin
my relationship and my business,
but my incessant moping is
ruining Christmas for everyone.
I should have just stayed
in Chicago and moped in peace.
You've got to stop.
Try something new.
Look what Maddie did.
-Social media...
and a website, too.
-This looks really good.
-There's an order form
and everything.
You don't need the stand
at the Christmas fair.
-You don't need a permit
from anyone.
-I've tried this
online-business thing.
I couldn't keep up with it while
running the actual business.
There's just too much.
-You just need some help.
-I know you feel alone, darling,
but you do have
more than just Ginger.
-You have us.
-Oh, I don't know how
to accept this.
-It's done! Accept.
-And hire me as your PR
and social-media manager.
-Yeah, you need
someone on your level.
-Okay.
Let's do it.
-Good...
because I already got you
another gig.
-Already?
-Question.
How do you feel
about good-looking farmers?
-My tree is set up in my room
with my favorite ornaments.
It's magical. Thank you.
-I'm so glad.
I'll see you in there.
You're a lifesaver.
-Saving lives with cookies.
What was that about?
-We had some spare branches
from the farm, so we put
Charlie Brown Christmas trees
in all the rooms.
-Are you a real person?
-What?
-Nothing.
It's just really nice.
-Anyway, I guess Mrs. Rockwell
used to supply desserts
to tonight's party every year.
Looks like they didn't get
the memo she left town.
-I appreciate the work.
-Oh, you're glad to see me, too.
-No. I mean...
-Money, money, money.
I-I know. I know.
Do you need to take that?
-Uh, no.
Let's set up.
-Okay.
-Oh, no, don't please.
You're too nice.
-Oh, yeah, here.
Just kidding.
Maybe I am too nice.
-That's an awful lot
to choose from.
My wife used to make these.
Pretzels for antlers.
-Did she really?
Sounds like a fun lady.
-It's a hard time of year
to miss someone.
-It is.
Merry Christmas.
-Merry Christmas to you.
-I never know if I'm saying
the right thing.
-You're doing pretty good.
Can I introduce you to someone?
-James, you've thrown another
wonderful party.
-Grandma, this is Felicity.
-Pleased to meet you.
I'm Nora.
-Lovely to meet you.
-James told me you
baked these cookies.
They're remarkable.
-She should know.
She gave Mrs Rockwell
her first job as a baker.
-Of course, she wasn't
Mrs. Rockwell then.
She was just Bonnie.
-That is an honor, then.
Thank you.
-Did you go to culinary school?
-Actually, I went to art school.
-Really?
-Really.
But after I graduated,
I got a job at a bakery
to pay the rent,
and I fell in love with it.
-Art for the taste buds.
-That's right.
-Do you have a new bakery
here in town?
I'm sure you're successful.
-No, I live in Chicago now.
Uh, my bakery...
Well, we had to close.
-So, uh, what are you
doing here now?
-Well, I guess this is the part
where I'm getting back
on my feet.
-Sometimes, trying again is even
harder than just starting out.
-Yeah, I think you're right.
-You're polite with me,
but I can tell you're a fighter.
Takes one to know one.
And James knows something
about hard times.
-She doesn't want
to hear about that.
-But he has put such
dedicated work into the farm.
He's made us proud.
-Yeah, I can see that.
-Hey, thanks again.
You made her week.
I didn't realize you've been
going through all that.
-Oh, it's okay.
-With that and the wedding,
it must be...
I'm sorry.
Grace mentioned.
-Grace always mentions it.
It's no big deal.
Hey, thanks again.
It was really nice
to bake for people
who actually appreciate it.
-So you're gonna have a booth
at the Christmas fair
tomorrow night, right?
-Nope. Caitlin wouldn't
give me a permit.
No permit, no booth.
-Caitlin is a stickler
for the rules.
-You think?
-But...
I have a booth.
Who's to say
I can't sell dessert?
-No, I can't let you do that.
-We've been a success twice.
We should team up again.
-Okay.
Okay, in the spirit
of letting people help me,
which I'm trying to be
better at...
count me in.
-Great!
Business partners.
-Kiss!
Kiss.
-Uh...
I hung that. Sorry.
-It's a weed, right?
-Uh, yeah.
Yeah, it's a ... it's a weed.
-It's tradition!
-You can do better than that.
-Uh...
-Okay, I'm gonna ...
I'll see you later.
-See you later, Felicity.
-Hey, sweetie.
-Hey, Mom, Dad.
-You're in a good mood
this morning.
-Yeah, I guess I am.
Something about
a fresh snowfall.
I see you two playing footsie,
by the way.
Reminds me of Christmas morning.
-Oh, every year, a tangerine
at the bottom of your stocking.
Your grandmother did it, too.
-I'm gonna borrow these
to make something ...
gingerbread with
tangerine essence and peel.
Dipped in chocolate?
-Mm, shaped like stockings.
-Love it.
Do not love it.
-What is it?
-Look at how many orders I have.
-Oh, my.
That's a good problem.
-And I'm doing the cookies
for the Christmas fair tonight.
I'm gonna faint.
-No, you're not.
We're here for you.
-We are.
-Wow!
-That's a lot of orders.
-You just tell us what to do,
kiddo.
-Okay, everybody, smile!
-Hello.
-Felicity?
-Brian.
How are you?
-Good. I'm, uh...
It's good to hear your voice.
-You, too.
Sorry about that.
-Having a good time?
-Actually, I am.
You?
-Well, I was on a break
at work,
just wasting some time online,
and I saw some amazing cookies
come up in my feed.
Beautiful photos,
a great, great website.
-Business is booming.
-It looks like it, yeah.
I'm proud of you.
-I'm proud of me, too.
Oh, that was corny.
-No, no, no, no.
It's good to hear you
laugh again.
I know it's been hard.
-Well, your name was on the
wedding invites, too, remember?
-Oh, I remember.
-I can't tell
what you're thinking.
-I'm thinking, I miss you.
-I miss you, too.
But we shouldn't ...
-I miss you cooking dinner.
I miss that spot of flour
on your cheek
at the end of the day.
I wonder, uh, maybe...
-Felicity!
How do you want to display
the snickerdoodles?
-I should go.
Um...
We have so many orders,
it's ridiculous.
But wonderful.
-Yeah.
Okay. Uh...
can we talk again soon?
-Yeah. Okay.
Um, I got to go.
-Okay. Uh, bye.
-Bye.
-Almost finished.
I'm gonna need coffee.
-Just wait.
Look. New orders.
-Good news travels fast.
-Thank you so much.
I'm not used to this.
It's been really...
-We're glad you're back, too.
-So, Brian called.
Twice.
-Why?
-Don't be mad.
-I'm not mad, I'm just...
I'm protective.
-Brian is a good man.
-Brian wants to be a good man.
-Well, his intentions are good.
He's made a few mistakes
in the execution.
-I still love him.
I think I always will.
-Of course you will.
-But how did you know that
Don was the one for you?
-It was not in the big gesture,
the way you see in the movies.
It was really..
ordinary.
I had just gone back to work,
and I was new at the office.
And he was this cute,
nerdy doctor.
I was rushing because
I was nervous,
and I was carrying all
these forms and a coffee.
And I ran right into him,
and I dropped my coffee ...
splat, on the floor.
It was a mess.
But as I was cleaning it up,
I just remember him
bending down and saying,
"Can I get you a new coffee?
How do you like it?"
And I knew.
-Well, that's a completely
boring story.
-Well, not to me.
'Cause I remember his face.
And I remember thinking,
"That's the man
you're gonna spend
the rest of your life with."
I was shocked.
I did not see it coming.
You know, Felicity,
you've always wanted things
in the extreme ...
big city, the painting studio...
a bakery, perhaps before
you were ready.
-Hey!
-It's not a bad thing.
But there is so much to be found
in the simple things.
There is magic everywhere,
even in Aspen Grove.
You just have to open
your eyes to it.
-Evening, folks.
Ready to warm up?
-Two cocoas, please.
-And two vanilla
shortbread cookies.
-Absolutely.
-We've been trying
to figure it out,
but what do you
put in your cocoa?
-Definitely cinnamon.
-Definitely.
But what else?
-Don't look at me.
I still haven't tried it.
-It's Christmas cheer.
-Fine. Keep your secrets.
-Merry Christmas.
-Well, this is all gorgeous.
You two should take a walk
and check it out.
-Grace, your sister has
never had my cocoa.
-Have you had any of my cookies?
-You hit me
the last time I tried.
Oh-ho, I am not falling
for that again.
-What?
You can't sell
if you don't know
what the goods taste like.
So do a taste test
and take a walk.
Go!
-After you.
-And that, dear,
is how it's done.
-Let's get some cookies.
-Just one.
-Oh, hey, Caitlin.
Have you been able
to enjoy the fair?
-Yes, Daniel was
willing to put up with
his mom for an evening, and I'll
take whatever I can get.
-I understand.
Maddie's gotten into working
with her aunt,
so I have been lucky
to see more of her lately.
-You decorated these?
-Some of them.
-Cool.
-Speaking of which,
is Felicity...?
-Oh, she's just on break.
Get her mind off
that ex-fiancé of hers.
And James is so sweet, right?
-He is.
-I do feel bad, though,
about the whole permit thing.
-Yeah.
Cait, you got to loosen up.
I know you're overwhelmed,
but it's the holidays.
-Right?
Right. I shouldn't have
been so hard on Felicity.
Is she, um...
still mourning
about the wedding, you think?
-She thinks she is.
Keeps talking about Brian.
She's had a hard year.
But I say, rock bottom
is a blessing.
In with the new.
-Brian ... rock bottom.
Got it.
-So, which cookie's
got your eye?
-I'll take a snowman.
-And I'll do a brownie.
Wow, that's good!
Peppermint?
-Genius, right?
-Okay. Sorry I waited.
This is the best hot cocoa
I've ever had.
-Cayenne.
-Really?
-Yeah, just a pinch.
-That's not very
Wisconsin of you.
-No, no. Something I got
from my teammate's aunt.
-Hmm, you're changing my whole
perspective on football players.
-But these cookies ... I could
get fat on these.
-All that innocent butter.
-No, I can just tell you know
what you're doing
'cause I have never had
anything like this around here.
-That's big-city French bakery
training for you.
Layers of unsalted butter,
room-temperature eggs,
creaming the butter
and sugar just right
so the sugar crystals
perfectly aerate the butter.
It's scientific,
but also an art.
-You miss your bakery, huh?
-I used to wake up at
4:00 a.m. every morning
just to roll out cookie dough
and bread loaves.
Take the rolls out of the oven
for the die-hard
early customers.
I was so proud of it.
For a while.
-What happened,
if you don't mind?
-Well, it wasn't the baking.
Never was.
I just didn't know what I needed
to know as a new business owner,
if ... if that makes sense.
-It does.
-It was so expensive.
At the same time, my
relationship was falling apart.
I couldn't pay rent.
Brian had just made partner,
and he would come by the bakery
after work,
and he'd be in a suit,
and I'd be on the kitchen floor
covered in flour, crying.
When did it get so complicated?
When I was younger,
I used to think
that you would
just fall in love,
and that would be enough.
So stupid.
Real life isn't romantic at all.
-I'm not buying that.
-Not buying what?
-I think you do believe
that life is romantic.
You might even believe
in Christmas cheer
and all that other corny stuff.
But you're telling yourself
you don't, that you're above it.
-Why would I do that?
-Maybe because sometimes
second chances hurt.
They can be even harder than
starting out for the first time.
-Wait a minute, did you
just quote your grandma?
-No.
-You so did!
-I'd be more embarrassed if
she wasn't right all the time.
-Why do you love
Christmas so much?
-Oh, you think it's funny, a guy
would like Christmas this much?
-No.
I mean, a little.
-Well, we did miss each other
in high school.
-You would have never liked me,
by the way.
-Oh, I don't know about that.
I think you would have
intimidated me.
You may not know this,
but after graduation,
I went right into college ball
and was slated to go pro,
get snatched up pretty quickly.
-What happened?
-That's where my luck ran out.
I got knocked down,
like everybody does,
but I hit my head
too many times.
Got a few concussions.
And the last one I had was the
final practice before Christmas.
I got knocked out cold.
It was terrifying.
My mom tells me
it was terrifying, I mean.
Uh, all I remember is waking up
on Christmas morning.
My family had slept
at the hospital.
My parents, grandma,
brother and sister.
The room was just decorated.
There were lights and
a tree in the corner.
Mom was crying.
My grandma, she was crying.
My dad, he was trying
not to cry.
Every Christmas since then...
I just feel really grateful
to celebrate the holiday.
To try and make the world
just a little bit happier.
-You're...
-What?
-You're different
than I thought you were.
-So are you.
-I think I'm starting to see
why you like Christmas so much.
-I like Christmas so much.
-What are you doing?
-Listening to it.
-What's it telling you?
-That it's done.
-You're awfully chipper.
Did you have a nice walk
last night?
Enjoy some Christmas carols?
Sample some hot chocolate?
-So what if I did?
-Look at little miss
"I hate Christmas."
All star-eyed.
-Can I help?
-You want to remove that cake
from its round?
-Sure thing.
-Ow!
Oh! Ow, ow, ow, ow!
I'm sorry.
-Not so graceful, are we, Grace?
-How rude.
-Don't worry about it.
I'll just bake another one.
This is cute.
-Yeah, I like that.
-For your mom?
-I think she has
that one already.
-What is one more reindeer?
-Oh, Aunt Felicity? Can you
pick up something and pose?
I want to show you
being normal and shopping.
-Being normal?
-You know what I mean.
For the socials.
We need to populate the pages.
Smile!
And who's that for?
-No one.
I just picked it up
'cause you told me to.
-But we have to tell a story.
Right. Um...
-People will respond more
if there's an emotional
connection.
They want to know
why you're buying it.
Like, is it for someone special?
-Someone special?
-I mean, we can make it up
or whatever,
but we don't want to lie,
so it's a balance.
-Let's just say
it's for your grandpa.
That's someone special, right?
-Not James?
-That's a can of worms
I can't deal with yet.
-But you are gonna
get him something, right?
-Maybe.
But don't post that.
-Why?
-I can't put my feelings
out into the world.
It's too soon, and what if
somebody sees it?
-Like James?
-Or Brian.
I don't want to blindside him
at Christmas.
I'll let him know
in my own time.
-Okay, so it's for Grandpa.
Aunt Felicity...
how do you know
if a boy likes you?
-You're asking me?
-Well, you do have two boys
that like you right now.
Okay, fair enough.
Well, the first question
I would ask is,
do you like this boy?
-I don't know.
-But maybe, right?
-Yeah, but I don't want to
like him if he doesn't like me.
-Yeah, that's the hard part,
because you got to
put yourself out there,
and that might mean
you could get hurt.
But if you don't,
you might miss out on the chance
at being really happy.
-Okay.
-There are ways that
you can tell, though, like...
does he listen to you?
Do you feel like
you can be yourself around him?
-This is stressful.
-Tell me about it.
But it's like you were saying ...
it's a balancing act
between protecting yourself
and putting yourself out there.
-Thanks.
Sometimes it's hard to talk
to my mom about this stuff.
-Sure. I mean,
what are aunts for?
-Are you actually gonna
buy that for grandpa?
-Well, I don't want to be
a liar on the social.
-Sharon, I don't care
if your daughter has the plague.
I need those cupcakes
in two days.
Don't bother me
until they're done.
-Peppermint mocha for Felicity.
-Caitlin, hi.
-Festive drink order.
-I feel like I'm getting into
the holiday season, finally.
Oh, your cousin Brenda
ordered cookies.
If you see her, tell her
they'll be ready tomorrow.
-Well, you'll have to
tell her yourself.
She quit.
-Oh, I'm sorry.
Like I said, never mind,
I'll do it myself.
-But the Snow Ball's
coming together?
-Amazingly.
Couldn't be better.
-Great. Well, my family and I
are planning on being there.
So good luck with everything.
Really.
-Bless you.
-Triple-shot gingerbread latte.
-Hi, baby.
Making friends out here?
What's gotten into...?
You.
-Felicity.
-Good morning.
I did not mean to startle you.
-Let me get that.
-Thank you.
-Can I get you a new coffee?
-How do you like it?
-Hello?
-Um, Brian, what are you
doing here?
-Brian?
-James, this is Brian.
Brian, this is James.
-Nice to meet you.
-I'm sorry, who are you?
-Um, James sells the incredible
butter I use in my cookies.
-Fantastic.
The local supplier.
-Brian, listen ...
-I know.
I know it's a surprise,
but let me take you to lunch.
-I-I-I have so much to do.
-Oh, come on.
You've got to eat.
It's so good to see you.
-James, I-I'm sorry.
I need to...
I'll see you later?
-Of course, yeah.
-It was nice to meet you, man.
-James.
-Right.
Come on, Ginger.
She missed me.
-So, now you've met the fiancé.
-Ex-fiancé.
-Well, not quite.
Last night, Grace was telling me
that Felicity has been
talking about him
the whole time she's been back.
Well, I mean, of course,
I'm sure you can tell that
Grace has been trying
to push Felicity on you.
-You don't...
They're not...
back together?
-Oh, yeah, she's stuck on him.
And who can blame her?
Successful lawyer.
But I'm sure you gave her
a huge confidence boost
when she needed it most?
Nice guy like you.
-Bless you.
-Thank you. See?
Nice.
-I almost forgot how this town
goes all out for the holiday.
I think I saw
a snowman-building contest.
-Isn't it great?
-I guess you got to find
something to do
in a town this small.
-Well, I kind of like it.
-Well, let's cut to the chase.
-Always a lawyer.
-Well, I'm ... I'm nervous.
-No, don't be.
-It's just me.
-Yeah, it's just you.
I miss you.
You miss me.
Chicago misses you.
-I doubt that.
-It's so good to see you.
-You, too.
I've been thinking about you.
-Oh, yeah?
-Yeah.
Now you're here,
and I have to say,
it's kind of strange.
-I get that.
But hear me out.
I was wrong not to believe in
you when I had the chance.
-Thank you.
-I mean, you're blowing up.
-Yeah, I am.
-I always knew you could do more
when you put your mind to it.
-I seem to remember you making
that point clear.
-Right, uh ...
-Before work.
After work.
After that party
at the Shadducks'.
-I had a huge case I was
dealing with at that time.
-And you were embarrassed by me
at that dinner.
-No, that's not accurate.
-You had just made partner,
and you laughed
at my sales figures
in front of everyone.
-It was some gentle mocking.
I wanted you to be better.
I-Isn't that what
loving someone is?
Seeing the best in them?
-But it wasn't for
a lack of trying.
I needed help.
If I could start over
and go back,
I would do things
the way I'm doing it now,
from the ground up,
but with you,
it always felt like
I was chasing your approval.
-It kills me because I never,
ever meant for it
to come off like that.
You argue a lot more
than you used to.
-I learned from the best.
-Listen, I have it
on pretty good authority
that there's a storefront
in Lincoln Park near the office
that would be perfect
for a bakery.
-I can't afford that yet.
-I can help you.
Pay for professional marketing,
whatever you need.
-So what?
I set up shop in a place
that you like
in a neighborhood
that you approve of,
now that I have this
online following,
now that I'm a success?
-Exactly.
-What about you and me?
-We can give it another go.
I mean, you've ...
you've grown so much.
-Now that you're proud of me?
-You were floundering.
It was so hard before.
You were unhappy.
-That's when you fight
for the other person.
I helped you pay your bills
during law school by baking.
-I know that. You don't
have to bring it up.
-I loved you
when you were struggling,
and when the tables were turned,
you laughed at me.
-And I said I was sorry.
-What am I even doing here?
This is why we broke up.
-Felicity.
You're making a scene.
-I have to go.
-Felic...
-Lost your number.
James.
-Hey.
I wanted to explain
to you about earlier.
-That was your fiancé,
wasn't it?
-Brian is not ...
-How sweet of him to drive in
from the city to see you.
-Yeah, well, I wanted
to explain to you about ...
-There's no need to explain.
I just...
I don't want to hear
any more about this guy.
-Okay.
-I thought something
was happening here or...
I'm not interested
in ... in this.
-Okay, got it.
-I'm glad you're feeling better
and you're all set
to get out of Aspen Grove.
I think you're just...
-You think I'm what?
-Doesn't matter.
Look, I'm a nice guy.
Sure, but there's a line.
You called off your wedding
six months ago.
You're not ready to move on yet.
-Okay, got it. I thought
you were being nice to me.
I thought you liked me,
but you're actually
just nice to everybody.
James ...
everybody's best friend.
But it's just a cover
because you're afraid to commit.
-I'm nice.
I am a nice guy.
But I'm not a fool.
-Okay, no.
Thank you, but please stop.
-What?
-Where's Maddie?
She's so much better at this.
-I miss the Christmas Felicity,
back when you lived up
to your name.
-Look, you want to help?
Order forms, boxes, cookies.
You know the drill.
Thank you!
-This really is impressive.
Do you think you've made enough
to move back to Chicago?
-I think so.
I mean, I don't have
a future here.
-You mean you don't have
a future with James.
I haven't seen you
so happy in years.
You should talk to him.
-He's right.
I wasn't fair to him.
Six months after
calling off a wedding?
I blew it.
I wish I could blame Brian,
but it's me.
It's always been me,
standing in my own way.
-Well, at least you've come
to your senses.
-Enlightenment is a blast.
It's not too late, you know?
Tomorrow's Christmas Eve.
There's time for
a last-minute miracle.
-Grace, please.
I'm so tired of Christmas.
I just wanted to survive the
holidays without falling apart,
and here I am again.
-Mom! Aunt Felicity!
-Hey, who's this?
-Oh, this is Daniel.
-Where Madison has been
instead of cookie decorating.
-Mom!
Thanks for ratting me out.
-See?
Everyone gets their
priorities confused
between romance and work.
-You have to come.
My mom ...
-She's losing it.
Sorry.
-Maddie!
-What?
That's what's happening.
-Who's your mom?
-You're not gonna like
the answer to that one.
-Mom, I brought back-up.
-No, I don't want your help.
-Uh, too late.
What's going on?
-All of the volunteers
have given up,
and everyone who said they were
gonna bake cookies have...
have quit.
I guess I'm not
very good with people.
-Oh, no.
-Who would say that?
-Please.
I'm just trying
to make everything
beautiful and perfect.
And I'm so tired.
-Listen, Caitlin!
That Christmas you see
in magazines or...
-Social media.
-It doesn't exist.
Christmas is just
a bunch of imperfect people
getting together and doing
their best to celebrate life.
-It's just, ever since
Daniel's dad and I got divorced,
I've been pushing so hard.
-You're doing great.
-Why are you being
so nice to me?
-Because I've been
where you are,
and when I needed help,
people stepped in.
-What is it?
-I'm so sorry,
I shouldn't have told James
that you were getting
back together with your ex.
-You what?
-Please don't hate me.
-No.
I don't hate you.
I just...
It makes sense.
-I mean, you just show up here,
lost and broke,
all, "Oh, I don't know
what I'm gonna do.
I'll just bake cookies, I guess.
And I'm so pretty and angry
and interesting because
I live in Chicago."
-Okay, that's one take
on the situation.
-Nobody helps me do anything.
And then you come here
and you push people away,
and then they help you,
and you don't even have to ask.
I mean, how do you do that?
-Honestly, I have no idea,
but you're totally right.
-And you were rude to James,
and he just liked you more.
-How can we help you?
-Can you say that part
about James again?
-I just get lonely sometimes.
I'm so sorry that
I've been so...
-Caitlin, how can we help?
-Are you serious?
-You have to let people
in sometimes.
I had to learn that, too.
-And what better time
than at Christmas?
-Well.
I guess James has
the pine-bough decorations,
but the lights aren't up,
the stage isn't set,
and I have no drinks ready
and no desserts.
-Okay.
We're in emergency mode.
Operation Snow Ball.
Don't roll your eyes at me.
This is big, people.
Let's get to work.
-Mmm!
Whoo!
Carol, you have really
outdone yourself
with this eggnog!
The belle of the ball!
-Oh, stop.
-Oh!
Think you can make room
on your dance card for me?
-Always.
-All right, you two lovebirds.
Let's go.
-Oh sweetheart, you look lovely.
-Oh, thanks, Mom.
But look at you.
-You're both beautiful!
Look at me, I'm all hopped up
on Christmas cheer.
-What did you put
in his nog, mom?
-Come here.
We have loved
having you home, darling.
-Aww, thanks, Dad.
And I was wondering,
if it's not too big of a pain,
if Ginger and I stayed
through New Year's?
-Not at all.
We'd love to have you.
-Does this mean you're staying
in Aspen Grove?
-Yeah, I guess it does.
-Oh, our family all together
in the same town.
We couldn't be happier.
-Well, I promise I won't
stay too long.
I know you two like
your privacy.
-Mm, that's true, we do.
-Little bit. Yeah, we do.
-All right, I get it.
You're in love.
Knock it off. Let's go.
-I feel like I got
my sister back.
The one who loved
Christmas so much
and believed anything
was possible.
I missed her.
-Well, who knew that having
your heart broken
and losing everything
and then baking and baking...
-And baking.
-...could do that to you?
Merry Christmas, Grace.
-Merry Christmas, Felicity.
-Doors open in five.
Where's Caitlin?
-Poor thing.
-She's got a lot of expectations
to sleep off, I guess.
-It's a shame
we do that to ourselves.
-Doesn't really fit in with
the holiday season, does it?
You end up missing out
on the best time of year.
-Oh, can I get you and Maddie
in the photo booth
before there's a line?
-Absolutely.
Wait just one minute, though.
-Just one?
-One minute is literally
all this should take.
-Grace.
Grace.
-James, Felicity is
obsessed with you.
I haven't seen my sister
so happy in years.
-But Brian...
-Forget Brian.
She has, I have, we all have.
He's back in Chicago.
She sent him away.
-You did?
-Yeah.
-Kids, get it together.
Talk.
Merry Christmas.
-Ooh, look at you!
-Hey.
-Hey!
-Did it work?
-Yes.
-I thought you guys
were getting back together.
-I thought you didn't want
somebody so lost and confused.
-I don't.
But that's not you, is it?
-No.
I know what I want.
I want to stay in Aspen Grove.
I want to bake.
And I want to do things my way
in my business.
-No kidding.
-But I also want to do it with
a little help from my friends.
-That's good news.
-Why is that?
-'Cause you're gonna need
the best butter
in the state of Wisconsin,
and I just so happen to know
a nice guy who can help you out.
-Oh, do you?
-Yeah.
Felicity, whose name means
delight and joy.
-I am not always delightful.
-Yes, you are.
-Look.
-Well, that weed
just won't quit, will it?
'Cause that's where I wanna be
- Want