- Let's go
over it one more time.
What happened after that?
Answer the question.
- I was talking to him.
- Where were
you when that happened?
- A few feet away.
- Did you try to stop
him?
Answer the question.
Did you try to stop him?
- Have you ever had a
moment when your mind
was completely free, blank?
No thoughts at all I mean.
Empty.
Peaceful.
I was looking for that my whole
life,
but all I ever found
was obsession, darkness,
cold, deep darkness.
- And what
happened after the phone call?
- The
station sent two officers
to check the apartment.
- Sir, this is the police.
Put the gun down.
- They found Jay on his
knees,
pointing the gun to his own
head, frozen.
They kept calling him,
but he wasn't moving.
- I could feel it.
A painful crack in my chest,
My ribs falling apart.
Bones crumbling.
I had to learn how to deal with
it.
- The main door was
cracked open,
and they could see someone
laying on the floor.
That became the priority.
- But now I knew
what it is.
It was you.
You are always in the air.
I was breathing you.
Hey, shh, shh, shh.
Everything's gonna be okay.
I know what I need to do now.
- There were mirror
stands everywhere, all broken.
A pool a blood from one side to
the other.
It was too late.
The victim was stabbed in the
stomach with a shard of glass.
- You're the one who
smokes.
Not me.
- I've never seen
anything like this before.
He wasn't moving, and
his eyes were wide open,
staring into the distance.
- Just like Judie said.
- I remember.
I remember everything.
- Everything is gonna be
okay.
I promise.
- Our beloved Judie faced
this disease in the same way...
She was an example to all of us,
always putting the needs
of others before her own.
Judie was a good daughter.
She was great sister to Jay.
And she was a friend.
A real friend.
She only asked for one
thing before she passed.
I'm glad that we can all be
here today to do this for her.
She always loved the light here.
This is where she wanted to be.
Judie...
we'll never forget you.
- I'm so sorry for your loss,
Jay.
I want you to know that the
entire crew is with you.
- Jay.
We never met before,
but I knew your sister,
and I'm really sorry for your
loss.
She was a very special, special
person.
Take care of yourself.
I wish you well.
- How dare you?
How dare you bring one of your
sluts here?
Do you have no respect for your
sister?
Shame on you.
- You're just jealous.
Jealous I finally have
somebody else in my life
except for you.
- Don't play with me, kid.
This is family stuff. This is
family.
Our family.
- Yeah, well, maybe that's
family now.
- Don't be stupid. You don't
even know these people.
Is that the watch?
Shame on you.
- Can you tell
me about your relationship
with his sister?
- I was her therapist
for the last eight years.
She died of cancer about six
months ago.
The only time I ever met Jay
was at his sister's funeral.
- Did they tell
you who the victim is?
- But I don't understand,
detective.
Why do you need me here?
- No.
- Is everything okay?
- I'm fine.
- I saw your mother
talking to you.
She was staring at me the whole
time.
- Don't worry about her.
- Probably wasn't the
best idea for me to come.
- Don't say that.
- No, I didn't belong there.
- You do belong there.
You're family. She needs
to understand that.
She's always trying to
control my fucking life.
I'm sick of her.
- I understand. But she seemed
pretty...
- She's just like that.
You know what she's like.
- No, I don't.
Jay, seriously, how could I know
that?
I'm just saying maybe
it wasn't the best idea
to introduce me at your sister's
funeral.
- What are you talking about?
- How did he wake up,
detective? What did you do?
- I did nothing. I just
called him by his name.
Jay...
Can you hear me?
He didn't know how he got there,
what happened in his house,
or why he was trying to kill
himself.
- No.
- Mm!
This is delicious.
Did you make it?
- Yes. All fresh and
organic.
- Mm!
- It's from the store,
right?
- That's right.
- What store?
- Jay didn't tell you?
I run a distribution company of
organic
and mostly vegetarian food.
And last year I opened a brick
and mortar store downtown.
- It's actually where we
met.
- So you were the client
falling in love with the owner.
- Maybe.
Maybe it's the other way around.
- Hmm. Maybe.
- Let's start from the
beginning.
How did you get to this point?
- He called 911
himself a few hours ago.
Sergeant, can you play
the recording please?
- He's trying to do it
again.
I can't allow it. Not this time.
I think I know how to stop him.
This is wrong.
Shut up!
- Who's he talking to?
We think it's possible there
may have been someone else
there.
- He brought her to my
house. He brought her here.
- And what happened
after the phone call?
- So you're a vegetarian now?
- I like to eat healthy.
- Just saying, have you
seen yourself in the mirror?
- The mirror?
What about the mirror?
- I've never seen you so skinny.
And I hardly see you.
- Can you stop?
You wanna stop telling me what
to do?
- Hey, hey, come on.
Let's not get into one
of your fights right now.
Okay? Let's just enjoy this
dinner.
- I'm just saying you
need your protein,
or I'm gonna be seeing
your bones very soon.
- Meat is not the only
way to get protein.
We can all get plenty without
eating meat.
- Are you one of those animal
lovers?
- Yes, I am.
You have any pets?
- We used to have a dog
many years ago
when these two guys were kids
and living in the country
with me.
- What was his name?
- Roy.
His name was Roy.
- Do you guys
remember him?
- Vaguely.
- You were very little,
maybe eight or nine.
- What happened to Roy...
if I may ask.
- Someone left the door
open, and he ran away.
- Ran away?
- Yeah. Simple as that.
He left.
See, it isn't true that
animals always love you.
- There's something...
something very dark in this
family
that I was never quite able to
see.
Judie had been keeping a
secret for over 20 years
to protect her little brother.
But there's a time in one of our
sessions
that she told me about something
that happened in the country
house.
Jay was only eight years old.
Something happened with their
dog.
- So how's work, sweetheart?
- It's...
fine.
We closed down the contract this
week, and um...
They start in a couple weeks.
- Good.
I hope you'll be able to afford
a better place than this soon.
- Jay...
I'm so proud of you.
Congratulations.
Congrats.
- Congrats.
- What?
- Yeah, what, mom?
Stop it.
- We don't need
guns here.
Okay? Just calm down, Jay.
Guys, lower the guns.
- At this point, we're not
rushing.
We're just taking the time to
negotiate.
All right, Jay. Now it's your
turn.
Put your gun down so we can
talk.
Slowly.
Very slowly.
I'm going outside to smoke.
- You said you were
gonna stop.
- Give me a break, Mom. Hm?
- Judie, you shouldn't be
smoking in your condition.
- She's actually right, you
know.
- I'm gonna die anyways, right?
So just let me enjoy the
time that I have left.
You wanna smoke?
- Oh, no thanks.
I don't smoke.
- It's okay. You don't have
to be shy if you wanna smoke.
Go with her.
- No, Jay.
I don't smoke.
I never did,
But I will join you
outside for some fresh air.
- All right.
Let's have some girl talk.
- Just like Judie said.
- This happened before?
- Not while I knew her, and not
like this.
I mean, Judie did talk about how
Jay
had some strange experiences
in his sleep as a child,
but after we discussed it some
more,
I realized it was just sleep
paralysis.
It can be pretty disturbing
if you don't know what it is.
It's kind of the state in
between being awake and
dreaming.
Your mind is aware, but
your muscles are relaxed
as if you're still asleep.
You can think clearly, but you
might also have visions, too,
which makes it extremely unclear
what is real and what is the
dream.
You have no voluntary muscular
control.
It's like being trapped in your
own body.
You can see, but you
might also have flashes
from your dreams as well,
because the door to the
unconscious mind
hasn't quite closed yet.
- Don't be
afraid.
Do you remember me?
She wouldn't let see you for a
long time,
your sister, but I never left
you.
Now that she is gone, there is
one more thing you have to do.
Remember.
Do you remember me?
- Jay.
- Do you remember me now?
- Jay, wake up!
- I'm Dr. Rivers.
I was called here to assist.
- Thank you for coming.
Please have a seat.
Wait here for a moment.
- He's here.
- What did he say to you? The
cop.
Was it about me?
- No, Jay. It was not
about you.
But I have to leave for a
moment.
- Why? It was about me, wasn't
it?
- I just need a few
moments, Jay.
Just a few minutes.
Everything's fine, I promise.
Are you gonna be okay?
- Just a few minutes.
Okay.
Be quick.
- Jay? Can you hear me?
- Judie.
What are you doing here?
- Thank you for coming.
I am Diana Suarez, the detective
in charge of this case,
You have already met Sergeant
Marquez,
who's directing the police
response.
As you can see, we're dealing
with a very complicated
situation here.
- I was her therapist for the
last...
Why do you need me?
Something happened with their
dog.
- Jay's talking to
me as if I was his sister.
- Did she follow the
procedure?
Officer, I need you to
answer the question.
- I think she saw the
opportunity to connect with him.
- I understand that it's
difficult to believe
that he sees Judie instead of
you,
but our mind can affect the way
that we experience the world
and what we call reality.
We see what we want or
what we need to see.
And right now, Jay needs his
sister.
Maybe...
Maybe we can take advantage of
that.
It's a long shot, but we might
be able to use the connection
that he has with Judie to
delve into his unconscious.
- How do we go about
doing that?
- If it was sleep paralysis,
he wouldn't have been
able to move or speak,
but he still would have been
a conscious, silent witness.
He just doesn't remember it.
- It's worth a shot.
But how do I keep the illusion
going?
I made it work for a while,
but having a confrontation
is very different.
- Connect on the same emotional
level.
We all have secrets.
Think back to something that
you feel responsible for,
to something that you feel
guilty about.
Bring it forward.
Project it onto Jay just like
Judie did.
Our mind is an incredible tool.
It has a way of connecting us
on a number of different levels
that we can't even
understand or comprehend.
We need to guide Jay to
that part of his unconscious
that he shares with Judie.
That's where we're gonna
find the broken memories
of what happened here.
- Do you want to talk about it?
- You want a drink?
- I'm good.
- There was something
different this time.
- What was it?
- I saw who was keeping
the dog in the leash.
It was a kid.
- A kid?
- Yeah.
- Who was he?
- I don't know.
- What did he look like?
- He wore a mask on half his
face.
This side.
The whole left side.
- So you don't know what he
looks like?
- He showed me, but I couldn't
see.
I think he hurt himself.
- Hey...
It's okay.
You're tired, Jay.
It was a stressful day
yesterday at the funeral.
It was a big deal.
All this is gonna take time.
- There was something else.
The kid...
He said he'd been with me the
whole time.
- Hey...
Jay...
- I don't wanna...
Don't touch me.
- Jay.
- Don't fucking touch me.
- Jay, Jay, Jay.
It was just a dream.
It was a dream. It was just a
dream.
It was a dream!
Jay.
- Okay.
- Well, what was it then?
- Dr. Rivers, I've set up a line
for you.
Detective Suarez will hear
everything that you say.
I've also set up a camera
with a view of everything
that is happening in the yard.
You can see it on that screen
right there.
- You want to protect Jay.
Judie wants to protect him from
the world,
from other people, from himself
too.
Remember, it's all about
Jay. There's no resistance.
- Where have you been?
You said a few minutes.
- I know.
- Only a few minutes.
That's what you said to me.
- Yes, I know. I know. You're
right.
I'm sorry, okay?
But I'm here now.
Like always.
Jay, I just wanna talk.
Like we always did.
- She cares about him.
- I'm worried about you.
I've never seen you like this
before.
I feel for you.
There must be a reason
why you would point a gun
to your head.
- I'm trying. I'm trying
really hard, but I...
I can't remember.
- There's one thing that
Judie always said about Jay.
Hidden fear.
He may seem distant, but
he's deeply tormented inside.
Go with it. You feel what he
feels.
- I'm scared, Jay.
I'm scared.
Because I know how painful
it is not to remember.
- I'm broken.
- You need to connect with that.
- I can't put all the pieces
together.
- Use that connection.
- Yes we can. Yes we can.
We can do it together, you
and I. Okay?
- And dig deep into his
memories,
starting with the last
thing that he remembers.
- What is the last
thing that you remember?
- Last night, I fell asleep.
I passed out and I...
I woke up here. I don't know
how.
- What did you do last
night?
- I was just drinking.
- Were you alone?
- He left me.
He left me, Judie.
So I started to drink.
I passed out and he wasn't here.
- Did he say "he"?
- He?
- I didn't do this.
I didn't kill him.
I loved him.
- The person that he sees on the
floor
is not the same person that we
see.
You need to stay with that
memory.
Follow that.
- I know.
I know you didn't.
- I thought things were good
between us.
Did you notice anything weird
the last time you saw him?
- Judie never said anything
about this.
- No. No, I didn't.
Why do you think he broke up
with you?
- We had a fight.
- So you saw him last night? He
was here?
- No, I mean before that.
We went out for dinner, and
there was this girl there.
She was staring at me the
whole time as if she knew me.
She looked mean,
made me feel like I'd
done something bad to her.
- Keep looking at?
- Sean noticed what was
going on,
so I tell him about this girl
and...
- Sean.
- He looks at her and...
he doesn't know her either.
- Do you know her?
She's staring.
- She finally stands up and
walks towards our table.
She stands in front of
me without saying a word.
She's just staring at me.
So I say something like...
Do I know you?
"Do I know you?"
- She flashes this smile, this
fake smile.
And then she pours her drink on
my lap.
And then she says...
- It turns
me on how wet you are.
I love to feel it between my
fingers.
I wanna fuck you.
I wanna fuck you now.
- And then she turns
to Sean and she says.
- That's what
he said to me three days ago.
Tuesday night.
Just like every Tuesday for the
last year.
- And then she just
leaves.
Maybe this is all my fault.
- What makes you feel
that way?
- We went back home and he
wasn't even talking to me,
so I pushed him.
I already told you I have
never seen her before.
- Jay, I was right in front of
you.
You know what? I'm tired.
And it's not about what just
happened.
I didn't want to say anything,
but...
- I brought up some things,
things that had been bothering
me
for the last couple of weeks.
I told him he felt different.
- Since the
funeral you've become...
- He became...
- Distant.
- Aggressive.
- Mean.
- I didn't say anything until
last night,
but everything started
the day after the funeral.
- I told him...
I felt like I didn't
even know him anymore.
- I don't even know you anymore,
Jay.
I really don't know you.
- He left.
He left me, Judie.
- I'm sorry everything fell
apart.
But this is probably
how it's supposed to be.
Goodbye, Jay. Take care of
yourself.
- So last night, after
he left,
you did not see him again.
- No. I never saw
him again until now.
- What the fuck was that?
What kind of asshole are you to
pretend you don't know me?
I'm talking to you, asshole!
You don't even have the
balls to look at me?
Are you still pretending
you don't know me?
I only came here for one reason.
This piece of shit belongs to
you, to your fucking family.
I don't want anything more from
you.
You sick fuck!
- Do you really
remember nothing after that?
- I was just drinking.
I passed out, and I woke up
pointing this fucking gun to my
head.
Everything started the
day after the funeral.
- You said "he".
You said Sean...
started changing after the
funeral.
- Yeah. Pretty sure it
was that same night.
- What funeral was that?
- What do you mean?
- I'm just a little bit
confused.
There are so many things going
on.
I'm just a little bit nervous,
and I've been to more than one
funeral
over the last few months.
- I'm talking about the
last time you saw Sean.
At mom's funeral.
- Holy shit.
- Judie.
- He's projecting
his mother's funeral
over Judie's.
- Hey, Judie...
- Yes, yes.
- Ask him when the funeral was.
- Jay, do you remember
what day that funeral was?
- Is something wrong with you
right now?
- I am just trying to remember
something
that happened on that very same
day.
- It was Thursday.
It was two weeks ago.
- He has blacked out the last
six months.
There must be something more
than what just happened here.
Judie's death must have
triggered
some old broken memories,
'cause he's created a
lot of false memories
that he actually truly believes
but to the extent that I've
never seen
anything like it before.
Remembering things differently
than the way that they actually
happened is not uncommon.
He's actually distorting
reality,
stretching people, places.
You see, when you suffer
a traumatic experience,
one that you can't accept
this part of yourself,
the mind can hide or
remove those memories.
So he actually believes that the
funeral
was only two weeks ago,
and that it was far his
mother, not his sister.
He believes that she is here,
right now, in front of him.
And he believes that he
passed out last night
and then suddenly woke up to
this.
This is just a distortion.
It's all a projection.
He didn't pass out last night.
He blacked out six months ago.
Now we've got two questions.
What's he been doing
for the last six months?
- And who's Sean?
- This piece of belongs to
you, to your fucking family.
I don't want anything more from
you.
You sick fuck!
Well, what was it then?
It was just a dream.
You're okay.
Jay, Jay, Jay, Jay.
You're okay, Jay.
- Is that the watch?
This is family. This is family.
Our family.
Come on, make a wish.
- Aloud, please. I wanna
hear it.
- No, it doesn't work that way.
Think of something.
Something you really want.
- Ready?
Do it.
- Okay.
I have something for you,
Jay. Something really special.
I'm gonna go get it. I'll be
right back.
- How do you feel, Jay?
I know it's been a difficult
summer,
and this change is tough for
you,
but everything is gonna be okay.
I promise
You'll like the new school, and
living in the city is great.
It's a good thing.
And we can see each other
the whole time if you want.
I know you don't get this now,
but trust me, you need to hear
this.
You need to get away from mom,
Jay.
- Here's my present.
For you.
Go ahead and open it.
You always used to ask
me about this watch.
Your father gave it to me. He
made it.
It was one of the first
things that he made
when he started the company.
He made two, and he used to wear
that one.
And he used to always say,
no matter where we go or where
we are,
it'll always be the same time
for both of us from now on.
It was his way of being close
to me while he was traveling.
And now, you're always
gonna feel my presence,
even when I'm not with you.
Come on, put it on.
Come on, put it on,
Put it on.
- Everything is gonna be okay.
I promise.
- I'm gonna die anyways, right?
Just let me enjoy the
time that I have left.
- Do you
remember me?
She wouldn't let me see
you for a long time.
Your sister.
Now that she is gone,
we can finally finish what
we started a long time ago.
You must do something.
You remember what happened,
right?
- It was a dream.
It was just a dream. It was a
dream.
- Remember?
Remember.
- Relax.
Five...
Relax.
Four...
Remember.
Three...
Relax.
Two...
One...
Zero.
Remember.
Deep sleep.
What do you see?
- When I got back from school...
my mom wasn't home.
She had already left for
the weekend with this guy,
her lover.
I don't remember his name.
I was supposed to take care of
Jay.
As soon as I entered the house,
I knew there was something
wrong.
The chair was tilted over on its
side,
and the big mirror in the
living room was broken.
It was scary.
- There were
mirror stands everywhere.
- It was happening again.
- Sergeant, can
you play Jay's 911 call
again for me?
- He's trying to do it
again.
I can't allow it. Not this time.
I think I know how to stop him.
This is wrong.
Shut up!
- Stop it there.
Can you play that last part
again?
- There was a lot of blood.
I tried not to be scared, not to
panic.
I remember thinking,
I just want to protect my little
brother.
- I think I know to stop
him.
This is wrong.
Shut up!
- Stop.
Did you hear anybody else's
voice?
He sounds like he's
talking to somebody else,
but I didn't hear anybody else's
voice.
- He was standing right in front
of me.
He was talking to someone.
There was a tree, so I
couldn't see who it was.
I just kept moving.
- And listen closely to
the part right before that,
where he says, "This is wrong."
Play it again.
- I got closer.
I called his name.
Jay, can you hear me?
But he was somewhere else.
Who are you talking to?
Like when he used to have those
dreams.
He was standing there,
staring into the distance.
- This is wrong.
Shut up!
- And his voice...
his voice was different.
- This is wrong.
Shut up!
- His voice is different.
- I don't follow you.
- And he finally turned around.
I will never forget that look on
his face.
It was as if he had never seen
me before.
- Listen to
the tone of his voice.
It's slightly different.
- There was so
much blood everywhere.
- I think I know how to
stop him.
This is wrong.
Shut up!
- I got closer...
and closer.
And then I saw it.
Roy...
the dog...
was there on the floor.
He was dead.
I couldn't move.
- That is wrong.
Shut up!
- He's got a slightly different
tone.
Sounds like he's he's talking
into the phone, but then...
then it sounds a little more
distant,
like he's moved his head
away from the phone,
talking to somebody else in the
room.
It's like somebody else could
have said those words before,
even if it wasn't Jay himself.
- There was nobody there.
He was just staring at
another broken mirror.
- Come here. Touch it.
Touch...
it!
- He wanted me to touch that
mirror.
So I did.
- Detective...
I think there's something you
should know.
- Who are you talking
to?
- I am a friend.
His friend.
- He was not Jay anymore.
I asked his name.
What's your name?
And he said...
Sean.
- Sean.
- My name...
is Sean.
- "My name is Sean."
- I think I know who Sean is.
I'm starting to put the
pieces of the puzzle together.
Jay is much more complex
than I ever imagined.
He is...
someone special.
I've never seen anything like
this before.
Jay is a man that is obsessed.
He's constantly fighting
against a barrage of disturbing
thoughts.
He might show a lack of
emotion, apathy, loneliness.
But he is...
extremely tormented by
something deep and obscure...
in his mind.
Whatever happened to him
when he was a young child
just destroyed his personality.
Judie was the only thing
keeping him together.
Now that she's gone,
he is suddenly experiencing
everything
that he's held back for so many
years.
- What has all this to do with
Sean?
- A lot.
A lot. We need to...
We need to understand
what's going on in his mind
before we go any further.
It's important to recognize
him suffering like loneliness
or low self-esteem as potential
risk factors for violence.
And people like Jay can
target their aggression
towards themselves just as
easily as somebody else.
- That would explain why he
was trying to kill himself.
And the scars on his arms and
face
could be self-inflicted too.
- It's possible, yes.
Judie recognized that, when Jay
was young,
he had what we would
call an imaginary friend.
Imaginary friends can
be something positive
when you're young; it can
help you deal with something
that is an uncomfortable
reality.
But in other cases...
they can become pathological...
pushing you to do something very
bad.
- Like murder.
- There's something else that
you should know, detective.
The intimate gathering where
they spread Judie's ashes,
I don't remember seeing
Jay there with a man.
As a matter of fact,
I remember him being there with
a woman.
She was off to the side,
smoking away from the people
while he was talking to his
mother.
- So who's Sean then?
Just another projection of his
mind?
- Probably, but we've gotta
treat him like he's real,
just like he is to Jay.
What I'm saying, detective,
is...
I don't think Sean is
just an imaginary friend.
Not anymore.
Somehow, in the last six
months...
he became Sean.
- Can you do something for me?
I know this is hard, but I
want you to look at the body.
- Why?
- Please, Jay, tell me what you
see.
Jay, please. Do it for me.
Tell me exactly what you see.
- I see Sean. There's blood
around him.
He's laying there...
on the floor.
- Now look at the face.
- Why are you doing this?
- I am sorry.
I really am.
I know how important he was to
you.
He always was, right?
I was there.
I was there with you right
by your side the whole time.
Remember?
- After mom's funeral,
I started to remember
everything that we've
been through in the past.
- After mom's funeral, I
started thinking about
everything
that we've been through
together in the past.
- There was a moment when
something, everything, changed.
- There was a moment
when everything changed.
- I guess it might have been
when we moved from the country
house...
- I guess it was when we
left the country house...
- To the city.
- To move into the city.
That night was the
night of Jay's birthday.
That night, my mom gave
him the other watch.
The one that my dad used to
wear.
- It was the
night of your birthday.
Do you remember that?
- Mom gave you that watch.
- Mom gave you the watch.
Remember?
There's something about that
night that...
always stuck in my head.
It never left me.
- There was something about that
night
that I could never get out of my
head.
- There was
something about that...
- It always stuck with me.
- Always stuck to my
head.
- Do you know what it was?
It was the look on his face.
It was the look on your face.
It was not just sadness.
- It wasn't just
sadness.
- It wasn't just sadness
or the move to the city.
- It wasn't that
we were moving to the city.
- It wasn't the move to
the city.
It was something...
- Something...
- Something deeper.
- Deeper.
Something...
Something older.
- Something...
older.
- Something older.
Tah summer he was sick the whole
time.
- You had a fever for weeks.
We couldn't get it under
control.
- And you were crying.
You were crying so much.
He was crying so much.
And then, after that summer,
I...
I never saw him cry again.
- Then I never saw you
cry again.
- And then, after that summer,
I never saw you cry again.
I remember sometimes thinking
that...
he probably had no tears left in
his eyes.
- Thought maybe that...
- I used to think
that...
- You didn't have any
more tears.
- You probably had no more
tears.
He cried them all that summer.
You cried them all that summer.
I felt all of his pain just...
I could feel all of you pain.
Just by looking at him.
And I wanted to carry it.
- I wanted to carry that pain.
- I wanted to carry that pain
for you.
for him.
I never asked him.
I never asked him asked you,
Jay.
I never asked him what it was.
- I never...
I never asked what it was.
What was it?
- What was it?
- You know, I felt somehow
responsible.
- I used to feel somehow
responsible
for not understanding what it
was.
- Don't, please.
It had nothing to do with you,
Judie.
- I thought he must have been
thinking
about something that...
that happened a long time ago.
Something he couldn't remember.
You were probably thinking about
something
that happened a long time ago.
Something you had forgotten
you just remembered that summer.
That's probably what made you
sick.
- What are you trying to say?
- I thought he realized...
what he had done to Roy.
- Do you remember Roy, Jay?
- Do you remember Roy?
- Roy.
Mother's dog.
Yeah.
Why?
- Do you remember what happened
to him?
- Yeah, he just left.
- Are you sure about that?
Think about it.
- Yeah, yeah, I'm sure.
Why are you asking about Roy
now?
About that dog?
- Think about it, Jay.
- Try to remember that
weekend when mom came home.
- Think about the day when mom
came back from that weekend.
- Remember the dinner that
night?
- Think about that dinner.
- So, how was your weekend,
sweeties?
- Good.
- Just good?
- Yes, good.
Nothing special.
- Huh.
Did she take care of you, baby?
- Yes, I did.
- Good.
So I might go away again next
weekend.
So I'm wondering how long I have
to wait
before somebody tells me
what happened to the mirror.
- It was my fault.
We were playing with the
ball, and I was just clumsy.
Don't pull your sleeves up,
okay?
- What happened to your face,
baby?
- You did that at school.
You were playing soccer with
your friends
and you scratched yourself.
Do you remember?
You were at school, playing
soccer with your friends,
and you scratched yourself.
It happened yesterday.
He scratched himself at school,
playing soccer with his friends.
- Is that what
happened?
Are you okay baby?
- It's just a scratch.
- Where's Roy?
- Where is Roy? I haven't seen
him yet.
- Did you see him today?
- No. I didn't see him.
When I got back from
school, he wasn't here.
- He was here this morning.
- You guys remembered
to close the back door
before you left this morning,
right?
You know that Roy cannot be
outside alone.
Jay, did you close the door or
not?
I don't know.
- What do you mean you don't
know?
- I don't remember.
- What do you mean you don't
remember?
It's a simple question.
Did you close the door or not?
Jay, did you close the door?
- I don't know, Mom.
I'm sorry.
- Well, think about it.
Think about it.
How many times do I have to tell
you
to keep the back door closed?
It's a simple thing.
One simple thing.
Is that so much to ask?
- I did it.
I did.
- Did what?
- When I was in the kitchen this
morning,
I heard something outside,
so I went to the backyard to
check.
But it was nothing.
- Nothing?
- Yes, just...
some birds.
- Birds.
- Yes, birds.
But then I stayed there
outside for a while.
Maybe too long.
I guess I was thinking
about something else.
- Something else? Like what?
- School.
Something I had to do for
school.
- Well, I hope you did it right!
- I think so.
I think I got it done.
- Tomorrow, you're gonna
go out and look for Roy,
and you better find him.
This was your responsibility,
Judie.
It's all your fault.
- Yeah.
Yeah, I remember.
- What exactly do you
remember?
- Why do you wanna talk about
that?
- There's something that I need
to know.
- Judie, it was such a long
time ago.
It was it long time ago, Judie.
I'm not mad at you.
I'm not upset about him.
- He replaced the actual event
with the lie that Judie
told to protect him.
- Do you still think about it?
It's not your fault.
It just happened.
You shouldn't blame yourself
just because you left the front
door open.
He was just gone.
- It's all your fault.
- No, detective, you need to
stop.
- Hey.
What did you say?
- All of this bullshit.
How did she do it?
You know what, Jay? I
think it's time to wake up.
Judie, Judie, Judie.
It's all Judie's fault.
Judie didn't have a life because
of you.
Come on, Jay, wake up.
- Please stop.
- You know the truth.
You know exactly what
happened to that dog.
You know the reason why you got
sick that summer, don't you?
You finally remembered what you
did,
and you couldn't take it, right?
You couldn't take it.
Judie was there all the
time to protect you.
But you never said a word, ever.
- Not one word!
- Judie.
- Come on, Jay.
Come on. Tell me.
Tell me, and yourself,
what you really did?
- I didn't do anything.
I didn't do anything.
- You killed your own dog?
- No, He just left.
- You held him in your arms
while cutting his throat.
- You're lying.
- No, I didn't.
- Did you do the same here, huh?
- Isn't that what you did here,
Jay?
Isn't it?
- No.
Is that what you did?
No.
- Is that what you did?
- Okay, this may be the moment.
Ready for my orders.
Go!
- Stay away!
Stay away from me!
Back off!
- Detective.
Get back. Clear!
- Damn Diana,
what are you doing?
Stop. Nobody shoot.
Back off, back off, back off.
- Judie!
Come back here!
Get her back here.
- Did she follow the
procedure?
- Fuck off.
- Officer, I need
you to answer the question.
Did she follow the procedure?
Yes or no?
- You know it's her fault
you can't remember, right?
Judie.
She's the one that made
you forget about me.
That fucking bitch sent me away
from you.
But now that she's gone.
We can finish what we
started a long time ago.
What are you talking about?
Today's a very important day for
us.
We can finally fix this.
There's just one thing I need
you to do.
And I've already prepared
everything.
What did you do?
I called her while you were
sleeping.
I told her that we should meet.
She's actually on her way here
right now.
No, I won't do it.
Yes you will.
You know exactly what to
do when she gets here.
There she is.
- There was someone like him
in your life, am I right?
- It's Judie.
- You see a lack of strength
on Judie's part, but...
maybe this is a distortion.
Ask yourself if you're
interpreting what Judie did
in her life with your own
experience.
Maybe just can't see what
Judie was really doing.
- No, Dr. Rivers, I can't. What
was it?
- Love.
Judie was one of the strongest
people
I'd ever met my whole career.
She made a clear choice that
she maintained her whole life.
She chose to protect her little
brother
from the painful truth, and
she died with Jay's secret.
Isn't that love?
- Or guilt.
- Is that easier for you to
relate to?
That sense of guilt?
Is that better for you?
You have a lot more in common
with Judie than you think.
A lot more.
You can use that.
Use it.
- It's happening
again.
You both need to see this.
- Jay.
Can you hear me, Jay?
- What's going on?
- Wait, don't touch him.
- Why is he
pointing the gun at that door?
- He is not pointing the gun at
the door.
He's pointing the gun at
himself.
- Yeah, you're right.
- What are you talking
about?
- I can see the both of
us through that window.
- Not following.
- When we found him here frozen,
pointing a gun to his head,
he wasn't trying to kill
himself.
He wanted to kill Sean.
- You're right.
The mirrors. That's how he sees
Sean.
- It's not just the mirrors.
It's the reflections.
- Yes!
Reflections! The reflected
image of himself.
- Why didn't he do it before?
And why is he not pulling
the trigger right now?
- No, he's not gonna do that.
- Why not?
- Because right now he's not
Jay. Right now he's Sean.
- That's why Jay broke all the
mirrors.
He was trying to kill Sean.
- If Jay wants to kill Sean,
he has to avoid seeing him,
or else he loses control.
That's why he broke
every reflective surface,
to keep Sean far away from him.
In order for Jay to kill Sean,
he has to kill himself,
because Sean is a part of him.
But he didn't count...
on that door window.
- Okay? So what do we
do now?
- What is it?
It's the light.
- Yes.
- When they got on the scene,
the sun must have been there,
and it lit this window.
Think about it.
When the sun hits that window,
if you are on the other side
of it, you can see through it.
But if you're on the
side with the sunshine,
you can't see the other side at
all.
And Jay was on this side.
And in this situation-
- The glass. It acts like a
mirror.
- Exactly.
He could only see his
reflection.
- He broke every reflective
image of himself in the house,
but he didn't think it was gonna
happen
when he walked outside.
- I remember when I got here,
the sun was there, and it was
cloudy,
so it wasn't hitting that window
anymore.
- And that's why he woke up
when he heard the sound of your
voice,
because he wasn't Seam anymore.
- Exactly.
- So what happened.
- When the sun does not
shine through that window,
it's just a window.
He couldn't see his
reflected image anymore.
He was Jay again.
- So what now?
- There's an overlap.
I can see through the glass,
but I can also see Jay and
myself at the same time.
- We need to find out where
that light's coming from
that's causing that reflection.
- There's a street light over
there.
- No Uh-uh.
It's gotta be closer to our
side.
- Detective, a few minutes
ago that light turned on.
- It must be an automatic
light that switches on
when the sun comes down.
We must find the breakers for
that light and turn it off.
- I will take care of it.
I found it.
I am gonna switch it off.
- Sean!
Sean! Where are you?
- Step back, detective. Don't
touch him.
Just gimme a minute here.
- Sean!
Sean, what did you say?
- He's still asleep, he's still
dreaming,
but he's not Sean anymore.
He's in between being awake and
dreaming.
Let's bring Judie in there,
into his unconscious.
I'll guide you through it.
I just need you to remember
to talk in a low tone,
almost a whisper type of a tone.
Follow my words,
Jay...
relax.
- Jay, relax.
- Don't be afraid.
- I'm here with you.
- Judie!
Where are you? I can't see you.
- Relax.
Don't be afraid.
- Jay relax. I'm here with you.
- Listen to me now.
- I want you to close your eyes.
Trust me.
Close your eyes.
- You're sitting on a
chair.
- You are sitting on a
- And don't know where
you are.
- And you don't
know where you are.
- You can't move.
You're tied up.
- You're tied up.
You try to break free, but you
can't.
Your body is bound.
- Your body is bound.
You can't even ask for help.
- But you can't ask for help
either.
You have rope in your mouth too.
You can't do anything.
- But I found you, Jay.
- But I have found you.
- I'm in front of you.
- I'm right in front of
you now.
- You can see me.
open your eyes.
Open them.
- Open your eyes.
I'm here for you.
I'm here to help.
- I'm gonna take that
rope out of your mouth
so you can talk to me.
- I'm coming closer.
I'm touching the rope now.
- I'm touching the rope now.
- It's tight.
- I know it's tight.
- But I'm loosening the knots
now.
- Almost there.
- Can you feel it?
- Almost done?
- You can feel that the
rope's not so tight anymore.
- Almost there.
Here we go.
Your mouth is free now.
- Your mouth is free now.
- Judie
- Where are you, Jay?
What do you see?
- The dog.
He's angry.
He's always so angry.
- Don't be afraid, Jay.
- He's not mad at you.
He's trying to tell you
something.
Something you need
to remember.
- Remember.
- Jay, just look at him.
- Look at him deeply in the
eyes.
- What do you feel?
- What's in my stomach?
I can't move.
It's dark, dirty.
It's wrong.
It's consuming me.
- It's okay, Jay.
It's okay. Don't be afraid.
You're just feeling guilty
for something you did,
for something bad you did to
that dog.
- Remember?
- Is it Roy?
- What happened to Roy, Jay?
- Roy didn't just leave us.
- I didn't
leave the door open, Jay.
- Remember?
What do you see now?
- I see myself.
I'm in the house.
The country house.
And I'm young
Roy is there too.
- What is he doing?
- Eating.
- What do you see now?
- I'm in the kitchen.
And that kid's there.
- What kid?
- The one I always see in my
dreams.
He wears a mask on his face,
but only on the left side.
- You know the kid, Jay.
Think about it.
Think about when you were young.
- Jay, what do you see now?
- Blood.
- Jay...
what do you see?
- Did you see?
- You did
good, Jay.
- Jay...
talk to me.
What did you see?
- I remember now.
I remember.
It was me.
- Know, it's hard to see.
you did a terrible thing to that
dog.
There was a reason why you did
it, Jay.
- He told me to do it.
That kid.
This is what she deserved.
- He said it was what she
deserved?
- Who?
What did she deserve.
- Your
mother.
She has to pay for what she did
to me.
- My mother.
I don't know why he said that.
- Who is he, Jay?
Who is the kid?
- A friend.
But he had to go away.
Because...
Because of you.
Because of you, Judie.
You wanted him to leave.
Told him to go away.
I remember now.
- Jay...
now I want you to remember your
birthday,
the night of your birthday.
- When we left the country
house to go to the city.
- We were in the car.
- Remember.
- What do you see now,
Jay?
- The watch.
- Where are you.
- In the car.
You're there.
You're young.
Mom's driving.
I see myself right there next to
me.
- You...
cried a lot that summer.
- You couldn't stop.
- I remember.
- Was it because you
realized that you killed Roy?
- No.
It was something else.
- What was it?
- Something happened
that I can't understand.
I did something I wasn't
supposed to.
Something wrong.
I don't know why. But
I'm not a child anymore.
I shouldn't have done it.
- What did you do?
- I can't see what it is, but
it's still deep inside me...
destroying my soul.
Even if the memory's gone.
- What are you thinking
about?
- This watch makes me feel
dirty.
Like my body doesn't exist
anymore.
I feel violated.
- That night, my mom
gave him the other watch,
the one my dad used to wear.
- Why do you think the watch
makes you feel that way?
- Jay.
Jay.
- Jay, talk to me.
Who gave you that watch?
- Why did you say that?
- What?
What did I say?
I know you don't get it now.
But trust me, you need to hear
this.
You need to get away from Mom,
Jay.
- You told me I should stay away
from Mom.
You told me to stay away from
her.
You wanted me to leave.
- He made two watches that look
alike.
And now Jay had one...
so my Mom could feel connected
with him.
Jay...
Jay, I want you to close your
eyes now.
- What are you doing?
- Trust me.
- Oh, no, no, no.
Detective.
- Close your eyes.
- Stop doing what you're doing
right now.
This is very dangerous.
- You are sitting on a chair.
You can't move. You're tied up.
You're trying to break
free, but you can't.
Your body is bound.
But you can't ask for help
either.
But I have found you.
I'm right in front of you. You
can see me.
- Open your eyes.
I'm going take these ropes off
of you
so you can finally move.
I'm touching the rope now.
Untying the not.
You can feel that it's
not so tight anymore.
- I am almost done, Jay. Almost
there.
- Almost there, Jay.
You're free.
You can move now.
I'm sorry.
Please forgive me, Jay.
I could have said something.
I didn't though.
I never did.
It was her.
That's why you killed Roy.
You wanted to punish her for
what she had done to you.
That's why you felt violated and
dirty.
She seduced you.
God, you were just a kid.
You loved your mother,
but there's another part
that knew that it was wrong.
There's another part in
you that rejected it.
Part of you even hated
your mother for all of it.
- No, it was that kid.
It wasn't me.
- You told me he was wearing a
mask
on the left side of his face,
right?
What about the other side?
- The other side, he had...
He had a scar.
- Where did he have the scar?
- Under his eye.
- Under his right eye.
- Yeah.
- What else, Jay?
- His arm.
Roy hurt him.
- Did he have dog bites on his
arm?
- Yeah.
- Look at your arm, Jay.
Look at it.
That's your right arm. Your left
arm, Jay.
What do you see?
- I don't understand.
- And you have a cut
under your left eye too.
Jay...
who is Sean?
- How dare you...
bring one of your sluts here?
Do you have no respect for your
sister?
- You want a smoke?
- Oh, no thanks. I don't smoke.
- You don't have to be shy.
You can go smoke if you want.
- No, Jay.
I don't smoke.
I never did.
- You know what she's
like.
- No.
- Jay, seriously, how can I know
that?
- Do you know her?
- No, I don't know her.
She's just staring.
- You've become
distant, aggressive.
Mean.
- Goodbye, Jay. Take care of
yourself.
- Who the fuck was that?
What kind of asshole are you
to pretend you don't know me?
- I only came here for one
thing.
This piece of shit belongs to
you, to your fucking family!
- And what about
your Sean? Your boyfriend?
- I don't want anything more
from you, you sick fuck!
- What about his arm?
- They were cigarette
burns.
- Congrats.
- How did he get those?
- I don't know.
- Was it on his right
arm?
- Yeah, the right arm.
- Did he have a scar
too?
- Yeah, he did.
- Under his right eye?
- The right eye.
- Jay, the kid...
that kid that was in your house,
that same kid from your dreams,
Sean...
you can't see the left side of
face
because you don't want to see
it.
You can't see what's under the
mask
because you don't want to.
But it's time now, Jay.
It's time for you to see...
there is no mask.
That's what you needed to see,
Jay.
- What are you talking about?
- To protect yourself from
what you are experiencing.
To pretend that it
wasn't happening to you.
The kids' scar was your wound,
but you saw it on the right
side because of the mirrors.
- Every time we're this room,
I'm gonna call you Sean.
- The mirrors, Jay.
Your reflected image.
You're looking at yourself, Jay.
You...
Are Sean.
- No.
It can't be true.
It can't.
If I'm Sean...
who's in there?
Who's in there?
- Jay...
do you know who I am?
- Judie?
Yeah, I know who you.
- Where is Judie?
- You're Judie!
- Where's your sister, Jay?
- Maybe it wasn't the best idea
to introduce me at your sister's
funeral.
- What are you talking about?
- Where is your mother?
- My Mom?
- Jay, look at me. Please, look
at me.
Look at me.
- No, no.
- Who has the other watch?
You're wearing the watch
right now, the same watch.
And Sean is not here.
There are two watches, remember?
And that body on the floor...
is wearing the same watch.
If you are wearing one of
them...
who has the other one?
- Who are you?
- Diana.
- My name is Diana.
It's time to go, Jay.
I'm going to take the
gun from you now, okay?
It's okay. It's okay.
Nothing's happened. Nothing's
happened.
I just need to take the gun
from you now, all right?
- I know who I am.
I know what I've done.
I know what I'll see if I turn
around.
- So don't.
Don't turn around, okay?
We'll figure this out.
You don't have to turn around.
- He'll never leave me, Diana.
- That's not true.
That's not true.
- I killed my own mother.
How am I supposed to live with
that?
Can you imagine what
it's like to look around
and realize everything you
see isn't actually there?
- This thing that happened
to you, it is not your fault.
We can fix this.
- Do you see that mirror?
Can you fix that, Diana?
Some things are too broken.
You can try to put the
pieces back together,
but they're never gonna be the
same.
They're just gonna be
fragments of something broken,
trying to be whole.
It's time to face the
consequences.
- Wait, Jay. Please don't
Please, Jay, don't do it. Don't
do this.
Please.
Listen, Sean...
Sean will not let you do this.
Please don't do this.
- It's different this time.
He can't control me anymore.
Thank you for showing me
the most important thing.
The truth.
I am Sean.
- Did you try to stop
him?
Answer the question.
Did you try to stop him?
Did she follow the procedure?
Officer, I need you to
answer the question.
Did she follow the procedure?
Yes or no?
- Yes.
- She did everything that she
could.
- She did.