- Jump high on water, please
Come on
Jump higher!
Jump!
[chattering]
- Hmm...
You're only supposed to... being here for fifteen minutes
- Swear God! Health Inspectors get younger every year!
- What?
- You want those kid playing their game?
- Yeah
- What is that?
- Hmm...water polo
- What the hell is water polo?
- It's a sport
- Are you good at it?
- No, not really. I mean
my dad is paying for the camp, so I have to go.
[sighing]
[chattering]
- Hey!
Your parents are paying these people
and they put you on the bench?
- Thanks
Ankle seems fine...
- Oh, yeah.
It did recover quick.
What?
- Which is the wise
And this comes from a man who
didn't learn to embrace athletic endeavors
until his collapsed role level gave him no choice.
- Yeah...
- Time moves the all lot faster
when you actually try.
- Hmmm...
Hmmm...I was wondering if I could play goalie today?
- Okay
- Hey!
Hey!