Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
[bells ringing]
- [waves lapping]
- [birds chirping]
[bright music plays]
[children singing in Tamil]
[train engine chugging]
[train whistle tooting]
[children speaking in Tamil]
[in Tamil] This is for the bride…
Catch.
[children speaking in Tamil]
[train whistle tooting]
[in Tamil] Hey…
You’re such a bore.
Always reading too much.
Look at her.
Look…
Tell her to stop.
Stop fighting you two.
Oh, Janaki, you're so useless.
Massage here and here.
[in English] Six, no trumps.
[singing in Tamil on radio]
[boy 1 in English] A Four! That was
a clear Four!
[boy 2]
No it isn't.
You're a bloody cheat, Diggy.
[girl] No he isn't,
you're the cheat.
Hey, Diggy.
Hey, a four Appa,
I got a four!
[in Tamil] Superb.
[singing in Tamil]
[in English] Sonali, would you take Arjie
as your lawfully wedded wife?
I do.
[Lakshmi]
Arjie, would you take Sonali,
as your lawfully
wedded husband?
I do.
Okay, you now may
kiss the bride.
[all] Yay, yay!
[giggling]
Hey, I want to be the bride!
You can't Arjie's the
bestest bride of all.
But he's not even a girl!
A bride is a girl.
Not a boy.
A boy cannot be a bride.
A girl must be the bride.
If you can't play properly,
just go away!
We don't need you.
You Fatty!
[in Tamil] You fatso.
Just go away.
Yeah, you just go
away Fatty. Kundu.
You're a pansy, a sissy!
A fag!
You are now in Colombo,
not in silly England.
We don't know your
stupid English words.
Yes, now you just go
away Fatty boom boom.
♪ Hey fatty-boom-boom,
sweet sugar dumpling ♪
let me tell you something ♪
[screaming and singing]
♪ Hey fatty-boom-boom,
sweet sugar dumpling ♪
let me tell you something ♪
What's the matter?
Stop that!
Stop that, Arjie!
Quiet! All of you out.
I said out!
- See what he did.
- What did he do, darling?
See what he did to me,
he called me Fatty.
And he hit me
with the cross.
Arjie, come here!
But she tore my red sari!
Arjie, come now!
Come here.
[in Tamil] Why does your son
have lipstick on?
[Aunty 1]
Oh Nalini, he's so cute.
[in Tamil] He looks like a real girl…
[in English] …So sweet.
Chelva, looks like you have
a "Funny One" here.
[in Tamil] Take care, Nalini.
[in English] This might look innocent now,
but before you know it...
Shut up Kanthi,
just stop with the drama.
Come on, Diggy!
[in Tamil] Pack up. Let's go.
[in Tamil] Darling, it's okay.
[Appa in English]
See, I told you.
[in Tamil] Encouraging all his nonsense.
[Sonali]
♪ We are a happy family ♪
♪ Yes a happy family ♪
♪ And we live at the foot
of the fruitful tree ♪
Dropsy and Mopsy, how
can they be so sweeter?
And funny little
Cottontail and Peter.
Whoa!
Go and sit down, Arjie.
Now!
Diggy!
[in Tamil] Quickly.
Okay, mister.
[in Tamil] This is an order Diggy.
I want you to include your
brother on the cricket team.
[in English] Huh? Come on, Amma!
I hate cricket!
It's good for you.
Arjie's useless!
We'll never win if
he's on our team!
An order, Diggy.
Please Amma, please!
Why do I have to
play with the boys?
Because the sky is so high
and pigs can't fly, that's why.
I won't play with
the boys ever!
What the hell, Arjie!
Hold you bat properly, man.
Get him out of this team!
What the hell was that?
What's wrong with you?
As it is, I don't
wanna play with you guys.
Okay, one last
chance but that's final.
If you don't play properly,
I'll hit you!
[birds chirping]
Hey, what the hell?
Hey, where is he going?
Arjie!
You bloody thief!
You bloody coward!
If you ever come
near me again,
I'll kill you.
Don't worry, I won't.
I will never come!
♪ I got the bat! ♪
♪ Got the bat! ♪
Ammachi, Ammachi!
[knocking]
- [in Tamil] Grandma, Arjie stole our bat.
- I got the bat!
[Ammachi in Tamil] Steal a bat
and end up polishing brass.
Idiot.
You’re ruining my brass.
Harder, harder.
Rub harder! Rub harder!
- [soft piano music plays]
- [Arjie crying out]
[Ammachi] Don't let it dry.
Rub faster.
[in Tamil] Honestly Amma, what is this?
I'm teaching him a skill.
Harder, harder.
[Ammachi in English]
He's your Funny Boy nephew.
[Diggy in distance]
Run, run, come on run.
[in English] Ammachi, is she the aunty
who's marrying a white man?
White man?
[in Tamil] Disgusting.
He's a Canadian.
[in Tamil] But Tamil like us.
[in English] Carry on, carry on!
Radha.
Come help me unpack.
Come on.
["Famous Blue Raincoat"
by Leonard Cohen plays]
♪ It's four in the morning ♪
♪ The end of December ♪
♪ I'm writing you now ♪
♪ Just to see
if you're better ♪
♪ New York is cold ♪
♪ But I like where I'm living ♪
♪ There's music
on Clinton Street ♪
♪ All through the evening ♪
♪ I hear that you're
building your little house ♪
♪ Deep in the desert ♪
That's the one.
♪ You're living
for nothing now ♪
♪ I hope you're keeping ♪
Hey, Arjie.
[in Tamil] Want to try make-up on?
[in English] Is it wrong for
a boy to do it?
Why?
Are you hurting anybody?
Will it make you happy?
♪ Did you ever go clear? ♪
♪ Ah, the last
time we saw you ♪
♪ You looked so much older ♪
[Radha] I'm only
painting your toes.
That way you can wear
them under your socks
and no one will ever know.
A joyful secret.
[bright instrumental music plays]
♪♪
A joyful secret.
Now, what are we going to do
with you, Arjie Chelvaratnam?
Hm?
[bell ringing]
[Arjie]
♪ Do Re Mi Fa So La Ti Do ♪
♪ Do Ti La So Fa Mi Re Do ♪
Chip off the old block, Radha! Again.
[Arjie]
♪ Do Re Mi Fa So La Ti Do ♪
- [teacher] Bravo!
- [claps]
Very good, very good.
You should've seen him,
he aced the audition.
Think: Arjie and I are
going to be in a musical
in my old school.
And your friends
will see him shine.
I don't know, Radha.
[in Tamil] This will encourage
his girly tendency.
[in English] You know the issue.
[in Tamil] Really? What issue?
His talent should be developed.
[in Tamil] Actors… useless.
[in English] Actors?
What about Sean Connery?
Peter O'Toole?
The last time I checked
they were actors.
[in Tamil]
You know exactly what I mean.
[in Tamil] Wait… Weren't you in the
same drama society in school?
[in English] Shakespeare, it's a
whole different thing.
Some have greatness thrust
upon them and some achieve it.
[laughs]
[in Tamil] Chelva, Radha is right.
[in English] Arjie’s just creative.
Artistic. Yes.
He's just creative.
Chelva.
[in Tamil] Arjie will be in the play.
[in English] Yes!
Come on.
Oh goodness me,
he'll be fine!
[upbeat out-of-tune
piano music plays]
♪♪
[Director]
One and two.
And one and two.
And one, two.
All right, stop,
stop, stop, stop!
Anil, look at your
feet and not Radha.
And again and places.
And...
[dramatic piano chords]
[Director]
And one and two.
One and two.
One, two.
[upbeat music plays]
[singing in Tamil]
[Ammachi in Tamil]
Our Radha is very talented.
She plays the piano so well…
the famous Canadian
song "Suzanne."
The one about the river
and the hand.
[Radha in Tamil] Please, Amma, stop.
[Ammachi in Tamil]
Would you like a biscuit?
Do you have any
brothers or sisters?
[Rajan in English]
I do, I do.
I have a brother
and a sister.
[in Tamil] We are very happy.
They make a good match.
[in Tamil] We are also happy.
[in English] An accountant in our family.
Mm, yes, and working for the
Canadian Government no less.
There's nothing so stable
as a government job.
[Ammachi in Tamil] A perfect couple.
[Appa in Tamil] Rajan will be a good
influence on Radha, no Amma?
[Ammachi in English]
Yes, doesn't drink.
Nor womanize.
There's no insanity
in our family.
[Kanthi Aunty]
That's nice.
[Arjie chuckles]
Have a safe flight, Rajan!
[both laugh]
Our whole motto was
to work hard, party hard.
And so we would
go to classes
and then after that we
would go to the bar
and the next day we would
do it all over again.
And well, that was just the
partying on the weekdays
in Toronto.
The weekends
would roll around
and often we'd go
to Club David's,
me and my gay pals.
And what happens
at Club David's
stays at Club David's.
Come on Radha,
you can't just leave it there!
Come on, come on let's go!
All this fuss for an
amateur production.
Ah Rajeev, you're such a cynic!
Come on, Arjie.
Hi, Radha!
It's going to rain.
Can I give you a lift home?
No, no.
We are in the
King and I together.
I'm Anil.
I know.
Yes, sir?
No, sir?
Three bags full, sir?
Please.
Sure, why not.
Ah, ah.
Over one.
[rain pattering]
[bright music plays]
This is an interesting route.
Ah, it's the best route,
also the shortest.
It's not the shortest.
But it's the best.
[bright music plays]
[Anil] I enjoyed those
stories you told.
It sounds like you had a
riotously good time in Toronto.
Not like us,
stuck in this small pond.
It's a island, not a pond.
Thank you, Arjie.
Welcome.
[Radha]
And it's exotic here.
Old fashioned but exotic.
[Anil]
No Radha, I really think...
Rubbish!
You probably think a girl
should never go to a bar.
Look, I'm not the
traditional type
who's going to...
[Anil]
Tradition?
I certainly don't want
a traditional woman
with a plait down her back.
I'm an admirer of
Gloria Steinem you know.
Honestly, you're
the bloody limit.
Gloria Steinem?
Indeed.
Royal Prince and Princesses.
[bright upbeat
off-tune piano music plays]
♪♪
Arjun!
[in Tamil] Come on up.
Come on. Fast.
[in English] Why are you dancing
around like that?
Those are girly things.
But I don't understand,
why are girls things bad?
Are you saying they're bad
when girls do them too?
Arjie, of course not.
[in Tamil] Only when boys do them.
But how can they
suddenly become bad
because boys are doing them?
[in Tamil] What about Meena?
She plays cricket with the boys.
[in English] No one says that's bad.
[in Tamil] Just trust me on this Arjie.
[in English] And why does everyone
say I'm funny.
What does that mean?
Well Funny means…
A bad man.
Orre, a bad man who
does bad things.
Am I a bad man?
[in Tamil] Of course not.
But you could be a bad man.
That's why I tell you to
play with the boys.
Understand?
[in English] But, Appa, I hate cricket,
I hate cowboys.
How can doing something
that I hate make me good?
[in Tamil] That's just how it is.
[melancholy music plays]
♪♪
The thing is Arjie,
life is full of
boring people.
Like, well, like your father.
Yes, boring.
Boring. He's my brother,
so I can say it.
And like so many,
he's frightened of
anyone who's different.
But different, is wonderful.
And you are different,
precocious and wonderful.
Am I precocious?
Yes.
Now, you have to find a way
not to let these boring people
rob you of your precociousness.
It means super bright, by the way.
What you've got
to do is this.
Stand up!
[clicks fingers]
Don't mess with
the Grand Diva.
the Grand Diva!
Yes!
[Anil]
Okay, ready?
Step one.
Okay.
Step one, you're to hold
this with your right hand.
Okay, and then with
your left index finger
and your left thumb
you put it in and you
hold it like a catapult.
Yeah, you put it in.
Yeah, good.
Now here comes
the tricky part.
Okay, you send
the needle under
and over to the point
of the right needle.
Under, over, yes!
Radha Aunty, I can knit!
How did you learn
all this wool stuff?
My grandmother.
I can teach you also.
Well done, Arjie.
[Arjie]
See this!
Mm-hmm.
You my friend are about to
make something indispensable
for the tropics.
A woolen scarf.
- [announcement in Tamil]
- [chatter]
- [train engine roaring]
- [train whistle tooting]
[chuckles]
Hi.
Arjie, hi.
I thought you were
going to miss it.
Almost.
[wistful instrumental music plays]
♪♪
[indistinct chatter]
[birds chirping]
[in Tamil] Putting her sandal on
as if he was Prince Charming.
[Kanthi Aunty in English] I can't believe
my sister is so shameless.
You have totally
spoilt Radha, Amma.
[Ammachi in Tamil] I'm so shocked…
…so speechless.
The girl is almost married.
I wish you weren't dead Appa.
[Amma in Tamil]
They were just there in public.
They didn't even care.
[Kanthi Aunty in English] He had
his hands all over her!
Hmm, sneaking in?
Like a thief.
Radha?
Radha!
Imagine implicating
a child in all this.
Well, here I am.
[in Tamil] You think this is funny?
[in Tamil] No, Amma.
[in Tamil] Okay then…
Who is this boy?
[in English] A boy from the play.
[in Tamil] His name?
His name?
Anil.
Jayasinghe.
[in Tamil] Only a Sinhalese would
seduce a betrothed girl.
[in English] Radha, how could you?
[Kanthi Aunty]
You're a traitor.
A traitor to our
father's memory.
He was butchered by
the Sinhalese, Radha.
A martyr!
I don't give a damn.
- Radha, please.
- What?
So who cares if he's
Sinhalese, Amma.
I like him.
Don't you have any shame?
[in Tamil] Behaving immorally in public…
Honestly, Amma, you would
think I was a prostitute or...
[Radha cries out]
[in Tamil] I'm sending you to Jaffna.
Our Tamil homeland will
straighten you out.
[in Tamil] How could you?
You think you love
this boy now?
Are you Radha?
[in Tamil] How can this ever work?
Amma, I heard Anil
with my own ears.
He said he loves
Radha Aunty.
Who cares if
he's Sinhalese?
You knew all along
he was Sinhalese?
Aiding and abetting?
Arjie, you are only
eight years old,
what do you know
about love?
Radha Aunty will never be
allowed into any of our houses
if she marries a Sinhalese.
[Arjie in Tamil] I’m not going.
[Ammachi in Tamil] Yes you are…
I'm teaching you diplomacy.
[cow grunting]
[cow mooing]
Jayasinghe?
Yes?
- Jayasinghe?
- Yeah.
[in English] Anil is your son?
Keep your son away
from my daughter.
Bloody Sinhalese
in my family?
Never.
[in Sinhala] You Tamil bitch.
[in Tamil] What?
What did you say?
[in Sinhala] A bitch.
You think we want a Tamil
in our family?
Typical Tamil arrogance.
[in English] A minority with a
majority complex,
thinking they can
have half our island.
Oh, yes we will take it.
Then let's see how you
bloody lazy Sinhalese
will survive without us.
Because you speak Tamil
doesn't make you smart!
Sinhalese is our
national language.
Speak it or swim
back to India!
Father.
[in Tamil] We are more intelligent
than you Sinhalese.
You're jealous… jealous…
jealous.
First they rape our women,
now they steal our daughters.
[in English]Can I offer you
a cup of tea?
[solemn instrumental music plays]
♪♪
[in English] If you come near
my daughter, I will kill you.
Would you like a biscuit?
[train horn blowing]
[announcements in Tamil]
Arjie?
Give this to Anil.
Okay?
Look after him, Arjie.
[Appa]
Arjie.
[in Tamil]
Son, Radha will be back soon.
[in English] Before you know it.
[in Tamil] Travel safely, Radha.
[train horn blowing]
[coughing]
Life is so unfair.
- [thunder rumbling]
- [lightning cracking]
She writes to him every week.
Imagine, four letters for
an eight-year-old boy.
More nonsense about
that Sinhala boy?
[in Tamil] How would I know?
Don't you read them?
[in English] What kind of woman
do you think I am?
A nosy one.
Very funny.
[in Tamil] Will Arjie be okay?
He's creative.
He’s creative.
[in English] So childish.
[children singing]
[soft music plays]
♪ He has a thousand dreams
that won't come true ♪
♪ You know that he
believes in them ♪
♪ And that's
enough for you ♪
She's back tomorrow.
I know.
♪ You'll always go along ♪
♪ Defend him
when he's wrong ♪
♪ And tell him
when he's strong ♪
♪ He is wonderful ♪
♪ He'll always
need your love ♪
[horn blaring]
[train rumbling]
[solemn instrumental music plays]
♪♪
[in Tamil] Move, move, there's trouble.
[screaming]
Get up…
Hide anything Tamil…
your jewelry.
[cries out]
[metal slicing]
[in Sinhala] Bitch. Defending the Tamils.
[man in Sinhala] Come on! Come on!
It's the fucking Police…
Let's get out.
- [baby crying]
- [men yelling]
[baby crying]
[dog panting]
Was Radha Aunty hurt?
I don't think so.
Amma.
[in Tamil] It'll be okay.
[car engine roaring]
[in Tamil] Come sister, come.
[Janaki sobbing]
[in Tamil] Stop crying.
[whispering] Radha Aunty.
Radha Aunty.
[Anil]
Radha.
I'll kill those bastards.
Anil, I can't.
I just can't.
Can't?
Radha, that doesn't
make sense.
[Radha] Women and
children, all butchered,
simply because we are Tamil.
If you had only seen.
Radha, please look at me.
I'm not my father.
But you're Sinhalese
and I'm not.
How can that be changed?
- [knocking]
- [Ammachi in Tamil] Open the door!
Jayasinghe?
Open the door!
[Arjie in Tamil]
Go away, you old witch.
Arjie, open the door.
- [Appa] Hey!
- Come with me.
- It won't work, Anil.
- [Ammachi in Tamil] Open the door!
- [Anil] Please.
- [Appa] Arjie.
Don't do this.
[in Sinhala] I love you.
Please go, Radha Aunty.
Please go!
[banging]
[Priest] May the Lord in his
goodness strengthens your consent,
and fill you both
with his blessings.
What God has joined,
men must not divide.
[organ music plays]
♪♪
[melancholy instrumental music plays]
[hopeful instrumental music plays]
♪♪
Welcome to Victoria Academy,
Arjun Chelvaratnam.
[school bell ringing]
[indistinct chatter]
[Arjie in Tamil]
Diggy, I won't make the team.
You're such a loser, Arjie.
Why did Appa send you here?
Here, proceed.
Your classroom, okay?
Chelvaratnam.
This is 12C.
The Sinhala class.
You want 12F for
your brother,
the Tamil class.
No, Salgado, I want 12C.
Go on in.
How come you're in a
Sinhala class, huh?
My parents put me
here to assimilate.
Assimilate?
We want our separate state.
We want our independence.
You Tamils have been whining
here for the last 15 years.
We don't want you
here anymore.
Go.
[Shehan]
Hey, Salgado.
To the Tamil class...
Were you born fully,
or abbreviated at birth?
Soyza, you better watch out.
[school bell ringing]
Come, don't be shy.
[Teacher]
Morning boys.
Sit down.
I'm Arjie.
Arjun.
We only use surnames
here at Victoria.
[Teacher] So, today, we're gonna
read one of my favorite books,
A Tale of Two Cities,
by Charles Dickens.
Chelvaratnam.
Now, when we're reading this,
I want you to think about-
I'm Soyza.
Now the book is about
London and Paris,
but it can be anywhere.
It can be here,
it can be Sri Lanka.
It can be anywhere
you want it to be.
It can be you in the story.
Imagine that the story is
happening to you, okay?
Let's start.
Chapter one.
"Book the First,
Recall to Life: The Period."
"It was the best of times,
it was the worst of times.
It was the age of wisdom,
it was the age
of foolishness.
It was the epoch of belief,
it was the epoch
of incredulity.
It was the season of light,
it was the season
of darkness."
- [whistling]
- [singing in Sinhala]
[in Sinhala] Another Tamil dog.
[in Tamil] Chelliah, let's get out.
I say, Chelliah.
Don't you know better
than to use this toilet
without your Tamil pals?
Salgado, he's done nothing,
Salgado.
[grunting]
There are plenty of
toilet stalls here
but no big brother
in sight, huh?
Get out.
Hi.
Um, what's your real name?
Shehan.
Shehan. I'm Arjie.
Yeah, I know.
Right, right,
of course you know.
So, Shehan,
that's a...
it's a pretty modish name.
"Matters of grave importance,
it's style, not sincerity.
It's the important thing."
You've never heard of
the esteemed Mr. Wilde?
Style not sincerity!
Can't run from us!
Chelliah wants his Mummy!
Catch the fucking Tamil!
Some Sinhalese think the
sun shines out their asses.
You know, I'm not
afraid to say it.
It's at times like these
I'm ashamed to be Sinhalese.
Well then, I guess I... I'm
ashamed to be Tamil, too.
You know, our Tamil Tigers
up north.
So you don't hate me then
for being Sinhalese?
I despise you.
I abhor you.
Abhor?
What a big word,
old chap?
[laughing]
[singing on radio]
[chickens clucking]
- [chopping]
- [chicken squawking]
[in Tamil] Madam, 1.8 kilos.
[in Tamil] Don't you dare cheat me again.
[in Tamil] Madam, speak to
me in Sinhala, not Tamil.
[in English] Huh? Never.
[in Tamil] You’re rich. If you
speak Tamil, you'll be fine,
but I'm poor and stuck here.
[in Tamil] The butcher is losing his
Sinhalese customers…
…because he's Tamil.
We are the Jews of Asia.
[in English] We are the Jews of Asia.
[in Tamil] It will pass.
[in English] As the economy improves,
so do the differences.
[in Tamil] It's all a distraction Amma.
[in Tamil] No. it isn't.
[ball pinging]
[Ammachi in English]
I pray to Jesus every night
your hotel will be safe.
You keep praying, Ma.
Come on, Arjie!
[Arjie in Tamil] If they're fat and need
exercise, why don't they take up jogging?
[in English] Arjie, keep your eye on
the ball not the girls.
Chelva, stop.
He means the boys,
you know.
Shut up you Fatty boom boom.
Arjie!
[gentle instrumental music plays]
This boy has no
hand-eye coordination.
[gentle instrumental music plays]
♪♪
[bell tinkling]
[waves crashing]
[Appa]
Nalini!
Akka! Once you're past the waves
it's always calm, remember.
Of course I remember
that very original
quote of yours, Jegan!
[in Tamil] Jegan's been asking about you,
his favorite.
I was showing him
around the place.
I see Chelva has given
you his Bible.
Hey, Diggy, Sonali, Arjie!
Come here. Come.
[Amma in English] Chelva thinks that
Dale Carnegie made him who he is,
hey Chelva!
[in Tamil] This is Jegan. I’ve known
him since he was a boy.
He's Buddy's son.
He's here from Jaffna
to work at the resort.
[in English] Hi, Jegan!
You play cricket?
I like Arjuna Ranatunga a lot.
I love him.
- I also like cricket.
- Yeah?
[in Tamil] Why is Jegan really here?
Tamil Tigers.
He joined the Tigers?
Yes, he's hardly
the boy we knew.
Buddy wants him away from the Tigers
and the trouble they're causing.
No political talk.
[in English] Uh, this is... Your Appa gave
me this book, it's Dale Carnegie.
Hard to stay awake.
Jegan, was it a long trip?
About eight hours.
I took the train.
[in Tamil] Is Jegan staying
at staff quarters?
No. In town.
[Arjie in English] How long is
your train ticket?
[Jegan]
No, please.
[reflective music plays]
♪♪
["Flashdance… What a Feeling" plays]
♪ First there was nothing ♪
♪ But a slow glowing dream ♪
♪ That your fear
seems to hide ♪
Why are you sitting
here with me?
Go and find a nice
girl to dance with.
Go on.
♪ Deep inside your mind ♪
♪ All alone I have cried ♪
- [Jegan] Good evening, akka.
- [in Tamil] Nice to see you.
Can I get you
something to eat?
[in Tamil] I don’t need anything.
Thanks.
Come Jegan, sit.
No, akka.
Don’t be formal.
♪ Made of stone ♪
[in English] Is that Diggy smoking?
No, akka.
[in Tamil] What are you reading?
That’s a difficult book, no?
Quite impossible.
But it keeps my brain engaged.
[in English] But what about you
and Dale Carnegie?
Hm? How's it going?
Action breeds courage
and confidence.
If you want to conquer fear,
do not sit at home
and think about.
Go out and get busy.
Oh my goodness.
I doubt you and Dale Carnegie
would agree
on what you
consider is action.
I sincerely doubt it.
Excuse me.
♪ Pictures come alive ♪
♪ You can dance right
through your life ♪
Hi.
Bye.
["What A Feeling" continues playing]
♪♪
♪ Now I hear the music ♪
Arjie, come.
♪ Close my eyes,
I am rhythm ♪
♪ In a flash it takes
hold of my heart ♪
♪ What a feeling ♪
♪ Seein's believin' ♪
♪ I can have it all ♪
♪ Now I'm dancing
for my life ♪
♪ Take your passion ♪
♪ And make it happen ♪
♪ Pictures come alive ♪
♪ You can dance right
through your life ♪
♪ What a feeling ♪
[Teacher] "Every human
creature is constituted to be
that profound secret and
mystery to every other."
What does that mean?
Every human creature is
to be a profound secret
and mystery to every other.
That we will never know.
That no matter how close we
get to somebody and still…
I think I forgot my book.
Can we share?
[Teacher] …we don't know what
they're feeling
or why they're
doing something.
That every beating heart in
the hundreds of thousands
of breasts there
is in some of
its imaginings
a secret to the
heart nearest it.
[whistling music plays]
[dog barking]
BOARDING HOUSE FOR MEN
[baby crying]
[Arjie]
Amma.
[Amma in Tamil] Come on.
[in English] Okay, go and take
those clothes.
- Sorry, akka.
- [in Tamil] It's okay.
Pass the suitcase.
[in Tamil] Please, understand.
I don't want any trouble.
No, I don’t understand…
You’re kicking out
an innocent man.
But I have a boarding
house to run.
The boarders don't want
a Tamil here.
What can a woman do?
That’s not an excuse,
that’s cowardice.
A child has more
courage than you.
We all need to be united
as a country.
Let's go.
Come.
[in Sinhala] Tamil Pariah.
Tiger. Terrorist.
[Amma in Tamil] Jegan, stop.
Stop, Jegan!
[Amma in English] Look at me!
Look at me!
[in Tamil] No need for this.
Come on.
Woo!
[in Sinhala] What are you looking at?
[in Tamil] Here.
[in Tamil] The landlady said…
[in English] all you Tamils are
liars and murderers.
[gentle music plays]
[in Tamil] I cannot say this
to my husband…
♪♪
but I admire the Tamil Tigers.
They are the only ones
fighting for us Tamils.
Yes. Once I joined them,
I felt the same.
I'm sick of people…
[in English] Just like your landlady.
[in Tamil] I agree, but…
[in English] You end up killing people.
Innocent people.
Isn't that what you
call collateral damage?
[in Tamil] Easy for you to talk about
"collateral damage"…
…knowing your wealth
protects you.
It’s the poor who always
pay the price.
Here I am sitting in
all this luxury,
talking about
a Tamil Homeland…
[in English] But you aren't exactly
in the trenches, are you?
[in Tamil] I must go.
[in Tamil] Akka. Thank you for letting
me stay here.
Thank my husband.
It was his idea.
[Arjie]
♪ La la la la la ♪
[singing in Tamil]
[cow mooing]
Whoa.
[in Sinhala] Yes?
Ah, Shehan. Hi.
Welcome to my humble abode.
[in Sinhala] It's okay. He's a friend.
[in English] Thank you.
- Hey.
Hi, what lovely hair you have.
Thank you.
All the better to mess it.
Off limits.
Okay.
So, who else lives here?
- Just me.
- [peacock calling]
And Jeeves.
[laughing]
Wow.
A chicken coop.
[rooster crowing]
[hens clucking]
Welcome to my
den of iniquity.
Oh my god,
is that a computer?
Mm-hmm.
My father travels a lot.
Likes to bring me things.
My mother died
when I was three.
Oh.
Forehand or backhand?
Backhand, obviously.
It's the only way to win.
And you?
Hmm.
Oh, wow.
Who are these people?
Again, courtesy of my father.
Though he was not so
thrilled to bring me these.
[chuckling]
All yours.
Thank you.
Like this?
This.
[both giggle]
[vibrant orchestral music plays]
♪♪
So, what do we do,
you know?
I mean, I know people
like us exist.
They do?
Abroad.
Where it's not
illegal to be like us.
Most of these people are.
[Arjie]
Tell me about them.
A British band.
♪ Run away, turn away ♪
[Reporter in English]
This Sri Lankan army
has been patrolling aggressively
in the North of Sri Lanka
since last evening.
When the Tamil Tigers took over
the Kandivli railway station,
and set fire to a train.
The Tigers,
an armed group fighting
for a separate Tamil state
in the North,
intend such attacks as a way to
bring the civil administration
in the North to a halt,
thus creating a
defacto Tamil state.
The younger Tamils feel drawn
towards the Tigers,
seeing them as the
only protection
against what they call,
"States terrorism
by the Sinhalese."
[in Tamil] Where have you been?
[in English] I went for a film.
With a friend.
[Reporter]
…their homes, businesses destroyed
as well as the
violence and torture
used against Tamils
by the armed forces.
The Tamil Tigers have reacted to
the massacre of Tamil civilians
with attacks on
Sinhalese civilians.
[in Tamil] Where are Arjie’s manners?
[Amma in English] Arjie, where'd
you learn to play so well?
Practiced with a friend.
Chelva, look at his
hand-eye coordination.
Don't mess with
the Grand Diva,
Fatty boom boom.
[Sonali in English] Come on Anna,
it's Sunday, let's see a movie.
No, Sonali, I'd rather meet
your gorgeous cousin from Jagna.
Jegan's not a cousin,
he's a family friend,
he's sweet.
[piano instrumental music plays]
♪♪
Good shot.
[in Tamil] Why so quiet, Nalini?
[in English] I'm fine!
- You okay, Amma?
- [in Tamil] Yes, darling.
[ambulance blares]
[car horns]
[in Sinhala] It is on the radio.
Those bloody Tamils
attacked our people.
[in English] Oh, oh, sorry.
[in Tamil] Idiot.
[people yelling]
Arjie!
[in Tamil] Where the hell do
you think you're going?
[in English] To help!
The minute you
open your mouth,
they will know
you are Tamil.
[in Tamil] Come up. Now.
[gentle piano music plays]
♪♪
[in Tamil] "Those bloody Tamils."
[in English] You heard that.
Bloody Tigers.
Who told them to fight
for a Tamil homeland?
I certainly didn't.
Idiots… [in Tamil] Terrorists.
[in English] They're not fighting
for people like us.
Talking to Jegan, I see.
Is that what you
really believe Nalini?
Tit for tat?
Taking the Tigers' line?
[in Tamil] Unbelievable.
[in English] I'm not taking the
Tigers' line, Chelva.
I'm just saying that
they have a point
and we can't ignore it.
[in Tamil] And you,
don't you care for our people?
[in English] I've hired Jegan,
haven't I, Nalini?
[in Sinhala] Liar!
Shut up.
Go tell Appa.
[in English]
Sir, that man is a liar, sir.
[in Tamil] He said I can't instruct the
staff and that you gave
those orders.
Yes, son, those were my orders.
[in English] The Sinhalese staff they…
[Jegan]
Sir?
Look Jegan…
I have given you
a high position,
that's why
there's resentment.
[in Tamil] Because you’re Tamil
and I'm Tamil.
As if the Sinhalese
never favor their own.
[in English] Try and be more
practical, Nalini.
The trick is to
go out there
and make your money
while you can,
and don't step on
anyone's toes.
[in Tamil] Understand?
Yes, until the Sinhalese
decide to take it all away…
and wipe us out.
Just because they can.
[in English] You have a bright
future ahead,
don't spoil it, son.
[in Tamil] What bright future, sir?
[Diggy]
Sonali.
[in Tamil] Sit… idiot.
[in English] Do you think we
should talk to him?
Not now.
What happened to you, Nalini?
[in Tamil] What’s going on?
Nothing at all.
[in English] We've built a good
life together, Nalini.
And no marriage is perfect,
but we soldier along.
You think they'll be okay?
[in Tamil] I hope so.
[in English] You're both bloody idiots.
[Shehan] ♪ Can't you
see you belong to me ♪
[scatting]
[laughing]
[Shehan]
♪ How my poor heart aches ♪
♪ with every step you take ♪
[both laugh]
Pew.
♪ Every smile you fake,
every claim you… ♪
[school bell rings]
[Arjie] ♪ Oh can't you see,
you belong to me ♪
[Diggy]
Arjie!
- [bicycle bell rings]
- [in Tamil] Arjun, stop!
[in English] That Soyza... you,
you shouldn't be
friends with him.
I saw you both. It's
dangerous and it's illegal.
I don't know what the
hell you're talking about.
[in Tamil] Idiot. I warned you.
I abhor you.
[car engine roaring]
[in Tamil] Amma. What happened?
[in English] Well, it seems it's too
risky to have Tamil volunteers
at the hospital.
I'm sorry, Amma.
[Amma]
Oh my goodness.
My son is reading a very
controversial book.
Let me see.
Gore Vidal.
[in Tamil] A recommendation
from Radha, no doubt.
[in English] Do you think she's happy?
[soft piano music plays]
♪♪
No, I don't think she is.
Amma, my best friend,
Shehan Soyza,
can he come and
spend the day?
Sure.
[soft piano music plays]
♪♪
Shehan!
Hi.
Welcome to my humble abode.
Nice T-shirt.
Hi, Arjie!
- Hi.
- Hello.
Would you and your friend
like to go see a movie?
Fame is playing
at the Majestic.
Um, well maybe another time?
Sorry, Shehan,
this is my wonderful
sister Sonali.
Sonali, come say hi
to my friend Shehan.
- Hey, Sonali.
- Hi.
[Sonali] Would you like
something to drink, some snacks?
We'll just help
ourselves later.
I'll tell Lakshmi.
We'll just be in the garage
looking at some old photos.
Okay, I'm here if
you need anything.
Thank you.
Bye.
It should be around
here somewhere.
Here, yes this one.
This is my Radha Aunty.
You would have loved her.
She used to sing this
Leonard Cohen song.
What was it called?
♪ It's four in the morning.
The end of December ♪
♪ I'm writing you now,
just to see you're better ♪
Yes.
♪ New York is... ♪
Is something,
I don't know.
Oh, Radha Aunty.
Now, whenever things got bad,
she would do this
twirl and say...
"Don't mess with
the Grand Diva."
[both laugh]
[ethereal instrumental music plays]
♪♪
[in Tamil]
here are Arjie and Shehan?
In the garage.
And what are they doing
in the garage?
[Sonali in English] Looking at
some old photos or something.
[in Tamil]
Did Lakshmi give some snacks?
[Sonali in English] No, she
gave them lemonade.
[Amma in Tamil] Ah, okay.
Appa.
[in English] There's something
wrong with my bike,
can you look?
Sure.
[Amma in Tamil] Boys must be hungry.
[in English] Yeah, shall we give
them some snacks?
[in Tamil] Okay
[in English] Is Arjie's friend nice?
Yeah, he is.
That's good.
Chelva…
[in Tamil]
tell those boys to come out…
[in English] Tea is ready.
[Diggy]
Appa, wait.
[somber instrumental music plays]
♪♪
[Amma] Chelva…
[in Tamil] What happened?
Diggy.
[somber instrumental music plays]
♪♪
[in Tamil] I want you to
end this friendship.
[in English] Oh, Arjie,
how could you?
[sniffs]
[retching]
[somber instrumental music plays]
♪♪
Why are you crying, Amma?
[Teacher] "Had we but
world enough and time,
This coyness..."
Excuse me.
Sit down.
"Had we but world
enough and time,
This coyness, lady,
were no crime.
We would sit down
and think which way
To walk, and pass
our long love's day.
Thou by the
Indian Ganges' side
Shouldest rubies find;
I by the tide
Of Humber would complain.
I would
Love you ten years
before the flood,
And you should,
if you please, refuse."
[Shehan]
Arjie, can we talk?
Sure.
You and I,
we're normal, okay?
Arjie listen,
I love you.
I love you, Arjie.
Shehan...
I just can't.
Why?
My family.
Tamils, hm?
Filthy Tamils.
Fucking Tamils are
all the fucking same.
[student]
Stop it you two!
[yelling in Sinhalese]
You're all done.
Thank you.
Appa will sort
everything out, don't worry.
[Diggy in Tamil]
So far he’s done nothing.
But he will.
[in English] Police came and
took Jegan at work.
[in Tamil] They say he's a Terrorist,
a Tiger.
What happened?
Amma, Jegan?
There, Appa’s come.
Okay.
Where’s Jegan?
We kept phoning you.
The police kept him
for the night.
[in English] Just routine stuff.
Just routine?
Is it just routine to keep
someone in jail overnight?
[in Tamil] Didn't you insist
on releasing him?
[in English] Prevention of Terrorism Act.
They have every
right to keep him.
Look, if Jegan is innocent,
they will release him, okay.
[Amma]
Chelva.
[in Tamil] I have a business to run.
[in English] I cannot be accused
of harboring a terrorist.
No matter what you think,
Nalini,
not all of us have
the luxury to fight.
Come on, Appa!
[crowd yelling]
[Officer 1 in Tamil] Shut up!
[in Tamil] Where is my son?
[Officer 1] Stop screaming.
Nobody can help you.
Go home.
What's the meaning of this?
[Officer 2] Please help.
Idiots.
I’ll put you in jail.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
Officer…
…I've come to look
for my relative.
What’s his name?
Jegan Parameswaran.
Please, let my son go.
I told you to stand
in the queue.
Wait, only he can go in.
No, Officer, I must go in.
I told you already,
only he can go through.
Amma, I’ll go.
Come.
No.
I’ll go.
[crowd yelling]
[Officer] Jegan Parameswaran?
[overlapping chatter]
Jegan Parameswaran?
[crowd chattering]
You have two minutes.
[in Tamil] Jegan, how are you?
I am okay.
Amma’s contacted QC Nadesan,
the best human rights lawyer.
We’re Tamil.
No justice for us now.
[in English] Nalini's here?
Amma's outside, they won't let her in.
[Officer in Tamil] Your time is over.
Come on, let’s go.
Thank you.
[crowd chattering]
[horn blowing]
[door slamming]
[siren blaring]
[Officer] Come on!
[train whistle blowing]
[in Tamil] Son…
[in English] It was terrible, Amma.
[thunder crashing]
[dog barking]
[rain streaming]
[birds chirping]
[dog barking]
[reflective music plays]
♪♪
[indistinct chatter]
[crowd chattering]
[tense instrumental music plays]
♪♪
Arjie!
Arjie! Arjie!
Arjie, remember,
action breeds
courage and confidence.
[in Tamil] The Tigers need
young men like you.
[dramatic instrumental music plays]
♪♪
[banging on door]
Shehan?
[in Sinhala] He's in his bedroom.
["Every Breath You Take"
plays through headphones]
It's sincerity, not style.
That's the vital thing.
♪ Every single day ♪
♪ Every word you say ♪
♪ Every game you play ♪
♪ Every night you stay ♪
♪ I'll be watching you ♪
♪ Oh, can't you see ♪
- [softly] Wake up.
- Mm.
Wake up.
["Every Breath You Take" plays]
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Every breath you take ♪
♪ Every move you make ♪
♪ Every bond you break ♪
♪ Every step you take ♪
♪ I'll be watching you ♪
♪ Every single day ♪
♪ And every word you say ♪
♪ Every game you play ♪
♪ Every night you stay ♪
♪ I'll be watching you ♪
♪ Oh, can't you see ♪
♪ You belong to me ♪
♪ How my poor heart aches ♪
♪ With every step you take ♪
♪ Every move you make ♪
- ♪ Every vow break ♪
- [banging]
♪ Every smile you fake ♪
♪ Every claim you stake
I'll be watching you ♪
[in Sinhala] Tamils are being
attacked in the city.
You should go home.
I should go.
I'm coming with you.
[phone ringing]
[in Tamil] Are you okay?
Hello, Nalini?
Be careful.
No Tamil is safe in Colombo.
Oh, no… I will tell Chelva.
Chelva!
Quiet, stop crying.
[swelling distant, angry shouting]
[crowd in Sinhala] Kill the Tamils.
Burn them alive.
Bastards.
Fucking Tamils…
How dare they!
[somber instrumental music plays]
Every Tamil is a Tiger.
Kill the Terrorists.
♪♪
[explosion bangs]
[distant explosions]
[in English] Chelva, he's here!
Arjie… [in Tamil] Come.
Amma.
[in English] Where the hell
were you, Arjie?
I was at Shehan's.
No big deal, Appa.
He's here now.
Go! Pack a satchel.
Only important things.
- [Appa in Tamil] Make it fast, Arjie.
- Sonali!
[Appa] We're going next door…
Move it!
[Amma in Tamil] Chelva…
Got the passports?
[Appa] Yes.
[in English] Sonali, come,
what are you doing?
[Appa]
Lakshmi? Lakshmi!
Let's go!
[Appa]
Lakshmi!
[Amma in Tamil]
Diggy put the lights off.
- Mr. Perera?
- [knocking]
[in English] Come in, Chelva.
Right now, I’m ashamed
of being Sinhalese.
[distant explosions]
I'm so sorry, Nalini,
but it's the safest place.
[door locking]
[reflective instrumental music plays]
♪♪
[thunder rumbling]
[rain streaming]
[loud banging]
[man in Sinhala] Open up.
We know you're there.
You're hiding Tamils.
No, we are Sinhalese Buddhists.
Get out or I'll call the police.
We are the police.
Out of the way.
There is nothing to see.
[loud shouting]
[rain pouring]
Hiding Tamils in there?
No no, nothing there.
This is a store room.
Open it then!
[loud shouting]
Nobody is hiding there.
We don't believe you.
Door is locked.
[banging]
Break it open.
Move the furniture.
- Look there.
- [swelling dramatic music plays]
Push that away.
Come on out.
[thunder crashing]
You've seen there's
nothing there.
All junk here.
Better stuff next door.
Let's go.
[yelling in Sinhala] Motherfuckers.
Destroy them all.
[glass crashing]
Tear the place apart.
Take whatever you want.
- [somber music plays]
- [angry yelling]
♪♪
[singing over PA]
[man 1 in Tamil] Move.
[man 2 in Tamil] It' s my turn.
[man 3 in Tamil Don't push,
everyone needs water.
[bell tolling]
[man 4 in Tamil] Enough!
Get lost.
[in English]
Come with us to England.
Never.
[Priest in Tamil] Stop fighting.
This is a church.
[somber instrumental music plays]
♪♪
[baby crying]
[birds chirping]
What time's your
flight to Toronto?
A little after midnight,
I think.
I should get going though.
[gentle instrumental music plays]
♪♪
- [wind blowing]
- [hopeful music plays]
♪♪
[in Tamil] I told you to wait
inside the terminal.
[Appa mumbles]
Oh, look how big you are.
[in English] Come on.
[in Tamil] Get inside the car.
[in English] We simply must get you
some proper winter clothes.
[in Tamil] Where is Rajan?
[in English] Who knows.
Who cares.
[in Tamil] It's so cold.
[in English] My feet are turning blue.
Feet of a refugee.
I wanna go home.
[in Tamil] Shut up…
[in English] You can't go home.
Oh, Arjie.
Radha Aunty?
Why the hell isn't
he getting in?
He can do what he wants.
[in Tamil] In this new world,
we're all free slaves.
[in English] Come on, get inside.
[pensive instrumental music plays]
♪♪
Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org