Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
(scary music)
On October 31, 1988,
10-year-old Robert Maxwell
attended a classmates
Halloween party.
Several of the children
there tormented Robert,
giving him a panic attack.
His nose began to
bleed uncontrollably.
Confused and scared,
he ran out the house
as children chased him deep
into the neighboring woods
known as Diablo's Den.
That night, eight children
returned but Robert did not.
Through the following weeks,
a Fall Creek Valley search
party scoured the woods,
but he was never found.
As the years passed,
many claimed to see the ghost of Robert
wandering the streets
on Halloween night.
Still wearing his costume
leaving a crimson trail
from his bleeding nose.
Thus began the urban
legend of Bloody Bobby.
(typewriting sounds)
(turning pages)
I just want this all to go away.
I know.
Maybe this could be
kind of therapeutic
for you to talk
about all of this.
You're not gonna
spin this around?
No I won't, Alex.
I'm a journalist too you know.
I've seen it all
and I know when I'm being duped.
I'm not gonna dupe you.
This...
This is the biggest tragedy
in the history of
Fall Creek Valley.
It's not gonna go away.
You know, maybe I could
write my own story huh?
That way it wouldn't
have all the lies
that other people
would put into it.
Yeah I don't think you could
be very objective about it.
It doesn't matter anyway.
People are gonna take away
from this whatever they want.
I could say whatever
I want to say
and you could write
whatever you want.
It's not gonna stop
it from becoming
some twisted urban legend.
Parents are gonna find their
kids in the dark chanting.
(scribbling)
As if they're trying
to channel his spirit.
Bring him back to life.
They're gonna hear
their kids whispering,
Bloody Bobby! Bloody Bobby!
Ooh!
That was like shaving my fuzzy
man-purse with a switchblade!
Hardcore!
My body is shakin'
and my head is quakin'
after that skull-pounding
number from Jetset Rejects.
If you can't get
enough from that band,
you can catch them
tomorrow night
at our Annual
Hallow-Scream Creepshow.
Rumor has it that
lead singer Mike Scott
will be judging the
costume contest.
First prize for Best Male
Costume is 5,000 big ones.
First prize for the ladies
is a night alone with
Mike Scott himself.
Now we've been
dropping clues all week
for the secret location
of this annual rock fest.
Last clue for you comes
tomorrow at two o'clock sharp.
Your last chance for this
devlishly-rockin good time
brought to you by 101.6.
Okay, listen, I know we've
been to Hallow-Scream
for the past last like 20 years
but I am so giddy I want to
pee in my pants! (laughs)
No seriously we are gonna
have the best costumes.
They are gonna kick so much ass!
Costumes?
What costumes?
I wanted to surprise you.
You're gonna be He-Man
and I am gonna be She-Ra!
Uh!
Oh great a shitty gay-ass
cartoon from the 80s!
Cool!
I can't believe
you just said that!
She-ra was my idol!
Aw man that show was propaganda.
It was a gay
recruitment cartoon.
Here we go.
Aw don't give me that.
Alright, look, gay guys
can't reproduce right?
Alright, look, you got He-man.
This buffed up hunk
protector of the universe.
But what's his true identity?
Prince Adam.
Boring, pale-faced,
purple-wearing sissy bitch.
Even his pet is a fucking pussy!
(laughing)
I'm not saying that
because its a cat.
Like it's all scared
and shit all the time.
So then you got Prince Adam
who wields his mighty
magic sword and bam!
By the Honor of Grayskull!
Aw fuck that for the
Honor of Grayskull shit.
That was She-ra's thing.
He-man said, "By the
power of Gray..."
"By the Power of Grayskull."
"I have the Power!"
Oh, yeah, so you know
a lot about He-man
for someone who doesn't
really like the show.
So, anyway, after Prince
Adam gets the power,
he transforms into He-man.
Tan.
Deep voice.
Shirtless with furry pants on.
Mm-hmm.
He was the inspiration
for male strippers
for the next 30 years!
Oh so what you are saying is
you think He-man was sexy.
No, I never said sexy.
I said He-man was gay.
Pay attention.
Look at all the other characters
from Masters of the Universe.
Man-at-Arms.
Gay.
Merman.
Beastman.
Totally gay.
I mean Fisto.
Fisto?
Supergay!
One million percent gay!
Alright then so all these
buffed-up homoerotic men
spend all their time
fighting for Grayskull.
And do you know what the
Castle of Grayskull truly was?
An All Man's Clubhouse.
No bitches allowed.
Sorry, women.
It's as simple as this.
Gay guys cannot reproduce.
So they have to recruit.
So they make this
awesome cartoon filled
with tons of gay overtones
to recruit future members
to join the Gay Alliance
later on down the road.
And I'm not being
homophobic either.
Just simple science.
Recruit or die off.
(sighing)
Don't give me that shit.
Yeah, I hardly think
it works like that.
I actually think that's
the dumbest thing
that's ever come
out of your mouth.
And, believe me, I've
heard some dumb shit.
Hey, you're going the wrong way.
It's a shortcut.
Over my dead body.
- (car crashing)
- (tires screeching)
What was that?
It's nothing.
You okay?
Yeah.
No, no, no stay in the car!
Okay?
I've gotta check it out.
- (haunting music)
- What?
What, what?
- (car door creaking)
- We hit a pumpkin!
What the fuck?
- (crickets chirping)
- (car door cracks)
Some asshole left a pumpkin
in the middle of the road.
Fuckin' up my rig!
(slow musicbox music)
Ash, just get back
in the car, okay?
Let's just go!
I gotta check this shit out!
(nature sounds)
This is bullshit!
I'm calling a tow truck!
(eerie music)
(clanking)
Hello?
(slow scary music)
(sharp dramatic music)
Don't go too far.
Take this.
Thank you.
(haunting music)
(ghostly laughing)
(slow haunting music)
(ominous music)
(grunting)
(distant smashing sound)
(creepy music)
Ash!
(weeping)
(scary music)
- (loud banging)
- (screaming)
(pulsating intense music)
(police radio chattering)
(haunting music)
What do we have?
I'm not sure but I bet we'll
find more answers down there.
Been down there yet?
No, not yet.
I wanted to get this scene
all squared away first.
So the vehicle is
registered to Ash Simpson.
There's a lot of
cash left in the car
so we can rule out robbery.
And based on this driver's
license that I found?
That is Crystal Cochran.
No signs of Ash Simpson.
(haunting music)
Did you find anything else?
Another gutless corpse
in Diablo's Den!
(sharp intense music)
(guitar solo music)
- (alarm blaring)
- (light tropical music)
♪ Your a book I can't put down ♪
♪ When you walk
by, I turn around ♪
♪ You're like Sunday
all night long ♪
♪ I can just unwind ♪
♪ It's a good time ♪
♪ I feel like I
been swept away ♪
♪ Loving you all day ♪
♪ Loving you all night ♪
♪ I wake up and I feel a smile ♪
♪ And talk a while,
everything's alright ♪
(door creaks open and closed)
(sound of urinating)
Reggie, it stinks in here!
What happened to your face?
What, I just woke up?
Just get in the shower
I can smell you from here.
(fart)
(sound of curtain closing)
(sound of shower)
Gross!
Blehh!
(pleasant piano music)
(bleeps and bloops)
Hey, Oswald!
There she is!
Where are you, in a hotel room?
Oh, yeah, I'm in
my cousin's room.
The bum just woke up.
He's taking a shower right now.
Oh, so what you're saying is
you have a few minutes alone?
Oswald!
I only have like two minutes!
That's all I need,
baby! (laughs)
Aaahhh!
Oswald!
Your lunch is ready!
Okay!
In a minute, Ma!
(chuckles) Sorry about that.
So I can't finally wait to
see you tonight in person!
This meeting?
Long overdue!
Mmm-hmm.
My heart is beating faster
just thinking about it!
Mine too, cowboy!
Mine too!
Nice!
Uh, how do these smell?
Ohh!
Um! (laughs)
Eww!
You know what?
If you need a second
opinion the answer is no!
Eww!
Oh, God!
Hey, did you see
that email from Alex?
Uh, what?
It looks like he finally
made it back into the States.
He's gonna be here
tomorrow morning.
It's about time.
Are you decent yet?
Yeah.
You know you could've
stayed with me.
I have a whole three
bedroom house to myself now.
Um, aside from the fact that
Grandma might be
haunting the place,
I really don't want to
hear you having cybersex
with your internet boyfriend.
Oh my God, that only
happened like one time
and it was purely by accident.
How does cybersex
become accidental?
Maybe I've accidentally had
cybersex and just don't know it.
Anyway I'm gonna meet
up with him tonight
for the first time ever.
Yeah, we're going to
this big Halloween party.
Hey, you should come!
You know what?
It's actually at your old house!
Huh?
Yeah Willy Anderson
bought your old house
like six months ago!
You said he was in
Wall Street, New York.
Doing that Wall Street stuff.
Yeah, I guess he
like tried to screw
his boss's daughter or assistant
or something like that.
So he totally got fired
for sexual harassment.
So he's back in good ol'
Fall Creek Valley again
for a fresh start!
Hmm, I think I'd rather
have dull pencils
just shoved directly
into my eyeballs
then actually hang out
with Willy Anderson again.
That kid used to kick my
ass everyday in school!
Oh my God, Reggie.
It's been like 20 years.
Get over it!
Hey, you know a
lot of our friends
are gonna be there too.
Like Erica?
Your wallet is
right here, genius.
Oh, thanks.
Erica is actually getting
married to Jebediah Osborn.
Is that the Preacher's Son?
Mm-hmm.
Totally turned her life around.
Turned to God and
now she's marrying
the Son of a Preacher Man!
Wow.
Oh and I believe Madison
is also gonna be there tonight.
Really?
Well maybe I'm not really
doing anything tonight.
Maybe I'll go with you.
Yay, you're coming!
You're coming!
Yay, goodie!
I'm so excited!
You can meet my new
internet boyfriend, Oswald.
Oswald Jeffrey Gacy.
Hm!
You realize that sounds like
a serial killer name, right?
Why does everybody
keep saying that?
(hard rock music)
(sound of egg cracking)
You have to remember
to chew, Deputy.
Sorry.
My first meal of the day.
We had a pretty early
call this morning.
Are people getting
teepeed already?
Not exactly.
The Sheriff and I, we
were up at Diablo's...
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
We found some graffiti.
Hmm.
And that's it.
Unless the bottomless pit
here wants something else.
No, I'm good.
Never ever say Diablo's
Den again, okay?
Okay.
It'll be 14.26.
Thank you, Sheriff.
Sure.
Actually, Sheriff,
can I holler at you
real quick for a second?
Um, early this morning
I saw some kid crawl over
my fence into my yard.
And I'm pretty sure
it's Missy Waters' kid.
Ya see, he wasn't
too keen about me
uh bangin' his Mom a
couple months back.
I mean, we had some really
good times together.
You know but then she tried
to get all serious with me
and everything.
And actually between you and I,
it would be a disservice
to all the ladies in Fall
Creek Valley if I settle down.
(chuckling)
So I dropped her.
And then she just
kept calling me up,
you know, cryin' on the phone.
"Can we work things out?"
Then I hear her Son
back there sayin' shit.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
What happened this morning?
Oh, oh um, shit, nothin'
out of the ordinary.
I mean other than that
little punk tresspassin'!
Alright.
I'll keep an eye out.
Thanks, Sheriff!
You were saying you found
something down in the Den?
No, you know what?
I really can't say where we were
because I still don't know
the area all that well.
But I could use someone to
really show me around town.
(bell dinging)
Hey, order up!
Be right back.
Mind if I join you, Deputy?
(grunting)
Ahh.
(mysterious music)
The Sheriff is right.
This town gets a little anxious
at the mention of Diablo's Den.
Especially her.
She's spent the last
20 some-odd years
trying to forget
about that place.
Excuse me?
I know you and the
Sheriff found something
down in Diablo's
Den this morning.
I don't know what
you're talkin...
Don't deny it, Son.
It may be just a
little graffiti.
But I know why the Sheriff
wants it kept a secret.
And why is that Mister?
Granger.
Horace Granger.
You'll get to know me.
I own Granger's Pub
off of Harvest Way.
It ain't graffiti
that the Sheriff
wants to keep quiet about.
It's the location.
Ah!
(sound of door)
Doctor Nolan!
Meet our new Deputy.
Nice to meet you.
Please join us.
She's doing a story
on Diablo's Den.
Do you mind if I
take some notes?
Go ahead.
Thank you.
You see Diablo's Den
is older than the town
of Fall Creek Valley.
Some say it's haunted.
Some believe it is
a gateway to Hell.
Either way, everyone
steers clear of that place.
Why?
You didn't feel anything
while you were out there?
Something unnatural?
Something unexplained?
Maybe even a little evil?
(mysterious music)
You mentioned Madison.
What does she want to forget?
Some bad things happened
out there over the years.
It started when she was a kid.
A 10-year-old boy,
Bobby Maxwell,
went missing on
Halloween night 1988.
He went to a party
and never came home.
The whole town was in a
frenzy looking for him
but no trace of the
boy was ever found.
What does that have to
do with Diablo's Den?
Ah!
About two months after
his disappearance,
some kid came forward
with information
about what happened that night.
Said a group of
kids from the party
taunted and chased
Bobby into the woods.
Bobby fell down into the ravine
that overlooks the highway
and was hit by a car.
And they never found the body?
No.
Like I said, no trace
of him anywhere.
Not in the woods.
On the highway.
Nowhere.
The only thing that showed up
was a tattered old comic book
with his name on it
found in Diablo's Den.
Some think the evil in Diablo's
Den just swallowed him up.
This Bobby.
Is he one of Madison's friends?
No.
The kid who came
forward said that she
was one of the
kids chasing Bobby.
Deputy.
Have a great day.
I have a feeling it's going
to be one helluva night.
Shall we?
Nice to meet you.
So are you gonna lick
the plate clean too?
(laughs) No, I've still
gotta have my protein shake.
- Do I owe you anything or...
- No.
Did the Sheriff
take care of it all?
No, he took care of it.
(light upbeat music)
That really isn't
necessary, Deputy.
Please.
Call me Trevor.
Thank you.
Whew!
Kind of a boring town.
Keeps you pretty busy.
And?
Bobby Maxwell is kin to me.
I never did get over his death.
That's why I stay in Fall
Creek Valley to find closure.
Can you hear voices?
Sometimes.
How about right now?
Now?
It's the quiet before the storm.
(loud rock music)
Service!
Hello?
Who's working here these days?
You'll see.
Oh my God!
Reggie?!
Oh my God, I haven't seen
you in like I don't know,
like, 20 years?
Hello?
Could we order now?
God, why does the service
always suck around here?
Very funny, Tiffany.
What can I get you guys?
Coffee.
- Black as midnight on a...
- Black like your soul.
Uh, yeah.
I'll have a grande
no foam soy latte
at exactly 130 degrees please.
Okay.
So two coffees at whatever
temperature I damn well choose
to serve them at!
And I'll go get
those while you guys
take a look at the menus.
(intense screamo music)
What the fuck, Madison?
I can't hear my customers.
The clues, woman, I
need to hear the clues!
(on radio) Begins
in just a few hours.
The last and final clue
as to its secret location:
"Halloween is no time
for pencils and books
"but time to raise Hell
with devils and ghouls."
Ooh, now that is the
easiest of them all!
Tonight is the night to
rock out with your cock out
if you got one,
if not then jam out
with your clam out!
(laughs) Brought to
you by 101.6, The RAWK.
Are you guys ready to order?
I want the chocolate
chip pancakes.
Ooh, those sound
so good right now!
I haven't had those
since I was 10!
You guys, we don't have
those on the menu anymore.
Come on!
Arrggh.
Okay, let me see what
kind of influence I have
on the big guy.
I'll be right back.
Wow this place is
like a time capsule.
Yeah that's kind of why I
wanted to bring you here.
I am so sorry about that, guys.
Big Dick McGee has been
like all week crazy
about the clues for that
Hallow-Scream Party.
Oh, tell him to try the
Riverdale University campus.
Okay.
No shit, really?
Well, I mean, that's
based on the last clue.
Um, the DJ mentioned
books, pencils,
and partying with devils.
And I know that the
Riverdale University mascot
is a crimson devil.
So that's just my guess.
So, any chance I'll be
seeing you there tonight?
Um, no, actually we
already have plans.
Madison, Reggie
wants to go with us
to the party at Will's tonight.
Oh, yeah?
Oh I was invited to that party!
Maybe I'll stop in for a few.
Wow, I thought Liz
was into girls now
but I think she's got a
thing for you, Reggie.
Hmm.
Anyways, I'll make sure
to pass on the message.
With any luck, this
will be the first year
he'll actually go to the party.
So, hey, what time can I stop
by for my Halloween costume?
I'll be home by Four.
Okay, cool. Four.
Well I'll stop by then
and, girl, can I just say
I am so glad that you're
coming out with us tonight.
I mean it's about time
you finally got over
your prudish ways.
Whatever.
I am so not a prude.
I had a kid out of wedlock.
Oh, yeah, I guess you just
got your sluttiness on
a little bit too early.
But, hey, oh my God, guess what?
My guy is coming tonight.
Oswald, my internet guy?
(laughs)
Uh, Mask Guy!
- (giggling)
- What?
Mask?
Who is this Mask Guy?
Well, if you must know,
when me and Oswald
first started chatting,
we would wear masks.
We just thought it would
help us open up a bit more
if we could preserve
the anonymity.
Mm-hmm.
Wow.
Tiffany, you just
keep finding yourself
in weirder and
weirder situations.
Wait.
Were you two wearing masks
when you were having the...
You know.
None of your business!
Okay, it's not what you
wanted but it's free,
it's on the house.
(growling noises)
You got the clue right!
What?
Like I said, I like that guy!
(acoustic music)
(knocking)
Look, that's fine.
Just bring her back
tomorrow at nine.
I just got home from work.
I don't have time for this!
Hi, come in.
Listen, I have guests.
I have to go.
Sorry about that, guys.
Penny is with her Dad tonight.
Is this her?
Yup!
That's my little girl.
Wow.
She's looks exactly like you
did when we were that age.
Tiffany, darlin',
Oswald just told me
he's gonna be there at eight!
Oh, Madison, that is fabulous!
- You like it?
- Mm-hmm!
Alright.
Who made these masks?
Uh, Penny did.
Yeah, isn't she a neat kid?
(laughs)
You know what?
She made those in
Mrs. Johnson's class.
- Really?
- Yeah!
That old bat is still alive?
(laughs) Yeah!
(laughing)
Who says Old Bat anymore?
I do, Tiffany.
Wasn't she like 50 or
100 when we had her?
No, I think she was
in her thirties.
Yeah, you're probably right.
She was probably
only, only looked 50.
(laughs)
Old Mrs. J still has her
Halloween mask
designing contest, huh?
Yup.
She sure does.
Remember when we had ours?
Yeah, you made the Elephant Man.
Come on!
It was horrible!
It was supposed to
be Michael Jackson.
Whatever.
Alex got second place.
I think I got third place.
Who got first place?
As if anybody could forget huh?
Bobby Maxwell.
I totally got cheated.
Cheated?
Yeah I had Old Bat Johnson
a couple years later
and they weren't doing
that mask contest anymore.
(phone ringing)
Oh!
It's Oswald!
I am just gonna
take this outside.
(giggling)
(door opening and closing)
Yeah, I guess getting
divorced wasn't all that bad.
I got rid of a scumbag and
I got this beautiful house
and three full-time jobs.
Three jobs?
Yeah.
Wow.
Anyways, I want to
hear all about you
and the last 20 years.
Um, nah, it's, you
don't want to hear it.
It's not pretty.
Come on.
It can't all be that bad.
Mostly.
You know, when we
left Fall Creek Valley
I was labeled the troubled kid.
And I guess I just
kind of kept up with
that label ever since.
So 20 years of straight trouble?
Yeah and I've been okay
the past three years.
You know, I've just
been kind of laying low
and staying clean.
What Tiff, she,
Tiffany, hasn't told you
about her deadbeat cousin yet?
Stop it.
She would never
call you a deadbeat.
And believe it or not,
she's very fond of you.
She might be getting
me confused with Alex.
No, she has nice things to
say about you both so stop it.
She said that you have your own
commercial painting company?
That's actually Alex's
and I, you know, I
sometimes kind of manage it
when he's away
playing journalist.
Yeah, Tiffany said
that he's in Africa.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
he's got this great story
he's really excited about it.
And he thinks he might
win the Pulitzer.
Wow.
Yeah and then we got
an email this morning,
he's on his way to
Fall Creek Valley,
he should be here
tomorrow sometime
so we can go through the
estate sale, you know,
Grandma's estate sale.
Well, it would be really
nice to see him as well.
(romantic music)
- Is, do I have...
- There's nothing on you.
- Oh.
- Am I staring?
- (laughing)
- I'm staring!
- I'm staring.
I'm sorry!
It's just so weird!
I can't believe that...
I just can't believe
that you're here!
Standing in front
of me in my house!
You know, I never thought
that I was ever
gonna see you again.
I mean nobody even
knew your parents
were thinking of moving.
Just one day you don't
show up to school.
And then I went to your
house and it was empty.
Tiffany had no idea
where you were.
It was just like your
parents upped and left
and didn't look back.
(door opens and closes)
Okay, we have got
to get out of here.
I have so much to do to get
ready for the party tonight.
Well, I guess we're going.
Yeah I have some really
important emails to check.
I will see you there.
You better not weasel out of it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And I am gonna go start the car
so if you're not there in
30 seconds I'm leaving.
(door opens and closes)
I guess I'll see you tonight.
You can tell me about
your past 20 years, huh?
(giggling)
Yeah.
It was really good seeing you.
I missed you.
(spooky music)
(chopping sounds)
(phone ringing)
(knocking on door)
(door opening)
I'm sorry, little guy.
I don't have any
candy this year.
You could try going next door.
I think they have some
really cool chocolate.
Are your parents with you?
Do you speak English?
Habla Espanol?
What are you supposed to be?
It looks familiar.
Is it from a movie?
(closing door)
(knocking on door)
(opening door)
Listen, kid, I don't
have any candy.
I'm really sorry.
I can give you an apple.
I don't know what to tell you.
Try the neighbors.
I'm sure there's gonna be
houses that have candy.
Okay?
Happy Halloween!
(closing door)
(loud knocking)
(opening door)
(door creaking closed)
(locking sound)
(very loud knocking)
(door creaking open)
(intense scary music)
You've had your fun!
Now get the hell out of here!
(explosive orchestral
percussion)
(door closing)
(scary music)
(chewing)
(rustling sounds)
(shower curtain opening)
(eerie music)
(unzipping sound)
(dripping sounds)
(shower turning on)
(eerie music slowly growing)
(shrill shrieking)
(fleshy stabbing and
screaming sounds)
(stilted breathing)
Boop Boop Boop. I see you.
Oh yeah, that's what
I'm talkin' about.
Hey!
(speaking in foreign language)
klaatu barada nikto
Hmm, the Devil!
El Diablo!
Ha ha ha!
Okay hmm mum murm.
Uh, you listen to me.
Fall Creek Valley.
I'm El Diablo!
I'm a horny devil!
Oh, Madison!
Titty titty titty titty titty!
Oh give it to me, Madison!
(laughs) Great!
(whispering sound)
It's all your fault!
(light musicbox music)
(whispering sound)
Trick or treat!
♪ What you gonna do
when it all comes down ♪
(hard rock music)
(party sounds)
Oh Jesus, Tiff.
What has the bastard
done with the place?
I'm not.
It's...
It looks way different
than it used to before.
Oh my God, quit stalling Reggie.
There's gonna be lots of
people in there that you know.
I have to find Madison
real fast to get my phone
'cause I just know Oswald's
been texting me like a madman!
(laughs) Come on!
So then I said,
"B cup not C cup!"
(laughing)
(party sounds)
Whoa!
Tiffy baby!
You are lookin' smokin' tonight.
Give us a twirl.
Thanks, Madison made
this costume for me.
Is she here by the way?
Uh!
Who is the man who's lucky
enough to be your date?
- (sighs)
- (laughing)
You remember Reggie, my cousin?
Oh!
Whoa!
Dude!
I haven't seen you in a minute!
Oh!
Jeez, the last time I saw you...
You were shoving my
head in a toilet.
Well that couldn't have been
the very last time I saw you?
That was actually the incident
that made my family move
out of Fall Creek Valley.
Uh.
Wow!
(laughs) I mean, it
was a long time ago,
we we were all kids then.
We're all grown up now, mature.
Let bygones be bygones.
Come on, let's get some brews!
Yeah come on, Reggie!
Ah, only the finest!
Pacifico Clara!
Eh!
I'm alright, actually.
(speaking in foreign language)
Do you want a beer?
Do you want to pick that
up too when you're done?
Just kiddin', man!
Thanks, Willy.
Oh, it's Will now.
It's more manly.
Yeah, yeah ladies seem
to like it better.
By the way,
did I tell you that you are
lookin' smokin' tonight?
Yes, you did and where
is your wife by the way?
All the way in Nevada.
With the kids.
Parents' house.
Hmm so is that why you're not
wearing your wedding ring?
Nah, the ring didn't
really go with the costume.
Hmm.
Yeah so I have to find
Madison really bad
and get my phone.
Come on, Reggie.
Um, yeah, cell phones suck!
I thought you said he
wasn't all that bad.
He's a bigger jerk now
than when he was 10!
Uh, you just have to
catch him on the right day
and, believe me, that
macho attitude of his
is definitely compensating
for something.
I don't even want to
know how you know that.
No, you probably don't!
(laughing)
(upbeat rock music)
Arrgh!
As long as he has a big fat...
Yeah.
Sausages are great!
I wanna bite it!
Ooh!
Who is this hot ma ma ma?
Hey, Erica!
Hey, you know Reggie, right?
Hey, hey.
(giggling)
Girl!
Whoa!
(crowd roaring)
Girl, you look so hot right now!
Get a picture of us!
(camera click sounds)
Hi! (laughing)
And to think that you are
the wife of a Preacher's Son.
Correction.
Engaged.
But I do not want to think
about that right now.
I am so tired of being
the old Church lady.
Tonight I let loose.
Ohh!
(laughing)
Drink another beer!
Drink, drink!
Is he really Big Dick McGee.
(giggling)
Bring that big dick over here.
Oh, I love that Big Dick McGee!
Well!
Hey, hey, hey!
Hey, Rick.
The party has just arrived!
What is up, Tiff?!
(laughs) Nothing.
Hey, you know Reggie!
Holy, Re, what?
Our Reggie Reggie?
Dude!
Shit, it's been like 20 years!
God, dude!
What's up man?
Wow!
And Tiff, I am sorry Tiff,
you are just looking absolutely
stunning in that, girl.
(laughing)
- Looking fabulous!
- Hey, Rick!
Like my costume?
Oh!
Well, yes, I do Erica.
You look good.
Hmm.
You look real good.
(giggling)
You always look good!
But tonight you look
downright yummy!
(laughing)
I'm sure that's just that
beer right there talking, huh?
If it wasn't that one,
it might have been the six
I had before it though.
(laughing)
Hey!
Rick, Reggie.
Remember, Rick.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I was just talking to him.
Dude, seriously, man, how
the hell you been, bro?
Uh, good I suppose, how are you?
Aw, shit, man.
I'm cool, cool, man, I'm cool.
I'm still stuck here
in Fall Creek Valley
but other than that I
can't complain, you know.
Ugh, I hate to interrupt
this little love fest
but has anybody seen Madison?
Nope, she probably
bailed out on us.
She is not fun since
she left Robbie.
Yeah, whatever.
Tonight we have bait!
(laughing)
(spilling sounds)
Erica!
Snap, it's all right!
(laughs) We might
have to just go ahead
and get you another drink.
(laughing)
I mean, I know of a special
little cocktail recipe
that I know you'll enjoy!
Oh!
(laughing)
I want to catch up with Reggie.
See what life has handed to him.
See if it's been any
better than the rest of us
who stayed back in Fall
Creek Valley to rot.
Who's rotting girl?
You just got engaged.
Shh!
Tonight I am a single lady!
(laughing)
Tomorrow when I wake up,
I'll go back to being the
soon to be Wife of a Preacher.
(laughs) Well
then, on that note,
how about we go
get you that drink?
And we'll catch up with Reg
and Tiff in a little bit?
Come on, I know where Will
hides the good tequila.
I wanna dance!
(laughs) You know what?
I better go get that girl.
Something tells me that
someone is gonna have to
help hold her hair
back later on tonight.
So, dude, seriously, it was
great seeing you again, man.
We'll catch up later, alright?
Tiff!
(giggling)
Oh my gosh, she is such
a hot mess right now!
Hey, are you okay, Reggie?
I'm just...
I'm just a little anxious.
I just keep seeing these
people that I haven't seen
since I left.
(sighs)
Hey, I know just what you need.
Come on!
Come with me.
So okay, so then the dog
said, fur not furbie!
(laughing)
(spooky music box music)
I happen to know
of a secret stash
that William keeps out here.
And I think it will
be just the thing
to calm those nerves of yours.
Oh, let's see, here it is.
Here.
I thought you were
desperate to find Maddie.
I am, I am, I just
I need something
to calm my nerves real quick.
Wow, you really are nervous
about meeting Oswald, huh?
Yeah, I actually really
like him, Reggie.
What do you really
know about this guy?
(sighs) I know you
don't take it seriously
'cause we met online
and everything
but we've really talked a lot.
We've really kind of connected
and shown each other our souls.
By souls do you mean genitals?
- (coughing)
- (laughing)
Oh my God, Reggie!
I'm trying to have a
moment with you here.
(laughing)
Do you want to walk down
to Madison's with me?
Is it cool if I
just hang out here?
I just, I don't know,
I just need some alone time.
It's cool.
Well, I will be back with
Madison so don't go anywhere.
I'll be right here.
(night sounds)
(snapping of lighter)
(ghostly whispering)
(background house music)
(scary music)
(cb radio) This is
Sheriff Leavitt.
We got an abandoned
vehicle at Borden Pass.
A gold Impala.
California plates.
Alpha Romeo One
Two Zero Charlie.
(spooky music)
(cb radio) That gold
Impala is registered
under the name of
Reggie Griffin.
(mysterious music)
(knocking)
(tense music)
(doorknob jangling)
(knocking)
Come on, Madison, I
know you're in there!
I really need to get my phone!
(sighing)
(door creaking open)
Madison?
Maddy, I think I left
my phone over here.
(slow tense music)
Ugh!
Oswald's probably been
calling me nonstop.
(intense music)
Come on, Madison, you promised
you'd go to Will's party!
- (door slamming)
- Huh?!
(light musicbox music)
(camera sound)
(breathing quickly)
Okay ha-ha, Madison!
This isn't funny anymore.
(squeaky violin music)
(loud booming)
(screaming)
(night sounds)
(lighter clicking)
(laughing)
I didn't spill a drop!
(giggling)
Where are we going?
- Hey, guys!
- (laughing)
(sexy music)
(giggling)
(bottles falling)
(light whispering)
Did you hear that?
I didn't hear anything.
I must be hearing things.
I thought I heard a kid.
(kissing and heavy breathing)
All your focus right now.
(kissing)
Needs to be right here on me.
(giggling)
(sexy music)
In the love shack!
Are you trying to seduce me?
Hmm.
(kissing and heavy breathing)
(wind blowing)
Did you hear that?
I think someone's out there.
You know what?
Just fuck me.
Oh!
Can't you just...
Can't you just go scope it out?
I'm serious.
I just, I won't be comfortable
if I know someone's right there.
Come on, you know my situation.
Can you just (sighs).
Can you just please,
please try, please?
Alright.
- Alright.
- Come on.
You'll still be ready
when I get back?
I guess I'll have to
keep myself warm won't I?
(laughing)
Don't be too long.
I won't be.
Sexy.
- (sharp ominous music)
- Hello?
(wind blowing)
Hello?
Somebody there?
(ghostly giggling)
Rick?
Hello?
(haunting giggles)
(scary music)
(stabbing sound)
Ugh!
(intense music)
Huh!
(screaming)
- (loud smacking)
- (body thudding)
The fuck was that?
Holy shit, you're bleeding!
No shit!
I think it's...
I think...
I think it's him.
I think it's him!
Him, who?!
He's getting up!
(intense music)
(screaming)
(clears throat)
Hey, man.
Hey.
Can I borrow your lighter?
Hey!
The fuck you guys
doin' out here?
Not smoking marijuana, are you?
(laughs) I'm just kiddin', man!
Ha!
Actually this is a safe spot.
You know, I have a
hidden stash out here.
I kinda, you know, get away
from the ole ball and chain.
Get my smoke on.
Hey, let me hit that.
Suck on this little
testicle you got for a pipe.
You alright, man?
Hey!
I just got a headache.
That's all.
Try some of this, it'll
make you feel better.
I'm good.
Oh, you're okay.
You're not seeing what
I am seeing, dumb ass.
Anyway, actually
I appreciate it,
I have to go take a piss.
See you asswipes on
the flip side, huh?
I'm really nervous.
I'm meeting a lady
friend here tonight.
A chick I met online.
What did you say your name was?
I didn't.
Oswald.
(chuckling)
Reggie.
(laughing)
Yeah, don't worry, I'm sure
you'll hear from her soon.
(laughing)
Reggie, huh?
Mm-hmm.
That is a name you
don't hear everyday.
You wouldn't happen to be
Tiffany's cousin Reggie would you?
Mm-hmm.
Shit, man!
That's who I'm here to meet!
(chuckling)
Ya don't say?
(laughing)
Yeah, Tiff Tiff
will be here soon.
Oh, man, what a small world.
You know, I was hopin'
I would get to meet
you sooner or later.
I have been doing some research
and trying to get
in touch with you.
And then it turns out
you are the cousin
of the girl I am
chatting with online.
It is great to finally meet you!
Why would you want to meet me?
I do an internet show
and wanted to do a couple
segments about you.
I just think you are
an interesting cat
and I want to know more
about you, Reggie Griffin.
You know, actually,
(clears throat)
I think I need to go inside.
I think I need to take a piss.
Uh, yeah, yeah, man.
Hey, hey, maybe we
should re-up on brews!
You know, you can tell me
about yourself you know?
Like hobbies?
Favorite foods?
What your childhood was like?
You know what?
I don't think Tiffany is
gonna be coming by tonight.
I think she said
she's gonna be sick.
What?
Dude!
(house music)
Fuck!
What's up with the line, I
gotta piss like a racehorse!
Really, Will?
You throw a party and you
only have one working toilet?
Okay, first of all,
the contractors told me
that the remodeling would
be done like two weeks ago.
And I paid those
fucktards the money
and now I haven't
seen them since!
Second of all, there's
a big gaping hole
in the bathroom upstairs.
Ooh, boo-hoo, sob story.
It still sucks though.
Slutty Bumble Bee
has been in there
for what seems like an eternity!
Tell that bitch ass to hurry up
and get out of there!
Sometimes you just gotta
put them in their place!
They're called women, Will.
(chuckles)
We aren't just one of your bros.
You can't talk like
that in front of a lady.
Mmm-mmm.
(giggling)
Okay, first of all,
I don't consider you
two tuna cans ladies.
Second of all don't
you, you know,
go fishing on each other?
We're gay, yes,
but we're still
considered women.
Right.
(chuckling)
Lezbo Liz.
Lez lesbian Liz.
Liz Lizbo and her muff-diving
sidekick, Dykey Deli.
Thank you, thank you
for reminding me
why I prefer women.
(giggling)
I really have to pee!
I'm tempted to go
water those rosebushes
- outside your house.
- (laughing)
You are not pissing in my yard.
Why not?
All the guys have been.
What?
Who the fuck did that?
You know what, I'm
gonna handle this.
Oh!
(knocking)
- Hey!
- (giggling)
Why don't you snap that
turd off and get outta here?
Huh?
There are people like
getting angry out here
trying to get in there!
Will!
Do you always have to
be such a douchebag?!
(chuckles)
Douche your bag.
Uh!
What?!
My house my rules.
I don't wait for nobody.
Fuck you, Will!
Hey!
(knocking)
Knock it off out there!
You're going to scare
the piss back in!
(scary music)
You're such a
fuckin' jerk, Will.
I'm going to go piss in the
middle of your front lawn!
Yeah I dare ya, Lizbo.
I hope when you're
crouching out there
a lesbian bug flies
up your cooch!
(chuckling)
You two will be
very happy together!
- (laughing)
- Eat shit, Will!
I'm gonna go in your bedroom
and piss on your
pillows instead!
Oh, yeah, try it, rugmuncher.
You don't think I didn't
lock the door to the bedroom?
(chuckling)
(loudly smashing)
Get the fuck out!
(bones crunching)
(toilet flushing)
(upbeat hip hop music)
Hi!
You, don't you
work at the diner?
Yeah, that's right, handsome.
I never did catch your
name this afternoon.
Reggie.
Hey, Liz.
Nice to meet you, Reggie.
Nice meet you.
I'm Deli.
Liz's girlfriend.
Uh, let me guess.
Let me guess.
Ladybug?
Lumberjack!
Whatta dick!
She wasn't wearing a costume!
Oh!
I didn't mean anything by it.
I'm sorry.
Naw, don't worry about it.
She's just PMS-ing.
Makes me wanna go
back to men again.
So, is this still the only
bathroom in the house?
Yeah, I've been
waiting here forever.
Then Will cut in front of me.
Been in there like
10 minutes now.
Knowing him he's doing
hand-to-gland combat
while dreaming of Deli.
He's such a jerk!
(knocking)
Hurry up, Will!
The line has tripled since
you've gone in there!
Will!
(knocking)
- Goddammit!
- (spooky music)
You know, I used to
live in this house.
And the door is a little,
there's a little trick with it.
I could get us in there if
you wanted to get back at him,
we could open...
Hell, yeah!
What are you waiting for?
(jiggling doorknob)
(spooky music)
Wait, Reggie, what is that?
What's what?
I think it's blood.
Whoa!
(banging on door)
Will!
(intense music)
(screaming)
Someone should call the cops.
(intense percussive music)
(phone) 911, what's
your emergency?
I'm at this party.
And someone is dead outside.
(wind blowing)
Huh!
(painful breathing)
- (intense music)
- (loudly screaming)
(scared breathing)
(frightening woosh)
Please, let me go!
I remember you.
You're Bobby Maxwell!
(breathing quickly)
(intense music)
(knocking)
Madison!
Reggie!
(intense music)
(crunching)
(terrifying ghost sounds)
(intense percussion)
(crunching)
(light musicbox music)
(loud crunch)
Argh!
(intense music)
(loud crunch)
(thud)
(heavy breathing)
(ghostly whispering)
(scary music)
(doorknob turning)
Madison.
No!
Maddy!
(intense music)
(gooey crunch)
(doorknob jangling)
(shrill music)
(creaky door opening)
(fast breathing)
(crunching)
(grunting)
(crunch)
(painful grunt)
(intense music)
(fast breathing)
(growling)
(bloody crunch)
(light musicbox music)
(door opening)
(footsteps)
Freeze!
Reggie, you're done!
What happened tonight?
I stabbed him.
He was right there.
Who did you stab?
Bobby Maxwell, he,
he came back and killed Tiffany.
Bobby Maxwell?
I guess the next thing
you are gonna tell us
is that Bobby Maxwell also
killed the man we found
in the trunk of your car.
What?
Don't play innocent, Reggie.
The man's name was Ash Simpson.
You killed him, his
girlfriend Crystal Cochran,
and everybody else tonight.
No.
It was Bobby Maxwell.
(sighing)
He killed Tiffany,
Madison, Erica and Will.
I saw their bodies.
You forgot about Rick?
- (intense music)
- Rick, too?
Cut the crap.
None of this was me.
I didn't hurt
anyone except Bobby.
I stabbed him and
he was right there.
There is no Bobby Maxwell.
Reggie, it was you.
(knocking on door)
Is this some kind of
twisted revenge thing?
Are you still holding a grudge?
No.
You pathetic, pill
poppin' piece of shit!
I always knew you were no good.
But I never ever thought you'd
be capable of any of this.
I'm not.
It was Bobby Maxwell.
It was all Bobby Maxwell.
(knocking on door)
(door creaking open)
(door creaks shut)
What are you doing here?
I'm interested in a case.
We got a situation.
Those voices in your head, huh?
They're not gonna
help you anymore.
You want this to
be over tonight?
Right now?
Tell me the truth.
I'm a Paranormal
Forensic Investigator.
I don't got time for this.
I got cop shit to do.
Every one of us was to blame.
(light musicbox music)
We were ruthless with
the name-calling.
The incessant bullying.
You never fought back.
You stayed to yourself
and tried to hide in
those comic books.
- (intense music)
- (weeping)
We just kept after ya.
You just stayed in
those comic books.
You deserve your revenge
but no one deserved to die.
(weeping)
Not like this.
Get the fuck off my crime scene.
I can't do that.
It's too important.
Just give me a few minutes.
Talk to me.
I think I can help.
Everything that happened tonight
wasn't caused by some little boy
that went missing 20 years ago.
It was you!
You're responsible
for everything.
(weeping)
(door creaks open)
Sheriff.
Can I see you for a minute?
(weeping)
(door creaks open and close)
What is she doing here?
I told her she needs to leave.
But she won't stop with
this ghost story shit.
(haunting music)
(ghostly whispering)
(haunting sounds)
(musicbox music)
(intense music)
(stabbing sound)
(squishy gross sounds)
(groaning)
(coughing)
(squishy gross sounds)
(slimy bloody sounds)
(door creaking open)
What the hell just
happened here tonight?
(static sounds)
This is Glen Rossi with
KVCB Channel Five News
reporting to you live from
Downtown Fall Creek Valley.
We are interrupting
your regular programming
for a brief moment
to report to you this
heartbreaking story.
Perhaps the biggest tragedy
in the history of
Fall Creek Valley.
It is with a heavy
heart to report
that the bodies of eight local
residents have been found
at various locations
around town.
Here to comment is
Sheriff Ryan Leavitt
with more information.
Sheriff, what can you
reveal about these murders?
Well, Glen, at this time,
all of the events
for the past 24 hours
are under investigation.
We have seven
separate crime scenes.
One suspect.
A Reggie Griffin was taken
into custody late last night.
And you believe these murders
could possibly be linked?
Well, we explored the
possibility of a connection
between several of
the murder victims
and the disappearance
of Bobby Maxwell.
I see.
And is the suspect
still in custody?
(clears throat) Unfortunately,
Mr. Griffin died in custody
early this morning.
How did he die so suddenly?
That's under investigation.
So you still have yet to
determine his cause of death?
Glen, an autopsy is pending.
Of course.
So Sheriff, in conclusion,
is there anything
you'd like to say
to the residents of
Fall Creek Valley?
To the citizens of Fall
Creek Valley, remain calm.
We are confident we found
the person responsible
for these horrible crimes.
But remain vigilant.
If you see anything suspicious
call 911 immediately.
In essence, if you see
something, say something.
In memorium of the victims
of this terrible tragedy,
there will be a candlelight
vigil held tonight
at sunset at the Fall Creek
Valley Towne Center Hall.
We will be bringing you
more updates and information
as it becomes available.
This night will
forever live in infamy
as the night of the Fall
Creek Valley Massacre.
(car door closing)
(keys jangling)
(on radio) Waaaooo!
That was an amazing,
mind-altering Halloween night
for the ages!
The ghosts and ghouls
rocked the halls
as the demons and witches
danced with the dead.
Zombies and werewolves feasted
on the flesh of the innocent
and the Harvest Moon
dripped with blood.
20 years of throwing this party.
And without patting myself on
the back too much, my freaks,
I think yours truly
raised the bar yet again.
It was one wild and crazy night.
I got a call that my
twin brother is here.
Reggie Griffin?
Alex?
Alex Griffin?
(light musicbox music)
Your nose is bleeding.
(on radio) Well, my Rockodiles,
don't fear the reaper just yet
'cause even though
tonight's festivities
have reached the end,
there's always next year.
(echoing whispering)
Bloody Bobby!
(electronic rock music)
♪ Can't reach, your reputation,
there's nothing left to do ♪
♪ It's as plain as day
looking right through you ♪
♪ I'm just wasting time ♪
♪ And don't know what to do ♪
♪ Well, it's a lonely night ♪
♪ There's not a lot to say ♪
♪ And the break of
dawn's a lifetime away ♪
♪ Well, I'm wasting time ♪
♪ Should I leave or stay ♪
♪ I sense the darkness coming ♪
♪ Far beyond the light ♪
♪ It was in your eyes ♪
♪ And never wondered why ♪
♪ I been wasting time ♪
♪ And baby that's a crime ♪
♪ Crime ♪
♪ I'm just wasting time ♪
♪ And baby that's a crime ♪
♪ I had a premonition ♪
♪ All about this night ♪
♪ There was a funny feeling ♪
♪ That things just
weren't right ♪
♪ I've been wasting time ♪
♪ It's time to say goodbye ♪
♪ Yeah, I've been wasting time ♪
(soft electronic music)
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull