[WATER RUNNING]
[MOANING]
[GASPS]
[GRUNTING]
BABY, IT'S OKAY,
YOU'RE DREAMING.
[TV CLICKING ON]
[MAN CHATTERING ON TV]
COME ON, SWEETHEART,
WE'VE GOTTA GO.
I'M GONNA MISS MY FLIGHT.
OKAY. YOU SEEM TENSE.
YOU DIDN'T HAVE
THAT DREAM AGAIN, DID YOU?
NO.
I'M JUST ANXIOUS
ABOUT THE MEETING.
I'VE GOTTA
MAKE THIS GUY TALK,
OR ELSE MY STORY SUCKS,
GRIFF WILL NEVER BUY IT,
AND THERE GOES MY INTERNSHIP.
JUST BE FIRM.
DON'T LET HIM INTIMIDATE YOU.
IT'S EASIER SAID THAN DONE.
THE GUY'S TOUGH.
YOU KNOW INTIMIDATION
IS NOT EXACTLY MY STRONG SUIT.
HEY, YOU'RE SMART, KIDDO.
I KNOW YOU CAN DO IT.
COME ON.
ALL RIGHT.
[FEMALE ANNOUNCER]
THE WHITE ZONE IS
FOR IMMEDIATE LOADING...
ALL RIGHT, REMEMBER,
NERVES OF STEEL.
I'LL TRY.
DON'T TRY, JUST DO IT.
BE A GOOD GIRL, HONEY.
I'M ALWAYS GOOD.
[MOUTHING WORDS]
[FEMALE ANNOUNCER]
THE WHITE ZONE IS
FOR IMMEDIATE LOADING
AND UNLOADING
OF PASSENGERS ONLY.
NO PARKING.
[BLOWING WHISTLE]
I'M GOING, I'M GOING.
[PASSENGERS CHATTERING]
[WOMAN OVER P.A.]
WE'RE PROCEEDING
TO TAXI ONTO THE RUNWAY.
AT THIS TIME WE ASK
TO YOU FASTEN YOUR SEATBELTS
AND PREPARE FOR TAKEOFF.
[SIGHS]
HI.
HELLO. HOW ARE YOU?
OH, I'M FINE.
LOOKS LIKE IT'S
GONNA BE A SHORT FLIGHT.
NOT SHORT ENOUGH
AS FAR AS I'M CONCERNED.
THEY NEVER GIVE US
ENOUGH LEG SPACE.
[CHUCKLES]
YOU'RE RIGHT ABOUT THAT.
[WOMAN]
SO, WHAT BRINGS YOU
TO SAN FRANCISCO?
A STORY ON A CITY BIG-WIG
WHO'S BEEN IMPLICATED
IN A HUGE SEX SCANDAL.
HOW EXCITING.
WHO DO YOU WRITE FOR?
WE@R
MAGAZINE.
GREAT ARTICLES.
YOU LIVE IN L.A.?
YEAH. DO YOU?
I NOW SPEND MOST
OF MY TIME UP NORTH.
WE HAVE A HOME
IN NAPA VALLEY.
MMM.
I LOVE THE WEATHER.
I HAVE SPACE TO THINK,
RIDE MY HORSES.
IT'S SO HARD
TO FOCUS IN L.A.
MY HUSBAND, THOUGH, HE PREFERS
THE HOUSE BY THE BEACH.
GOD, IT MUST BE BEAUTIFUL
UP THERE RIGHT NOW.
STORYBOOK GREEN, RIGHT?
I WENT TO CATHOLIC
BOARDING SCHOOL UP THERE.
NOTHING BUT GREEN PASTURES
AND COWS.
OH, WE REPLACED THE MILK
WITH THE WINE, DARLING,
A LONG TIME AGO.
HOW FUNNY. I WENT TO CATHOLIC
BOARDING SCHOOL MYSELF.
YOU DIDN'T.
YOU KNOW, MY HUSBAND
ALWAYS TEASES ME.
HE SAYS THAT THAT'S WHY
I'M SO SCREWED UP--
FOUR YEARS WITHOUT BOYS.
MY HUSBAND WOULD AGREE.
AND YOU KNOW WHAT?
THEY'RE PROBABLY RIGHT.
PROBABLY RIGHT.
[ELIZABETH]
YOUR ELECTRONIC PARKING CARD
SHOWS YOU DIDN'T
CHECK OUT OF THE GARAGE
UNTIL MIDNIGHT THAT NIGHT.
[MAN]
SOMETIMES I WORK LATE.
[ELIZABETH] CAN YOU TELL ME
WHY BEVERLY WAS AT YOUR OFFICE
THE NIGHT OF THE RAPE?
SHE WASN'T AT MY OFFICE.
I SAW HER WAITING
AT THE BUS STOP
OUT OF MY WINDOW.
THAT WAS NEVER
IN THE POLICE REPORT.
THERE WAS NEVER A BUS SCHEDULED
FOR THAT LINE, THAT NIGHT.
HOW COULD SHE HAVE BEEN
WAITING FOR A BUS THAT
WAS NEVER SCHEDULED?
I'M GONNA TRY TO SAY THIS
IN A NICE WAY
ABOUT SOMETHING THAT
COULD GET EXTREMELY UGLY.
IT WOULD BE VERY WISE
OF YOU NOT TO PROCEED
WITH YOUR INQUIRIES.
GOOD, WE AGREE.
THERE IS NO STORY.
YOU'LL EXCUSE ME,
MISS BARTON.
[SIGHS]
TAXI!
I HAVE A RESERVATION
FOR MRS. BARTON, PLEASE.
ELIZABETH?
OH, MY GOD,
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
MY FLIGHT WAS CANCELLED--
THE FOG.
MINE TOO. ISN'T THIS CRAZY?
BOB, THIS IS THE WOMAN
I WAS TELLING YOU ABOUT.
WE MET ON THE WAY UP.
PLEASURE.
NICE TO MEET YOU.
JOIN US FOR A NIGHTCAP?
OH, COME ON,
LIVE A LITTLE DANGEROUSLY.
IT'LL BE FUN.
WHY NOT?
EXCUSE ME.
I DIDN'T REALIZE YOUR HUSBAND
WAS JOINING YOU UP HERE.
BOB? OH, HE'S NOT MY HUSBAND.
OH, COME ON, DARLING,
DON'T SAY YOU DIDN'T
FIGURE IT OUT.
WRITERS ALWAYS FIGURE IT OUT.
WOULDN'T YOU SAY, BOB?
YOU'RE INTERESTED
IN CHARACTER, AREN'T YOU?
OH, YEAH. AND I'M
INTERESTED IN DESSERT.
REAL DECADENT
AND SWEET.
[WOMAN LAUGHING]
SO, WHAT ARE YOU GONNA
DO TO ME TONIGHT?
THAT'S KIND OF A STRANGE
QUESTION, 'CAUSE WHEN YOU
SEE IT, YOU WON'T BELIEVE IT.
[LAUGHING]
GOOD NIGHT. I'LL CALL
YOU BACK IN L.A.
OKAY. GOOD NIGHT.
GOOD NIGHT.
[CHUCKLES]
WHY DON'T YOU START
SHOWING ME?
[SOFTLY MOANING]
[TROLLEY BELL RINGING]
[BOB'S VOICE MURMURING]
[BOB, WOMAN SOFTLY MOANING]
[MOANING CONTINUES]
[MOANING]
[MAN] SO WHAT
YOU'RE SAYING IS A YEAR AGO,
WE WOULD HAVE QUALIFIED.
I'M AFRAID WITH THE CHANGE
IN YOUR WIFE'S SALARY,
IT MAKES IT RATHER IMPOSSIBLE
AT THIS TIME.
DUE TO THE CHANGE
IN YOUR WIFE'S SALARY.
YOU CALL WHAT
THEY PAY A SALARY?
HONEY, INTERNS DON'T--
YEAH, BUT CHRIST!
75K A YEAR PLACING EXECUTIVES,
YOU HAD IT MADE.
NEVER HAVING TO LEAVE
THE HOUSE, NEVER HAVING
TO LEAVE YOUR STUDY.
COME ON, HONEY. WE BOTH
KNEW IT WAS GONNA BE TOUGH
IN THE BEGINNING.
RECRUITING MADE ME MISERABLE.
YOU DON'T WANT ME TO BE
MISERABLE, DO YOU?
YEAH, BUT IT'S BEEN
OVER A YEAR NOW.
I MEAN, WHY NOT AT LEAST
TRY ANOTHER PUBLICATION?
WHAT'S SO BIG ABOUT
WE@R
MAGAZINE, ANYWAY?
GRIFFIN. HE'S THE BEST
EDITOR IN TOWN.
THAT'S RIGHT.
YOUR MENTOR, THE ONE
WHO CHANGED YOUR LIFE
ONE COLLEGE AFTERNOON.
THAT MUST HAVE BEEN
ONE HELL OF A LECTURE.
ERIC, STOP IT!
LOOK, I'M PRETTY SURE HE'LL USE
THE PIECE I'M TURNING IN TODAY.
THEN I'LL BE ON STAFF,
AND EVERYTHING'S GONNA BE OKAY.
ALL RIGHT?
COME ON.
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
GIVE ME A KISS.
[MAN]
WHY DO YOU
ALWAYS PRETEND, LAURA,
THAT YOU DON'T HEAR
WHAT I SAY WHEN I KNOW
THAT YOU HEAR WHAT I SAY?
DO YOU WANT ME TO BELIEVE
THAT YOU'RE STUPID,
BECAUSE IF YOU DO,
I WILL.
AND AS FOR YOU,
YOUNG LADY,
THIS HAPPENS
TO BE A BUSINESS,
NOT A HOBBY BETWEEN
GETTING YOUR HAIR DONE
AND HAVING LUNCHES.
YOUR STORY'S LATE.
WHERE IS IT?
IT'S RIGHT HERE.
ELIZABETH, THE FIRST LINE
DOESN'T WORK.
THE STORY DOES.
I HOPE SO, FOR YOUR SAKE.
STAFF MEETING TOMORROW
MORNING, 10 A.M. SHARP.
TRY TO BE THERE.
♪ COME ON IN
♪ I'LL BE THERE IF I CAN
♪ ANY TIME DAY OR NIGHT
♪ I KNOW THAT EVEN IF
♪ I'M MILES FROM HOME
♪ THE BRIDGES BREAK
THE TUNNELS BURN ♪
COME ON, BABY. I'M READY.
♪ THERE'S NOTHING ELSE
THAT'S COMING THROUGH ♪
♪ SAID THERE'S NOTHING
IN THE WORLD THAT SHINES ♪
♪ LIKE YOU
[MAN]
OH, YEAH.
YOU LOOK BEAUTIFUL.
COME HERE.
MMM.
[MOANING]
YOU LIKE THAT? YEAH.
OH, DOES THAT FEEL GOOD?
YEAH.
[MOANING]
[BOTH MOANING]
HOW DID YOU KNOW HE'S
ONE OF MY FAVORITE ACTORS?
I THOUGHT YOU'D LIKE IT.
WHERE DID YOU GET IT?
THE MASK.
IT'S A SECRET.
OH, YOU MEAN LIKE THE SECRET
OF WHO THE REAL BOB IS?
DON'T WORRY, LOVELY.
I'M NOT INTERESTED
IN YOUR CHECKERED PAST.
I JUST WANNA KNOW
WHAT'S WHAT, WHO'S WHO.
PURELY SOCIOLOGICAL.
IF ANYTHING, IT GIVES
A CERTAIN EDGE TO THINGS.
I LIKE AN EDGE.
[MOANING]
NOW, FOR OUR THEME ISSUE
ON SEXUAL IDENTITIES,
JULIA'S GOING TO COVER
THE PIECE ON MARRIED MEN
AND THEIR INFIDELITIES.
BE CAREFUL
WITH YOUR RESEARCH, JULIA.
[ALL LAUGHING]
[GRIFF]
AND, CARL, YOU HAVE A HANDLE
ON THE GAY DATING SERVICE ISSUE?
I'M ALL OVER IT, GRIFF.
I'LL COVER THE DEMOGRAPHICS.
GOOD.
THAT MAKES FOUR FEATURES.
BUT I WANT TO HAVE A FIFTH.
IF I DON'T HAVE AN ACCEPTABLE
IDEA BY NOON TOMORROW,
I BELIEVE THERE MIGHT BE
A LITTLE TROUBLE IN PARADISE.
ELIZABETH, IN MY OFFICE.
YOU'VE GOT A PRETTY GOOD
STORY GOING THERE, BUT YOU
WIMPED OUT. HAVE A SEAT.
I DISAGREE.
I THINK IT WORKS.
BULLSHIT.
IT'S VERY OBVIOUS
THAT YOU BACKED OFF.
ELIZABETH,
YOU SHOULD HAVE DUG IN,
YOU SHOULD HAVE NAILED
THAT LAWYER MAN
RIGHT THERE AT THE END.
YOU SHOULD HAVE
JUST CONFRONTED HIM
AND TAKEN HIM DOWN.
NO GUTS, NO STORY.
THE THING IS--
WHAT IS THE THING?
[WOMAN OVER INTERCOM]
GRIFF, YOUR WIFE'S ON TWO.
I CAN'T TALK
TO HER RIGHT NOW.
WOULD YOU PLEASE TELL HER
I LOVE HER AND I'LL CALL
HER BACK IN A FEW MINUTES?
LET ME TELL YOU
WHAT THE THING ISN'T.
THE THING ISN'T JUNIOR LEAGUE.
THIS IS JOURNALISM.
AND JOURNALISM
IS TELLING THE TRUTH.
IF YOU CAN'T TELL THE TRUTH,
THEN WE DO HAVE A PROBLEM.
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE
TO GET TOUGH, ELIZABETH.
THE THING IS, I JUST--
DON'T TELL ME
WHAT THE THING IS!
WE ALL HAVE OUR DEMONS.
NOW, THE BOTTOM LINE IS,
IF YOU CAN'T CONFRONT
YOUR DEMONS
AND NAIL YOUR ENDINGS,
WELL, THEN MAYBE
YOU JUST DON'T BELONG HERE.
WILL YOU PLEASE EXCUSE ME.
I'D LIKE TO CALL MY WIFE.
[ERIC]
MY SAUCE CAME OUT GREAT.
ANY REACTION TO THE STORY?
NO.
ACTUALLY, YES.
HE SAID HE DIDN'T LIKE IT.
GRIFF?
WELL, WHAT'D HE SAY?
HE TOLD ME
NOT TO GIVE UP MY DAY JOB.
[DISHES BREAKING]
HAPPY NOW?
IT'S NOT THE END
OF THE WORLD, LIZZY.
MAYBE NOT FOR YOU.
[PHONE RINGING]
HELLO?
ELIZABETH? THIS IS ANN.
SAN FRANCISCO LAST WEEK.
YEAH, SURE.
HOW ARE YOU?
GOOD. I JUST CALLED
TO SAY HI.
SEE HOW YOU WERE DOING.
I REALLY ENJOYED
OUR TIME TOGETHER.
SO DID I. IT WAS FUN.
SO, HOW IS EVERYTHING?
GREAT.
HOW'S BOB?
OH, BEHAVING HIMSELF,
THOUGH NOT WITH ME.
ANN, I'VE BEEN REALLY
CURIOUS ABOUT SOMETHING.
I KNOW IT'S NONE OF MY BUSINESS,
SO FEEL FREE TO TELL ME
TO SHUT UP,
BUT I HAVE ASK.
HAVE THERE BEEN
OTHERS LIKE BOB?
GOD, NO.
NEVER?
WHAT DO YOU THINK? I MEAN,
I CAN'T ACTUALLY BELIEVE
I'M DOING
SOMETHING LIKE THIS.
NEVER IN MY WILDEST DREAMS.
I WASN'T LOOKING,
YOU UNDERSTAND.
IT JUST HAPPENED.
IS IT SERIOUS?
I DON'T KNOW.
I'M CONFUSED. YOU KNOW,
I COME FROM A VERY SHELTERED,
PROTECTED BACKGROUND.
OH, GOD, I CAN'T BELIEVE
I'M TELLING YOU ALL THIS.
SHE TRIES TO RESIST,
BUT THE CHEMISTRY'S TOO GOOD.
IT'S LIKE SOME
WEIRD KIND OF FATE,
BUT OF COURSE, SHE'S TORN
WITH THAT NAGGING GUILT.
SHE'S A GOOD GIRL.
AND GOOD GIRLS DON'T
INDULGE IN AFFAIRS.
[MAN]
SHE MARRIED TOO SOON.
SHE DIDN'T SOW ANY WILD OATS.
I KNOW A LOT OF WOMEN
WHO MARRIED NUMBER ONE
AND THEY'RE DOING JUST FINE.
THIS ISN'T ABOUT RIGHT OR WRONG.
IT'S ABOUT HER REACTIONS
TO WHAT'S GOING ON.
THE DRAMA, THE DECEIT,
THE GUILT, THE SELF-LOATHING.
BUT THEN THERE'S
THE RAW PASSION OF THE THRILL,
THE WHOLE, CRUSHING EXPERIENCE.
I THINK THAT'S WHAT
THIS SPECIAL ISSUE IS ABOUT,
SEXUAL DISCOVERY.
THIS IS A WOMAN IN TRANSITION,
COMING OUT OF HER COCOON.
WHAT'S THE SCOOP?
ANATOMY OF AN AFFAIR,
A FIRST TIMER.
THE VIRGIN ADULTERESS.
THAT'S GOOD.
VERY GOOD.
MAYBE EVEN EXCELLENT.
CATHOLIC GIRL GOES ASTRAY,
BUT NOT TOO FAR.
MMM, VERY NICE.
BUT, ELIZABETH,
THE TERRAIN, INFIDELITY,
ADULTEROUS, SEXUAL ACTIVITY,
ISN'T THAT FOREIGN TERRITORY
FOR YOU?
YOU MAY NEED A PASSPORT.
[GROUP LAUGHING]
I THINK I CAN HANDLE IT.
YOU DO?
YES, I DO.
I HOPE SO, FOR YOUR SAKE,
BECAUSE IF YOU DON'T HAVE
A ROUGH DRAFT IN TWO WEEKS,
YOU MAY WANT TO CONSIDER
A NEW SOURCE OF EMPLOYMENT.
PUT THAT CIGARETTE OUT.
LOOK, JUST DO THE BEST YOU CAN
AND DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
OKAY.
I LOVED YOUR PRESENTATION.
YOU WERE SO GREAT.
HOW'D YOU GET
THAT WOMAN TO OPEN UP?
I DON'T KNOW, IT'S WEIRD.
IT'S ALMOST LIKE SHE WANTS TO.
DO YOU BELIEVE IT'S POSSIBLE
TO HAVE AN AFFAIR
AND NOT HAVE IT EFFECT
YOUR MARRIAGE?
I DON'T KNOW.
SHE SEEMS TO THINK SO
AND SHE'S LIVING IT.
GOD, LAURA,
SHE SEEMS SO FREE.
I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
I MEAN, IT'S BAD KARMA.
YOU PUT THAT KIND OF ENERGY
OUT THERE AND IT'S BOUND
TO COME BACK AND HURT YOU.
YOU KNOW, YOU SHOULD CALL
MY PSYCHIC, KALIA.
SHE'S SO IN TUNE.
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
I'M SERIOUS.
I DON'T KNOW.
YOU KNOW, IT SOUNDS
A LITTLE KINKY.
KINKY?
YEAH.
WHY IS IT OKAY FOR
A MAN TO HAVE AN AFFAIR?
AND A WOMAN HAS AN AFFAIR
AND IT'S "KINKY."
WELL, MAYBE I DON'T WANT
YOU GETTING ANY IDEAS.
THIS IS NOT ABOUT ME.
LIZZY, DON'T START
THAT AGAIN.
I TOLD YOU, I HAVEN'T
BEEN WITH ANYBODY ELSE
SINCE WE'VE BEEN MARRIED.
GOD, YOU'RE SO INSECURE.
I WASN'T TALKING ABOUT YOU.
I WAS TALKING ABOUT HER.
YOU KNOW, IT WOULD BE REALLY
NICE IF YOU WERE A LITTLE
SUPPORTIVE FROM TIME TO TIME.
DON'T TASTE IT.
NEEDS GARLIC.
[PHONE RINGING]
THAT'S PROBABLY HER NOW.
HERE, STIR MY SAUCE.
HELLO?
WHY DON'T YOU TELL ME
HOW YOU MET BOB?
THIS IS GREAT, ANN.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
HOW MUCH WE COVERED.
LET'S MEET AT THE BEACH
TOMORROW. I'LL SEE YOU THEN.
OH, GOD, YES,
I WAS SO NERVOUS.
SO, WHERE DID IT
FINALLY HAPPEN?
THE MIRAMAR.
ON SANTA MONICA?
MM-HMM. YES.
WE GOT A ROOM
AT THE HOTEL
AND WE HAD LUNCH SENT UP
WITH CHAMPAGNE.
IT WAS ABSOLUTELY DIVINE.
HE WAS SO SWEET
AND ADORING, AND THE SEX,
IT WAS AMAZINGLY GREAT.
GOD, I DON'T MEAN
TO BE SO BLUNT,
BUT I NEVER
HAD SEX LIKE THAT.
I JUST DIDN'T
KNOW IT EXISTED.
SO IT WAS LIKE,
"YOU MEAN, THERE'S THIS?"
[SIGHS]
YOU KNOW
THE SWEETEST THING?
HMM?
HE SENT A BOUQUET OF ROSES
TO THE HOUSE WITH A CARD
THE NEXT DAY.
THIS IS JUST SO STRANGE.
REMEMBER HOW YOU WERE TELLING ME
ABOUT HOW YOU FIRST MET BOB,
STANDING IN LINE AT THE MOVIES
AND HAVING COFFEE AFTERWARDS,
AND NOW MAKING LOVE FOR
THE FIRST TIME AT THE MIRAMAR
AND GETTING ROSES
AND A NOTE LATER,
IT'S ALMOST EXACTLY LIKE
IT HAPPENED WITH ERIC AND I.
NO. YOU'RE SERIOUS?
YES.
I THINK
IT'S TIME WE HAD
THAT FABULOUS BOTTLE
OF WINE THAT WE BROUGHT.
HERE YOU GO.
EITHER YOU AND I
ARE INCREDIBLY ALIKE
OR THAT'S AN AWFULLY
BIZARRE COINCIDENCE.
CHEERS.
TO COINCIDENCES.
COINCIDENCES.
BETH, I HATE TO SAY THIS,
BUT I'VE DECIDED TO LIKE IT,
SCREWING SOMEONE ELSE
BESIDES MY HUSBAND.
THIS IS JUST
SO HARD TO BELIEVE.
DARLING, LOOK. YOU AND I,
WE'RE THE GOOD GIRLS.
PRIM AND PROPER,
MARRIED THE FIRST MEN
WE SLEPT WITH,
LOVE AND HAPPINESS,
FOREVER AFTER,
BUT THAT WAS THEN,
THIS IS NOW.
AND I'D LIKE TO THINK THAT
I'M A BIT OF A LATE BLOOMER.
[ANN]
AND THAT I HAVE A WHOLE LOT
OF EXPERIENCE AHEAD OF ME.
I CAN DO ABSOLUTELY
ANYTHING WITH HIM.
DO YOU KNOW HOW GREAT
THAT IS, TO BE
LIKE THAT WITH SOMEONE?
WHENEVER YOU WANT,
WHATEVER FANTASY YOU WANT?
[ELIZABETH]
YOU MAKE IT SOUND
SO AMAZING.
ERIC MAKES ME FEEL
LIKE A WOMAN.
[ANN]
THAT'S GOOD.
LIKE A SEXY WOMAN?
[ELIZABETH]
SEXY?
SURE, WHATEVER THAT MEANS.
[ANN]
DO YOU PLAY GAMES?
[ELIZABETH]
OH, WELL, WE USED TO.
ERIC CAN BE PASSIONATE.
I COULD GO HOME
AND DRESS UP AND I KNOW
IT WOULD DRIVE HIM CRAZY.
ERIC CAN TAKE ME IN
HIS ARMS AND MAKE LOVE
TO ME FOR HOURS.
AND I KNOW HE
REALLY APPRECIATES ME.
ERIC AND I ARE SPECIAL.
AND I KNOW I CAN DO
ANYTHING WITH HIM.
I KNOW I CAN
COUNT ON HIM.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
[SIGHS]
WHAT'S GOTTEN INTO YOU?
DO YOU LIKE IT?
LIZZY, I DON'T NEED THAT
TO FIND YOU ATTRACTIVE.
[ELIZABETH]
I TOLD YOU,
I'M PERFECTLY HAPPY
WITH ERIC.
ADMIT IT, YOU'RE CURIOUS.
YOU DON'T EVEN HAVE
YOUR TAPE RECORDER ON.
YOU'RE ASKING ME ALL THIS STUFF
NOW BECAUSE YOU WANT TO KNOW,
NOT PROFESSIONALLY,
PERSONALLY.
I THOUGHT THIS WAS GONNA
BE ABOUT SEX, BUT IT'S NOT.
IT'S ABOUT DISOBEDIENCE
AND EMPOWERMENT.
TO DISOBEY THE RULES
OTHERS MADE US LIVE BY
AND LIVING WITH
WHAT WORKS FOR US, FOR ME.
BUT TELL ME TRUTHFULLY.
YOU DON'T FEEL GUILTY
MAKING LOVE TO BOB?
YOU CAN LIVE WITH YOURSELF.
THERE'S NO DIRTY FEELING?
NO SENSE OF BETRAYAL?
IT'S NOT LIVING WITH MYSELF,
IT'S LIVING FOR MYSELF.
AND AS FOR BETRAYAL,
MY HUSBAND FORGED THAT ONE
A LONG TIME AGO.
HE'S CHOSEN
TO GET DIS-INVOLVED,
SO I GET INVOLVED
ELSEWHERE.
LOOK, HAVING AN AFFAIR
IS HAVING AN AFFAIR.
YOU GO, YOU DO IT AND THEN
YOU GO HOME. EVERYTHING
STAYS EXACTLY THE SAME.
IMAGINE THAT YOU
MET SOMEONE NEW.
HANDSOME AS HELL AND JUST
LOOKING AT HIM MADE YOU HOT.
AND CIRCUMSTANCE MADE IT
SO YOU COULD GO
TO BED TOGETHER.
YES, YOU COULD.
NO ONE WOULD KNOW.
YOU COULD DO IT AND YOUR LIFE
WOULD STAY EXACTLY AS IT IS.
YOU COULD DO IT
AND LOVE EVERY
FUCKING MINUTE OF IT.
I COULDN'T.
I WOULDN'T.
BUT WHAT IF YOU COULD?
[HELICOPTER WHIRRING]
[TOILET FLUSHING]
BOB, I'M HERE.
SORRY, I'M LATE.
[PHONE BEEPING]
[ELIZABETH]
HI, WE'RE NOT HOME.
LEAVE A MESSAGE.
[MACHINE BEEPS]
[ANN] THOUGHT YOU WOULD
GET A KICK OUT OF
EAVESDROPPING ON BOB AND ME.
ALMOST LIKE BEING HERE.
HE'S SO GREAT.
WELL, IF IT ISN'T
MR. MOVIE STAR.
MMM.
HMM.
[ANN] GOOD.
[BOB] YOU LIKE THAT?
DO YOU LIKE THAT?
MMM, YEAH.
[ANN]
OH, BABY.
ELIZABETH?
WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN?
MAN, SHE'S BEEN SNIFFING
ALL DAY FOR YOU.
EVER SINCE YOU GAVE HER
THAT BONE.
I'M GLAD SHE LIKED IT.
[MUTTERING]
[GASPING]
[SCREAMING]
SO, WHERE'S THAT GOOD-LOOKIN'
HUSBAND OF YOURS?
HE'S OUT WITH SOME FRIENDS.
I'M KINDA WORKIN' TONIGHT.
[KNIFE SLICING SKIN]
[GRUNTING]
WELL, I STILL WANT YOU GUYS
TO COME OVER FOR DINNER.
WE'D LOVE TO COME, THANKS.
OKAY, BYE.
I'LL SEE YOU LATER.
[GAGGING]
GET THE TAPE.
[ANN]
THE TAPE.
[SIGHS]
[WHISTLING]
[ELIZABETH]
HER MESSAGE
SOUNDED FRANTIC,
BUT I COULDN'T QUITE
MAKE IT OUT.
I THINK YOUR IMAGINATION'S
GETTING THE BEST OF YOU.
LOOK, I JUST DON'T WANT
TO MISS HER CALL AGAIN.
THERE IS SOMETHING DEFINITELY
OFF WITH THAT ANSWERING MACHINE.
YEAH, BUT STEVE AND MARY
ARE EXPECTING BOTH OF US.
COME ON, HONEY.
COME ON, A NIGHT OUT
WILL DO US GOOD.
RELAX, UNWIND, A LITTLE WINE.
I WANT TO, JUST NOT TONIGHT.
I HAVE TO STAY HERE.
YOU ARE SO SELFISH,
YOU KNOW THAT?
SPENDING YOUR DAYS
IN THERE STAGNATING.
I'M SICK OF THIS WRITING THING,
THIS-THIS FUCKING LITTLE HOBBY!
YOU'RE MY WIFE!
[CAR STARTING]
[CAR DRIVING AWAY]
[ANN]
IT'S SO RAW, SO PRIMAL.
AND MY LOVER WANTS
THE SAME THING I DO--
FULFILLMENT.
YOU SHOULD TRY IT.
DARLING, THE ROMANCE FADES FROM
EVERYONE'S MARRIAGE EVENTUALLY.
[METAL SCRAPING]
DROPPED THE ANSWERING
MACHINE OFF.
THEY SAID IT'D BE
A COUPLE DAYS,
SO I GOT A REPLACEMENT.
I TOOK THE TAPE OUT.
IT'S, UH, ON YOUR DESK.
ANY NEWS ABOUT ANN?
NO.
THERE'S SOMETHING REALLY WRONG
WITH HER NOT CALLING.
THE NUMBER BEING DISCONNECTED.
I CAN JUST FEEL IT.
THE WOMAN CAME TO HER SENSES,
THAT'S WHAT HAPPENED.
I MEAN, WHY SHOULD SHE
EXPOSE HERSELF, HER AFFAIR?
SHE BAILED OUT.
SHE WOULD TELL ME.
WE GOT CLOSE.
PLEASE, YOU JUST MET.
FACE IT, LIZZY,
SHE'S GONE,
SO IS YOUR STORY.
NO!
IT'S NOT OVER!
MAYBE IT'S A DIFFERENT STORY.
MAYBE IT'S A BIGGER STORY.
DON'T YOU GET IT, ERIC?
I REALLY FEEL
LIKE THIS IS GONNA BE
MY BREAKTHROUGH PIECE.
YOU KNOW HOW MANY TIMES
I'VE HEARD THAT PATHETIC LINE?
[CRYING]
LIZZY.
JUST DROP
THIS WHOLE THING, HUH?
COME ON, GIVE US A CHANCE
TO FINISH THE HOUSE,
BUILD A GREAT LIFE TOGETHER.
FUCK YOU.
JESUS CHRIST.
WHY SHOULD I GIVE UP
MY DREAMS LIKE YOU?
JUST LET THEM SIT IN A CORNER
AND GATHER DUST LIKE
YOUR PHOTOGRAPHY EQUIPMENT?
WHY IS THAT OKAY WITH YOU?
IT'S NOT OKAY WITH ME.
THERE'S JUST SO MUCH ABOUT US
THAT IS NOT OKAY.
I KNOW DINNER
WAS CANCELED LAST NIGHT.
WHERE WERE YOU?
JUST HAVING A DRINK.
HAVING A COUPLE DRINKS.
BY MYSELF, ALONE. OKAY?
[MACHINE BEEPS]
[MAN]
ERIC, THIS IS DAVE
AT THE OFFICE.
THE BOSS IS
[TAPE GURGLES] BIGALOW FILE
AND I CAN'T FIND IT.
I KNOW YOU [TAPE GURGLES]
FOR SAFEKEEPING, YOU S.O.B.
HE SEEMS PRETTY ANXIOUS,
SO CALL ME [TAPE GURGLES].
[BEEPS]
HEY, ELIZABETH, IT'S SARAH.
WE HAVE [TAPE GURGLES] CALL
YOU. SO CALL ME WHEN YOU
GET A CHANCE. OKAY.
[BEEPS]
[ANN]
ELIZABETH,
THOUGHT YOU MIGHT GET A KICK
OUT OF EAVESDROPPING
ON [TAPE GURGLES].
ALMOST LIKE BEING HERE.
HE'S SO GREAT.
[TAPE FAST-FORWARDING]
ANY TIME, DARLING.
[BOB]
TELL ME,
WHY [TAPE GURGLES]
[ANN GASPING]
[TAPE FAST-FORWARDING]
[BOB MUTTERING,
TAPE GURGLES]
[ANN SCREAMING]
[BOB]
SO, LIKE, I'M IN THIS,
YOU KNOW, TOTAL FUNK.
THE ACTING IS LIKE,
COMPLETELY BACK-BURNER.
I'M LIKE BILL HOLDEN
IN "SUNSET BOULEVARD," RIGHT?
AND I'M IN NEW YORK,
DOING MY USUAL SATURDAY
NIGHT AT THE PIERRE BAR.
THE NIGHT MAN FLOATS ME
A DOUBLE CUANTRO,
'CAUSE HE KNOWS I LIKE
THE FRENCH STUFF.
IT IMPRESSES THE LADIES
OR WHATEVER.
SAYS HE'S GOT A GUY
FROM L.A.,
WANTS TO MEET ME,
IT'S A HUSH-HUSH THING.
BUT HE SMELLS MONEY, RIGHT?
SO RIGHT AWAY,
I MEAN, YOU KNOW,
I'M INTERESTED.
ANYWAY, LISTEN TO THIS,
BY THE WAY.
"BOB, THE NEWCOMER,
"FROM NEW YORK,
WITH A HAUNTING PRESENCE,
TURNS IN A TRULY
INSPIRING PERFORMANCE."
[LAUGHS]
COOL!
ISN'T THAT SOMETHING?
ANYWAY, SO, I MEET THE DUDE,
WHICH IS WHAT I CALL HIM,
THE DUDE, RIGHT, AND HE
LAYS OUT THE GIG FOR ME.
ALL I GOTTA DO, IS I HAVE
TO INITIATE AN AFFAIR
WITH THIS BROAD, RIGHT?
BUT HE'S GONNA GIVE ME
ALL THE PARTICULARS THAT I NEED
TO LIKE, PROPERLY SEDUCE HER.
NO SHIT!
SERIOUSLY.
I MEAN, HE'S GIVING ME
ALL THE ACCOUTREMENTS.
I'M TALKING A CAR,
UPGRADING THREADS,
EVERYTHING, RIGHT?
SO HE SHOWS ME A PICTURE.
I GOTTA SEE WHAT SHE LOOKS LIKE.
AND SHE LOOKS GOOD.
I MEAN, SHE'S ALMOST A BABE.
IT'S LIKE, I MEAN,
SHE'S A LITTLE BIT
SEDATE LOOKING.
BUT I'M THINKING,
"THIS ISN'T A PROBLEM."
TOTALLY DOABLE, NAILABLE THING.
PLUS, HE GOT YOU
THE LEAD IN THE PLAY, RIGHT?
MM-HMM, YES.
GOD, I LOVE THIS CITY.
COCKROACH TO BUDDING STAR
IN TWO MONTHS.
MM-HMM.
WHAT SORT OF EXTENSION
ARE WE TALKING ABOUT?
MAYBE JUST A WEEK.
YOU'RE IN TROUBLE,
AREN'T YOU?
NO.
THEN LET'S HAVE IT.
I JUST NEED A FEW DAYS
TO VERIFY SOME THINGS
THAT SHE TOLD ME.
DON'T TRY TO BULLSHIT ME.
WHAT'S THE REAL REASON?
I NEED TO NAIL MY ENDING.
THAT'S ALL YOU HAD
TO SAY, ELIZABETH.
I'LL GIVE YOU ONE WEEK
BECAUSE I RESPECT YOUR HONESTY.
ELIZABETH, WHICH ONE OF THESE
WOULD YOU GO WITH?
WHO'S HE?
THAT'S OUR CHOICE.
[ELIZABETH]
SO, WHY DIDN'T YOU TELL ME
YOU WERE AN ACTOR?
UH, WELL, BECAUSE,
WHENEVER YOU SAY THAT,
PEOPLE THINK YOU'RE A FLAKE.
ESPECIALLY IF
YOU'RE NOT FAMOUS.
WHAT'S ON YOUR MIND?
WELL, I WAS INTERVIEWING ANN
FOR THIS STORY I'M DOING
AND NOW SHE'S DISAPPEARED OFF
THE FACE OF THE EARTH.
WHAT DOES THAT HAVE
TO DO WITH ME?
I MEAN, 'CAUSE IF YOU THINK
I CAN HOOK YOU UP WITH HER,
YOU'RE WRONG.
ANYTHING PERSONAL
WOULD REALLY HELP.
NO, SEE, ANN WAS-- SHE WAS
REAL GOOD AT KEEPING HER LIFE
EXTRA-PRIVATE.
SO, ARE YOU SAYING THAT
YOU'RE HAVING A RELATIONSHIP
WITH A WOMAN AND YOU DON'T KNOW
THE FIRST THING ABOUT HER?
HOW IS THAT POSSIBLE?
NO, I'M NOT SAYING
THAT AT ALL. I KNOW PLENTY.
I KNOW ALL KINDS OF THINGS.
I KNOW, LIKE, UH,
WHAT HER FAVORITE FOREPLAY IS.
I KNOW HOW SHE TREMBLES
JUST BEFORE SHE COMES.
I KNOW LOTS OF THINGS
ABOUT HER, PRETTY PRIVATE STUFF,
JUST NOT STUFF
THAT'S RIGHT FOR YOU
OR YOUR LITTLE INTERVIEW.
HOW ABOUT HER HUSBAND?
DID SHE EVER MENTION HIM--
MAYBE WHERE HE WORKS,
WHAT HE DOES FOR A LIVING?
NOPE. WOULDN'T HAVE A CLUE.
I'M SURE SHE TOLD YOU.
REALLY, IT WAS
NO STRINGS ATTACHED.
MAYBE SHE JUST HAD HER FILL
AND THOUGHT ENOUGH'S ENOUGH.
HMM. LAST TIME
I SPOKE TO HER,
SHE TOLD ME THAT SHE WAS
FALLING IN LOVE WITH YOU.
SHE SOUNDED VERY EXCITED.
WHAT?
[LAUGHING]
IT'S BULLSHIT.
OKAY? SHE WAS IN LOVE
WITH HER HUSBAND, NOT ME.
SHE HAD GREAT SEX WITH ME.
IT WASN'T LOVE.
I THINK SHE KNOWS
THE DIFFERENCE.
WELL, SHE'S WRONG.
SHE DIDN'T SOUND WRONG.
ANN CAN SOUND
A LOT OF WAYS, OKAY?
SHE WAS VERY PRACTICED
IN THE ART OF DECEPTION.
I HAVE A FEELING YOU'RE
NOT BAD AT IT YOURSELF.
ONLY WHEN I'M PAID TO BE.
I'M AN ACTOR.
OH.
THAT'S NICE.
THANK YOU.
SHE MADE QUITE A POINT
OF A CATHOLIC BOARDING SCHOOL
THAT SHE WENT TO.
GRADUATE AT THE
TOP OF HER CLASS.
[LAUGHING]
WHAT'S SO FUNNY?
A CATHOLIC BOARDING SCHOOL,
THE TOP OF HER CLASS?
COME ON. NO, NO, NO, NO.
ANN DIDN'T FINISH HIGH SCHOOL.
ARE YOU SURE?
I'M POSITIVE.
[ANSWERING MACHINE
MESSAGE, GARBLED]
[TAPE REWINDING]
WHAT ARE YOU TRYING TO SAY?
I FIGURED IT OUT.
[GASPS]
GOD, YOU SCARED
THE HELL OUT OF ME.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
HOW DID YOU KNOW
WHERE I LIVE?
WASN'T HARD TO FIND.
WHAT DID YOU FIGURE OUT?
SOMETHING ABOUT ANN?
NO.
ABOUT YOU.
SEE, FIRST,
I THOUGHT TO MYSELF,
WHAT IS THIS NICE,
HAPPILY MARRIED WOMAN DOING
WRITING ABOUT
EXTRAMARITAL AFFAIRS?
IT DOESN'T ADD UP.
I GET PAID
TO BE INTERESTED.
I DON'T BUY IT.
THIS ISN'T ABOUT ANN
OR HER AFFAIRS.
THIS IS ABOUT YOU.
PORTRAIT OF THE WRITER
EMERGING FROM DARKNESS.
HMM?
THAT'S RIDICULOUS.
IS IT?
[CLEARS THROAT]
YOU'RE NOT LOOKING FOR ANN.
YOU'RE TRYING
TO FIND YOURSELF.
YOU DON'T KNOW
ANYTHING ABOUT ME.
YEAH? INDULGE ME.
I MEAN, YOU--
YOU HAVE TAKEN GREAT CARE
TO-TO HIDE YOUR LIFE
INSIDE THIS NARROW
LITTLE COMFORT ZONE.
IT IS SO OBVIOUS,
WHAT KIND OF WORLD
YOU'VE CREATED FOR YOURSELF.
YOU ARE NOT THE SUCCESSFUL
WRITER THAT YOU SHOULD BE.
WHY IS THAT?
BECAUSE TRYING
TO PROTECT OURSELVES
DOESN'T WORK-- IT NEVER DOES.
LIFE IS NOT ABOUT
TRYING TO BE SAFE
AND COMFORTABLE.
LIFE IS ABOUT ONE THING--
IT'S ABOUT LIVING.
TO BE TRULY ALIVE,
ISN'T THAT WHAT YOU WANT?
TO FINALLY BE FREE?
I UNDERSTAND THAT.
YOU SEE, I GET IT.
I GET YOU.
AND HE DOESN'T, DOES HE?
YOUR HUSBAND, I MEAN.
OF COURSE HE DOESN'T,
BECAUSE HE IS NOT LIKE US.
HE'S NOT AN ARTIST.
SOMETIMES I GET SO SCARED.
I KNOW YOU DO.
BUT IT'S CALLING YOU,
AND YOU'VE GOT
TO FOLLOW YOUR HEART.
BECAUSE YOU DON'T WANT
TO LIVE WITH REGRETS, DO YOU?
HMM?
NO.
[PHONE RINGING]
[GASPS]
HELLO?
[ERIC] I GOT
THE BIGALOW ACCOUNT!
THAT'S GREAT, HONEY.
CAN YOU GIVE ME
A RIDE TO THE AIRPORT?
SURE. JUST LET ME KNOW
WHERE AND WHEN. OKAY.
ALL RIGHT. I LOVE YOU.
[SIGHS]
[ANN'S VOICE, GARBLED]
[BOB]
ARE YOU READY?
[GARBLED TAPE CONTINUES]
[ANN'S SCREAMS, GARBLED]
SHE SOUNDED REALLY SCARED,
LIKE SOMETHING AWFUL
WAS ABOUT TO HAPPEN.
ELIZABETH, STOP OBSESSING
ABOUT THIS, JUST DROP THE STORY.
I CAN HANDLE IT!
YOU KNOW, I DON'T
GET YOU ANYMORE.
THIS SOUNDS DANGEROUS.
IT'S TIME TO BACK OFF, OKAY?
I CAN'T BACK OFF.
I HAVE TO DO THIS.
I KNOW YOU PROBABLY
WOULDN'T UNDERSTAND. TRY ME.
LIFE IS NOT ABOUT BEING SAFE,
IT'S NOT ABOUT PRETENDING.
IT'S ABOUT SEEING THINGS
FOR WHAT THEY REALLY ARE.
LIKE NOT PRETENDING
WE'RE NOT HAVING PROBLEMS
WITH OUR MARRIAGE,
THAT I DIDN'T FIND
A BOOK IN THE CLOSET
FROM ANOTHER WOMAN,
OBVIOUSLY A RELATIONSHIP
YOU FEEL YOU HAVE
TO HIDE FROM ME.
WHY CAN'T YOU
LET GO OF THE PAST?
WHY CAN'T YOU?
I CAN'T GET INTO THIS
RIGHT NOW. I GOTTA GO.
YOU'VE ALWAYS GOTTA GO!
I'M NOT BACKING OFF, ERIC!
[GRUNTING]
MAN, YOU ARE GOOD.
IF I WERE GRIFF, I WOULD
NOT WANT TO MESS WITH YOU.
[PANTING]
I THINK I FEEL BETTER.
YEAH.
[LAUGHING]
IT'S YOUR TURN NOW. GREAT.
HEY, I'VE BEEN
MEANING TO ASK YOU,
HOW'D THAT SURPRISE GO?
WHAT SURPRISE?
YOU KNOW, ERIC SITTING
NEXT TO YOU ON THE FLIGHT
TO SAN FRANCISCO.
I THOUGHT IT SOUNDED
VERY ROMANTIC.
WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT, LAURIE?
WHAT?
HIS SECRETARY CALLED ME
AND SHE ASKED ME
TO BOOK A SEAT NEXT TO YOU.
ERIC DOESN'T
HAVE A SECRETARY.
HE DOESN'T?
SO, WHO DID
SIT NEXT TO YOU?
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
OKAY, I'M OUT OF HERE.
HERE'S THE NUMBER
OF THE DETECTIVE IN NEW YORK.
I GAVE HIM THE RUNDOWN
AND I TOLD HIM
TO CALL YOU WITH SOME ANSWERS.
PERFECT. THANK YOU,
LAURIE. YOU'RE A LIFESAVER.
I'M SO ON TOP OF IT,
IT'S SCARY.
I'VE GOTTA RUN. CIAO.
YOU HAVE A GOOD ONE.
GOOD NIGHT, LAURIE.
WELL, IT'S NICE
TO SEE YOU HERE.
ONE MIGHT BELIEVE
YOU ARE ACTUALLY A WRITER.
YEAH, LITTLE OLD ME,
OUT IN THE REAL WORLD
LIVING DANGEROUSLY.
WHY THE LONG FACE?
YOU HAVING A LITTLE TROUBLE
WITH THE ARTICLE?
WHY DON'T WE
GO ACROSS THE STREET
AND HAVE OURSELVES A DRINK
AND WE CAN TALK ABOUT IT.
COME ON, GRIFF,
YOU KNOW I DON'T DRINK.
YOU'RE A BIG GIRL, ELIZABETH.
AND I'M A GOOD LISTENER.
COME ON.
WHAT THE HELL.
[ELIZABETH]
SHE'S IN THE SEAT NEXT TO ME,
SHE'S AT THE SAME HOTEL.
MAKES SURE SHE RUNS INTO ME.
JUST TOO MANY COINCIDENCES.
IT'S LIKE SHE'S LYING TO ME
ABOUT EVERYTHING.
YOUR SUBJECT IS BECOMING
A SLIPPERY CHARACTER.
WHEN WAS THE LAST TIME
YOU HEARD FROM HER?
FOUR DAYS AGO.
DO YOU KNOW
WHAT'S REALLY WEIRD?
I CAN'T QUITE EXPLAIN IT,
BUT IT'S LIKE SHE WANTS ME
TO WRITE THIS ARTICLE.
LIKE SHE FOUND ME.
I'D GIVE HER A COUPLE
OF DAYS. DO YOU HAVE
ANY LEADS TO GO ON?
MAYBE.
THERE'S THIS GUY.
HER LOVER?
YES.
BUT HE DOESN'T
SEEM TO KNOW ANYTHING.
GRIFFIN, HOW DO YOU KNOW WHEN
YOUR MATE IS HAVING AN AFFAIR?
I'M SURE THERE ARE SIGNS.
INTIMATE ONES, BUT I
WOULDN'T KNOW ABOUT THAT.
WHY ARE YOU ALWAYS
SO HARD ON ME?
EVER SINCE I CAME HERE,
IT'S LIKE I CAN
DO NOTHING RIGHT.
ELIZABETH, YOU HAVE
THE POTENTIAL TO FLY,
BUT YOU'RE STILL CRAWLING.
AND THERE IS ANOTHER REASON
WHY I HAD
TO KEEP MY DISTANCE.
I KNOW WHY. IT'S BECAUSE
YOU'RE A PROFESSIONAL,
AND I'M NOTHING
BUT A SCANDALOUS FRESHMAN.
BELIEVE ME, I GET IT.
ELIZABETH, EVER SINCE
WE FIRST MET
WHEN I WAS LECTURING
AT COLUMBIA UNIVERSITY
I SAW HOW MUCH ALIKE WE ARE.
I'VE WATCHED YOU BLOSSOM
INTO THIS INCREDIBLY
AMAZING WOMAN.
AND I'VE ALWAYS KNOWN
THAT YOU HAD IT IN YOU
TO BE AN INCREDIBLE JOURNALIST.
YOU THINK I'M GOOD?
YES, I DO.
WHY DIDN'T YOU EVER TELL ME?
WHAT I DIDN'T COUNT ON WAS--
WAS FALLING IN LOVE WITH YOU.
ELIZABETH,
LET ME JUST SAY,
I THINK WE WOULD
BE A GREAT TEAM.
I THINK WE COULD HAVE
AN AMAZING LIFE TOGETHER.
WOULD YOU CARE TO DISCUSS THIS
AT ANOTHER TIME?
[ANN]
HE GIVES ME FLOWERS,
BEAUTIFUL FLOWERS.
WHEN HE KISSES ME,
IT'S ELECTRIC.
AND DID I MENTION TO YOU
THAT HE REALLY KNOWS HOW
TO SATISFY A WOMAN?
[ELIZABETH]
YOU'RE SHAMELESS.
[ANN LAUGHING]
PERHAPS. BUT I'M HAPPY.
YOU DON'T KNOW HAPPINESS
UNTIL YOU'VE HAD
A LOVER LIKE BOB.
[PHONE RINGING]
HELLO?
DO YOU LIKE THEM?
YES. THEY'RE VERY BEAUTIFUL.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
I DIDN'T MEAN
TO UPSET YOU EARLIER.
[SIGHS]
IT'S OKAY, IT'S JUST--
WELL, YOU CAUGHT ME
OFF GUARD.
LISTEN, I THINK I MIGHT
HAVE SOME GOOD NEWS FOR YOU.
I FOUND ANN'S HOTEL RECEIPT.
MAYBE IT'LL HELP.
WHEN CAN I GET IT?
OH, UM, HOW ABOUT
TOMORROW NIGHT?
AFTER MY SHOW.
REALLY?YEAH.
YOU COULD, UH--
YOU COULD COME OVER.
YOU HAVE THE ADDRESS, RIGHT?
IT'S ON THE CARD
WITH THE FLOWERS.
OKAY. I'LL BE THERE.
OKAY. GOOD.
I CAN'T WAIT TO SEE YOU.
WAIT A MINUTE, BOB?
YEAH?
ONE MORE THING.
WHERE WERE YOU
LAST WEDNESDAY?
HMM. I WAS--
[CHUCKLES]
I WAS DOING MY PLAY.
DID YOU SEE ANN
AFTERWARDS?
NO, I WISH I DID.
LET ME SEE.
I CAME HOME,
I FINISHED THIS BIO
I WAS READING ON OLIVIER.
I, UH, MADE A POT OF COFFEE.
MOCHA BEANS. UM--
I SMOKED A CIGAR,
BRUSHED MY TEETH,
HAD A PINT OF GREAT ICE CREAM.
ALL RIGHT,
I GET THE PICTURE.
[LAUGHING]
WAIT, WHAT FLAVOR?
OH, UH, PEANUT-BUTTER SWIRL.
MMM.
I HOPE THIS WAS
PRE-TOOTH BRUSHING.
[LAUGHING]
YOU KNOW, YOU'RE WEIRD.
YEAH. WAIT, I DIDN'T TELL YOU
ABOUT MY WHOLE HAIR PROCESS.
ALL RIGHT, THAT'S ENOUGH.
[LAUGHING]
I'M, UM-- I'M REALLY SORRY
ABOUT EARLIER TODAY.
I'LL SEE YOU TOMORROW.
TOMORROW NIGHT.
[CHUCKLING]
HERE YOU GO.
THANKS.
LET'S GRAB A COFFEE.
CAN WE HAVE A COUPLE
OF ICE COFFEES, PLEASE?
THANK YOU.
NO PROBLEM, HERE YOU GO.
HOW'S THE STORY
COMING ALONG?
GOOD.
AS A MATTER OF FACT,
I HAVE A DATE TONIGHT TO PICK UP
A PIECE OF THE MISSING PUZZLE.
AND WHO HAS THAT PIECE?
FRIEND OF A FRIEND.
DOES THIS FRIEND
PLAY A PART IN THE FANTASY?
YOU COULD SAY THAT.
BUT IT'S JUST
A FANTASY, RIGHT?
LAURIE, I'M JUST DOING MY JOB.
I KNOW. I BELIEVE YOU.
HAVE YOU HEARD
FROM THE DETECTIVE
IN NEW YORK ABOUT BOB?
NOT YET.
HE ALWAYS DELIVERS.
[ELIZABETH]
GOD, I HOPE SO.
[KNOCKING]
COME IN, IT'S OPEN.
HI.
WELCOME TO MY BEAUTIFUL ABODE.
WOW, IT'S GREAT.
THANKS.
CONGRATULATIONS.
I READ YOUR REVIEWS,
THEY'RE REALLY GREAT.
YEAH. YEAH,
LOOKS LIKE I'M, UH,
FINALLY STARTING TO GET
THE RECOGNITION I DESERVE.
"KISS OR KILL."
[LAUGHING]
I LIKE THAT.
ME TOO. SIT DOWN.
MAKE YOURSELF
COMFORTABLE. RELAX.
TAKE YOUR COAT OFF.
THANKS.
I THINK WE SHOULD
HAVE A DRINK.
HERE'S TO BEING ABSOLUTELY
TOTALLY,
100% ALIVE--
TRULY ALIVE.
[LAUGHS]
I HAVE A FEELING
YOU KNOW A LOT ABOUT THAT.
I DO.
OH, MY GOD, I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU HAVE THAT PICTURE.
I HAVE THE SAME
EXACT ONE IN MY HOUSE.
REALLY? I'VE HAD THAT
SINCE HIGH SCHOOL.
ME, TOO.
NO WAY.
WHEN I FIRST SAW IT,
I WAS TRULY AMAZED.
YOU BOX, TOO?
YES, I DO.
SO DO I.
YOU DO?
A LITTLE BIT.
LET ME GET THAT
RECEIPT FOR YOU.
OKAY.
HERE.
THANK YOU.
HERE, HERE, HERE.
TASTE THAT.
I GOTTA GO.
[MOANING]
WHERE YOU GONNA GO?
OH.
[MOANING]
SON OF A BITCH.
WHAT THE HELL--
THINK YOU'RE GONNA NAIL ME?
NO FUCKING WAY.
[SIGHING]
[DOOR OPENING, CLOSING]
SHIT.
[TOILET FLUSHING]
[WHISPERING]
WHERE IS IT?
"JENNIFER."
[MOUTHING]
YOU WANT SOME COFFEE?
YEAH. THANKS.
[SPITTING]
MORNING.
[MACHINE BEEPS]
[ERIC]
HEY, IT'S ME. YOU THERE?
LIZZY?
I MISS YOU.
[BEEPS]
[ERIC]
BABY, WHERE ARE YA?
I HOPE EVERYTHING'S OKAY.
LOOK, THINGS
ARE GOING GREAT UP HERE.
I WANT TO APOLOGIZE.
I'M SORRY. I LOVE YOU.
CALL ME AT THE HOTEL.
[BEEPS]
[GRIFFIN]
WHERE'S MY STORY, ELIZABETH?
YOUR TIME'S UP.
[BEEPS]
[WHISPERS]
WHAT IF I CAN'T DO THIS?
[MAN]
YEAH, THIS IS
DETECTIVE JAMES MARTIN.
I GOT THAT INFORMATION
YOU REQUESTED.
I'M GONNA FAX YOU
THE RAP SHEET ON THIS GUY.
HE'S A SEASONED CRIMINAL WITH
SEVERAL FELONIES ON HIS RECORD.
YOU SHOULD BE REAL CAREFUL
AROUND HIM.
[BEEPS]
[GASPS]
[EXHALES]
ERIC, WHERE ARE YOU?
[CRYING]
WHERE ARE YOU?
[WOMAN]
SAN FRANCISCO HILTON.
ERIC BARTON, PLEASE.
UH, HE CHECKED OUT
THIS MORNING.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN
HE CHECKED OUT?
ARE YOU SURE?
YES, POSITIVE.
YEAH, OKAY. THANK YOU.
HE CHECKED OUT.
ERIC, WHERE ARE YOU
WHEN I NEED YOU?
WHERE THE FUCK ARE YOU?
FUCKING LIES!
[SOBBING]
HI.
HEY.
CAN YOU HELP ME? SURE.
A FRIEND OF MINE MAY HAVE
PURCHASED SOMETHING HERE.
CAN YOU MAKE
ANY SENSE OF THIS?
CAN MAKE OUT A FIRST NAME--
JENNIFER. BUT THAT'S ABOUT IT.
LAST NAME IS TOO SMUDGED.
[SIGHS]
WELL, IS THERE ANY OTHER SOURCE
WHERE IT MIGHT BE?
NOT ON A FIRST-TIME BUYER.
NICE-LOOKING LADY, THOUGH.
GREAT LEGS.
CAN YOU TELL
WHAT SHE BOUGHT?
SONY EIGHT MILLIMETER VIDEO
CAMERA WITH AN AUTOMATIC TIMER.
SHE WANTED THAT.
FOR THE CAMERA?
SURE. SECURITY, SURVEILLANCE,
KINKY STUFF IN THE BEDROOM.
[CHUCKLES]
NO, JUST KIDDING. SHE DIDN'T
SEEM THE TYPE. HE DID.
HE?
YEAH, THE GUY WITH HER.
TALL, DARK,
KIND OF ITALIAN.
PASSING HIMSELF OFF
AS AN ACTOR.
GREAT EXCUSE NOT TO WORK
IF YOU ASK ME.
FUNNY, I JUST CALLED.
HIS ORDER IS READY.
WHAT ORDER?
MADE SOME DUPES FOR HIM,
COPIES OF A VIDEO.
IT WAS A RUSH ORDER, I GUESS.
SOMETHING IMPORTANT.
I'D GET IT FOR YOU,
BUT IT'S NOT HERE.
WE FARMED IT OUT.
HE'S PICKING IT UP
DIRECTLY FROM THE LAB DOWNTOWN.
TELL THEM I SENT YOU.
THANK YOU.
HEY, COME BACK ANY TIME!
I GET YOU A DEAL ON A VIDEO.
[BELL RINGS]
MMM!
YEAH.
[GRIFFIN] HONESTLY, I DON'T
SEE ONE DECENT PHOTOGRAPH
OF THE WHOLE BUNCH.
WELL, I'LL TELL YOU WHAT--
PLEASE, JUST ONE MORE DAY.
I'M ONTO SOMETHING, I SWEAR.
HOLD ON A SECOND.
ELIZABETH, I NEED REAL PROOF.
I'M GETTING IT.
LEAVE IT HERE. I'LL GIVE IT
A READ. MEET ME ACROSS
THE STREET AT 5:30
AND LEAVE
YOUR CELL NUMBER.
NO, NOT YOU.
WELL, HONESTLY, JUST THE THOUGHT
OF LOOKING AT THEM AGAIN
MAKES ME NAUSEOUS.
FORGET ABOUT IT.
I'M PULLING YOU OFF THE PROJECT.
[LINE RINGING]
[MACHINE BEEPS]
GRIFF, ELIZABETH.
I'M ON TO SOMETHING.
335 BRILL. I'M GONNA BE LATE
FOR OUR 5:30, BUT I'LL BE THERE.
GOTTA HAVE THE GUTS
TO KNOW YOUR ENDING, BETH.
OKAY.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[BOB'S VOICE]
SHE WAS AN ABSOLUTE LEGEND.
[BOB LAUGHING]
I THINK THAT THIS
CHANGES EVERYTHING.
NO WAY.
HEY, I FULFILLED MY END
OF THE DEAL, MAN!
YOU CAN'T JUST DECIDE THAT NOW!
I'M NOT GONNA LET YOU DO THIS!
HEY, FUCK YOU, MAN!
WE HAD A DEAL.
THE GIRL IS FINE.
LISTEN, I'M WATCHING
THIS THING RIGHT NOW.
WELL, LISTEN TO ME.
I'VE GOT THE ORIGINAL AND
I'VE GOT THE ONLY COPIES, OKAY?
SO, WHAT'S IT GONNA BE?
LOOK, IF SHE BECOMES
A PROBLEM, I'LL TAKE
CARE OF HER PERSONALLY.
UH, I'M GONNA CALL YOU
RIGHT BACK.
[BOB]
HEY!
ELIZABETH!
WAIT UP!
[SCREAMS]
[PANTING]
[HITTING BUTTONS]
[SCREAMS]
COME ON!
COME ON.
[PANTING]
DAMN! FUCK!
[SCREAMS]
ELIZABETH, GOD,
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
MY STORY JUST GOT BIGGER.
THE WOMAN I'VE BEEN
LOOKING FOR, I THINK SHE'S DEAD.
DEAD? MY GOD,
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
I'LL CHECK IN LATER.
NAILING THE ENDING
OF YOUR STORY DOES NOT MEAN
THE END OF YOU, ELIZABETH.
DO YOU HAVE PROOF?
I'M THIS CLOSE.
MY GOD, CHILD, WHAT HAVE YOU
GOTTEN YOURSELF INTO?
[GRIFFIN]
LIZZY, HONEY, WHERE ARE YOU?
LIZZY?
IS HE AT THE THEATER YET?
HE'S SCHEDULED TO GO ON TONIGHT,
BUT HE ISN'T HERE YET.
DAMN IT, I'VE GOTTA
GET THAT TAPE.
I KNOW THAT'S WHAT
ANN WAS TRYING TO SAY
ON MY ANSWERING MACHINE.
HOW DO YOU KNOW HE HASN'T?
BECAUSE I SNUCK OVER TO HIS
PLACE AND SAW HIM WATCHING IT.
I'VE GOTTA GET IN THERE,
GET IT AND GET OUT.
YOU'RE IN WAY OVER YOUR HEAD.
YOU SHOULD BE CAREFUL.
I KNOW, BUT LIKE GRIFF SAYS,
NO GUTS, NO STORY.
LAURIE, I NEED YOU
TO BUY ME SOME TIME.
IF HE SHOWS UP HERE,
JUST MAKE SURE
HE DOESN'T LEAVE.
BE CAREFUL.
[TRAIN WHISTLE BLOWING]
[DOOR OPENING]
[MAN]
OKAY, THANKS!
SEE YOU LATER.
BOB?
[MAN GASPS]
[GASPING]
THE DUDE.
I'M NOT--
[FOOTSTEPS CLIMBING STAIRS]
[MAN WHISTLING]
[PLASTIC RUSTLING]
[ZIPPER CLOSING]
[BODY BAG DRAGGING
ON FLOOR]
[GASPING]
[CAR DOOR OPENING]
[DOOR CLOSING]
ERIC?
[NO AUDIO]
OH, MY GOD.
[DIALING]
[LINE RINGING]
COME ON, PICK UP.
PICK UP.
GRIFF!
ELIZABETH?
YOU'RE NOT GONNA BELIEVE
WHAT I'VE JUST SEEN.
WHAT'S WRONG?
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
ELIZABETH, WHAT'S WRONG?
ELIZABETH?
[CAR DOOR CLOSING]
WHERE ARE YOU?
OH, SHIT.
HE'S STILL HERE.
ELIZABETH!
HE'S HERE!
WHO?
PICK ME UP AT THE MARKET
ON OCEAN. PLEASE HURRY.
[TRAIN WHISTLE BLOWS]
[ENGINE NOT TURNING OVER]
[ENGINE STARTS]
DRIVE!
[PANTING]
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
YOU'RE NOT GONNA BELIEVE
THIS VIDEO-- WHAT'S ON IT,
WHAT I SAW TONIGHT.
HAVE YOU SPOKEN
TO ANYONE ELSE ABOUT THIS?
NO, I MEAN, I HAVEN'T HAD TIME.
I JUST CAME FROM THERE.
WHERE?
BOB'S.
BOB?
BOB WAS MURDERED
TONIGHT BY--
OH, MY GOD. BY, I THINK,
ERIC, BUT I DON'T KNOW.
IT JUST HAPPENED SO FAST.
MURDERED?
WELL, JUST RELAX, ELIZABETH.
I HAVE TO TAKE YOU SOMEWHERE
WHERE YOU'LL BE SAFE.
[GASPS]
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
MM-HMM.
WHERE ARE WE GOING?
I JUST HAVE TO MAKE
A LITTLE DETOUR.
I HOPE YOU DON'T MIND.
WHERE ARE YOU TAKING ME?
I HAVE A LITTLE SURPRISE
FOR YOU, ELIZABETH.
[CHUCKLES]
DID I EVER TELL YOU
THAT I HATE SURPRISES?
[GASPING]
YOU CAN RUN, BUT YOU
SURELY CANNOT HIDE.
WHAT IS DESTINED
TO BE, SHALL BE.
[GRIFFIN]
PLEASE, MY LOVE.
[ELIZABETH]
WHAT IS IT?
[GRIFFIN]
IT'S FOR YOU.
[ELIZABETH]
I CAN'T.
OH, I THINK YOU CAN.
I THINK WE CAN.
CAN WHAT?
CAN DO WHATEVER WE WANT.
WHATEVER YOU WANT, ELIZABETH.
WE THINK WE KNOW LIFE.
WE THINK WE KNOW PEOPLE,
BUT WE DON'T KNOW ANYTHING.
THE ONLY THING I AM CERTAIN OF
IS MY LOVING YOU.
I NEVER REALIZED I WAS CAPABLE
OF SO MUCH LOVE.
NOR OF DOING WHAT
I HAVE UNFORTUNATELY DONE,
WHICH CIRCUMSTANCES
HAVE FORCED ME TO DO.
ANN WAS AN EXCEPTIONALLY GIFTED
WOMAN AT MAKING PEOPLE BELIEVE
WHAT SHE WANTED
THEM TO BELIEVE.
EVERYONE THOUGHT
SHE WAS SUCH A DEVOTED WIFE.
WIFE?
OH, DON'T WORRY
ABOUT THAT, ELIZABETH.
THE HATE IN OUR MARRIAGE STEMMED
FROM SOMETHING MORE SUBSTANTIAL
THAN MERE INFIDELITY.
SHE WANTED TO DESTROY ME,
DESTROY ALL MY DREAMS,
WHEN SHE REALIZED I WAS
NO LONGER IN LOVE WITH HER.
AND SHE WOULD HAVE
TAKEN EVERYTHING FROM ME.
SHE WAS AS MANIPULATING
AND COLD-BLOODED AS THEY COME.
SHE WAS PEERLESS IN THAT.
BUT LET'S NOT DWELL
ON THE MORBID.
WOULD YOU LIKE
TO HAVE SOME STRAWBERRIES?
PLEASE.
OUR LIFE TOGETHER WILL BE RATHER
EXTRAORDINARY FROM NOW ON.
TOGETHER WE WILL CONQUER
THE LITERARY WORLD.
WE'LL START AT A FIVE-YEAR
CONTRACT WITH THE MAGAZINE
STARTING AT
A SIX-FIGURE LEVEL.
CAR-- YOUR CHOICE OF COURSE.
HOW WOULD YOU LIKE
TO HAVE A HOUSE IN MALIBU
AND A PENTHOUSE IN NEW YORK CITY
AND A TABLE OF YOUR OWN
AT ELAINE'S?
WE'LL GO TO ALL THE BEST PLACES.
YOU AND I WILL TRAVEL
THE WORLD TOGETHER. RIGHT?
ANYTHING YOUR HEART DESIRES,
YOU WILL HAVE.
HAVE YOU FORGOTTEN
THAT I HAVE A HUSBAND?
OH, YES, A HUSBAND THAT
STARTED THIS WHOLE DIRTY THING.
THE HUSBAND THAT CHEATED,
THE HUSBAND THAT LIED,
THE HUSBAND THAT DIDN'T
BELIEVE IN YOUR DREAMS,
JUST CARED ABOUT YOUR
PAYCHECK, DIDN'T GIVE A DAMN
ABOUT YOU AND YOUR LIFE.
YES, YOUR HUSBAND.
I'VE BEEN CONSIDERING THIS.
YOUR PRECIOUS HUSBAND.
HOW WILL YOU EXPLAIN ANN?
APPARENTLY,
ANN AND HER LOVER
ARE ON AN EXTENDED VACATION
IN BARBADOS.
PROBABLY WILL NOT BE RETURNING,
AND THAT OF COURSE
WILL DEVASTATE ME,
BUT I WILL CARRY ON.
WHAT ABOUT BOB?
SOMETIMES A MAN'S CHECKERED PAST
CATCHES UP WITH HIM
WHICH REQUIRES
A HASTY DEPARTURE,
USUALLY TO A FARAWAY,
FOREIGN COUNTRY.
YOU CERTAINLY
HAVE THOUGHT OF EVERYTHING.
YES, I HAVE.
LET'S SAY I'VE EDITED IT DOWN
TO A WORKABLE PIECE.
[LAUGHING]
BUT THE BOTTOM LINE,
ELIZABETH, IS I LOVE YOU.
I KNOW THE LIFESTYLE
THAT YOU WANT.
AND I CAN GIVE YOU
EVERYTHING YOU WANT.
THERE IS, HOWEVER,
ONE THING I MUST INSIST UPON.
WE TAKE CARE OF ERIC.
TAKE CARE OF?
WE'LL DO IT TOGETHER.
THAT WILL SEAL
OUR BOND OF LOVE.
[LOUD KNOCKING]
[GASPING]
[KNOCKING CONTINUES]
I HOPE YOU DON'T MIND,
I'VE INVITED A FRIEND OF YOURS.
ERIC.
THANK YOU
FOR JOINING US. PLEASE.
I'M SURE YOU KNOW
THE YOUNG LADY,
OUR NEW STAFF JOURNALIST.
PLEASE HAVE A SEAT.
SO YOU ACTUALLY MADE
THE BIG TIME? YOU'RE
THE NEW STAFF WRITER?
OH, YES.
ELIZABETH IS DESTINED
FOR BIG THINGS, INDEED.
CONGRATULATIONS, HONEY.
YES. I WAS JUST TELLING
ELIZABETH ABOUT THE APARTMENT.
FASCINATING STORY OF HOW
I CAME ABOUT FINDING THIS PLACE.
I THOUGHT THIS PLACE
WAS ANN'S.
SO DID ANN. LITTLE DID SHE KNOW
SHE WAS SUBLETTING FROM ME.
ERIC, I BELIEVE YOU KNOW
MY WIFE, ANN, DO YOU NOT?
UH, POSSIBLY.
HMM, POSSIBLY.
FUNNY.
I THOUGHT FOR SURE YOU AND
MY WIFE WERE HAVING AN AFFAIR.
[SCOFFS]
ALL RIGHT. LIZZY,
THIS GUY'S OUT OF HIS MIND.
LET'S GET OUT OF HERE.
[GRUNTS]
NOW, DOES THAT HELP
REFRESH YOUR MEMORY?
[COCKS GUN]
ONE OF THOSE LONG,
LINGERING AFTERNOONS
UP THERE IN MY HOTEL
WITH MY WIFE.
OR DO YOU NEED TO SIT DOWN,
COLLECT YOUR THOUGHTS?
PUT YOUR PATHETIC ASS
IN THIS CHAIR.
WHAT IS THIS BULLSHIT?
I DON'T KNOW WHAT THE FUCK
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT!
SEE? HE DOESN'T
KNOW ANYTHING.
HE DOESN'T?
EXHIBIT "A",
ANN'S DIARY.
LET ME READ A FEW PASSAGES.
"AUGUST 19TH,"
JUST SEVERAL MONTHS AGO,
"ERIC MADE SUCH A FUNNY JOKE
TODAY ABOUT THAT NITWIT WIFE
OF HIS, THE WRITER.
"THE JOKE WAS, 'WAS SHE MORE
INEXPERIENCED AT MAKING LOVE
OR WRITING?'
GOD, DID WE LAUGH."
YOU'RE LYING.
I NEVER SAID THAT!
IT'S ALL RIGHT HERE.
NO!
NO! YOU'RE LYING!
HE'S LYING!
IS THIS LYING?
ALL RIGHT.
IT HAPPENED BEFORE
WE MET, I SWEAR.
IS THAT BEING
A DEVOTED HUSBAND, ERIC?
I THINK IT'S DISGUSTING.
MAKING FUN OF YOUR
LOVELY WIFE'S DREAMS.
I KNEW IT.
I KNEW IT ALL ALONG.
ALL RIGHT, I HAD JUST
ABOUT ENOUGH OUT OF YOU,
YOU FUCKING PSYCHO!
[GUNSHOT]
GODDAMN!
[GROANING]
WHAT THE HELL IS WRONG
WITH THIS MAN?
WHY DO PEOPLE NOT BELIEVE
WHEN SOMEONE HAS A GUN
THEY WILL USE IT?
I HAVE YOUR WIFE AND A GUN
AND I WILL USE THE GUN AGAIN.
[GRUNTS]
[GROANING]
YOU OKAY?
[ERIC]
GET THE GUN!
[GUNSHOT]
[MOANS]
HONEY! HONEY, YOU OKAY?
OH, GOD. OH, FUCK.
[SIRENS WAILING]
COME ON.
[ERIC]
IS HE DEAD?
[ELIZABETH]
I'M A WRITER NOW--
A SUCCESSFUL, SINGLE WRITER.
ERIC AND I TRIED
TO WORK IT OUT,
BUT IT WAS OBVIOUS THERE
WAS NOTHING LEFT TO WORK OUT.
OF COURSE,
GRIFF WASN'T DEAD.
[APPLAUSE]
TWO WEEKS AGO,
I HEARD THAT HE'D ESCAPED
FROM THE SANITARIUM.
THEY TOLD ME THAT HE SAID
THAT HE LIVED ONLY FOR ME.
AND IT'S FUNNY BECAUSE
I ALMOST ENVY THAT.
I WISH I FELT
THAT WAY ABOUT SOMEONE.
WHO KNOWS?
MAYBE SOMEDAY, I WILL.
GREAT BOOK.
THANK YOU.
THANKS FOR COMING.
AND YES, I AM
WRITING ANOTHER ONE.
THIS IS EXCITING.
THE TURNOUT IS SO GREAT.
I KNOW.
I'M SO PROUD OF YOU, LIZZY.
I'M GONNA GET YOU
SOME WATER.
OKAY.
CONGRATULATIONS, ELIZABETH.
YOU'VE BEEN ABLE TO SATISFY
A LOT OF PEOPLE'S FANTASY.
HOW'S THAT?
YOU SHOT THE BOSS.
OH.
I'D LOVE TO TAKE YOU TO DINNER.
I'M IN TOWN FOR A COUPLE DAYS.
I DON'T THINK SO.
UM, THIS PRESS TOUR,
IT'S KILLING ME.
BUT THANKS FOR THE OFFER.
RIGHT.
[GIGGLING]
NOW THAT IS
ONE GOOD-LOOKING MAN.
WHY DIDN'T YOU ACCEPT?
LAURIE, I'M NOT INTERESTED
IN ANYTHING CASUAL.
AND EVEN THE MOST
INNOCENT LITTLE AFFAIR
CAN END IN DISASTER.
I SUPPOSE YOU'RE RIGHT.
[GRIFFIN'S VOICE ECHOING]
YOU CAN RUN, BUT YOU
SURELY CANNOT HIDE.
[GASPS]
I'M SORRY.
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
WHAT HAPPENED?
YEAH, I'M FINE, UH--
CAN I SIGN THAT FOR YOU?
YES, PLEASE.
HERE YOU GO.
THANK YOU.
[GRIFFIN'S VOICE ECHOING]
WHAT IS DESTINED TO BE,
SHALL BE.