we knew there were others out there
who felt adamant against increasing
our self-defense military power.
We knew they’d take action against us if we had.
How could we have gauged how they would react?
They are crazy. Their actions aren’t always logical.
They shoot random missiles all
around the world for no reason.
But they haven't declared "war”--
It's Yuichi.
We are in danger because we underestimated them
and now we don’t have a plan to fight back.
So... but...
Should we live in constant fear of them?
I never said fear them.
We must become more cautious with our immigrants--
Are you eating?
No, I’m fine.
Hey!
-screen who’s entered and do
thorough background checks.
Keep tabs on every single foreigner in the country?
Now I know you're insane.
Some may have come in using a fake identity.
What you're suggesting is a surveillance society.
Stop putting words in my mouth.
I'm pointing out flaws in our system
that should be revised--
-people are getting impatient with the media--
Is he home?
-they feel as though they aren't
getting enough information--
Can you help her?
It’s fine, I got it.
Aren’t you two up early for another live show tomorrow?
Better get to bed. You too, mother.
-we never seem to have an answer
for any tragedy or crime--
...Yes, of course.
-they don’t know who to turn their anger towards--
-how do we fight back without stooping to their level?
What will help us get our hostage back?
It must be an unimaginable time for Tetsuya's family...
That's right.
I certainly feel odd about calling him a "hostage."
Why is that?
There's no proof that these abductions are--
Last month on a cold winter day
our youngest brother was taken from us.
When our parents were younger, a series
of abduction cases terrorized Japan.
The abductees were victims of an international conflict
that had nothing to do with their lives.
30 years later, they stole from us yet
another innocent civilian.
This time, a 14-year-old boy.
My brother.
It became clear that the kidnapper abducted Tetsuya
when he released a video confessing to the crime.
It was a form of protest against the Japanese
government and their decision to
strengthen the country’s self-defense
military force.
My parents immediately contacted the police.
They joined the "Association of the Families."
We publicized our loss.
The media picked this up immediately.
Tetsuya was popular.
He always got good grades in school.
He was the star of his soccer team.
People loved him.
It was easy to sympathize for
the loss of such a great kid.
...Or so it seemed.
It only took a handful of people on social media
to plant seeds of doubt in everyone's mind.
People found out that my father is a journalist
known for his radically conservative work.
They began to make accusations.
“Staged Abduction: The Journalist Lied for a Story.”
They toyed with the news,
making up rumors based on what
they read and saw online.
The accusations spread like rapid fire.
"Coincidence or Faux?"
Moreover, people became extra skeptical when they found out
my parents were separated some time ago.
Because it meant we weren't one big happy family,
there were reasons to find us suspicious.
Also...
Sorry.
The public's been hardest on Yuichi.
As if nothing happened
Yuichi suddenly picked up boxing again.
He appeared to be insensitive to the situation,
almost mindlessly aggressive
which made him an easy target for
public harassment.
I see him practice day and night without explanation.
He never talked about his intentions or his
feelings on Tetsuya's disappearance.
Except for a favor from us--
I'm fighting a match next month on the 15th.
Please come.
-They're out!
-Mr. Hiiragi!
-Would you say you communicate well with your family?
-Are you close?
What are some things that weren't said?
Excuse us.
Give us something!
We are being interviewed live on the news today.
We will answer your questions afterwards.
Tell us about you and your wife's separation!
Why were you separated for 16 years ago?
Did Tetsuya know? How did it affect him?
Look.
Heartless... look at him...
He acts like a bystander.
...#BoxingBrother...
I guess he doesn't give a damn, huh?
Wanna stick around for a bit and see what happens?
Could be interesting.
Relax, they’re gone.
Can’t blame them.
I did similar things back in the day.
Might have been worse.
We all just want the truth.
They are expecting us to mess up.
Especially now since the rumors began.
That's why we have to prove
ourselves now. Am I right?
We don’t have time for this kind of crap.
There are more grave things to worry about.
As we have discussed
it will only add fuel to the fire if we fight back with words.
And don't you think I as a journalist
have an obligation to not play into their bullshit?
Listen, just let me do all the talking today.
You just answer whatever they ask you.
Oh sure, because we women sound
hysterical when we’re defensive.
Right?
How old.
How do you plan to explain the boxing?
Good morning.
Hey, did we make any progress since yesterday
towards hiring the new grads?
Um, no...
...okay.
Hey! Aren’t you Yuichi? Yuichi Hiiragi?
You are!
Hey man, why don't you stop and talk to us!
Mr. Hiiragi?
Are you leaving for practice?
What’s up with all the practices?
Aren’t you worried about your brother?
You know the whole world’s
watching you right now on this?
Are you admitting that the rumors are true? Is it all fake?
It feels so much colder all the sudden.
I got you coffee.
I think we still have the blanket
we got last year somewhere.
Should I go get...
Tetsuya had a life we weren't aware of...
...wife and I both work...
...his older siblings live on their own...
...couldn’t keep track of everything...
It's fine, it's fine.
"Boxing Brother"
Kaede.
I want to start off by saying,
you are a great employee.
You’ve got a great reputation in our company
and your work ethic is admirable...
And of course, this...
...what I'm about to do isn't a
reflection on your performance.
It's just... currently...
You must understand, we are
an advertising agency.
We have to uphold a certain appearance.
Your family has been
quite the topic in the media these days...
Although, I understand you can't help it,
for the sake of the company...
Right.
Of course.
I'm sorry, I was also thinking
I should take some time to
think about what more I can
do for my little brother.
I'm terribly sorry if this has inconvenienced
the company in any way...
Of course, of course.
I'm glad you feel that way too.
I'm sure you will get through this.
You just have to keep it up...
Mr. Hiiragi.
It is probably true that there isn't
a single person out there today
who doesn't know about what you're going through.
Many of us deeply sympathize with your situation
and are saddened by this repeated tragedy.
At the same time, however
a lot of us are baffled by a certain rumor
that has spread across the internet.
Today you were invited here to share
with us your side of the story
Are our intentions clear and are we ready to begin?
Yes.
Certainly.
Mr. Hiiragi
in the past 15 years you have built
yourself quite a reputation
as a conservative journalist.
You are well known for your radical
approach to criticizing anyone that
presents opposing opinions to you.
The articles you write actively oppress any
ideas or movements that disagree with the government.
We won’t beat around the bush here.
The rumor says the kidnapping of
your son is a made-up story
to fuel some type of a political revolution in Japan.
Is that true?
That is completely untrue. It is a baseless rumor.
As a journalist, I have always upheld the dignity of truth.
I would never abuse my power of
freedom of speech and expression
by disrespecting the privacy of my subjects.
I have always done what is right
and respectable under the law.
To be accused of using my own son
in a matter of politics is appalling and abusive.
It is abusive to me, to my family
and all of the past victims.
What do you have to say
Mrs. Hiiragi?
I don't blame the people on social media.
I understand that you are curious and
engaged in this issue at hand.
But please realize that your insensitive actions
directly affect the work of
the "Association of the Families" as well.
How can you think that we would use our
14-year-old son in a matter of politics?
Tetsuya is our son.
Not our tool!
Okay.
Moving along.
We may touch upon some sensitive subjects here on out.
We have information that your marriage was
once on the verge of a break
and that some issues have never been resolved.
Also
we've recently conducted interviews
with Tetsuya's classmates
and they revealed to us that
Tetsuya often didn't want to go home.
Instead, he stayed out late, gambling,
smoking or sometimes even drinking.
Do you have anything to say about that?
It is true that my wife and I were
briefly separated in the past
but that was before we had Tetsuya.
It’s got nothing to do with my son.
In our family, my wife and I have always
done what's best for the children.
Sure, things were not perfect,
but we always tried our absolute best.
I can insist we have never had any serious...
...problems...
Yes, it seems like Tetsuya had a life we weren't aware of.
My wife and I both work full time,
and both of his older siblings live on their own.
As I've explained in past interviews
there was no way to keep track of everything he did.
So perhaps he acted out because he was lonely.
That is one possibility.
One that my wife and I would deeply regret if so.
Our following questions are on Tetsuya's siblings.
Your daughter is working
and your eldest son is a University student?
That is correct.
Are you two aware that this other son of yours
has recently become a prime
subject on social media?
Yes.
First of all, exposing my son's name and identity
without his permission in a public ambush
is a violation to his privacy. It is illegal.
He can sue them.
Secondly, my son is an adult. We are no longer
responsible for his actions
or what he does with his own time.
Though Mr. Hiiragi
it seems like just a couple of hours ago
your son was involved in a confrontation of a sort...
Two web journalists who were doing a live coverage
have reported that they were hit by your son.
They recorded a video of him violently
confronting the reporters and that video has gone viral...
Unfortunately, we are unable to stream the video here...
...What video? Let me see.
The video is currently unavailable to us.
It is stated here that your son exclaimed
"if you want to know the truth about Tetsuya,
come to my match on the 15th!"
Then he went on to attack the reporters...
This "match"... we assume that it is about boxing.
Is this what he's been training for these past few weeks?
Mr. Hiiragi? What does this boxing have
to do with Tetsuya's disappearance?
Why does your son act so
provocative towards the public?
Mr. Hiiragi
you insisted your family has a good relationship
but in reality
it appears that you know nothing about them.
Ayyy.
You're still at it!
...It's been a while man.
Dammit, left the lights on again.
C'mon in, take a seat.
I got the video for you.
You've been so serious about it
totally worth going out there.
Still not sure if you'll win, though!
Is this Sanders?
Oh, you recognize him? He's my favorite.
I gotta say though. Sanders is coming to an end too.
He's just not making cash.
Oh yeah?
I guess I haven’t been keeping up.
You have to man.
New rookies come into play every year.
-live interview at Eleven Today News.
Their effort to reconcile misunderstandings
to the general public
ended up revealing a deeper issue
rooted within their familial matters.
A month after Tetsuya's disappearance, assumably--
All in one gulp.
-for his personal gain as a political journalist.
Coming up next.
Tetsuya Hiiragi disappeared last month.
A few days later a video went viral with--
I'm guessing it's pretty rough for you now, huh.
I mean I don't really watch TV, so I don't know.
I guess...
I can't imagine what it must be like
to lose your brother.
Like, actually have no idea though.
Cause I'm an only child.
Alright. This is Mizoguchi today.
I told him I'm a freshman and that I'm a fan.
He let me shoot him no problem.
Look at that.
Isn't it cinematic?!
Here! You see that?
His punches are fast, but it always leaves
his lower left wide open.
There! Again.
He always does that. Even during tournaments.
I have footage of that too if you wanna see.
Yeah.
-and today we have two very special
guests as commentators
a world championship winner--
Why did you turn the light out?!
Come here Kaede.
Look at that.
It's so cinematic.
I don't know if this is what Kaede wants to see.
-announces the two fighters to--
"This journalist is an egotistical fuck."
"NO ONE LIKES YOU DIE LIAR DIE"
"Despicable people. They don't deserve to be on the news."
What are you doing?! Stay away!
Back up! Don’t touch the camera.
You wanna know the truth?
If you wanna know the damn truth...
Are you training to hit innocent people?
To me, it seems like each of us are
trying to find our own answers.
But the more we try
we are only getting further from the solution...
Each day is a struggle
and by the end of the day, it's only
more apparent how powerless I am.
We cling onto the smallest things that
show us any sign of hope.
Usually amounts to nothing.
After days and weeks of it
I face moments in my day where I just
don't want to care anymore...
Tetsuya was stolen from our lives.
It's not our fault. There is no point in blaming myself
or anyone, except for the one who did it.
Is it fair that I have to sacrifice my life
because of what happened?
Can't I live separately from this incident?
Can I forget about Tetsuya...?
Maybe Yuichi realized this before any of us...
But...
"How Can You Accept Peace in Your Heart?"
"It All Begins with a Little Faith in World Peace."
Good morning.
Hi.
I woke up this morning to an email from
the "Association of the Families."
They're folding a thousand origami paper cranes.
I ran to the store to get some myself.
Where will they hang it?
What will this do?
I don't know sweetheart...
But if we make it, the news may pick it up...
...maybe Tetsuya will hear about it too, somewhere.
And?
What happens then?
How can we know what'll happen in the future?
Maybe Tetsuya will be back home by then.
No matter what we say on the news,
it won't make a difference.
We have to keep trying new things
and pray for the best.
Sure.
Things that'll be "effective beyond words."
Dad’s awake right? Yuichi too?
Yeah.
I think Yuichi went for a run.
Oh, that's right...
What?
Tomorrow’s the 15th...
Oh...
Kaede...
Do you know why he's training so hard?
No.
He started boxing in high school, right?
I remember, I didn’t want him getting beat up so much
I told him to keep up with soccer instead.
Not that he listened. By then,
he already didn't talk to me much...
I guess he preferred an independent sport like boxing.
I never actually went to any of his matches.
He barely comes home since he's gone off to college.
I had no idea he was so passionate.
I heard it's only recent he joined the club at his college.
Is that right...?
I guess I don't know anything about my own son.
I don't know any of you.
They made it so obvious to me yesterday on that show...
How pathetic...
What a parent I am.
I can't blame Yuichi if he stopped caring...
You can still play that?
It's muscle memory.
I remember I played this so much I began to hate it.
I'm going out to the office.
I thought you were taking time off?
Circumstances have changed.
Can't get the world to see the truth,
all we can do is show them.
The citizens should face their anger towards the politicians.
I have to show them before the heat wears off--
This is an international issue.
Why don't you spend your time on
something more useful too?
Yuichi!
If you don't care so much why
don't you go back to your apartment?
I bet you’re skipping classes at the university too.
Don’t worry, I’ll be gone after tomorrow.
That video... you are damn
irresponsible. You know that?
Don't you understand your actions impact the family?
Get your head out of your ass.
We better get going.
Ey yo!
Don’t act so tough, kid. You think this shit is easy?
A month ain't gonna do it.
Don’t embarrass yourself.
-And now, perfect mood music for a TGIF night
here you have DCas "I.D.K.W.W.G."--
Poser!
Yo, let's go.
My bad.
Excuse me...
Shit, it's raining.
It's 7 o'clock. Time for your evening news.
After the alleged abduction of the 14-year-old boy,
Japan is on high alert.
The United States maintains a neutral stance--
What are you doing here?
-to this particular foreign affairs issue--
Long time no see.
-announced that they have no intentions of sending
military support or taking any coercive action.
Foreign Minister Nakata of Japan commented as follows:
"There is no proof this case of abduction is
a forcible political action taken against Japan.
We agree the United States is not obligated to support--"
I made you dinner.
Egg rolls, your favorite.
Sorry...
I can't really eat that stuff before my match.
Oh... well shoot.
Sorry.
I should have done more research...
So...
what can you eat?
If it's right before a match,
simple poultry or tomatoes are good...
I should only drink water... and so on.
It’s only a practice match...
can’t even eat normally?
I mean I can
but why should I half-ass it? You know.
I saw the video...
It was so strange. I used to see you every day
and all of a sudden, the only place
I can find you is on the internet.
Sorry I haven't been able to come home.
It’s no problem, really.
But why did you announce your match like that?
Imagine all those people coming to harass you
you won’t be able to concentrate.
No one will show up.
How do you know that?
I know they won't, I mean...
You'll see tomorrow.
No one actually gives a damn about what my family does.
They don't actually care "why" I'm boxing.
They're just picking on whatever they can find.
Irresponsible parents, false abduction
the rumor became gossip.
Now every single bored person online is
pretending to be a detective.
But why would you get into this now?
It makes no sense.
You told me you’re not that close to your family.
But show a little care for your little brother.
It'll improve your image.
Who gives a fuck what society thinks of me?
I’m not the one who disappeared!
...That's why I said...
for Tetsuya...
Do you remember 6 months ago
when a 13-year-old boy was stabbed to death?
We watched it on the news together.
He was a good kid.
Good grades, popular in school, also played soccer.
People loved him.
People were shocked when they found him
dead by the river.
It was even more shocking because the murderer was
a group of teenage delinquents.
Under juvenile law their identities were kept private.
But society didn't accept that.
We saw the face of the boy that was killed.
We saw his smile that made us
even more sad and angry about
this brutal murder.
People wanted retribution for him.
So, someone found their identity
they exposed the kids and their entire family
all of their private information.
and ruined them.
It was such a big deal.
But that was all they did.
Do you have any idea what I'm saying?
It was such a big deal until they figured out who they were.
As soon as they knew, that's it!
We never heard of it again.
It became irrelevant.
What happened to justice? Wasn't it fucked up?
No one actually gives a damn.
The sorrow and the shock people feel about the news?
They fade as life goes on.
Teenagers stabbing a 13-year-old boy
to death becomes old news.
And in their spare time, these people keep an eye out
for the next breaking news to talk about.
I mean of course.
Who cares if someone was cut up into pieces?
Or if a terrorist bombed an entire city somewhere?
It doesn't affect your life, or how society treats you.
These issues exist in a different realm.
It sucks, because the family
affected will probably never forget their pain.
But we can. You can and I can too!
They are left alone to wallow in their own sorrows.
But… so who, then?
Who will continue to sympathize, listen,
understand and care for these victims?
What really saves them?!
What?!
Are you not coming home anymore?
I don't know.
When will this end? How about school?!
Hey...
I see...
You’re a trooper.
I’ll mail you the keys.
...I have to go.
What in the world were you thinking?
How could you write something like that?!
Do you have any idea what you have done?!
All you are doing is breeding hate!
Oh, for Christ's sake.
Don't you see that I can make a real impact
in this country right now?
Will we get Tetsuya back if we swallow our words?
It's time to stand up and make a change
once and for all!
Why do you only think of yourself?
Is your career more important than your family?
Why can't you see I'm not just doing this for my job.
I'm doing this for Tetsuya!
Please stop...
What a load of crap.
You're just using him as an excuse.
Now hold on...
You always wanted to "make an impact."
You haven't had an opportunity like this in years.
Ever since getting laid off from your old publisher
you've been stuck at the crappy B-rated agency...
Piss off. That's got nothing to do with it!
I am using my resources to produce the best
possible outcome from this situation!
You think your provocations help us?!
You're just putting your family in danger.
They might come after you next.
What will you do then?!
What's the point of playing "nice?"
You think that'll bring Tetsuya back?
You think apologizing to the world will help any of us?!
Please stop yelling
both of you...
And how about you?
What have you done?
What have you done for your little brother, huh?
You knew your mother and I were busy with work.
Tetsuya was your responsibility to look after.
You were barely home even in high school.
I'm not saying it's your fault.
But what have you done for him since?!
You're not a fucking child!
Well isn't that convenient.
Now you're the victim because I'm yelling.
You are a monster!
Those vultures aren't wrong.
You are a user. You're just using Tetsuya!
How dare you! Learn your place!
I should’ve divorced you when I had the chance!
Tetsuya wouldn’t have been born!
None of this would have happened!
Don’t come near me! Don’t touch me.
Get away…
GET OUT.
Sweetheart...
Hey... sorry.
Wanna go out tonight? Are you free?
I know it’s late. Sorry. I just...
Please
can we do something fun?
Poor baby...
you’re probably cold... frightened...
I’m so sorry...
If you weren’t born
none of this would have happened...
Tomorrow.
What?
Come tomorrow.
Please.
I’m sorry sweetheart
I don’t think we can come tomorrow.
I'm sorry...
Please be there. All three of you.
Why did you turn the light out?!
Come here Kaede.
Look at that.
It's so cinematic.
I don't know if this is what Kaede wants to see.
-announces the two fighters to the ring.
This is scary.
No it's not, it's exciting...
-altogether his 7th world title match.
His weight is 61.2 kilograms--
-Admitting that the rumors are...
-Have no idea. I'm an only child...
-What are you doing?! Stay away...
-Your actions impact the family...
-Why were you separated for 16 years...
-Get your head out of your ass...
That's why I said...
for Tetsuya.
Sorry...
Wait!
I think... I think I know what you’re trying to do.
We'll be there!
All three of us
together.
Alright, it’s about that time.
Phew, check that confidence.
Well, he was the champion in his high school class.
Truth be told brother
you and him are like mountain and hill.
But listen, he hasn’t trained against you. You know?
’Scuse me, you're on standby.
And?
It's your turn... sir.
Please go on up.
Damn, I lost that one.
It’s only 3 rounds. Don’t let the air press you.
You got this
remember high school?
What?
So apparently, he's famous or something
but doesn't he look like a sissy?
You should just give it to him good.
Fighters in the middle.
This is an unofficial match, the result...
You famous or something?
Ready to be ruined?
Focus on the match.
Make it a fair game.
Touch gloves.
Corner.
Second, out.
Round one.
Jab him! Right... jab!
Get the body...
Get the body! I said...
Yuichi?!
Corner.
He's weak already.
You got him on the next round.
You keep this up, you'll lose in a unanimous decision.
You've got to attack.
He's not tired yet.
Never mind, drink.
Second, out.
Yuichi, attack! Get him!
Round two.
Break it up.
Break.
Get up.
You alright?
I'm good.
Alright?
Ready, fight.
Break!
Break. I said break!
That was a deliberate clinch. That's a warning.
Next time is a strike.
Dude, are you listening?!
Yuichi!
Down! Neutral corner.
Take your stance.
Ready?
Fight!
Back to your corners.
KO Yuichi! KO.
That's all you got left bro!
Are you LISTENING?
Is he okay?
Can you see?
He got it, he got it.
You sure?
Thank you, he's fine.
Alright.
Yuichi, listen to me. You got this.
You good? You got it?
It's the last round. You got this.
Second out, second out!
Give us a second. Give us...
I said give us a second!
Third Round.
Down! Neutral Corner.
Ready, fight.
Yuichi wasn't isolating himself from us.
It wasn't that he didn't care.
He knew he wouldn't be ready in time to win this match.
He knew everyone else would be against him.
He saw through it all, and even then
he took action the way he believed would
show us
and us only.
We only have each other.
This is scary.
It's not, it's exciting.
Yuichi, come join us.
-It's his first World Title Match. If he wins, he would be
the oldest Japanese champion in history.
The referee is Katsumata Takaaki.
The crowd cheers--
-the one in black is the challenger. Blue is Sasai--
-That's his lucky color--