(light music)
(electronic rock music)
- Hello there.
- Hi.
James Caulfield.
Hey, you'll be rooming with Mark Brown.
Good luck.
- I'm James Caulfield, your roommate.
- You a freshman?
- Yeah.
- Great.
- You a number cruncher?
- [Mark] A what?
- An accounting major.
- Look, Caulfield, I'm not
interested in giving you
my life history.
I am interested in graduating.
So why don't you just
shut up so I can study?
- Well excuse me, your holiness.
- Don't mess with me, Caulfield.
I'll kick your ass in five seconds flat.
- Oh really?
And just how are you gonna do that?
Taekwondo.
Tangsudo.
Kenpo.
Hapkido.
Jujitsu.
- Do you jog?
(alarm ringing)
- Caulfield!
What the hell do you think
you're doing setting that alarm?
Damn near took my head off.
- Well you said early, didn't you?
- Oh man.
- Jeez, I guess I'm just
not used to college life.
- That's it, you think
you're some kind of hotshot
kung fu artist, great.
Now's your time to prove it.
Let's go, see what you've got.
- Let's go.
- Ugh!
You wanna get serious?
Hey man, I'm sorry about that.
I didn't mean to hit you that hard.
- Way to go.
Whip that nigger's ass.
- What'd you say?
- I said whip the nigger's ass.
That's what their asses are for.
Right?
- Look jerk, I don't
know what your problem is
so just stay out of my face
or I'll show you whose ass needs whipping.
- Ooh, I'm scared.
- You better be.
- You're new on campus here aren't you?
Well I'll let it go this time.
But I suggest you be very careful
about who your friends are.
This is a dangerous place.
Sometimes people get hurt real bad.
- That's Craig Tanner.
He's the leader of a gang
called the White Tigers.
He's been a local badass for a long time.
They say his parents used to
send him off for treatment
but I think it just made him crazier.
Anyways, if I were you I
wouldn't mess with them.
- Yeah.
This guy needs his ass kicked.
Well excuse me.
- Well I'm late for class.
- Oh, yeah, me too.
Ecosystems?
- It's ecosystems.
- Look, I'm new in town.
Would you like to get together after class
and show me around?
- I'm chairperson for the
Students for Cleaner Environment
and we have a meeting after class.
- Excuse me, young man.
Would you be good enough to find a seat?
Thank you.
Class, I'm hoping that
by the end of this course
you will all come to
realize that the earth
does not belong to man but rather man
belongs to the earth.
(cars zooming)
- Well this is the place.
- So how long have you been teaching here?
- Well, for a few years.
Most of the kids have a
really bad background.
But they're doing okay now.
Only thing is, the owner
sold out last month.
They're tearing it all down to build
some kind of minimall
condo complex or something.
- That's too bad.
- Yeah, just when things
were getting good.
Let's go.
Share a bow.
And up!
Face your bow.
Yes.
Okay, today class I have
a couple announcements.
First, there's a
tournament coming to town.
It's open to all competitors.
Grand champion will
receive 25,000 dollars.
So of course I'll be entering myself.
- Do you think Craig
Tanner's gonna be in it?
- Probably.
Anyway I've saved the best for last.
I'd like to introduce
to you a friend of mine.
His name is James Caulfield.
He's an excellent
fighter and his technique
is very, very good.
Almost as good as mine.
So I want you to pay very close attention,
watch and learn.
James?
- Okay, everybody take a seat.
Okay today we're gonna be
working on kicking combinations.
First we're gonna work
on is low round kick
going to the leg or to the knee.
Recoiling, round kick to the head.
Spin heel kick again to the head.
Place sets!
Again first one comes
in taking out the knee.
Recoiling, coming through,
knocking the hand down,
heel kicking to the head
and coming through ready to
follow up with the hands.
Okay.
Everybody stand up, get a partner.
Ready, begin!
(energetic music)
Well they're a pretty good group.
- Yeah you should have seen
some of them a year ago.
Busted for dope, barely
getting out of gangs alive.
- Well, you've done a good job with them.
- That's why I need that prize money
so I can open up my own
school for kids like these.
You gonna enter?
- Me, I don't know.
I need the money now,
not six months from now.
- Well brother, I may
be able to help you out.
(register clicking)
- Don't forget to leave a tip.
I love this job.
Hi, Kimberly.
Out a little late tonight, aren't we?
- Oh, hi, James.
I didn't know you worked here.
- Yeah, well I just started tonight.
- Teresa, this is James.
James, Teresa.
- Hi.
- We're recruiting people
for our environmental group.
You wanna join?
- Uh, yeah well I'm pretty busy.
I mean I got this job now
and karate after classes.
- Oh I guess it doesn't matter to you
if we pollute our planet to the point
where we obliterate all forms of life
including our own.
- Well, no I mean of course I'm interested
in cleaning up the environment.
I just don't know if I have time to join
your group right now.
- Well probably by the time you do,
we will have completely
destroyed the ozone.
- Don't you think you're
being a little bit, ow!
- New man, no talking, do dish, now.
- Would you excuse me?
Just what in hell do you think
you were doing out there?
I was trying to score.
- You think your life football game?
Wrong, macho man.
- Butt out, buddy, my personal life
is none of your business.
- (laughing) You talk big,
but your mouth stinks.
(buzzing)
- Go James.
They need to order go fast.
- Yes sir.
(crunching)
- Well I'll be, if it isn't the wonderboy.
Our friend, the freshman.
Hey.
Are you still friends
with that jungle monkey?
- What is your problem anyway, Tanner?
- I don't have a problem.
Hey, you guys got a problem?
I didn't think so.
Looks like you're the one
with the problem, pretty boy.
You know you shouldn't get close to--
- I'm warning you, Tanner.
Don't insult my friends.
- And I warned you not to make friends
with porch monkeys.
- [Cook] James?
- All right, tough guy, outside.
- Yeah.
Outside.
(tense music)
(speaking in foreign language)
- You want it, Tanner, let's go.
(bashing)
- Ah, you're good, pretty boy.
But I'm better.
We could use a guy in
the Tigers just like you.
- I wouldn't join your slime
if you were the last people on earth.
- Well as far as you're concerned, I am.
- Why don't you just go
back into whatever hole
you climbed out of?
- I will Jamie, I will.
But think about this.
I'm better.
- I'm down there (mumbling) with a friend,
and he starts a fight with me.
- Really?
- I can't believe it.
First day in the job and
I'm already in a fight.
- I know it was a matter of time
before that guy got it coming.
- You gotta love it.
- See, I have 100 signatures
that I have to get by tomorrow.
- Gotta go, chief.
- They're burning hundreds of acres
of Amazon rainforests every day.
- That must make one big bonfire.
- Do you want to sign the petition
or haven't you got the time?
- Ooh, do I detect a little
hostility in that voice?
Okay, okay, I'll sign.
So where'd you disappear to last night?
- I don't like fights.
- I don't like bigots.
- Well we finally have
something in common.
- Good.
Then maybe we can discuss
it over dinner tonight.
- I don't date jocks.
- Do I look like a jock?
- No.
There's a test coming up in ecosystems.
I could use a study
partner if you're serious.
- Your place or mine?
- Okay.
Here's one.
What plant species dominated
the paleocene period?
- Huh?
- You're not paying attention to me.
- I am paying total attention to you.
- We've been studying for over an hour
and you haven't answered one question.
- Well I'm distracted.
- That's it.
I knew I shouldn't have done this
but I did anyway, that's my fault.
But I don't have to sit here and be ogled.
- I am not ogling.
I'm admiring.
- That's a typical jock remark.
- And what's that supposed to mean?
- That means that you've only
got one thing on your mind
and one organ in your head
and it's not your brain.
- Well maybe if we discuss
something interesting
I would use my brain.
- Like what?
- Like martial arts.
- Huh, right.
A real significant discovery
to the history of mankind.
More ways to annihilate
one another, great.
- Why don't you just go save a whale?
Good night Mr.Chan.
- That's our boy.
This is how we treat
coon lovers in this town.
- Don't move, pretty boy.
- Break the son of a bitch.
Drop him, boys.
(bashing)
(laughing)
Crawl to me, boy.
Crawl to me, pretty boy.
- Go to hell, Tanner.
- Crawl to me.
You know what it feels
like, pretty boy, to crawl
without a hand?
- Hold his hand down, boys.
And never mind.
I'll do it myself.
- Hey!
What do you want, what do you want?!
- Ah shut up.
- Stay out of this, China man.
We just want to see if the
pretty boy here can crawl.
- Oh you want crawl, I crawl.
Go away.
- You crawl or I'll
cut you too, China man.
- Don't, don't do it, Wing.
- Oh, I crawl I crawl, I crawl.
- Crawl man, crawl!
You crawl!
- That's it, China man.
Crawl.
Left, right, left,
right, crawl! (laughing)
(laughing)
- Come on, over here, China man.
Right here, buddy.
- Okay.
I come over there, okay. (laughing)
(men jeering)
(bashing)
(screaming)
- You want to take it?
- Let's get out here!
Come on!
- How did you do that?
- Lucky.
Hey, where heal that?
- You better take me to a hospital.
- You not hurt bad.
- The hell I'm not.
Watch it, watch it, watch it.
(grunting)
- Now, you try walk.
- Where did you learn that?
- Ancient Chinese art.
Learn from comic book.
- Don't give me that comic book crap.
Hey, wait a minute.
I thought you were gonna drive me home.
- Drive yourself.
You're big macho man.
- What the hell happened to you?
- Tanner.
- Tanner?
Tanner did this to you?
He's better than I thought.
- Not just Tanner, he
had other guys with him.
Pipes and chains.
One of them even had a gun.
- And you fought them
all off single handed?
- Wing saved me.
- Wing?
That pudgy Chinese chef?
- He's a master's master, Mark.
- [Mark] In what, Kung fu?
- Kung Fu, Karate, I don't know.
I've never seen anybody move so fast.
I gotta get him to train me.
- You mean us.
- Wait a minute, Mark.
You don't know this guy, he's bizarre.
I don't know if he'll
teach me, let alone you.
- Come on, James.
You're my man.
You've gotta get him to train me.
It's not just for the tournament.
Think of how many kids I
can keep off the streets
with that money.
Come on man, let's get you fixed up.
(door creaking)
- [Mark And James] Master!
- Hey, why you call me that?
I'm not your master.
- But we want you to be, Wing.
- No teach you, macho man.
- Please, we just want to learn.
- No.
- Well if you don't teach
me, at least teach Mark.
He needs to win the tournament money
so he can start a karate school
for underprivileged kids.
- Tournament?
What tournament?
- It's the Melbrook
Martial Arts Tournament.
The winner gets 25,000 dollars.
25 grand.
- No.
Kung Fu for money no good.
- But it's for a good cause.
It's for the kids.
- Doesn't matter.
Money make people crazy, no way.
- Then I won't enter the tournament.
Just teach me.
- Okay.
I teach you both.
- All right, all right.
- Come on.
You pass test first.
You fail, then I no teach you.
- What kind of test?
- You, you, together.
Last one minute, I teach you.
- Here, now?
- You afraid?
(bashing)
So sorry, you lose.
See you tomorrow.
Hey, don't forget to
clean the toilet, huh?
Bye bye.
(car starting)
- There goes the karate school.
- Don't be so sure.
- Your parking not so good.
- No, but I'm damn good
at learning martial arts.
I'm not gonna give up, Wing.
- Kung Fu not game.
Not for money.
Kung Fu is life.
- That's right, it is my life.
It's all I've ever wanted to do.
- You don't understand.
- I do understand.
It's the only thing
that keeps me together.
You were right about me, Wing.
I've been a macho man with my martial arts
trying to impress people.
I guess I'm just trying to
make up for other things.
But there's something different about you.
How can I learn that unless you teach me?
- You wait here for me.
I think tonight.
- Really?
- No promise, just think.
- Great, great.
(speaking in foreign language)
Yes!
(light music)
Did you think about it?
- It?
- What we talked about last night.
- Oh, it.
No, so sorry I forgot.
- What do you mean you forgot?
I waited here all last night
and that's all you're gonna say?
- I say I'm sorry.
- You're a real pain in
the butt, you know that?
- Oh, I understand.
Like fire in wok.
Bye bye.
- Hey James, what's going on, man?
- Not too much.
Man I am getting nowhere with Wing.
- Man, you may as well give it up.
He's not gonna give in.
- No way.
I'm just as stubborn as he is.
- Ah!
- Couldn't resist, could you?
- Well you are the most
conceited pig I ever met.
You really think the whole world
just revolves around you, don't you?
See what that attitude got you?
- It wasn't my fault, I got jumped.
- Yeah, right.
- What's up with you two anyway?
I thought you guys were happening.
- No way.
She has gotta be the biggest
pain I have ever met.
All she talks about is
how she's gonna save
the world from pollution.
And she's got the nerve
to call me a dumb jock.
- Man, have you got a lot to learn.
Patience, my friend.
Especially when it comes to women.
Be patient and the world will come to you.
- Master!
- No.
No decide yet.
- You will.
Take all the time you need.
I have plenty of patience.
(light music)
(car starting)
Master!
- Get in.
- Master, I knew you would say yes.
Yes!
Was it my patience?
- [Wing] Junk.
- [James] Junk?
- Last night you eat two sandwich,
two cokes, three candy bars, three donuts.
They're junk.
Made me sick.
And don't call me master again.
Call me Sifu.
Sifu Wing.
Okay.
Show me your best kick.
(laughing) Like in movies.
Not practical.
- So what am I doing wrong?
- Give me your fearsome kick.
Kick at me, full force.
- Okay, but remember, you asked for it.
(bashing)
- Your waist is weak.
Therefore, your kick has no power.
- So what am I supposed to do?
- Up.
What do you feel?
- I definitely feel the power.
- Your waist is your foundation.
If the foundation is firm,
your kick will be faster
and more powerful.
Now I teach you how to build more power
in your waist.
One.
Two.
One, two.
Yes.
One.
Two.
One, two, one, two, you go.
Good.
You start today.
Meet me here tomorrow, six a.m.
- Pay attention, bookworm.
- What?
- He's doing it.
- Who?
- Wing, he's teaching me.
I just had my first lesson today.
- No way.
- Nelson, I promised him I
wouldn't fight for money.
But it didn't say anything
about teaching you.
- Yeah!
- [Both] Yes, yes, yes!
- Hi.
- Hi, Wing, nice to see you again.
- This place closed?
- Yes.
- How'd you get us in here?
- He's married to Chan's sister.
- So what did you tell Mr.
Chan to get him to do this?
- Tell him, no limping.
- I like that.
Where's the skates?
- No, no this.
- No socks?
My feet will freeze.
- Come on.
- Okay, god.
(grunting)
Agh!
- Attack me.
Look like Bambi.
- It's not funny.
I can't do this, Wing.
- You want it easy?
Movies easy.
This is life.
Slippery, cruel, hard.
Again.
Concentration is very important in life.
Always remember to keep your
balance anytime, anywhere.
Training on ice can
teach you good balance.
Balance good.
You can defend and attack.
Now, let me show you.
(tense music)
- [James] Ayaa!
- Hey, bad man.
- You ready to do it?
First lesson.
What you're gonna do is give me a punch
then a front kick.
- Hey, that was a smooth move, man.
- Get over there, partner.
Okay, okay.
Heel kick, front kick.
Give me two.
- Hey, hey, hey, hey!
- Hi, Sifu!
- Hi James.
All right, jump in and jump out.
- That's easy.
- Hole too big.
Now, you try again.
- Whoah!
I can't even bend my knees in here.
- Take part in hard to do.
Use here, not this.
(grunting)
Good, good.
You try hard.
I come back later.
- Hey, wait a minute.
This is impossible.
Who do you think I am, superman?
- How you do?
- Horrible, I haven't gotten out once.
I can't do this.
I don't understand what
you mean about heart.
It just seems impossible.
- Impossible?
Come up, let me show you.
(tense music)
- Ya!
In Kung Fu, nothing is impossible.
Try again, and again.
- Class, now we come
to the neanderthal man
who is one of our ancient predecessors.
While the neanderthal may not have been
the brightest of fellows,
at least he lived in
harmony with the earth.
(groaning)
- Oh, terribly sorry.
You all right?
- Yeah.
- It's okay.
- He knew the basics of survival
and didn't litter up his landscape
with a lot of toxic waste
or non-biodegradable trash.
Take a good look at this fellow.
We may all end up like him again.
Especially if we don't
clean up the ozone layer.
(laughing)
(fly buzzing)
(spray hissing)
- That's real kung fu.
- I can't believe this.
- Hey, we practice now.
- Here?
- Yeah, come on.
- There's no room.
- Come on.
Kung Fu like life is everywhere.
- I know, you said that before.
Kung Fu is like life.
- Yes.
- Okay, but no kicking.
My legs are still sore from the sand pit.
- Do kick later.
Now we do hands.
Try hit.
- Ouch, that hurts!
- Yeah, good is put pain teacher.
Teach you to be faster.
Do again.
- Ow!
- Where you look?
- I'm looking at your hands.
Where else would I look?
- No, no, no, not hands.
Primitive.
- Look, you are using your hands.
I have to watch your hands.
If you're using your feet,
I would watch your feet.
How else can I know what
you're gonna do next?
- Look shoulder, better than hands.
- All right, I see what you mean.
- Good, locked arm.
Faster!
Now, look at my eyes.
Better than shoulders.
See more in eyes than anywhere.
- All right!
- Table need cleaning.
- I'll do it right now.
- You need detergents.
His hand very soft.
(laughing)
- Oh now what happened?
- Oh it seems your boy
here is a bit of a clutz.
- Be more careful James.
Dishes break, I lose money.
- Yes, Mr.Chan, it won't happen again.
Didn't think you had the
nerve to show up here again.
- And miss dining at one of the city's
most elegant restaurants?
I was just discussing with my friend here
how excellent the food is.
Congratulations, bus boy.
Obviously he's not too good at walking.
Maybe he can't shake hands either.
Come on man, let's get out of here.
- Is that the guy?
- Yeah.
We'll be seeing you Caulfield.
When you don't have the Chinaman's apron
to hide behind.
- Oh, chop too harsh.
Get new pan tomorrow.
- Better, huh?
- Better.
Practice hands.
- Wait a minute.
- (laughing) Good, clever boy.
- Part of Kung Fu, heartless.
- Great, I ran as fast
as you today, didn't I?
Oh man.
- You try it.
- Ankle weights, great.
- [Wing] You run now.
- Run?
I can hardly walk in these.
- Keep running, no more talk.
Do this for next two weeks.
Then we run again.
(tense music)
- He's coming.
- Humor's good.
It is a part of martial arts, thank you.
Today's lesson is gonna be on legs.
(energetic music)
- That was a great lesson, sir.
- All right, take care.
- I will.
- [Girl] Thank you sir.
- Yeah, okay we'll see you guys tomorrow.
And you know the guys really appreciate
what you've been doing for them now.
You know you really should
enter the tournament.
You'll do great.
- I can't, I gotta keep
my promise to Wing.
No fights for money.
- Yeah, I understand.
By the way, Kimberly called again.
- I know, I got the message.
- You want me to tell her to stop calling?
- No.
I mean, I'm just busy working
out with Wing right now.
(tense music)
(crickets chirping)
(men screaming and bashing)
(growling)
(calm music)
- Sifu!
Come here.
Sifu, Sifu, please.
I overslept last night.
- You broke promise.
I no train.
- Please.
It will never happen again.
- Make promise, keep promise.
No excuse.
- I am truly sorry.
- Take it off.
How many days?
- 14 days.
Can we run now?
So what's this for?
- I test you now.
Use kick, break it.
- Focused energy here.
Total concentration.
One more.
- I did it!
I did it, I did it.
- Not finished.
- What do you mean, I thought this was it.
- This is nothing.
Now come the hard part.
Come tomorrow.
(knocking)
Good, here come.
Sit down.
So far, you learn very
well, but there's more.
- More?
- Now I teach you something special.
Remember this.
But you tell no one.
No one!
- Okay.
- Swear.
- I swear.
Okay, I swear, I promise.
- Wait here.
Don't touch!
- I'm sorry Sifu, I was just wondering.
- This from my Sifu.
I teach you something about life.
- Are you serious or is this a joke?
- This is Eric.
- Eric?
And what does Eric do?
- You know acupuncture?
- Acupuncuture, the stuff you used on me
in the alley after the fight?
- Yes.
- What does Eric have to do with that?
- See this?
- That's where you touched
me after the fight.
- See this?
(laughing)
Too much laugh.
- What is all this?
- Too much make love.
- Oh no, you don't.
- Now, attack me.
- I can't attack you, Sifu.
- It's okay, attack.
- All right.
(coughing)
- What do you learn about this?
- Um, I've learned that different parts
of your body control other parts.
And depending on what parts you touch,
acupuncture can be used
to heal you or to kill.
- Yes.
- This is what you used on those guys
in the alley, isn't it?
- Yes.
- But you could have killed them.
Can heal.
Can kill.
- How do I know which one to use?
- When you are hungry,
you will know when to eat.
- So I can use this if
someone's trying to kill me?
- But only when life is
in danger, you swear.
- I swear.
- Promise!
- I promise.
Hi.
- Hi.
You're not working tonight?
I thought you weren't ever
gonna speak to me again.
- Yeah, well I'm really sorry about that.
I was really rude and I can see that now.
- What happened?
- Well I'm doing some
different kind of training
and it really opened my eyes.
- Acupuncture?
Is that part of it?
- Yeah.
That's part of it.
- I didn't know you were
into that kind of thing.
- That's a lot of things
you don't know about me.
- I can see that.
(light music)
- Come get it.
Come get it.
(laughing)
- Turn off these bubbles.
James, you've really changed
in the past few months.
I like you better this way.
I never would have
thought you could get this
from martial arts.
- Yeah well I kind of owe that to Wing.
He's taught me a lot.
- What do you mean?
- Um, well for instance, acupuncture,
you see you have these passive energy
that run through your body.
They're called meridians.
And you have one runs up along here
to here,
up to here.
- And what if I get a pain?
- Let's say you get a pain right here.
That would mean the energy is stuck.
- And what would I have to
do to get the energy unstuck?
- Stimulate it.
Hey, Joey, looking pretty good out there.
How are you doing?
- Sir, I decided to enter the tournament.
I don't care if Tanner's gonna be in it.
- That's great Joey, I'm proud of you.
Actually that's part of the
reason why I'm here today.
I used to think that my
martial arts was a way
to defend myself.
Then I thought it was a
way to prove to everybody
just how tough I was.
I got pretty cocky about it.
Thought I was a real macho man.
And I would deliberately provoke fights
just to prove what a man I was.
Well I was wrong.
Martial arts isn't about
being tough or a wiseass.
It's about being true to your inner self.
So when you go into the
tournament on Saturday,
don't go in there thinking
you're gonna prove
how tough you are.
Go in there to learn
about who you really are.
And no matter what happens,
you'll all be winners.
(clapping)
- Nice speech, James.
Tough words from such a sweet boy.
- What do you want, Tanner?
- I was just checking the fight listings
and your name isn't on it.
- That's right.
- What's the matter, don't they have
a pretty boy division?
Scared your face might get hurt, Jamie?
- I'm in the tournament.
You can be damn sure I'm
gonna kick your ass, Tanner.
- You?
You won't even make it past
the first round, shoeshine.
Ding!
It's too bad old James won't be there.
It's his ass that needs kicking.
- Sorry I can't help you out, Tanner.
I'm gonna sit this one out.
- Oh Caulfield, I get
extremely mad sometimes.
Fortunately, my friends help me out.
Wouldn't want anything to
happen to your baby face.
I sure wish you'd sign up.
Come on, let's get out of here.
- Let him go.
Sifu, you'll never guess
what happened tonight.
- Hey, hey, here.
Beat this egg, come on.
- Tonight, I finally learned
the meaning of patience.
- Hurry up, order's waiting!
- Willy McCoy spit in my face tonight
and I didn't fight him.
- Ooh, so, you spit in my egg
and I don't fight you too, hmm?
- So what do you guys want for lunch?
- Oh, here we go again.
- What, I'm hungry.
- You are always hungry.
- How's pizza?
- That's great.
- That sound good?
Pizza, huh, yes.
- You watch.
Two months down the road,
she's gonna get huge.
I'm gonna dump you 'cause you're so fat.
(laughing)
- Hey, why don't you get
the shoes you wanted?
- I can do that.
Okay, I'll go get the shoes
and I'll meet you guys back at the car.
- All right, man.
- Well I'm gonna go get some candy.
- My god.
How can this be happening?
You're a disgrace to the race, woman.
- Back off, Tanner.
- Shut up, boy.
Don't you get it?
You're not supposed to be with his kind.
(bashing)
(crashing)
- Joey, are you hurt?
- Oh, I'm okay.
- We've got to get him to a doctor, Mark.
- Back up.
(bashing)
- What happened?
- My arm.
- Hey, get the cops.
- Come on, get up, it's the cops, come on!
Get up, come on you guys!
Get up, get up, come on!
- What happened?
- It was Tanner and McCoy.
- That's it.
They are not getting away with this, Mark.
Tanner and McCoy are history.
God!
Come on.
You going to the tournament tomorrow?
- I can't believe it but I am.
- Maybe I'll stop by.
I guess Joey might be fighting
and I'd like to watch him fight.
- Good night, Mark.
- [Mark] Good night, Kimberly.
(sighing)
- You know I was thinking, Mark.
Maybe I should enter
the tournament tomorrow.
I mean you took out Tanner.
Somebody's gotta handle McCoy.
If I don't do it, those
guys are gonna think
they can get away with anything.
- Wait a minute, James.
You sure about this?
What about your promise to Wing?
- I know.
- Look man, don't worry about the school.
I'll get a job after graduation,
save up some money for a downpayment.
It won't be so bad.
- That'll take years.
Look, I know I promised
not to fight for money
or to use the acupuncture points.
But this is different, Wing.
Now it's for Mark and the kids.
- No, you must remember your promise.
- But this is different.
- Not different.
You must be true to your principle.
You decide yourself.
- So remember, it's not
about beating the other guy.
It's about listening
to what's inside here.
I don't know, he was gone
when I got up this morning.
- I hope they get their heads bashed in.
- That's pretty tough talk from a girl
who claims she's a pacifist.
- Well, there's a time for everything.
- Then this must be the place.
Where do we go?
- [Announcer] Ladies and gentlemen.
Welcome to Millbrook first
martial arts tournament.
We got a great crowd turnout tonight.
And here come the judges.
We're about to begin the event.
But first we'd like to
inform you of some changes
in the program.
An original entrant, Mr. Mark Brown
representing the Red Dragon Kung Fu club
has withdrawn due to a personal injury.
He is being replaced
by Mr. James Caulfield.
(laughing)
- James, I told you, you
don't have to do this.
- Yes I do.
- What about Wing?
- Don't worry.
I think he'll understand.
- Hey, hey, hey.
There's plenty of time for that later.
Come on man, you're up.
(bashing)
(energetic music)
(crowd booing)
(bashing)
(crowd cheering)
(crowd applauding)
(bashing)
- That guy in the white
top, he looks dangerous.
- I know.
- Do you know who he is?
- I've never seen him before.
He's damn good.
(groaning)
(laughing)
(cheering)
- You were great!
- Thanks.
Guess that just about makes us even.
- This is it, man, one more to go.
You ready?
- You can do it!
- Brother.
- [Announcer] And now,
finalists James Caulfield
and White Tiger Gary
Carlisle will face off
for the Milbrook Karate Championship.
- I hope he doesn't get hurt.
- Don't worry, he can handle it.
(bashing)
(grunting)
(percussive intense music)
(bashing)
- Yes, yes!
(cheering)
- James, he has a knife!
(knife clanging)
(bashing)
- Oh, are you okay?
(crowd applauding)
(screaming)
- [Wing] This is airway.
- [James] So I can use this if
someone's trying to kill me?
- [Wing] Only when life's
in danger, it's rabid.
(bashing)
- What the hell.
(crowd applauding)
(tires screeching)
Sifu!
Where are you going?
- I'm leaving.
- Are you angry with me?
- Did you break promise?
- You nodded.
- Did I nod?
- Come on, let's go.
(car starting)
- Here they come.
- Well, come on!
(clapping)
- [Man] Hut!
Face Sifu Wing, bow.
- Would you do the honors?
(students clapping)
I finally learned your lesson.
Strength without judgment means nothing.
(somber music)
- If I were you, I would
have done the same.
Catch.
(rock music)
- [Narrator] For James
Caulfield, getting an education
was getting him into trouble.
- You're new on campus here, aren't you?
(bashing)
This is a dangerous place.
Sometimes people get hurt real bad.
- [Narrator] He's found the right girl.
- There's a lot of things
you don't know about me.
- I can see that.
- [Narrator] He's made the wrong enemy.
- Drop him, boys.
(bashing and groaning)
- [Narrator] Then one man,
- Hey!
- Stay out of this, China man.
(bashing)
- [Narrator] He found
a teacher and a friend.
(screaming and bashing)
- How can I learn unless you teach me?
- You want it easy?
Movies easy.
This life,
(screaming)
Train on ice will teach you good balance.
Balance good.
You can defend.
And attack.
(crashing)
(bashing)
- [Narrator] Now, for honor,
for love, for friendship.
- Make promise, keep promise.
- [Narrator] James Caulfield
either fights for his life
or he'll lose it.
(bashing)
(cheering)
College Kickboxers.
- What the hell.
(bashing)