LOCK AND LOAD.
YOU READY?
TIME TO GO.
FBI!
DON'T MOVE!
YOU'RE UNDER ARREST!
THERE'S A GUN!
PUT YOUR HANDS
WHERE WE CAN SEE THEM!
NOW OR I'LL BLOW
YOUR HEAD OFF!
WHY DIDN'T YOU
GO FOR IT, ASSHOLE?
WHY DON'T YOU KILL ME?
ANDERSON?
WHAT THE HELL?
PURSUIT OF BLUE DODGE VAN,
ILLINOIS PLATE NUMBER...
SHOTS FIRED!
SUSPECT TURNING EAST
AT DERRICK.
[STATIC]
OFFICERS RETURNING FIRE.
WE'VE GOT HER CORNERED.
SQUAD OFFICERS ARE
COMING OUT OF VEHICLES
WITH WEAPONS DRAWN.
STAND BY.
FBI!
THROW OUT YOUR WEAPON!
COME OUT OF YOUR VEHICLE, HANDS OVER YOUR HEAD!
YOU HAVE 10 SECONDS!
[UNIVERSAL HONEY PLAYS]
WHERE YOU BEEN,
SWEETHEART?
I'VE BEEN PLAYING MUSIC,
SWEETHEART.
JACK
WITH WATER BACK.
SO THIS GEEK
COMES INTO THE STORE.
HE KNOWS ZIP ABOUT GUNS.
HE WANTS SOMETHING
FOR HOME PROTECTION.
THE GUY WANTS
A HAND CANNON.
I COULDN'T SELL
THE GEEK A CANNON--
BREAK HIS WRIST.
I SOLD HIM
A SNUB-NOSED .38.
CINDY HEARS THIS,
SHE GOES BALLISTIC.
"WE'RE IN BUSINESS
TO MAKE MONEY!"
TOO MUCH GUN,
TOO LITTLE GUY.
YOU DID RIGHT.
TELL THAT TO CINDY.
IT'S GETTING
REALLY CLEAR!
YOU NEVER CARED
ABOUT ME!
FUCK YOU!
I LEAVE,
I'M NOT COMING BACK.
SO LEAVE!
GET OUT!
I'M FUCKIN'
OUTTA HERE,
YOU CRAZY,
FUCKIN' BITCH!
YEAH, YOU, TOO.
BIG FUCKIN' LOSER.
HEY, LET ME
SEE THAT.
OH.
DON'T WORRY.
THIS IS, UH, CLEAN.
YOU WANT TO KEEP THAT
ELEVATED UP LIKE THAT.
YOU WANT TO DANCE?
I DON'T DANCE.
NEITHER DO I.
COME ON.
YOU MIGHT HAVE
TO HOLD ME UP.
WELL, I CAN DO THAT.
♪ I FOUND LOVE,
I FOUND LOVE ♪
IT'S TRUE ♪
♪ I FOUND LOVE
♪ BABY, IT'S YOU
♪ WELL, IT SEEMS
I BEEN WAITIN' FOREVER ♪
♪ AND I KNOW...
I'M PAM.
♪ YOU'VE
BEEN WAITIN', TOO ♪
♪ WELL, I WOULD WAIT
A THOUSAND MORE LIFETIMES ♪
♪ 'CAUSE I KNOW I WOULD
BE WITH YOU, BABY ♪
♪ I FOUND LOVE,
I FOUND LOVE ♪
[SMOKEHOUSE PLAYS]
♪ BUCK BUCK BUCK
AW WAH ♪
OH, FUCK!
FUCK, FUCK, FUCK, FUCK.
♪ I HAD A BOTTLE
OF WHISKEY ♪
♪ YEAH, AND A BAG
OF WINE ♪
YOU'RE HEADED BACK
TO THE SHITHOUSE ♪
♪ I HAD TO FOLLOW
YOU BACK ♪
WHAT ARE YOU READING?
GUY IN THE WHEELCHAIR.
SO HOW DID YOU FIND ME?
I'M A COP.
I DIDN'T TELL YOU?
NO.
YOU KNOW,
YOUR REGISTRATION'S
EXPIRED,
AND YOU'VE GOT
ABOUT $300 WORTH
OF VIOLATIONS--
PARKING TICKETS
MOSTLY.
SO IS THAT WHY
YOU'RE HERE?
NO.
I'M ON MY LUNCH HOUR.
I THOUGHT I'D GET
A LITTLE TARGET
PRACTICE.
YOU GOT TIME?
YEAH. I MAKE MY OWN HOURS.
THEY LOVE ME AROUND HERE.
O.K.
TAKE A DEEP BREATH.
LET HALF OF IT OUT
AND HOLD IT.
NOW AIM...
SQUEEZE.
AHEM!
AGAIN.
[CLICK]
YOU DON'T SHOOT ANIMALS,
DO YOU?
NO.
TO ME, SHOOTING IS
ABOUT PRECISION, CONTROL.
I JUST LIKE KNOWING
WHATEVER HAPPENS,
I'M READY.
SOMEONE LIKE YOU,
I'M SURPRISED YOU
DON'T CARRY A HANDGUN.
SOMEBODY LIKE ME?
YOU'RE SO BEAUTIFUL.
GUYS MUST ALWAYS
BE HITTING ON YOU.
YOU ALWAYS TAKE GIRLS
SHOOTING?
DID A LOT OF SHOOTING
IN THE CORPS.
IT'S JUST A HOBBY.
NICE HOBBY.
HEY, PAM!
WHAT?
SAME TIME TOMORROW.
YOU SHOWED ME YOURS.
I'LL SHOW YOU MINE.
109 REQUESTS BACKUP,
CORNER OF COURT
AND SACKETT.
THIS IS UNIT 103 RESPONDING,
VICINITY COURT AND SACKETT.
WHAT'S THIS, HUH?
GET ON THE CAR!
17-2.
93, OVER.
93, 9, WHICH ONE?
OH!
POSSESSION, SPEEDING,
RESISTING ARREST.
IS THAT WHAT
YOU CALL IT?
FUCK YOU, BOOKWORM.
GET UP!
OHH.
COME ON!
GET IN THE CAR,
SHITHEAD.
COME ON.
SO THERE. TRY IT NOW.
YEAH, I SEE IT.
IT LOOKS ALMOST BLUE.
O.K., NOW GO DOWN A LITTLE
AND TO THE LEFT.
YEAH.
NOT AS BRIGHT.
IT'S KIND OF BLURRY.
LIKE IT'S SMUDGED, RIGHT?
RIGHT.
THAT'S 'CAUSE
IT'S NOT A STAR.
IT'S ANOTHER GALAXY.
WOW.
THAT'S INCREDIBLE.
THE GRAVITATIONAL PULL
OF THE BLACK HOLE
IS SO STRONG
THAT EVERYTHING NEARBY
GETS SUCKED INTO IT.
EVEN LIGHT CAN'T ESCAPE.
THAT'S WHY
THEY'RE INVISIBLE...
LIKE A BIG HOLE
IN THE SKY.
HOW DO YOU KNOW
THEY EXIST?
IT'S VERY THEORETICAL.
ALTHOUGH
ABOUT 100 YEARS AGO,
SOMETHING HIT SIBERIA
AND MILES OF FOREST
WERE FLATTENED,
BUT NOBODY EVER
FOUND ANYTHING.
NO METEOR, NOTHING.
SO SOME PEOPLE THINK
IT WAS A TINY BLACK HOLE
PASSING THROUGH THE EARTH.
THROUGHTHE EARTH?
LIKE A BULLET
THROUGH SMOKE.
BLACK HOLES
ARE REALLY INTENSE.
THEY'RE PART
OF WHAT'S CALLED
THE DARK MATTER
OF THE UNIVERSE.
I LOVE THAT.
MOST OF THE MATTER
IN THE UNIVERSE
IS INVISIBLE...
AND NOBODY KNOWS
WHAT IT IS
OR WHERE IT IS,
AND YOU THINK
YOU'RE SEEING
WHAT'S OUT THERE...
BUT YOU'RE NOT.
DOESN'T ALL THIS
MAKE IT SEEM LIKE
NOTHING YOU DO MATTERS?
YEAH.
ISN'T IT GREAT?
IT'S LIKE YOU
DON'T HAVE TO BE SCARED.
DO YOU EVER THINK
ABOUT DYING?
SOMETIMES.
THERE WAS
THIS TRAINING TAPE
AT THE ACADEMY.
A COP PULLS OVER
A PANEL TRUCK
FOR A BUSTED
TAILLIGHT,
SOME MINOR
VIOLATION.
YOU APPROACH
THE DRIVER'S SIDE.
SEEMS FRIENDLY
ENOUGH,
SO YOU GET
HIS LICENSE.
BUT THE RADIO'S
SQUAWKING
OR SOMETHING,
SO YOU
TURN YOUR HEAD
FOR JUST A MOMENT.
BLAM, BLAM!
WHITE LIGHT.
THAT'S THE END
OF THE TAPE.
COULD HAPPEN
ANY DAY.
I JUST WANT IT TO BE
ONE CLEAN SHOT
TO THE HEAD,
YOU KNOW?
THEN IT'S OVER.
NO TOUCHING.
I WISH...
I WISH I COULD FALL
INTO A BLACK HOLE,
AND I'D LIKE
TO DIE THAT WAY.
I'D DISAPPEAR INTO
THE SUPERDENSE NOTHING,
BUT MY IMAGE
WOULD LINGER FOREVER
ON THE EVENT HORIZON.
AND IN A BILLION YEARS
AN ALIEN STARSHIP
WOULD PASS BY...
AND SEE ME
STILL FALLING.
OH, GOD,
YOU'RE SO CRAZY.
HEY, PAM?
OH, COME ON, PAM.
PAM.
NO, I DIDN'T
MEAN IT LIKE THAT!
I DIDN'T
MEAN IT LIKE THAT.
PAM, NO, PLEASE!
WAIT! STOP!
I DIDN'T--
I DIDN'T MEAN IT.
[CRYING]
I MEANT GOOD CRAZY.
THE WAY YOU MAKE ME
FEEL, IT'S CRAZY.
THAT'S ALL I...
I WOULDN'T SAY
ANYTHING TO HURT YOU.
O.K.?
I'VE NEVER
FELT ANYTHING LIKE YOU.
IT'S O.K.
COME ON.
♪ THIS SHOULD BE THE LAST
FIGHT TO FIGHT ♪
♪ THE LAST
TRADE OF FIRE ♪
WAIT HERE.
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
[SNAPS FINGERS]
HEY, HOT SHIT.
HEY.
D.A. SAYS SHE HAS
TO DROP RESISTING
ARREST.
KNOW WHY?
YOU WOULDN'T
BACK ME UP.
YOU DIDN'T
SEE NOTHING.
I SAW YOU PUT CUFFS
ON THAT KID
BEFORE KICKING HIM
IN THE BALLS.
ANDERSON,
YOU'RE AN ARROGANT
MOTHERFUCKER.
EVEN FOR A ROOKIE,
YOU GOT
A LOT TO LEARN.
YOU AIN'T
GOING TO FIND IT IN
YOUR FUCKING BOOKS.
YOU GOING TO TEACH ME?
PUT CUFFS ON ME FIRST.
YOU'LL LEARN,
ONE WAY OR ANOTHER.
YOU'LL LEARN.
JESUS, CHRIS,
DID YOU HAVE TO SPIT
IN HIS FACE, TOO?
YEAH, I DID.
I HAD TO.
HI.
WHAT ARE YOU
DOING IN HERE?
I SAID
STAY IN THE VAN.
YOU WERE GONE SO LONG,
I THOUGHT THAT YOU
MIGHT NEED...
SOME BACKUP.
GOODBYE.
YOU'RE CROSSING
THE LINE HERE.
YOU GOING
TO BUST ME?
ISN'T IT NEAT?
IT'S MY HOUSE.
IT'S NICE.
THIS COLOR, THOUGH.
I DON'T GET IT.
IT USED TO BE YELLOW.
ARE YOUR FOLKS HOME?
WE COULD SAY HELLO--
THAT'S MY ROOM
IN THE MIDDLE.
I USED TO LIE
THERE IN MY CRIB.
I LOVED TO WATCH
THE WALLPAPER.
IT WAS STARS
AND ROCKET SHIPS.
THE EXHAUST
FROM THE ROCKETS
WAS RED.
THEY MOVED
IN THE DARK.
IT WAS SO BEAUTIFUL.
THEY PROBABLY
WANTED A BOY.
EXCUSE ME.
MAY I HELP YOU PEOPLE?
NO, UH...
WELL, MY FRIEND
USED TO LIVE HERE.
SHE JUST
WANTED TO SHOW ME.
WE, UH, BOUGHT
THE HOUSE LAST YEAR.
IS SHE ONE
OF THE STAWICKI
CHILDREN?
NO.
NO, SHE'S NOT.
SORRY TO DISTURB YOU.
THERE WAS SOMETHING
WRONG WITH ME.
I HAD ASTHMA OR SOMETHING.
I COULDN'T BREATHE.
OBVIOUSLY THEY NEEDED
TO GET AWAY.
YOU CAN'T REALLY
BLAME THEM.
I MEAN...
KIDS ARE A TOTAL
PAIN IN THE ASS
EVEN WHEN THEY TRY
TO BE GOOD.
AND I'M SURE
THEY EXPLAINED IT TO ME.
WHAT DID I KNOW?
I WAS 4 YEARS OLD.
DO YOU KNOW HOW LONG
I WAITED FOR THEM?
SHE'S LYING...
SMASHED UP IN A CAR
WITH HER HEAD
ROLLED OFF
IN A DITCH,
AND I'M WAITING.
WAITING LIKE
A FUCKING IDIOT.
HA!
SHEWWW!
HA HA HA!
[BREATHING HARD]
AM I DOING
SOMETHING WRONG, PAM?
NO, YOU'RE GREAT, CHRIS.
YOU'RE THE BEST.
'CAUSE IT SEEMS LIKE
YOU NEVER GET OFF,
AND I WANT YOU
TO GET OFF, TOO.
LOOK, I DON'T COME, O.K.?
GOT A PROBLEM
WITH THAT?
NEVER?
YEAH, NEVER.
THINK THERE'S SOMETHING
WRONG WITH ME? FUCK YOU.
YOU GET WHAT YOU WANT.
WHAT DO YOU CARE ANYWAY?
I JUST--
I WANT TO KNOW
I CAN MAKE YOU
FEEL GOOD, TOO.
BULLSHIT!
YOU'RE JUST LIKE
EVERY OTHER GUY
WITH A FAT MALE EGO.
YOU GOT TO PROVE
WHAT A STUD YOU ARE
BY MAKING
SOME WOMAN SCREAM.
WHO AM I TO GIVE YOU
THE FUCKING SATISFACTION?
LOOK, PAM...
C-CAN YOU LOVE ME?
WHAT?
I SAID
CAN YOU LOVE ME?
IT IS A SIMPLE QUESTION.
BECAUSE I LOVE YOU.
I LOVE YOU,
AND I WANT TO MARRY YOU,
BUT YOU'VE GOT
TO LOVE ME BACK.
YOU'RE CRAZY.
WHY SHOULD I TRUST YOU?
BECAUSE YOU NEED ME.
AND BECAUSE
I'LL TAKE CARE OF YOU.
I WANT YOU
TO BE MY WIFE.
IS THIS SO WEIRD?
I MEAN, COME ON.
THAT'S WHAT PEOPLE DO,
RIGHT,
WHEN THEY
LOVE EACH OTHER?
I'LL LOVE YOU FOREVER.
I'LL--
I DON'T CARE
ABOUT THE SEX.
IT'S NOT THAT
I DON'T WANT TO COME.
I JUST NEVER DO.
WE CAN CHANGE THAT.
BUT YOU GOT TO DECIDE
WHETHER OR NOT
YOU WANT ME.
I COULD STAY OR GO,
BUT YOU GOT
TO DECIDE, PAM.
DO YOU, CHRIS, TAKE PAM,
HERE PRESENT,
TO BE YOUR
LAWFUL WEDDED WIFE,
TO LIVE TOGETHER
IN THE STATE OF MATRIMONY,
TO LOVE HER, COMFORT HER,
HONOR, AND KEEP HER
FROM THIS DAY FORWARD,
FOR BETTER OR FOR WORSE,
FOR RICHER
OR FOR POORER,
IN SICKNESS OR IN HEALTH,
UNTIL DEATH
DO YOU PART?
I DO.
[COUGHS]
DO YOU, PAM,
TAKE CHRIS, HERE PRESENT,
TO BE YOUR
LAWFUL WEDDED HUSBAND,
TO LIVE TOGETHER
IN THE STATE OF MATRIMONY,
TO LOVE HIM,
COMFORT HIM,
HONOR AND KEEP HIM
FOR BETTER
OR FOR WORSE,
FOR RICHER
OR FOR POORER,
IN SICKNESS
OR IN HEALTH,
UNTIL DEATH
DO YOU PART?
I DO.
YOU MAY EXCHANGE RINGS.
[COUGHING]
BY VIRTUE OF THE POWER
VESTED IN ME
BY THE STATE LAWS
AND CONSTITUTION,
I NOW PRONOUNCE YOU
MAN AND WIFE.
[RETCHING]
WE'RE HERE.
PUT THOSE AWAY.
YOU'LL SCARE THEM.
HI.
HEY.
HIYA, MA.
OH, THIS IS
MUCH NICER
THAN I THOUGHT.
HI, PAM.
IT'S SO COZY.
YOU LOOK PRETTY.
WHAT'S THIS
OVER HERE?
OH, UH, PAM'S
PUTTING TOGETHER
A TELESCOPE HERE, DAD.
IT'S A--A
NEWTONIAN REFLECTOR,
AND THOSE SCREWS,
UM, ADJUST THE MAIN
MIRROR IN THE BACK.
YEAH.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'M SORRY. I HAVE
TO SET THE TABLE.
CAN I HELP?
HEY, ADELE, DON'T GO
RUNNING OFF LIKE THAT.
WE HAVEN'T GIVEN HIM
HIS PRESENT YET.
IT'S FOR
BOTH OF YOU.
IT'S
A HOUSEWARMING
PRESENT.
PAM.
FRANK.
FRANK, LET
THE BOY DO IT.
UH, HONEY,
COME IN HERE.
WE ALWAYS MEANT
FOR YOU TO HAVE THIS.
YOU ALWAYS LOVED IT SO
WHEN YOU WERE LITTLE.
OH-HO, THE SCOUT.
WE ALWAYS HAD
THIS PICTURE.
IT WAS
A WEDDING PRESENT.
THE SCOUT, WE CALLED IT.
CHRIS ALWAYS
LOVED THIS PICTURE SO.
REMEMBER WHEN YOU
WANTED TO BE A COWBOY?
WHAT WAS THE NAME
OF THAT PROGRAM, FRANK?
COWHIDE.
ALL THROUGH
THE SCHOOL YEARS,
THAT'S ALL HE WANTED.
"I WANT TO BE
A COWBOY, MOM."
IT'S GREAT.
CHRIS, IS THE FOOD
GOING TO BURN?
OH, I DON'T KNOW.
I'LL CHECK. HERE.
BUT, CHRIS...
[CLEARS THROAT]
IT'S VERY GOOD, PAM.
CHRIS MADE IT.
I'M SURE
YOU HELPED.
[COUGHING]
I'LL GET SOME WATER.
DAD, YOU O.K.?
YOU GOING TO
BE O.K.?
FRANK,
DRINK THIS.
HEY, PAM.
[ROCK MUSIC PLAYING]
HE'S HAD A BAD WEEK.
IT'S HIS THERAPY--
THIS NEW THERAPY.
I THINK WE SHOULD
TAKE HIM HOME.
WANT TO
GO HOME, FRANK?
PAM!
[KNOCKS ON DOOR]
COME ON OUT
AND SAY GOODBYE,
HONEY.
YOU CAN
COME OUT NOW, PAM.
THEY'RE GONE.
IT'S SAFE.
[ROCK MUSIC PLAYING]
SO, LIKE,
ONE WAS BARELY A "B,"
AND THE OTHER ONE
WAS LIKE A "C."
WAIT A MINUTE.
MAYBE IT WAS
THE OTHER WAY AROUND.
I DON'T KNOW.
I DON'T REMEMBER,
BUT SHE WAS VERY
SELF-CONSCIOUS.
WELL, SHE COULD HAVE
JUST GOT AN IMPLANT.
JUST ONE.
I DIDN'T CARE...
BUT TO ME, SHE WAS
INCREDIBLY SEXY,
BUT CALL ME CRAZY.
I JUST LOVE TITS.
EVA.
HMM?
HOW'D YOU KNOW
WHAT YOU WERE?
YOU MEAN A DYKE?
HOW DID YOU
FIND OUT?
I ALWAYS KNEW.
IT'S JUST LIKE
HOW YOU KNOW YOU LIKE GUYS.
RIGHT?
IT'S THE SAME THING.
YOU JUST KNOW WHO YOU ARE.
RIGHT.
[ROCK MUSIC PLAYING]
♪ YEAH, YEAH, YEAH
CINDY WANTED ME
TO INVITE YOU GUYS
OVER ON SUNDAY.
WE'RE GOING
TO BARBECUE.
I CAN'T
ON SUNDAY, MIKE.
I NEVER SEE YOU ANYMORE.
WHAT IS IT WITH YOU TWO?
STILL ON YOUR HONEYMOON?
TOO FUCKING BUSY
OR TOO BUSY FUCKING?
BUSY, I JUST--
SUNDAY
I'M PUMPING OUT A BASEMENT
FOR STU'S UNCLE, AND...
MOONLIGHTING ALREADY.
I TOLD YOU
MARRIAGE IS EXPENSIVE.
PAM'S WORTH IT.
PAM.
I'M HOME.
OH, I MUST HAVE
FALLEN ASLEEP.
WHAT'S TO EAT?
I HAVEN'T HAD ANY DINNER.
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
BAD DAY?
NOT BAD.
JUST 37 HOURS LONG.
CHRIS, I'VE BEEN THINKING
WE SHOULD GET A DOG.
A DOG WOULD BE
PROTECTION, CHRIS.
I THINK WE NEED A DOG.
YOU'RE GONE
ALL THE TIME.
I GOT TO WORK
I KNOW, BUT
IT'S JUST AN IDEA.
BESIDES, A DOG
WOULD BE COMPANY,
AND IT WOULD
LOVE US.
DON'T YOU WANT
A DOG TO FETCH
YOUR SLIPPERS
AND LICK YOUR FEET?
I THOUGHT THAT'S
WHAT I HAD YOU FOR.
LOOK, PAM,
I KNOW YOU WANT A DOG.
LIKE A LAB, MAYBE,
OR A HUSKY.
THEY GOT TO EAT.
YOU GOING TO FEED THEM?
YOU DON'T FEED ME.
THERE'S NO FOOD HERE.
WELL,
DON'T LOOK AT ME.
I'M NOT YOUR
GODDAMN HOUSEWIFE.
NO KIDDING.
GOD, SHIT.
WHAT TIME IS IT?
I'VE GOT
TO GO TO WORK.
RIGHT NOW?
YOU'RE GOING--
THIS IS WRONG.
WE HAVE GOT TO SET
SOME GROUND RULES
AROUND HERE.
GO TO GO.
WHEN YOU COME HOME,
WE'LL SET SOME
GROUND RULES!
YOU'RE
50 MINUTES LATE.
I CAN'T LET THIS
GO ANYMORE.
I WARNED YOU
A MILLION TIMES.
IF YOU CAN'T
MAKE IT ON TIME,
DON'T BOTHER
TO COME IN.
YOU'RE DOCKED
FOR THE NIGHT.
GO ON. GET
OUT OF HERE.
IF YOU CAN'T
GET HERE ON TIME
TOMORROW,
DON'T COME BACK
AT ALL.
WHAT, ARE YOU
ON BREAK?
PAM, WAIT UP.
YOU O.K.?
JESUS CHRIST.
WHAT A FUCKING ASSHOLE.
HE HATES ME.
HE'S GOING
TO FIRE ME.
NO, NO. HE'S NOT
GOING TO FIRE YOU.
LOOK, I'M GOING TO CALL YOU
TOMORROW NIGHT, O.K.?
9:00 I'LL MAKE SURE
YOU'RE UP.
HERE, CUTIE.
HEY, ENJOY
YOUR NIGHT OFF.
THANK YOU, EVA.
YOU'RE
MY ONLY FRIEND.
YOU KNOW THAT?
I'LL TALK
TO YOU LATER.
I'M SORRY, MISS.
YOUR CARD'S
BEEN DECLINED.
MAGNETIC STRIP'S
WORN OUT. JUST OVERRIDE.
NO CAN DO.
IT'S A DECLINE.
IT'S NOT A CAN'T READ.
GET THEM
ON THE PHONE.
THEY NEVER OVERRIDE.
YOU WANT TO SELL
THE EYEPIECE?
CAN I HELP YOU?
YES. A CUSTOMER
REQUESTS AN OVERRIDE.
TELL HER YOURSELF.
HI.
OF COURSE
I UNDERSTAND,
BUT THESE AREN'T
NORMAL CIRCUMSTANCES.
THE LUNAR ECLIPSE
IS TONIGHT.
OBVIOUSLY I NEED
THE EYEPIECE NOW.
I SENT MY CHECK OUT
FIVE DAYS AGO.
THE POST OFFICE
IS SCREWING UP AGAIN.
THERE WON'T BE
ANOTHER PARTIAL ECLIPSE
VISIBLE IN THIS
LATITUDE FOR SIX YEARS.
BY THEN,
THE POST OFFICE WILL
HAVE DELIVERED MY CHECK
AND YOU WILL HAVE
LOST MY BUSINESS.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
YES?
THERE'S AN ECLIPSE
TONIGHT?
YEAH. IN THREE MONTHS.
LET ME SEE THAT KNIFE.
THIS IS
AN EXCELLENT TANTO.
GUARANTEED...
TO PENETRATE A CAR DOOR.
I DON'T CARE
WHAT IT DOES, PAM!
I DIDN'T GIVE YOU
PERMISSION TO SPEND $500!
I NEED
YOUR PERMISSION?
I WORK, TOO,
REMEMBER?
YOU HAVE NO IDEA
THE SHIT I PUT UP
WITH--
NO. I DON'T WANT
TO HEAR IT, O.K.?
BECAUSE WE AGREED--
WHY DO I HAVE TO
ANSWER TO YOU?
'CAUSE YOU'RE
THE ONE WITH
THE PRICK?
BECAUSE ONE OF US
HAS TO BE IN TOUCH
WITH REALITY.
I'M NOT BECAUSE
I WANT THINGS
AND PAY FOR THEM
WITH MY OWN MONEY?
THAT WAS OUR MONEY.
NO. THE WAY THINGS
WORK AROUND HERE
IS WHAT'S YOURS
IS YOURS,
AND WHAT'S MINE
IS YOURS!
YOU DON'T
HAVE A PROBLEM
SPENDING OURMONEY
WHEN YOU SEE
A GUN YOU WANT!
YOU DON'T ASK
MYPERMISSION!
HOW MANY GUNS
DO YOU HAVE?
AND YOU'VE GOT
YOUR BIKE,
YOU GO NIGHT RIDING
WITH MIKE.
YOU WORK NIGHTS.
IF YOU DIDN'T,
YOU COULD GO WITH US.
I SHOULD QUIT MY JOB
AND BE COMPLETELY
DEPENDENT ON YOU?
I'D HAVE TO ASK
PERMISSION TO BREATHE!
I HAD THAT BIKE
FOR TWO YEARS
BEFORE I MET YOU--
FUCK THE BIKE!
FUCK YOUR WHOLE
STUPID FAMILY!
YOU NEVER FUCKING
LISTEN TO ME!
NO, I DON'T,
'CAUSE YOU ARE FUCKED!
JUST SHUT THE FUCK UP
RIGHT NOW!
I TRUSTED YOU.
I TRUSTED YOU,
AND YOU'RE JUST
LIKE ALL THE REST!
I NEVER SHOULD
HAVE MARRIED YOU!
AND I WOULD LIKE TO SEE
HOW YOU COULD SURVIVE
WITHOUT ME!
GET THE FUCK
OUT OF HERE!
OH, MY GOD.
CHRIS, WHERE
ARE YOU GOING?
WILL BE VISIBLE IN
THE CONSTELLATION PERSEUS.
ALSO KNOWN
AS THE DEMON STAR,
BETA PERSEI IS IN FACT
A CLOSE BINARY--
TWO STARS CAUGHT IN TIGHT
ORBIT AROUND EACH OTHER.
BETA PERSEI IS WHAT WE CALL
A DARK ECLIPSING VARIABLE.
ON THE 15th,
STARTING AT 11 P.M.,
LOOK FOR ITS BRIGHTNESS
TO FADE ABRUPTLY
AS THE DARKER STAR
OBSCURES ITS SMALLER,
BRIGHTER COMPANION.
MARS WILL BE VISIBLE
ALL THIS MONTH.
THANK YOU FOR CALLING
THE SKY REPORTER.
[DIAL TONE]
PAM.
HONEY.
I'M SO SORRY.
HEY.
OH, MY GOD!
PAM, HONEY, COME ON.
YOU'VE BEEN IN BED
FOR THREE DAYS NOW.
PAM.
[ARF ARF]
OHH, OHH, OHH.
OH, MY GOD.
OH, YEAH.
HI.
SHE HAS PAPERS?
OF COURSE.
THAT'S $400 WORTH
OF DOG RIGHT THERE.
BUT I DIDN'T THINK
WE COULD AFFORD--
I TALKED TO
CENTAUR SECURITY.
THEY SAID I COULD
PUT SOME HOURS ON
THERE.
I'LL TAKE
CARE OF IT.
THANK YOU, CHRIS.
I COULDN'T LIVE
WITHOUT YOU.
AND NOW CHAOS
AND YOU AND ME--
WE'RE A REAL FAMILY,
JUST LIKE I'VE ALWAYS
WANTED,
AND YOU MADE IT HAPPEN.
I LOVE YOU SO MUCH.
I'D DO ANYTHING
FOR YOU, PAM.
I JUST WANT TO
MAKE YOU HAPPY.
UNCLE CHRIS,
UNCLE CHRIS.
COME ON, HELP ME.
AAH, AAH.
GOOD SOLDIER.
HEY, YOU MADE IT
FINALLY.
COME ON IN.
MIKE'S IN THE BACK.
COME ON, YOU.
HOW YOU BEEN?
O.K.
HI, EVERYBODY.
HEY, MIKE.
HOW YOU DOING?
ALL RIGHT, BRO.
WHO WANTS
SOMETHING TO DRINK?
I'LL HAVE
ONE OF THOSE BEERS.
I WILL TAKE ONE
AS WELL.
PAM.
PAM,
YOU WANT A BEER?
RIGHT.
IS YOUR LAWN MOWER
BROKE DOWN?
[MIKE]
THAT'S HOW FAST
IT'S GROWING.
I CUT IT
FOUR DAYS AGO.
[CINDY]
I TOLD HIM
HE HAS TO CUT IT
EVERY TWO DAYS
IN THE SUMMER.
WATCH OUT.
SO, WHAT DO YOU
LIKE BETTER?
THIS OR SWING SETS?
I LIKE SWING SETS.
THIS IS MORE HARD.
FOR YOU.
ESPECIALLY
WHEN IT'S BY--
RIGHT BY A BIG
WALL OF WOOD.
JEREMY, I'M NOT
GOING TO TELL YOU AGAIN.
YOU KNOW, THEIR FATHER
IS MUCH WORSE.
ADELE SAYS
YOU AND CHRIS HAVEN'T
BEEN OVER IN A WHILE.
CHRIS CALLS HIM.
JESUS, PAM.
IT'S NOT
THE SAME.
[CHRIS]
YOU'VE HAD QUITE ENOUGH
TO DRINK ALREADY, PAM.
PAM, ARE YOU
LISTENING TO ME?
WHAT ARE YOU
GOING TO DO, HUH?
YOU'RE GOING
TO GET OUT THERE,
YOU'RE GOING TO
GET STOPPED!
THAT'S REALLY
RESPONSIBLE!
THAT'S WHAT YOU SHOULD
BE DOING RIGHT NOW--
DRIVING A MOTORCYCLE!
ARE YOU
LISTENING TO ME?
[PAM]
NO, I'M NOT
LISTENING TO YOU!
STOP IT!
JUST STOP IT!
THE FOOD SUCKS!
CINDY SUCKS!
IT'S NOT ABOUT FOOD
OR CINDY OR MIKE!
EVERY TIME I WANT
YOU TO GO SOMEWHERE
WITH MY FAMILY,
YOU CAN'T DO THAT
FOR ME!
NO!
PLEASE?
GET YOUR--YOU WANT--
SON OF A BITCH!
FUCKED IT UP FOR ME!
[MOTORCYCLE REVS]
PAM, YOU ARE NOT GOING
ANYWHERE WITHOUT ME!
PAM!
PUT ON A DRESS, O.K?
I DON'T CARE IF YOU
GOT TO GO TO SEARS.
BE AT THE FUNERAL
HOME AT 6:00.
I'M GOING TO BE
WITH MOM ALL DAY.
BE THERE.
BYE.
SOMETHING WRONG?
YEAH, I GUESS.
CHRIS' DAD DIED.
OH, JEEZ, PAM,
I'M SORRY.
WHY?
DID YOU KILL HIM?
WHOOP.
YOU CAN'T COME IN
HERE WEARING THOSE.
MICHAEL.
I'LL TAKE THEM OFF.
I CAN'T HELP YOU
RIGHT NOW.
CHRIS.
I'M SORRY
ABOUT YOUR DAD.
I KNOW YOU LOVED HIM.
I'M REALLY SORRY.
HIS JACKET
WAS TUCKED
UNDER THE HOLSTER
LIKE HE WAS BEGGING
SOMEBODY TO GRAB
HIS WEAPON.
GIVE IT A REST, O.K.?
EVERYBODY KNOWS
SWIFT IS BRAIN DEAD.
WHAT MAKES YOU
SO GODDAMN SPECIAL, HUH?
IT'S THE REAL WORLD,
CHRIS.
YOU'VE GOT TO LIVE
WITH THESE GUYS.
YOU BACK THEM UP,
THEY BACK YOU UP.
HEY, HEY, MEET US
AT GILREIN'S.
ECKERT'S BUYING.
SCREW THEM,
ALL RIGHT?
I DO MY JOB.
YEAH. WELL, I GUESS
YOU'LL BE DOING IT ALONE.
YEAH, I'LL BE THERE!
♪ I WONDER WHO,
I WONDER WHO ♪
♪ WHO'S THE REAL
CRIMINAL ♪
♪ ME OR YOU?
♪ I WONDER WHO,
I WONDER WHO ♪
♪ WHO'S THE REAL
CRIMINAL... ♪
THIS IS UNIT 36
ON HIGHWAY 20
A MILE EAST
OF THE INTERCHANGE,
REQUESTING BACKUP,
OVER.
♪ ME OR YOU?
♪ I WONDER WHO,
I WONDER WHO ♪
♪ WHO'S THE REAL
CRIMINAL ♪
♪ ME OR YOU?
YEAH, THIS IS
UNIT 36 AGAIN.
I'M OUT ON HIGHWAY 20
REQUESTING BACKUP, OVER.
♪ WE SHOULD HAVE NEVER
LET IT GET THIS WAY ♪
♪ YOU EVER HEARD OF
A FEDERAL RESERVE BOARD? ♪
♪ A BUNCH OF RICH FAMILIES
STRIKING ACCORDS ♪
♪ IN 1913,
CONGRESS' THING WAS... ♪
YOU LOUSY FUCKING
COCKSUCKERS,
I'M SUPPOSED
TO SIT OUT HERE
AND GET MY ASS
BLOWN AWAY
BECAUSE NONE OF YOU
LAZY FAGGOTS
HAVE THE BALLS
TO EARN YOUR PAYCHECK!
ADIOS...
JAG OFF.
HA HA HA.
[MICROWAVE TIMER BEEPS]
THAT'S MY DOG.
WHERE'S MINE?
I DIDN'T
MAKE YOU ANY.
WHY NOT?
WHAT, YOU DIDN'T
THINK THAT MAYBE
I'D WANT TO EAT, TOO?
YOU COULDN'T JUST
STOP TO THINK,
"GEE, CHRIS HAD A REALLY
LONG, HARD, SHITTY DAY.
"HE LOST HIS JOB.
"MAYBE HE'D LIKE
TO COME HOME
TO A DECENT MEAL
FOR A CHANGE."
HUH?
COME HERE, PAM.
SIT DOWN. COME HERE.
I'VE BEEN GOING OVER
OUR SITUATION.
NOW, IF I CAN GET ON
FULL-TIME AT CENTAUR,
AND ASSUMING YOU MAX OUT
ALL YOUR OVERTIME AT UNIWORLD
AND I KEEP WORKING IN
MY SPARE TIME FOR STU'S UNCLE
AND WE CUT OUR EXPENSES
TO THE BONE,
WE CAN BE OUT OF DEBT
IN EIGHT YEARS.
WELL, PAM...
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
I THINK MY DINNER'S
GETTING COLD.
YOU JUST
DON'T GET IT, DO YOU?
WE ARE
IN SERIOUS TROUBLE.
THOSE ASSHOLES.
HOW COULD THEY
FIRE YOU?
YOU WERE
SO MUCH BETTER THAN
THEY'LL EVER BE.
I MEAN, MY GOD.
ASSHOLES.
JUST FUCK 'EM.
YOU HATED
THAT JOB ANYWAY.
LISTEN, CHRIS,
MAYBE WE SHOULD
LOOK AT THIS
AS AN OPPORTUNITY.
I MEAN, YOU HATED
THOSE JERKS, RIGHT?
WELL, YOU'RE FREE
OF THEM NOW,
AND YOU'RE
ALWAYS SAYING
YOU WANT TO START
YOUR OWN BUSINESS.
MAYBE THIS
IS THE TIME.
MAYBE YOU JUST
CAN'T SEE THIS IS
A GOOD THING.
HAVEN'T YOU HEARD
A WORD THAT I SAID?
STARTING A BUSINESS
COSTS MONEY.
WE DON'T HAVE ANY MONEY.
WE DON'T HAVE ANY CREDIT
'CAUSE YOU MAXED OUT
THE CARDS!
WE DON'T HAVE ANY ASSETS.
WE CANNOT MAKE RENT
ON THIS DUMP!
EVEN WITH ME BEING A COP,
WE WERE DROWNING.
WHERE WILL I MAKE
THAT KIND OF MONEY NOW?
YOU TELL ME!
WHY DON'T YOU
JUST GO EAT?
YOU CAN CONTINUE
EMPLOYMENT
ON PROBATION
ON THE CONDITION
THAT YOU ENTER
A DRUG TREATMENT
PROGRAM.
IT'S ALL HERE.
LET ME KNOW IF YOU
HAVE ANY QUESTIONS.
PAM, YOU'RE
A VERY BRIGHT GIRL.
GET SOME HELP.
WAIT A MINUTE.
DON'T DO IT YET.
IS THIS THE WAY YOU WANT
TO PLAY IT, PAM?
I'LL PLAY ANY GAME
YOU WANT.
YOU DON'T WANT
TO LIVE ANYMORE.
I DON'T WANT TO LIVE
ANYMORE, EITHER.
ARE YOU HAPPY NOW?
'CAUSE IT'S OVER.
ON THE COUNT
OF THREE.
1...
2.
NO. NO.
CHRIS,
I'M SO SORRY.
I JUST CAN'T FIX IT.
I CAN'T.
I'M SORRY.
[TIRES SCREECH]
[CAR HORN HONKS]
[DIALING]
[WOMAN]
911.
THIS IS CENTAUR
SECURITY.
CORNER OF DWIGHT
AND CHARLTON.
[WOMAN]
ENTER THE CODE.
[DIALING]
[WOMAN]
HARRIS UNITS
706 AND 709,
I HAVE
A HOLDUP ALARM
AT FIRST BANK
OF COMMERCE,
CORNER OF DWIGHT
AND CHARLTON.
[MAN]
709, CAN I GET
THE LOCATION?
YOU WERE
BREAKING UP.
I COULDN'T HEAR.
[MAN]
709 APPROACHING
FIRST BANK OF COMMERCE,
INTERSECTION OF
DWIGHT AND CHARLTON.
[SIREN]
19 MINUTES.
PATHETIC.
IT'S ONLY REHAB,
PAM.
IT WON'T KILL YOU.
I'LL BE BACK TO
PICK YOU UP AT 3:00.
DON'T FORGET TO EAT,
O.K.?
I LOVE YOU.
I FALL APART SOMETIMES,
BUT AT LEAST
I'VE GOT CHRIS.
HE'S A ROCK.
BUT STILL I KNOW I--I HAVE
TO TAKE CARE OF MYSELF.
I CAN'T ALWAYS EXPECT HIM
TO MAKE THINGS RIGHT.
CHRIS WANTS
WHAT'S BEST FOR ME.
UH, HE'S OF COURSE NOT CRAZY
ABOUT ME BEING HERE.
HE JUST WANTS US
TO GET BACK TO NORMAL.
[WOMAN]
AND WHAT
DO YOU WANT?
I JUST WANT
TO GET THROUGH THIS.
I WANT MY LIFE BACK.
[STATIC]
CHRIS DOESN'T UNDERSTAND
ABOUT DRUGS.
HE'S STRAIGHT.
HE'S A TOTAL
STRAIGHT ARROW.
IN FACT,
HE WAS A COP
IF YOU CAN
BELIEVE THAT.
BUT, UM, THERE WASN'T
ENOUGH ROOM FOR ADVANCEMENT.
SO, NOW HE'S
IN PRIVATE SECURITY,
AND HE'S ABOUT
TO START HIS OWN FIRM.
HE'S GOT
ALL THESE PEOPLE
WHO WANT
TO INVEST IN HIM.
IT'S GOING
TO BE GREAT.
FREEZE, MOTHERFUCKERS!
I MEAN NOW!
NOBODY MOVE.
GIVE ME
THAT FUCKING GUN.
NOBODY MOVE.
GET OVER THERE.
LAY DOWN
ON THE FLOOR.
BITCH, LAY DOWN!
GET ON
THE FLOOR NOW.
GET THE FUCK
OVER THERE.
WHO'S
THE HEAD TELLER?
YOU? GET UP HERE.
FRONT AND CENTER
NOW.
FILL UP
THIS FUCKING BAG.
YOU GOT TWO MINUTES.
AND I MEAN FILL IT.
DON'T LOOK AT ME.
LAY DOWN.
FILL IT UP.
LAY DOWN!
I SAID LAY DOWN!
COME ON. MOVE IT.
YOU TWO, LAY DOWN
ON THE FLOOR.
BOTH OF YOU UGLY
MOTHERFUCKERS, DOWN.
[WOMAN ON RADIO]
ALL UNITS,
I HAVE A ROBBERY
IN PROGRESS
AT THE FIRST BANK
OF COMMERCE
ON DWIGHT
AND CHARLTON.
REPEAT,
ROBBERY IN PROGRESS.
OH, YOU HEAR THAT?
THE COPS ARE COMING.
I'M NERVOUS.
AND YOU'RE
GOING TO DIE.
LOOK AT THE FLOOR.
FILL IT UP.
WHAT'S THAT?
YOU THINK
YOU CAN CATCH ME
WITH A FUCKING
DYE PACK?
YOU WANT TO DIE,
BITCH?
YOU WANT
TO FUCKING DIE?
LAY DOWN.
ALL RIGHT.
GET DOWN ON
THE FUCKING GROUND.
DOWN!
DON'T LOOK AT ME.
[MAN ON RADIO]
FIVE MINUTES OR SO.
ANY UNITS
ON THE SCENE YET?
[MAN]
WE'RE ABOUT A BLOCK
ACROSS FROM THE BANK.
WHEN WE ARRIVE,
WE'LL REQUEST BACKUP.
[WOMAN]
10-4, 709.
SKOAL.
SO, WHAT'S
THE SURPRISE?
AHH.
MMM.
COME ON.
THIS IS SO GOOD.
CHRIS, COME ON.
MMM.
NO. I CAN'T.
COME ON.
ALL RIGHT.
I GOT SOMETHING
FOR YOU.
HA HA HA.
UM, THIS IS LIKE--
IT'S $1,000,
AND THERE'S MORE.
BUT, UH, I'M PUTTING YOU
ON AN ALLOWANCE.
BUT WHERE
DID YOU GET IT?
I TOLD YOU I'D TAKE
CARE OF EVERYTHING.
CHRIS, AREN'T
YOU GOING TO TELL ME
WHERE YOU GOT
THE MONEY?
I TOLD YOU.
I'VE BEEN
WORKING OVERTIME
BUSTING MY ASS
AT CENTAUR.
IT'S FINALLY
STARTING TO PAY OFF.
BUT NO MORE PLASTIC,
ALL RIGHT?
WE PAY CASH
FOR EVERYTHING.
THAT IS SO GREAT.
I TOLD YOU
NOT TO WORRY.
I'LL TAKE CARE OF US
FROM HERE ON OUT.
I'M GOING TO GET
A NEW EQUATORIAL
MOUNT
FOR THE TELESCOPE
AND MAYBE
A NEW LENS.
UH-UH.
GO TO SLEEP.
I LOVE YOU.
ARE YOU GOING
TO TELL ME?
WHAT?
WHERE DID YOU
GET THE NEW PIECE?
I DON'T KNOW.
I PICKED IT UP.
HOW MUCH DID
IT SET YOU BACK?
ABOUT 800.
WHAT IS
YOUR PROBLEM?
YOU DON'T EVEN
KNOW ANYMORE.
I'M WORKING MY ASS OFF
AT THE STORE.
I'M BARELY KEEPING
MY HEAD ABOVE WATER.
YOU SHOW UP WITH
A NEW STAINLESS .9.
YOU DON'T REMEMBER
WHERE YOU GOT IT?
I REMEMBER.
YOU DIDN'T
BUY IT FROM ME.
I'M SORRY.
I'VE BEEN CAUGHT UP
IN MY OWN STUFF.
I GOT IT
AT THE GUN FAIR
AT RILEY
THE OTHER DAY.
FORGET IT.
LET'S JUST SHOOT
THESE CANS, ALL RIGHT?
[MAN]  THE BEARDED BANDIT STRUCK AGAIN YESTERDAY,
MAKING THIS THE FOURTH  SUBURBAN BANK HE'S ROBBED.
[WOMAN]
HOW MUCH DID
HE GET AWAY WITH?
THE BANK HASN'T RELEASED THAT FIGURE.
WHY DON'T YOU
HOLD YOUR BREATH
WAITING
FOR THEM TO RELEASE
THAT FIGURE, CHUCK?
NO PRINTS,
NO CONSISTENT FIBERS.
OH, AND THIS TIME,
HE LAID DOWN
SOME GOOP.
SCREWED UP
THE VACUUM CLEANERS.
SMELLS
LIKE OVEN CLEANER.
THE GUY PLANS AHEAD.
HE'LL FUCK UP.
DON'T WE ALL?
YOU ARE REALLY SICK,
YOU KNOW IT?
IS THIS LITTLE
POWER PLAY
GETTING YOU HARD?
COME ON.
OH, SHIT.
O.K., GO ON.
O.K., YOU READY?
THERE.
IT'S OURS.
WOW.
IT'S BOUGHT
AND PAID FOR.
OH, YEAH.
AND THIS.
AAH!
OH, MY GOD.
YEAH. I ORDERED YOU
A WINDSCREEN
SO YOU CAN RIDE
AND YOUR HAIR WON'T
GET ALL TANGLED UP.
COME ON.
MORNING.
BEAUTIFUL DAY.
COME ON.
OH, YEAH.
FILL UP THE BAG
OR DIE.
FILL IT UP NOW.
COME ON.
FILL IT UP!
MOVE. COME ON.
[RADIO PLAYING]
PAM.
THAT FUCKING PUNY,
SHRIMP ASS JERK.
HE THINKS
HE CAN FIRE ME?
MAN,
HE DOESN'T KNOW WHO
HE'S DEALING WITH.
THE KIND OF
FIREPOWER I'VE GOT.
I'M A VERY
GOOD SHOT.
WHAT WILL
I TELL CHRIS?
I PROMISED HIM
I'D MAKE IT WORK.
MAN, FUCK HIM.
PAM,
IF HE KICKS YOU OUT,
YOU COULD ALWAYS
COME STAY WITH ME.
I TELL YOU WHAT.
LET'S GO CELEBRATE.
FOLLOW ME
TO THE VAN.
WOW.
COOL.
I GUESS
THIS IS AN O.K. TIME
TO TELL YOU
I GOT FIRED TODAY.
IT'S AS GOOD
A TIME AS ANY.
LET'S GO HOME.
[ROCK MUSIC PLAYING]
HOW MANY BANKS
HAVE YOU DONE?
TODAY WAS
NUMBER NINE.
I'M GOING TO HELP
WITH NUMBER 10.
NO, YOU'RE NOT.
NO. IT'S
TOO DANGEROUS.
LET ME COME.
YOU DO IT.
I KNOW
WHAT I'M DOING.
OH, I CAN LEARN.
NO.
PLEASE.
NO, PAM.
I'LL BE
YOUR SIDEKICK,
YOUR PARTNER,
YOUR ACCOMPLICE,
YOUR SLAVE, ANYTHING.
PLEASE JUST
LET ME PLAY.
IT'S NOT A GAME.
IT'S ARMED ROBBERY.
YOU DON'T PRACTICE.
LET'S GO.
FILL IT UP.
PUT THE MONEY
IN THE BAG.
COME ON.
I'LL KILL YOU.
PUT IT IN.
PUT THE BAG IN THERE.
GIVE IT TO ME.
LAY DOWN!
YEAH.
WHAT THE HELL
WAS THAT ABOUT?
YOU COULD'VE GOT US
KILLED BACK THERE.
IT WAS
JUST FOR FUN.
PULL OVER.
STAY DOWN.
IF I SAY GO,
YOU GO.
YOU GO!
CHRIS.
WHAT?
DO YOU THINK HE'LL DIE?
NO.
NO, HE WON'T DIE.
I DIDN'T KILL HIM.
I JUST STOPPED HIM.
SHOT HIM
IN THE SHOULDER.
HE'LL BE O.K.
DON'T WORRY.
I'M NOT WORRIED.
IT'S JUST THAT WHEN
SOMETHING LIKE THIS
HAPPENS,
IT'S EASY
TO GET FREAKED OUT.
YOU GET SCARED,
BUT YOU CAN'T LOSE
YOUR MOMENTUM.
YOU GOT TO GET RIGHT
BACK ON THE HORSE.
YOU FALL OFF,
YOU GET BACK ON.
WHAT HORSE?
I THINK WE SHOULD ROB
ANOTHER BANK RIGHT AWAY.
IT'S OVER.
DON'T YOU SEE?
WE'RE HOME FREE.
BILLS ARE PAID.
WE OWN THIS HOUSE.
WE GOT CAPITAL
TO START OUR OWN
BUSINESS.
I SAW A PLACE
THE OTHER DAY
OVER AT HARRIS PARK.
IT HAD
GREAT PARKING,
LOTS OF TRAFFIC.
WE GOT
THE INITIAL STOCK
AND THE FIRST-YEAR
EXPENSES COVERED.
PAM?
HOW CAN YOU QUIT?
ONCE YOU'RE INTO IT,
HOW CAN YOU STOP?
IT'S THE WAY
IT'S GOT TO BE.
THE TIME COMES,
YOU JUST WALK AWAY.
SINCE HE SHOT
ONE OF THEIR OWN,
THE LOCALS HAVE
A REAL HARD-ON
FOR THIS GUY.
WE HAVE THEIR FULL
COOPERATION.
GOOD. FROM NOW ON,
ALL REPORTS
ON STOLEN
LATE-MODEL IMPORTS
WILL BE CHANNELED
THROUGH THIS OFFICE.
WE FIND ONE
OF HIS WORK CARS,
WE STAKE IT OUT,
WE NAIL HIM.
DRAMA.
UH, PUT THOSE
WITH LITERATURE.
SHIT, MAN.
THIS STUFF WEIGHS MORE
THAN FIREARMS.
WATCH THIS.
YOU WANT TO TRY?
OH, COME ON.
THERE'S ONLY ONE BULLET.
THAT'S GOOD ODDS,
OR BAD, DEPENDING.
WHAT'S GOTTEN
INTO YOU, CHRIS?
YOU USED TO BE FUN.
FUCK YOU IF
YOU CAN'T TAKE A JOKE.
HEY, CHRIS.
HANK.
I HARDLY RECOGNIZED YOU.
SO THIS IS
YOUR STORE, HUH?
YEAH, IT FIGURES.
YEAH.
HOW'S IT DOING?
UH, IT'S DOING GOOD.
WHY DON'T YOU COME
IN AND TAKE A LOOK?
ALL RIGHT.
SO, HOW'S THE COP BUSINESS?
MY WIFE'S ON ME TO
DO SOMETHING ELSE.
SHE KEEPS
DREAMING ME DEAD.
I TELL HER
IT'S NOT LIKE THIS
IS L.A. OR DETROIT,
BUT EVER SINCE
THAT COP GOT SHOT--
OVER IN WALES?
I HEARD SOMETHING
ABOUT THAT.
HOW'S HE DOING?
HE'S GOT USE
OF THE ARM,
BUT HOW O.K.
CAN YOU BE WITH
SOMETHING LIKE THAT?
ANYWAY,
GOOD TO SEE YOU.
LET ME BUY A BOOK.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO.
NO, REALLY.
I NEED ONE.
I'M ON A STAKEOUT.
WHAT'S GOOD?
TRY THIS. ON THE HOUSE.
REALLY?
THANKS.
WHAT IS IT, MYSTERY?
IN A WAY.
IT'S GOOD.
[RADIO PLAYS]
HI.
SELF-HELP?
IT'S DOWN TO THE RIGHT.
HI. THIS IS CHRIS AND PAM.
AT THE SOUND OF THE BEEP,
LEAVE A MESSAGE. BYE.
[DIALS]
YOU HAVE NO NEW MESSAGES.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
ALL RIGHT,
ALL RIGHT.
WHO IS IT?
I'M LOOKING FOR PAM.
YOU MUST BE CHRIS.
CAN WE TAKE A WALK?
I'M LEAVING YOU.
I'VE LEFT,
AND I'M NOT COMING BACK.
WHY?
WHAT, YOU'RE
LEAVING ME FOR HER?
WHAT DOES SHE HAVE
TO DO WITH ANYTHING?
WELL,
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
IF YOU DON'T
LOVE ME, PAM,
YOU'RE GOING
TO HAVE TO SAY SO.
I DON'T LOVE YOU ANYMORE.
WHY ARE YOU
DOING THIS TO ME?
CHRIS, YOU'RE BETTER OFF.
JUST GO.
YOU DON'T NEED ME.
EVERYTHING
THAT I'VE DONE
I DID FOR YOU.
I ROBBED THOSE BANKS
SO WE COULD
HAVE A LIFE.
SO WE COULD HAVE
OUR OWN LIFE.
WHY CAN'T YOU
LOVE ME?
COME HOME WITH ME?
CHRIS,
YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND.
MAKE ME UNDERSTAND,
PAM.
CHRIS, I CAN'T
HANG IN THERE ANYMORE.
I CAN'T DO IT.
I AM NOT
A NORMAL PERSON.
YOU CAN HAVE A LIFE.
YOU'RE GOOD AT IT.
YOU'VE GOT THE BOOKSTORE
AND YOUR CUSTOMERS,
AND THE NEIGHBORS
TALK TO YOU,
AND EVERYTHING'S FINE,
AND INSIDE I AM DYING
IN PIECES.
IF I'M GOING TO BE ALIVE,
I'M GOING
TO BE REALLY ALIVE.
IF I'M GOING TO BE DEAD,
I WANT TO BE DEAD.
SOMETIMES I THINK
THAT DEAD IS BETTER.
IT DOESN'T MATTER.
LOOK, WHATEVER.
JUST DON'T LEAVE ME.
JUST GO.
GO!
GO! GO!
GO WHERE? DO WHAT?
LEAVE ME ALONE.
I'M JUST TRYING
TO DO WHAT'S RIGHT
FOR ONCE.
YOU DON'T KNOW
WHAT'S RIGHT.
YOU'RE MY WIFE,
AND YOU PROMISED ME!
FOREVER YOU SAID!
YOU SAID FOREVER!
DON'T BE ANGRY
AT ME.
I LOVE YOU SO MUCH.
I'M NOT ANGRY.
JUST DON'T LEAVE ME.
DON'T EVER LEAVE ME.
THE STAR SHOW
IS ABOUT TO BEGIN.
PLEASE TAKE YOUR SEATS.
MAN ONCE BELIEVED
THAT THE STARS
WERE UNCHANGING.
IN THE MAJESTIC MARCH
OF THE CONSTELLATIONS
ACROSS THE NIGHT SKY,
HUMANKIND SAW AN IDEAL
OF ETERNAL PEACEFULNESS
AND ORDER.
TODAY WE KNOW
THAT LIKE THE UNIVERSE
ITSELF,
STARS ARE BORN
AND THEY DIE
IN CATACLYSMS
OF UNBELIEVABLE VIOLENCE.
[EXPLOSION]
LOCK AND LOAD.
YOU READY?
TIME TO GO.
COME ON.
THAT'S IT.
STAND BY FOR MY SIGNAL.
GO ON, CHAOS. GO ON.
FBI! DON'T MOVE!
YOU'RE UNDER ARREST!
[SIRENS]
IN PURSUIT
OF BLUE DODGE VAN.
ILLINOIS PLATE NUMBER--
SHOTS FIRED!
[INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER]
THE FBI!
THROW OUT YOUR WEAPONS!
COME OUT OF YOUR VEHICLE!
PUT YOUR HANDS
OVER YOUR HEAD!
YOU HAVE 10 SECONDS!
ENOUGH TIME
TO CREATE A UNIVERSE.
[GUNSHOT]
IN YOUR DEPOSITION OF, UH...
I DIRECT
THE COURT'S ATTENTION
TO PAGE 67
OF THE WITNESS'S STATEMENT
OF OCTOBER 19th,
WHEREIN YOU WERE TOLD
BY WITNESSES
TO THE ROBBERY IN QUESTION
OF THREATS THAT WERE MADE.
YOU WERE
DESCRIBING STATEMENTS
THAT THE WITNESS...
SHE'S LOSING THEM.
I WOULD ASK YOU
TO DESCRIBE FOR THE COURT
STATEMENTS THAT YOU KNOW
THAT FROM WITNESSES
THAT YOU HAVE SPOKEN WITH
THAT THE ROBBER MADE
DURING THE COURSE
OF THIS ROBBERY.
I REFER SPECIFICALLY
TO YOUR STATEMENTS...
FROM THE BACK,
SHE LOOKS
JUST LIKE MY PAM.
THIS IS THE MORNING
OF SEPTEMBER 30th--
[JUDGE]
WE'LL RESUME
TOMORROW MORNING, 9:00.
CHRIS, YOU WERE
GREAT TODAY.
YOU'RE GOING
TO GET OFF.
WHAT'S THE QUICKEST WAY
TO THE CEMETERY?
FROM HERE?
TIME TO GO.
CHRIS...
CHRIS.
SEE YOU TOMORROW.
[DING]
HE'S GOT MY GUN!
HELP!
PAM!
[GUNSHOT]
♪ I HAVE THIS DREAM
♪ IT'S INVOLVING
YOU AND ME ♪
♪ IT GROWS AND BREATHES
♪ CHANGING EVERY DAY
♪ RIGHT TO THE END
♪ AND EVERY TIME AGAIN
♪ REAL
♪ MY KIND OF CRIMINAL
♪ COULD IT BE
♪ YOU DON'T TRY
TO UNDERSTAND?♪
♪ HOW COULD IT BE?
♪ YOU SHOULD
REALLY COMPREHEND ♪
♪ HOW COULD IT BE?
♪ I WON'T GIVE IN
TO YOUR DEMANDS ♪
♪ REAL
♪ MY KIND OF CRIMINAL
♪ COME ON, LET'S DANCE
♪ YOU TELL ME NO OFFENSE
♪ MY GENOCIDE
♪ RIGHT BETWEEN THE EYES
♪ WHY DO I STRAIN?
♪ MY TEARS WASH DOWN
THE DRAIN ♪
♪ STAND BACK AWAY
♪ LISTEN TO WHAT YOU SAY
♪ IT'S GOT TO GO
♪ AND I THINK
YOU SHOULD KNOW ♪
♪ REAL
♪ MY KIND OF CRIMINAL
♪ COULD IT BE
♪ YOU DON'T TRY
TO UNDERSTAND? ♪
♪ HOW COULD IT BE?
♪ YOU SHOULD REALLY
COMPREHEND ♪
♪ HOW COULD IT BE?
♪ I WON'T GIVE IN
TO YOUR DEMANDS ♪
♪ REAL
♪ MY KIND OF CRIMINAL
♪ EVERYBODY'S SO IN LOVE
♪ BUT THEY DON'T TOUCH
OR MEET ♪
♪ EYES ARE WEEPING
♪ EYES ARE RED
♪ BUNCH OF FLOWERS
IN THE STREET ♪
♪ I LOVE A MILLIONAIRE
♪ THE CHAMPAGNE
WAS NEVER CHEAP ♪
♪ BUT I COULD PAY SOMEONE
♪ TO DRINK IT FOR ME
♪ NEVER RISE UP
FROM THESE SHEETS ♪
♪ WATCHING TIME
JUST ROLL AWAY ♪
♪ I LOVE A MILLIONAIRE
♪ STRETCHING OUT MY BONES
♪ A MILLION MILES
FROM HOME ♪
♪ LUST CORRODES MY BODY
♪ I'VE LOST COUNT
OF MY LOVERS ♪
♪ BUT I CAN COUNT MY MONEY
♪ FOREVER AND FOREVER
♪ I LOVE A MILLIONAIRE