[man] Where are you?
The Masi tree.
The Masi tree
The love inside me
Will set you free
When I don't define love
By the Masi tree.
I look everywhere and see
I look everywhere and ask myself
- "Is it just a nightmare?"
- [shutters clicking]
Dreamless dreamers
There are no stars here
There are doors that open
To a place behind the sky
But the computer
Catches fire inside rainbows
As all the lovers dance
And completely disappear.
Lovers.
Dreamed?
It's early. What time is it?
It doesn't matter.
- Do you love my shoulders?
- [chuckles softly]
Yes.
What part of my body
do you love the most?
- My feet?
- Mm-hmm.
My back?
My hair? My nose? My lips?
Everything.
Everything?
Mm-hmm.
[woman]
Forever his inspiration
We've always been a team
But the artist is nothing
Without his muse
[shutter clicks]
He sees
the beauty of life in my eyes
[shutter clicks]
It's all a beautiful confusion.
- [shutter clicking]
- Are you going to be like this?
You think it's interesting?
What is this face?
Again, look at me.
Don't move.
I didn't do anything at all.
Look at me.
I can't photograph your soul.
I can photograph
your space in a way.
Uh, it's...
something with
your body language.
The way that you move.
[woman]
But the artist is nothing
Without his muse
[man] Marker.
- [man 2] Set.
- [man] Good.
And... Action.
[host] You know,
I've seen everything
Taschen has put out this year.
It's good.
Thank you.
[chuckles softly]
How hard was it for you to find
and decide on the photographs
you wanted to collect
- and use for your book?
- Hmm.
Are you fed up
with celebrity life?
It wasn't hard at all.
I never liked celebrity culture.
And I think...
I think there are a lot
of talented people that I like.
I mean, I love to know
about the people
who create things because, um,
it helps me to understand
the things that they create.
[woman] The butterfly
Who fell in love with the bee
We... We stand-in lovers
Dancing blissfully
In cerulean skies
The one who always flutters
Wandering wild
Wishing on endlessly to be free
And the other
Bumbling, busy
Laden
Over-pollinated with love.
Fragile patterns pricked apart
By reckless lovers
All for art.
["La Femme Flamme"
by Mort Rose playing]
♪ J'ai pas grand-chose
under my skin ♪
♪ Un frame de alley cat avec un
beau sourire ♪
♪ Juste 3000 de marge
sur ma Visa ♪
♪ Et le poids du monde sur mes
épaules pour te faire jouir ♪
♪ Mais ton soul est mon âme,
on les attache together ♪
♪ Regarde-moi dans le feu,
je brûle mon coeur ♪
♪ Ah, mon amour ♪
♪ C'était vraiment
la bonne chose à faire ♪
♪ Moi le coeur gelé,
ma vie un éternel hiver ♪
♪ La femme flamme,
t'as soudé nos âmes ♪
♪ Jamais, pour vrai,
j'aurais pensé ♪
♪ C'était vraiment
la bonne chose à faire ♪
♪ Moi le coeur gelé,
ma vie un fuckin' long hiver ♪
♪ Bébé, que toi pis moi ♪
[photographer] What did you
do today?
- [woman] Did some video work.
- [photographer] Mm-hmm.
- [woman] Did you miss me?
- I did.
[woman]
How much did you miss me?
[photographer] A lot.
[woman] Tell me I'm beautiful.
You are beautiful.
Dance with me.
Dance with you?
Where? Here?
[both laugh]
[photographer]
I can't dance. Come on.
Am I your favorite girl
to photograph?
Hmm. You're my...
You're my favorite girl.
[woman] I want
to know who you are.
You still don't know?
Not always sure.
I don't know
what's going on in here
when you look at me like that.
I don't know
what's going on in there.
What are you thinking about?
[sighs] A lot of things.
Weird things.
Tell me I am your favorite
girl to photograph.
You're my favorite girl.
[woman whispers] I love you.
Have you changed
since your beginning?
I don't think in those terms.
I think photography
has changed a lot
in this last 15 years,
especially with
the digital things.
Anyone can take pictures now,
but what I can say is... [sighs]
...I don't take pictures.
I make pictures.
Your father was a famous painter
in the 1980s.
He died at only 30 years old.
How did his art influence you?
I have a great admiration
for what he did as an artist.
[father] Photographing faces is
more complex than landscapes.
You can't act afraid, Nicolas.
You must be in control.
- Excuse me.
- Hi.
Would you be okay with my kid
taking a picture of you?
[chuckles softly]
Of course.
- [pulls the cocking lever]
- Go ahead.
[shutter clicks]
[pulls the cocking lever]
[woman] You going to be
a photographer when you grow up?
Take pictures of things
that inspire you.
If you see something beautiful,
or something that catches
your eye, then go for it.
Don't hold back.
What inspires you?
- [soft piano music]
- That music right there.
[chuckles]
[laughs]
[woman] I love you the most.
[Nicolas] Do you want me
to say it to you?
- Yes. Say it to me.
- [chuckles]
[both chuckle]
[Nicolas] No.
[both moaning]
[heavy breathing]
You know, what can an artist do
to grow creatively?
To... evolve?
[Nicolas] Everyone has to find
their own path.
And what's your path?
It's a constant struggle
with oneself.
Um...
I love you.
[woman] Do you believe in fate?
[man] Only when everything
good happens to me.
[woman laughs]
[laughing continues]
- [woman] Kiss me.
- [man] I am gonna kiss you.
[woman] Give me a kiss.
Stop teasing me.
- [man] Am I?
- [woman laughs] Yes, you are.
We missed you today.
Had a really good time
with Matilda.
- [Nicolas] Yeah?
- Yeah.
We talked about going to Brazil.
- [Nicolas] Oh, yeah?
- Yeah.
- [Nicolas] Brazil.
- Yes, yes, yes. [sighs]
I'd love to surf the waves
out there, man. [chuckles]
Life.
I mean, everything
has an influence on me.
Women, men. You. Um...
You have to steal
because if you don't steal,
you cannot really do it.
I mean, there are people who
think that they are original,
but, um...
they are not.
I'm curious about your portrait
of the famous writer,
Terry Collins.
You... You bring
something new of him.
Uh... [chuckles]
A coolness
I've never seen before.
What is it that you put
from your personality
into your images?
Nothing is personal, Nicolas.
[Nicolas]
Everything is personal.
Every moment of
my existence is personal.
- I'm a person.
- I've worked with you
since you were 17,
and this is ridiculous.
Maybe you need a vacation.
How do you feel?
Don't lie to me, Nicolas.
And everything is bullshit.
I am trying to help you.
You know you are my number one.
Our number one.
The world sees fashion's
superficial.
It's a strange world
of business, you know?
Do you know how many copies
my book sold?
The client was unhappy
with your last...
- Fuck the client.
- But we have to work
with these people.
It's part of the job.
They want something new.
They said
your photographs were...
Were too dark.
Not enough colors.
They wanted to have fun.
They said your photographs don't
pop like they used to.
You were a thousand miles away.
You need a creative reset.
I don't know. Take Matilda
to Europe or something.
Try something new.
Yeah, I don't need your help.
Do you really believe
you're at the top of your game?
- Fuck it.
- Okay, we're done here.
Great.
Can you define what you do?
No. I don't want to define
what I do,
and I don't like to define
what I'm doing.
Um...
I create. That's it.
So what's your next project?
I'm still working on it,
but you'll be the first to know.
Do you even have
another project?
[director] Here we go.
Quiet, please. Thank you.
[indistinct chatter]
[director] Roll sound.
Thank you.
[indistinct chatter]
[woman] Sam's meeting you.
[moving lips silently]
[male narrator on TV]
Butterflies usually attempt
to accumulate around
the base of the tongue.
They don't hold
their tongue too straight
like other types of flies.
They curl it and...
even more remarkably.
They can put a sharp bend in it.
These butterflies
have got pollen,
not necessarily on its tongue,
but all over
its pretty legs as well.
[birds chirping on TV]
[Cassandra] You once called me
your "Eternal Tiger."
[Nicolas] Cassandra
was my greatest love.
[Cassandra]
These flowers will fade
and wilt,
our love...
will not.
[Nicolas]
We both thought we would
spend our eternity
just together.
- [wind blowing]
- [rustling]
[Cassandra] I think
dreams do come true.
If you believe...
I'll never leave you Nicolas.
[Nicolas] Her actions
eventually altered
parts of my subconscious.
[Cassandra] I do feel
dreams come true.
I do.
[Nicolas] And changed the way
I view relationships.
[Cassandra]
I just showed you exactly
what our relationship is.
I hate who I become
when I'm with you.
I can't live with you anymore.
So here we are...
wasting my fucking time,
wasting my life away with you.
I feel like I'm suffocating
in this relationship.
Suffocating!
[inhales deeply]
[speaks softly]
Yes, I fucked him.
I fucked him.
So, it's finding balance
between, um, life and art.
Honesty always
gets my attention.
Not particularly someone
who is honest to me,
but someone who is honest
with himself.
[both chuckle]
I'm very proud of you, you know?
Hmm.
Take it in. I'm...
I'm really proud of you.
Yeah, but still,
I want to be something more.
I'm lost, man.
What do you mean by that?
But I want to be free
when I create.
Mm-hmm.
- Free yourself.
- How?
Let go...
[laughs] ...have fun?
- Do you remember what happened?
- Mm-hmm.
You became a photographer.
You were obsessed
with taking pictures.
I envied that, man.
I really did.
- I know.
- I do.
- It's not enough.
There's a fashion bubble
that needs to be burst.
Fashion photography
holds me down.
What do you mean?
I don't know.
I feel like a liar in a way.
I get it, man. I do.
- You know?
- It's crazy.
Just...
You got to find it in you,
you know?
That's the tough part.
- Impossible.
- [both laugh]
I was never interested in people
who doesn't do anything
at the end of the day,
and just wears high heels
and spends too much time
in front of a mirror.
I don't know
what you're talking about.
[chuckles]
I have to be completely honest
with you.
I need to know
how you grind your beans.
[both laugh]
I just taste your beans, coffee.
[slurps]
[woman] How do you feel
about being unfaithful?
What do you want me to admit?
Unfaithful is just a word.
- Tell me.
- This coffee is shit.
What do you mean?
[Nicolas] The truth
is my life, but...
sometimes I just want to escape
and be alone, you know?
[man] I think that's normal.
I mean that
there are no meanings
and words are just words...
where it's like...
relationships.
Love. Marriage.
Unfaithful, cheating.
[no audio]
Fucking.
[speaks softly]
Yes, I fucked him.
[woman] Why do you put up
with these antics?
[woman] I fucked you.
[host] Don't you see
how empty all of this is?
How empty you are.
How was the party?
It was good.
You came home late.
-It was a good party,
-Did Cedric have fun?
I think so.
Did you call your mother back?
I think it'd be good if she
stayed with us
for a couple of days.
I'd like to get
to know her better
and last time she came
it was a bit weird.
Weird?
I didn't know it was a problem
for you to speak to your mother.
Why are you shutting me
out of your life?
What do you mean?
This is life.
Mm.
Is this the last gasp
of a dying artist?
[woman] Do you believe in fate?
[Cedric] Are you serious?
[laughs]
If I'm honest.
Which I try to be.
[woman laughs]
Only when everything good
happens to me.
[woman chuckling]
Hey.
Do you want some coffee?
[crying]
[sniffles]
[breathes deeply]
[cell phone vibrating]
- It's Serena.
- Tell her I said hi.
Hey, Serena.
[woman] I am gonna
get ready for work.
I'll be right back.
[sobs]
He went for a wave, and...
he went down, and he...
[no audio]
- [seagulls screeching]
- [water gushing]
[Nicolas]
Do you remember Sophie?
[Cedric] Who?
I don't know.
[both laugh hysterically]
No, no. Can we be
serious for a moment
because it's really important?
- I need to tell you.
- Yeah, I am listening.
You are?
Yeah?
- Sophie.
- Mm-hmm.
- Paul's mom?
- Oh, yeah.
Paul's mom, man.
- [laughing hysterically]
- Yeah.
- Paul's mom. Fuck.
- Paul's mom, dude.
- She was hot.
What?
It's just that...
I don't know.
I mean,
she kind of looks like Paul.
- [laughs]
- She does?
Yeah, a little bit, I mean...
- Yeah.
- No, she doesn't.
- No.
- [Cedric] But tell me about it.
I got... I got the no.
[Cedric] Ah.
The greatest sadness
is not being able to kiss
an invisible woman.
[mouth moving wordlessly]
We cannot touch it.
[chuckles]
I think we should go.
- Where's the key?
- You know where key is?
I don't know.
You were just driving.
[Nicolas crying] Sorry.
I am so sorry.
You look so much
like your father.
Why don't you come with me to
New York for a couple of days?
We talked about that, remember?
And it's not a good idea.
Why?
Because it's not.
I'm loving you.
I care about you.
You mean everything to me.
And I don't have anything else.
- [voice breaks] I am sorry.
- Okay.
- [cries] I love you.
- Me too.
I don't want to be without you.
Look... Okay, come here
[speaking indistinctly]
Take care.
[crying continues]
I can't believe
I'm never going to see Cedric
walking over here again.
Nothing means anything anymore.
I know.
This is fucking chaos.
[speaks softly]
Please don't leave me.
I won't.
- I can't do this all alone.
- [speaks softly] I know.
I know.
[knock on door]
[woman] What's wrong?
[Nicolas] Everything's wrong.
[woman] What do you mean
everything?
I want you...
to fuck...
You're home.
[sniffles]
I love you.
It's okay to be lost.
[Matilda] My dispirited lover
Your patterns
Are fading.
I'm wandering
Wistful
Nicolas
Where are...
Thank you.
I feel pretty good.
[woman]
Is something bothering you?
- [Nicolas clears throat]
- [woman] Photoshoot was crazy.
You argued with the clients.
You left the studio.
It was very awkward
between you and the model.
[Nicolas] How is your life?
Are you still in love?
It's complicated.
[chuckles]
We still love each other, but...
Come on.
[model] something is broken.
[Nicolas] Look at me.
- So what?
- [shutter clicks]
Clients are usually uptight.
What happened?
Well, you need
to impose yourself just...
take control
and don't give a shit.
[woman] Don't be so aggressive,
Nicolas.
[Nicolas] Don't move.
[Cassandra] You're just gonna
stare at me and judge me, right?
That's... That's your position.
How do you live like this?
[model] Yes, he seems
to be changing now.
You know, I don't care anymore.
I have been disrespected
for a long time.
[Nicolas] Okay, that's good.
Move up. Are you afraid of me?
- Maybe you let me out.
- [Nicolas] Are you scared?
Oh, I hit a nerve.
[shutter clicking]
You okay? [sniffles]
[model] You are so mean to me.
Fuck off Nicolas
you fucking little brat.
You're fucking selfish.
[model] Do you have any secrets?
[Nicolas sniffles,
clears throat]
You make me sick!
[Nicolas]
This is not what I want.
Do something new.
I have seen this.
Don't touch me.
I don't wanna shoot
with you anymore.
You're making me crazy.
[model]
Don't touch me.
[Cassandra]
How do you live like this?
[model]
Let me out...
[chuckles]
Aren't you afraid
that people are going to see
what a fraud you are?
You know what I see?
Fear.
You waltz in here...
like you're
some kind of magician.
Hey.
[clatter]
Hey, what are you doing?
You're pretending to ask me
what am I doing,
but the real question is,
why am I doing it?
Right?
Why I am working?
Yeah?
Because I can.
I am sorry. I am sorry.
Let's drink wine and make love.
I'm gonna go outside first
and get some air.
[Nicolas] No.
- Nicolas, stop now.
- No.
You're hurting me.
Shh.
Please.
Hey...
Something you can fix.
Hit me.
No?
You like that?
I break things.
You clean up.
No? You don't like it?
Okay.
I don't want to irritate you,
but you're an artist.
You write poems. You are good.
Yeah, so?
You can't even
believe yourself now.
You want to teach me
how to live my life?
how to survive?
Go ahead. Come on.
Come on. You believe
that you are better than me?
You are not better than me.
Forget about us.
We don't exist.
Get out of my face.
- Fuck you, Matilda.
- Hey!
Fuck you!
You know what it is, Nicolas?
You're afraid.
And you can't even see it
because you're so arrogant.
Fucking look at yourself
right now!
I am sorry.
Stop it.
- Don't fucking touch me.
- Fuck off.
Get out.
Go. Let me work now.
It's 8:00AM!
[whimpers]
Stop it.
[exhales heavily]
[sniffles, sighs]
[woman] Are you daydreaming?
You don't know shit.
When are you going
to get fucking real?
And you better get real,
fucking fast.
[woman shouting indistinctly]
[urinating]
[flush]
Matilda.
[cell phone ringing]
Hello?
Matilda?
[telephone ringing]
Are you Nicolas Yarna?
Are you wondering
where Matilda is?
I'll ask you a final time.
Are you wondering
where Matilda is?
- Do I have your attention?
- Yes.
Meet me at the Hotel Vista Tide
at 9 p.m.
Room 1009.1009.
The door will be open.
Do you understand?
What the fuck is this?
Did you hear something?
[door opens]
- [telephone ringing]
- [door closes]
[ringing continues]
Where is Matilda?
[woman] Good, you can
follow instructions.
[Nicolas]
Where is she?
You keep asking
the wrong questions.
Besides, anticipation
is the greatest pleasure.
If you don't tell me
where Matilda is, I'm going to...
Do tell, Mr. Yarna.
What are you going to do?
That's the sound of a man
realizing he's not in control.
[Nicolas] Who is this
and what do you want?
Where is she?
Is she okay?
When things
start to feel strange,
you should stop and check
your surroundings.
[woman hangs up the phone]
[woman's voice in Nicolas' head]
When things start
to feel strange,
you should stop and check
your surroundings.
[woman] It's a lovely dress.
Unfortunately she wore it
under those circumstances.
Are you wondering
where Matilda is?
Do I have your attention?
[bees buzzing]
[cell phone ringing]
[Nicolas] Yes?
[woman] Don't worry.
It's easy to lose
when it's weighing us down.
Darkness extinguishes light.
They can coexist.
The light has left you.
Do you know where she is?
She's lost.
[door closes]
[woman]
All luminescence, eventually,
fades to this.
Are you daydreaming?
[woman] I know
what you dream at night.
I don't ever want
to hear your voice again.
[jazz music playing]
I apologize.
You were looking for
some peace and quiet.
It's okay.
I haven't seen you here before.
It's the first time.
I spend too much time here.
Did you know the only part of
the human body
that requires sleep
is the brain?
You can... run,
walk, fuck...
twenty-four hours a day.
Just the brain
that can't keep up.
I'm most tired when I travel.
I'm so excited to leave. But...
when I arrive at my destination,
it's my brain.
There's a tough time adapting.
I'm Hannah.
Nicolas.
It's nice to meet you.
You too.
May I tell you a story?
It's funny, I promise.
When I was 16,
there was this 31 year old
that I was dating.
On a trip to Norway,
we found this small town
surrounded by 100 tiny lakes.
All of a sudden, I...
I felt the urge to make love
with him for the first time.
I was still a virgin.
That part of the forest
was dangerous
because there was a species
of man-eating wolves.
I undressed...
he entered inside of me,
and we were
waving our flashlights
and making all these
strange noises
so that the wolves
would stay away.
[chuckles]
I dream about that sometimes
when I'm making love
to other men.
And when it happens, I...
have to stop having sex.
[scoffs]
Because my burst
of laughter goes on
without ever coming
to a stop. [chuckles]
[both chuckle]
I'm going to go for a swim.
[Hannah chuckles softly]
[Hannah] You have a secret.
I'm psychic.
Relax, you can tell me.
Relax.
- We all have them.
- [Nicolas] I've lost something.
Something or someone?
My girlfriend, she's gone.
She's left you
or she's gone missing?
I'm at the hotel because I
got a strange phone call.
I hoped it was Matilda.
Who was it?
[Nicolas] I was beginning
to think it was you.
[Hannah laughs]
No, that's too cruel.
Even for me.
I went to this room
and I got a call...
but it was cryptic.
[Hannah]
And you have no other clues?
Nothing.
That there's nothing
to be gained by being here?
You coming?
[beep]
[door lock clicks]
I have the package
for Mr. Yorke.
You are an hour late.
[Hannah] I understand that.
I'm sorry.
He's here to learn.
No more mistakes.
[man scrubbing an object]
[knock on door]
- Hello.
- Thomas.
This is my new friend, Nicolas.
Nicolas.
My name is Thomas.
How about a drink?
Scotch, bourbon, rye?
Soda pop?
[Nicolas] Are you having
a glass of scotch?
Maybe.
Come in.
Sit down.
I've missed talking to you
in person.
When did you get back
from India?
India?
Uh, about a week ago, I think.
I was there for six months.
India.
Have to go back in January.
[speaks softly] Thank you.
- Nicolas.
- Thank you.
And where are you from?
I was born in Naples, but when I
was ten, I moved to New York.
Um-hmm.
Where are you now?
I'm in Los Angeles.
Where are you?
Don't you mean I just told you?
Was New York stressful to you?
Uh, no.
Uh, I like to change.
I used to travel a lot.
Nicolas is a photographer.
So you're an artist. Ah.
So you're an artist.
I'm interested in people.
[scoffs softly]
What are you most afraid of?
I don't need to be
analyzed right now,
but thank you for your interest.
Uh, are you afraid to see
who you really are?
Is it because you are afraid
to see who you are?
Strange.
I see you're
interested in people,
but you are cut off
from yourself.
Living and dying.
Identical twins in the Matrix.
Shadow and light.
Light and shadow.
You know how that feels,
don't you, Nicolas?
- Excuse me.
- [Thomas chuckles]
If I say childhood,
what comes to mind?
[Hannah] I think
it's time to go.
- [Nicolas] What?
- [Thomas] I think you heard me.
[Hannah] That's enough.
We're going.
This was a mistake. Sorry.
Good night.
Wicked people of the night.
[door opens]
[whispers] Mr. Yorke
doesn't like it
when his plans change.
[Thomas] Wicked
people of the night.
[birds chirping]
[Nicolas] I'm beginning to...
forget the shape of your face...
Where am I?
I hear things...
you once said to me.
Spoken.
By unfamiliar faces.
[woman] We're alive when we
just fall from the sky.
[Cedric] It was
an almost perfect wave.
I got this feeling,
this rush, like...
I was a part of everything.
You know,
I didn't exist anymore.
And I froze.
Time stood still.
[woman] What shape is your heart
when it's really, really broken?
There is no shape.
Because it's an illusion...
until you know you are...
Why do you feel life is strange
when it gets really strange?
What if I fail?
[woman] We loved.
From hate.
Stop it. Don't fucking touch me.
And because
we set things on fire.
What if... I took it
and it was the ride of my life?
I knew I'd never
have that chance again.
[Matilda] Where are you?
- It's okay to be lost.
- [voice echoes]
[Nicolas] Where is she?
[woman speaking indistinctly]
When things start
to feel strange...
you should probably stop
and check your surroundings.
Hannah.
Is she dead?
[Nicolas sighs]
I know her.
I have been working with her.
You are the woman on the phone.
I want the truth
It's your turn now.
[Nicolas] Who do you
think you're fooling?
I mean,
what is all this charade?
The least you can do
is be honest with me.
Where's Matilda?
[detective] I don't know.
[Nicolas] Since I saw you
in that black and white movie,
my life was unraveled.
[Hannah]
What are you talking about?
[Nicolas] I don't know.
Do I need a lawyer?
[detective] Only guilty people
need lawyers.
Never mind about her.
[Thomas] Shadow and light.
[detective]
Take care of yourself.
- [Thomas] Light and shadow.
- [detective] Now.
[Thomas]
Identical twins in the Matrix.
[host] You know what I see?
Fear.
I see a scared little shot.
You know shit
and you better get real fast.
[detective] Let me guess.
You have never seen the victim
before your in your life, right?
What's your relationship
to Hannah?
There's a hell
of a lot you don't know.
When was the last time
you saw her?
You're that pretty boy
fashion photographer,
aren't you?
You're the one that
takes all those pictures
of that gorgeous girls for
Details magazine, am I right?
You hate Details?
[chuckles]
No.
I've read about you.
Seen all your interviews.
Talking about the truth
like you intended.
So I got to look people in
the eye, criminals, thieves,
liars, degenerates.
I got to look for the truth
in their eyes,
day in, day out.
Usually, I don't find it...
but every so often.
I see the truth...
and I know it.
So I'll tell you what.
Why don't we start this again...
and you give me some
of that truth for a change, huh?
You're a photographer.
You think you see the truth,
but you don't.
Your camera sees it.
I don't got no fancy camera.
Now get the fuck out of here.
Go.
Oh, one more thing.
[scoffs softly]
Aren't you afraid
that people are going to see
what a fraud you are?
[male narrator on TV]
Butterflies usually attempt
to accumulate around
the base of the tongue.
They don't hold
their tongue too straight
like other types of flies.
They...
These butterflies have got...
not necessarily on its tongue,
but all over
its pretty legs as well.
[speaking Greek]
"Know thyself,
for thou knowest his power:
- then put on a new mind."
- [knock on door]
[glass breaks]
[Nicolas] Where is Matilda?
[woman] You keep asking
the wrong questions.
It's a lovely dress.
[Nicolas] Where are you now?
Where are you?
[door bell chimes]
[door closes]
Hello, Nicolas. [chuckles]
When was the last time
you heard Matilda's voice?
What the fuck
is going on, Hannah?
No, you... I am Kate.
You met my sister, Hannah.
Your sister?
My twin. [chuckles softly]
Do I really look
better on the telephone?
I don't know what to believe.
[jazz music playing]
- Did Hannah kill Margaret, then?
- [scoffs]
[laughs] No, don't be silly.
I don't know what's real.
But when was the last time
you heard Matilda's voice?
Do you want to hear it?
Do you want to?
There's one thing
you need to know.
- [slams the table] Where is she?
- No, okay.
Your emotions. [sighs]
They mean nothing to me.
I want you to play this.
- [click]
- [Matilda] I told you
not to try to find me.
- I'm sorry.
- [click]
[slams the table]
Take me to her.
I know what you're thinking.
[car doors close]
So, who is he?
Someone she fell in love with?
Someone she's fucking?
Nicolas, did you
ever really love her?
Think about it.
Hey! Nicolas, give me
your fucking money.
- [Kate] Calm down.
- Shut up.
[gunshot]
[flies buzzing]
[Thomas] The love inside me...
will set you free
when I don't define love.
I look everywhere and see.
I look everywhere
and ask myself...
Hey.
I feel pretty good.
[Thomas] Where are you now?
You say you're
interested in people,
but you are cut off
from yourself.
[woman] Who is this man?
He's not even
supposed to be here.
[Thomas] Where are you?
Dreamless dreamers.
There are no stars here.
There are doors that open
to a place behind the sky.
As all the lovers dance...
and completely disappear.
[Matilda]
Nicolas, where are you?
[Thomas] Dreamless dreamers.
There are no stars here.
[Matilda]
Nicolas, where are you?
[fire crackling]
Why did you save me?
I don't decide.
God put you in my way.
He who fights.
That is my name.
Do you ever think about death?
When I was at war,
death was all around.
[Nicolas] I'm afraid of death.
But I'm afraid
of everything, really.
Fear... is always there.
I no longer waste my time
learning about things
I have no control over.
[Nicolas] I had a girlfriend.
But I was lost and unhappy.
And when I felt her love,
I was ashamed.
So she disappeared.
I don't know where to go.
[man] But you have
known all along.
[birds chirping]
[Matilda] Nicolas.
Stop the car.
Matilda!
Tell me what's going on.
You hurt? Are you okay?
Matilda!
Where are we?
I can't explain.
Weird things happened to me.
[Matilda] Yeah,
that was the plan.
What plan?
I almost got killed by a man.
You were saying that
it was part of the plan?
I almost got killed by a man,
and it was part of the plan?
Are you crazy?
- I did it for you.
- For me?
I know it's crazy.
Okay? I had to do something.
You are destroying yourself.
I did it for you.
I don't know who you are.
I know it's crazy.
It's a crazy fucking plan.
But what the fuck
did you expect me to do?
Before I disappeared,
I kept having this dream.
And in this dream,
you were looking for me,
but you could never find me.
And I was there and I screamed.
And I would scream
and call for you,
but you'd never hear me.
[Nicolas] The greatest sadness
is not being able to kiss
an invisible woman.
[Matilda] We're standing
right next to each other
in the darkness.
[Matilda crying] Nicolas.
Before I disappeared,
we kept trying
to define what love is.
I am trying to label it,
give it a meaning,
but love can't be defined.
It wasn't working
and I was so lost.
Do you understand?
I was so lost.
Sorry.
It's okay.
[Matilda] There's so much
distance between us.
I found you. I am sorry.
You saw things, didn't you?
I can't explain.
Weird things happened to me.
You can't explain...
what you saw.
But you can
say that you've seen.
[Kate] Are you Nicolas?
[woman] ...thousand miles away.
[Kate] When was the last time
you heard Matilda's voice?
- Where are you?
- I saw you.
[Hannah] He's here to learn.
[Kate] Are you wondering
where Matilda is?
[little girl]
She just disappeared.
- [Matilda] It's okay to be lost.
- [Thomas] Where are you?
[Matilda] I love you.
[Nicolas] Matilda, I found you.
[Matilda]
I've been here all along.
[gasps]
[water running]
[Thomas] The messy tree.
The messy tree.
The love inside me...
Will set you free
When I don't define love
By the messy tree.
Look everywhere and see
I look everywhere and ask myself
"Is it just a nightmare?"
Dreamless dreamers
There are no stars here
There are doors that open
To a place behind the sky
But the computer
Catches fire inside rainbows
As all the lovers dance
And completely disappear.
Love.
["Night Drive"
by Head to Head playing]
Thank you. [chuckles]
[ethereal music]
[Thomas] Where are you?