* SAVATE *
Stand up!!
You lost your hat, Yankee.
I am not a yankee.
Go away.
Bravo! Bravo!
Thank you very much, sir.
Attention!
He is alive! Thank God.
Can he get up?
Damn Yankees.
Kane, the war is over.
Give me some water.
Water...
Give me water.
Maybe Benedict should know.
He's a human being,
he deserves help.
Thank you. It's ok
I am very happy, miss.
What did he call you?
I don't understand,
in a foreign language.
He must be a bandit,
crossed the border.
Very well, thank you.
I don't think he's French.
French, Mexican,
everything is the same for me.
Will you help me or not?
When I get back,
he better go.
Thank you Madam.
Here if you get hungry.
Sorry,
you must have dropped this.
That's weird.
Everything is good.
You will get hurt,
Miss Mary.
You need help?
No, thank you.
Now, a beautiful lady like you,
shouldn't be working.
Do not be shy.
Lift it up!
Come, I will help you.
No!
I do not accept negative responses.
Please stop.
Leave her alone, Mitch!
I just wanted to help.
I told you to leave her
alone and get out of there!
How do you intend to carry
out that command, like that?
I'm moving, no!
Bastard!
Blow up, Slim! Ah!...
Don't interfere, stranger.
Come back. Let me go?
Come on, stranger.
I will show you now.
High! Stay where you are!
Give up Mitch.
Miss Mary, Kane.
I hope you will accept my offer.
I am not selling.
Everything is for sale.
Forget Benedict.
The answer is no"!
Why don't you make a deal,
Kane?
You, I don't know you!
What's your name?
Charlotte,
sir. Joseph Charlerogne.
Charlerogne, French, huh?
And what are you looking
for here in my city?
Maybe you would come
to my tournament?
Well interested sir.
Yes, I'll make sure you
don't do anything else.
Thank you, Mr. Charliogran.
And what are you looking at?
We saw this
in a soldier's fight.
Last month, another stranger,
a blue guy,
he killed three while
playing poker at Carson.
Lots of spider!
Are you sure?
She said, she said.
Why don't you do
something smart?
Mr. Charlotte!
I want to thank you.
Glad you stopped me.
Otherwise, he would have
killed them. No doubt.
Sir, are you hungry?
Maria is a great cook.
What is the name
of this foreign boxing?
"SAVAT"
How? Savat.
Shopping!
Yes it is!...
It's French boxing.
Did the French invent?
Boxing like boxing.
There is nothing good
in a fight.
Female business.
He doesn't understand anything.
Thank you God,
for the food you give us.
Help me to know
your commandments
and don't give up on kindness.
Help me to avoid greed
and to serve you with humility.
Bless us a new friend,
who saves us from the bullies.
We will live in peace forever.
Amen. Amen.
Amen.
Maria, you will make
the future groom happy.
I know I need to take
care of my own life...
but what about you
in the desert and Rio Grande?
There he howls at deserters.
I assure you that
I am not a deserter.
What are you doing
in San Miguel?
Because of the tournament?
I'm just passing.
Too bad, the reward is great.
Hm!
Dinner was great, miss!
Especially an apple
pie from the ground.
Earth apples?
Ah...
of potatoes.
Many! Well many!
All food comes from
the land of this farm.
Not much, but it's ours.
What is your goal?
I do not!...
I'm looking for a friend.
Are you sure, he's here?
Nowhere else.
Kane! Zakarias is coming.
Zakarias, Riel, yes...
It's okay, he's our friend.
We have to tell you something.
What Zakarias...
We sold our land
to Benedict.
Damn it! And now?
How much did he pay you?
100 silver dollars.
100 dollars?!
Zakarias did you sell your soul,
for 100 dollars? Kine!
Otherwise, we would not have
property taxes for the season.
In the morning you will understand,
if you were afraid!
Can't you wait one day?
Who will guarantee me,
Won't he poison our water
and steal our winnings?
You don't understand anything!
Damn Benedict!
Without evidence, we are helpless.
Don't start again!
With or without Benedict,
I'm sorry.
What gives this.
We're leaving.
Take care, okay.
God blessed you.
And you. Bye!
We will!
What are you doing,
Kane?
The colonel is asking us,
100 dollars.
Otherwise, I lose the country.
There is no one to complain to.
Jim, we survived the war.
We will survive this too.
Did you turn to the law?
We filed a complaint
a month ago.
The colonel should,
give us an answer tomorrow.
However, nothing from the Great Dane.
I will not leave the country.
Benedict.
Jim, don't touch the gun!
I do not allow shots to
be fired on my property.
What do you want, Benedict?
I come with the latest offer.
I'm not asking for $ 100.
It won't be worth 50 tomorrow.
You are very confident.
Look, you are insignificant
in comparison to all of Texas.
And I don't care,
what makes the difference to me!
He is trying to help you,
as well as others.
We are natives.
We don't need your help,
thank you.
Get off my land!
Dress on my property.
Leave her!
Mitch, come on?
Mitch!
Get off the property!
Mitch, I'm moving,
I'm warning you!
It's the end!
Now you will see...
Stop! No, you will hurt.
Son of a bitch!
This one broke my arm!
Break my arm!
Wait! But why!
I am a businessman,
not a murderer.
My patience has a limit.
The people told you:
get out of your land.
I'm trying to be reasonable.
If any blood is spilled,
it certainly won't be mine.
Keep that, Mitch.
For horses.
Let's get out of here, now
We have to be tougher with them.
Watch out, Mary!
People are panicking.
Power is strength. Aou.
Why is Benedict going
to need so much land?
I dont know.
It came to an end after the war,
full of money.
Thinking,
you can buy everything.
Do you have, as they say, a Sheriff?
Sheriff?
A single law, which sold its
own weapons and land.
I'm going to sleep.
I'm too tired.
Give him my clean clothes.
Good night. Good night.
Good night.
I think it will do, for you.
Where did you get that?
I was bitten by a shark.
Let me, wash your shirt.
Thank you and good night,
Miss Mary.
Put that knife away before
it hurts anyone, Slim.
Do you think French
is dangerous?
I will beat him.
You think? Yes.
If you hadn't stopped me,
I would have killed you already.
Do not.
I want you on our side.
This is my plan,
so we can have everything!
For him.
No, give it to me.
We will. Oh...
Oh, ah! We will.
Come on, come on!
April 11 Reference
to the Texas Court.
Considered by a federal court
responsible for Texas territory
She's distracted. No!
How legally dispensed?
Quietude! Quietude!
Under Texas law,
which allows me to make
the following decision:
Gains are taxed,
for red skins and others,
The state of Texas,
increasing properties,
for all the locals,
in 1,000 dollars
This is too much.
I cannot pay much.
Sit down!
Texas's failure to pay rights
leads to land confiscation,
which will be confiscated,
in favor of Texas and resold.
How do you dare!
Worked, cultivated, and now
you're taking my land away?
I tried everything,
but that is Washington's order.
Taxes must be paid by
the 4th of July holiday.
You heard the colonel.
Now, my offer is $ 50,
per family.
You know where to find me.
I will sell.
At least I want to go,
to Clifornia.
People! Think!
All of you just know,
how to farm the land.
In dreams.
Where did I get 1,000 dollars?
How many do you have?
I maybe 200 bucks!
Then another 800.
Another 8000.
Maybe you know where to get it,
the rest of the money.
I know where 500 is.
Kane, you are crazy.
You cannot go to a tournament.
I can.
It's like fighting a Yankee.
No anger, Cheney.
No hard feelings.
In addition to my sincere wishes,
you are losing another $ 300 right
Not if you bet on me.
What if you lose?
Then we will have nothing.
People think about it.
I will fight.
Do whatever you want.
Distance is important.
It's English boxing.
And like this Frenchman or Savat.
You shoot low.
Oh!... Or aside.
Different blows.
Ah!...
In the end...
That's how you fight.
But always fair.
Like this?
Now it's your turn.
I pick you up
and throw you on the floor.
Kane...
how can you fight,
if you've been a farmer all your life.
You will suffer.
I will not.
I am not trained by Joseph.
Kane!
Someone needs to stop them.
I have the right
to defend, my own.
Where's your dignity?
You would fight, wouldn't you?
It is a professional wok.
Fighting is your life.
You can go to a tournament.
It's not that simple,
that's why...
We are born!
Stable!
Kane!
Kane, here!
Skirt!
This afternoon.
Benedict!
Oh my God!
Gentlemen, I saw a fire from a distance.
Someone wants to scare us.
You know, who else can
you ask, Benedict.
What will you do?
Make a new barn.
It cannot be so.
Well, it won't work!
Hell, come on, girl.
Are you a lonely cowboi?
I believe this is yours.
And I think you are very
wrong.
I am not mistaken.
It's yours.
What job did you get, boy?
This man attacked,
my farm.
But it wasn't just that!
This is a serious charge.
I hope you have evidence.
This man attacked,
my farm.
You are accusing me,
we need to clear this up now!
Solve your problems here.
Fair and honorable.
If you are a man.
Go Go!
Oh!
What happened?
Didn't your corset unbutton?
Hya, oh!...
Oh my gosh!
Keep your weapons!
Kane, no!
Don't give this...
I am truly sorry, Miss Mary.
I tried to stop him, but...
You know what he was like,
he didn't hear me.
Take it and take care of it.
Nobody wants to bother you.
I give you my word.
As for you, Frenchman,
I have nothing to do with you.
He was a good man.
Watch out, Mary.
If you decide to come to California,
you can live with us.
I don't know what he wants.
Talk to him.
Listen to me.
Please.
Don't give up on the country.
An honorable man is
being buried today.
As a friend and officer,
I will defend your honor.
I will take Kane's
place in the tournament.
with him we have a chance.
I'm...
What is happening?
Come here.
Sir!...
Benedict,
write to me for tomorrow.
You see, Mr. Zachariah.
It's my pleasure.
Congratulations,
Hern Benedict.
You made two old friends.
He is known for his
grace in Europe.
They think he is the best.
Can you beat him?
Who do you think you are, Mr?
Great...
we thought we had a decent one,
and it would end up falling out the window.
Shut up Jenki!
Damn French is good.
Yes!
Von Trot too. Yes.
I want to hold on.
What kind of man is that?
His name is Siegfield Von Trot.
The murderer of some
civilians in Mexico.
And he had no mercy on what he did!
That was it Mr!
He was taken
to a military court.
He said he suffered
from chicken blindness.
He was demoted.
From that day on,
he vowed to paint.
Shit!
Philip!...
The medallion saved
me from the bullet.
I would be dead now.
I will not.
I can't watch this.
I want to bet on...
Everything.
Everything for Charlemagne.
All.
$ 197 for French.
Start, we need to start.
Come on!
Come on,
today is your lucky day.
On the 4th of July,
we opened a fighting tournament,
with the elimination
of the opponent.
The winner received
$ 500 in silver.
Tournament rules?
None.
In the first round I see,
a terrible great Bruno...
and the mysterious French...
He's closing!
God, this one is really huge!
David defeated Goliath.
David had a stone.
I blew up, French.
French!
The winner is Charlie Grand!
Give me your hand.
You fight well.
Come on!
The next fight will...
I'm sorry, Mrs. Mary.
Go ahead.
Are you lost, Pance?
Yes, Benedict.
Don't worry, Miss Mary.
I'll make sure there's nothing
wrong with your little head.
I need to know...
that's all.
Be a gentleman.
The following participants are:
Mr. Kang Wu,
coming up from China...
and the invincible Prussian
Siegfield von Trot!
He's a real beast.
Ah!...
You have to lose,
the next match.
Otherwise he will die
The magnificent knockout
winner is Von Trot!
Now the semifinals.
The winner will fight
in the final,
for a grand prize
of $ 500 silver.
The great duel between,
the Brazilian Sartana.
And Mr. Charlie Grand!
What is his attitude?
I dont know.
Wonderful.
That's better!
Get him away from me!
Get him away!
Stay away from me!
Sit on his lap!
The position of the peoples
in the next battle is Duke von Trot
and the horrible Justin Creole
from New Orleans!
Ring that bell!
The German will crush
your head.
that you are in heaven,
hallowed be your name,
so that your kingdom may come,
both in heaven and on earth.
Forgive us our debts, for we...
Share the menu too.
Since I've been
waiting for this.
You're breaking my arm!
Ah!...
Look that...
Who said he was dead?
Yes, a sad untruth.
It's a real pleasure for
a man to see you fight.
Hello Major! Sergeant
with pleasure.
Please sir.
As you can see, not very well.
Oh yeah!
Elegant player.
This is not true.
What did you say?
The verdict is false.
He wanted the land,
where the railroad will go.
The railroad?
This will be announced shortly.
Coming soon.
Did you know that
all along?
I hope you burn in hell!
Your leg!
You are hurt.
It's all over.
Not yet.
If I don't win,
you will lose all your money.
It's my time to say goodbye.
Yes Mery...
Milost!
Now the long-awaited
moment arrives.
The final fight,
for 500 dollars of silver.
Mr. Charlie Grand is
coming any minute now.
At least I hope so.
I told you not to invest
all the money in French.
He will come.
You need to have faith.
Last call,
for Mr. Charlie Grand!
He will come.
He has to come.
This is for Kane.
And that for me.
That person cannot fight.
I don't see how.
How did he leave us?
Will see.
When Napoleon entered
the battle, wearing a red ribbon.
He will fight!
His name is
Siegfield Von Trpota.
Then he said he would suffer
from blindness in the hens.
Chicken blindness...
Come, you see.
Ah!...
It's because of Philip.
Winner!
Take him there.
Very well friend.
I knew it.
I always knew that.
How are you?
Winner, Mr. Charlie Grand,
deservedly won,
500 silver dollars!
This is for you.
Thank you.