Hey, what's that?
Ah! That is our ticket to success.
Drink that, and any time you want,
you can throw up.
Throw up?
I'll get it.
Is this The Monkees' pad?
I'm the lawyer for the estate
of the late Lancelot von
Baresfitresily the fourth,
known to his friends as Chuck.
Mr. The Fourth has left
his entire fortune to The Monkees,
provided you spend
one evening at his mansion.
A mansion, which some say is...
...haunted.
Uh, oh, I think we did that one already.
Mike, uh, when did
we do the, uh, staying in
the haunted mansion for
the inheritance episode?
Oh, gosh, it was years ago, like episode
one eighty-six or something.
We were wearing bell bottoms!
Yeah, I'm sorry, we did that,
but thanks anyway.
- Would you like a drink?
- Thank you.
Blagh!
Here we come, walkin'
down the street
We get the funniest looks
from every one we meet
Hey, hey, we're the Monkees,
and people say we monkey around
But we're too busy singing
to put anybody down
We go wherever we want to
Do what we want to do
We don't have time to get restless
There's always something new
Hey, hey, we're the Monkees,
you never know where we'll be found
So you better get ready,
we may be comin' to your town
Hey, remember that band last week that got
the job instead of us by trashing the place?
There are a lot of funny
euphemisms for "throw up".
You know, they were spinning around
and stuff? Well, they had a gimmick.
They were grungy and offensive and loud.
And rich!
Like "toss your cookies"?
Yeah, exactly, and rich!
What's the name of that other band,
the one with the blood
and the make-up, um...
Kiss?
No thanks. You know they have,
uh, high heels, and, uh,
the guy has a nine foot tongue?
What is their name?
Uh, Kiss?
No, but Davy wants one.
Anyway, they're rich too.
Or, uh, "driving the porcelain bus"?
So, I figured, we could become
the world's first throw-up band.
You know,
Hey, hey, we're The Monkees.
People say we bleech!?
Ha ha ha! Kids'll love it.
Two year olds, maybe.
Tonight, we are playing
the most prestigious
country club in this city.
The name of the band is Kiss.
Could be the world!
They're like... kabuki metal.
We can't just go there,
and well, I don't know-
Blow chow? Although, that's a
lot like blow lunch.
Well, it wouldn't have to be gross.
It could be more like confetti.
People don't wanna see us- what'd
you say- "tossing a sandwich"?
No, but that works. Better if it's hurl
a sandwich, but toss works.
Look, even if it does look like confetti,
the club today is only for the best people.
We have to dress up,
and we have to play it straight.
I can do Tasmanian kabuki.
See? That's great!
No, it is not great.
It is silly.
What's in this stuff?
Don't ask.
Davy's right; we don't really need a
gimmick. I mean, you know, it's like...
"Believe": I believe for every drop
of rain that falls, a flower grows.
And every time The Monkees sing,
they also blow!
Ah!
What'd I say?
On your right, the remnant of a tomato
hurled at Micky during a concert in
nineteen eighty-three by an irate
cattleman who believed he had purchased
tickets to a chili cook-off. Now if you'll
follow me upstairs to the freezer section,
we'll see what is believed to be the world's
first TV dinner, a gift from a fan who-
Terrible! No gimmicks!
How can you say that?
What about all those
"Davy falling in love" stars, huh?
That's a gimmick.
No, I never ever did those on purpose,
and besides,
that was such a long time ago anyway.
Uh-huh, what about that one?
Leftovers!
Well, maybe not entirely.
I did run into someone the other day,
but I just don't do that on purpose,
you know.
- Mm-hm.
- It just happens.
- But that is not a gimmick.
Mm-hm.
I can do "Donald Duck
has a temper tantrum".
See? That's great too!
We better start rehearsing before
another plot line shows up.
Are we gonna dress alike?
Absolutely. People still wanna
see a professional show.
Hey, how about if we dress
as professional wrestlers?
Come on, you guys!
Is this, is this the club
that wouldn't let in
Ethel Merman because
she was wearing pants?
Don't you mean Esther Merman,
the underwater swimmer?
No, Esther Williams was
the underwater swimmer.
Then who's Esther Merman?
Esther Merman's the underwater
singer. Ha ha ha ha ha!
Ha ha ha.
Come on, guys. We really do
need to rehearse before-
Uh oh. Too late.
Quick! Hide me! I'm being chased by a
bunch of guys with cell phones and...
...black gloves.
Sorry, darling.
We already did that one.
Hey, hey, Mike.
When did we do that one, anyway?
Ages ago.
But there was no cell phone.
We're starting to rehearse.
How about this? I can't remember who I am.
I woke up sitting
on a bus stop with a note
pinned to my dress that read...
..."return to sender".
Wow. That is not bad.
What do you think, guys?
I'm really sorry, but we have a very
important gig tonight at the world's
most prestigious country club,
and we really do have to rehearse.
Oh, can I listen?
Mm... okay. Go on.
Actually, I'm with a friend.
Do you mind if they come in?
Sure. Fine.
What? What?
We weren't expecting an audience,
but since you're here,
there's drinks in the microwave. Ha!
After all the spotlights
and the flowers
After all the parties and goodbyes
There was something in the air
Something that we realized
People always say
'Cause it was you and I
You and I
After all the music and the madness
After all the late night fantasies
We knew that we
would make it through
There was little in our way
Nothing they could do
'Cause it was you and I
and promises not broken
You and I and magic memories
After all was said and done,
they never understood
How we always made it
You know we always would
'Cause it was you and I
You and I
Now it seems that we
are still together
When all the others
never made it through
Someday They learn
what's our way
It isn't such a secret
It isn't hard to do
'Cause it's just you and I
and promises not broken
You and I, magic memories
After all was said and done,
they never understood
How we always made it
You know we always would
'Cause it's just you and I
You and I
Wow, that sounded great.
I'll tell you what, though, we should, uh,
rehearse some of the old hits, because
they're gonna be asking for them for sure.
Yeah, yeah, you're right. Okay, uh,
let's start with "Clarksville", huh?
Take the last train to Clarksville
? And- ?
- What was that?!
The laugh track.
Sounds broken.
What, the laugh track?
Not again!
Yeah, but I like it when that happens.
The house is on fire!
People are starving!
There is no fruit!
I think we better shut it off.
Good idea.
This'll fix it.
Uh oh.
This is really messed up.
Just turn 'em all off.
What, even the wild applause?
Yes! We have to rehearse!
Everything!
Ah, man, I was just having fun.
Whoa!
Now what?
A lizard sunning itself on a rock.
What?
Stock footage.
I think the show may be a little
short of film,
and they're having to put in this-
Oh!- this stock shot that they're
getting from a film library.
Well, it's really annoying!
Let's get out of here. Go to the
beach or something, huh?
Suits me. I'm starting to
get thought balloons.
Thank you. Thank you,
thank you. You like me.
You, you, you really like me!
You don't really think that
we need a gimmick, do you?
After all these years of being just us.
Oh, I guess not.
Because, you know, Mike has turned
the Monkeemobile into a low-rider.
He what? You turned our
car into a low-rider?
Well, I was in traffic the other day,
and this guy pulls up beside me,
and his car started hopping up and down like
one of those colorful South American birds.
But that's silly! The Monkeemobile
is our special thing.
Oh, I left it Monkees; it's a
dimension machine now as well.
Ooh!
Like a time machine, except it
goes into different dimensions.
We cannot go to the
most prestigious country
club in the whole world
in a hopping bird.
We can if we're in another dimension.
Please!
Now, see how it feels?
Well, I can put it back.
Well, I should think so.
I mean, you can't change our car.
It's the Monkeemobile,
for heaven's sakes.
These are the bones of the Elephant Man.
And these are the bones
of the Invisible Man.
And this is the transmission
from the Monkeemobile.
It's a classic.
Right? Right. Right? Right. Ahh, ooh!
Oh, he's dead!
Ha ha ha ha ha ha!
Come on, guys, let's go.
You know, we've still got to rehearse,
and that gig's only a
couple of hours from now.
You will, you will fix
the car, right, Mike?
Yeah.
But don't change that dimension thing.
I don't wanna go back to the pad.
Hey, well, why don't
we do it right here?
This could draw a crowd.
Yeah.
Yeah, in your dreams. Okay, guys, strap in.
Go, uh, "Circle Sky", new version.
One, two, three, four!
Circle sky
Telling lies
Raison d'être
Idol threat
'Cause it looks like we've
made it once again
Yes, it looks like we've
Color sound
Run way around
Seagull sails
Holy grail
'cause it looks like we've
made it once again
It looks like we've
It's a very extraordinary scene
To those who don't understand
But what you have
seen you must believe
If you can, if you can
Hamilton
Smiling down
N.R.G.
Falling free
'Cause it looks like we've
made it once again
Yes, it looks like we've
It's a very extraordinary scene
To those who don't understand
But what you have
seen you must believe
If you can, if you can
Circle sky
Telling lies
Raison d'être
Idol threat
'Cause it looks like we've
made it once again
Oh yes, it looks like we've
made it to the end
Were we that bad?
I raised a pig from birth,
and now, my dad
tells me we have to sell him for... bacon!
Hey, uh, bacon!
Hey, that's not bad, huh?
We did that. It was a calf thing, but it
was essentially the same story.
Well, we can't just let a kid cry like this.
We have to entertain him somehow.
Hey. Wherever there's a cop beating
up on a guy, I'm gonna be there.
Wherever there's the poor and the
homeless and the hungry, I'll be there.
Waaaah-ha-ha!
Hey! What did you do?
I did the closing scene
from Grapes of Wrath.
Henry Fonda's speech, it's one of the great
scenes in movies. You said entertain him-
Yeah, but you're scaring him.
You have to entertain with a capital E!
? Gonna build a mountain
from a little rope ?
? Gonna need an onion and a little soap ?
? Gonna build a mountain- ?
Waaaah-ha-ha!
Those aren't the words, are they?
Well, I can never remember,
but it's not about that;
it's about the emotion, you know.
The rope, the soap,
the hope, you know, just-
Let me, let me. Hey, kid.
Wanna see me throw up?
- Yeah!
- Heh heh heh heh.
Whoa, dude, that's chill!
Can you do that again?
Yeah, sure.
I gotta go get my friends.
Wait a minute.
What about your pet pig?
Um... I never really
liked him that much.
Hey, guys? You don't think that we
need any kind of storyline?
I kinda liked that "pet pig into bacon"
thing- sweet and scary at the same time.
Well, really, not as long as
we're having a good time.
Think it's perfectly alright that we don't
have any visible means of support?
Well, who says our
means have to be visible?
Don't you think that we should
have some dramatic tension?
Some, some, some drama, distress,
some worry, some... some kind of goal?
Why? I mean, we been hanging
out like this for years.
Once every five years or so, a good
storyline comes along, but other than that,
it's better just to be hanging out,
having a good time.
We're on the beach, life is a bowl
of oysters, what could be better?
I wonder, if the pig talked...
Now, see, it doesn't make any
difference if the pig talks.
I got it. Alright. The landlord, he comes
to the door for the last rent payment,
and then, and then, all of a sudden,
we're on a desert island.
Yeah.
On the other side, there's
some buried treasure-
Rent? We probably own the house by now,
and besides,
who wants to do a story just
for the sake of doing a story?
Ah, now it's your turn. That's how
I felt about the Monkeemobile.
Yeah, and that's the way I
felt about tossing sandwiches.
What do you think, Peter?
Sandwich- no, no sandwiches.
If the pig talks, sandwiches wouldn't work.
Oh, whoa!
- Ah, lizard's back.
- It's alright.
I'm telling you, guys,
we need a storyline.
No, it's okay. No.
We just need to do... music!
Let's just come on,
and we'll do music.
? Antarctica is where I wanna be ?
Antarctica is where I wanna be?
? Antarctica is where I wanna be,
? I wanna be ?
? Antarctica is where I wanna be ?
? Antarctica... ?
THIS IS NOT A PIPE
THIS IS NOT A BAND
Hey, did you see the way that
kid reacted to my throw-up idea?
Mick, he was eight.
Stop calling it that;
it's only confetti.
It's Magic Monkee Dust.
Hey, how about calling it
Magic Monkey Hurl?
I think eight year olds
deserve better than that.
Look, what's that
purple dinosaur thing?
Remember these?
Precisely my point. All that dinosaur thing
is is one of those, but way out of control.
I mean, you're talking about
mesmerizing four years olds, here.
I think Davy's right.
Just 'cause you can thrill a toddler
by chewing with your mouth open,
doesn't mean you should.
It's not exactly a reference standard.
Don't you think playing for
little kids would be fun?
I think playing for little kids is fun,
but I don't think we have to do
any more than play our music.
I mean, maybe a few dance steps,
but other than that, we're The Monkees.
That's all we need to be.
This is it.
Once, hundreds of years ago, four guys moved
into this house and went crazy,
and never moved out.
They still live there?
Oh yeah. They have chainsaws
and hockey masks,
and they chase little kids.
One of them... has a hatchet.
Are you afraid? Wanna kiss?
I'm scared of kissing you.
And so he should be.
Huh huh. Come on.
You know, in today's
world of safe sex,
it seems we've forgot
about safe kissing.
Now, while not as dangerous as,
say, bringing a toaster
into the bathtub with you,
kissing does have its perils.
For instance, remember at the
beginning of the show,
when Davy asked me for that kiss?
Now, that was as dangerous
as it was bizarre. Huh huh.
You know, I've seen people catch
fire just by shaking hands.
Ah, Mike!
The Monkeemobile jumped up!
I'll fix it! I'll fix it!
I promise.
It ruined my routine! I was doing a
riff on the dangers of kissing.
Why?
Oh, there was a couple parked out by
the house, and the girl was doing
"crazy guys live there"
in order to scare the guy into kissing her.
Well, it always worked for me.
It always works for everybody. I was
just interrupting before it turned into
"and the only good crazy
person is a crazy
person whose house is
covered in toilet paper".
Well, they were just
telling ghost stories.
MAN: Your bumper fell off!
How does it work?
I put it on the radio.
This is the first dimension.
Not a lot to do there.
And this is the second dimension.
Which is, you know,
Flatland sort of thing.
And this is the third dimension.
- Yeah, right.
- Which is normal.
- Mm-hm.
- Well, Monkees normal.
- Yep.
- Yeah, right.
And then this is the fourth dimension.
Whoa!
Yeah! Stephen Hawking, eat your heart out.
I can dig it.
And really, that's as far as I got.
Well, but there's more buttons.
Wait!
That's the sixties button.
It changes us back into the sixties.
The problem is, it changes everything else
around the car for about
a hundred yards too.
What's that last one do?
Well, the last one is kind of,
I don't know, it's an odd button.
It just changes one object
into another object.
It's, uh, doesn't really work right yet.
The real problem is that none of
it stays completely in the car.
Very Monkees.
Heh heh. Yeah, thanks.
Ah, I still wish it was the way it was.
Me too.
Not even the hop?
Mm... neh.
Well. Here.
- Hm?
- You drive.
- Okay.
- I'm tired.
Good evening.
Can I help you?
Hi! We're The Monkees.
The Monkees?! Huh huh huh, yeah,
right, and I'm Ethel Merman.
No! I'm Ethel Merman!
? Dance with me! ?
? I can see in your eyes
you wanna dance with me ?
? Let's dance, dance,
dance, dance, dance! ?
? - Let's dance ?
- Outstanding!
But I still can't let you in.
Sorry, women are not
allowed to wear pants.
That guard wasn't gonna let us in.
Yeah, good thinking, Dave.
Huh! I never met a guard yet that
wasn't a sucker for Ethel Merman.
Sound check!
Yeah, here we go.
One, two, three, four!
She's a regional girl
Come to the big city,
give it a whirl
She thinks that she can make it
She thinks that she can take it
I think she's gonna end up
flippin' burgers in a basement
She's a regional girl
He's a regional guy
Come to the big city,
give it a try
He wants to be a mover
Yeah, he wants to shake it up
I think he's gonna end up
pourin' Pepsi in a cup
'Cause it's a regional lie
It's a regional lie
Mary, Mary, Mississippi,
Indiana Jones
Did you think that you could
really make it on your own?
A-singing whoa, oh oh oh,
whoa, oh oh oh
Eddie, Eddie, good and ready,
now you've got your chance
Try to keep the little buggers
playin' with your pants
A-singing whoa, oh oh oh,
whoa, oh oh oh
It's a regional lie
The grass is always greener,
and the loyals never lie
You wanna hit the big one
Yeah, you wanna strike it rich
I think you're gonna end up
flippin' burgers for some bitch
'Cause it's a regional lie
Mary, Mary, Mississippi,
Indiana Jones
Did you think you could
really make it on your own?
whoa, oh oh oh,
whoa, oh oh oh
It's a regional lie
The grass is always greener,
and the loyal that's a lie
You wanna hit the big one
Yeah, you wanna strike it rich
I think you're gonna end up
flipping burgers for some bitch
'Cause it's a regional lie
It's a regional lie
Well, hello! I am so
honored to meet you!
Ha ha.
I'm Chuck.
...the manager of the club?
Oh.
And this is my drop-dead beautiful
daughter, the princess entwined.
The princess?
Not a real princess. That's just
what daddy calls me to be nice,
because he seems to think I've
lost a few tiles on re-entry.
Excuse me?
He says I didn't quite come through the
rocket ride, and I'm a little bats.
I don't know, he may be right,
or he may be disturbed.
There's a lot of funny
euphemisms for "dumb".
A few cards short of a deck.
Well, I hope you fellas
play all your old hits,
because if this party isn't
successful, I may...
...lose the club.
Lose the club?
That's a good episode!
Lame-o!
Hey, how about if the princess and
I are stranded on a desert island.
We have one more rent payment
to pay, and there's
some buried treasure on the
other side of the island!
One oar in the water...
You know, we really, we got a
new record out, and we need-
Oh, but you are gonna play
some of those old hits?
"Boil That Cabbage Down, Boys"?
One brick shy of a load.
Uh, we were mostly gonna play the new CD.
We really need the publicity...
"Boil That Cabbage Down"?
One of my favorites. I loved it!
I thought love was only true in fairy tales.
Meant for someone else,
but not for me.
That's "I'm a Believer".
Uh, love was out to get me.
Da-doo dat, da-doo.
Somewhere else it seemed.
Up the river without a clue.
We really need to promote this new CD.
Thanks for joining me.
You know, ever since I invented
my new non-stick cookware
and psychic make-up,
I've been getting more
endorsements than I can count.
Today, my guests are Davy Jones of
The Monkees and Martha Stewart.
Davy, how long have you been using my new
psychic make-up and con-stick nookvare?
We have a new record out.
I beg your pardon?
Me and the guys.
We have a new CD.
And Martha, when did you notice cheese
wouldn't stick to your eyebrows when...
are you really Martha Stewart?
Yeah!
Well, how do you make a wedding gown
out of whipped cream frosting?
Well, uh, it depends on the flavor.
We have a new record out.
Does it have "Boil Thatâ-"
No, no, see, really, that,
that's "I'm a Believer".
The new record is, well...
well, it's new. Uh...
How old are you?
I don't know. Oh, but tonight, you are
gonna play the hits, aren't you?
Hot dogs, get your hot dogs, peanuts,
popcorn, hot dogs, game starting, hot dog.
Well, I suppose we could
play a couple of them, yes.
And will Mike wear... the hat?
The hat?
Um... oh, maybe.
Dear!
Don't worry, that's just
some old library film footage.
You see, money is a little tight.
Uh, and the show, it's about
to start, so, I better go.
I just think there's so
much more we could do.
I mean, think about it: television!
The possibilities are endless!
What, do the news in interpretive dance?
Yeah, yeah, that's a good idea!
Dateline Cairo, home of the-
Mike, Mike?
Are you wearing the hat tonight?
The hat? The woolhat?
Davy, I haven't seen that
hat in twenty-five years.
Have you got any other kind of hat?
Well, yeah, I got a baseball hat,
but if I wear it with this outfit,
I'll scare everybody.
I'll look like a cross between a
serial killer and Steven Spielberg.
Or Forrest Gump.
Uh! Even scarier!
Life is like a box of chocolates.
Please, please, just for tonight?
Look, I told the princess that you would.
And that we'd play some of our hits.
Otherwise, her father may...
...lose the club!
David, that's just another gimmick.
A trick to get us to do a storyline.
Really? But she had stars in her eyes!
Yeah, and raisins and grapefruits and the
international symbol
for "slippery when wet".
Oh, hey, look. Ha ha! Hey, how you doing?
What? Huh?
What? Ha ha ha.
No, no, I can't do that.
No. Oh, alright, alright.
Okay. Okay, okay,
here we go. Ready?
Do that again.
- What?
- You know.
You mean this?
That confetti's a special effect, isn't it?
Yeah.
It's not throw-up.
Nope.
That's why we keep running
out of production money and
having to cut to a lizard
sunning itself on a rock.
I keep having this trouble.
Every time I come up with a neat idea,
I keep getting this weird side effect,
I don't- here he is.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Could I have your attention please?
And me. Me too!
Of course, you too... princess.
If I say the name "The Monkees",
what do you think of?
Yeah, so do I. Okay,
we won't go there tonight.
How many of you remember
going to school with
your Monkees lunchbox
and getting beaten up?
All of you? It was quite a
weapon though, wasn't it?
I personally thought
the fingerpuppets were
just a little on the strange side,
but you know.
Forgive and forget.
Water under the bridge.
But tonight, singing from their brave
new record, some songs that you...
probably won't recognize...
along with some of their greatest hits
that you've come to know and love.
Arlo and Charlie,
Humphrey and Bing, also known as
Davy, Micky, Mike,
and Peter, it's The Monkees!
Take the last train to Clarksville
And I'll meet you at the station
You can be here by four thirty
'Cause I made your reservation
Don't be slow,
oh, no, no, no!
Oh, no, no, no!
Just I'm leavin' in the morning
And I must see you again
We'll have one more night together
'Til the morning brings my train
And I must go, oh, no, no, no!
Oh, no, no, no!
And I don't know if
I'm ever coming home
Oh, I could hide
'neath the wings
Of the bluebird as she sings
The six o'clock alarm
would never ring
But six rings, and I rise
Wipe the sleep
out of my eyes
My shaving razor's cold,
and it stings
Cheer up, Sleepy Jean
Oh, what can it mean
To a daydream believer
And a homecoming queen?
Cheer up, Sleepy Jean
Oh, what can it mean
To a daydream believer
And a homecoming queen?
I'm Not Your Steppin' Stone
You're making your
mark in society
Using all the tricks that
you used on me
All them high
fashion magazines
The clothes you're wearin',
girl, are causing public scenes
I'm Not Your Steppin' Stone
Not your steppin' stone
I thought love was only
true in fairytales
Meant for someone
else but not for me
Love was out to get me
That's the way it seemed
Disappointment haunted
all my dreams
Then I saw her face,
now I'm a believer
Not a trace of
doubt in my mind
I'm in love, I'm a believer
I couldn't leave her if I tried
The local rock group
down the street
Is trying hard to
learn their song
They serenade the
weekend squire
Who just came out
to mow his lawn
- Another Pleasant Valley Sunday
- Sunday
Charcoal burnin' everywhere
Rows of houses that
are all the same
And no one seems to care
- Another Pleasant Valley Sunday
- Sunday
Charcoal burnin' everywhere
Another Pleasant Valley Sunday
Here in status symbol land
- Another Pleasant Valley Sunday
- Ah, Pleasant Valley Sunday
Well, you fellas certainly are pros.
A happy ending, and no story!
I get my lease renewed
for ninety-nine years,
and there's absolutely no dialog about it.
There are no stupid chases,
there are no silly
scenes of exposition,
just stacks of goofy jokes and-
silly special effects.
Thanks to you.
And it was a dream come
true for me as well,
to see the four of you
all together like this.
Even though you're all grown up,
you're just as stupid as you ever were.
Hoo!
Oh, and Davy?
I found out how old I am.
Oh, really? How old?
...I forgot.
What a maroon.
Heh heh heh heh heh.
You guys mind if I play with this?
Go ahead.
So what episode was that?
Seven hundred and eighty-one, or...?
Yeah. Seven hundred and eighty-one.
I wonder if the general public knows
that TV shows like ours never die,
that they just go on and on,
even though they're not being broadcast.
The princess does. She's still watching
new episodes of The Flying Nun.
And Charlie's Angels,
and M*A*S*H and Cheers and...
..whoa.
Holy smokes.
They papered the house.
You know?
It doesn't look half bad.
Well, might as well finish it off!
End the show? 'Cause this will finish up the
rest of the production budget, right?
Yeah.
Well, it's as good a place as any.
Endings are always hard.
So?
Okay.
Here goes!
Subtitles: Kilo