(BIRDS CHIRPING)
(CHICKENS CLUCKING)
(SOFT PIANO MUSIC PLAYING)
VALENTINA: Hey.
CAL: Hi.
VALENTINA: Didn't know
when to expect you.
CAL: I got here
as soon as I could.
It's good to see you.
VALENTINA: You, too.
CAL: The tree isn't
as bad as I thought.
VALENTINA: Joey worked on it.
He'll be back this afternoon.
I'm making lunch, you hungry?
No, I'm good, thanks.
We, uh, had to move him
to the study, so...
Okay.
I made up your room.
Thanks.
VALENTINA:
Oh, Cal, this is Ace,
from the hospital.
ACE: Hello, Cal.
I am very sorry
about your father.
I will do all I can for him.
Okay, thanks. Um...
I'm gonna drop my bag.
ACE: Yes, of course.
Just let me know when you're
ready to come in to see him.
Yeah, I will.
Okay.
(STRUMMING SOFTLY)
VALENTINA: My cousin Bambi
was in a coma once,
she was in this
head-on collision.
Anyway, she said that
while she was in the coma,
she could float through
the quarters of the hospital,
and that she saw
this one nurse...
(VENTILATOR BEEPING)
(VALENTINA CONTINUES
SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
(WIND WHISTLING)
(HORSE SNORTING)
Hey, Mr. T.
Hey, beauty.
How you doing?
Yeah.
I missed you.
(HORSE WHINNIES)
(SOFT PIANO MUSIC PLAYING)
(VENTILATOR BEEPING)
Oh, Cal.
I'm sorry, I didn't hear you.
It's okay.
I found the puzzle in a closet,
I hope you don't mind.
No, make yourself at home.
What are you listening to?
Oh, uh...
Brahms, I think.
Classical music is what
most people ask for.
My father hated classical music.
Okay.
No, I mean, uh...
Listen to whatever.
Ah. Okay.
Thank you.
CAL: Hmm.
(MUSIC STOPS)
Please, sit.
Be with your father.
You should probably wear
a mask, just to be safe.
I can wait it in the kitchen.
Okay.
Thanks.
(VENTILATOR BEEPING)
(SIGHS)
(CHAINSAW BUZZING)
Hey.
Mom told me
about the tree, so...
Yeah, thanks, I heard.
Yeah, no problem.
Almost done.
You, uh, seen him?
Yeah, just now.
It's a rough deal, huh?
Painful to watch.
Yeah.
VALENTINA: Hey, Joey.
CAL: Let me help you.
Thank you.
This is stuff for the Goodwill.
They're gonna come for
the treadmill tomorrow,
and the other stuff.
CAL: Okay.
(SIGHS) See you Wednesday?
Yeah.
Okay.
(WHISPERS) Thank you.
Uh, I'll come by later
and finish up.
Be strong, huh?
Yeah, thanks.
(TRUCK DOOR CLOSES)
(ENGINE STARTS)
(LIGHTER CLICKING)
(MICROWAVE WHIRRING, BEEPING)
(FAUCET RUNNING)
ACE: Hello, Cal.
Uh...
Oh! Uh...
Sorry, just a sec.
ACE: Oh, no. Take your time.
How was dinner?
Uh, you know, dinner.
(ACE LAUGHS)
So, uh...
Ace, is that your real name?
Is Cal your real name?
Sort of.
It's short for, uh, Calvin,
after Cal Ripken,
who broke the record
for consecutive baseball games
played the year I was born.
Oh, so you have a famous name?
Well, to my father, at least.
(ACE LAUGHS)
(CHUCKLES)
Ace is short for
Apiyo-ma-ka Nyadimo.
Because nobody in Montana, USA,
can say Apiyo-ma-ka Nyadimo.
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
Is your family here, in Montana?
Uh, no.
They are at home.
In Nairobi, Kenya.
Well...
Have a good night, Calvin.
Good night.
Apiya-ma-kan Wadimo.
Not too bad.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
(CAL SIGHS)
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYING)
(SIGHS SOFTLY)
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
(CHICKENS CLUCKING)
(COCKEREL CROWING)
(UTENSILS CLANKING)
CAL: Didn't think
I'd see you 'till tomorrow.
(CABINET THUDS)
VALENTINA: Ow!
(VALENTINA INHALES SHARPLY)
Cal! (SCOFFS)
I'm sorry.
(VALENTINA SIGHS)
CAL: You okay?
Thought you were in bed.
No, I can't sleep.
I was just looking for this,
for the store.
Mmm.
If you're hungry,
there's, um, some fresh eggs.
I just brought 'em in.
(FAUCET RUNNING)
So, um...
Were you able
to talk to the store
about going full-time?
Yeah.
They said maybe after
the beginning of the year,
but not now.
Everyone wants extra hours
now, for the holidays.
(SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING)
So, I think,
more than likely, uh,
when we finally sell the ranch,
it'll still leave enough to
cover the new medical bills.
Uh, depending on
how much we get.
And how long he lives.
I'm assuming
Medicaid's kicked in
for the in-home care, now?
Most, but not all.
And there's still
household stuff,
Valentina's still coming
three days a week.
DON: You have enough
to cover that?
I can sell some things.
(SIGHS)
DON: Remember, proceeds
from anything you sell
technically belong
to the bankruptcy court.
Yeah. What about my mom's car?
They were never married.
Still, a good idea
to keep it quiet.
You don't wanna
give his creditors
anything to squawk about.
You thought more
about that old horse?
Gotta deal with it,
sooner or later.
Um, yeah.
I only ask, 'cause
the big animal vet from Butte
came over to my place
this morning.
Said he'd come by
and take care of it
tomorrow morning,
before he leaves.
Wait, tomorrow?
Okay, yeah.
It's the right thing to do,
he's an old horse.
Lived a long life.
Any other animals
left out there,
might need looking at?
Uh, no, just the birds.
DON: Hell, I'm real sorry
about all this.
Crying shame,
Wade going out this way.
Especially after
what he's been through,
the last couple of years.
With losing your mom and all.
Most important thing though,
he's home.
You got him home,
where he wanted to be
in the end.
Hey!
Saw your car.
Got a sec?
Sure. What's up?
Uh...
My, uh... My mom
talk to you about hours?
Yeah.
She said they weren't gonna
give her more time at the store.
Yeah, well,
it's actually less time.
What do you mean?
I mean, business sucks,
so they're cutting back.
You know, with the holidays.
Yeah, she mentioned.
Any chance
she could go back to...
Joey, with the bankruptcy
and everything,
even at three days a week,
it's a stretch.
You know,
whatever people say,
he always did right by her.
Keeping her on.
What happens to the ranch
when he dies?
It gets sold.
I mean, he borrowed against it.
It's not gonna be up to us.
You know, she lived on
that ranch a long time.
Before Wade bought it.
Before you and Erin.
It's a part of her.
I know,
but there's nothing left now.
For anybody.
(KEYBOARD TAPPING)
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
ACE: Mama.
(ACE SPEAKING LUO)
(CHUCKLES)
(ACE CONTINUES SPEAKING LUO)
(CAR BEEPING)
(COUNTRY MUSIC PLAYING
ON RADIO)
♪ Hey, baby
♪ It's your time now
♪ You made it somehow
♪ Don't let nobody
♪ Come and bring you down
♪ Hey, baby ♪
(CAMERA CLICKS)
(MELLOW MUSIC PLAYING)
(BIRD SQUAWKING)
Fuck.
Oh, God.
NEWSREADER: (ON RADIO)
A federal judge
has ordered the shut down
of the Dakota
access oil pipeline,
pending an environmental review.
It's a major victory for
the Standing Rock Sioux Tribe.
The pipeline crosses
beneath the Missouri River,
where the Tribe gets its water,
and has raised concern
about pollution.
The head of the North Dakota
Petroleum Council,
insists that
the pipeline is safe.
MAN: (ON RADIO) There has
been a lot of back and forth.
(CAR BEEPING)
Erin?
I just wanna see him
one more time.
Okay.
How did you know what happened?
Valentina called me.
You're in touch with Valentina?
How long's that been going on?
Since you left?
The whole time?
Yeah.
She doesn't know I'm here.
But she's known where you live?
Where you've...
Where you've been?
Your phone number?
Like I said, I just wanna
see him one more time.
I'm leaving tonight, okay?
Um...
Give me a sec.
(FAUCET RUNNING)
CAL: Erin?
(FAUCET STOPS)
Erin?
He's not up here.
He's dead, isn't he?
No.
He died before I got here.
Erin!
Oh, miss. I'm sorry.
Who are you?
Erin, this is Ace.
He's taking care of Dad.
So, where is he?
In the study.
Alone?
You can leave him alone?
Uh... He's not going anywhere.
Take a breath, all right?
(VENTILATOR BEEPING)
It's okay, you can go inside.
You'll want to wear a mask,
just to be safe.
Right.
ACE: Would you like some
privacy with your father?
ERIN: No.
I can wait just here...
ERIN: No, please.
Don't leave me alone with him.
ACE: Yes, okay.
(VENTILATOR BEEPING)
ERIN: Is he completely
brain dead?
ACE: No.
Not brain dead.
The stroke has left him
unconscious, in a coma.
ERIN: Can he hear me,
right now?
ACE: Probably not.
His brain continues to function
to keep his body alive.
But it is very badly damaged.
(SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING)
ERIN: He looks asleep.
Like he might wake up.
ACE: No, he will not wake up.
Erin, are you okay?
(ERIN GASPS)
(SIGHS) Yeah, I...
She's been away a long time.
It's never easy, Cal.
Yeah.
(WIND WHISTLING)
(ERIN SIGHS)
(ERIN EXHALES)
I just wasn't expecting him
to be so not himself, you know?
Shrunken and pathetic.
Yeah.
He's definitely not himself.
But it was the car
accident too, with Connie.
You know, so he had kind of
a two-year running start,
even before the stroke.
God!
How is it that I'm feeling
pity for him, right now?
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
I think I should go.
Yeah, I'm gonna
just wait at the airport.
It's just a couple hours, so...
Really? You just got here.
ERIN: No, no, this is better.
Stay the night, at least.
ERIN: Damn it.
Damn it.
If you're not Verizon,
you won't get much of a signal.
You're really leaving,
just like that?
Really?
Here, just use mine.
I can Venmo you.
Don't worry about it.
(WIND WHISTLING)
(CELL PHONE VIBRATING)
You're still doing business
with this sleazeball?
He was worse than Dad.
CAL: Hey.
It's fine.
(DOOR CLOSES)
Yeah, tomorrow's still good.
Hey.
Um, I'm leaving, so thank you.
Sorry about before.
It was very nice to meet you,
Miss Erin.
Um...
I'm sorry, what'd you ask me?
His regular vet
is Dr. Preston.
Yeah, 4:00's fine.
Bye.
Who's the vet for?
Um...
For Mr. T.
He's still alive?
Yeah.
Erin!
(GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING)
ERIN: (WHISPERS) Hey, yeah.
Hi.
(HORSE WHINNIES)
Hi, it's okay.
It's okay, Mr. T.
Hi, beauty.
Hi.
Been a long time, hasn't it?
Yes, it has.
Hi.
I can't believe
he's still alive.
He must be...
CAL: Twenty-five.
Same as you, remember?
(MR. T WHINNIES)
(CHUCKLES)
You're still such a lover,
aren't you?
Hey.
Hi, Mr. T. Hi.
Hi.
CAL: Hey.
(MR. T SNORTS)
(CAR HORN HONKING)
Erin, why don't you stay?
Really, cancel the ride.
You just got here.
No.
I should go.
What was that about, the vet?
Is there something wrong
with Mr. T?
Um...
No. No, nothing's
wrong with him.
We're gonna put him down.
What?
It's just what has to happen.
He's old, and he doesn't
have so much time left.
And there's not gonna be
anywhere for him
after the ranch gets sold,
I mean...
So, you're just gonna kill him?
Well, what do you suggest?
He's not living a life here,
anyway.
I mean, he's... (HESITATES)
No one's around to exercise him.
His arthritis
is getting so bad, that...
Right, yeah, so I know.
Let's just kill him then.
Fuck, Erin.
(SIGHS) He's at
the end of his life.
It's the right thing to do.
The big animal guy from Butte
happened to be around, so...
He's coming by tomorrow.
(CAR HORN HONKING)
(MR. T SNORTING)
Erin!
(ENGINE REVVING)
(BRAKES SCREECH)
(TIRES CRUNCHING)
ERIN: Yes, that sounds good.
Shit.
You're breaking up, but yes.
Same flight, same time tomorrow.
Sure, fine. I'm fine
with the change fee.
Hello?
Damn it!
CAL: What are you doing?
I'm changing my flight.
Why?
Because if you're
gonna kill Mr. T,
I'm gonna be there with him.
Erin, there's no point.
Yeah, well,
I've made up my mind.
I'm gonna be there with him.
So, really,
there's no service anywhere?
Um...
Up by the gate,
that works sometimes.
Hello?
Yes, I was just on the phone
with another operator.
I'm trying to book
a flight for tomorrow.
It's the exact same flight
that I was on today,
but I just need to book
for tomorrow, please.
(SOFT PIANO MUSIC PLAYING)
CAL: Valentina's
gonna be here tomorrow.
ERIN: Have you told her?
About Mr. T?
Uh, no.
Um, it only came together this
morning, after I met with Don.
Maybe you ought to?
Not everyone can handle this
sort of thing as well as you.
Okay, I'll tell her.
I mean, what is all this
still doing here?
You know, I'm good.
I can finish this, thanks.
Okay.
Um...
You can use the bathroom
in the hall, I'll use Dad's.
Okay.
Good night.
(DOOR OPENS)
(SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING)
(INSECTS CHIRPING)
(SOFT GUITAR MUSIC)
(MR. T SNORTING)
(WHISPERS) Hi.
Hey.
Hi.
You're okay.
(GASPS SOFTLY)
What happened?
What's wrong?
I'm taking Mr. T back with me.
Back where?
To New York.
You live in New York?
Upstate, yeah. Focus.
I'm not gonna let you kill him.
I'm taking him home with me.
Erin, I'm not killing him.
Yes, you are.
That's exactly what
you're doing, it's murder.
How would you
even get him there?
I mean, can you afford that?
Boarding, feed?
I can figure it out.
You really think this is right?
It's exactly what it is.
It's right.
It's the right thing to do.
For him, to be there for him.
Right?
Good night.
(DOOR OPENS)
(DOOR CLOSES)
(SIGHS)
(WIND WHISTLING)
(VALENTINA GASPS)
ERIN: I'm sorry.
It's okay.
(VALENTINA GASPS)
ERIN: I'm sorry.
I know I said I wouldn't come.
VALENTINA: It's okay.
(PATS ON BACK)
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
I'm sorry.
I don't understand.
I gave her my word,
I wouldn't tell you.
But you knew
what I was going through.
How much I missed her,
how hard I tried to find her.
It broke my heart.
And yet.
All those nights
you stayed up with me.
I promised.
She wants to take Mr. T
back to New York with her.
(VALENTINA CHUCKLES)
I heard.
It's insane.
Maybe.
You don't think so?
I think she doesn't know
how to make the pain go away.
But maybe this, she can do.
(SIGHS)
ERIN: Hey. Can you hear me?
Great, okay.
Yeah, I'm just trying to...
It's... It's a family thing,
so I kinda have to be here,
you know?
Yes, I'm aware.
Okay, don't yell!
Thank you.
No, I... (HESITATES)
Yes, I'll try to cut it shorter,
but, I figure probably a week.
Yeah, yes, so, uh, the baby
carrots and the radishes,
if you still have them.
Both the red
and the golden beets,
and everything else
is the same as last week.
Yes, great.
Thank you, bye.
I tried getting on the Wi-Fi,
but there's a password now?
Oh, yeah.
And?
Um, it's Libby, capital "L."
Libby, for real?
He chose it.
Of course he did.
You can use my computer...
No, it's fine.
You called off the vet?
Yep.
Good.
(ERIN SIGHS)
(VENTILATOR BEEPING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Okay, yep.
All right.
ACE: Good.
Just place it there.
Okay.
CAL: About half
of the 200 acres
go south from there.
The eastern boundary's
the river.
It's quite a piece of land.
Yeah.
We used to raise cattle,
but not really.
My dad liked the whole idea
of it, but he was a lawyer,
so you know, we had a foreman.
(REALTOR CHUCKLES)
Still a couple dozen apple trees
in the orchard, back there.
You want me to take you?
REALTOR:
Yeah, that'd be great.
CAL: My mom used to keep
bees back there, too,
but I don't think there
are many of them left.
ERIN: Wait, wait,
you're kidding right?
Well, I have like
three other options
that are way cheaper
than that, so...
(REALTOR LAUGHING,
SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
Need a hand?
ERIN: Uh-huh.
Yeah, you know what?
Um, actually,
just forget it, thanks.
So, three bedrooms,
three baths...
ERIN: Yeah, I get it.
I just... Um, yeah, bye.
And with a new roof
about five years back.
REALTOR:
Oh, that's meaningful.
That's the garage.
It only takes one car.
REALTOR: More than
a lot of ranches.
(MELLOW MUSIC PLAYING)
(VACUUM WHIRRING)
ACE: There is still
blood circulating,
and neurological activity.
The muscles and the tendons,
they feel and react.
And perhaps
communicate something
to whatever being still
resides in your father's body.
Would you like to help me?
Here.
Uh...
No, um, I don't know how.
Trust me.
No training required.
Um... (SIGHS) Should I?
No, no mask.
You've been here
long enough, it's okay.
ACE: Okay. Place your hand
right there.
Okay, place this one here.
Can you feel his pulse
in your hands?
I don't think so.
Hold him lightly here,
around the ankle.
Yes, like that.
Okay.
By the bone,
as lightly as you can.
(VENTILATOR BEEPING)
Good.
And now, can you feel
your own pulse there, too?
For me,
when a person who has come
to a place like this,
alive, but in a way
we don't understand,
that rhythm you're feeling,
it can be like a conversation.
ERIN: What are you doing?
Um... Helping Ace.
ERIN: I need to talk
to you for a minute.
Please.
ERIN: Um...
I found a truck and a trailer,
but it's up north near
Browning, at the reservation.
Valentina hook that up?
ERIN: Nope, Craigslist.
CAL: You're buying
a truck and trailer?
ERIN: Mmm-hmm.
CAL: To take back to New York?
ERIN: Yup.
CAL: Why?
ERIN: Because you wanna
kill Mr. T, and I don't,
so, I need to figure out a way
to get him back home with me.
And I just need you to
drive me there, tomorrow.
CAL: It's fucking
freezing out there!
ERIN: Jesus, Cal!
Okay, fine.
I'll drive you.
ERIN: Thank you.
(SIGHS)
Did you hear all that?
Not all.
Mr. T is the old horse
in the barn?
Yeah.
He must be very special to her.
She wants to take him back
to New York.
Her horse, I understand.
No, not hers.
I mean, Mr. T was ours.
Hmm.
Erin had a horse called Pepper.
(ACE CHUCKLES)
Pepper and Mr. T.
CAL: Yeah.
Pepper died the night she left.
Seven years ago.
You must have been thinking
something was up with her,
yesterday.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY) Yes, I...
I could see she was agitated
with your father.
CAL: Yeah, she was agitated.
It was our father
who killed Pepper.
(SIGHS) I don't think
I can do that anymore.
Uh, yes, no, of course.
No problem.
Thank you for your help.
(GRUNTS SOFTLY)
I just can't believe
she came back like this, now.
She didn't just leave here...
Seven years ago, she ran away.
From him.
She wrote this article
in the school paper,
about what a slimy lawyer he was
for helping cover up
the toxic mess at the mine.
And then this TV network
got hold of it,
and everything just went nuts.
I mean, she...
She probably
shouldn't have done it.
It was humiliating for him.
But what he did to her...
I mean, he'd hit us before.
Not like super violent
or anything, or all the time,
but he was that kinda guy.
And the thing is,
she's sort of like him.
Not the violent part,
but, temperamentally.
All that fire in their bellies,
and how smart
and quick they both are.
Could you, um...
Yeah.
Thank you.
We have different moms,
Erin and I.
Hers died
while she was being born.
And that was kind of it,
for him.
He hired my mom
to help take care of Erin,
and then...
you know, I came along.
But it wasn't the same
with Connie.
My mom.
Not like it was with Libby.
And Erin could feel his
distance too, you know?
Everyone could, it was obvious.
Maybe that's why
she held me so close.
I mean, we were always together.
Inseparable.
I saw what happened that night.
What he did to her.
Coming home
from cross country practice.
As soon as I came into
the house, I could hear it.
Right here, in this room.
I looked in,
and he was just...
Just whaling on her.
Really bad, like a crazy person.
And I just froze.
I didn't know what to do,
I just stood there.
He's screaming,
and she's crying.
And I'm just standing there,
dumb.
And then she looks up at me,
and she's not crying anymore.
And I knew what I should do.
What was right.
That I could stand up to him,
that I could stop him.
But I didn't.
And then,
I ran out of the house,
and I tried
not to think about it.
I thought everything
would be okay.
Next morning,
I found Pepper in the barn,
lying in a pool
of her own blood.
Bullet in her head.
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
That part had to be
the worst for her,
just knowing what he'd done.
I tried finding her
any way I could,
but, you know,
she didn't wanna be found.
And... (GULPS NERVOUSLY)
After a while, her phone
stopped working, and I...
I stopped trying.
(BREATH TREMBLING)
Your father,
you have spoken with him
about what he did?
No.
No, never.
I mean...
(SIGHS) I was 15,
I didn't know how to do that.
I guess I still don't.
(SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING)
(COCKEREL CROWING)
Hey, it's Erin.
Um, we're...
We're getting ready to leave,
and I just wanted to call
and check in about, like,
the payment situation.
Yeah.
Well, I was thinking
I could just...
My bank's out of state,
so I can...
It'd probably be easier for me
to wire you the money, or...
(CAR BEEPING)
Yeah, I'll just get out
however much I can,
and then the rest, I dunno...
Do you have a Venmo,
or something?
Okay.
Okay, cool.
See you then, bye.
You know,
there's a phone inside.
You don't
have to stand out here.
I'm good.
I can't believe you
still drive this thing,
it smells like high school.
CAL: Suits me.
(CELL PHONE VIBRATING)
Hello?
Oh, yeah, this is Cal, hi.
Um...
Yeah, well,
it's a 2013 Lexus RX-350.
Well, it's original paint.
Um, it's in great shape,
and the seats are leather.
Tan.
It was my mom's,
she barely drove it.
Um...
Wanna come take a look?
Well, I'm gone today, but, um...
Okay. Yeah, sure.
All right, thanks, bye.
You good?
(WIND WHISTLING)
The Lexus you're selling,
that was Connie's?
Yeah, why?
She bought it a little
while after you left.
They were in his car
when she died.
It'll be two years in March.
Oh.
I live in Cheyenne, now.
Junior year, I did an internship
at the city planning department.
I'm a civil engineer.
I will be, eventually. Um...
And after I graduated,
they took me on.
It's mostly ADA compliance
stuff, but I like it.
And we're building some, too.
A big library next year,
and a pedestrian bridge
downtown.
You know how I love bridges.
I live by myself.
Little house
on the south side of town.
Not far from where
we saw Kid Rock that time.
You remember, uh,
Cheyenne Frontier Days?
I have a cat.
Oscar Wilde.
Souvenir from
my last relationship.
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING ON RADIO)
(MUSIC STOPS ABRUPTLY)
CAL: Do you wanna check
my phone for reception?
ERIN: You don't have any,
I just checked.
He said to make the second
left after the trailer, so...
Okay. So, this...
Yeah, turn left.
ERIN: He's got a red pickup.
Is that it?
Yeah.
Yeah, that must be him.
Mukki?
Sure am.
I'm Erin, this is Cal.
Welcome.
Sorry if you were waiting long.
Oh, I'm used to it.
We're just gonna head up
this way a bit,
and round the corner.
Well, let's go then.
Take a left here.
Drive must have been
beautiful, innit?
CAL: Yeah.
MUKKI: Day like this,
you could drive forever.
ERIN: Yeah, it was nice.
MUKKI: You need
to take a right, here.
Must be a little cold up here
for you guys, huh?
CAL: Yeah, a bit.
MUKKI: Uh, right here.
What's this, a '93?
CAL: Uh, '94.
Nice!
CAL: Yeah.
MUKKI: And you're gonna
take a left, here.
Pull up right there, that's it.
Well, there she is!
Give me a sec, and I'm gonna
go fetch the battery.
You wanna pop the hood?
CAL: Sure.
Is that the trailer?
MUKKI: Yeah, it is.
(DOG BARKING)
(CAR HOOD THUDS)
I like to keep it fresh.
Right.
Um, so, I'm just wondering
when the last time
it got moved was?
Like, since you ran it?
MUKKI: Hmm...
A month or so ago, maybe.
Maybe less.
Nah, maybe more.
I can't remember.
Funny thing
about not remembering.
Sometimes you're glad for it,
other times
it gets you into trouble.
Well, let's get her
humming for you.
ERIN: Sorry.
(ENGINE STARTING)
Like I said, keeps it fresh.
(ENGINE ROARS, SQUEAKS)
What's that?
MUKKI: Shit!
The alternator belt is loose.
Give me a second,
I'll tighten it up.
Okay.
(DOGS BARKING IN DISTANCE)
Um...
Erin, have you really
thought this through?
It's just an old truck,
calm down.
What?
Two seconds.
Sorry.
You got a phone
to shine a light down here
for me?
Oh, yeah.
Are there spare tires
in the truck and trailer?
MUKKI: Sure are.
You might wanna
check the pressure.
(GRUNTS) But, yeah,
that ought to do it.
(CAR HOOD SLAMS)
ERIN: Sorry.
(ENGINE STARTING)
Purr like a kitty cat, right?
(ENGINE RUMBLING, STOPS)
Nice.
So, you got the cash?
And then we'll go
take care of the Venmo?
Yeah.
CAL: Erin. Um...
Maybe you wanna take it
for a test drive, first?
Just make sure
you're comfortable, right?
Okay.
I mean, you don't mind, do you?
No, go ahead.
Road loops around.
(ENGINE STARTS)
She your girlfriend?
Sister.
Ah.
Right.
(RADIO STATIC)
(COUNTRY-FOLK MUSIC
PLAYING ON RADIO)
♪ Hell, that one paper kid
♪ Wasn't really so mean
♪ Just a little bit weird
♪ 'Cause times were so lean
♪ Now he's gone to a place
♪ Where it's legal to dream
♪ No camels
♪ No coffee
♪ No cold morning winds
♪ It was wrote on a rock
♪ The one paper kid
is rollin' again ♪
MUKKI: Taking this
right back down state?
Yeah, just for a bit,
just to get the horse.
Where then?
New York.
New York, really?
Your horse don't like
Montana no more?
CAL: He's a very old horse.
Twenty-five.
Oh, you're one of them
sentimental horsey girls?
He's a special horse,
so I'm bringing him
back home with me.
MUKKI: Home?
Where you planning on keeping
an old horse in the Big Apple?
I'm upstate.
You got other horses at home?
ERIN: No.
What, you think
I'm being stupid?
MUKKI: Of course not.
I've done way
stupider things for animals
than drag a horse from
Montana to the Big Apple.
Hey, why don't you jump in?
We'll test the lights.
MUKKI: Okay, uh, left now!
Now, right!
Now, tap the brakes!
Eh, we're good to go!
Easier than I thought.
(CAR DOOR CLOSES)
The heater should be
working fine.
I left a blanket in there
for the horse,
but they're usually good
for some cold.
Cool, thanks.
You know, my family came
from there, back in the day.
Yeah, from New York?
You're a New Yorker?
Mohican.
My people wandered to Wisconsin,
that's polite company
for "got run off."
Grandfather went to Montana,
got married in the '30s.
Now home is here
with the Ampskapi Piikani,
the Blackfeet.
Just like your old horse
is gonna be home upstate.
(MELLOW MUSIC PLAYING)
You got bars?
ERIN: Yeah.
Just straight up that way,
100 meters away.
Okay. Nice to meet you!
You, too.
(MELLOW MUSIC CONTINUES)
(UPBEAT COUNTRY MUSIC
PLAYING ON RADIO)
♪ Looking for the sign
(SINGING ALONG) ♪ But here
I might learn how to rest
♪ I might learn
peace of mind
♪ The one who taught
my lesson was
♪ The soft wind
through the pines
♪ And I'm gonna be
a country girl again
♪ Oh, yes, I... ♪
What do you think
Mukki does for a living?
I don't know.
Did you see his keyring?
Yeah.
He's got a lot of keys.
NEWSREADER: (ON RADIO)
As Yellowstone Public
Radio News reports,
buckthorn is now pushing
out native vegetation
by the Yellowstone River,
in south eastern Montana.
McConnell:
Eventually we would end up
with dense shrub layers,
rather than the iconic
Yellowstone River
cottonwood forests,
that we have currently.
NEWSREADER: McConnell's
concerned that if left alone,
this insidious invasive could
overtake the entire park.
McConnell: Once it gets in,
it literally chokes out
everything else.
(ENGINE SWITCHES OFF)
CAL: What's up?
ERIN: It just started
losing power,
and cutting out and sputtering.
CAL: Let me look.
It's probably the fuel line.
(CAR DOOR SLAMS)
ERIN: Okay, wait,
let me help you.
Just stop, back up. Let me...
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Cal?
Hey, what's going on?
No.
Are you two okay?
Yeah, yeah,
I'm sure he can help.
Okay, I got it.
Thank you, you're a life saver.
Ah, don't worry.
Yeah, I'll keep you posted.
Here's the number.
Oh, no.
I'm not doing that.
He'll like hearing
from you better.
What do you mean?
Just stuff about the ranch.
What stuff about the ranch?
Nothing.
Just call him.
(KEYPAD DIALING)
(ERIN SIGHS)
Hi, Joey.
Yeah, yeah. It's me, hi.
Um...
Yeah, so I'm just here
for, really, just a bit,
just to see Dad, but...
(CONTINUES INDISTINCTLY)
(BIRD CAWING)
Well, that was awkward.
But I mean, he seems happy
to help, so...
Well, I mean, help me.
You're dead to him.
See, I told you.
ERIN: It was a joke,
he sounded fine.
He's just gonna be
a while, so...
Well, it could be worse.
Thanks.
(METAL CLANKS)
This rig is a piece of shit,
isn't it?
Yup.
You mind?
Not good for the palate,
but cooks all seem to smoke.
It confuses people.
You're a cook?
Mmm-hmm.
This little farm-to-table place,
near Red Hook, called Sinew.
In the Hudson Valley,
in New York.
Right.
Upstate.
Supposed to be ironic.
"Sinew."
Tough and strong,
not something anyone
would actually wanna eat.
(SCOFFS) Get it?
(CHUCKLES)
Our thing is that we use
the whole animal,
snout to tail.
You heard of that?
Mmm.
So, we kill it.
Cook it.
Serve it. All of it.
(ERIN SCOFFS)
When I first left here,
I went out and stayed with
my mother's sister in Albany.
You know, Deena?
She got me a job at this...
...diner near her.
It was a shit-hole,
but I liked it.
Loved cooking.
So...
Saved my money...
...and got into
the Culinary Academy,
and that was that,
now I'm a cook.
You know where we are?
Um...
MT-69, the middle of nowhere.
(CHUCKLES) Yeah, that.
(ERIN SMACKS LIPS)
But, no, we're 15 minutes
from Copperhead.
Yeah, I guess we are.
Let's go.
Really?
In for a penny...
Come on!
(CAL SIGHS)
(PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING)
ERIN: What's with this state,
and phone service?
CAL: Oh, yeah,
I remember where we are now.
ERIN: That's it, just pull up
right over there.
CAL: I didn't think
I'd ever be back here.
ERIN: Somehow,
I always thought I would.
(GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING)
ERIN: Wow,
you sort of forget...
CAL: And then, there it is.
(WIND WHISTLING)
This place always seemed
like a miracle to me.
Like they were building
something into the ground.
Not just digging a hole,
but actually making something.
Carving one shape
out of another.
I see now where
the engineer in you was born.
Yeah, from the belly
of the beast
that our dad helped shield
from government oversight.
(PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING)
Reminds me more
of Dante's Circles of Hell.
What?
Inferno, you read it?
The unbaptized
are in the first circle.
Then there's the gluttons.
The avaricious, the wrathful.
The heretics.
And our people,
the plunderers, the hypocrites.
You have this memorized?
Yeah.
Then the barrators...
The counselors of fraud,
my fave.
Wait, counselors of fraud,
really?
Yeah.
I mean, in translation, yeah.
CAL: That could have
been his business card.
Hmm.
You'd think they'd have filled
it in or something, by now.
Nah.
Cheaper and easier
to leave it alone
and keep everyone away.
Just another crime scene
out in the Old West.
Yeah, there should be
caution tape.
ERIN: Growing up,
we were so indoctrinated
with the whole Big Sky thing.
The field trips to
Yellowstone, endless horizons.
I really bought it.
Then after I left,
and being in New York,
I started wondering
if it's just so big that...
you lose any sense
of perspective at all.
If it's so big that you...
step outside and feel like
you're inside of something.
And now?
Have you found
your way out of it?
You know what
the final circle of hell is?
The very bottom of the pit?
It's reserved for the...
betrayers of
special relationships.
Like, community...
Kin.
We should go.
Okay.
Yeah.
CAL: When did you read
the Inferno?
Cooking school.
What where you
doing with him yesterday?
With who?
Dad, when I saw you.
You and Ace.
Um...
Ace was explaining to me
how a body can still react,
even after the brain
stops functioning.
Did you talk with Ace,
about us?
About me, what happened?
Why does it matter?
Just curious.
I was just explaining to him
what was going on...
Never mind, there's Joey.
(WINCH WHIRRING)
Erin, jeez!
Hey.
It's so good to see you!
ERIN: Yeah, good to see you.
Thanks for coming, Joe.
Yeah, sure.
Is this Mukki's old-ass truck?
You know Mukki?
Yeah, I know Mukki.
Okay, well, um,
I'll ride with you, yeah?
Okay. All right.
Uh, Cal, do you wanna follow us?
Yep.
JOEY: Cool.
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYING)
JOEY: My mom said she's known
where you've been
this whole time.
Yeah.
You always had a way with her.
I think she just understood,
that's all.
JOEY: Uh-huh.
(SIGHS) Man, you've been
missed around here.
I mean, Cal, you know,
but me, too.
The three of us being together.
I had to go.
Yeah, I get it.
You know, it's just...
It's just not the same place.
It's not the same place
without you home.
You know, I can fix this, uh,
old-ass truck for you
if you want?
Oh, yeah?
I think so.
Yeah, that would be great.
And if I can't, you know,
maybe you outta let me drive
you and Mr. T out east.
Why would you?
Why not?
Why wouldn't I help you?
It'd be fun.
And it's what's right.
Thank you, Joey.
I'll think about it, okay?
Okay.
You think about it. (LAUGHS)
(MANDOLIN STRUMMING)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
(CHICKENS CLUCKING)
(CHICKEN SQUEALING)
(KNIFE SLICES)
(BLOOD DRIPPING)
(BOWL CLATTERS)
(WINGS FLAPPING)
(FLAPPING STOPS)
(CONTINUES STRUMMING)
(MELANCHOLIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(SONG PLAYING ON VINYL)
♪ You walk the floor
♪ And leave the room
♪ You want me
far away from you
♪ But when you're tired
and laying down
♪ You seem to want me
back around
♪ Am I that easy
to see through? ♪
This is very beautiful, Erin.
ERIN: Well, there wasn't
much other than the bird,
but, the orchard still
has apples and honey, so...
Erin's a cook, Ace.
Ah, yes, I can see!
Some things are clear
without explanation, Cal.
Bon appetit.
(GLASSES CLINKING)
ACE: Mmm, that's good.
CAL: Mmm-hmm.
ACE: I remember
noticing the orchard
when I first arrived.
Makes the house so beautiful.
Yeah, and I'm okay with that.
CAL: Takes forever
getting anywhere.
Which is fine.
What I will never
get used to is the cold.
No one does.
(CHUCKLES)
CAL: You know what they say
about Montana.
You don't like the weather,
just wait five minutes.
(THUNDER RUMBLES)
(ACE CHUCKLES)
ERIN: So, um...
Ace.
I hear you've gotten
a little taste
of our family history
from my brother.
ACE: Ah, yes.
This is true.
Pretty rough, huh?
(LIGHTS FLICKERING)
(RECORD PLAYER DISTORTS)
Well, I mean, I'm glad you know.
Right? You should know, you
spend a lot of time with him.
You should know whose
asshole it is you're wiping.
Our asshole.
(ACE LAUGHS)
I can tell you,
to a nurse,
one asshole
is very much like another.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
Your father is a man
whose past is complete now.
Nothing more
will be added to his story.
He is the sum of his days.
(LIGHTS BUZZING)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(VENTILATOR BEEPING)
Excuse me.
This still happens?
I guess, I don't know.
(VENTILATOR BEEPING)
Okay.
CAL: Ace,
is everything all right?
ACE: The ventilator
backup power isn't working.
I have to bag him.
CAL: Uh, there used to be
a generator in the garage
for when this would happen.
Go, quickly!
(VENTILATOR BEEPING)
(DOOR CLOSES)
How long can you do that?
Uh, if the electricity
doesn't return,
we'll have to get him
to the hospital.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(RAIN POURING)
ACE: Over there.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
Fuck!
(VENTILATOR BEEPING)
What's going on?
Erin, I need you
to come over here.
Put both your hands on this,
do what you see me doing.
I can't.
Erin, now.
Erin, please,
we don't have time!
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
Watch your step,
watch your step.
This one down here.
Okay, and then
your left hand. Okay.
Okay.
I think he may be
having a heart attack.
Please, just be steady and
consistent, as you squeeze.
(ACE GRUNTING)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(RAIN SPATTERING)
(COUGHS, SPITS)
(SNIFFLING)
Please try and squeeze
more firmly, just a little.
(BREATH TREMBLING)
(ERIN SOBBING)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(GRUNTING)
(PANTING)
Well, I guess we don't
need the generator anymore.
What happened?
Erin?
Erin, what happened?
I should never
have come back here.
What happened?
I should never have
fucking come back here.
CAL: Erin?
I should never have come.
I mean, what the fuck?
Why did you just leave me
alone with him?
Erin, I'm sorry.
He had a heart attack!
What?
He had a fucking
heart attack! Are you deaf?
Why did you just
leave me alone with him?
Ace needed to do the chest
things, the compressions,
so I had to keep that bag
going with my hands.
I'm, like, breathing for him,
keeping him alive
with my fucking hands!
I just saved his life!
I feel sick.
(SIGHS)
Why did you leave me
alone with him?
CAL: Erin, I thought
I could get the generator.
Not tonight, seven years ago.
You saw what he was doing
to me, but you left.
You left me alone
with him. Why?
How?
I saw you there, and I thought,
he'll stop this.
He's gonna do something,
he'll save me.
I'm so sorry.
But you didn't!
What more did you need to see?
What did he have to do to me
to push you into that room?
That fucking room, right there?
I don't know.
I... I couldn't.
I was afraid.
And I didn't think that he...
That he'd kill me?
He almost killed me.
He broke my nose.
Separated my shoulder.
Cracked my ribs.
And it went on.
And it went on, and I
couldn't get him to stop!
And at the hospital,
they wanted to call the police,
but I wouldn't tell them
what happened.
(SOBBING)
I loved you, so much!
So much!
(SNIFFLING)
How could you just walk away?
I don't know.
How could you abandon...
I don't know!
I've been asking myself
that for seven years,
and I don't fucking know!
Am I a coward?
Is there something wrong
with me?
Every night I close my eyes,
and all I see is your face.
That look on your face,
pleading with me
to make him stop.
And every night I wake up,
and I think that
something must be wrong.
That can't be what happened.
I couldn't have walked away.
(SOBS)
But I did.
That is what happened.
And that's how
it's always gonna be.
I didn't stop him.
I didn't even try.
And I am sorry, I really am.
(CAL SNIFFLES)
I missed you.
So much.
(SIGHS)
Yeah.
Yeah, me, too.
Okay.
(BOTH SIGH HEAVILY)
(ERIN SNIFFLES)
(BREATH TREMBLING)
(SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING)
(CAL PANTING)
(PANTING)
(SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES)
Why don't you go get some rest?
You can use my room,
I'll sit with him.
That is okay.
I'm good, Cal.
Really, I'd like to.
ACE: It has been
a trying night...
I need to be
alone with him, now.
Okay.
I'm going to go for a walk.
I see the rain has stopped.
Good night, Cal.
(VENTILATOR BEEPING)
I would have liked to
have known Erin's mom.
To see how happy she made you.
But maybe
that's just a story, right?
That you told yourself.
And us.
Your great love for Libby.
Your great sadness
when she died.
It was something my mother
always took in stride.
Being less for you.
An afterthought.
Much like she accepted
your anger,
and your distraction.
All just...
part of the package.
But Erin was different.
It hurt her,
and you couldn't see that.
You couldn't see
why she did what she did,
how much she needed you.
I used to think to myself,
how can someone so smart
be so dumb?
Now I wonder...
how could someone so loved
have been so cruel?
You lived as if life
were a sad burden.
Maybe being dead will be better.
(CAL WHISPERS INDISTINCTLY)
(SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING)
(VENTILATOR BEEPS, FLATLINES)
(SOBS)
(WIND WHISTLING)
ACE: During the power failure,
he may have experienced
a cardiac event.
But after, yes, he was stable.
For a time.
Did you call the hospital?
No, the storm had not stopped,
and, his vital signs
were strong.
Our decision,
my decision,
was to wait until morning.
But most sadly, then, he passed.
(SIGHS)
They're taking the body away.
Hey, Mr. T.
Hey.
Hey, beauty.
Did you get a hold of Joey?
Yeah.
And?
He likes the idea.
(AMBULANCE DOORS CLOSE)
Are you going to be okay?
Yeah.
(AMBULANCE DRIVES AWAY)
Thank you.
Ace, how many of these
have you had,
your patients?
Um...
I don't know.
I guess it's not something
that I like to count.
No.
Of course not.
(COUNTRY-FOLK MUSIC PLAYING)
♪ Cowboys and Indians
♪ And trees he could climb
♪ Tomorrow came too fast
♪ But he didn't mind
♪ The distance was short
♪ So light it again
♪ It don't take no time
♪ To get where I am
♪ But one paper kid
♪ Wasn't really so mean
♪ Just a little bit scared
♪ And a little bit green
♪ And he heard of a place
♪ Where it's legal to dream
♪ So he sat with his coffee
♪ In a blue Texas wind
♪ And wrote on a rock
♪ The one paper kid
♪ He's rollin' again
♪ He's rollin' again ♪
(ENGINE STOPS)
ANNOUNCER: (ON PA)
The curbside
is for immediate loading
and unloading only.
Violators may be
ticketed and towed.
Thank you for driving me.
Yeah, sure.
Of course.
Thank you for coming home.
Okay.
Call me.
Yeah.
Soon.
I will.
You, too.
Okay.
Drive safe, back to Cheyenne.
(SENTIMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING)
What kind of cat is Oscar Wilde?
He's an ornery gray tabby.
He would be.
Okay.
Bye.
(MELLOW MUSIC PLAYING)
(MR. T NEIGHS)
JOEY: (GRUNTS) I'm comin'.
I'm comin'.
All right, come on.
(MR. T WHINNIES)
Easy, boy.
Yeah, I know.
Beautiful, innit?
All right, here we go Mr. T.
What do you think?
It's all yours.
Go on.
Go on, now!
(MR. T WHINNIES)
Hey.
Hoka hey!
Montana horse
still wants to run, innit?
Sure seems that way.
Maybe you ought a try
running after him. (CHUCKLES)
You'd be surprised.
I'll give him a head start.
We have plenty of time.
Yeah.
(UPLIFTING GUITAR MUSIC
PLAYING)
(HORSE WHINNIES)
♪ Remember me as a baby
♪ Remember me as a child
♪ The night is coming on now
♪ And children
♪ It's my time
♪ To bloom
♪ Like a flower
(MUSIC PLAYING)
♪ Take my hand, daughter
♪ It's been such a long,
long time
♪ I want to feel blood
on my blood
♪ I want to feel
your eyes on mine
♪ And remember me as a baby
♪ Remember me as a child
♪ The night is coming on now
♪ And children
♪ It's my time
♪ To bloom
♪ Like a flower
♪ Like a flower ♪
(MUSIC CONTINUES)
(MUSIC ENDS)
(BIRDS CHIRPING)