♪ He's got it
♪ He's got everything
♪ Uh-huh
[♪ Calypso ]
♪ In the island
♪ He's the man
♪ He's the only man
♪ For you and me
♪ I love the man
who love to trip ♪
♪ Love to trip
♪ That is a girl's fantasy
♪ Fantasy
♪ In the island
♪ He's your man
♪ He's the only man
♪ For you and me
♪ Ooh ♪ Just chillin'
♪ Ooh, ooh
♪ Trippin'
♪ Feelin' giddy
♪ Gettin' jiggy
♪ Time for playin'
♪ Know what I'm sayin'?
No worries ♪
♪ In the island
♪ He's the man [ Snoring ]
♪ He's the only man
♪ For you and me
♪ He's the man [ Snoring Continues ]
♪ Who loves to trip
♪ The only man
♪ Who love to trip
[ Snoring Continues ]
[♪ Hip-hop ]
Mm-hmm! Whoo!
Mmm! Huh!
[ Chuckles ]
♪ I got everything
♪ Any man can ever want
♪ More money
than the banker's vault ♪
♪ Your girl's jacket,
it ain't my fault ♪
♪ I got benzos
and limousines ♪
♪ You be like me
in your dreams ♪
♪ He's got it,
Everything ♪
♪ G's got it,
♪ He's got everything
♪ Yeah, I got style
Everything I do with class ♪
♪ Hit records
coming out my ass ♪
♪ I got more power
than a blast of napalm ♪
♪ What's the bomb?
Me at your prom ♪
♪ He's got it,
Everything ♪
♪ G's got it,
♪ He's got everything
♪ He's got it,
Everything ♪
♪ G's got it
[ Alarm Clock Buzzing ][ Woman ]
Gregory Reed!
[ Alarm Continues ]
Greg, school time.
I'm not gonna tell you
again, boy!
[ Whimpering ]
Damn.
Jamal,
get outta my bed, man.
Ow! My butt.
[ Man ]
Greg. Greg!
[ Woman On TV, Faint ]Oh, there you are, boy.
Sit down and eat.
Greg pushed me
out the bed, Ma.
No, I didn't.
Shut up, you little punk.
Don't call him that.
And I heard him hit the floor.
[ Chuckles ]You, right here.
Would somebody
please pass me the bacon?
Here you go, Granddaddy.
You can have some of mine.
No, he can't.
Eat the food, boy.
Oh, Ma, Dad, when you all
gonna hook a brother up
with some "mins" for the prom?
When you ask me
in English,
I'll answer you.
I want bacon! I want bacon!
I want bacon!
No. Now take these pills.
The doctor said
to avoid meat.
So I die Wednesday
instead of Thursday.
Who gives a shit?[ Chuckles ]
If I don't get some bacon,
I'm gonna spit
all over everybody's food!
Oh, not today.Uh-uh. No.
All right, all right.
Here. Take the damn bacon.
And cut the shit!
You're a good boy, Son.
[ Refined Accent ]
Parents, can you find it
in your heart...
to give your son
some money to fund
his senior prom activities?
No.Hell, no!
Aw, come on.
It's my senior prom.
Bacon!Oh, Lord. It's 7:15 already.
Greg, you have a job.
You can fund
your own prom activities.
I can't get a fly tux
with what I make
at the Rib Shack.
[ Father ] Told you
to save your money, boy.Mmm. Mmm. Mmm.
But, no, you had
to go buy some $150
tennis shoes.
You know in some
foreign countries,
for $150 you can buy
some damn feet?
Daddy, they're Jordans.
Necessary gear for a brother.
You will be necessarily naked
at the prom, 'cause you ain't
gettin' no money here.
[ Scoffs ]
Daddy.Don't even try it.
Gramps, can you help me?Why you askin' me?
I just had to show my ass
to get a strip of bacon.
[ Chuckles ]Why y'all coming down on me?
'Cause you're a senior,
and you haven't filled out
one college application yet.
What the hell?
Greg, you promised me
you'd take care of that.
I-I'ma get round to it.Then we'll get round to givin'
you money for the prom.
[ Mother ]
Greg, what are you gonna do
after you graduate?
You better think
about your future, boy.Your father and I go out...
You are about
to graduate outta here.
We have asked you
to do one little thing.
Fill out
the college applications...[ Voices Fading Out ]
[ Women ]
♪ G's got it
[ Chattering ]
[ Woman ]
Ladies, do you want
some grapes?
I want some grapes.
When are you getting
in here?
Well, Greg,
I'll get right down to it.
We want you
at Harvard University.
I think you'd fit right in.Well, of course he would.
Greg is a wonderful son.[ Chuckles ]
He makes me want to have sex
with his mama again.
Oh.[ All Laugh ]
What kind of honeys
y'all got up in there?
Well, Harvard boasts
some of the most refined,
intelligent young women
in the...Next!
Greg, my brother,
you don't need to be educated
by the white man.
Now, Morehoward,
this country's premier
black university,
wants you.
Yeah, well, uh,
you see, my son...
is concerned
about what kind of women
y'all have up there.
[ Greg ]
That's right.Because, you see,
we expect him to get
a whole lot of sex
while he's in college.
My people. My people.
Mo-Ho has some of the finest
sisters in the world.[ Woman ] That's right.
And they give it up easy.
Good, 'cause I don't like
my son to have to wait
for the booty.
Now let's cut to the chase.
What kind of basketball team
y'all got up there?
Uh, team?
You see, we got a team, but...
[ Chuckles ]
Where did y'all place
in the N.C.A.A. finals
last year?
Um, we got the bombest
lacrosse team
in the country, bro.
Negro, say what?Lacrosse, brother.
You want my son
to play lacrosse?
Get out!
But-But, brother, we...Out!
Before I have to kick your ass
lacrosse the street!
Out! Get out![ Man ]
Give Mo-Ho a chance.
[ Recruiter ]
What about
the United Negro College Fund?
Peace out, my brother.
Greg, how about coming
to Minnesota?
[ Scoffs ]
Minnesota?
What do y'all have to offer
up in cow country?
Um, welcome to
the Twin Cities, Greg.
[ Gasps ] ♪ Will you give me
all your attention? ♪
♪ 'Cause the love
I'm talkin' about ♪
♪ Love, love,
sweet love ♪
♪ Love, love
[ Greg ] Yeah ♪ Can you give me
Your sweet smile? ♪
I'm worried about you, boy. [ Needle Scratches,
Music Stops ]
[ Chuckles ]
That's a good yolk.
Y'all need to taste this yolk.
Greg, what are you doin'?Greg's trippin' again.
You better stop
all that daydreamin', boy.
There ain't
nothin' wrong
with daydreamin'.
Well, there is if you
ain't doing nothin'
with your life.
Greg, life is real.
It's time for you
to get real with it.
No prom money unless you get
some college applications goin'.
That's right. Not a penny.What are you gonna do
about your life?
[ Man ]
Man, fuck college!
My Mom's always be nagging me
about college too.
I just ignore her.
Yeah, I told my old lady
I ain't even tryin'
to hear that shit.
Nah, you couldn't
have said that.
You still got your teeth.
[ Sneezes ]Damn, man.
Oh, no. You just did not spit
on everybody back here.
[ Man ]
Cover your mouth.
Whoa![ Gasps ]
Excuse you!My bad.
[ Chuckles ]
[ Cell Phone Ringing ]
Hello? What's up?
[ Man ]
I haven't made up
my mind about the prom yet.
People got scars.
They break dancin'
on Formica and stuff.
You gotta understand.
Hey, June.
Let me call you back,
all right?
What's up, man?What's up, baby?
Listen, man...What?
I'm gonna tell you
right now, watches
are five dollars today.
Whoo!And I got this
nice little Discman.
Man, you breakin'
in like a swap meet.
Wait a minute.
This is Kurtis Blow's.
Where'd you get this from?
It's old.Yeah, it's old school,
but check it out.
I got it for $80.Uh-huh.
I'll sell it to you for 20.
What's up?Twenty?
Twenty dollars.All right. I got 15.
All right, bet.All right?
You cool with that?
I'm cool with that.
Hook it up. Hook it up.
You put a CD
in here for me?
You hook me up?
Yeah, it's free,
all right?
It's some old school stuff,
but you know, I got you.
Yo, June,
what are you selling now?
Disc players, man.
Pookie hooked me up.
Where'd he get 'em from?You know.
Truck goes over a bump,
about 12 of those bad boys
fall off a truck,
and there you go.
June, they're stolen,
just like them vibrators
you had last week.
Man, you gotta get out
of this mess.
It's that old school zag.
June! June!
All right, remember this?
June, you got
the CD's all day.
Hey, Greg.
June, I got our colors
picked out for the prom.
What?You're taking me,
remember?
No, I'm not.
Wait a minute.
I already got the dress.
Oh, well,
I changed my mind.After you got with me?
No. No, it wasn't right
after I got with you.
That was two weeks ago.
You know you lyin'!
Nigga, do you know
how much money
my mama spent on that dress?
June, watch out, man.
Women take prom seriously.
Oh, man,
I got it all under control.That's what you think, man.
What's up, my brothers?Man, we just finished
getting chased...
Fish man!by some beastie women.
Don't do that, brother.I can't believe
y'all still going to class.
[ Greg ] What's the haps
on the sneak party?
You got the 411?
[ Fish ]
Man, I don't know right now,
but I'm on it like funk on pig.
Whoa!
That's what
I'm talkin' about.
Whoo. Check me out, y'all.
[ June ] Put it on tape.[ Greg ] Is he crazy,
messin' with Snap's girl?
[ Fish ]
Man, I'd like
to unsnap her bra.
Hello, Miss Dennia.Hello yourself.
[ Greg ]
That's the kind of flirtin'
that'll leave your ass hurtin'.
[ Fish ]
It's worth it.
Look at the back, y'all.
[ Greg ]
Film that, man.
You gotta remember this.
He gonna get his ass whooped
fuckin' with her.That's what I'm talkin' about.
Last tape... Oh!
Oh, what's up, Snap?
How you?
Oh, have you?Uh-huh.
So, if you basically stick
to the 23rd page...
Do you think I'm stupid?
Uh... no!
[ Man ]
Hey, yo, I wouldn't
tape that if I was you.
Hold up.
[♪ Whistling ]What you looking at, sissy?
That you, Snap?
Boo![ Woman ]
That boy is so crazy.
He gonna hit a blind man.[ Greg ] You need to take it
out in the field.
[ Fish ]
Get me a date
for the prom, June.
Who can resist
the twist, huh?
You know, quite a few people.
You ugly.
Oh, I'm ugly,
just 'cause I don't
wear makeup like you, huh?
Yo, that was skin cleanser,
man.Oh, skin cleanser.
Yes.Like to keep it right
next to the tampons.
Fish, you're not ugly,
all right? ♪ G, you've got everything
[ Argument continuing ]
Cinny!
It's time, baby.
[ Babbles, Barks ]
[ Growls ]
Time? Time for what?
For me and you, girl.Oh. I understand.
Tell me
what you want, baby.
[ Fish's Voice ]
$500.
Huh?It's only $500.
Say what?All we need is $500
to get that limo. That's it.
[ Together ]
Nah, man.
Man, y'all buggin', man.
Hey.What's up, June?
It's in style, man.
We can get jiggy with it.
[ Woman ]
Do you have a prom date yet?[ June ] Yeah.
Who is she? Tay-Tay?No.
Shaneekwa?No. Hell, no.
Nozinga?No. Y...
When I roll up, you'll see.
You'll be surprised.When you roll up?
When I roll up.Oh.
All right?
Mm-hmm. Okay.[ Fish ] They got liquor
in the limo. Don't drink it.
'Cause if you drink
the limo liquor,
you alcoholic.
And let's call
some hookers, man.
In the limo.
Did you see that kiss?[ Scoffs ]
Yes.
We going to the prom.Oh, God. June?
Why? You know he has a girl.
He got a lot of girls.
Well, I'm gonna be
that girl that goes
to the prom.
You have to be more realistic.
[ Gasps ]
Ooh, what about Rashid?Rashid?
Yes,Uh-uh.
His dashiki stay dirty.
Mm-mmm. That's you.
Yes, it is.Uh-uh. No.
Okay, everybody. Quiet. Quiet.[ Chattering ]
I know you want to talk about
what you did last night,
but this is something
that's very important.
Something that took place
about 60 years ago.
So we have to talk about it.
Harlem Renaissance.
Some brothers and sisters
wrote a lot of good stuff then.
[ Student Coughs ]The end!
[ Laughing ]No, but seriously, people,
we all make
our own philosophy.
We just have to learn
to articulate it, all right?
Now, the Harlem Renaissance
writers...
put their philosophy
into their works.
What I want you to do
is to put your work
into action.
Miss Hawkins,
I'm a prospective employer,
so I'm trying to see if I
should give you a job
or to dump you like
so much unemployable trash.
So I want you
to describe yourself to me.
Well, I would say
that I'm a hard worker,
and my G.P.A. is...
Miss Hawkins,
I'm a crazy employer.
[ Babbles ]
I majored in philosophy.
I'm a nut.
I want you to give me
the essence of yourself,
the reason beyond
the obvious as to why
I should hire you.
Well, then I'd say...
that I am the light
that illuminates the answers...
to everything
you need to know.
[ Students jeering ][ Woman ]
Go, girl!
[ Chuckling ]
That's my cousin. She's so deep.
Damn, that's all right.
Miss Hawkins, you are hired.
You get the job,
you get the bonus...
and the company car,
which is not quite
as nice as mine.[ Students Laugh ]
Mr. Reed? Mr. Reed!
Hmm? What? Yeah.
[ Coughs ]
Me too.
Oh, Harlem is in New York.
Yeah, it's in New York. Yeah.
Got a cousin
that lives there. Mm-hmm.
Mr. Reed,
you don't get the job,
you don't get the bonus,
and I kick your butt
out the door.
Here's the bottom line,
students.
If you don't know yourself,
what do you know?
School has got
to be about more
than just memorizing...
what great people did.
Or playing it safe.
It is learning
to find your own greatness.
[ Sighs ]
All right. Listen up.
I know the movie's an old one,
but the message in it
is still relevant.
[ Whirring ]
It's called Mission Life.
[♪ Orchestral ]
Hello, seniors.
"Seniors"...
Sounds good, doesn't it?
Well, with this new status
comes real responsibility.
[ Continues, Faint ][ Women ]
♪ G, G, G
[ Woman Screaming ]
Oh, God, he's here!
Oh, God! He's here!
He's here! Oh, God!
[ Cheering, Squealing ]
Students! Students, please!
Calm down! Calm down!
Calm down!
It is my honor and privilege
to introduce to you...
that renowned author, poet,
and my former student,
G. Reed!
[ Screaming ]
Thank you.
[ Clears Throat ]
I really didn't have time
to come here,
but Mr. Shapic
is my boy and shit.
[ Chuckling ]And shit.
His words are so powerful.
Mm-hmm.Yeah. True.
Before I go, I'd like
to leave you with a poem
from my new collection,
G's Ghetto Mine,
Volume Two.
Trumpet! Trumpet!
This is called,
"Don't Be Fuckin' with My Shit."
Don't be fuckin'
with my shit.
Ooh.
Get your own stuff,
you greedy bitch.
Yeah!
Keep your hands
off my clothes
and your eyes off my cash,
or I'll break off a size 12
in your motherfuckin' ass!
[ Laughing ]
If I find two dollars,
when I know I had seven...
Preach! Preach!
I'll be on your monkey ass
like five minutes to 11:00.
So your eyes may look,
and your teeth may grit,
but don't be fuckin'...
[ Together ]
With my shit.
[ Cheering ]
For the ladies.
[ Chuckling ]
[ Screams ][ Giggling ]
Separate the crowd.
Separate the crowd.Come on.
[ Man ]
Move back! Move back! Get back!
Move! You got to move!
G. Reed! G. Reed!
I can't find
the words to say how...
brilliant you are.
[ Greg ]
Don't need no words, baby.
Don't need no words.
I got a few words for you, baby.
[ Gasps ]
Mr. Shapic, don't do that!Oh, you hold tight.
Yes, Greg, I see you
staring at Ms. Hawkins
all the time.
All the time? Not me.Mm-hmm. Yes, you.
Greg, that young lady
is one of the most
exceptional students...
I've ever had
the pleasure
of being around.
You can just look at her
and see that she's destined
for greatness.
Men are drawn to women
with greatness
in them, Greg.
We need that power
to fuel our own dreams.
And you know what?
You'll never have her.
You don't get
to the moon, Greg,
riding a bicycle.
And you certainly don't
get a fine young lady
like Ms. Hawkins, half-assing.
I ain't half-assing.
I gave a bad answer.
No, it's more than that.
Greg, I've watched you
become a young man here.
I've also watched you
become afraid of trying
to better yourself.
Afraid?
I'm about to graduate.
A high school diploma
just gets you into the game.
The real deal starts
when school ends.
That's when life begins.
Now, look,
I have information for you
on community colleges,
armed services,
trade schools, whatever...Trade school?
I don't want
to go to trade school.
That's for stupid people.
No, prison
is for stupid people.
It's time for hard choices,
and only you can make 'em.
[♪ Hip-hop ][♪ Woman Vocalizing ]
Annetta. Come on.♪ Come on
Come on, G.
You been scopin' Cinny
for what, three years now?
We got a month left
of school.
If not now, when?
Go talk to her.
[♪ Vocalizing ]
Man!Don't hurt yourself.
Don't hurt yourself.
[ Cinny ] One more time.[♪ Annetta
Continues Vocalizing ♪]
♪ Just wave your hands
from side to side ♪
♪ If you want to be down
see your eyes open wide ♪
♪ Chocolate man,
what's up with the tan? ♪
Y-You got a nice flow
to your rap.Thanks.
Greg.Right.
Look, you can't come at her
with that weak game.
Do a math problem for her.
Help her out.
Annetta, stop.I'm just saying.
Listen. Hey, Greg?
We'll do you a favor.
We don't want your boys
to think you got dissed,
so we'll smile
and act nice.
[ Chuckles ]Bye.
Right. Exactly.
See you soon.Ooh. Yeah.
[ Sniffs, Clears Throat,
Chuckles ]
What's with that?[ Annetta ]
Walk it off, sweetie.
He's kinda cute though.
[ Chuckling ]
You see that, my brother?
You get them digits?No.
I ain't see shit.
[ Tires Screeching ]
What's up, my brothers?
[ Chuckling ][ Siren Blaring ]
Get in. Hurry! Hurry, man.
Old man Francis is comin'.
He's lookin' for this cart.
Come on, let's go.Let's ride, baby!
Let's ride!
Go! Go!Get back here!
[ Mother ]
Greg, I have something for you.
It's a book that
teaches you how to fill
out college applications.
Well,
say something, boy.
Yeah, boy,
answer your mama.
Jamal. Well, Greg?
Thanks.
I'll read it later.
Will somebody pass me
the sausage?
Comin' right up, Daddy.
You're a good boy, Son.
I want you to read that book
and apply to some colleges.
Your father and I will
help you where we can.
So if I read the book,
I can get money for the prom?
College first, prom later.
Yo, I ain't missin'
the prom.[ Coughs ]
[ Spitting ]
This ain't sausage!
It's turkey sausage, Daddy.
I am a 75-year-old black man
from Alabama,
and I want my pork!
Pork is not good for you.
Pork got me to be 75!
And what sick mother
would make sausage
out of a goddamn turkey?
Will you just try
and eat it, please?
What does a man have to do
to get some food
around in this...
Fuck it.
[ Chuckles ]
Dad, come back.
Don't go nowhere.
Damn. Daddy.
Daddy!
Jamal, go to your room
and get ready.
[ Sighs ]
Dang.
You know, why don't we
just let him eat
what he wants?
Don't you worry
about what we do.
That's our problem.
But you're gonna
have some big problems
if you don't
start fillin' out
those college applications.
Don't I have something to say
about what I do with my life?No.
And your life
is part of ours.
That's why they call it
a family.
So I say that our part
of your life...
is takin'
its ass to college.
[ Fish ] Y'all want a ride?[ June ] In your car?
[ Greg, June ]
Hell, no!
Oh, well, be Spike
and get on the bus.
My engine roars, baby.
[ Engine Backfiring ]
Sound like your engine
got the flu, dog.Like it's constipated.
Yo somebody get
the hood, man.Oh, damn. Oh...
Just needs some adjustment.
That's all. That's all.
Damn.
[ Coughing ]
[♪ Hip-hop Blaring ][ Fish ]
Yo, do me a favor, man.
Oh, shoot.
Robo-thug and Dumpy.
I could've went
a whole day without
seeing these asses, man.
[♪ Continues ]
[ Cackling ]
Hey, you know what?
I bet every last one
of you bitch-ass niggas...
get "a-spended" from school.[ Laughing ]
Lazy-tongue asshole.Word.
Nigga, what you trying to talk
to me like I ain't got
a "diplomay"?
Nigga, I kick your ass,
you bitch-ass nigga!
[♪ Ends ]Talking to me like
I gotta "artificate"...
in every class
that I was in.
Who you think you talking to,
gettin' smart with the lips?
Is his name June, July, August?
Whatever it is...
What's up, man?I need to rap with you
about your little side thing
you got goin' on.
Nobody here need to answer
to you two, all right?
No, no, no, baby.
It ain't all right.
This here...
this Kenyatta's hood.That's right.
You want to sell
a cough drop up in here,
you got to ask permission.
Where... Where... Where...We don't even let them little
Girl Scouts sell them cookies...
unless we get
a cut of that shit,
you bitch-ass nigga.
'Cause we running things,
all right?
'Cause we here,
we regulate this
whole neighborhood.
All right?Yo!
You ain't runnin' no...
Let me get at them
for a second.
[ Laughs ]
Yeah.Who that over there?
Who that is, nigga?Your baby's dad.
Who that is, you bitches?Go and talk to him, man.
Take your ass over there.Go on.
Go on.[ Laughing ]
[ Chuckling ]
Hey. Yo, Mr. Kenyatta, man.
I ain't mean to get all
in your business and stuff.
It's... You know...
He didn't know nothin'.
I didn't know nothin'.
Nobody knew nothin'.
That's why we're in school
tryin' to learn.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Fellas, chill.
What do I look like,
some kind of devil?
Hey, you African
booty scratcher.[ Chuckling ]
Lookin' like you just got off
the Amistadparty boat.
"Cinque, give us free!"
Uh-huh. I'll give you
some fat-free water.
That's what you need.
Hey, look, man.
Why don't you go ahead
and fix your car, man?
You messin' up
the ozone layer.[ Chuckling ]
I know,
I got a bad "notobriety."
Notoriety.
Say what?
I... I think the word you're
looking for is notoriety,
not "notobriety."
Boy, I got a degree
when I was in the joint!
You got a damn degree?
Hey, hey, hey.
My boy here, he's just dumb.
You gotta pardon him, man.
He got a bad "notobriety"
for being stupid.Boop. Oh, not that.
Yeah.
See, I like you, June.
You're all right, brother.
You's a hustler,
just like I was.
So, I got a proposition
for you.
Come work for me,
I give you a cut
on what you make.
No. No, man,
I can't work for you.
I work for Pookie.
Pookie? You ain't heard?
Uh, Pookie had
a freak accident, man.
The brother ran himself over
with his own car.
Hey, man, uh,
are those legs recyclable,
Mr. Gump?
'Cause you know what?
I need a screw.
Let me get one of them.
[ Chuckling ]
I screwed your mama.You know what?
I know why
your car broke, nigga.
Why's that?
'Cause every time
your little black ass
get out of it,
the oil light come on,
nigga.
You're just mad, man,
'cause you can't do this.
[ Cackles ]
Yeah, but what happens
when he wants you
to steal some old lady's car?
You got my word, man.
Electronics
is all you'll sell.
And when you're ready,
you come talk to me.
Leave your boy here behind.
He's a real "dubiostic" type.
Peace!
Get my door.
What is "dubiostic"?Man, I don't know.
The fuck is "dubiostic"?
[♪ Rock ]
♪ I got that
itchy-gootchy feeling ♪
♪ Up and down my spine Hey, Mr. Collins.
It's about time
you got here, boy.
Wrap up that,
uh, rib for me, please.
I want you to put up
some flyers at school.
I'm runnin'
a senior prom special.
All the ribs you can eat
for 19.99. Get it?
[ Laughs ]
Oscar Nicholson's doing
the same thing prom night.
Nic Burgers?He stole that idea from me.
Damn Nicholson.
I think a lot of kids want
to go to a fancy restaurant.
First-class service.
Red carpet, you know.
All I want you to do
is pass out the flyers,
and make sure your friends
come over here prom night.
Okay, I'll try.Try?
Don't try, Greg. Do.
[ Woman ]
I want beef ribs and coleslaw.Hey, Cinny.
Greg. You work here?
Oh yeah, I'm the, uh,...
assistant executive manager.
Yeah. I run the whole spot
when Dale's gone.
You want me to hook you up?
I got some ham hocks,
fried gizzards, neck bones...I'm cool.
Just made a fresh bucket
of chitlins.Who is this?
Oh. Uh, hey,
I'm just, you know...
I was just...Yeah, you was just nothin'.
You need to step off.Phillip, sit down.
[ Phillip ]
I'm sure he's got something
to clean up in this place. Whoo.
That was not necessary.Hey, hey, hey, hey.
I'm sorry I'm late.
What did you say you were
doing Saturday night? Um...
Oh, I have a college
orientation meeting.
Uh-huh.
Um, what about this?
Two tickets
to Lauryn Hill.
Uh... Uh-uh. You lyin'.
Oh, but that's not all.
Uh-uh.
Pow-yow. Mm-hmm.Backstage passes?
Baby, where
did you get these?Mmm.
Ah.
Oh, maybe
I should reschedule.Mm-hmm.
I thought after that we could
maybe hit an after-party,
and then take a walk
along the beach,
and, you know.
Look, this meeting
is really important to me, baby.
I'm sorry. I can't.
What you doin'?[ Cinny ]
You know, I mean...
It's college.
It's my future.
And every time I have
an orientation meeting,
you throw something
like that at me.
Now you know,
that's not fair.That is not true.
[ Man ]
Watch that door.
Somebody get some grease
on that door.
Gimme some
barbecue sauce, boy,
so I can put it on,
and you know, lick it off.
Go on.
Get outta the way.Oh, man, what the... Oh!
Damn!
Shoot!
Oh, damn!
[ Woman ]
♪ Oh, G
[ Electronic beeping ]
[ Schwarzenegger Voice ]
All ugly motherfuckers
must leave now.
Oops, I'm gone.What the...
Yo, Z-boy.What?
LaDennis.Yeah.
Pop some caps in his ass!
That's your ass,
you bitch-ass nigga!
[ Man Shouts ][ Woman Screams ]
Die!
Yeah![ Laughing ]
Take your Eddie Murphy Raw,
Terminator-lookin'...
Oh, shit.
[ Spitting ][ Bullets Hitting Floor ]
[ Man ]
What the fuck?[ Snorts ]
[ LaDennis ]
Shorty, this pleather
coat-wearing motherfucker...
spittin' bullets
out his nose, man.
Spit this out.
[ Groans ]
[ Bones Crack ][ Groans ]
Aw, fuck this!
Yes, nigga.
I'm cripply-crazy, nigga.
Cripply crazy. Come on!
[ Groans ]
You don't like that,
huh? Huh?
Uh-oh.
You trying to disable
a motherfucker, huh?
Oh, shit!
Bye, Mama.
Hey! "Schwarzenigga"!
You know,
I get sick of people
coming from the "fruture,"
and fucking with
a brother!
I'm about to get off
on your "robotiniacal" ass.
Try it!
You're a fucking bonehead.
[ Grunts, Groans ]
[ Phillip Whimpering ]
Oh, no. No.
Don't!
This is my boyfriend.
Don't beat him down
and make him cry like a bitch
in front of all these people.
Then come with me.
You better get your ass
outta this booth!
All right!Get up!
I ain't goin' out like this!
I'm gonna get you!
I'm sorry!
[ Shrieking ]
It's hot, goddamn it!
[ Sobbing, Moaning ]
[ Phillip ]
There are a million women...
who would die to go
to this concert with me.
[ Scoffs ]
Oh, really?Yeah, really.
Well, go with one of them.
See? There you go.
Come back on Thursday.
We havin' pigs' feet
and okra.
I'll hook you up.
[ Chuckles ]
[ Man ]
♪ Lean on me
♪ So hold your head up
♪ There's gonna be
rough times ♪
♪ But the rough times
sure enough go ♪
♪ Hold your head high
♪ Up to the sky
♪ Let me tell you why
'Cause it's shinin' ♪
Damn. ♪ The sun is shinin'
Whoo.
You'd be good
for my prom picture.
Do you read?
Well, reading isn't required.
[ Chuckles ]
Just stand there
and look pretty for me.
You need to stop.Well, forget you then,
Urkel.
[ Groans ]
It is so hard being
a black woman these days.
Don't start, Annetta.
You have plenty of time
to find a prom date.
Hey, you want me to ask
Phillip to hook you up
with his friend?
I don't need a man.
I mean, my personality
and my mind is all I need.
You guys are juniors,
you understand?
You juniors,
you gotta handle your business.
[ Man ]
All right, man.
Good lookin' out.
[ June ]
So, who's gonna
take over the legacy?
June!
Excuse me.
Get outta the way.
Get outta my way.
Excuse me.
[ Woman ]
Where is that...
Where...
Ooh.
Cinny, I gotta talk to you.
Hi, Greg.
Look, stop pushing up
on my cousin.
Take that discount-player act
on the road.
[ Cinny ]
Annetta. Midterm.
[ Sighs ]
Girl, I'll see you
at fifth period.
Okay.Don't look at me.
Bye.
[♪ Humming ]
Oop, I need these right here.
Uh... Duh...
Oh, hey, Cinny.
[ Chuckles ]
Um yeah, look,
I was wondering if, um...
I mean, we've
been going to school
for a number of years now,
and the whole barbecue incident
probably kills all of this,
but what I really
wanted to know was, um...
Greg, I have a boyfriend.
How you know
that's what I want?
Oh. Sorry. That was
kind of conceited of me.
What do you want?
To be your boyfriend.[ Scoffs ]
No, Cinny.
Wait, wait. Hold on.
Cinny, come on.
You know I was jokin'
about the boyfriend thing.
I don't have time to be
anyone's boyfriend
in the first place...
filling out
college applications,
and all.
Oh. Yeah,
that's hard work, right?Yeah, of course.
Where are you applying?
State, university...
all of them. You know.
Yeah. You must be
on, uh, wait listed
or late admissions.
There you go.
Whoo. It's a trip.
How'd your S.A.T.'s
turn out?Good, good. Big numbers.
Look here,
I was wondering if...
You know,
I really need someone
to talk to about this
whole college thing.
I mean, everyone around here
tryin' to distract
a brother...
when he's tryin' to get
his college on.
You know what I mean?
I mean...
They just make it...
so hard.
Now you know
you need to quit.
Okay, not that hard.
[ Chuckles ]
Look, um, Greg,
I don't mind hooking up
to talk about college.
Cool. Cool.Um, here.
Call me.Will do.
Okay.
[ Chuckles ]
All right.
Hey, I was looking
for this.
Oh, yeah. Go ahead.
You can take it.
Yeah, I read it.
Go ahead. It's a good book.
[ Chuckling ]
Wait a minute.
He told you he was taking
you to the prom?
Yes. What did he tell you?He told me he was taking me.
[ Greg ]
Yeah. Got them digits,
my brother.
All right.
A hundred more,
and you'll be like me, man.
Man, go ahead.Hey, Greg, do me a favor.
What's that?Hold this.
Is that his friend Greg?Greg, where's June?
He went that way.
Get his ass.
I am gonna find him,
and I'm gonna kick his ass.
I'm tired...
Women be trippin', man.
[ Man ]
Oh!What's up, my brothers?
Yo, check it out.
I found out where Carl's
sneak party is this weekend.
Hook us up with the 411.Now hold on. Hold up, man.
You can't get the 411
until one of y'all
nappy-head brothers...
hook me up with a date
for the prom.
All right?This cat here.
Check this out. Rita.
That's what I'm talking about.
Right there, baby.
How you doin'?Hey, June.
This is my man, Fish.
Fish, this is Rita.Hi.
Rita, how would you like
to go to the prom
with Fish?
You gotta be kiddin', June.
I can do better than that.
[ Chuckling ]
I forgot they can see
your ugly ass.
June, what the fuck
is wrong with you, man?
Tryin' to hook me up
with that old stank-ass heifer.
You see her feet?
Yo, she comin' back.
Excuse me, but you did not
just call me a stank heifer.
Oh, I'm sorry, sister.
Did I say stank heifer?
See, what I meant to say was,
you ugly beeyatch!
[ Chuckling ]
[ Together ]
Oh! Damn!
Fish got knocked out
by a girl!
[ Laughing ]
[ No Audible Dialogue ]
[ Man ]
♪ I see you walkin'
in the high school halls ♪
[ No Audible Dialogue ] ♪ In the classroom
two seats across ♪
♪ Away from me
♪ Baby, can't you see?
♪ You are the kinda girl
that the guys fall for ♪
♪ The kinda girl
that you can't ignore ♪
♪ But I'm the one Greg!
♪ Who really wants you,
girl ♪
Give me my book!
♪ I wanna show you ♪ Yeah
♪ How I feel ♪ Won't you be my girlfriend?
♪ Girlfriend ♪ Can you be my
♪ I wanna tell you
how much you mean ♪
You see that big ship?
My father works at the docks
loading machine parts...
on boats just like that.
When I was 10,
he took me on board
my first ship.
It was huge.
There were all
these brothers there,
but they spoke French.
Never seen anything
like it.
It made me feel...
Small?
Yeah.
Like there was a whole lot
I didn't know.
You know,
my dad's cool and all,
but he never once
stops to think
of how those
little machine parts...
will get to go places
he'll never see.
But I do.
Every time I see
one of those ships,
I think of where
it's headed,
and if I'll ever get there.
[ Grandpa ]
No, no, no, no, Son.
I don't need no "Niagara."
I'll tell you that right now.[ Father ]
It was just a recommendation.
Yes.The man doesn't know you.
I know he don't know me!
But the whole thing
in a nutshell is this...
Shh!
What's going on?He's finally filling out
those college applications.
Well, good.
Now I don't
have to go to jail
for killin' his ass.
I thought you said
the boy was stupid.
I... I never said the boy
was stupid.
Whatever. I'm going
into the kitchen.You stay out of that pork.
I know I didn't hear him say
you called my child stupid.
You're right.
You know I didn't say that.
What I said was the boy
needs to bring his grades up.
That's all I said.
Why would he lie?
He don't have no reason
to lie on you.
Why would he lie? What...I got one question to ask you.
Where you sleeping at tonight?
[ Father ]
That's what I'm talkin' about.What?
What are you doing?
I'm filling out
my college applications.
Why?
College is for smart kids.
Now you are dumb.
You're just jealous
'cause I'm the man.
[ Father ]
To get a piece of pork.
He's lyin'!
You spelled "education" wrong.Boy, please.
I-I've been spelling
before you was born.
Boy, go ahead.
Ignorant little...
[ Father ]
I'm telling you,
the man is a pathological liar.
[ Mother ]
He ain't got no reason
to lie on you.
He lies all the time!He may lie to you,
but he don't lie to me.
[ Woman ]
♪ Baby's got
Baby's got everything ♪
[♪ Hip-hop ]
[ Woman ] Hi, Greg.[ Woman ] Hi, Greg.
Welcome to your dorm room.
Oh, ladies.
Oh, no. Not now.
[ Chuckles ]
I didn't even
wanna be on this bed,
but I fell on this bed.
Ooh, ladies. Oh.
You guys are so sexy.
But you know what?
I have a really
important call to get.
So why don't you guys
watch TV or something?
I'll be back.[ Groaning ]
All right.
Hey. Oh, hey.
I see you, G. What's going down?
Ladies, give it up
for the man himself,
Greg Reed!
That's me.
[ Grunting Rhythmically ]
What? Uh-oh.[ Women Chanting ]
Go, Greg. Go, Greg.
Go, Greg.
[ Greg ]
Spank it. Spank it.
Lick it. Lick it.
[ Chuckling ]
I love the job you're doing.Lookin' out for you, bro.
I talked to the dean.
Got you your own cart
and topless caterers.
There you go.
That's why you the man.Hey, I try.
[ Together ]
Put some stank on it.
All right.Do your thing,
player.
Hello, Greg. Cohiba?
Mmm.
Cuban.
[ Chuckles ]Mmm.
Uh... Whoa. Whoa.
Not now.
I got a little business
to take care of.
But there are
two ladies on the bed.
Go help them out.
Thank you, baby.Hey, yo, G.
You know it's time for you
to bestow your wisdom...
on those less cool
than you.Mm-hmm.
Well, which is
basically everybody.Mm-hmm.
Let's go do it.Hey, G,
the dean wants to know
if you're free
for dinner tonight.
Damn. Tell him
I'm busy gettin' busy.
[ Chuckling ]
He knows what I mean. Whoo.
Yo, G, these rich boys need
assistance with their grades.
[ Man ] Yeah.
Please. We have money.
But we're fuckups
who screwed up
our whole semester
thinking we were better
than you.
Give them my butt
to kiss first.
Your butt?
Oh, man.
No, no.
Get all in the crack. Yeah.
There. Done.What'd you do?
I broke the school's
computer code,
which was easy,
since I invented it.
I gave you all C's.[ Together ]
C's?
I can erase it.No!
It's fine. It's fine.Thank you. Thank you.
Next!
Yo, G,
the sororities want you...
to pick their spring pledges.
Your "Flyness".
Then bring 'em in.
Mmm. Too much booty.What?
Mm-mmm. Not enough booty.
Girl, go get a steak sandwich
or something.
Your navel ring is crooked.
Where'd you get that done,
Crenshaw?
Get out of here.
You.
Greg, I didn't think
you'd remember me...
after coming to college
and blowing up like you did.
Cinny, how could I
ever forget you?
Everybody, out!Yes, your genius.
[ Man ]
♪ You come around me
♪ Shakin' your thing around Girl,
I'm about to hit that ass
like a home run
in the ninth inning.
Oh, thank you.
♪ Girl, lay your body
♪ Right here next to mine
♪ You can ride like a pony
Mmm. I'm about to rock
your world, girl.Greg.
Baby, I didn't know
you had it like that.
Ooh, that's right.
That's right. Yeah! Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
Greg!
[ Moaning ] Say my name! Say it!
Greg. Greg!
[♪ R&amp;B music
abruptly stops ♪]
Proud of you, Son.
Make sure you mail
those applications today.
[ Kenyatta ]
Hey, June. Get in, boy.
You done made
an "approperly" decision.
[ LaDennis ]
You a smart man, April.Fuck you! My name is June.
[ Kenyatta ]
Yeah, whatever it is.Yeah, whatever, nigga.
[ Greg ]
There it is.[ Fish ] Where everybody at?
[ June ]
It's a sneak party, fool.
What you think?
[ Greg ]
You're not supposed
to park out front.
You're supposed to park
in the back.
[ June ] Damn.[ Fish ]
Man, this is V.I.P. Sneak party.
[ Car Backfires ]
[ Fish ]
Whoo! Sneak party!
Sneak party!
Names?
Oh...
What? What? What? Names?
Since when did sneak party
get a guest list?
Since now, little man.
Twiggy.
[ Chuckles ][ Cackling ]
Baby Godzilla got jokes!
I know you just didn't say that.
You ain't never gettin' in
with that attitude.
Callin' me Baby Godzilla.
Who he think he is?Let me talk to you for a second.
With his little worm-head self.
Gonna try to tell me.
I got the list.
She been drinkin' too much milk.She kinda big,
but we trying to groove.
[ Mutters ]Are you... Are you serious?
All right, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.All right, let's go.
What'd you say to her?I told her I'd take her
to the prom.
[ Laughing ]My man.
[♪ Hip-hop ]
Fish is in the house!
[ Fish cheering ]
Get a room! Get a room!
Get a room!
Damn! Whoo!
[ Chattering, Laughing ]
Yo, they're ballin' up
in this piece.
[♪ Continues ]
You like that,
don't you, boy?
[ Cackles ]
Ooh.
Whoo![ Groans ]
Move over that way.
What?
[ Whispering ]
So?No, no, no, girl. Look it.
I swear that Master P
is my cousin, girl.
You seen Dennia?No, I ain't seen her, bro.
Look here now.Wait a minute.
I know who you are.
I go to school
with a couple of your kids.
Wait a minute.
You are Tyricus's dad.
Tyricus! Your daddy over here
tryin' to flirt with everybody!
Look, Phillip,
I think I need a little space.[ Scoffs ]
Like, in my life.You need space?
You need me.
That's all you need
to worry about.
Greg, cut it out. I just...Greg?
Who the hell is Greg?
[ Chattering ]
Cinny, is everything okay?Greg.
Oh, this is Greg.
Yo, you need to stay
the hell away from my woman.
I am not your woman!
That's all I've been
trying to tell you all night.
Yo, like I said,
your punk ass is mine!
Are you listening to me?You need to chill out.
Are you listening
to me at all?
Yo, later for you, man.[ Greg ]
Later for you,
Philip Michael Thomas-lookin'
knob.
[ Sighs ]
My God. I am so sorry.
No, it's all right.
I think you deserve
a lot better.
So...
[ Clears Throat ]
in light of what happened,
I figure you probably don't
have a date to the prom
anymore, but...
Greg.
I... I just kind of thought
that dating would
mess things up between us.
Maybe we should
just stay friends.
Hey, you know what?
[ Chuckles ]
I forgot totally. Wow.
I came up here
to tell you something.
I got into college.
Greg, you did?
Oh, congratulations!
What college?UCLA.
Really? Tell me about it.
Not much to tell.
Got the letter, got happy.
[ Chuckling ]
Oh...It's just such good news.
I'm so happy about it.
Now, please,
don't say no to the prom.
Okay.
Yeah, I'll go with you.
Wanna dance?Sure.
[ Chuckles ]
[♪ Slow R &amp; B ]
Mmm.
Mmm. It's time
to get our food on, baby.
Mmm. What?[ Chuckling ]
Food on.
[♪ Hip-hop Continues ]
[ Chuckling ]
Ooh, how you doing, baby?
You havin' a good time?
Mm-hmm.Uh-uh. Look, Fish man
got something for you.
There you go. Why don't you
go ahead and suck on...
I mean, uh, sip on that.
Damn!What, you don't like it?
That's good.That's what
I'm talkin' about, baby.
Yo, Fish.What's up, boy?
I got her to go
to prom with me.Who, Cinny?
That's right.My man!
All right, man, lookee here.
[ Clears Throat ]
Why don't you slide
your boy a condom, man.
I got me some hot drawers
right here.[ Chuckling ]
I'm gonna tear it up.Come on, Fish.
I'm coming, boo.
That's what I'm talkin' about.
Here, man.
Oh, man, this is bullshit!
Man, this old-ass condom?
This like the one
Adam used on Eve.
That's right!
You ain't getting my new one.
Why not? You...
Cinny. Ha!
My man.
Damn, man. Tear it up.
Dark chocolate.Ooh. Damn.
Mmm.[ Chuckling ]
I feel it.
Are you sure that's chocolate
or some other liquid?
It's chocolate, baby.Oh, for real?
It's not slobber?
Mmm. That's saliva.
That's a tongue. Mmm.
Lemmie just, uh,
some whipped cream.Mm-hmm.
Whoo.Some sprinkles.
[ Moaning ]Gots to have the sprinkles.
[ Chuckling ]
Anybody seen Dennia?[ Moaning ]
Hey, somebody
seen my butterfly?
Got to have the banana.Oh! Where you wanna put that?
[ Chuckles ]
This is you right here?What?
Baller.
[ Chuckles ]
Chrome wheels.
Oh, man.
Whoo!Well, a little graduation
presents from my parents.
Whoo. I can't
even get a pair
of skates in my house.
Where's my butterfly?
[ Moaning ] ♪ Why am I so nasty?
♪ And I tried my best
to answer ♪
♪ What's your girlfriend
lookin' at? ♪
[ Moaning ] ♪ And now
I'm in the back room ♪
[ Chuckling ]
Huh?Hey, baby.
[ June ]
Snap!
I just wanted you
to know that...
you've been
a good friend to me lately.
Aw...No, I mean it.
I wanted you to know
I appreciate that.
You're welcome.
But it hasn't been easy.
What, you don't like
hangin' with me?
[ Stammers ]What's that?
No, it's not that. It's...
I'm feelin' something
bigger than friendship.
Hey, yo, Greg.
Greg, do me a favor.
Get my clothes, all right?
Get my clothes.What you talkin' 'bout?
[ Chuckling ]Did you see her tattoo?
Your ass is mine!
[ Fish ]
Hey, yo. So, Greg, baby,
you and Cinny.
[ Chuckles ]
I'm proud of you, son.
Shoot, I can't believe
how fast you pulled Dennia.
Uh, let's not forget
I pulled Vanessa.
Fish, the girl was drunk,
all right?
She's probably at home right now
trying to kill herself.
Uh-uh. She's home trying
to find a prom dress,
'cause I'm takin' her.
[ June ]
All right.
Yo, June.What's up?
What you gonna do
after school is over?
Gonna start my own
900 hotline.
But I'm gonna call it
"Psychic Honey Hotline."
You see what I'm saying?
Press "1" for psychic advice.
Press "2"
to get your groove on.
[ Chuckles ]
I know what I'm doing
when school is over.
Yeah, me too.
The 12th grade again, stupid.
No. And I'm takin'
your mama to the prom.
Fish, man, for real.
I done told you,
and I'm tryin' to be nice.
All right. I'm sensitive
about getting left back!
You know what I'm saying?
I got big plans too.What's your job gonna be?
First of all,
I'm gonna be the man.
Second of all, I'm gonna be
rich, rich, Richie Rich.
And third, I'm hittin'
a different girl every night!
[ Chuckles ]
What's your job
gonna be?
Who cares when you're hittin'
a different girl every night?
Y'all both being unrealistic.
What?You just being a butt.
Fuck you.[ June ]
I know what it is.
It's Cinny.
That's what it... Yup.Mm-hmm.
She probably hit you off
with some of that
philosophical booty.
No, I'm just thinkin'
about the future, that's all.
You should just forget
about the future
and focus on the prom.
We going with
the flyest girls.Mm-hmm.
We got the flyest limo.Mm-hmm.
We gonna be struttin' into
the biggest night of our lives.Mm-hmm.
Let the future come
when it comes,
you know what I'm saying?
All right?
[ Fish ]
All right?Yeah, man. No doubt.
That's my dog.
My dog.
[ June ]
Go on, girl.
Meet me at my house.Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
Carryin' books,
kissin' all in public.
Look at you.
Oh, what's up, Snap?
[ Laughing ]That's not funny.
Hey, fellas, fellas.
Hey, hey, hey, ho, ho.
Looks like you're ready
for Career Day.
But it's in
the opposite direction.
Oh... Oh.
[ Chuckles ]
Well, Mr. Shapic, they got
any professional rappers
up in there?
'Cause if they do,
that's where me gonna be.
[ Laughing ]
Did you know that
a rapper has to learn
traditional forms
of rhyme and syntax?
Basically everything you were
supposed to learn in English.
I'll just be a manager then.
They got a lover's booth
over there? 'Cause that's
where I'm gonna be.
Yeah, yeah, June,
you could make a lot
of money doing that.
Male prostitute...
See, but you're going
the wrong way.
Selling sex for money
is prostitution.
[ Fish ]
Just like his mama.
Yo. For real, man,
that's not funny.
What did I tell you
about that, man?
What about you, Greg?
Oh, I don't know.
Well, then there are
some options
I think you might want
to check out at Career Day.
I'll be a teacher if I could
drive a car like yours.
You want to drive
a car like mine?Yes, indeed.
I worked hard
for that car, Greg.
Before I was a teacher,
I was a businessman.
I owned my own company
for 20 years.
[ Chuckles ] In fact,
I was just like you dogs
when I was in high school.
[ Chuckles ]
And then I met someone
who told me about choices.
I had no idea.
He said, "You can go left,
or you can do
what's right."
Now, I'm... I'm headed
for the future, guys.
Who's brave enough
to join me?
Man, I'm skippin' next period.[ Fish ]
I'm down.
Not me, man.
I'm meeting Cinny.
[ Chuckling ]
Damn, man. You always with
that old chicken-head-ass girl.
You can't get enough of her.
That's right.
Can't get enough.
You know what?
You should have
seen Shawn's face
when I told him
you knocked Cinny's boots
at that sneak party, dog.
What? Fish, what the fuck
did you do that for, man?
Yo, man. Chill. Geez.My shirt.
What's the matter
with you, man?What the hell's your problem?
Nothin', man.
It's just she's real sensitive
about that kind of stuff.
I don't want it
getting back to her.
I'm sensitive about my shirt.
You shouldn't have told Shawn.
You got a big mouth.
Shawn ain't got nothin'
to do with my shirt.All right. All right. Come on.
It's a brand-new shirt, man.All right, y'all.
Please?Hey, what, you in love?
Nah, no, no, no.
Not love.
[ Chuckles ]
All right, man. 'Cause we'll
take your player card, man.
Take your player card quick,
brother.
[ Woman On P.A. ]
Attention, students.
Career Day is ending
in 10 minutes.
I thought you'd come.
[ Greg ]
Yeah, I wanted
to check it out
in case I didn't
get accepted into college.
That's smart, Greg.
There are a lot
of other alternatives
right here in this room.
Thanks.All right.
[ Woman ]
Young man, learn
the wonders of H.T.M.L.
Get a degree in computers.
[ Man ]
Have you considered an M.B.A.
from Pierce College, young man?
What grade did you get
in geometry?
How about algebra?
Interested in med school?
What are your S.A.T. scores?
Cornell University
has the finest law school
in the country.
Son, the army makes men.
You can be all you can be.
And you don't have to be
a genius to take orders.
Can you cut
the mustard, son? Huh!
♪ G, you better
watch yourself ♪
[ Explosions ][ Helicopter Whirring ]
Damn, I'm surrounded.
All right. Uh-huh.
It's okay.
They gonna make a motherfucker
get real loco up in here.
Mi vida loca.Ah!
Get up!
[ Grunts ]
[ Machine Gun Firing ][ Shouting ]
[ Grunting ][ Shouting ]
[ Greg ]
Yeah!
Hoo-wah![ Man ]
Game over.
Oh...
Oh, shit.
[ Whimpering, Shouting ]
Hoo-wah!
[ Thuds ]
[ Announcer ]
Ladies and gentlemen,
the president
of the United States.
[ Applause ]
It's my honor to give you
the Purple Heart,
the Medal of Honor...
and these unreleased CDs
from Tupac
and the Notorious B.I.G.
[ Audience Affirming ][ Clatters ]
Ladies and gentlemen,
Greg Reed!
[ Cheering ][ Man ]
Way to go, Greg!
Thank you all.
Please, no.
I'd like to thank all of you
for coming out,
especially the president.
You my nigga.
[ Chuckles ]
Right.
And as soon as you retire,
I will run
for your office.Hear, hear!
Thank you. Thank you.Hold up! Hold up!
This man is a fake.
He didn't even go to college.
[ Audience ] What?
The only thing worse
than a liar
is a man with medals
he doesn't deserve.
What the fuck?
No, not my Biggie! My Biggie!
No! Give me one more chance!
Yeah. That's right.
What? What?
Son, this is the opportunity
of a lifetime.
You can travel the world
and earn up to $40,000
for college.
Son![ Bell Ringing ]
It's not too late
to get your yearbooks.
Yearbooks are
still available.
Hey, hey, hey.
Cinny, I've been looking
all over for you.
Yeah, I bet.
I need two... Damn!Cinny, what's wrong with you?
What's wrong with me?
It is all over school how
you screwed me at that party...
like some ho.
[ Woman ]
Ooh! Somebody a ho.
I got it. I got it.
Excuse me, brother.
Look, Cinny, I didn't lie.
It was my boys.
They got it all wrong.
I would never start a rumor
about you.
Okay, fine. So we had
a misunderstanding.
So, when do you start UCLA?
Um, the first day.
Stop frontin'.
I heard you and Mr. Shapic.
Annetta,
stay out of this, please,
all right?
Now, Cinny,
it's not like it seems.So you did get into UCLA?
No, I didn't, but...And you didn't use these
damn lies to get next to me,
to drop my defenses?
Cinny...Damn, Greg. Tell me
that's not what you did.
I thought you were special.
[ Clicks Tongue ]
Um...
Hey, baby.
What the hell is this?Oh, no. I forgot
to put up the flyers.
Oscar Nicholson
put out flyers, huh?
He's already
sold out prom night.
Already sold out prom night!
Guess I can't put 'em up now.
They all dirty.
No, you can't put 'em up now,
'cause you're fired!
You know, I don't need
this damn job anyway.
You're never gonna
amount to nothin'!
Get out of my place!
Wash your stank, greasy,
old-ass barbecue stained
from Malcolm X's last rib shirt!
Wash it!
I knew you were a spy
for that Oscar Nicholson!
Talkin' about my shirt.
You wish you had one!
[ Mother ]
Greg, honey,
these envelopes
are from college.
Go on, Son.
Open 'em.
UCLA said no.
Didn't get into USC either.
Pepperdine said no too.
Here.
Let me open the last one.
[ Mother ]
What do these people
know anyway?
Hey, look, don't worry, Son.
There's still one more
you haven't heard from.
I don't want you
to leave anyway.
Forget about them, son.
I never went to college,
and look at me.
Hey, June bug.
Come here, bro.
Got a little package
for you.
Yo, Kenyatta,
that's drugs.
My man, you said
I was gonna be
selling electronics.
Look, man,
I know what I said.
Things change, baby.
People grow up.
Shoot, you need
to be "emanciated."
You got a problem with that?Yeah, this ain't me, man.
I can't play...
I can't play with this, dog.
This ain't... Nah.
Okay. That's cool.
I thought
you was a man.
Guess you still
a little boy.
[ Sighs ]
All right.
Then take your little
young ass home.
Give him a few days
to quit watching his back.
Yeah.Then bring his ass to me.
[ Chattering ]
♪ G, you had everything
♪ You stupid motherfucker [ Knocking ]
♪ You know you're stupid
♪ Your ass is stupid
What the hell you want?I want to see Greg.
What you want with my man?Your man got me pregnant!
Pregnant? What?Greg! Greg!
[ Shouting ]
I know she didn't just
come into my house!
Hold on, girls.You old sorry ass...
Hold up! Hold up. Don't be
talking to my man like that!That's right.
Motherfucker! Get out.
Get out.
I want you out of my house!
I don't care. I'll go stay
with Renee. Right, baby?Wrong, baby!
And give me
my bus pass back!
[ Woman ]
Just try it.
Sorry, shiftless...
Who you think you're dealing
with, brother?No good, lazy, good-for-nothing.
You think I'm some
welfare fool up in here?
Have you ever heard
of a job?
I'm happy to say
I have a good job,
lots of money
and handsome men
with cars and muscles.
[ Man ]
Sounds like your priorities
are in order. And why not?
You're young,
beautiful, articulate.
There you have it.
Cinny Hawkins,
president of Cinny Industries.
Thank you for coming in.
Thank you, Steve.
[ Shrieking ]
No! No!
He ain't goin' nowhere!
My baby needs him.
Whoa! No, it ain't mine!
I swear I'm not
gonna daydream no more.
I'm not gonna trip.
Let me go! Let me go!
Wake up, man! Wake up!
June's in trouble.What?
June is in trouble, man.
I saw Kenyatta's boy
snatch him up.
I think he's been
selling for him.Selling for him?
Yes.Oh, damn!
He our boy, man,
but he brought it on himself.
We gotta go get him, man.
Are you crazy?
You can do what you want,
but it's time for me
to get real.
G. G!
All right,
I know where he at, man.
Come on.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
What the hell
you doin'?
You been watching Shaftreruns
with your moms again, huh?Shut your mouth.
This stuff works, man. Shh.They need to take
y'all cable away.
Hey.Look what we got here,
LaDennis.
"I'm Gonna Git You Sucka"
and "Encyclopedia Black."
Come on up in here.
Come on.
Come on up here!
I don't like you anyway.Go on up there.
Go on up there.
Come on. Come on, man. Come on!
Go on,
you young black youth.Keep going up to the top.
Go on up to the top.Hold on. Ho... Ho...
Hold on! Hold on!
What is it? What is it?
I done locked, dog. I locked.Come on down here.
He locked up.
Come back down here.
Stay right there.
Grab... Get a grip. Come on.Come on.
You on me?I'm goin'. I'm goin'.
Hey, dog, I'm stuck, dog.
I'm stuck, dog.Are you stuck?
Hold up, dog.
Don't move.Stop! Stop!
Okay. Okay. I'm off.[ Gasping ]
Okay.
Go to the top.
Go to the top.Okay. Go to the top.
Go on. Keep going.
Hey, slow down before
I shoot both y'all in the ass.
I got 'em. I got 'em.
I got 'em.Slow down, chumps.
Right there. Right there.Yeah.
Yeah. Go on. Get close to 'em.
Go on.Yeah.
Go.Scared, ain't you?
That's right.
You should be scared, 'cause
I'm the big boss around here.
I'm the boss of all bosses
out this joint.
Dennis. Dennis.Don't interrupt me
while I'm talking.
Oh, so you're
making decisions now,
huh, LaDennis?
Oh, Mama, can...
can I call you back?Nah, boss.
It's just that you
paid me to do a job,
so I'm just doing
what the paycheck requires.
Boy, shut up!
How many times I got
to tell your supremely
ignorant butt not to think?
Yeah, you... you right...
you right, boss.
You got that look
in your eye again,
you know, like in '93
when you shot me
in the spine,
and that's why
my shit fucked up now.
But it's all...
You pay a dude to do a job.
Don't get an attitude.Where's June?
June Nelson! Come on up!
[ Elevator Whirring ]
[ Gasps ]
Look at... Look at this.Oh, man, June!
Oh, damn, dog.
What they do to you?
How can a brother do this
to another brother, man?
Just be still. We got you.Don't move, June.
Oh, June. Get him, get him,
get him, get him.Don't move. Don't move.
[ Fish ]
Oh, man, they got you way up
in the air like this.
Don't worry. We here for you.
Just stay still, man.
This is wrong.
This is wrong.We gonna get you, man.
My mama taught me
how to make that knot.
That's a good knot
right there.You did a good job.
You did a good job.It was a good idea to hang him
from there. That was all you.
I never knew a fat boy
could tie a knot like that.
Grab him. Grab him.
Got him. Got him. Got him.Be still.
Easy.You okay?
Ah!
Hmm.
Why you waste my time?Man, I'm sorry, all right?
Oh, you sorry?
You obviously don't have
a lot of "bidness acamin."
Is that a word?What did you say, Negro?
I didn't say nothin'.
Nothin'.
I don't know
what the fuck he said."Bidness acamin"?
June ain't like you,
all right?G, shut up.
No, man. You messed your
life up. Let him have his.
[ Cackles ]
I like him!He pretty too.
That's a man that say
what he got to say.
Praise his name.
Hey, get your...
Goddamn... [ Gasping ]Fine, Kenyatta,
I'll work for you.
Just let my man go,
please.
Boy, you better say it
with some conviction!
I'll work for you.Huh?
[ Chuckling ]
Get your butt over there.
Hey, don't touch me,
nigga.
Step out the way, fool!
[ Chuckling ]
I got you.
You all right?
[ Z-boy ]
Look at 'em.
Huggin' like little punks.That's 'cause they dark,
bald head and darker.
You know what, man?
Normally I kill
little punk-asses like you
for wasting my time.
But I'm feeling a little
"generostisity" today.
[ Chuckles ]
So y'all don't want
to work for me?
It don't matter.
You know why?
'Cause I got
y'all's asses anyway.
Yeah. 'Cause, see,
sooner or later,
you gonna find out
what kind of options you really
have in your sorry-ass life.
So, when you need a car
and you can't get a loan...
and when things get really bad,
you gonna be right back here
to buy my shit!
Or you'll be right back here
begging to work for me.
Get out my face!
That's right.
Try your luck, nigga.
[ Z-boy ]
Better not see you
on the street!
[ Mortal KombatSound Effects ]
[ Gasping ]
[ Mother ]
It's from Morehoward.
[ Paper Rustling ]
[ Chuckling ]
My boy's going to college.My prayers
have been answered.
♪ Keepin' it real
[♪ Humming ]
I got everything
anybody could ever want.
More money
than the bank and vault.
More heat than
the sun in June.
More honeys
than a ladies' room.
[ Sighs ]
He's comin'.
Oh, Son, you look good.Aw, thanks, Ma.
You look nice.Yeah, you look like me
when I was your age.
Aw, watch out now.I don't want you out there
hurtin' nobody.
I won't.Please.
Ooh-wee!Whoo!
All right. All right.
Get y'all smiles on over there.
[ Camera Whines ]All right. Let's see
if I can get there. Smile!
[ Shutter Clicks ]Oh, good one. Good one.
Boy, you look somethin' good.
Thanks. Thanks.I thought you were gonna
get the one with the tails.
That was the old me...
trippin', trying to be
something I'm not.
From now on,
I'm keepin' everything real.
[ Chuckles ]All right.
Don't do nothin'
I wouldn't do.Don't wait up.
Don't worry.That's my grandson, boy.
[ Mother ]
Boy, you look just like your
dad. You look so good.
[ Father ]
Don't he look sharp?[ Grandpa ] Yes.
[ Jamal ]
Yo, I can't believe he's going
to the prom by himself.
My poor baby.It's a damn shame.
This is some
embarrassing shit. Whoo.
♪ Party over here, huh
♪ Party over there, huh
[♪ Record Scratches ]
[ Fish ]
Whoo! Yeah, baby. Yeah!
Yeah, I'm at the prom,
and I'm-a graduate, y'all!
Whoo!
Yeah. Yeah! I made it!
Ooh, thank you, Jesus.
Thank you, Lord. Ooh!
Ooh, man, look at you, girl.Thank you.
Look at this butt! Ooh!
Wait till they see you.
What? What? What?
♪ Been a long time since
you had such a fat chance ♪
♪ So slip into
your platform shoes
and do your disco dance ♪
♪ All aboard, all aboard
Come ride away with me ♪
♪ I'll take you to a place
that we never, ever did see ♪
♪ Listen while I tell
just where I'm coming from ♪
Killin'.Thanks, bro. All right.
[ Woman ]
You looking good, baby.
[ Phillip ]
Hold on. You got
something on your lips.
[ Cinny ] Phillip, stop.
We came as friends.
Can you please respect that?
Fine. All right.Thank you.
Welcome, sir.Thanks, man.
Have a good night.Thank you.
[ Annetta ]
Um... That's my leg, boy.
Get you... Let me out, boy.What are you doing? Phillip.
Nothing.
[♪ Hip-hop ]
Fish man has arrived!
I have arrived!
[ Cackles ]
How you doing?Fine, baby.
Hey, come on.
Let me get this picture
with ya'll.
Hey, come on.
What's up, y'all?
All right now.
We got to get
a picture of this.Let me see some smiles.
Don't leave me hanging, baby.I got you, dog.
I got you, dog. It's '99, y'all.
[♪ Continues ]
All right.
I'm gonna get this picture.
That's it.
Very nice. There you go.
One more now. Hold on.
Um...
Smile.
[♪ Hip-hop ]
Greg, what's up, baby?
I can't believe you came
by yourself, man.
You a bad boy.I don't need no date
to validate me.
I'm just keepin' it real.Uh-huh. Real lonely.
[ Chuckles ]
Don't do it, G.
Come on. It ain't worth it.
Leave it alone, man.
Hey, what's wrong?
Nothing.[ Annetta ]
Don't let him touch you.
Phillip, we came
to the prom together.
That does not mean
we are back together.
Okay? He's all up on me.
I'm just trying
to be sociable, girl.Please. "Sociable."
Anything could happen tonight.No, it can't.
Hey... Hey, come on.
You just need to loosen up, huh?
Let's... Let's dance.Okay.
Bye, girl.
[ Gasps ]
[ Shrieks ]
[ Cackling ]
What's up?My dog.
Ah, you came dolo?Keepin' it real.
Right on. Right on.How you doing, Dennia?
Hi, Greg.You see Cinny here
with that... [ Gasps ]
Snap!
What... What's up, man?
Yo, that's a bangin' tux, man.
Did you...
Don't "what's up" me.
You with my woman?
Oh! [ Gasps ]
Eugene, you're killing him.Fuck him.
Man, why it gotta be like this?
Over a woman, man?
[ Grunting ]
Listen, man,
she don't want you.
She was only with you
for the popularity.
Now when you get
an NFL contract,
there'll be a thousand
gold diggers like her
chasing you down the street.
So get the hell over it.
Yeah. You right.
You blew it, woman.
Yeah. Now let's go get some ice
for your family jewels.
Thank you. I appreciate it.
NFL contract?Don't even think about it.
[ Greg ]
So, yeah, man,
keep the ice on there.
That way,
your nuts won't swell up.
If that happens,
you have a little wee-wee
and some big elephant nuts,
and you look crazy,
all right?
Okay.My man.
[ Man ] Damn.Fellas, can you
give my lady some space?
Yo, Shapic.All right. All right.
Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep.
Would you like to dance?Sure.
♪ My body
needs your lovin', girl ♪
♪ So break me off
a little bit ♪
♪ In the mornin'
In the mornin' ♪
♪ Well
♪ In the evening
Hey, June.
Ooh, You are looking good
tonight, baby.
Oh, thank you very much.Bye-bye.
Mm-hmm.Oh, damn, you better get that.
What's the deal?
Come back here!
Come here!
Look, baby, if you wanted
to get freaky with June,
all you had to do was ask.
You didn't have
to take my hat.Ladies.
Ladies? Ladies. Lad...
I told you it was going
to be nothing nice.
Listen, um, I just want
to tell all of you... I mean...Mm-hmm.
You guys look
absolutely beautiful.Mm-hmm.
[ All Shouting ]
[ June ]
Oh! Ah, that's enough!
Ah! That's enough! Aw, damn!
[ Man ]
What's up, Greg? Goddamn, man.All right.
[ Man ] What's up, Greg?
What's happening, man?What's up, man?
Greg, you all right?Yeah.
Honey, this is the student
I was telling you about...
Greg Reed.
[ Woman ]
Mr. Shapic.Greg, this is Naomi.
Miss Hardwick.Hello, Greg.
Sweetheart, I've got
to talk to this teacher.
I'll be back in a moment. Greg?
So, women problems, huh?
Damn, is it written
on my forehead?
[ Chuckles ]
So, Greg,
what'd you do to her?
I lied to her.
Everyone makes mistakes.
What really matters
is what you do
after the mistake.
You know?
You'll get it.
[♪ Hip-hop Continues ]
Hey, Annetta.
Wanna dance?No. I don't need any charity.
Look,
I'm not offering charity.
But you're so busy
doggin' brothers out,
you can't see that.
That's why you ain't
got no date.
[ Scoffs ]
Why, you funny-looking liar.
You have no game, no car,
and you don't have
a date either.
Well, maybe I'm the one
that needs the charity.
Come on, Greg. ♪ Hump, baby
♪ Why don't you just
work that body
Whoo, whoo ♪
♪ Hump, baby
I know you got it ♪
Work that body ♪
♪ Hump, baby
I know you got it ♪
♪ Come on, come on, whoo
♪ Whoo
♪ Come on, come on
Whoo ♪
Get it, get it ♪
♪ I like the way
you shake your ass ♪
♪ Let me see
that butt-mobile ♪
♪ Move your hips
and bring your friends ♪
♪ Come on, baby, hook me up
You know what the hell I want ♪
♪ Hump, baby
Why don't you
just work that body ♪
♪ Hump, baby
♪ I know you got it
♪ Hump, baby, whoo
[♪ Music Stops ][ All Groaning ]
All right, seniors.
Whoo! Yeah.
Well, I just want
to welcome you guys
to the class of 1999
Dubois High School
senior prom.
[ Cheering ]Yeah. Whoo!
I just want to say
to everybody that
tonight is
a very special night.
This is the last time
we may see each other.
This is the beginning...Yeah.
of something bigger.
Just really take the time
and analyze it...
[ No Audible Dialogue ]
I thought you were special.
[ Echoing ]
[ Chambers ]
We have spent four years
with our best friends
and loved ones...
1,080 days.
I've really done the math
and the calculation.
We have spent
8,640 hours together.
[ Woman ]
Get Einstein off the stage!
This is
a very sentimental moment.
Excuse me. Excuse me, bro.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
Sorry, Chambers,
but I got to do this, man.
[ Man ]
Get off the stage!I've seen some of y'all
pointing at me and laughing...
because I came here by myself.
Yo, get your sorry ass
off the stage![ Cheering ]
Not till I say
what I gotta say.
Now hold on, y'all.
Wait a minute.
[ Man ]
This ain't Montel.I lost my woman...
because I acted like
a typical man.
[ Man ]
This ain't talk radio![ Woman ] Let the boy speak!
That's why I came here
without a date tonight.
'Cause I didn't want
to be with nobody but her.
Man, why don't you
shut the fuck up, man?
I'm sorry, y'all.
I know I'm breaking up
the whole prom and everything,
but just listen to me,
all right?
The woman I lost...[ Man ]
Is your mama!
...was real.[ Man ] Yeah, real smart
for leaving your ass!
I treated her like a dream,
like she didn't deserve
honesty and the truth.[ Man ] I feel you, bro.
And now I know better.
I really am better.
And I hope that you can
see that in me.
[ Woman ]
Come on. Forgive him, girl,
so he can put the music back on.
Can you believe this punk ass?[ Man ]
That was right on, bro.
Excuse me.That was really nice.
Hey, Phillip, wait!Yo! I'm tired
of your punk ass!
[ Man ]
This ain't Miami Vice,Tubbs.
[ Grunting ]
[ Woman ]
Ow! My goodness.
What's wrong with you?
Can't you see the man's in love?
Thanks, man.
[ Chambers ]
All righty then.
I just want to announce
our high school's
prom queen for 1999.
I'm sorry, Cinny.[ Man ]
Party started!
Miss Cinny Hawkins.[ Cheering ]
Are you gonna yell that
you're king of the world?
I would if I could.
Nice crown you got.It's a tiara.
Yeah. Tiara. I knew that.
That's female. Tiara, yeah.Mm-hmm.
[ Chuckles ]
That was...
That was nice,
what you said inside.
You better get back inside
with your man.
He might need you to ride
in the ambulance with him.[ Laughs ]
You got jokes.
I am with my man.
Good choice.
[♪ R &amp; B Intro ]
♪ Come on, baby,
hook me up ♪
♪ You know
what the hell I want ♪
♪ Push it in
Now pull it back ♪
♪ Let your feet
go straight ahead ♪
♪ Hump, baby
♪ Work that body
♪ I know you got it
♪ Hump, baby
♪ Work that body
♪ I know you got it
Come on, come on, whoo ♪
♪ Come on, come on
Get it, get it, whoo ♪
♪ Come on, come on, girl
♪ Come on, come on
Get it, get it, whoo ♪
Get it, get it ♪
♪ Come on, baby,
where you at? ♪
[♪ Continues, Indistinct ]
♪ I like the way
you shake your ass ♪
♪ Let me see
that butt-mobile ♪
♪ Move your hips
and bring your friends ♪
♪ Come on, baby,
hook me up ♪
♪ You know
what the hell I want ♪
♪ Hump, baby
Why don't you just
work that body ♪
♪ Hump, baby, I know you got it
Come on, come on, come on ♪
♪ Hump, baby
Work that body ♪
[♪ R &amp; B Intro ]
♪ Baby's got
Baby's got everything ♪
♪ That's da bomb
That's da bomb ♪ ♪ Rock to the beat
That's da bomb ♪
♪ Ain't nothin' but a party
Ain't nothin' but a party ♪
♪ Hey, Fury, why don't you
tell them what time it is ♪
♪ Whoo! Like this ♪ Lift up, break it down
like this ♪
♪ And it's gonna break
yo back ♪
♪ Like to make
your speakers crack ♪
♪ That's da bomb
when you pop that track ♪
♪ Wanna let it
Gonna watch the crowd ♪
♪ That's the way I pipe
Freak down ♪
♪ Won't y'all
if you like that sound ♪
♪ We get in the moto
tear it right down ♪
♪ Old wrecks
Don't wheel that stand ♪
♪ Get some oil
Let's juice this jam ♪
♪ Come to me
if you think about sex ♪
♪ Big money
ain't on the level ♪
♪ Send flowers,
bring one friend ♪
♪ We can pump the rhymes
Let's all jump in ♪
♪ Jump on the floor
and let me see ♪
♪ Get on the floor
and show me ♪
♪ Rock to the beat
♪ That's da bomb
That's da bomb ♪ ♪ Rock to the beat
♪ Here we go
Here we go ♪
♪ That's da bomb
That's da bomb ♪
♪ You come around me
♪ Shakin' your thing around
♪ But you can't
keep turnin' me on like ♪
♪ Well, I just can't
hold it down ♪
♪ Girl, lay your body
♪ Right here next to mine
♪ You can ride like a pony
on a merry-go-round ♪
♪ You can ride it anytime
♪ I wanna know
how deep is your love ♪
♪ I wanna fall
so deep in your love ♪
♪ I wanna rock and roll
and lose control ♪
♪ Inside your candy rain
♪ Sexy lady ♪ Oh, break it off
♪ Darlin' baby ♪ Break it off
♪ My body needs
your loving, girl ♪
♪ So break me off
a little bit, baby ♪
♪ In the mornin' ♪ Break it off
♪ In the evening ♪ Take it off
♪ Take it off ♪ My body needs
your lovin', girl ♪
♪ So break me off
a little bit ♪
♪ No more hesitating
♪ Baby, let me help you
take your clothes off ♪
♪ Drink a little wine
Relax your mind ♪
♪ I guarantee
we'll both get off ♪
♪ Tell me, can you handle this
I wanna get scandalous ♪
♪ I want to taste
your candy, girl ♪
♪ And when your sugar drip,
let it drip upon my lips ♪
♪ On and on and on
♪ Sexy lady ♪ Break it off
♪ Darlin' baby ♪ Break it off
♪ My body needs
your loving, girl ♪
♪ So break me off
a little bit ♪
♪ In the mornin' ♪ In the mornin',
break it off ♪
♪ In the evening ♪ Take it off
♪ My body needs
your lovin', girl ♪
♪ So break me off
a little bit ♪ ♪ Whoa
♪ Baby, keep it right there ♪ Keep it right there
♪ Slow and easy is the way
I wanna love your body ♪
♪ Run my fingers
through your hair ♪
♪ Stare into my eyes
and say you want it, baby ♪
♪ Wanna love you all night
♪ Until the morning light
♪ Girl, what does it take?
I don't wanna wait ♪ ♪ I don't wanna wait
♪ Just a little piece
of your love ♪
♪ Sexy lady ♪ Break it off
♪ Darlin' baby ♪ Break it off
♪ My body needs
your lovin', girl ♪
♪ So break me off
a little bit ♪