**
[Woman's Voice]
The deal was simple.
Buy the drugs at one-tenth the
street value,
and sell them and
make a bundle.
We knew the drugs were stolen.
We knew it was dangerous.
But that's why I came.
[ motorcycle engines ]
[ footsteps ]
[ chains breaking,
gate creaking]
Come on, give me a little taste.
[ laughs ]
Ray!
So how come Speed ain't here?
Heather, damn it!
Ugh, why do you deny me?
Some other guys...
Wouldn't put up with your shit.
Here, dopey.
I think the guera should stay
here.
She just came to get high!
Why do you keep calling me that?
Shit, a god damn cat fight!
Shut up, pendejo!
[ door creaks open ]
You coming, Pole?
[ door creaks shut ]
[ lighter flicks on ]
[ footsteps echo ]
[ loud scraping noise ]
[ yelling ]
Would you quit fucking around?!
Hey! [ laughs ]
Would you cut it out please?!
[ heavy breathing ]
Can't you do something about
her?
This isn't a game!
I'm not gonna fucking die
because of you.
Heather!
This isn't a place for stupid
rich girls.
[ footsteps echo ]
[door creaks open ]
Maybe Speed rigged the lights.
He's a dope dealer, fool, not a
roadie!
Yeah, well...
Wait up. Wait up.
Okay, Judd, you and you three go
that way.
We're gonna go over here.
Shit, Speed ain't even here!
Go, go, go man.
[ footsteps, scraping ]
[ creepy music ]
[ door creaks open ]
[ roar ]
[ laughter ]
[ music ]
[ panting ]
I love you, Heather.
What you gonna do with your
share?
Me? I'm gonna open up a coffee
house.
One of those nice ones with
style.
Serve food, live music. Great.
Hey, sounds good!
Stupid assholes.
You should be doing what my
cousin Hector does.
He's got his money in no-load
mutual funds.
I've got your load for you.
Shut up, dickhead. What are
those?
I don't know, but he's got a
pinche Lexus.
What's going on? Where's Speed?
I'm going to the bathroom.
[ door opens, shuts ]
[ creepy music ]
[ door creaks ]
[ door shuts ]
[ rat squeaks ]
[ urinating ]
[ door creaks ]
[ scream ]
[ punch ]
[ cries ] Shit! Oh man!
Hey, man! Are you OK?
What happened, man?!
I'm just trying to use the
fucking can, man!
Fucking bitch!
Okay, fourteen. Fourteen five.
[ interrupting ]
Thirteen. Thirteen five.
Um... [ stuttering ] fifteen.
Twelve!
Would you shut up?!
[ laughter ]
Um... fuck it! It's all there,
man. [ laughter ]
[ cash rustling ]
Slow down there, Speed.
Where's the stuff, huh?
Do I know you?
Are we pals, huh?
This is quality ice, man.
Very little color.
Very little, very little.
And it's close.
It's real close, man.
What are you doing?
Hey!
[ engines revving ]
Shit! We got company!
[ engine turns off ]
[ intense music ]
[ running ]
[ Speed whimpering ]
No way, man.
No fucking way.
[ door slams ]
Ray, let's just get out of here.
Don't listen to her!
That 20,000 might be chump
change to you,
but it's everything we had.
[ Speed whimpering ]
Suki!
Shut the fuck up.
It's our money, we
have to get it.
What about the crew down there?
We hide. They don't even know
we're here.
Oh yeah? They just parked next
to our god damn bikes!
Judd, look. You and I are
gonna go downstairs.
We're gonna check things out.
Maybe we can still get the
money.
Look, man! If we can't, at
least we can look for a way to
escape.
Heather, You and Suki are
gonna stay here with Pole.
No, I'm coming with you!
No, I said you're gonna stay
here.
Please don't make this any
harder than it already is.
I'm not leaving this
place without you.
[ door opens ]
Fuck.
Yeah.
[ Speed choking ]
What are we supposed to use to
protect ourselves?
Speed took your gun.
Now, this plan bites, man.
Real bad.
Listen to this candy-ass!
You want some, man?!
Knock it off! Knock it off!
Now look! We're gonna use what
we have, OKAY? You got it?
[ Speed screaming ]
[ scared breathing ]
Ray, don't do this, please. We
can all hide until they leave.
She's right.
Yeah, and what about our money?!
Man, when did you become so
afraid?
Look, I just don't like shitty
odds!
[ Pole laughing ]
Look man, we ain't gonna wait
here for them to find us. okay?
Now, let's go.
Heather, it's something
we gotta do.
I'm sorry I got you into
all this.
[ screaming ]
Stay here.
[ Speed whimpering ]
That toilet doesn't flush.
Can we get on with this, please?
My parents are expecting us for
dinner.
Jesus Christ.
Okay, Speed.
So you took the stuff...
Speed: I was gonna pay you,
man...
Say it Speed.
"I took what didn't belong to
me."
Speed: I was gonna pay you!
You took a kilo out of stock
without telling anyone.
You stole from us.
That's really the point here,
isn't it?
I was gonna pay!
I see that.
That's what this is for, right?
Gotta be fifteen,
twenty grand there.
What do you think, Bobby?
Bobby: Twenty thousand bucks.
Twenty thousand dollars?
But a kilo's gotta be worth
thirty-five?
Forty in the current market
value,
and with a kicker to
cover transportation, storage
overruns.
That's fifty.
And you've got twenty here. So,
help me with the math, Bobby.
Bobby: About thirty thousand
short.
Thirty thousand dollars.
You notice how I didn't ask
Nicky to do the math?
You know what I think?
I think you were trying to fuck
us.
Speed: No, man, I was
trying to pay you...
Shut up!
Which brings me to my next
point...
Where is my father's property,
Speed?
Speed: No! No! I was gonna get
the rest of the money, Dan. I
was really...
[ Speed screaming ]
[ whimpering ]
[ quiet footsteps ]
You know?
You haven't been very
nice to us.
You also seem to think that
we're stupid!
Speed: No, man!
You know, I don't think that you
respect us.
[ snap ]
[ gunshot ]
Why in the fuck did
you do that?
Snapping means "hurt," you
asshole. Pointing is "kill."
Shit.
Now how will we find
the stuff?
Don't worry, Dan,
we'll find it.
Now fucking do what he says!
[ creepy music ]
[ electricity crackling ]
[ Pole flicking lighter ]
[ quiet footsteps ]
[ footsteps ]
Has Ralph disabled the
motorcycles?
It's taken care of.
How many others do you think
there are?
Three bikes, who knows?
Great.
[ scary music ]
Judd: All of the doors are
sealed and there's bars on the
windows.
What about the front entrance?
One of them's watching it.
Fuck this, fuck the money.
Man, let's go back upstairs.
We're not gonna get it,
let's go. Come on!
[ intense music ]
[ rattling ]
[ crash ]
[ punching ]
[ knife whooshing ]
[ crashing ]
[ grunting ]
[ slam ]
[ slamming ]
[ punching ]
[ pipes clanging ]
Come on, fucker!
Come on.
Come on!
[ hitting ]
Nicky!
[ running ]
[ pipe clanging ]
You alright, man?
[ running ]
[ music ]
Get the fuck out of there, you
wormy little fucker.
-Easy.
-Fuck!
[ screaming ]
That's enough.
[ thud ]
[ grunting ]
[ punching ]
This is bullshit!
What have you been doing down
there all this time?
Trying not to get caught.
Well, pretty soon they're gonna
start looking up here.
We should've hid. There are a
lot of rooms, it'll take them a
long time...
And then what?
We go from room to room like
rats?
They'll stay here as long as it
takes and eventually they'll
find us.
When Ray gets back...
-Ray is dead, pendejo .
No, he's not!
Where are you going? Are you
crazy? We can't go down there.
I'm not leaving him!
Look, he made his choice. This
whole thing was his idea.
Look, we have to go after him,
but you stay here.
No!
Fine. You want to be a pinche
hero?
Jesus.
Look at you, you stupid
gavacho.
You know what a Mexican man
does? He protects his own, no
matter what.
Look, I am not...
-Mexican? Not even close.
Why I ever hooked up with you...
I just came to make a buy.
Alone?
[ choking ]
Then why are there three
motorcycles outside?
[ footsteps. creepy music ]
I want those drugs.
Bobby: This is getting it
slowly.
Let me make this simple.
Either you take us to where the
drugs are, or we kill you.
After that, we'll find the
others and we'll kill them.
Is that plain enough for you?
Sure.
[ footsteps ]
[ clanging ]
[ slow footsteps ]
You like art?
I just bought this incredible
book on Italian painting.
I'm giving it to my parents
tonight for their anniversary.
Look, this is just business.
You know I went to USC?
I was an econ major.
Speed, you little piece of shit.
What the hell were you doing?
Now, Bobby, look at him. The
man's exhausted.
He's got a wife, two kids to go
home to.
But we all have to work despite
our disadvantages.
Mine happens to be a good
education.
I don't care what they say, it
doesn't prepare you.
Do you know where you're going?
Yeah.
You know I can't believe you two
guys are taking orders from this
little prick.
Some guy put him in charge?
No, I know what it is. You
pretend to listen when he talks
in that stupid voice.
But you'd kill him in a second.
[ rustling ]
The old man had a stroke and
little wet-ass here steps in.
And then junior takes over the
family business.
With his good shoes and high
voice...
Shut your fucking mouth!
[ punching ]
[ inhaling ]
[ exhaling ]
[ grunt ]
[ grunting ]
Now that the old man's out of
the picture, you'd go back to
sleeping with mommy?
[ laughing ]
[ scary music ]
[ gunshot ]
I think we'd better call your
father.
Nicky, get the gun
under the desk.
Under the desk,
you Neanderthal.
I'm gonna get the others.
I'll go.
Don't argue with me,
god damn it.
I want those drugs.
Let's just get through this,
okay?
Just before I fired...
I had a vision.
Come on, I need you, kid.
Hey Ralph!
It's Rif.
Whatever man. Cover
the door, okay?
[ coughing ]
[ sniffling ]
They shot Ray.
These assholes could be
anywhere. We're wasting time.
Why don't we burn down the
building?
Oh great, and the drugs with it?
Let's look around some more,
then you and Ed can go to the
party. We can finish up here.
Yeah right.
No, we need to search this place
room by room.
I think you should think it
over.
I don't need your advice. Okay?
Whatever you want, Dan.
[ quiet footsteps ]
[ electricity crackling ]
Oh my god.
The bullet didn't go in.
[ crying ]
Come on, I'll help you up.
[ moaning ]
Stop it.
[ weakly ]
Always gotta be moving forward.
Life is short.
Ssh.
I'll be fine. I left before,
Heather.
I should've called, there's no
money.
The way things are going...
Heather, hurry up.
Come on.
Come on, get up.
Ray, come on!
Heather, where's Heather?
Ssh. I'm right here.
[ spanish ]
Mierda.
[ breathing ]
[ doorknob rattling ]
Okay, what's the story?
Nobody got in or out.
Look, Nicky. I don't want any of
your stupid bullshit.
We find the drugs, right?
You were gonna keep this,
weren't you?
You dumb piece of shit hayseed!
You know, you're full of
it as usual, Judd!
I'm saving our lives.
Don't you hear what they said?
This is all they want!
Now, I give it over, and we walk
out of here!
Charlie, you don't know nothing!
Oh no?
I'm the fucking hero!
Look at him.
He wants to hide like a scared
little baby.
But I'm the one who's gonna save
all your sorry asses.
You should be lining up
to suck my dick!
Now, is anybody
coming with me?
[ silence ]
You bunch of goddamn losers.
You're all gonna die in here.
Look, his big mouth is gonna get
us killed. You better go after
him.
This is that Mexican man thing
again, isn't it?
I want you to wait out
in the car, okay?
For what?
[ sigh ] I just don't
want anything to happen
to you, okay?
Now go on.
Go!
Fuck no.
I don't need you to take care of
me, all right? I don't need
anybody.
Goddamn self-sufficient,
badass motherfucker.
Who doesn't need his stupid-ass
paranoid brother watching
him all the time.
[ coughing ]
Shh.
Could you help me?
[ coughing continues ]
-Ssh.
It's just some saliva.
[ screech ]
[ creepy music ]
Now, I don't think you really
wanna shoot me.
[ lighter flicks ]
Especially since I just happen
to know where the rest of them
crystals are.
Interested?
I don't particularly want to
talk to you, though.
You get me someone in charge.
Dan, over here! I got
one of them!
I tracked him over here. I was
gonna blow his fucking head off
if he made a move.
[ punch ]
I was fucking brilliant, man.
Yeah, whatever.
So anyway, I got what you boys
want.
Now, I give it over, I walk
out of here, right?
Right?
That's right.
We just want what belongs to us.
That's what I thought.
Hey, let me see your gun.
Nah, come on now!
I got nothing against you boys.
In fact I was thinking maybe I
could be of service, you know,
in the future?
That's enough. Let's go.
[ male laughs]
[ door opening ]
Let's see if I remember now.
This is it.
This is it!
Stuff's up there in that box.
So that's it, right? I can
walk out of here?
I want you to tell me how many
others there are.
Now I'll be happy as shit to
tell you just as soon as I'm
outside, nice and safe.
[ Dan snaps ]
[ gunshot ]
Aah!
[ screaming ]
Are you crazy?!
What'd you do that for?!
[ screaming ]
-How many others?
How many?!
You can suck on it, asshole!
[ gunshot ]
[ screaming ]
I fucked your money! You
college-educated piece of dog
shit!
Okay! Okay! Okay!
There's one more! One other guy!
No! No God! No! Please!
[ multiple gunshots ]
You fucked it up!
I'm going back down there.
I figure I can distract them
long enough to get outside.
Even if I can't get to my
motorcycle, I can run.
I'll get to a pay phone, I'll
call the cops. It'll all be
over.
You're crazy.
Look, I can do this.
They're not that smart.
I'll make it, Suki.
You and Heather stay here, don't
make a sound. They don't know
that you're up here.
[ coughing ]
Judd, what are you doing?
I'm taking care of my own.
[ sad music ]
[ music ]
[ coughing ]
Christ, now what?
[ vomiting ]
[ gagging ]
[ dripping ]
[ groaning ]
[ paper ripping ]
[ intense music ]
[ door opening ]
It's wrong.
I have to find Judd.
Heather, if one of them finds
you, you use this.
[ music ]
[ metal rattling ]
[ music stops ]
[ breathing ]
[ footsteps ]
[ gate slamming ]
[ intense music ]
[ Judd yelling ]
[ metal banging ]
Where is she?!
Tell me where she is!
[ Judd screaming ]
[ screaming continues ]
[ footsteps, dragging ]
[ music ]
[ quiet crying ]
God, I hate LA.
[ coughing ]
Jesus, what?
Nicky.
Okay. He's the last one.
We can go.
I'll find Nicky. Where's Ed?
[ bangs on door ]
[ whimpering ]
[ whimpering, breathing ]
[ banging repeatedly ]
[ banging continues ]
[ door opens ]
[ door closes ]
[ banging ]
[ suspenseful music ]
[ cocking gun ]
[ whacking ]
[ pipe clanging ]
I don't wanna kill you.
You don't wanna kill me.
You're the one that's gonna die.
[ laughing ]
I don't wanna kill you.
[ screams ]
What are you gonna do, huh?
Cry?
[ whack ]
You stupid bitch!
[ splashing, bubbling ]
[ bubbling stops ]
[ gunshot ]
[ gasping, coughing ]
We have to go now.
They know we're here.
[ music ]
[ coughing ]
Quick, we'll take him up
the back stairs.
Pull him up!
1, 2, 3, up!
[ shuffling ]
Come on! We're too slow.
No, Heather, we gotta go.
Heather, we better get the
F- up the stairs. Let's go.
Now. Let's go.
-Wait.
-Wait for what?
Now!
[ music stops ]
Jesus.
No no no.
Come on, Ed! Ed! Ed!
Ed. Ed. Oh Jesus.
He's choking - he's choking
on something. Okay.
Ed! Ed! God damn it!
Bobby: Dan, leave it alone.
Not today. Okay. I got him.
I can save him.
You piece of fucking shit!
You stupid fucker!
[ screams ]
God damn piece of shit!
Dan! God damn it, let him go!
Leave it alone.
Dan! Let it go.
[ grunting ]
Okay.
Bobby, Nicky, get Raf
and meet me at the front.
I want them all dead.
I'll keep looking up here.
[ door slams ]
You're not getting out of here!
You think this is some kind of
game?
Now you listen to me. You
primitive piece of rogue crap.
You don't have a life!
You don't have an agenda!
What do you want to do
with the body?
Okay.
[ dialing ]
Dad?
Um, I really need to
talk to you.
And um... Jesus.
Um, call me back, Okay?
Call me back.
DIE, YOU SON OF A BITCH! FUCK!
[ crashing ]
[ breathing ]
Bobby.
[ crying ]
[ panting ]
[ grunting ]
Maybe Judd made it.
I couldn't do it.
You have to!
They don't care about anything.
Do you understand?
They will kill us all. It
doesn't matter to them.
When I was 17, I had never fired
a gun, and then I had to kill
someone.
It was like this impulse inside
me I didn't even know I had.
I just did it.
Didn't feel like anything.
I just did.
I have to get the cell phone.
He can't save you.
[ coughing ]
Sssshhhh.
I don't care if you've
got fucking cancer, get
your ass inside.
That's what we
pay you for.
Not to do this.
Alright, alright.
Leave it out.
[ bottle cap loosening ]
[ intense music ]
[ shells clicking ]
[ coughing ]
[ shotgun cocking ]
[ suspenseful music ]
Heather: I don't know if this
means anything...
But I love you too Ray.
I do, oh God, I do.
This fucking bullet can't stop
us.
And these assholes can't stop us
either.
[ intense music ]
We'll ride forever, baby.
We'll make it.
Bobby: Nicky, where are you?
Bobby: Nicky!
You gotta be strong for me now,
Ray.
Why don't we wait for them
outside?
That's not the plan.
We finish this now.
Look, let's just follow the
plan.
This is gonna take all fucking
night.
Hey, where's Ed?
[ indecipherable yelling ]
Back off!
Come on then!
Come on!
What's the matter with you two?
[ yelling ]
Shut up and back off, both of
you, dammit!
Now let's just finish this!
Now Ralph, get your ass upstairs
and check it again.
It's "Ralph," you degenerate
pimp.
You're with me.
[ breathing ]
[ banging ]
[ crying ]
[ rattling ]
[ music ]
[ banging ]
Oh, fuck it!
[ distant coughing ]
[ bag rustling ]
[ coughing ]
[ sniffing ]
[ music intensifies ]
[ gunshots, richochets ]
[ coughing ]
Oh, shit.
I want that phone, you fucker!
Sure.
[ gunshots, running ]
[ gunshots ]
[ footsteps, labored breathing ]
[ coughing ]
[ banging ]
[ sneezing ]
[ spraying ]
[ panting ]
If I make you a hostage, will
they let us out of here?
Yeah, right.
Until one of them could get a
clean shot.
We're not part of this, we just
want out.
Do you think he cares?
[ crying ]
Empty your pockets.
Is this getting you off?
Shut up.
How are you gonna tie me up?
[ breathing ]
Why don't you just kill me and
get it over with?
You think I'm like you?
[ whacking ]
[ gunshots ]
[ gun jamming ]
Fuck!
[ grunting ]
I told you.
Give me that phone. Give-
[ gunshots ]
Dan, are you alright?
Yeah. Bitch.
[ coughing ]
Nicky.
Nicky! Nicky!
Bobby, something's wrong with
Nicky.
I thought you said you could
control him.
Nicky won't leave here alive.
I'll put him down tonight.
What went wrong?
Bad luck, I guess.
That's it?
No. It wasn't a good plan.
This is my fault.
No.
Oh Jesus.
What am I gonna tell my father?
Dan, I want you to go to the
car.
We'll clean this up.
Tell my dad it wasn't
my fault. Okay?
I'll tell your dad how you tried
to protect Ed. Don't worry.
[ creepy music ]
[ choking ]
[ crying ]
[ gunshots ]
[ stumbling ]
[ spanish ]
Mierda!
[ Dan falling ]
[ breathing ]
[ gate sliding open ]
[ electricity crackles ]
[ breathing ]
[ running ]
[ phone ringing ]
[ bang ]
[ intense music ]
[ struggling ]
[ door slamming ]
[ music stops ]
[ grunting ]
[ breathing ]
[ crying ]
[ creepy music ]
He'll kill us all.
[ breathing ]
Why aren't we dead?
I don't know.
You were like a guerrera.
A what?
A warrior.
[ laughing ]
From one of those Mexican movies
on TV.
[ slamming ]
[ screaming ]
[ shotgun blast ]
[ thud ]
[ silence ]
[ bag rustling ]
[ gasp ]
[ scary music ]
Ray.
Ray!
[ echoes ]
[ running ]
[ door closing ]
[ footsteps, breathing ]
[ wood creaking ]
[ electricity crackling ]
[ breathing ]
He'll kill us all.
[ shirt ripping ]
[ distant voice ]
[ music intensifies ]
[ music stops ]
Run.
[ intense music ]
[ shotgun blast ]
[ struggling ]
[ cutting ]
[ scary music ]
[ groaning ]
[ police sirens ]
[ helicopter ]
Ma'am, how many of
them were there?
I just came to get high.
[ radio chatter ]
The day you die feels just like
any other day.
That dark and rancid building on
the edge of nowhere,
that is where I died.
Now I know death isn't an
ending,
but a beginning.
A door to a place within
yourself,
deep within your soul.
The day you die,
that's the day
you know who you really are.
**