NETFLIX PRESENTS
[woman] They're like worms.
[boy] What kind of worms?
[woman] Like worms,
they're everywhere.
[inhales]
[boy] Worms in the body?
[woman] Yes, in... in the body.
[birds chirping]
[boy] Earthworms?
[woman] No.
Another kind of worm.
- [leaves rustling]
- [footsteps approaching]
[woman] I can't move.
[breathing shakily]
[gasps]
But someone is dragging me.
Is that you, David?
[David] You have to stay awake, Amanda.
You have to understand what's important.
[Amanda gasps]
What is important, David?
Why are we seeing all of this?
[David] Because what you see,
we all see.
[birds whistling]
[David] We have to go back
to the garden, Amanda.
- [water burbles gently]
- [birds chirping]
[David] Amanda.
Amanda.
Am I in the garden?
[Amanda] N... no, you're not.
But Carola, your mother, is.
I met her a few days ago,
when Nina and I arrived at the house.
We'd just come back from the river.
[David] What is my mother doing?
[Amanda] She finishes her lemonade
and leaves the glass in the grass,
next to the lounger.
She gets up and walks away.
She forgets her sandals, which are
only a few feet away on the pool steps.
But I don't say anything.
[David] Why not?
[Amanda] Because I want to see
what she does.
[David] W hat does she do?
[Amanda] She slings her purse
over her shoulder
and, in her gold bikini,
she walks to the car.
She walks around the car,
running her hand along it.
She doesn't look at me,
but she gets me to stand up
and walk over to her.
[David] What else?
Why aren't you saying anything?
[Amanda] I check on Nina,
who's still asleep on the porch.
[David] This is not important.
We have to start over.
Your first day in town.
[inaudible]
[Amanda] Am I screaming?
Yes. You are.
[singing along to
"Ain't Got No-I Got Life" on the radio]
♪ Then what have I got? ♪
♪ Why am I alive anyway? ♪
♪ Yeah, hell
What have I got? ♪
♪ Nobody can take away ♪
♪ I got my hair, got my head ♪
♪ Got my brains, got my ears ♪
♪ Got my eyes, got my nose ♪
♪ Got my mouth ♪
♪ I got my smile... ♪ [laughs]
[laughs]
♪ I got my tongue, got my chin ♪
♪ Got my neck, got my boobies ♪
♪ Got my heart, got my soul... ♪
[dogs barking]
[pulls handbrake]
[man] Good day, ladies.
- [Amanda] Hello. You must be Geser.
- That's right. Nice to meet you.
[Amanda] Thanks for coming to meet us.
I didn't want to arrive
at the house on my own.
- Of course.
- [Nina screams]
[dog barking angrily]
- Stop, Bronco. Calm down.
- [barking, growling]
[Geser] I'll tie up the dog
and go with you.
- [Amanda] Yeah.
- [Bronco barking]
[David] This is important.
[Amanda] Why is this important?
I need to understand which things
are important and which aren't.
[David] The details, Amanda.
- [Geser] Quiet down.
- [David] W e need to see the details.
[barking]
[Geser] The house isn't far from town.
It's a 20-minute walk.
And the young lady
can ride her bicycle up there. [chuckles]
- This is a nice car.
- [chuckles]
It was my father's.
[Geser] Oh.
Your father was from Argentina.
[insects chirping]
[birds whistling]
[Amanda] I see you for the first time.
My hands are shaking.
[David] I'm looking at your hands now,
and they're not shaking.
[Nina] Is that our house?
[Geser] No, it's just a bit further.
You're gonna love it. It has
a really nice swimming pool. [chuckles]
You hear that? [chuckles]
[laughs softly]
[pulls handbrake]
- [dog barking]
- [car door closes]
[Nina humming]
[David] It's the day you met my mother.
[Amanda] She's like a ghost.
She puts the buckets down
to open the gate,
and then puts them down again to close it.
I liked her right away.
- Good morning.
Sorry to just show up,
but I brought you water.
Sometimes you can't drink the tap water,
and since you're new here,
I've brought you some.
Thanks.
- Carola. Nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you. Amanda.
That's Nina, my daughter.
[Carola] Hello, Nina.
[Amanda] We can make lemonade.
Would you like some?
Oh yeah, that'd be great. It's so hot.
[chuckles]
Are you here by yourself?
We came early. My husband is on the way.
[Carola] Mm.
They've been preparing
the house for a few days. It looks good.
We don't always get nice neighbors.
[chuckles]
- Will you be staying for a while?
- No, just for the summer.
I wanted to make sure I brought Nina here.
Mm.
[glass clinking gently]
You're not from here either?
[David] Why did you think
she wasn't from around here?
[Carola chuckles] What a compliment...
[Amanda] She seemed so sophisticated.
...but I am.
[Amanda] I remember the way
she moved her hand in the car.
Her arms, the sound of her bracelets.
[indie music playing on radio]
[Amanda] The scent of her sunscreen
when she moved in the seat.
[David] Don't get distracted, Amanda.
Let's go back to the garden.
[Amanda] Why do we always
go back to the garden?
[David] Because it's when my mother
told you about me for the first time.
That is where it starts.
[insects buzzing]
You're not gonna wanna see me anymore.
[exhales]
If I tell you,
you won't let him play with Nina.
Who?
David?
You won't want to, Amanda.
He's your son. He belongs to you.
He used to, but...
now he doesn't belong to me.
[Amanda] She means you, David.
[David] I know. Keep going.
[chuckles] I don't understand, Carola.
A child is yours forever.
[Carola] No, darling.
[inhales] I need a cigarette.
[searches inside purse]
[Amanda] There's a kind of
mutual fascination between us.
And at times, brief periods of repulsion.
When David was born, he was an angel.
Of course he was.
In the hospital, when they put him
in my arms for the first time
I lost my mind a little because...
I was convinced he was missing a finger.
The nurse said
that happens sometimes with anesthesia.
It can make you a little paranoid.
But until I counted
his ten fingers twice, I didn't...
I wasn't convinced
that he wasn't deformed.
[baby David cooing]
[Carola] What I wouldn't give now
for him to be only missing a finger.
What's wrong with David?
He was an angel. When he laughed...
- Where's the ashtray in this car?
- [Amanda] Here.
[Carola] And then David got sick.
That was about seven years ago or so.
I had started to work
for my husband. [chuckles]
It was the first time in my life
I worked for a living. Can you imagine?
[Amanda laughs]
[Carola] I did his bookkeeping,
but bookkeeping had nothing to do with it.
I'd run errands
around town in a nice dress.
It's different for you.
You're from somewhere else.
Here you need an excuse to be glamorous,
and I had the perfect one.
What did your husband do, then?
[Carola] Omar bred horses.
Yeah, if you can believe it.
Omar was different.
When I met him,
he still smiled all the time.
[chuckles]
Back then, we had two spectacular mares.
Sad Cat and Fine Suede.
They were beautiful.
[laughs]
But the secret isn't in the mares.
The real secret is having a good stallion,
and that costs a fortune.
[man] One third isn't enough.
And I'm not waiting until you sell it.
You pay me everything up front.
Half up front,
the rest when the foal is born.
I'm telling you, I can get
at least two hundred thousand.
Nobody is going to find out.
[exhales]
[whistles]
Prince of princes.
You aim high, Omar.
I've had my eye on that one
since he was born.
But if anything happens to him,
they'll hang us both.
Mm? Three days.
And if the boss comes home earlier,
I want him back in half an hour.
[horse trailer door closes]
Can that kid be trusted?
Yeah.
[horse neighs]
- [chuckles] Which color do you like?
- [David laughs]
When I strike it rich,
I'll even carpet the kitchen for you.
- [David laughing]
- [chuckles, smooches]
Eye, eye, boop.
- [David laughing]
- [smooching]
- [David] It's magic...
- [Carola] It's magic...
[horse trotting]
[kisses]
Look at her.
Pretty, isn't she?
[splutters]
Look at her.
[David] There's the black one.
[Omar] Look at how she moves
her tail for him.
She wants him to like her.
Then she'll have a little baby.
- [hooves clopping]
- [breathing deeply]
- Oh.
- [horses neighing]
[gasps softly]
[whispers] Oh.
[horse neighs]
[horse neighing]
[Omar exhales]
[dog barks]
- [horse growling, breathing heavily]
- [dog barking]
[unzips pants]
[Carola] The damned stallion.
You are jealous.
And you're freezing cold.
[both breathing heavily]
[whistling]
[horse neighs]
[neighing]
[door closes]
[Carola] Morning, darling.
Hi.
[footsteps approaching]
I'm going out for little a bit.
Keep an eye on him.
You don't care
about anything but that horse.
I'll be back around five, I promise.
I'm sure he'll mount the other one today.
- [David] One horse.
- [Carola] This one.
- [David] Yeah, she's the mommy.
- She's the mommy. And this one?
- [David] Her son.
- Her son.
- And what are you? What are you?
- Your son.
♪ Run, my little pony ♪
[vocalizes]
- ♪ From the meadow to the what? ♪
- [David] ♪ The meadow to the sea ♪
I love you.
- [David laughing]
- [Carola smooching]
[Carola vocalizes]
♪ Run, my little pony... ♪ [vocalizes]
[horse neighs]
[breathes heavily]
[tense music playing]
- Where are your boots?
- Don't know.
- Your boots, where are they?
- They're lost.
[panting]
- [David] Mommy?
- [panting]
[spluttering]
Mommy.
[Carola] Keep up with me, David.
Come on, catch up.
[groans]
[horse exhales sharply]
[shushing softly]
[horse nickers]
[David] A puddle.
- Look at what I'm doing, Mommy.
- [horse nickering]
Mommy, look.
- [horse snorts]
- [David] I'm going to drop it.
What are you doing? Get out of there.
- [David vocalizing]
- [horse snorts]
Are you crazy?
- If I lost you, I'd lose my house, okay?
- [horse snorts]
- Come on.
- [David] Pretty water.
[vocalizing]
- Stop it. Stop it. David.
- [horse snorts]
[Carola sighs] Come here right now.
- [horse neighs]
- [David laughing]
I thought losing my house
would be a disaster.
Turns out, there are worse things.
I'd give up my home, my life,
to go back and let go
of the reins on that damn horse.
I never told Omar.
Why should I?
I thought my mistake
was over and done with.
But that night I couldn't sleep,
and the next day I understood...
And it was the worst day of my life.
What do you mean he's no there?
That's impossible.
[Omar] You try the other side.
He's not there. He's not there!
[horse neighing]
- [horse neighing]
- [Omar] Where are you? Where did you go?
[mysterious music playing]
[horse neighs, exhales]
[groans]
[squealing]
[squealing continues]
- [groans]
- I found him.
[horse groans]
[nickers]
[groans]
[Carola] What's wrong?
[Omar] Don't touch him!
Are you crazy? [exhales]
- [Carola] Should I call the vet?
- [horse nickers]
- He won't come at this hour.
- [horse groans]
[squeals]
I'll go get him. Stay with the horse.
[horse snorts]
[horse groans]
[breathing loudly]
[Carola breathing intensely]
[somber music playing]
- [David breathing loudly]
- [Carola whispers] David.
Wake up, David.
David.
- [David breathing loudly]
- [nervously] David.
[screams] Omar!
- [sad music playing]
- [panting]
[grunts] Ow.
[David coughing]
[David breathing loudly]
[David winces]
[David coughing]
[exhales]
And so I went to the green house.
What green house?
Sometimes the people
who live here go there.
Couldn't you have taken him to the ER
if he was breathing so bad?
No, Amanda.
[puts out cigarette]
I've seen too many
tragic things in this town.
I had to do something quickly.
I wasn't gonna wait
two hours for a country doctor
who wasn't gonna arrive
in time to save him.
There was something in the water
and it poisoned that horse.
And whatever it was,
it poisoned David too.
Sometimes your eyes aren't enough.
I don't know how I didn't see it.
Why was I taking care of that
goddamn horse, instead of my own son?
[exhales, cries]
[exhales]
[Amanda] I wonder
what I would have done in Carola's place.
Right now I'm calculating
how long it would take
for me to jump from the car
and reach Nina,
if she suddenly fell in the pool.
I call it the "rescue distance."
The thread that ties me to my daughter.
I spend half of my time
calculating that distance,
but I always take
more risks than I should.
[suspenseful music playing]
The invisible thread gets tighter.
[wind rustling]
The woman
from the green house isn't psychic.
She always makes that clear.
She says that everything is energy
and that she can manipulate it.
My grandmother said that too.
[Carola] The house is
about five kilometers by boat.
You go upriver.
David was burning up.
When we arrived,
she was already waiting for us.
[David] The green house, Amanda.
What happened next?
[birds whistling]
[Carola breathing heavily]
[panting]
We're almost there.
David. David. [cries, pants]
Sit down there.
My son...
- [David winces]
- [woman] Calm down. Sit down, please.
Here, drink this.
- Give some to the boy.
- [David wincing]
[Carola crying]
The horse is dead already.
[gasps]
It was poisoned.
The boy has a few hours left,
perhaps a day.
But soon, to survive,
he'll need assisted ventilation.
[Carola crying] My David.
His body is too small and weak to fight
against such a powerful poison.
It will attack his heart.
[cries]
[woman] He won't survive.
No, please, you have to help me.
You have to save him.
[sobbing] Please...
My David.
[crying] Help me, please.
[crying]
[exhales]
If you want, we can try a migration.
There isn't much time,
but we could try to save him.
A migration? What's a migration?
If we can move
David's spirit into a healthy body,
then part of the poison
would also go into that body.
Split into two bodies, he could survive.
[crying]
[woman] It's not certain,
but sometimes it works.
Now, drink this tea.
It will help you make your decision.
Drink it.
Drink slowly.
[Carola crying softly]
[David breathing loudly, coughing]
This is the time to do it. Bring him now.
No, wait a minute.
- Where does his soul go?
- [David breathing loudly]
The other half of my little boy?
[breathing loudly]
[woman] I know you're weak, sweetheart...
...but we have to wash these little hands
very thoroughly.
That half leaves.
We have to let it go.
He won't be the same anymore, Carola.
That's why I'm asking you
if you're willing to accept his new form.
The migration brings an unfamiliar spirit
into the sick body.
But you have to understand
that even without all of David,
you will still be
fully responsible for that body.
No matter what happens.
Wait there.
[thunder rumbling]
- Is that water?
- [woman] Don't worry.
[David breathing loudly]
[sobbing]
[scoffs, exhales]
[exhales forcefully]
You have to stay still, Carola.
If you walk around too much,
you might move things.
Move things?
Without meaning to.
It's a migration.
Only the things that are prepared to leave
should be in motion right now.
[thunder rumbles]
Sit down here.
[crying]
[woman] Don't move.
[Amanda] I want to tell Carola
this is all insane.
And David?
Did you hear anything?
It was almost four hours, I'm not sure.
It was an eternity.
I don't know how long it was.
But do you believe in all that, Carola?
I don't understand.
You understand perfectly, Amanda.
[Amanda] Did you hear anything
during that whole time?
Nothing.
[thunder rumbling]
[door unlocking]
- [door creaking]
- [Carola breathing heavily]
[floor creaking]
[insects chirping]
[insects chirping loudly]
[birds whistling loudly]
[woman] It seems cruel,
but we have to make sure
that the spirit has left.
The migration has taken
most of the poison away.
It's now split between two bodies.
It will lose the battle.
You didn't touch him?
You didn't hug him?
That wasn't my David. It...
[scoffs]
Another boy.
A monster.
[David] I'm not a monster.
I'm a normal boy.
[Amanda] You're not normal, David.
None of this is normal.
Don't be angry, Carola,
but I have to check on Nina.
[Amanda] Her story was unbelievable.
[David] You're entitled to your opinion.
[Amanda] No, David.
You're a voice in my head.
I don't even know
if this is really happening.
[David] It's happening, Amanda.
[Amanda] Am I going to die?
Will that happen, David?
[David] You're wasting your time.
[Amanda] And Nina?
If this is really happening,
where is my daughter?
[David] The details, Amanda.
You have to see the details.
[Amanda] Nina climbs
onto the chair and slides the lock.
[Nina] Mommy, my mole.
Is she gonna take it?
[shushes gently]
[Amanda] Nina is suspicious.
[David] Yes, she is.
What else?
What else is happening
at that exact moment?
[Amanda] I shift the weight
of my body from one leg to the other.
Lately, even staying
on my feet takes a lot of effort.
When I told my husband,
he said I might be depressed.
[Nina singing] ♪ Here's where I found it ♪
[both singing] ♪ Here's where I lost it ♪
♪ Here's where I found it ♪
♪ Here's where I lost it ♪
♪ Find the ring, find the ring ♪
♪ Tell me where it is ♪
- [Amanda chuckles, laughs]
- [laughs]
It's bed time for you.
Come on.
I wanna sing another song.
- I...
- [sleepily] I...
I... I...
[exhales]
[insects chirping]
[Amanda] I didn't want to believe it,
did I, David?
I didn't want to believe
a story like that.
Why did I let something like this happen?
Is this where it began?
Is this the exact moment?
[David] No. This isn't the moment.
[Amanda] It's hard to find it
if I don't know what I'm looking for.
[David] It's something in your body.
It's imperceptible.
That's why you have to pay attention.
[Amanda] That's why
the details are important.
[David] Yes, that's why they're important.
What do you feel now?
[Amanda] I feel uncomfortable.
[grunts] It hurts.
Is it because
the nurses injected me with something?
[David] It's the fever.
The discomfort comes and goes.
We don't have much time.
Let's go back to the day
you met my mother.
Don't forget the details.
[Carola] The river is pretty.
There's a lovely little dock.
Do you drive?
[Amanda] Yes, I love it.
- [Carola] That's great.
- [chuckles]
May I?
I love the feel of carpets.
If I had the money,
I'd have them everywhere.
It's okay?
[sighs] Mmm.
[Amanda] After what happened,
they had to sell everything, right, David?
[Carola breathing heavily]
[David] After the horse died,
they had to sell everything.
David?
[grass rustling]
What are you doing?
[Amanda] Is what your mother told me true?
Did you kill them, David?
[David] I buried them. I didn't kill them.
I found them floating in the river.
[Amanda] In the end, you get used to it.
And changing cities
every so often is part of the routine.
Marco's work has always been like that.
With Nina,
it's getting a little harder but...
I've been to places
I'd never have gone to otherwise.
Living in different houses...
I'd love that.
Do you remember all of your addresses?
[chuckles]
And where do you work?
I do a bit of everything.
I even clean houses.
But I finish early. By noon, I'm free.
Can you get this?
[chuckles softly]
[Carola chuckles softly]
Come down, David!
David, come down from there!
He loves it.
[Amanda] Climbing?
Making me nervous.
[water burbling]
[Carola] Why did you end up coming here?
[Amanda] My dad
always told me about this place.
He used to come here
to fish when I was little.
I always wanted to come but...
I never had the chance.
My mother wouldn't let me.
Sending me alone
from Spain was impossible.
Then my father died when I was 13,
so I never had the opportunity.
[twigs breaking]
Until now.
[grass rustling]
San Lucas is the name of the lake.
[Carola] Mmm.
- [Amanda] Do you know it?
- [Carola] Yes.
[Amanda] I promised Marco we'd wait
for him to get here and go together.
Yes, perfect. It was a smooth trip.
[man speaking indistinctly on phone]
[Amanda] Seriously?
So when are you coming?
[man speaking indistinctly on phone]
[Amanda exhales]
Yes, Marco.
But you never see her.
She asks about you all the time.
[Marco speaking indistinctly]
We promised we'd spend
more time as a family.
[Marco speaking indistinctly]
[sighs]
Hmm.
[Marco speaking indistinctly]
Okay, do what you want.
We've got all the time in the world.
- [sighs]
- [tense music playing]
[dog barking in distance]
[Amanda] Why do mothers do that?
[David] Do what?
[gate creaking]
[Amanda] Always imagine
the worst possible scenario.
Measuring danger...
the rescue distance.
[David] The thread.
- [scraping in the distance]
- [dog barking]
[scraping getting louder]
[dog whimpers, barks]
David?
What are you doing out so late?
- Your mother know you're here?
- [panting]
- David!
[David] Keep going, Amanda.
We don't have time for this.
We are looking for worms.
Something like worms.
The exact moment
they touch your body for the first time.
- [Amanda chuckles]
- [Nina laughs]
- [laughs]
- [high-pitched shooting]
- [Nina screams]
- [Amanda gasps]
[breathes intensely]
Sweetheart.
Look...
It's just to scare away the birds.
[car horn honking]
[dog barking]
- [indistinct chattering]
- [child laughing]
- [dog barking]
- [sniffs]
[child babbling]
Nina?
- [child vocalizing and babbling]
- [toy squeaking]
[child babbling]
[laughs]
- Abigail? Listen to me Abigail.
- [Abigail laughs, shouts]
- [laughs]
- Not around customers.
- [Abigail babbles]
- Sorry about that.
[snorts]
[laughing]
- Hello.
- [Abigail shouts]
[babbles]
- [woman] Anything else?
- [Amanda] I'll take the shark, please.
- [toy squeaks]
- [Amanda] Do you know this girl, David?
[toy squeaking]
[Amanda] Is there part of you in her body?
Where is your other half?
[David] Those are
just the stories my mother tells.
David.
Hop in the car. We'll give you a ride.
It's too hot to skateboard home.
Do you remember my name?
Amanda.
- [birds chirping]
- [breathing intensely]
[screams playfully, panting]
[Nina laughing]
What's this?
[David ticking spoon on jar]
It's an experiment.
[Amanda] You really don't want to come in?
Do you go to school?
[sighs]
I miss school.
I didn't know I would.
Do you ever get out of here?
Out of this town?
Never.
[Amanda exhales]
You're invited to come
and play whenever you want.
[chuckles]
[owl hooting]
[Carola] Omar!
Omar, answer the door.
- [exhales]
- [high heels clip-clopping]
Amanda. Everything okay?
[Amanda] Yeah, yeah. It's nothing,
but the other day I noticed that
David's skateboard needed new wheels,
so I got these.
They're phosphorescent, see?
They glow in the dark. [chuckles]
Thank you.
Hold on. I'll get my smokes.
- [Amanda] Okay.
- Wait here.
Don't wait for Marco.
You should go to the lake.
Why?
Because this is your trip.
You should do it for yourself.
Then you should learn how to drive a car.
Okay.
[chuckles]
You nervous?
You should be.
- [puffing]
- [chuckles]
[laughing continues in the distance]
[Amanda] That's the first time I did it.
[David] Did what?
[Amanda] I left Nina alone with Elvira.
Do you think we need to make more?
[Amanda] The thread that connects
us together was stretched again.
To give each of us more independence.
["Mujer Noche" by Mar de Copas
playing in Spanish on radio]
[laughs]
Now, get it up to speed.
Super. Really good.
- Wow, I'm doing it.
- Really good!
[Carola laughs] I'm driving.
[Amanda] Really good! [laughs]
[both laughing] Oh!
["Mujer Noche" continues]
[both whooping and laughing]
[Amanda] Watch out.
Watch out! Brake! Brake!
[tires screech]
[Amanda grunting] Ah.
- I'm sorry.
- [Amanda] Ow. [inhales]
- You okay?
- Yeah. Yeah. [breathes intensely]
- I'm okay.
- [Carola] Let me see.
[breathes intensely]
- Looks like you hit your head.
- Yeah.
You hit your head.
[exhales] Yeah.
[chuckles] It's nothing.
Well, that wasn't
a very elegant finish, was it?
[both laugh]
It was fine.
- [laughs]
- [seat belt unbuckles]
[car door opens]
- [exhales, chuckles]
- [car door closes]
[car door opens]
[Carola] Thank you for the lesson.
If only you'd come into my life sooner.
If I'd known how to drive,
maybe my life could've been different.
[birds chirping]
[insects chirping]
[Carola] Should we go in?
Nice.
[chuckles] Yeah.
[Amanda] David,
am I going to die?
[David] Dying isn't so bad.
[Amanda] It's strange that I feel so calm.
Were you there?
[David] What happens next?
What a beautiful little lion she is.
I'd steal this little lion for myself.
Those little ears...
These little dimples...
I'll eat them with a teaspoon.
I'll take you while you're asleep.
I'll take you away with me.
[gasps]
I wish I had a Nina for myself.
[sniffs]
[suspenseful music playing]
[Amanda] Where is Nina, David?
Where is my daughter?
[David] Amanda.
I need you to concentrate.
I don't want to start again
from the beginning.
Amanda.
[insects chirping]
[gasps]
[grunts lightly]
[leaves rustling]
[gasps]
[grunts]
[David and Amanda grunt]
[Amanda grunting]
[grunts, breathes heavily]
- [footsteps approaching]
- [Amanda grunting]
[Amanda grunt, breathes heavily]
[birds twittering]
[morose music playing]
[water burbling]
[weakly] She called you a monster.
[Nina] Mommy, my mole.
Is she gonna take it?
[shushes gently]
- [Amanda] I...
- [Nina] I...
- I...
- [sleepily] I...
Nina?
Marco, what are you doing here?
Where's Nina?
She's here.
[kisses]
I thought you weren't
going to be here until next weekend.
Nina has something to tell you.
Nina... Come on. Go ahead and tell her.
It's an experiment, Amanda.
Where did this can come from, Nina?
I'm not Nina. I'm David.
[David] Are you lying to me, Amanda?
Stop it, Nina!
[Amanda] No, David. It's a dream.
Stop it!
[inaudible]
[Amanda] A nightmare.
[yells] Stop it!
[gasps]
[breathing heavily]
[Amanda] Where is Nina, David?
Where is my daughter?
- [David] That's not important.
- [Amanda] It's the only important thing.
- [David] It's not important.
- [Amanda] David.
[David] Keep going.
- [soft music playing]
- [bird squawks]
[water burbling]
- [horse neighs]
- [gasps]
[horse neighs]
[Amanda] I decided not to wait
for Marco and went to the lake alone.
[David] Why?
[Amanda] As your mother said,
it was a journey
I needed to take for myself.
[water swishing gently]
[Amanda] Something's gonna happen now.
[engine starts]
[brake pedal creeks]
[Carola] He's in your house.
He's in your house!
- What happened?
- [Carola] David is in your house.
What do you mean?
I stepped out to water the flowers,
and when I came back, the door was locked.
- [Amanda] Nina!
- [Carola] Do you have the key?
- He locked both doors.
- Nina! Nina, open the door!
- We have to get in there.
- [Amanda] I left everything open.
[Carola] He closed everything.
He's gonna do something bad.
Nina! Just shut up for one minute!
You're driving me crazy!
- [Elvira] My God!
- [Amanda] Nina! [bangs on door]
- [Carola] He's gonna do something!
- Don't say that. He's just a child!
- [Elvira] Oh my God!
- [cries]
[Amanda] Move!
[somber music playing]
[panting] Nina!
Nina!
- [Carola] David!
- Check the bathrooms.
- [Amanda gasps]
- We were hiding, Mommy!
- [Amanda sighs] Are you all right?
- [sighs]
- [Carola] You found her.
[Nina] I was hiding.
[Amanda sighs in relief]
Nina, what happened?
[Elvira] Oh my God,
what happened? I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry. Is everything all right?
- Let me take her.
- [Amanda] Yes, please.
[Elvira] Come here.
- What happened? What's wrong?
- [Amanda sighs]
[Carola sighs] Thank God nothing happened.
This is so crazy.
Are you completely insane?
[Carola] Amanda, I'm sorry.
- You have to be careful with David.
- No!
You're the one I need to be careful with!
David didn't do anything!
You're the one saying David, David, David!
You don't trust him,
and he's your own goddamn son!
[Amanda breathing heavily]
Let's go, David.
[Amanda cries]
[humming a lullaby]
[insects chirping]
[bed creaking]
[David whispers] Amanda.
You invited me.
[Amanda screams]
[panting]
What are you doing?
[somber music playing]
Go away!
[grunts]
[panting]
[David] You should leave!
- [glass shatters]
- [Amanda screams]
[grunting]
[crying]
[breathing heavily]
Marco.
Marco, it's me! Pick up!
Pick up!
Nina. Nina.
Hey, you need to wake up.
Come on, sweetheart.
- [owl hooting]
- [dog barking]
[introspective music playing]
[Amanda] I think about Carola.
About you.
And I wonder if I'm part of this madness.
[David] You're thinking
about talking to her.
[Amanda] Maybe your mother was right
to be so afraid of you.
I need to apologize
for yelling at her yesterday.
[introspective music intensifies]
[sighs]
[David] You just need to see her again.
Talking to Carola is a mistake.
[Amanda] It's done.
[David] The details, Amanda.
Don't forget the details.
[workers speaking indistinctly]
[woman] Can I help you?
- I'm looking for Carola. Is she here?
- [woman] Okay, let me call her.
Carola?
There's a woman here looking for you.
No. No, I don't know.
Okay, I'll tell her. [hangs up phone]
She's on her way.
But it'll take her a while to get here.
No problem. We can wait outside.
Come on, Nina.
[birds chirping]
[Amanda] I don't remember much more.
[David] No.
Amanda, there's more.
[workers speaking indistinctly]
[David] You're close. So close.
But there's more.
Mommy, I got wet.
It's just dew, sweetheart.[clicks tongue]
Who's here for me?
Hey!
[Amanda] I'd never seen her
in her uniform.
[Carola] Hi, Nina.
[Amanda] I got distracted for a moment.
[Carola] Amanda, is everything all right?
[Amanda] Yes, everything is fine.
We have to leave,
because of my husband's job.
Where are you going?
We're going back.
Right now?
[Amanda] I just wanted to apologize.
It was nothing.
But wait.
What happened?
[Amanda] Everything is fine.
It's because of David.
I knew that if I told you,
you'd never want to see me again.
[Amanda] It's not that. I swear.
[David]
Weren't you going to leave, Amanda?
[Amanda] No, David.
Nina is going to run now.
She's going to turn round and shout,
"Look, Mommy. The plane."
[Nina shouts] Mommy, look. The plane!
- [plane whirring]
- [Amanda] We're going to walk.
And I'm going to ask myself
if I'm doing the right thing by leaving.
[Carola] I'm sorry I got upset yesterday.
There are just some days
where things hurt too much.
I haven't thought about
what I want in a long time.
I only think about what I would've wanted.
That's something you wouldn't understand.
Why wouldn't I?
[Carola] You think
I don't fantasize about leaving?
About starting another life?
About finding someone
who will let me take care of them?
[Amanda] What do you mean by that?
You won't come back, Amanda.
You'll leave, and every year
you'll pick a different place...
farther and farther away.
And I'm tied to this fucking town.
I can't escape
from the things that scare me.
I made my own decisions.
I don't regret anything.
You only see yourself, Carola.
And you?
You never look at yourself.
[Amanda exhales]
[breathing heavily]
You look pale. Are you okay?
[Amanda breathing heavily]
[tense music playing]
[David] Amanda, are you all right?
[water burbling gently]
[Amanda] I don't want to go on, David.
I'm exhausted.
[David] We're very close. Hang on.
Can you see me?
[Amanda] I see the treetops.
Everything is moving.
I hear the wood creaking underneath me.
- [water burbling]
- [David panting]
- [Amanda] Where's Nina?
- [panting]
[weakly] Don't leave Nina alone.
What's wrong with me?
- Are you going to pass out, Amanda?
- [Amanda breaths heavily]
[breathing loudly]
[David] That happens later, Amanda.
- [gasps, cries]
- [David] Concentrate.
- [EKG beeping]
- [David] You have to put things in order.
[morose music playing]
[Amanda] Nina is near me,
and it calms me down.
[Nina] Mommy.
Mommy, I'm thirsty.
[Amanda] My mother always said...
[Amanda, weakly] It's okay, sweetheart.
[Amanda] "Sooner or later,
something bad is going to happen,
and when it happens,
I want to have you close."
Daddy?
[Amanda breathing heavily]
[Carola] How are you?
[woman] She has sunstroke.
Take her home so she can rest.
She'll be fine.
[Amanda] She strokes my hair,
and her fingers are cold.
But it feels nice.
[David] Concentrate, Amanda.
Where does my mother take you?
If I'd known you were coming,
I would've tidied up a bit more.
[breathing heavily]
You can rest here for a while.
[footsteps receding]
[Omar] Carola.
[footsteps approaching]
[Carola shushes]
[Carola] What's wrong?
All the lights are on.
[Omar] David.
- [Carola sighs] Go to sleep.
- [Omar] He isn't in his room.
- [somber music playing]
- [Carola] Didn't you lock his door?
[Omar] I locked his door,
and he was asleep. That's what I did.
Great. You can relax, then.
[Omar] There's noises
coming from the stable,
and the front door is open.
Someone broke the latches.
[Carola gasps]
[somber music playing]
[Amanda breathing heavily]
- [leaves rustling]
- [gasps]
[rustling stops]
- [yelling] Run!
- [screams]
- Get away! Get away from here!
- [panting]
Nina. Nina. [grunts]
[Nina] Mommy?
Mommy.
[shushes]
- [owl hooting]
- [Amanda panting]
[car door opens]
[engine sputters]
- [gasps]
- [engine sputters]
[thumping on car]
[engine sputters]
- [gasps]
- [engine sputters, then starts]
[engine revs]
[Amanda breathing rapidly]
[Nina] My eyes itch, Mommy.
- [Amanda] Are you okay, sweetheart?
- [Nina] I'm very thirsty.
[breathes heavily]
We'll get water in town, okay?
[breathing heavily]
[tires screech]
[Amanda grunts]
[children shouting indistinctly]
[screaming and shouting]
- [Amanda gasps]
- [child shouting]
[Amanda] Are they like you, David?
[David] What am I like, Amanda?
Very few children are born normal here.
[Amanda breathing heavily]
[Nina] Mommy.
- [thuds]
- [Nina] Mommy!
[woman] No, no, she's much better.
Yes. Yes.
I'll put her on. She just woke up.
It's your husband.
Talk to him.
- [weakly] Marco.
- What's going on?
- [cries]
- [EKG beeping]
Marco, there's something wrong.
[crying] I can't move at all.
It's all right. How's Nina?
Nina?
I don't know where Nina is.
Hurry. Please, you have to come right now.
Do you know where she is?
Who's taking care of her?
- [tense music playing]
- [Amanda] No.
- No. [crying, grunting]
- [nurse] Calm down, calm down.
- Hello, yes.
- My daughter. Where is she?
[nurse] The little girl? Her friend is
taking care of her, don't worry.
The doctor is coming. It'll take a while.
Yes, I know.
[EKG beeping]
[grunting weakly]
[softly] Amanda.
Nina is sick too.
She's too little.
She can't hold out.
And the doctor won't get here in time.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
I told you I have no regrets.
You think I'd rather
my David were dead, but no.
I'm glad he's alive, I swear.
I have to take her.
I have to take Nina to the green house.
[grunts weakly]
Tell me you would do the same.
I need your consent as her mother.
[morose music playing]
[Carola sniffs]
She'll save her.
Everything will be all right.
[grunts weakly]
[Amanda] She isn't asking me
for permission.
She's asking me to forgive her.
[cries]
[Carola] Come on.
- [Nina laughing]
- [Carola] Whoop.
[Amanda] She wants Nina.
She wants her for herself.
We have to go to the green house.
[David] We're close now.
Hold on.
[Amanda] What are they doing to Nina?
Is it happening now?
I can't let them touch her, David.
[David] There's not much time left.
You still can't see it.
There's more to see.
- Just look around you.
- [Amanda grunting]
Look.
[Amanda] I don't see it.
[David] You see it,
but you still don't understand.
Do you feel it?
Mommy, I got wet.
It's just dew, sweetheart.
[woman] Carola,
there's a woman here looking for you.
This is the exact moment.
[Amanda] It's not dew.
It's everywhere.
[David whispers] Amanda.
[Amanda] Take me.
- [Amanda] Take me.
- [Amanda] Take me to the green house.
[Amanda] Take me
to the green house, David.
[Amanda grunting]
- [Amanda] Am I screaming?
- [water burbling]
[David] You are, yes.
You're screaming Nina's name.
- [Amanda] What's going to happen to Nina?
- [panting]
[Amanda] Where will her other half go?
- [grunting]
- [Amanda] Can't you do something?
Can you bring her close?
[grunting]
[David] Close to whom?
[Amanda] Close to me.
[melancholic music playing]
- [David] Amanda.
- [grunting, shivering]
[David] I'm here.
The thread.
It... it's getting tighter.
[Amanda shivering]
It's Nina.
[crying]
[breathing heavily]
She's pulling the thread to find me.
[grunts]
It feels like
the thread is tied around my waist.
[cries]
Splitting me
in half.
[grunting]
Is it because I didn't see the danger?
The rescue distance.
[grunting]
Is... is this what you wanted me to see?
What do you see, Amanda?
[crying]
The thread.
[David crying]
[sobbing]
[David] The thread has already snapped.
[crying]
Amanda, I know you can hear me.
I'm going to keep going.
[water burbling]
[David] One last try.
We have a few seconds.
Pay attention.
There's one more thing to understand.
What do you see?
["Ain't Got No/I Got Life" playing]
♪ Ain't got no home ♪
♪ Ain't got no shoes ♪
♪ Ain't got no money ♪
♪ Ain't got no class ♪
♪ Ain't got no skirts ♪
♪ Ain't got no sweaters ♪
♪ Ain't got no perfume ♪
♪ Ain't got no love... ♪
Hello?
[dog barking in the distance]
[door closes]
[footsteps approaching]
[Omar] Come in.
Thank you.
I'm Marco Casali.
May I have a word?
Amanda was my wife.
[Omar] I hardly knew your wife.
But I think your wife knew her.
My wife left.
What do you want?
Nina isn't well.
It's been over a year.
She's recovering
despite all that happened, but...
There's something else,
and I don't know what's wrong with her.
Do you know what happened?
- What happened to Nina?
- [door opens]
[footsteps approaching]
[Omar] No.
I don't.
[sips]
[Marco] You must know.
Somebody has to know.
[panting]
[door closes]
As you can see,
I'd like for someone
to answer my questions too.
I don't know what you're looking for,
but you won't find it here.
You need to leave.
- [birds chirping]
- [dog barking]
[Marco] Get him out.
[angrily] Tell him to get out!
Get out, David.
[seat belt unbuckles]
[Omar] Come on.
[David grunting]
- David! David!
- [David grunts]
[both grunting]
- [David grunting]
- [Omar] David!
[both grunting]
As if he was going anywhere.
[engine starts, revs]
[David breathing heavily]
[birds chirping]
[breathing heavily]
[sad music playing]
BASED ON THE NOVEL BY
SAMANTA SCHWEBLIN
["Ain't Got No-I Got Life"
bt Nina Simone playing]