Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
GIRL: The number one rule
in my family?
Honor your parents.
They're the supreme beings
who gave you life
who sweated
and sacrificed so much
to put a roof
over your head,
food on your plate,
an epic amount of food.
The least you can do
in return is
every single thing
they ask.
'Course some people are like,
"Be careful.
"Honoring your parents
sounds great,
"but if you take it too far,
"well, you might forget
to honor yourself."
Luckily,
I don't have that problem.
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
I'm Meilin Lee.
And ever since I turned 13,
I've been doing my own thing.
Making my own moves,
24/7, 365.
I wear what I want,
say what I want
and I will not
hesitate to do
a spontaneous cartwheel
if I feel so moved. (GRUNTS)
- (MAN GASPS)
- Oh, crap!
Not to brag,
but being 13 means
I'm officially a grown-up.
At least according to the
Toronto Transit Commission.
Good for you.
MEILIN: Mmm-hmm, mmm-hmm.
All about that hustle,
am I right?
(UPBEAT MUSIC CONTINUES)
(YELPS)
Besties, assemble!
- Miriam!
- Hmm?
Hey!
- (BOTH LAUGHING, WHOOPING)
- Priya!
(IN DEEP VOICE) Yo.
Abby!
- (SPEAKING KOREAN)
- (ALL GASP)
(IN ENGLISH)
Yeah. What's up, Mei?
- (ALL FLAPPING LIPS)
- Ready to change the world?
(SNAPS FINGERS) So ready.
I was born to do this.
Let's burn this place
to the ground!
Y equals negative four.
(SPEAKING FAUX FRENCH)
(IN ENGLISH) Manitoba,
Alberta, and Saskatchewan.
I know, it's a lot...
(PLAYING NOTE)
But this is grade eight.
I don't got time
to mess around.
I guess you could call me...
A very enterprising,
mildly annoying young lady.
A major weirdo.
An overachieving dork-narc.
(MEILIN GRUNTS)
I accept
and embrace all labels.
(GRUNTS)
- Oops.
- Hey!
- Aah!
- Oh, you're dead!
- (SCHOOL BELL RINGING)
- MEILIN: Coming through!
Move, please! (PANTING)
Share the sidewalk, people!
Anyway, who cares what stupid,
evil Tyler
or anyone else thinks?
This is gonna be my year.
(GASPS) Mei, Mei, Mei,
come see this!
And nothing's gonna stop
this train from... (YELPS)
ABBY: Shh. Come on, come on!
- Get your butt over here!
- PRIYA: Go, go, go.
MIRIAM: Come on, come on.
Mei, Mei, fast!
MEILIN: Shut up!
ABBY: Shh!
- Huh?
- Mmm-hmm!
- Uh...
- Mmm.
Devon.
(DREAMY MUSIC PLAYING)
My mom cuts his hair
at the salon,
and I felt it. It's very soft.
Whoa. Can I have some?
Yeah, Abby, hook a sister up.
Ugh!
He looks like a hobo.
A hot hobo.
May I remind you
what real men look like?
ALL: (GASPING) 4-Town!
Yes! 4-Town!
(ALL SIGHING)
MEILIN:
Jesse went to art school.
- (TRUE LOVE BY 4-TOWN PLAYING)
- (SIGHS WEARILY)
- (KISSES)
- Tae Young fosters
- injured doves.
- (CHUCKLES)
Robaire speaks French.
AARON T: Hey!
And Aaron T. and Aaron Z.
are, like,
really talented, too.
We are 4-Townies, remember?
(ECHOES) Ride or die!
(ROMANTIC MUSIC CONTINUES)
(ROMANTIC MUSIC STOPS)
Yeah, but tickets
to 4-Town are, like,
a bajillion dollars,
and Devon's right here.
And free!
(TRAM BELL CLANGING)
Ah, fudgesicles! I gotta go.
Wait! We're going
karaokeing today.
- Yeah!
- Come with us.
- Please.
- (ALL WHINING)
- MIRIAM: Please.
- I...
can't. It's cleaning day.
Mei, every day
is cleaning day.
Can't you just
get one afternoon off?
But I like cleaning.
(GASPS) Plus,
I got this new feather duster
and, oh, my gosh, you guys,
it picks up so much dirt,
it's bananas!
Fine. I'll let you go.
If you can pass the gauntlet.
- Come on. Uh! Oh.
- Mir, not now...
You can't resist it.
(CHUCKLES) Come on.
- You know you want to.
- (MEILIN SIGHS)
- (ABBY BEATBOXING)
- Here we go.
(BOTH SINGING)
You're never not on my mind
- Oh, my, oh, my
- Oh, yeah, oh, my
I'm never not by your side,
your side
PRIYA: Yeah.
Your side
PRIYA: Peace sign.
ALL: All right!
- (ALL GIGGLE)
- ABBY: Yeah! Go, Mei!
- See, that was good!
- ABBY: That was dope!
- You passed.
- (SIGHS)
- And here is your reward.
- (GASPS)
MIRIAM:
Ninety-nine Australian tour,
with the Girl I Love
Your Jeans remix.
O-M-G, Mir!
I'll guard it with my life!
(KISSING LOUDLY)
Oh, thank you,
thank you, thank you!
4-Town 4-ever!
ALL: 4-ever!
(ALL ULULATING)
We'll karaoke another time,
I promise!
Okay, sure, Mei!
It'll be on me.
The snacks, the tunes...
- Whoo!
- You're my jam, girl.
(TRAM BELL CLANGING)
She's so brainwashed.
(PEOPLE CHATTERING, GASPING)
(PANTING) Crud, crud, crud.
MEILIN: Okay.
Excuse me.
- I know what it looks like.
- (MAN SPEAKING IN CANTONESE)
(IN ENGLISH)
I am my own person.
(PANTING, YELLS)
But that doesn't mean
doing whatever I want.
- Hello, Meilin.
- Hey, how's it going?
- (GRUNTS)
- Thank you, Meilin!
Like most adults,
I have responsibilities.
Hey, Bart. Hey, Lisa.
- Hello, Meilin.
- 'Sup?
Still down for a rematch,
Mr. Gao?
Bring it, Lee!
- (ALL CHUCKLE)
- What a good girl. (LAUGHS)
It's not all about me,
you know?
(MEILIN PANTING)
I do make my own moves,
it's just that...
(EXHALES HEAVILY)
...some of my moves
are also hers.
Mei-Mei, there you are.
- Hey, Mom...
- You're ten minutes late.
What happened? Are you hurt?
Are you hungry?
Um... (MUFFLED GRUNT)
How was school today?
Killed it per usual.
Check it out.
Oh. That's my little scholar.
Today, honor student,
tomorrow,
UN Secretary General.
The ancestors
would be so proud.
Sun Yee, revered ancestor,
guardian of the red pandas.
We humbly thank you
for protecting and guiding us.
Especially Mei-Mei.
May we continue
to serve and honor you
and this community.
BOTH: Always.
(GONG SOUNDING)
- (BIRDS COOING)
- (SERENE MUSIC PLAYING)
(BELL CHIMING)
(BOTH BREATHE DEEPLY)
- You ready?
- Let's do this.
- (KNUCKLES CRACK)
- (NECK CRACKS)
(HIP-HOP MUSIC PLAYING)
- (BOYS LAUGHING)
- BOY: Have fun
- getting that off.
- (BOTH GASP)
MING: Shoo-shoo! You vandals!
BOY 2: Oh, snap!
They're coming!
- You good-for-nothing hosers!
- BOY 3: Go, go, go!
I'm telling your mothers!
Our family runs
one of the oldest temples
in Toronto.
And the most unique.
Instead of honoring a god,
we honor our ancestors.
And not just the dudes either.
Our most revered ancestor,
Sun Yee,
was a scholar, poet,
and defender of animals.
She dedicated her life to
the creatures of the forest.
Especially the red panda.
- Ta-da!
- TOURISTS: Ooh!
Which she loved
for its fiery coat
- and mischievous nature.
- (MEILIN GROWLS, WHINES)
Ever since, the red panda
has blessed our family
with good fortune
and prosperity...
- And it can bless yours, too!
- (TOURISTS EXCLAIM)
- WOMAN: Bye-bye!
- See you next time!
Thanks for coming.
(BOTH SIGH HEAVILY)
- Give me five. (GRUNTS)
- Yeah.
- Come on. Dad's making dinner.
- Ooh.
(UTENSILS CLANKING)
(SWEEPING MUSIC PLAYING)
(PAN SIZZLING)
(SLOSHING)
Mmm.
(BELL RINGING)
Huh? (EXCLAIMS) Uh...
(GLASSES SQUEAKING)
(MAN AND WOMAN CONVERSING
IN CANTONESE ON TV)
(SINISTER MUSIC PLAYING ON TV)
MING: (SIGHS)
He should have listened
to his mother
and married Ling-Yi.
Totally.
Siu-Jyu is so two-faced.
She's just using him
to get to the throne.
She'll probably stab him
on their wedding night.
Mmm-hmm.
Hmm?
Mmm. Hmm!
- Perfect.
- Yes!
ANNOUNCER:
You've heard their hits,
you've seen their moves.
And now, you get
to experience them live!
The worldwide
pop sensation 4-Town
will be kicking off
their North American tour!
Tickets on sale now.
(GASPS) Oh, my gosh!
Who are these hip-hoppers?
And why are they called
"4-Town"
if there are five of them?
Uh... I don't know.
Some of the kids
at school like them.
You mean Miriam?
That girl is odd.
JIN: Dinner's ready.
(4-TOWN SINGING NOBODY LIKE U
ON TV)
I've never met nobody like you
You're never not on my mind
- Oh my, oh my
- (MEILIN HUMMING ALONG)
I'm never not by your side
Your side, your side
I'm never gonna let you cry
Oh, cry, don't cry
I'm gonna be your ride or die
All right
(MEILIN CONTINUES
SINGING INDISTINCTLY)
Hmm. Kinda looks like Devon.
(SCOFFS) I don't get
what Mir sees in him.
He's not that cute.
Okay, his shoulder's, like,
kind of nice, I guess.
(SIGHS) His eyes are... fine.
(MYSTERIOUS MUSIC PLAYING)
(CHUCKLES)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
- MING: Mei-Mei.
- (GASPS)
- (THUDS)
- Ow! Ah!
(PANTING, GASPS)
Do you want a snack?
Cool, great, thanks.
Don't look at the notebook,
don't look
at the notebook, don't!
No!
- Oh.
- (CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
- Is this your homework?
- Mom...
- Don't!
- Oh, my. What... What is...
- Do not.
- Huh? What?
- Mom.
- Oh! Oh.
Huh? (GAGS) Huh?
Mei-Mei, what is this?
It's nothing. Just a boy.
He's no one.
- A boy?
- (GASPS)
Who is he?
Did he do these things to you?
- No! It's just made up, Mom!
- (BOTH STRAINING)
- It's not real.
- (PAGE RIPS)
That hat.
Is that the sketchy clerk
from the Daisy Mart?
(GASPS) Mom, no!
- (DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
- (TIRES SCREECHING)
(NERVOUSLY)
What are you doing?
No, no, no!
- No, no, no!
- (STORE BELL CHIMING)
(LAUGHS SMUGLY) Oh, snap!
(PANTING)
Mom, no!
- You!
- Whoa!
What have you done
to my Mei-Mei?
Uh... Who?
Meilin Lee, right here.
I should report you
to the police.
How old are you? Thirty?
I'm seventeen.
Oh, see, see?
This is what happens
when you don't wear sunblock
and do drugs all day!
She's just a sweet,
innocent child.
How dare you
take advantage of her!
Mom! No! (ECHOES)
- (HEART BEATING)
- (PEOPLE GASP)
- What?
- (ALL MURMURING)
(TYLER LAUGHS)
What a weirdo.
(PEOPLE WHISPERING
INDISTINCTLY)
GIRL: Look at her.
(AIR KISSING NOISILY)
- (LAUGHTER)
- (HEART BEATING RAPIDLY)
(GASPS)
The Daisy Mart has lost
a loyal customer today.
(LAUGHTER)
(SIGHS IN EXASPERATION)
Thank goodness I was here.
That degenerate
won't come near you again.
Now, is there anything else
I should know about, Mei-Mei?
Nope. All good.
(MUFFLED SCREAMING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
You sicko!
What were you thinking?
Why would you
draw those things?
Those horrible, awful,
sexy things?
It's fine.
You'll move to another city,
change your identity.
(MUFFLED YELLING)
(TEARFULLY)
Mommy, I'm so sorry.
(MUFFLED SCREAMING, GASPS)
You are her pride and joy,
so act like it!
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
This will never happen again.
(BELLS TINKLING SOFTLY)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(WIND WHISTLING)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(THUNDER CRASHING)
(GROANING)
(WHIMPERING)
(OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING)
(CONTINUES WHIMPERING)
(GASPING HEAVILY)
- (GASPS LOUDLY)
- (WHIMPERING)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
No! No, no, no!
(OMINOUS MUSIC BUILDS)
(GASPS, PANTING HEAVILY)
(HEART BEATING)
MING: Mei-Mei...
are you up?
- (TV PLAYING INDISTINCTLY)
- (MING SCATTING TUNE)
Breakfast is ready!
- Mmm.
- Hey! No sugar.
- (BED CREAKING)
- (MEILIN MOANS)
(LOUD THUD)
Coming!
- (FOOTSTEPS THUDDING)
- Mmm. Porridge.
(YAWNING)
- (MEILIN SCREAMING)
- (DOOR SLAMS)
(GULPS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
This isn't happening.
(PANICKED WHIMPERING)
(GASPS, SNIFFING)
(GAGS)
(SOBBING)
- Wake up, wake up, wake up!
- MING: Mei-Mei,
- is everything okay?
- (GASPS)
- Don't come in here!
- (OBJECTS CLATTERING)
Mei-Mei, what's going on,
honey? Are you sick?
Is it a fever? A stomach ache?
Chills? Constipation?
MEILIN: No!
Wait. Is it...
that? Did the...
Did the red peony bloom?
No!
- Maybe?
- (GASPS)
But it's too soon.
Don't worry, Mei-Mei.
I'll get everything you need.
Mommy's here.
Jin. Jin! It's happening!
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(STRAINING) Come on! Please!
(GROANS)
- MING: Mei-Mei, I'm coming.
- Crud.
- I'm coming.
- No!
It's going to be okay.
No, it's not!
Will you just get out?
Excuse me?
(SPUTTERS) I didn't mean that.
I'm a gross red monster!
(SOBBING)
Stop it! Stop talking!
(CLEARS THROAT)
Mei-Mei,
I know this is upsetting,
but we are going
to get through this together.
I have ibuprofen, vitamin B,
a hot water bottle, and pads.
Regular, overnight, scented,
unscented, thin, ultrathin...
- Uh-huh. All right.
- ...ultrathin with wings...
Awesome.
Just leave them by the sink.
Mei-Mei.
Perhaps we should talk
about why this is happening.
No! I mean, nah, it's okay.
You are a woman now.
And your body
- is starting to change.
- (MUFFLED) Mmm-hmm.
It's nothing to be
embarrassed about.
Mom, please!
You are now a beautiful,
strong flower.
No, no, no.
Who must protect
your delicate petals
and clean them regularly.
(ALARM BEEPING)
- JIN: Ming? Ming!
- (SNIFFS) My porridge.
- Jin. Jin!
- (ALARM CONTINUES BEEPING)
- (JIN YELLING)
- Jin, open a window!
JIN: Somebody call emergency!
(PANTING)
(GASPS)
I'll just go to sleep,
and when I wake up...
this will all be over.
- (SIGHS)
- (BED CREAKS)
(BREATHING DEEPLY)
(GASPS)
What the...
(EXHALES)
Whoa.
(BREATHING DEEPLY)
Yes!
No!
Oh.
(EXHALES)
I'm calm.
Zen.
Yes.
Okay. No biggie.
You'll figure this out, Lee.
Just be the calm,
mature adult
you totally are.
You got this.
(BED CREAKS)
(STUDENTS CHATTERING)
I know it feels strange,
Mei-Mei,
but I promise,
nobody will notice a thing.
Thank you
for your concern, Mother.
But I'll be fine.
Well, here's your lunch.
I packed extra snacks.
And herbal tea. For cramps.
It helps relax your...
I got it. Thank you. Bye.
(SIGHS)
(CAR ENGINE STARTS)
(SCHOOL BELL RINGING)
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
GIRL: Let's go, Beavers!
Let's go!
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Hey, Mei.
(AWKWARDLY) Hey, girlfriends.
What is up?
Uh, what's with the tuque?
- Uh... Bad hair day.
- (ABBY SNIFFS)
Did you, like,
work out this morning?
I got you, girl.
- Mei, we gotta talk.
- Okay.
(WHISPERING)
Tyler's been telling everyone
- about the Daisy Mart.
- What?
He said
your mom went nuts.
And that you're
kind of a perv.
I am not a...
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
Tyler is an insecure jerkwad.
Words were exchanged.
Slightly uncomfortable secrets
were revealed.
End of story... (SLURRING)
(ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(HEART BEATING)
(HEART BEATING RAPIDLY)
- MIRIAM: Uh, Mei?
- (GASPS)
Why are you staring
at Carter Murphy-Mayhew?
I wasn't.
- (EERIE MUSIC PLAYS)
- No!
- (GASPS)
- (MIRIAM GROWLS)
Tyler keeps putting these up.
- Knock it off, butthead.
- (LAUGHING)
ABBY: Not funny, Tyler!
Devon, my precious manly man.
PRIYA: I banish you.
- Literally go away!
- PRIYA: Begone!
- (GROWLS) I'm gonna kill him!
- (HEART BEATING RAPIDLY)
ABBY: What is wrong with you?
Oh, yeah? Yeah?
You wanna do this?
MIRIAM: Leave her alone!
ABBY: You want
a piece of me, huh? Come here!
Smell you later, dorks.
Yeah, that's what I thought.
Get out of here, dude.
(CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY) Gotta go.
- Uh, see you at lunch.
- Mei?
- (CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
- (SCHOOL BELL RINGING)
(PANTING)
(SIGHS)
- (GRUNTS)
- (UNZIPS BAG)
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
What's with her?
What's with your face?
What is with you?
You're being weird.
I'm just really excited
about math.
- (DOOR OPENS)
- TEACHER: All right, guys.
The quadratic formula.
- (EXHALES)
- (STUDENTS GROAN)
Let the fun begin.
Who can tell me
how the formula begins?
X equals...
What a surprise, no one.
Okay, listen up.
X equals negative B,
plus or minus,
don't forget that plus
or minus, or I promise you,
you will live to regret it.
(OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING)
(TEACHER CONTINUES
SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
(GASPS) No. No. No.
- GUARD: Hi. Uh, ma'am?
- This isn't happening.
- Hi!
- My child goes to this school.
Why don't you come
to the front office?
- I'm sure that someone can...
- Keep your...
- (MING GRUNTS)
- Ow!
MING: I pay my taxes.
BOY: Whoa, what is that?
All right, all right,
- settle down, little goblins.
- (STUDENTS EXCLAIMING)
- MING: Stop it!
- Whoa!
Mei-Mei!
- No. Please, no.
- Mei-Mei, help!
Mei-Mei, tell him it's me!
- (HEART BEATING)
- (BREATHING HEAVILY)
Mei-Mei!
I will report you
for trespassing.
Tell him it's Mommy!
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Mei-Mei!
Tell him you forgot your pads!
(ALL EXCLAIMING)
(SCREAMS, SHRIEKING)
(ROARS IN SLOW MOTION)
(ALL GRUNTING)
(GRUNTS, PANTING)
(ALL COUGHING)
(GASPS)
(WHIMPERS)
(GRUNTS AND COUGHS)
Mei-Mei.
Come back!
- (TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
- (WHIMPERING)
- (TRUMPET PLAYING)
- (BOY GRUNTS)
(WHIMPERING)
(GASPS LOUDLY)
O-M-G!
(DOOR RATTLING)
GIRL: Hey, I gotta go!
Open up!
(WHIMPERS, GRUNTS)
(GRUNTS)
Mei-Mei! Stop!
(ENGINE STARTS)
Jin. Jin, get home now.
There's been an emergency.
JIN: (ON PHONE)
Is it the woman thing?
No! Another one.
- It's so good.
- (SCREAMS)
- (BOTH SCREAMING)
- WOMAN: Run!
- MAN: It's a monster!
- (MAN 2 GROANS)
(GRUNTS, GASPS)
(STRAINING)
(GRUNTING LOUDLY)
(GROANS)
(GAGS)
(MUZAK PLAYING ON SPEAKERS)
Awooga! (GASPS)
Huh?
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
(GASPS)
- (SCREAMS)
- (CAR HORN BLARING)
- (SCREAMS, GRUNTS)
- (CAR THUDS)
- (BRAKES SCREECH)
- (CAR HORNS HONKING)
(MEILIN WHIMPERS)
(ALL ARGUING)
(METAL THUDS)
- Uh-oh.
- (CREAKING)
(WHIMPERING)
(PEOPLE GASP)
- (PEOPLE GASP)
- (BRAKES SCREECH)
(GASPS)
Mei-Mei.
Mei-Mei. (GRUNTS)
Gotta get home! Gotta hide!
(GRUNTS)
(ALL MURMURING, EXCLAIMING)
Mei-Mei.
(PANTING)
(MEILIN GRUNTS)
(SERENE MUSIC PLAYING)
- (DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
- (GASPS)
(GASPING)
- (MUSIC STOPS)
- (GRUNTS)
- (GROANING)
- (BODY THUDS)
(WAILING)
(GATE RATTLING)
- (PANTING)
- (DOOR CREAKING)
Mei-Mei. (PANTING)
Mei-Mei!
(GASPS)
Oh!
Mei-Mei!
(PANTING)
(MEILIN SOBBING)
Mei-Mei?
Don't look at me! Stay back!
Sweetie, (HESITATES)
it's okay. Mommy is here.
What's happening to me?
(SOBBING)
What is it? What... What...
(GASPS) It's happened already?
(SOBBING STOPS)
What did you say?
Ming?
It's time.
(DOOR OPENS)
(WIND BLOWING)
(MYSTICAL MUSIC PLAYING)
(SIGHS) As you know,
our ancestor, Sun Yee,
had a mystical connection
with red pandas.
In fact,
she loved them so much
that she asked the gods
to turn her into one.
(DRAMATIC TRADITIONAL MUSIC
PLAYING)
It was wartime.
The men were all gone.
Sun Yee
was desperate for a way
to protect herself
and her daughters.
Then one night,
during a red moon,
the gods granted her wish.
They gave her the ability
to harness her emotions
to transform into a powerful,
mystical beast.
She was able
to fend off bandits,
protect her village,
and save her family from ruin.
Sun Yee passed this gift
to her daughters,
for when they came of age.
And they passed it to theirs.
But over time,
our family chose
to come to a new world.
And what was a blessing
became...
an inconvenience.
Are you serious?
- JIN: No!
- Mei-Mei, no!
- MEILIN: It's a curse!
- She meant it as a blessing.
You cursed us!
It's all your fault!
Mei-Mei, stop!
Listen to me. Listen!
There's a cure!
(PANTING)
Really? How do you know?
Because it happened to me.
Why didn't you warn me?
I thought I had more time!
You're just a child.
I thought, if I watched you
like a hawk,
I'd see the signs
and be able to prepare.
But it's going to be fine.
I overcame it
and you will too.
On the next red moon,
you'll undergo a ritual
that will seal
your red panda spirit
into one of these.
And then
you'll be cured for good.
Just like me.
But any strong emotion
will release the panda.
And the more you release it,
the more difficult
the ritual will be.
There is a darkness
to the panda, Mei-Mei.
You only have
one chance to banish it,
and you cannot fail.
Otherwise,
you'll never be free.
Let's see, the next red moon
will be the 25th.
That's a whole month away.
We'll wait it out together.
And I'll be with you
every step of the way.
(MEILIN PANTING, STRAINING)
(JIN GRUNTS)
Not bad.
I saved Wilfred.
(GASPS) Thanks, Dad.
It's only temporary, Mei-Mei.
This way, we won't worry about
any more accidents. Hmm?
Sleep tight.
Red is a lucky color.
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYING)
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
MING: This is awful.
What are we gonna do?
JIN: Don't worry.
We'll get through this.
MING: No one
can see her like this.
I never wanted this for her.
Did you see
how she was in the temple?
- (CRYING)
- Her eyes...
(SOBBING)
(CONTINUES SOBBING)
(WHIRRING)
- (MEILIN GRUNTS LOUDLY)
- (LOUD THUDDING)
(MING GRUNTS)
(SIGHS)
(MEILIN CONTINUES GRUNTING)
(GRUNTING)
(GROANS, WINCES)
Please...
(GROANS)
just...
go away.
(SCREAMS)
No!
Why? Why?
- (KNOCKING ON WINDOW)
- MIRIAM: Mei, it's us.
- Open up.
- Crud, no.
Guys, what are you doing?
Go away!
Are you okay?
Tap if you can hear us.
One for yes, two for no!
We were so worried.
We thought
you died of embarrassment.
You need more pads?
I brought extra.
Forget that.
4-Town's coming to Toronto!
- What?
- (ALL SCREAMING)
MEILIN: Hey! (SHUSHING)
It's okay, everybody be quiet!
Everybody, it's just me!
Shut up!
- It's okay, it's me!
- (MUFFLED SCREAMING)
It's Mei!
Calm down, all right?
I'm gonna let go
and you're gonna be chill.
- Got that?
- (SCREAMING STOPS)
ALL: (MUFFLED) Mmm-hmm.
Chill.
Mei?
Are you a werewolf?
No! What?
- She is a red panda!
- Sick.
You're so fluffy!
- I've always wanted a tail.
- Priya, Abby, quit it.
Mei, what the heck happened?
It's just some, you know,
inconvenient, uh,
genetic thingy
I got from my mom.
I mean...
(SIGHS) It'll go away.
Eventually.
Maybe.
(SOBBING)
Aw, Mei.
I hate this!
I'm slobby, I'm smelly.
My mom won't even look at me,
and now 4-Town?
When are they coming?
May 18th.
They just announced it.
The 18th?
There's no way
this will be gone by then.
Just go.
Go become women without me.
Mei. It's gonna be okay.
No, it's not. I'm a freak.
Just... (SIGHS)
Just leave me alone.
(SOBBING)
(BEATBOXING)
(BEATBOXING ALONG)
Mmm. Yeah.
Mmm. Let's go.
Mmm.
Yeah. Mmm.
- Let's go.
- I've never met
nobody like you
Had friends
and I've had buddies
(ALL SINGING)
It's true
But they don't turn my tummy
(ALL SINGING)
The way you do
I've never met nobody
Like you
(SNIFFLING)
(MEILIN SINGING)
You're never not on my mind?
(ALL SINGING)
Oh, my, oh, my
I'm never not by your side
Your side, your side
I'm never gonna let you cry
Oh, cry, don't cry
I'll never not be your ride
or die
All right!
- Yeah! Whoo!
- Go, Mei!
Thanks, guys.
(SNIFFLES) You're the best.
- Aw, we love you, Mei.
- You're our girl.
Yeah. No matter what.
Panda or no panda.
(MEILIN SIGHS)
- (MIRIAM GASPS)
- Whoa.
- Mei!
- You're you!
And you look amazing!
Red looks so good on you.
Is it gone?
For now.
But if I get too excited,
it'll come right back... Ow!
Abby, what the heck?
Huh?
Something feels different.
Abby, hit me.
- (GROANS)
- (BODY THUDS)
MEILIN: (WEAKLY) Ow.
Oh, my gosh!
I stayed calm.
Something about you guys,
like, neutralizes the panda.
Aw! It's our love.
We're like a warm
and fuzzy blanket.
Yeah.
This means
I can have my room back.
(GASPS) I can
have my life back!
No. Even better.
You can come with us
to 4-Town!
ABBY AND PRIYA: Yeah!
This could be our only chance
to see them together.
We're all asking
our parents tonight.
We're making our stand.
Yeah. You in or you out?
But I can't ask my mom.
I'm a furry ticking time bomb!
(IN SING-SONG VOICE)
Of awesomeness!
(IN NORMAL VOICE)
And now you can control it!
So just prove it to her,
and she's gotta let you go!
MING: Mei-Mei?
Crap! You guys better go.
- But...
- No "buts," Mir.
My mom
already doesn't like you.
Wait, she doesn't?
I'll call you, I promise.
PRIYA: We love you, Mei.
ABBY: Hang in there, girl.
Everything okay?
I thought I heard...
Mom, I think
I've made a breakthrough.
Ready.
Deforestation.
(GRUNTING SOFTLY)
Sad orangutan.
Mmm! (GRUNTING)
Your second place
spelling bee trophy.
(GRUNTING)
The important thing
is you tried.
You spelled
your little butt off.
First place in our hearts.
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
What a shame.
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(DOOR CLOSES)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC BUILDS)
- (KITTENS MEOWING)
- (GASPS)
So cute!
- (DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
- No. So fuzzy.
- (MEOWING)
(GRUNTING)
Must resist.
(ALL SIGHING)
(RELAXING MUSIC PLAYING)
We love you, girl.
Panda or no panda.
(MEILIN SIGHS WITH RELIEF)
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
(KITTENS PURRING)
How adorable.
(GASPS) Mei.
How is this possible?
What happened to your panda?
It's easy.
When I start to get emotional,
all I do is imagine the people
I love most
in the whole world.
Oh.
- Which is you guys.
- Oh.
Oh, Mei-Mei.
(KITTEN PURRS)
So, now that that's settled,
I just have one
teeny-tiny favor to ask.
No. Absolutely not.
(PANTING) What?
But this is
once in a lifetime.
Mei-Mei, it's one thing to
stay calm at home or school,
but a concert?
You'll get whipped up
into a frenzy
and panda all over the place.
I won't, I won't! I promise!
You saw me keep it in.
Ming, maybe
we should trust her.
It's them I don't trust.
Look at those
glittery delinquents
with their...
(SHUDDERS) gyrations.
Why on earth
do you want to go so badly?
- (ALL CHEERING)
- ALL: Chug! Chug! Chug!
(SHRIEKS)
(ALL CHEERING)
Like I said,
I just want to broaden
my musical horizons.
(SIGHS) This isn't music.
This is filth.
And it's not worth
jeopardizing your life over.
- Right, Jin?
- Uh...
See? Your father agrees.
No concert. And that's final.
(INHALES SHARPLY)
Okay, well, thanks
for listening. Good night.
(GRUNTING)
(SCOFFS)
- (DOOR SLAMS)
- (SCOFFS)
What was that?
Am I the only one
who sees the danger here?
There's no way
she could keep her panda in.
And $200? For what?
Who do they think they are?
Celine Dion?
(PHONE RINGING)
Hmm. Unbelievable.
I saw that look.
Where did she get that from?
Treating her own mother
like that.
Hold on.
Ming, it's your mother.
I'm not here!
Mother. Hello.
(ON PHONE)
How's everything in Florida?
GRANDMA: Ming.
I know about Mei-Mei.
MING: I was just about
to call you,
but everything's fine.
(HESITATES) I'm gonna handle
the ritual on my own.
(SCOFFS) The way you "handled"
Mei-Mei being on the news?
No one knows anything.
They barely saw her.
GRANDMA: I'm on my way.
With reinforcements.
- No! I can handle it. I can...
- (PHONE DISCONNECTS)
(WHIMPERS)
- (WHISTLE BLOWS)
- GIRL: Run!
Eyes on the balls, guys!
- Be water! Be...
- (BOY GRUNTS)
(GRUNTS) That presentation
was bomb-dot-com.
I cited all my sources.
I had sparklers. (GRUNTS)
And she still said no!
My parents said
I could go when I'm 30.
Mine called it stripper music.
What's wrong with that?
(GROWLS)
Mine said yes,
but I have to buy the ticket.
Who the heck's
got that kind of cash? (YELPS)
I know my mom's worried,
but sometimes she's just so...
- (SIGHS) So...
- Wacko?
GUARD: (PANTING)
Ma'am! Please!
- (CAR ENGINE STARTS)
- I'm sorry, Mrs. Lee!
- I see you!
- (LAUGHING)
- (BOYS SNICKERING)
- Little momma's girl. (LAUGHS)
No wonder Mei is such a loser.
(LAUGHTER)
- (BALL SQUELCHING)
- (HEART BEATING RAPIDLY)
(GROWLING)
- (GRUNTS)
- (LAUGHING, SCREAMS)
- (STUDENTS GASP)
- (WHISTLE BLOWS)
Illegal throw!
You're out, Lee.
What? But, Mr. K, he...
MIRIAM: Mei, chill.
Let's go, let's go.
Calm down, Mei.
(MEILIN GRUNTS, PANTS)
Dude, keep it together.
I can't. We need
to see this concert.
Why doesn't my mom get that?
I never ask for anything.
My whole life
I've been her perfect
little Mei-Mei.
Temple duties, grades...
- Violin!
- Tap dancing.
Yeah. We've been so good.
If they don't trust us anyway,
then what's the point?
Wow! Who are you?
- I love it!
- Fight the power!
Yeah. Yeah.
This isn't just
our first concert.
This is our first step
into womanhood.
And we have to do it together.
I'm in, girl. We'll say
it's a sleepover at my house.
(GASPS) The perfect crime.
Yes! My mom will never know.
Now we just got to
raise the money for tickets.
(SIGHS) Come on, girls, think!
(ALL GRUNTING)
Know what'll help me think?
- A little panda.
- Abby...
Come on, Mei.
It'll clear my mind.
Just a little hit!
It's so cute!
Ugh. Fine.
(INHALES DEEPLY)
(DREAMY MUSIC PLAYING)
Mon amour.
(SQUEALING)
Happy?
Oh, yeah. That's the stuff.
GIRL: O-M-G.
Aah! Go away!
That was you in the bathroom!
I didn't imagine it!
- Yeah, you did.
- Get lost, Stacy.
But she's like a magical bear?
ALL: Red panda!
You are the cutest thing ever!
GIRL: Come out, please?
GIRL 2: Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Please!
Wait. So, you like the panda?
Like it? I love it!
I'll give you anything! Money?
- My kidney!
- My soul.
GIRL: Yeah!
STACY: Adorable!
- You're so cute!
- (GIRLS SQUEALING)
(U KNOW WHAT'S UP BY 4-TOWN
PLAYING)
Is it on?
- (CHUCKLES) Let's go!
- MIRIAM: Yeah, panda!
- Fuel for domination.
- Money, money, money!
Stop hogging
and give me some!
MIRIAM: Pass that over.
- 4-Town, here we come!
- (ABBY GROANS)
PRIYA: Stop! That's so gross.
Do it again.
All right, troops, listen up.
Operation 4-Town Shake Down
is about to commence.
The boys are coming
to the SkyDome May 18th.
Our goal, four tickets.
That's 800 bucks!
Step one,
neutralize the empress.
Mathletes?
Isn't it a little dangerous
to join an after-school
club now?
What's dangerous
is an academic record
with a lack
of extracurriculars.
Hmm... Huh.
Step two... Spread the word.
(U KNOW WHAT'S UP
CONTINUES PLAYING)
(CELL PHONES RINGING)
And step three...
hustle this panda
and squeeze
every last loonie
outta those kids.
(GIRLS SQUEALING)
(U KNOW WHAT'S UP
CONTINUES PLAYING)
And, baby, I did it on my own
Did it on my own
Own
Did it on my own, yeah
You know what's up
You know it's us, yeah
You ready?
Here we go
- You want it?
- I want it
Louder
- You want it?
- I want it
Give me one, two, three, four
You wanted it, you went for it
And, baby, you got it
I wanted it, I went for it
And, baby, I did it on my own
Did it on my own
Own
(EXCLAIMING SMUGLY)
- Let's go.
- MIRIAM: Yeah!
(PRIYA EXCLAIMING)
(ALL VOCALIZING)
Did it on my...
(MEILIN GASPS)
- Oh, no, it's falling!
- MIRIAM: Grab it!
(GIRLS LAUGHING)
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
- (WHISTLE BLOWS)
- (INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(BEATBOXING)
BOY: Yeah, dude, let's go!
Push it, dude! Come on!
BOY 2: Come on, new guy,
just keep on going!
(BOYS PANTING)
Come on, guys, keep going.
(RATTLING)
Check out Number 12.
He's got delts for days.
Forget that. I need lunch.
I'm starting to black out!
I think I'm getting
carpal tunnel.
No pain, no gain, Priya.
Come on, chop-chop!
Five, 10...
Girl, relax.
Yeah. We're doing our best.
It's not enough!
The concert's this Saturday
and we're still
a hundred short!
(GROWLS) I knew
we should have charged
more for photos!
Stupid, stupid, stupid!
Mei, breathe. It's in the bag.
- But...
- (TUTTING)
What's the point
of getting to the concert
if you're too exhausted
to enjoy it?
Now, take a break and help me
appreciate some boys.
(CHUCKLES) Okay, okay, okay.
(BOTH SIGH HEAVILY)
BOY: Hey, what's up?
BOY 2: Mei!
BOY 3: Hey, Mei, what up?
(PRIYA AND MIRIAM WHOOPING)
- Looking good!
- Nice calves!
Are you a triangle?
'Cause you acute!
(ALL GIGGLE)
TYLER: You guys are so weird.
- Hey!
- Are you spying on us?
I wanna talk to you, Lee.
- Forget it.
- Fine.
Wonder if your mom knows
her precious little Mei-Mei
has been flaunting the panda
all over school.
(GIRLS GASPING)
- (MEILIN PANTING)
- (POOFS)
- That's none of your business!
- (SHRIEKS)
One more step and
I'm telling her everything.
Now, put that thing away
and hear me out.
(GROWLS IN FRUSTRATION)
What do you want?
I wanna throw a sick
birthday party. An epic one.
It's this Friday.
If you're there,
everyone will come.
Simple as that.
A party?
(SIGHS)
Look, I've done you a favor
keeping my mouth shut.
All I'm asking for
is one back.
Hmm.
I'll do it.
But it'll cost you one...
No. Two hundred bucks.
Okay.
Uh, hold, please.
Are you serious?
You can't trust him.
It's a trap!
This sounds like
a boy-girl party.
Are we allowed
to boy-girl parties?
Guys! Two hundred bucks
will put us over the top!
We have to do this.
We'll meet at Tyler's,
I'll do my thing,
and then we'll bounce.
Easy-peasy.
Dude, what about your mom?
Forget my mom.
I'll be back before
she even knows I'm gone.
- But...
- Hey, dorkbag.
We're in. But you only
get the panda for an hour.
And we are not
bringing any presents.
Deal.
(DOOR OPENS)
(UTENSILS CLANKING)
Okay, I'm heading off
to mathletes. See you later!
Wait, what about dinner?
I made all your favorites.
(GASPS SOFTLY)
Thanks,
but Miriam's dad is, uh,
ordering pizza.
Save me leftovers?
- What if I come with you?
- Wha...
What are you doing?
Linear equations? Geometry?
I have a double-jointed elbow!
Look! I can make
a perfect circle!
Wow! Yeah, but it'll be
super boring.
Wouldn't you
rather hang with Dad?
Oh.
Let's get my flashcards.
- But...
- JIN: Hmm.
I was mathletes champ
- in grade 8, you know?
- Uh-huh.
They called me
the "Uncommon Denominator."
Cool. Oh, uh,
Jade Palace is on tonight.
- Can't miss that, right?
- Now, who's the weak link?
Priya and Abby
seem bright enough, but...
Oh, and traffic's a nightmare.
I can just
take the streetcar...
- you stay and rest.
- (INHALES) Miriam...
I mean, she's a nice girl,
but maybe
she's slowing you down.
Oh, Mom, you really
don't have to come.
Don't be silly.
We're already on the way.
(BREATHING NERVOUSLY)
But I don't want you to!
(GASPS)
- (HESITATING)
- (LOCK RATTLING)
WOMAN: Chop-chop, everyone.
Don't dawdle.
- Hurry up.
- (WOMEN CHATTERING)
(CATS YOWLING)
(EXPLOSION)
(UPBEAT TRADITIONAL MUSIC
PLAYING)
BOTH: Oh! What...
WOMAN: Hey, cuz! Surprise!
Aunties?
What are you doing here?
The ritual, silly.
- She's lost weight.
- No, no, she gained weight.
- She looks like her mother.
- She looks like her father.
GRANDMA: Ladies.
Mother.
Hey, Grandma.
GRANDMA: Poor dear.
It must be so difficult
keeping that
unruly beast at bay.
Your family is here now,
Mei-Mei.
And we will take care
of everything.
(CHA CHA SLIDE
BY DJ CASPER PLAYING)
Everybody clap your hands
Clap, clap, clap,
clap your hands
(COUGHS)
All right, now, we gonna do
the basic step...
(GROANS) Where is she?
(CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
Who's up for some Boggle?
AUNT 1: Eat. You need
your strength for the ritual.
- (AUNTIES FUSSING)
- (MUFFLED) Thank you, aunties.
Your hair is so thick,
like a pelt.
MING: What a surprise
that you all came so early.
You need all the help
you can get, Ming.
So, Mei-Mei,
you've been managing
to keep the panda in?
- Yep. Totally.
- (SCOFFS) Really?
What's that, Lily?
Well, it's a little hard
to believe
that Mei-Mei
could control such a beast.
She's just a child.
It's true.
And if Mei-Mei's panda
- is anything like Ming's...
- (ALL GROAN AND SHUDDER)
Mei-Mei's better
than any of us
at controlling the panda.
She passed every trigger test.
Even the kitten box.
AUNTIES: Oh!
LILY: Oh, my goodness!
- That's unbelievable.
- Impressive.
She just thinks
of my love for her,
and it gives her the strength
to stay calm.
Exactly.
- AUNTIES: Aw.
- How sweet.
- (YAWNING)
Anyway,
thanks for all the gifts,
but I think I'll go
to bed early. (CHUCKLES)
Keeping that animal
locked down
sure takes a lot of energy.
Okay, sweetie. Get some rest.
Night, everyone.
- AUNTIES: Good night, Mei-Mei.
- Sleep well.
LILY: Get some beauty rest.
AUNT: Get some rest.
(AUNTIES CHATTERING)
(GRUNTING)
Oh!
- (GRUNTS)
- (GLASS SHATTERS)
- (KNOCKING AT DOOR)
- (DOOR OPENS)
Mei-Mei, can I have a word
with you?
Uh, sure. What's up?
(MYSTERIOUS MUSIC PLAYING)
I found this.
Strange for a girl
who hasn't let her panda out.
It's, uh... (CHUCKLES)
It's not mine.
Mei-Mei,
I know what you're doing.
I know how hard it is
to keep the beast in.
It feels so good
to let it out. So free.
But each time you do,
the stronger it gets.
And then you'll be
bound to it forever,
and the ritual will fail.
Has that ever happened?
It cannot happen.
(SIGHS)
Your mother and I
were close once,
but the red panda
took that away.
I couldn't bear to see
that happen to you.
So, no more panda.
You are your mother's
whole world, Mei-Mei.
I know you'll do what's right.
Uh-uh. Mmm. Mmm!
- Uh, worm.
- Uh... Octopus!
- Spaghetti?
- Killer robot!
Mortality.
Hmm. Nice.
- (ALL GROANING)
- This sucks.
- Let's bail.
- Just wait. She'll be here.
- I knew she'd flake.
- (DOORBELL CHIMING)
- BOY: Panda girl!
- (ALL GASP)
GIRL: It's Mei!
PRIYA: Thank Cthulhu.
- (ALL CHATTERING EXCITEDLY)
- Ugh. About time.
(PANTING)
Yo! What up, peeps? (LAUGHS)
What are you wearing?
Hey, Tyler. Happy birthday.
I'm paying for the red panda,
not this garbage! Deal's off!
Wait! Can garbage do this?
(GRUNTING) Uh-huh.
Or this? Stir the porridge.
Come on, guys!
Stir the porridge. (GRUNTS)
Are you feeling okay?
(SIGHS) Guys, it's hard
to explain, but just, hmm...
Just trust me on this.
I can't panda anymore.
I'm sorry.
Okay, okay, okay. It's fine.
You don't have to do it.
We'll just, uh,
figure something...
I won't go.
What? Priya, you can't not go.
Jesse's your soul mate.
But we only have enough
- for three tickets.
- Then I'll stay home.
Abby, no! I'll stay home.
Guys, if we can't all go,
then none of us should go.
Right?
(MIRIAM SIGHS)
(SENTIMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING)
(ALL SNIFFLING)
(GROWLS)
Just one last time.
Hey, Tyler!
You want the panda?
You're getting the panda.
Let's hear it
for the birthday boy!
(ALL CHEERING)
ALL: Yes!
(BOOTYLICIOUS
BY DESTINY'S CHILD PLAYING)
ALL: (CHANTING)
Go, Tyler! Go, Tyler!
- Go, go, go, Tyler!
- Yeah!
MIRIAM: Okay!
(ALL EXCLAIMING)
Yeah! Get it, girl!
Yeah! Oh, yeah!
- Oh, yeah!
- (ABBY SHOUTING)
(ALL CHEERING)
Faster! Faster! Whoo!
- Yeah!
- ALL: Yeah!
ALL: Yeah!
You sure
the hotel's all right?
It'll do.
At least breakfast is free.
Get some rest. You look tired.
HELEN: Good night, cuz.
Try that tea.
- LILY: Good night, Ming.
- Good night.
Ming, this is a critical time.
Mei-Mei needs a strong hand,
now more than ever.
Don't let her
out of your sight.
I won't, Mother.
(EXHALES)
- Hmm. Oh.
- (WIND BLOWING)
- (GLASS PIECE SHATTERS)
- Oh.
Oh, no.
(GASPS) "Fur baby"?
Oh!
What?
(GASPS)
(GASPING)
What...
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
Mei-Mei. What is all...
- (GASPS)
- (CHOMPS LOUDLY)
(1 TRUE LOVE BY 4-TOWN
PLAYING ON STEREO)
Yeah! We did it!
We are seeing 4-Town!
ALL: Whoo!
PRIYA: Yes.
(ALL CHOMPING LOUDLY)
TYLER: Hey,
has anyone seen Mei?
- (KIDS CHATTERING)
- (TYLER GROANS)
Dang. He is working you.
(GROWLS) What a diva!
It'll all be worth it.
(SIGHS)
Tomorrow, we are walking
into that concert girls
and coming out women.
(GASPS) Literally goosebumps.
Hmm. What do you think
Jesse smells like?
(INHALES DEEPLY)
Milk chocolate and wet rocks.
- Wow!
- (ABBY GRUNTING)
- So manly.
- (DEVICE BEEPING)
Oh, yes!
It's happening,
Robaire Junior!
You're finally gonna
meet your daddy!
And your hot uncles!
(LAUGHTER)
What? It's true.
(ALL SIGH)
Mei, what if you
didn't do the ritual?
What if you kept the panda?
- What?
- Look at you!
You're not the same
feather-dustin',
straight-A, goody-goody...
Who we never saw, like, ever.
- Yeah.
- You're such a rebel now.
Guys, I can't be
like this forever.
My whole family would freak.
Especially my mom.
All her hopes and dreams
are pinned on me.
I know.
But you've really changed
and I'm proud of you.
Just don't get rid
of all of it, you know?
Yeah. If it weren't for you,
none of this
would be happening.
- You the bomb!
- Word. You da bomb, Mei.
No, you da bomb.
We all da bomb!
- Yes. Yes. Yes!
- (LAUGHTER)
MEILIN: We da bomb!
PRIYA: 4-Town, here we come!
MEILIN: Robaire, I love you!
We're coming for you!
We are women!
MIRIAM: We are women!
PRIYA: We are hot!
(ALL ULULATING)
DJ: (ON RADIO) All right,
homies, next up is 4-Town.
The boys are coming
to Toronto on the 25th!
So get your tickets now.
And check it, they'll be
cranking open the SkyDome
and performing under
a red lunar eclipse.
It's gonna be galactic,
for sure.
Abby...
you said the concert
was the 18th.
It is! He's wrong!
Look! The 18th, Toronto!
Uh...
This says Toledo.
What?
(SPEAKING KOREAN)
Toledo?
(CONTINUES SPEAKING KOREAN)
(IN ENGLISH)
What the heck is Toledo?
- Oh, no.
- What?
4-Town's the same night
as the ritual?
No!
The same night?
The same night? What?
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
- Mei, chill.
- It's okay.
No, it isn't! (PANTING)
I can't miss 4-Town!
We worked so hard!
But the ritual.
I'll let everyone down!
- No, no, no!
- TYLER: Hey, Panda Girl.
(GROWLS)
What are you doing?
We want more rides.
Buzz off, jerkface. I'm busy.
Oh, snap!
You gonna take that, Tyler?
You want your money?
Then get your butt
down here now!
Forget your money,
and forget you!
Mei! Let's just go.
- (GROWLS)
- What about our deal?
Shove your deal!
Fine! Get out of here!
Go back to your psycho mom
and your creepy temple,
you freak!
- (GROWLS AND YELLS)
- MIRIAM: Mei, no!
- (TYLER GRUNTS)
- Take it back!
Don't talk about my family
like that!
- You're hurting him!
- Mei!
- MING: Mei-Mei, stop!
- I hate you! I hate...
What is going on here?
(TYLER SOBBING)
I'm sorry.
Just get off of me. Please.
(KIDS GASPING)
TYLER'S MOM:
I cannot believe
you would
let your daughter do this!
TYLER'S DAD: Do you understand
what she did to my boy?
I am so sorry.
She's never done
anything like this before.
I don't know
what came over her.
I don't want to hear
your apologies, okay?
- I'm sorry again.
- She is an animal!
All right, party's over!
Everyone, go home!
(INDISTINCT MURMURING)
I can't believe you girls
would use her like this!
- What?
- But we didn't.
No, we'd never.
- What?
- I knew you were trouble.
Putting all these thoughts
into Mei-Mei's head,
parading her around.
Now she's lying, sneaking out.
She attacked
a defenseless boy.
You think this is a joke?
Do you know
how dangerous this is?
We didn't mean to,
we just wanted to see 4-Town.
4-Town! You manipulated her
for a bunch
of tacky delinquents?
- No! She wanted to...
- Don't you blame her.
She is a good girl,
and you've taken
advantage of her.
Mei, tell her.
- What? (SIGHS)
- Dude!
Come on, Mei-Mei.
Let's go.
(PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING)
(CAR ENGINE STARTS)
GUARD: Will call that way.
(CROWD CHATTERING)
All righty,
general admission, eh?
How many tickets?
(MIRIAM SIGHS)
Three, please.
(AUNTIES CHATTERING
INDISTINCTLY)
What is that?
Um, I think it's coming
from the SkyDome, Mother.
(SCOFFS)
Four is the worst number.
You know,
Vivian was due on the fourth,
but I held her
in until the fifth...
Quiet, Lily.
Hurry up, everyone.
It's almost time
to start the ritual.
Nervous, Mei-Mei?
- A little.
- Oh, well,
I've got 50 years' experience
as a shaman. (CHUCKLES)
This will be a piece of cake.
And mostly painless.
(SIGHS) Thanks, Mr. Gao.
Wait, "mostly"?
(GRANDMA CLEARS THROAT)
Long ago, the spirits
blessed the women
of our family
with a great challenge.
Mei-Mei, tonight is your turn.
Like all the women
around this table,
you too will banish
the beast within
and finally become
your true self.
May Sun Yee guide you
and keep you safe.
PING: Hear, hear!
CHEN: That's right.
Don't blow it.
Uh... It's almost time.
(CHUCKLES)
The red moon
is about to begin.
Mei-Mei, go get ready.
Yes, Mother.
MR. GAO:
Oh, where are the instruments?
HELEN: It's so amazing!
(ALL CHATTERING)
- Hmm. Huh?
- Jin!
- Help clear the table!
- Uh-huh.
Uh...
(GRUNTS) Oh!
MIRIAM: (ON VIDEO) Is it on?
(GIRLS CHUCKLING)
4-Town, here we come!
- (ABBY GROANS)
- JIN: Huh.
ABBY: That's so gross.
Hmm.
(GIRLS VOCALIZING)
(GIRLS SINGING)
Did it on my own
(CHUCKLES)
(PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING)
I hate you!
(GASPS)
(PANTING)
- (WHIMPERS)
- (KNOCKING AT DOOR)
Come in.
Hey, Dad.
I... I'm almost ready.
Did you make this?
(GIRLS LAUGHING)
Here, I'll erase it.
(GRUNTS)
What? We were
just being stupid.
The panda's dangerous,
outta control.
Huh. You sound
like your mother.
What has she told you
about her panda?
(SIGHS) Nothing.
She won't talk about it.
It was quite destructive.
(CHUCKLES) And big.
She almost took out
half the temple.
You... You saw it?
Only once.
She and your grandma
had a terrible fight.
Over what?
Your grandma
didn't approve of me.
But you should've seen
your mom.
She was incredible.
But I'm a monster.
(JIN SIGHS)
People have all kinds
of sides to them, Mei.
And some sides are messy.
The point isn't to push
the bad stuff away,
it's to make room for it,
live with it.
Mei, erase it if you want,
but this side of you...
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
made me laugh.
- MIRIAM: Dude, you're crazy!
- (GIRLS LAUGHING ON VIDEO)
MIRIAM: Come here!
MING: Mei-Mei.
It's time.
(MYSTICAL MUSIC PLAYING)
Just follow my directions
and breathe.
Now don't move
from the circle.
You understand?
For as long
as the red moon shines,
the astral realm will be open.
And this circle is the door.
(BOWL CLANGING)
(ALL CHANTING IN CANTONESE)
(IN ENGLISH)
What are they saying?
The door will open only if we
sing from our hearts.
It doesn't matter what.
I like Tony Bennett,
but your grandma, uh,
she's from old school.
Now, focus on their voices.
Let them guide you. (ECHOES)
(CHANTING CONTINUES)
Oh, Sun Yee, revered ancestor,
hear us now.
(CHANTING CONTINUES)
MR. GAO: Guide this girl
through her inner storm.
(MYSTERIOUS MUSIC PLAYING)
Louder! Louder!
(CHANTING CONTINUES)
And return
the red panda spirit
from where it came!
(AUNTIES CONTINUE CHANTING)
(MUSIC STOPS)
- (WIND BLOWING)
- (GASPS)
(ETHEREAL MUSIC PLAYING)
Sun Yee.
(GASPS)
(PORTAL HUMMING)
(GRUNTING)
(PORTAL BUZZING)
(SCREAMING)
(ALL CONTINUE CHANTING)
(GRUNTING)
(SCREAMING)
(GRUNTS)
(STRAINING)
(SCREAMS)
You can do it. Keep going!
(STRAINING)
(WHIMPERS)
(SENTIMENTAL TRADITIONAL MUSIC
PLAYING)
No!
(EXPLOSION)
- (GASPS)
- (ALL COUGHING)
(SIGHS HAPPILY)
GRANDMA: What happened?
- What was that?
- Mei-Mei...
- (BOTH COUGHING)
- HELEN: Is everyone okay?
LILY: Oh, my goodness,
I can't...
Mei-Mei.
It's okay. We can do it again.
Mei-Mei?
I'm keeping it.
- GRANDMA: What did she say?
- Keeping it?
I'm keeping it!
- LILY: Oh, no!
- Mei-Mei!
Stop her!
- What are you doing?
- Stop, Mei-Mei!
HELEN: Don't let her go!
MING: No!
- (STRAINS) Let go!
- What has come over you?
GRANDMA: Stop!
Get a hold of her!
- Mei-Mei! Stop!
- LILY: Don't do this!
- (ALL STRAINING)
- MING: Mei-Mei!
- No!
- (GRUNTS)
I'm going to the concert!
- Get back here! (GRUNTS)
- Mei-Mei! Stop!
- HELEN: A concert?
- No!
- (ALL CHATTERING)
- (BREATHING HEAVILY)
- (HEART BEATING LOUDLY)
- This is a disaster.
Unbelievable. Ming!
Too good to be true.
How could you let this happen?
- She's out of control!
- (BREATHING HEAVILY)
Ming, it's okay.
GRANDMA: Ming! Ming!
Answer me!
What are we going to do
about this?
How could she?
- (MING GROWLING)
- (HEART BEATING RAPIDLY)
How could she do this to...
her own mother? (ECHOES)
(MING GRUNTS)
(ROARS)
- Ming?
- (GASPS, SPEAKS CANTONESE)
Mei-Mei!
(EXPLOSION)
(PEOPLE SPEAKING IN CANTONESE)
Excuse me!
- (PEOPLE GASPING)
- (CAR HORNS HONKING)
(LIVELY MUSIC PLAYING)
(PANTING, GRUNTING)
(CHUCKLES)
(YELLING)
(CROWD CHEERING)
ABBY: Whoo! Yeah!
(ABBY CHEERING IN KOREAN)
4-Town!
(GIRLS EXCLAIMING
AND COUGHING)
- Mei!
- You're here!
- What are you doing here?
(PANTING)
I couldn't do it.
The panda's a part of me,
and you guys are too.
Mei, you threw us
under the bus.
I know and I'm sorry.
I've been, like, obsessed
with my mom's approval
my whole life.
I couldn't take losing it,
but losing you guys
feels even worse.
Well, too bad.
'Cause you did.
- (TOY BEEPING)
- (MIRIAM GROANS)
Robaire Junior?
She's been
taking care of him 24/7.
No.
And singing him lullabies
every night!
No, no, no, I haven't.
- (MUFFLED GRUNTING)
- They're lying.
- (TOY BEEPING)
- (SIGHS) Here.
Found him at Tyler's.
(BEEPING)
4-Town forever?
(SIGHS) 4-Town forever.
- 4-Town forever.
- 4-Town forever!
- Tyler?
- (GASPS)
No! Tyler? Who's Tyler?
I don't know a...
You are a 4-Townie?
- (ALL CHEERING)
- No! Stop!
- MIRIAM: No way!
- Yeah!
PRIYA:
Welcome to the sisterhood!
TYLER: Whatever, dorks.
(CHUCKLES AWKWARDLY)
Cut it out!
Your mom
must have gone nuclear.
Who cares?
What's she gonna do?
Ground me?
(LAUGHTER)
(FOOTSTEPS THUDDING)
CROWD: (CHANTING)
4-Town! 4-Town! 4-Town!
4-Town! 4-Town!
(CHANTING CONTINUES)
Let's go!
Is it starting? It's starting!
- (ALL SQUEALING)
- Guys, hold me.
CROWD: Four, three, two, one!
ANNOUNCER: Are you ready?
(POP MUSIC PLAYING)
Oh, my gosh!
TYLER: Yeah! Z!
I love you, man!
Yeah! Yeah!
(EXCLAIMS)
(KISSES)
Yes! Jesse!
Toronto! Who knows what's up?
(CROWD CHEERING)
(ALL GASP)
Yes! (SOBBING)
(POP MUSIC CONTINUES)
(SINGING) You want it?
(SINGING) I want it
- You want it?
- I want it
Give me one, two, three, four
You wanted it
You went for it
And, baby, you got it
(ALL SOBBING, GASPING)
I wanted it
I went for it
(ALL SCREAMING)
And, baby, I did it on my own
Did it on my own
Own
- (GASPING)
- MING: Mei-Mei!
- (GASPS)
- (MIC FEEDBACK)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(ALL SCREAMING)
No way!
BOY: Is this part of the show?
GIRL: Is this special effects?
- (4-TOWN WHIMPERING)
- Help! Help!
(ANGRILY) Mei-Mei!
Where are you?
Mom?
Mei-Mei!
(SCREAMS)
(MING GRUNTS)
(4-TOWN SCREAMING)
- I want a refund.
- What's her problem?
ALL: Mei!
(GRUNTS)
BOY: It was just getting good!
GIRL: This isn't cool.
- JIN: Mei! Mei!
- Dad?
We have to save your mother!
She's gone loco!
Mei, we have to do
the ritual again.
What happened? She's huge!
I told you she was big!
That big?
- Mei-Mei!
- (MEILIN GASPS)
HELEN: Ming!
She's your daughter!
Mei!
- Let her go!
- Don't hurt her!
You are in big trouble,
young lady!
Mom! Let go!
I'm shutting this down,
right now!
(4-TOWN YELPING)
Everyone, go home!
Where are your parents?
Put some clothes on!
This isn't you!
This is me!
(ROARS)
(SCREAMING)
- GRANDMA: Mei-Mei!
- Mei! Are you hurt?
(MEILIN PANTING)
I'm not your little
Mei-Mei anymore!
I lied, Mom!
What?
It was my idea
to hustle the panda.
My idea
to go to Tyler's party!
It was all me!
I like boys!
I like loud music!
I like gyrating!
I'm 13! Deal with it!
(PANTING)
(GROWLS)
(ROARING)
The ritual.
Everyone in position.
Mei-Mei, keep her busy.
Oh, I'll keep her busy.
Where's Jin? Jin!
(PANTING) Mei!
Keep her in the circle!
Get back here!
MEILIN: Make me!
MING: You think
you're so mature!
Lying to me!
Blaming me!
How could you be so, so...
crass?
(CHUCKLES SMUGLY) Oh!
That's nothing!
You wanna see crass?
- (GRUNTING)
- (HIP-HOP MUSIC PLAYING)
- What are you doing?
- You like that? Yes!
- Stop moving like that!
- What's wrong?
- Is this bothering you?
- Stop it!
Yeah, Mei!
Destroy her
with your big butt!
ALL: Yeah! Go, go, go!
Start singing now!
Ladies!
(ALL CHANTING IN CANTONESE)
- (MEILIN GRUNTING)
- MING: Stop!
(BUZZING)
Sing louder!
CHEN: We're trying.
- MING: Stop it!
- Let's get out of here!
(GASPS) Come on!
- Huh? Take it, Mom! Take it!
- No!
(GRUNTING)
Stop it! Stop!
(YELLS)
(GRUNTS)
All I wanted...
- (SNARLS)
- ...was to go to a concert!
I never went to concerts!
I put my family first!
I tried to be a good daughter!
(GROWLS)
Well, sorry I'm not perfect!
Sorry I'm not good enough!
And sorry
I'll never be like you!
- (GRUNTS)
- (MING GROANS)
(YELLS)
(GRUNTS AND GROANS)
(MING GROANING)
MEILIN: (GASPS) Oh, no!
Mom... Mom!
(COUGHING, GASPS)
(AUNTIES GROANING
AND COUGHING)
- (GASPS)
- No!
(PANTING) Mom!
You have to get in the circle!
(STRAINING)
Wake up!
I'm sorry!
Mom? Come on.
Please!
- (MEILIN STRAINING)
- (MING BREATHING HEAVILY)
(INHALES DEEPLY)
Sun Yee, give me strength.
- (GRUNTS)
- (ALL GASP)
(GRUNTS)
- Pull, Mei-Mei!
- (GASPS) Grandma?
I am not losing my daughter.
Don't just stand there!
(AUNTIES GRUNT)
(AUNTIES GRUNTING)
(TRINKETS CLINKING)
(ALL GROWLING)
CHEN: Make room
for your elders, Mei-Mei!
- What?
- PING: We're with you!
But what are you doing?
What if you can't turn back?
HELEN: Your mom needs us!
LILY: She's family!
Less talking, more pulling!
- This fur is so itchy!
- Quiet, Lily!
(GRUNTING)
(ALL STRAINING)
(ALL CHANTING IN CANTONESE)
(IN ENGLISH) Louder!
Sing from the heart!
Louder!
The circle isn't working!
(ALL CONTINUE CHANTING LOUDLY)
(BEATBOXING)
(ALL BEATBOXING)
(4-TOWN SINGING
U KNOW WHAT'S UP)
- Never met nobody
- Nobody
(GASPS LOUDLY)
Never met, never met,
never met
Like
You
(AUNTIES CHANTING
IN CANTONESE)
(4-TOWN SINGING IN ENGLISH)
(POP MUSIC PLAYING)
Get up
I never met nobody
(ALL SINGING ALONG)
Like you
(AUNTIES CONTINUE CHANTING)
(SINGING) Had friends
and I've had buddies
- (ALL GASPING AND CHEERING)
- It's true
But they don't turn my tummy
The way you do
I've never met nobody like you
You're never not on my mind
Oh, my, oh, my
I'm never not by your side
Your side, your side
I'm never gonna let you cry
Oh, cry, don't cry
I'll never not be
your ride or die
All right!
(GASP ECHOES)
(PANTS) Huh?
Mom? Mom!
- (SOBBING IN DISTANCE)
- (GASPS)
(PANTING)
(SOBBING)
Mom? Are you okay?
We have to...
(GASPS) Mom?
I'm sorry. It's all my fault.
(SOBBING)
What happened?
I... I hurt her.
Who?
My mom!
I got so angry,
and I lost control.
I'm just so sick
of being perfect!
I'm never gonna be
good enough for her.
Or anyone.
(CONTINUES SOBBING)
I know it feels that way.
Like, all the time.
But... it isn't true.
Come on.
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYING)
(SNIFFLES)
Really? I could explode
at any moment.
- We have to find them.
- Where are they?
- Finally.
- PING: Hurry, hurry!
LILY: Where have you been?
Come on!
- Let's get the lead out!
- GRANDMA: Ladies.
(GRANDMA SIGHS)
(SIGHS)
- I'm sorry.
- GRANDMA: Shh!
You don't have to apologize.
I'm your mother.
(SIGHS)
May Sun Yee guide you
and keep you safe.
One at a time, ladies.
And quickly.
CHEN: That's it?
Mei-Mei's keeping the panda?
It's her life. Now move.
(MYSTICAL MUSIC PLAYING)
(MEILIN GASPS)
Go ahead. It's okay.
(SOFT TRADITIONAL MUSIC
PLAYING)
No.
Mei-Mei, please.
Just come with me.
I'm changing, Mom.
I'm finally figuring out
who I am.
But... (GASPS SOFTLY)
I'm scared it'll take me away
from you.
Me too.
I see you, Mei-Mei.
You try to make
everyone happy,
but are so hard on yourself.
And if I taught you that...
I'm sorry.
So, don't hold back.
For anyone.
The farther you go,
the prouder I'll be.
(ETHEREAL MUSIC PLAYING)
I'm not going
to regret this, am I?
I'm Meilin Lee,
and ever since I turned 13,
life's been a lot.
People still talk about
Pandapocalypse 2002.
Mom and I just call it...
growing pains.
(TOY BEEPING)
(SIGHS) This thing's hungry
all the time.
Eat up, little one.
Oh, you're so hungry.
- Munch, munch, munch.
- What?
Mr. Gao had to put
her panda in something.
You should see Grandma's.
- (LAUGHS)
- Hmph! So unlucky.
(BOTH BREATHING DEEPLY)
You ready?
Let's do this.
- Hello! Welcome to our temple!
- What up, Toronto!
- Get in here!
- Yes, come on in.
And things at the temple
have never been better.
O-M-G! That looks so cute!
Our temple
is the oldest in Toronto.
And the only one that's home
to the great red panda.
Say "bamboo leaves!"
TOURISTS: Bamboo leaves!
MIRIAM: Mei!
- Hey!
- Guys!
- PRIYA: What's up?
- Bring it in!
- (ALL ULULATING)
- Ready to get your karaoke on?
Totally.
Bye, Mom! Bye, Dad!
Hold on. You're not
going out like that, are you?
(SCOFFS) My panda,
my choice, Mom.
(CHUCKLES) I'll be back
before dinner, okay?
(SIGHS) Fine. Oh, um...
You're welcome to join us.
(GASPS) For Mr. Lee's cooking?
- Uh, yeah!
- We're so there.
Don't load up on junk.
Thanks for covering
for me, Dad.
Have fun!
ABBY: And I'll beatbox.
And I can bleach my hair, too.
- (GIGGLES)
- MEILIN: And, yeah...
sometimes I miss
how things were,
but nothing stays
the same forever.
O-M-G! I'm so excited
for the new album.
- We've all got an inner beast.
- (MING SPEAKS INDISTINCTLY)
MEILIN: We've all got
a messy, loud,
weird part of ourselves
hidden away.
And a lot of us
never let it out.
But I did.
How about you?
(NOBODY LIKE U
BY 4-TOWN PLAYING)
Oh, yeah
I've never met nobody like you
Had friends
and I've had buddies
It's true
But they don't turn my tummy
The way you do
I've never met nobody like you
Yeah
You're never not on my mind
Oh, my, oh, my
I'm never not by your side
Your side, your side
I'm never gonna let you cry
Oh, cry, don't cry
I'll never not be your ride
or die
All right
Let's call it what it is
It's a masterpiece
Got a whole lotta love
for them city streets
Tonight is the place to be
Got a big boom box
and a new CD
- Come on!
- Everybody, let's tear it up
If you want mad skills
You can share with us
Everybody just stop and stare
And you know why, it's me
Robaire
Woo!
Unh!
Let's go!
You're never not on my mind
Oh, my, oh, my
I'm never not by your side
Your side, your side
I'm never gonna let you cry
Oh, cry, don't cry
I'll never not be your ride
or die
All right
Like you
Like you, like you
I've never met nobody like you
Had friends
and I've had buddies
It's true
But they don't turn my tummy
The way you do
I've never met nobody like you
You're never not on my mind
Oh, my, oh, my
I'm never not by your side
Your side, your side
I'm never gonna let you cry
Oh, cry, don't cry
I'll never not be your ride
or die
All right
(1 TRUE LOVE
BY 4-TOWN PLAYING)
Ooh
Yeah
Heavy rain from my cloudy eye
Every time you say
That it isn't why
I used to call you babe
But you're the light
of my life
I drove by your house
29 times today
And nobody else
could make me feel this way
Nobody else
Nobody else, nobody
'Cause you've opened my eyes
and stolen my heart
You make me believe
that love can be hard
And I can never survive
a minute apart
You are my one true love
My one true love
My heaven above
Heavy rain on a Saturday
When you said my name
in the saddest way
Nothing numbs the pain
You're still the light
of my life
I drove by your house
10,000 times last year
Nobody else
wanted to dry my tears
Nobody else, nobody else
'Cause you've opened my eyes
and stolen my heart
You make me believe
that love can be hard
And I can never survive
a minute apart
You are my one true love
My one true love
My heaven above
Yeah
Nobody else
(U KNOW WHAT'S UP
BY 4-TOWN PLAYING)
You know what's up
You know it's us, yeah
You wanted it, you went for it
- And baby, you got it
- You know what's up
You wanted it, you went for it
You know it's us, yeah
I'm gonna make it all the way
Just watch me
I'm gonna hustle every day
Ooh-oh
I'm making paper
like it's origami
I only came to win the game
Can't stop me
You wanted it, you went for it
And baby, you got it
I wanted it, I went for it
And, baby, I did it on my own
Did it on my own
Own
You know what's up
You know it's us, yeah
Ladies and gentlemen,
listen up.
I'm gonna ask you
a few questions,
and I just want you
to be honest with me.
You want those shoes?
You want that shirt?
You want that car?
You want that purse?
I'm gonna need you
to convince me.
You ready? Here we go.
- You want it?
- I want it.
Louder.
- You want it?
- I want it.
Gimme one, two, three, four...
You wanted it, you went for it
And baby, you got it
I wanted it, I went for it
And baby, I did it on my own
Did it on my own
Own
Yeah
Whoo!
You know what's up
You know it's us, yeah
You wanted it, you went for it
- And baby, you got it
- You know what's up
You wanted it, you went for it
You know it's us, yeah
All right, all right
Whoo!
(UPBEAT INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC
PLAYING)
- MEILIN: Dad?
- (JIN HUMMING)
Dad?
Have you seen my CD?
(U KNOW WHAT'S UP BY 4-TOWN
PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS)
(SCATTING AND SINGING ALONG)