♪ In every situation I
can't help but find ♪
♪ That I always seem to
put myself on the line ♪
♪ Not for me but for
what I can do for you ♪
♪ I'm giving it up, now I'm through ♪
♪ I'm living for me,
just try and stop me ♪
♪ I'm living for me from now on ♪
♪ It's my rules, my way ♪
♪ Don't care what you say ♪
♪ You lose today, from now ♪
♪ It's my rules, my way ♪
♪ Don't care what you say ♪
♪ You lose today, it's my
fault no one else to blame ♪
♪ My way ♪
(suspenseful music)
- Hey!
(frenzied music)
Hey, hey, hey!
(man exclaims)
I'm okay, I'm okay.
I'm okay.
Don't you tell anyone
what you just saw here.
- [Assistant] Yes sir.
- I want everyone that
owns a dog executed.
- [Assistant] Executed sir?
- Fired.
- Yes sir.
- Right now.
- Go!
Do it!
- I'll clean it up
right away sir.
- I've come to the conclusion
that you have the ability to run things
in my way in my absence.
- Thanks.
- Do you hear me?
- Yeah, I hear ya.
- Good.
- You know it never ceases to amaze me,
you put a little bit of
pressure on our opponent
they way you did this morning,
they come right around
to our way of thinking.
I really had a good time.
- It always works.
And everything we do in this company
from now on is gonna work.
Don't forget out
appointment in the morning.
I want to play my virtual
reality CD-ROM for you.
- Right, at 11.
Hey, why don't we do it now?
I've got time.
- No, no.
We'll both do it together in
the morning when we're fresh.
No, no, I have a better idea.
You will show the CD-ROM at
the stockholder's meeting
a week from today.
Then they will know our cutbacks,
they will understand your bonus,
and they will see how I can
cut to the bone like a butcher.
And if any of those idiot
savant snot pocket kids
come up and threaten to quit,
tell 'em they've already been fired.
- You got it.
- Okay.
(spy music)
(machine beeping)
Oh boy.
It's not easy.
No.
(upbeat music)
And so we will be making sizeable cutbacks
in order to remain profitable
for the coming season.
In my absence, Dexter Pearlsley
will be Commander in Chief.
We will be cutting salaries,
extended vacations will
be limited to one week.
Yearly bonuses will be
eliminated this year
and Dexter will discuss our
new animal control policy,
which is very strict, by the way.
There are other sweeping changes
which Dexter will send
out to you on your e-mail.
And for those of you who wish to,
you might start looking for another job.
In fact, find one, because in my opinion,
you're useless here
when you don't have
the courage that I have
to make profit no matter what it takes.
(tires pealing)
(dramatic music)
(thunderous crashing)
- [Woman] What are we to do with him?
- He has no redeeming value whatsoever.
The man has never done a good deed
in his entire life.
- What about the dog?
He didn't run over the dog, did he?
- His jerking of the
steering wheel was a reflex,
hardly an achievement.
(thunderous rumbling)
- That was cool.
Where am I?
- We've looked long and hard
and couldn't find one moment
that you actually helped
someone other than yourself.
- He doesn't like the dogs.
(angels whispering)
- If he wants to go back.
- Well that's cool.
They just made a mistake.
That's okay, everyone makes mistakes.
- That's not what you told your employees.
You remember the ones that made mistakes
and then you fired, don't you?
- Yeah.
- Like the temp you fired last week.
She needed that job; her mother's sick.
Or have you forgotten
about the pregnant girl
who has no insurance
because you cut benefits.
- Look at all the cruel and inhuman jokes
you played on your brother
and most loyal employee,
Dexter Pearlsley.
- So, when do I get to go back.
(thunderous rumbling)
(dog barks)
- Do you have a problem with dogs?
- Yes.
- He didn't hit the dog.
(angels whispering)
- It's been decided.
They want you to go back as a dog.
- Me, as a dog?
Going back?
I can't stand dogs.
- Your name is Quigley.
(playful music)
(Quigley barks)
- Please tell me you can see me.
- Oh they said I'll be the only one
who'll be able to see
you as you once were.
Everyone else will see you as Quigley.
- Am I a talking dog?
- Oh no, I'm afraid not.
You can talk to me, but I can't help you.
Say you could bark if you like.
(scoffs)
Why don't you give it a try?
Just.
(barks)
That was alright.
(dramatic music)
(thunder rumbling)
(men exclaiming)
You okay there?
- You gotta help me.
- Oh not an option Archie.
I'm here to watch and
keep you out of trouble
without lifting a finger to assist you.
- Well this isn't good.
Tell me what to do.
- They gave you two assignments.
And if you do them well, I
suspect they might consider
allowing you through the gates.
- What if I can't do them?
- Oh I think they'll find someone else.
Someone more cooperative.
- Okay.
Let's get it over with.
- Oh, I don't think they'd
approve of your hurried attitude.
- That was a dumb thing to say.
Dogs are always in a hurry.
(groans)
- Come on.
- Oh, oh, okay.
- On your way, on your way.
(playful music)
- Oh baby, you're so cute.
What's his name?
- His name is Quigley and he
loves to have his ears pinched.
- Oh, so precious.
- I know, we have to go right now.
But I'm sure Quigley thanks
you for the ear pinches.
Don't you boy?
You owned all of this
and you never did
anything nice for anyone?
- I was in a hurry.
I wanted to be a
multi-billionaire before I was 40.
- There's something you need to do
and there isn't much time.
- I'm a dog.
- What's that got to do with anything?
- Because dogs don't get along with me.
They've never liked me.
They chase me, they bite me.
I step in their poop.
I hate dogs.
- Well that's gonna make
things a bit more, challenging.
Isn't it?
Well, you're on your own.
And good luck.
- Okay, tell me what you want me to do.
- It's not what I want you to do.
This is something you
have to do for yourself.
From deep down within your own heart.
If you have one.
- I don't have a clue
what you're talking about.
- I'll see you when you're finished.
- Give me a hint.
(thunder rumbling)
(spy music)
- What is this?
How many times have I told people
to keep this door locked?
(door lock clicks)
Well?
- I don't know what Archie did with it.
- Where could he have hidden the only copy
of his prized virtual reality CD-ROM?
The stockholder's meeting is tomorrow.
- I know, I know.
- I gave him my word I'd
play the CD on his behalf.
- Well short of tearing his office apart,
I'm not sure what else to do.
- This is not a good way
for me to celebrate my
35th birthday, Sarah.
- I...
But happy birthday anyway.
Come on, things are gonna work out fine.
You'll see.
I mean isn't there anything
I can do to help this?
- I was just reading the
last memo I got from Archie.
He envisioned our interactive games
to perform like no others.
He saw the AC Diamex
with the dual pads and
the triple joysticks
to be playing in every home in America.
- Well I mean they are really fun to play.
You know when you have
to drop one joystick
and just as quickly pick
the other one up again,
I mean you can't help
but become completely
obsessed with this game.
- Exactly.
But there are flaws in the system, Sarah.
(suspenseful music)
(Quigley whimpers)
(man speaking in foreign language)
- How someone has been
in my supply closet.
(man speaking in foreign language)
Someone has placed a
chair in front of the door
without folding it up first.
I swear this place is full of morons.
What is this?
(tense music)
(speaking in foreign language)
So, you were here and now you're not.
But, I will find you.
- Alright, the order of the
day is to find that CD, Sarah.
Archie must've had a unique hiding place,
someplace he knew that
none of us would look in.
- Okay, well why is the
CD so important Dex?
I mean did Archie solve the
flaws of the AC Diamex player?
- No, no, no, no.
But I think I've figured out
how to correct the player.
The cost is another matter.
I just,
I just don't want everyone thinking
that the cutbacks and
the changes are my idea.
Archie--
- Is gone, Dex.
Archie is gone.
He put his trust in you,
so I would have to assume
that whatever changes you make
in his absence would be
made with his blessing.
- Let's just say that I want
to keep Archie's wishes intact,
for now.
Now, get somebody downstairs
and have another look around.
That CD's gotta be somewhere.
And let's find it.
- Alright.
(happy music)
(spy music)
- If Archie thought I was
gonna take responsibility
for all these changes, he
really did have a screw loose.
Archie!
I know you're wondering what I'm doing.
I'm gonna do everything I can
to make sure that your last wish happens.
But know this, after I play that CD,
I'm doing things my way.
(determined music)
- What did you do that for?
I hope God forgives you.
- Did you hear what he said?
- I thought you were
learning some self control.
Don't you feel some remorse or something?
- Okay.
I'm sure I picked up the keys.
But I need the keys to get in my office.
- And what about the really
nice move you just made
on the briefcase?
- When dogs have to go, they go quick.
And I hurt my knee, lifting my leg to pee.
It's not easy being a dog.
I wanna know are you
here to help me or what?
- I'm here to observe, not help.
- No one will know.
Are you telling me he
knows every move I make?
- Every single move.
- That's not good.
- I'll be outside.
(dramatic music)
- You must be kidding me.
What do they think I am,
the cleaning service?
I am Frank, the janitor.
(scoffs)
what a sad state of
affairs we are living in.
(scoffs)
(determined music)
- Oh, that's, that's
great, that's terrific.
I see you really know how to
take great care of yourself.
- What's that supposed to mean?
- Well I don't see any food or water.
This could be a very long night Archie.
- Okay.
How do I say I'm sorry?
- It's a little late for sorry.
- No, I'm sincere.
I'm sorry, I want to apologize.
- What are you apologizing for?
- Everything.
- That's not how it works, Archie.
You don't even have a clue
what you've done, do you?
You're so used to being
a jerk all the time,
you think that doing wrong is right.
I'll see you in the morning.
- Wait, wait, wait.
I am a control freak.
I am number one.
Until, until just recently.
- That's the whole point, Archie.
There is no number one.
You should've had some friends.
And maybe even a girlfriend.
- Why?
You can't trust men, you
can't trust your friends,
and women are like dogs.
- You're gonna have a really
hard time with that one.
Say listen, while we're on the subject,
let me ask you something.
- Okay.
- What do fire escapes,
bullet proof vests,
windshield wipers and laser
printers have in common?
- That's a trick question.
- Nope, but I'll tell you the answer,
just so you don't lose any sleep tonight.
All of those things I just named,
were invented by women.
- No they weren't.
- Have a good night Archie.
(gentle music)
(Quigley whimpers)
- Hi cutie.
Hi sweetie.
What are you doing in a broom closet, huh?
Archie'd have a heart attack if he saw you
in his beloved building.
But he isn't here anymore, so.
The only person we have to worry about is.
- [Dexter] Frank!
Get in here!
- Dexter.
(dramatic music)
- Frank, there are paw
prints on this desk.
- This is impossible.
- Could someone have left
a window open last night?
(speaking in foreign language)
- Not unless someone is
going home after I did.
And I do believe I was the last one
out of the building last night.
- Frank, if there is a wild
animal loose in this building,
I want it found by
whatever means necessary.
- This I will do, Mr. Pearlsley.
- [Sarah] You're so cute.
- Sarah!
Is that you?
Sarah?
Sarah what is that?
- This is looking like
a dog Mr. Pearlsley.
- Well get it.
- [Frank] Now?
- Yes now.
Go!
(playful music)
- Doggie!
Doggie!
Where are your papers.
- Don't hurt him.
- Don't hurt him?
Sarah how could you touch
a wild animal like that?
Call the guards.
Call animal control.
And someone bring my fishing nets.
Once we have captured that little beast.
I want to have a word
with you in my office.
And did you find that CD last night.
- No, Dex, we tore Archie's office apart.
We didn't find anything.
- Oh great.
That's just great.
Now I've got a wild animal
loose in the building,
a missing CD and a
stockholder's meeting in,
four hours.
I expected a lot more of you.
Archie would've been very, very
disappointed in you, Sarah.
- Archie didn't even know me Dex.
(Frank speaking in foreign language)
(Quigley barks)
- You're not a very nice doggie.
If I am not knowing better,
I would say as if you are
trying to get even with me.
There's something funny here.
You wait and see, Mr. Smarty Pants.
What goes around, is coming around.
- Got him trapped.
You two stick with me.
- What do we do?
- Stay with me.
- Okay.
- Where?
- We're going upstairs.
- What for?
- To catch the dog.
We're trying to catch a dog, remember?
- Yeah well, why do you
think the dog went upstairs?
- I don't know.
Maybe he thought he was
trapped or something.
- Who set the trap?
- You know, why don't you
guys just go downstairs
and guard the gate?
I think I can handle this on my own.
- Well someone must
know where the trap is.
I don't know what the big deal is.
- How big is the trap?
(dramatic music)
(pensive music)
- [Dexter] That dog, my desk.
- Here, let me get it, I.
- Guards, come down to
my office right away.
That dog is waiting here
for you to throw him out.
Over.
- [Man] Who is this?
And what office are you calling from?
- I'm Dexter Pearlsley, who do you think?
- [Man] Uh, I can't hear you very well.
Over and out.
- Here, tie him up.
- I really think he's trying
to tell us something, Dexter.
Look, look in his eyes.
- Carol, this Dexter.
I want you to get those guards down here.
Call animal control so I
can get this filthy beast
out of my office.
- [Carol] Yes, Dexter.
- I think I'm gonna keep him.
- Don't be ridiculous Sarah, that's a dog!
You know how Archie hated
those little varmints.
- Dex, Archie is gone!
You're the boss now.
- Yes, I know.
And as the boss, I think
that the company should be
run exactly as Archie wanted it run.
I mean look at how successful he was.
Look at what he accomplished.
- He was miserable.
And angry.
- Sometimes you just
have to make sacrifices.
- So in Archie's case, you
really think all those sacrifices
were worth it?
(thoughtful music)
- I don't know.
Why have I never seen you before?
Where have you been?
- I've always been right down the hall.
- Look Sarah, we both
have long term contracts,
but if we make any mistakes
running this company,
we can be replaced.
- Okay well what can I do?
- Just organize another
search of Archie's office
and I'll take care of this dog thing.
(tense music)
(growls)
Carol!
- What are you trying to do?
This is incredible.
This absolutely incredible.
(pensive music)
You are so cute.
I don't get it.
Do you want me to open the drawer?
What, did you hide something
in there earlier, huh?
There are no dog bones in here.
Trust me on that one.
Oh, I'm not sure what
we should do with that.
There's supposed to be some
pretty disturbing things on it.
Wait, Archie wanted that
played at the stockholder's meeting.
Put it down!
No! (gasps)
(CD cracks)
No.
Oh no.
Look what you've done!
Look at this.
(Quigley barks)
- Not a trace of him sir.
- Where did you look?
- Look, we, um.
I don't know what you mean sir.
- The dog.
I'm talking about the dog.
- We had to look for the nets.
So we wouldn't get attacked. (laughs)
But we're ready now sir.
That's if you are.
- Who hired you two?
- To do what sir?
- Nevermind.
Just follow me.
And don't get lost.
- Who got lost?
- Lost?
How did someone get lost?
Come on, before he tries to ditch us.
- Is that?
- [Sarah] Yes.
- That was the only copy.
What have you done?
I'm glad the CD broke.
I didn't wanna play it anyway.
- Well what are you gonna
tell the stockholders?
- I'm gonna tell them that
our new multi-media player
is gonna knock the socks
off of the competition
and that we're gonna need
a larger advertising budget
than we thought.
- Well should we anticipate
any changes, Dex?
- No, no.
No changes.
I think Archie would be very proud
of what we're about to do.
We're going to see to it
that he didn't life his life in vain
and that AC Tech lives on forever.
(gentle music)
- See, you don't really have to be as mean
as people believed Archie to be, do you?
- I hope not.
- This dog is so cute.
- Yeah.
- Pet him.
- Huh?
- Come on, pet him.
- I don't pet dogs.
- Try.
Come on.
- [Dexter] Hello.
- See it's not so bad, is it?
- Hey.
- Wouldn't it be fun to
have a dog like this?
- Would you like to have
dinner with me this evening?
- Yeah, I would.
(dramatic music)
(guards exclaiming)
- [Taller Guard] My arm, my.
- [Shorter Guard] Do we get it?
- [Taller Guard] I got it.
- [Shorter Guard] Alright.
(exclaiming)
- Stop, stop.
- Get out of here.
- We just.
- This way, this way.
- I'll meet you in my
office in 10 minutes.
- Maybe we're just on a break here.
- Now, where were we?
(gentle music)
Dogs.
- Yes.
- I agree.
I think dogs would be a great idea.
I mean, who knows,
it might be just what I need
to smooth all my rough edges.
Keep me from being so mean, as you put it.
Speaking of dogs, where is he?
(Quigley barks)
- This is so strange.
- And wasn't Archie the only
one who knew where the...
(playful music)
- So, how'd it go?
- I don't wanna talk about it.
- You have a hard time seeing
the good side of things
most of the time, don't you?
- Sweeney, I'm not in the mood.
What is the next assignment, what's next?
(thunder rumbling)
- Oh I gotta go.
- What did I do wrong now?
Oh.
(comical music)
(man groans)
- You can come out now.
- You.
(thunder rumbling)
You have no idea how hard this is.
- I think if I'm not
mistaken, they refer to it
as a dog's life.
- What's next?
- I'm sorry, you in a hurry Archie?
- I'd have a better time
cleaning a short person's teeth.
- Oh I see.
So it's just rush in and rush out
and that solves everything, right?
- They won't let me in heaven
until I complete your assignments.
- I've completed one.
Which one is the next?
This dog thing is getting old!
- Let's take a walk huh?
What do you say big guy?
There's a young family
man, a very good man,
who's in dire financial straits.
- As Archie I could easily help.
- Archie's gone.
But they would like Quigley to
try to help with the matter.
- Quigley.
(barks)
Who is this guy?
- Your brother, Woodward.
- My brother Woodward?
I haven't talked to my brother in years.
Woodward is a sap head.
He spends more time being married
and raising children
than he has sense for.
- So what are you saying?
- I'm saying you can't
help a guy like Woodward.
- Well did you ever try?
- (laughs) No reason to.
- Tell me something Archie,
do you even know what
he does for a living?
What his passion in life is?
- I didn't know he had one.
And I don't care because Woodward takes
a lot of his measly salary
and gives it to charities.
Now if that's not a sign of weakness,
you tell me what is.
- Giving to charity is a
sign of great strength.
You'll understand that Archie.
And we have to go.
- Wait!
You're always walking away.
(happy music)
(dog barking aggressively)
(dramatic music)
(officer laughs)
- Okay.
(happy music)
(tense music)
(exclaims) Yeah!
Yes!
(laughs)
Oh yeah, I got ya.
I got ya.
Oh yeah.
(sad music)
(thunder rumbles)
- I failed.
In my carelessness I lost him.
(bluesy music)
(dogs barking)
(thoughtful music)
Quigley, come here boy.
I know.
Say, you're so omnipresent.
Why don't you tell me where he is?
(thunder crashes)
I'm sorry.
I am, I'm sorry.
Stupid.
No, I'm not ready to give up.
You gotta remember, I'm
relatively new at this.
It's only been maybe, what, 60, 62 years?
(dog growling)
(laughs)
(dog barking and growling)
Someone musta taken him.
But where would someone take a dog?
(thunder rumbling)
(jazzy music)
- In you go.
And in ya stay.
(suspenseful blues music)
(clattering)
(dogs barking)
(laughing)
- This isn't funny!
- Of course it is.
Hey, I'm just happy to see you.
You look okay.
- I'm not.
Look carefully.
A grown man, locked
inside of the dog pound.
Now get me outta here, or adopt me.
Just adopt me.
- How does an observing guardian angel
stage a dog pound break?
(door rattles)
- They're sending another
dog in here with me.
(suspenseful music)
(bluesy music)
(officer babbles)
- Into your little jail cell.
(sighs)
Ah.
(blows raspberry)
Okay.
Stay.
(energetic music)
(whistles)
(dogs barking)
Okay, that's not funny.
That's not funny.
Alright?
I'll get 'em both back, you'll see.
Nobody runs away on Wally
Sprigs and gets away with it.
- What's my first move?
Because I don't know my brother at all.
- Well the way I see it, Archie
didn't know your brother.
But you're not Archie now, are you?
- What do I do now that I'm Quigley?
- You got me.
- Well I'm drawing a blank.
I'm lost, I can't figure it out.
- Well that's fine, but there's a fog bank
waiting to collect us if we fail.
- Hey, do you remember
you helped me escape
from the dog pound?
- I did not!
- Yes you did!
I only whistled.
It was that stupid man who let you out.
I had nothing to do with the fact
that the gate opened wide
enough for you to escape.
(growls)
- I coulda done that if I was Archie.
- You're right, you could have.
Now I'm gonna go take a walk.
I'll be around in case
you get, lost again.
- I didn't get lost.
- Right.
- I never get lost.
(thoughtful music)
(happy music)
(tense music)
(barking)
(gentle music)
- Hey!
What's your name?
(giggles)
I'm Megan Channing.
Would you like to meet my family?
Okay.
You have to be real quiet, okay?
My mommy's name is Joanne and
my brother's name is Brian.
But I guess you don't
have to know that, right?
'Cause you're a dog.
(giggles)
- Where'd you get the dog Megan?
- He saved my life.
- How did he do that?
- Well there was this
truck coming towards me
and he pushed me out of the way.
- Oh my, when did this happen?
- Just now.
My ball bounced in the
middle of the street
and there was this big
truck coming towards me
and he pushed me out of the way.
- Cool.
- You should hug the doggie Mama.
- Well yes, I guess I should.
(chuckles)
Well he looks well fed.
Why don't we get you both cleaned up
and then we'll go look for his owner
so he can go back home?
- Can we play with him first?
- Well I think someone
must miss him very much.
Don't you guys?
- Can we make up signs that
say that we found a dog?
- Yes, of course we can.
That is a wonderful idea.
- If no one wants him,
can we keep him Mama?
- Well it's a little early
to discuss that Brian.
But you know what,
why don't you go and get
some of Frisky's food
and see if this little guy's hungry?
- Frisky was our old dog.
But he died of old age.
He went to heaven where
he can run in the flowers
and tall grass.
Huh Mom?
- That's right.
- We really miss Frisky.
- You know why don't we
get you guys cleaned up
and get everybody fed.
And then we'll go make those signs up.
- Can he come with us
when we hang up the signs?
- Yeah, of course he can.
We'll use Frisky's old leash.
- Okay.
(happy music)
Thanks boy.
(playful music)
(kids exclaiming)
(Quigley barking)
Go get it.
Good boy.
(body thudding)
(thunder rumbling)
- I know.
I'm just making sure he
doesn't get lost again.
I won't help him!
- [Woodward] Hey guys.
- Hey honey.
- Hey, who's this?
- Well he doesn't have a collar
so we don't know who he is.
- He saved my life Daddy.
- He did?
- Um hmm.
- He pushed her out of
the way from a big truck.
So she wouldn't get smashed.
- [Megan] We hung up signs
all over the neighborhood.
So his owner can take him back home.
- Well that's really smart.
Who thought of that?
- I did.
- High five.
Good job.
- I think we should keep him.
- Well, I do owe you a
great deal of gratitude
for saving my little girl.
Has he been fed and given some water?
- Yes Daddy.
We've been playing with him all day.
- Well, so how was your day?
- (laughs) You go first.
- Well, the delivery service told me
they were cutting back my hours.
So I'll have to find another night job.
But the consulting business is kinda fun.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
I just wish it paid a little bit more.
But I did tell to this guy
how to run his business
and he offered me a job.
- What kinda job?
Good job?
Bad job?
None of the above?
- Well.
Nah I mean it's a, it's be a paycut.
So it's not gonna work out.
- Look, everything will work out
when you finish your new video game.
- Look, it's never gonna happen.
There's just, there's just
not enough time in the day.
- Your video games are sensational.
And they're almost finished.
Besides, you made a promise
to me a long time ago
that you were gonna make
video games for kids,
even their parents would approve of.
If only your brother would've
helped us in some small way.
- Look, just, let's not go there, okay?
Archie's in his own world someplace.
Look, I asked him for help once, once.
And he completely humiliated me.
- You're not angry about the dog, are you?
- No, no.
- Daddy, can the dog go to bed with us?
- No, the dog's still a stranger.
But I'll tell ya what.
Let's make a bed for
him in the utility room
and put some paper down for him.
That way if he barks if
won't bother any of us.
- Okay.
- Alright.
- Bye.
- Goodnight.
- 'Night.
- We got good kids.
(happy music)
Joanne.
- Oh, isn't he cute?
- I think he's reading the paper.
- And I think you've
been working too hard.
Why don't you come sit down
and have some breakfast?
- No, no, no.
I swear, his eyes are
going back and forth,
like he's reading the, the
stock exchange thing down there.
(exhales)
- Come on.
Okay everybody, grab a hand.
Lord, thank you for our many blessings
and for the miracle of
life and our health,
which we treasure.
- [All] Amen.
- Looks good.
So has anyone called for the dog yet?
- Not one.
- Good, we can keep him.
- Not so fast.
You know that dog belongs
to somebody out there guys.
And it's our responsibility to make sure
that they get back together.
- Maybe we can check the signs
and see if they're still up.
- Okay.
- While we do that, can we bring the dog?
- Excuse me?
- Speaking of which, why
don't you take the dog
into the backyard and see
if he has to go potty?
- [Megan] Okay.
(happy music)
(thunder rumbling)
- How you doing, you making progress?
- I might have made a mistake.
- Might've?
What's that supposed to mean?
- I shoulda helped him.
- [Sweeney] You can still do that.
(thunder rumbling)
- No, I can't.
It's too late.
- It's never too late to change Archie.
- Look at me.
I'm only 10 inches tall.
(playful music)
What can I do?
- Go help them.
I have to get back in the bushes.
- That was a nice move.
- Thank you.
(Quigley yipping)
- [Video Game] You have just
finished level three Megan.
Push the red button to continue.
Use the correct button quickly.
You must hurry or start all over.
- Oh, I almost got him.
- [Video Game] Lift
off, lift off, lift off.
(kids laughing)
Oh sorry Megan, not enough to give.
- Here.
- Okay.
- [Video Game] Welcome Brian.
It's your turn.
Welcome.
- Hi.
Wanna watch my daddy's game?
- You think he can play with us?
- No, but he can watch.
Come here and sit down.
Come on.
This is really neat.
- [Brian] You think he understands?
- [Megan] Probably not.
- [Video Game] Lift
off, lift off, lift off.
Yes!
You made it to level four.
- That's too bad.
We could use an extra player.
- Three people?
- With Mom it would be four.
- You think you could play?
(Quigley barks)
- [Brian] Let's show him how
and see if he can use the stick.
- He needs hands and fingers.
Nevermind.
You can watch if you like.
- Hello.
- Hey.
I have something I wanna show you.
- Oh yeah?
- Um hmm.
Come here.
- Yes!
- Nice one.
- That is the reason
you're going to finish your
video games, Mr. Channing.
- What would I ever do without you?
- You'd think of something.
- Unimaginable.
(kids laughing)
(Quigley barks and growls)
(chuckling)
- Do you think if the signs are still up
we'll be able to keep the dog?
- If no one wants him back,
I'm sure Mom and Dad
would let us keep him.
- But what if the signs are gone?
- Then we'll have to make up more signs.
- We don't wanna keep
someone else's dog, do we?
- No, I guess not.
- Promise me you won't
tell anyone where I went.
Promise?
- Yeah.
But you promise to come right back
after you check if the
signs are still up, right?
- I'll come right back.
- Okay.
- Now stay in my room
and pretend we're playing together.
Okay?
- Okay.
♪ They say you're lost not anymore ♪
♪ Now that you're with
us you're found again ♪
♪ It's been so long
since things went wrong ♪
♪ I feel like I'm on solid ground again ♪
♪ I found you ♪
♪ You found me ♪
♪ I'll prove you're free to stay with me ♪
♪ A friend like you
won't come around again ♪
♪ Won't you please stay
with me, I prayed ♪
(tense music)
♪ Where am I now ♪
♪ I've gone astray ♪
♪ Please help me now ♪
♪ Can't find my way ♪
♪ Ooo ♪
(cats meowing)
(Quigley barks)
(bright country music on radio)
- (laughs) you're not very funny.
(barking)
You have to go potty?
What, are you afraid
I'm gonna lock you out?
How about if I leave the door open?
Listen to me, I'm talking to a dog.
Oh boy.
Why aren't you playing with the kids?
Hmm.
Megan, Brian?
Megan!
Brian?
Brian, where's your sister?
- I don't know.
- What do you mean?
She was just up here playing with you
a few minutes ago.
Wasn't she?
- Yeah.
- Well then where is she?
Brian!
- She went out.
- She went out?
What do you mean she went out?
Where, when?
- I don't know.
- Brian, Brian, think.
- I don't know!
- Alright, come on, let's go.
(tense dramatic music)
Woodward, Megan went out this morning
and I can't find her anywhere.
(Woodward's voice garbles)
No, I haven't called the police yet.
Okay.
- Do you wanna go after him?
- Uh, he can find his way back.
Um, what about our daughter?
- Nothing yet.
But it's just been a short while.
She's probably right here in
the neighborhood somewhere.
- Our baby's out there all alone.
Please help us find her.
- Do you have a recent photo
of your daughter Ms. Channing?
- Of course.
Please come in.
(tense music)
- Hey, we're gonna need some help.
- I know.
- Well do something then!
- I can't.
- No, do something, do something.
I'm just an observing guardian angel.
Listen Archie.
- What?
- Can I have a hug?
- A hug.
- No!
Hey, hey!
(barking and growling)
Why did you do that?
- I hope you have what it
takes to solve this problem.
- I gotta go.
♪ I'm on my own, it's
up to me but now I see ♪
♪ Can't be the man I was before ♪
♪ I was a fool but how I've learned ♪
♪ The tide has turned I
understand that life is more ♪
♪ Cannot go back and get it right ♪
♪ Begin again at least
I've opened up the door ♪
♪ Give me one more chance ♪
♪ Say it's not too late ♪
♪ Oh let me change my fate ♪
♪ You came from out of nowhere ♪
♪ Giving me all you had to give ♪
♪ You healed a hurt that was aching ♪
♪ Turned a house back to a home ♪
♪ I can't believe I found you ♪
♪ You brought the light
back to our lives ♪
♪ Please say that this is forever ♪
♪ And I'll never want to say goodbye ♪
♪ I gotta change, I gotta try ♪
♪ I don't know how but I know why ♪
♪ I need to make it ♪
♪ If I could do it all once more ♪
♪ I'd change the score I wouldn't lie ♪
♪ Or try to fake it ♪
♪ I've learned to love
but now you're lost ♪
♪ If that's the cost then I
don't think that I can take it ♪
♪ Let this be our chance ♪
♪ Say it's not too late ♪
♪ We can change our fate ♪
♪ You helped me find a reason ♪
♪ To be the one that I could have been ♪
♪ You've given everything, anything ♪
♪ Now I need to get you home ♪
♪ If I can only find you ♪
♪ Maybe we'll be a family ♪
♪ We're stronger when we're together ♪
♪ Than we are when we're alone ♪
(Quigley barks)
♪ Stronger now, than we ever were before ♪
♪ No more looking in, now
you've opened up the door ♪
♪ And I found my way back home ♪
- Megan!
- Oh my God.
Oh my God are you okay?
- Megan.
- That's quite a dog you've got there.
- What do you mean?
- He found her and was bringing her home
when we located them.
- Thank you boy.
Thank you.
- Well everything seems to be okay.
You folks have a good evening.
- Thank you.
- thank you.
- Our pleasure.
- Are you okay?
- Uh huh.
- Alright?
- [Joanne] You scared us to death.
(thunder rumbling)
- So I was wrong.
Hey, isn't this the reason
we never give up on people?
- Yeah.
- Come on.
- Good boy.
- Look, lookie, lookie.
Oh, oh, oh.
(laughing)
Nice going Brian.
- Nice going Brian.
Bet you can't throw one that far.
- How are we gonna get
the ball back smartie?
(playful music)
(Sweeney exclaims)
- Hey.
(laughs)
That's funny.
Why are you so muddy and wet?
- Have you forgotten something?
- Such as?
- The reason you're here.
- Oh, I'm still trying to figure that out.
But it's not easy for a
dog to give man money.
- You're not supposed to
give him money Archie.
- I'm not supposed to give him money
but I'm supposed to help
him with his finances?
That doesn't make sense.
- You're supposed to save him from ruin.
Remember?
Now you have until tomorrow.
- That's impossible.
- Look, I gotta go.
I'm filthy.
- Shake yourself dry.
- [Sweeney] That's your job Archie.
- Just shake yourself dry.
(bright country music)
- Hey.
Hey kids.
- Hi Dad.
- Hey Dad.
- Thank you for all of your help kids.
- Um hmm.
Can we play video games
before we go to bed?
- For one hour and not a minute longer.
- But Mom!
- If you argue.
(laughing)
- Brian, no arguing.
- Okay.
- Come on.
Come on doggie, let's go.
(gentle music)
- What happened today?
- Well, first they cut the hours.
And then they cut the jobs.
And mine was one of the ones eliminated.
- I have to go back to work Woody.
- Look, the kids need you here.
It'll be alright.
- You know I could, work part time.
Some place close to the house.
That way I wouldn't be
gone for long periods.
- No, I, I don't want some
stranger coming into this house
taking care of the kids.
Look, what I'll do is
I'll put the games on hold
for a couple of weeks
until I can find another second job.
You've already got a
full time job right here.
(playfully suspenseful music)
- [Video Game] Welcome to Tiny-Tails!
Player, identify yourself.
Welcome Archie, what would you like to do?
Let's start a new game.
Come on Archie let's play skip the stones.
Up higher, higher, higher.
Sorry Archie, better luck next time.
Welcome to episode four, Archie.
Are you ready to play the game?
Let's play surprise party.
Good choice.
This is a fast game Archie.
Buckle up.
(toilet flushing)
(tense music)
You are now starting episode five.
You have entered the surprise area.
You decide if you can.
Good choice Archie.
Let's see how smart you are.
(rooster crows)
(thunder rumbling)
(sad music)
- Hey, everybody up.
Last one to the kitchen
has to do all the dishes.
What's that crazy dog done?
- (gasps) No dog.
- [Megan] What did he do?
- Everybody just get in the car.
Let's go, he's got my game!
Get in the car, get in the car.
- [Megan] What are we gonna do?
- [Woodward] Get in the car,
we're gotta get the car.
- [Brian] I don't know.
(frantic music)
- Where is he going?
- I don't know, but
those are my only copies!
(brakes squealing)
What got into him?
- Maybe he wants to play
the games all by himself.
- Wow, can he do that?
- Maybe.
- This crazy dog.
- Don't be so hard on him.
He's just a puppy.
- I know Dad, come on.
- Where's he going?
(tense music)
- [Business Man] Whoa!
(guards exclaiming)
- What kind of a place is this?
- Some sort of technological
development place I think.
Come on kids.
- Hey there little fella.
Hi.
Sarah!
Look, an old friend
stopped by to say hello.
Hi.
(chuckles)
- He looks thirsty.
I'll get him some water.
- Thanks.
(Quigley whimpers)
- Okay yeah, now I really think
he's trying to tell us something.
(Quigley barks)
- What, do ya think the dog
wants to play the CDs or something?
- Yeah, I definitely think
he wants you to play the CD.
- Sarah the dog's cute,
but this is ridiculous.
Alright, alright, alright.
- [Guard] He has that crazy look.
- Where do you look to see crazy?
(Dex laughing)
- [Video Game] Farther, farther, farther.
- This is the best game I've ever played.
I mean it's far better than
anything we've ever developed.
- [Sarah] Oh yeah.
- [Video Game] Sorry
Dexter, maybe next time.
- There he is.
Hey, hey, what are you
doing with my games?
- Your games?
The dog brought them in.
- Why do you look so familiar to me?
- Look, I've never seen you
people before in my life.
Just give me back my games.
- Wait a minute, wait.
Do you know what we do here?
- You're into technology.
- Partly.
- Can we take it from the top?
- No.
I want my games back and
then we'll all just leave.
- Daddy.
- Not now Megan.
- My name is Dexter Pearlsley.
And I run this place with
a bunch of other people,
including Sarah here.
These games are the best we've ever seen.
And we've been developing video games here
for over 10 years.
- Daddy!
- Uh yes, Pumpkin?
- They make some of the
games you call trash.
See?
- She's right.
She's right.
It's all garbage.
But do you have any more like these?
- Several unfinished ones.
- Well, if we were to offer you,
say half a million dollars
to develop video games
exclusively for us, what
would you say to that?
(stifling laughter)
- Please, say yes.
When can he start?
- Uh hello?
Hi.
Dexter.
You are?
- Oh I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Woodward, Woodward Channing.
And this is my wife Joanne
and these are my children.
This is Megan and Brian.
- I knew it.
You're Archie's brother, aren't you?
- Archie's brother, I didn't
know Archie had a brother.
- Well for the most part
I didn't know I had a brother either.
- Well why didn't he
ever bring you in here?
I mean, did he know what you can do?
- Um, no, no.
We weren't very close.
- Well we wouldn't have
known about you at all
if it weren't for your dog.
- Yeah.
- Oh he's not their dog.
I saw the signs you put
up in the neighborhood.
And then when I came
over you all raced out
and I had to rush over here to find you.
- Is he really your dog?
- Yes.
His name is Quigley and
he's my very best friend.
I've been looking all over for him.
(Quigley yips)
Well, I can't thank you enough
for taking such good care of him.
It really means a lot to me.
Are you ready to go home now Quigley?
- Goodbye Quigley.
- Yeah, now we lost two doggies.
- I, I just wanna know,
if he can't,
how did you guys...
Nevermind.
- Um, you know kids,
Sarah and I were so fond of that dog
that we went out and we found
a whole litter of puppies
that look exactly like your Quigley.
- Are you thinking what I'm thinking Dex?
- I think we're on the same page.
To seal the deal,
why don't you follow us
downtown this afternoon,
when we go to pick up our puppy.
- There are five puppies.
- And they all look like Quigley?
- Exactly.
- Well that would be wonderful.
If he turns out to be
half the dog Quigley was,
we'll be very lucky.
- Can I show you around?
(determined music)
- Okay.
That went pretty well, don't you think?
(thunder rumbling)
It's not too bad, was it?
- I'm glad I'm finally
getting to know my brother.
He's a nice guy.
(laughs)
(thunder rumbles)
- [Sweeney] I think you did great.
Personally, I'm on your side.
- Ah, phew, well I'm back.
And, I did good.
- You did the no no on
that man's briefcase.
- That was wrong.
- [Man] You almost caused
several accidents in your haste.
You continue to behave
as though are the only
one that's important.
- I did find the girl.
- Yes, after you forgot to watch her
and she slipped out of the house.
- You're still rough around
the edges, Archer Channing.
Still taking shortcuts at others' expense.
- I know.
Next time--
- There is
no such thing as next time.
There are no second
chances Archie Channing.
You are what you are, a
miserable human being.
The only thing you've ever cared about
is yourself.
(thunder rumbling)
- I mean when I go back.
- [God] There is no going back.
- Ah.
There gotta be a way.
There has got to be a way to do this.
I can't leave everything like it is.
- Unfortunately--
- No, no,
I can't leave everything like it is.
- [God] What you've done is done.
And nothing will change that.
- I'll do anything.
Wait!
- [God] You cannot earn
your way into heaven
by doing good deeds Archie.
The only way into heaven is
by faith and faith alone.
(exclaims)
- Is the dog alright?
- Dog?
- Yes, there was a dog.
- I don't think there
was a dog Mr. Channing.
You're a very lucky man
to have survived such a terrible accident.
God must be watching over you.
- Hmm.
Oh, why are you saying that?
- Well you only have a few scratches
and not one broken bone.
The police still can't
believe that you're alive.
- Whew.
I gotta use a phone.
- Of course.
And then you can check out and go home.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- Hello Dexter?
- [Dexter] Hello.
- I'm ready to come
home from the hospital.
Could you please come and get me?
- [Dexter] Yeah, yeah okay.
- Yes, and have you found the CD-ROM?
- [Dexter] Nope, I can't find it.
- Okay, that's not good.
We have to destroy that.
I don't want anyone to
see what's on there,
because it's not good.
- [Dexter] Yeah, yeah--
- No, it's not good.
And I have other things I
wanna talk to ya about too.
(happy music)
- Amazing how fast you recovered.
Don't forget to take your medication.
- Okay, thank you.
Thank you very much.
Did you get it?
- Yes.
I got it.
It is a little confusing though.
(laughing)
- Good, let's go.
(mutters)
There's gonna be some more
changes to the company as well.
People who have pets,
now have my permission
to bring those pets to
work with 'em every day
so they can be close together.
And there will be immediate raises
for every employee that
has a job well done.
And I'm beginning this right now.
Our profit sharing program.
So all employees can be
rewarded for their loyalty.
- Are you alright sir?
- Yes, I'm alright.
I wanna go see my brother.
- Your brother?
I didn't know you had a brother.
- I haven't seen him in years.
Let's surprise him.
1461 Juniper Lane.
Thank you.
- You say something Archie?
- Yes I did.
Thank you for putting up
with me during my bitterness.
And my selfishness.
I am going to ask you.
I've already made up my mind.
You're my partner.
Equally.
How do you feel about that?
- Thanks Archie.
(exuberant music)
(Quigley barks)
- Who is this?
Oh you've gotta be kidding.
- Oh.
I want to know if you
could find it in your heart
to forgive me.
- What do you want Archie?
- I want to know you for who you are.
I wanna know your family.
And I want you to know
me for who I am now.
- Why?
- Why not?
- Why not, exactly.
- Oh, I'm sorry.
This is my partner, Dexter Pearlsley.
(whispering)
- Look, is this another one
of your cruel jokes, Archie?
Because if it is, you should just leave.
- It's been a long time.
- It's been too long.
Brian, Megan, I'm your long lost uncle,
that hadn't been here for
ya like he shoulda been.
And I found something very unknown to me.
- What did you find?
- Life.
My life.
I didn't know I had one.
I didn't even know it was there.
- (scoffs) Are you alright?
- I'm better than I've ever been.
I just, came out of a
never ending nightmare.
So I've come here to ask
for your forgiveness.
- You've always been
welcome at our house Archie.
- Oh Joanne.
Thank you.
It means a lot to me.
I want to know everything
about your games.
- How do you know about my games?
- I've been to a very special place.
I don't know how I got there,
I don't know where it is,
but I was given good
visions of who I really am.
This is the bravest thing I've ever done.
Because it's the truth.
I have a surprise for the family.
(kids exclaiming)
His name is Quigley.
- Hi.
Oh hi there.
- Let's go.
We're a family again.
Let's go to the car kids.
We're gonna go.
Woody, good to be with you again.
♪ You can climb the highest mountain ♪
♪ Swim the deepest sea ♪
♪ Cross the widest valley ♪
♪ He's friends with you and me ♪
♪ He is something special ♪
♪ Lightens up our day ♪
♪ I wonder where he came from ♪
♪ Maybe heaven's where he stays ♪
♪ He came out of nowhere ♪
♪ Gave us smiles of happiness ♪
♪ Ask him what he's here for ♪
♪ And this is what he says ♪
♪ One more chance to find my way ♪
♪ Yeah, one more chance to save the day ♪
♪ Take one last glance and you will see ♪
♪ I'm Quigley and you can depend on me ♪
♪ One more chance for one last fight ♪
♪ One more chance, to make things right ♪
♪ Take one last glance and you will see ♪
♪ I'm Quigley and you can depend on me ♪
♪ He's not your average puppy ♪
♪ There's something unique ♪
♪ He knows what I'm feeling ♪
♪ Understands me when I speak ♪
♪ If you try to catch him ♪
♪ You're in for a surprise ♪
♪ He'll run you around in circles ♪
♪ Disappearing before your eyes ♪
♪ He came out of nowhere ♪
♪ Gave us smiles of happiness ♪
♪ Ask him what he's here for ♪
♪ And this is what he says ♪
♪ One more chance to find my way ♪
♪ One more chance to save the day ♪
♪ Take one last glance and you will see ♪
♪ I'm Quigley and you can depend on me ♪
♪ One last glance and you will see ♪
♪ Quigley ♪
♪ You the man, dog ♪
♪ I don't want to spend my time dwelling ♪
♪ On things I can't change ♪
♪ I'm better off trying to forget them ♪
♪ But sometimes it's hard
to keep 'em off my brain ♪
♪ I said this, I do that ♪
♪ It's now record and a matter of fact ♪
♪ Right or wrong, can't retract ♪
♪ Done is done and I'm not looking back ♪
♪ I don't want to have this recollection ♪
♪ Controlling my thoughts ♪
♪ I'd rather think that I
have learned my lesson ♪
♪ And try to be real ♪
♪ It was not a total loss ♪
♪ I'm keeping my eyes on tomorrow ♪
♪ Fading yesterday to black ♪
♪ The future looks good ♪
♪ I'm not looking back ♪
♪ If this world that I'm traveling ♪
♪ If it gets to hard
then where would I be ♪
♪ Where would I be ♪
♪ And if you would dare show me the way ♪
♪ Then would I see ♪
♪ That I needed guidance ♪
♪ I hear the words you say ♪
♪ I'm acting all in faith ♪
♪ I'm on a quest to find my destiny ♪
♪ I'm never looking back ♪
♪ And make a promise that ♪
♪ I'll never forget the
path you set for me ♪
♪ Forever and always ♪
♪ Yeah I hear the words you say ♪
♪ I'm acting all in faith ♪
♪ I'm on a quest to find my destiny ♪
♪ I'm never looking back ♪
♪ And make a promise that ♪
♪ I'll never forget the
path you set for me ♪
♪ Forever and always ♪
♪ Forever ♪
♪ And always ♪